- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
- ♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
- ♪ COME ON ♪
- ♪ WE WANT TO MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE ♪
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
- ♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
- KILLING IN A FEW SECONDS?
OR JUST ONE MOMENT?
THE MON-SOONOS
OF THE STATE ARMY
ARE NO MATCH FOR YOU AFTER ALL?
- GEKKO, COME IN.
THIS IS THE 909!
THE KLF SQUADRON WE
ENCOUNTERED HAS BEEN DESTROYED!
- WE'RE RETURNING NOW!
- HEY, LEADER, WAIT A MINUTE!
- THERE HE GOES, IGNORING ME.
- 909 AND 606 ARE RETURNING.
THE GEKKO SHOULD
TURN THE NOSE TO 270.
- UM...
- HEY, TALHO!
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO MAKE
ADJUSTMENTS LIKE THAT.
HE ALWAYS MAKES HIS BACK
WITHOUT IT.
- WAIT A MINUTE, LEADER!
THE 909!
IT'S COMING IN TOO SHALLOW!
- ( gasps )
- HEY, LEADER,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
HOLLAND! PULL UP! PULL UP!
- SHEESH, LUCKY YOU ONLY GOT
A FEW CUTS AND BRUISES
FOR YOUR TROUBLE.
WERE YOU DISTRACTED
WHILE YOU WERE LANDING?
IT'S NOT REALLY LIKE YOU.
BUT THEN AGAIN IT IS.
- YOU CAN LAUGH.
- I CAN'T LAUGH ABOUT THIS.
- UM, HEY, MISCHA.
- LOOK, DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I DIDN'T COME ABOARD THIS SHIP
TO ACT AS YOUR COUNSELOR
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
HOW'S EUREKA DOING?
- SHE'S OFF LOOKING, FOR RENTON.
- OH, NO.
WE'RE OUT OF TOOTHBRUSHES
'CAUSE RENTON'S NOT
HERE TO STOCK THEM.
I WONDER IF THERE ARE
SOME IN THE BACK...
EUREKA?
- OH, UM, WELCOME
TO THE SHIP'S STORE.
WAIT, WHY ARE YOU STOCKING
THE SHELVES WITH FRESH GOODS?
AND WHY ARE YOU
WEARING THAT OUTFIT?
- WELL, BECAUSE HE'S GONE.
- HUH...
- I WONDER IF
EUREKA'S ALL RIGHT?
- I THINK IT'S OBVIOUS,
SHE'S NOT ALL RIGHT.
- SHE'S IN PAIN, I'M SURE OF IT.
I KNOW JUST HOW SHE FEELS.
HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
DO ABOUT IT, MOONDOGGIE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
WHY DON'T YOU ASK HOLLAND?
AFTER ALL,
THE GEKKO IS HIS SHIP.
IT WAS HIS IDEA AS THE LEADER,
TO BRING EUREKA HERE,
AND THEN TO LET
RENTON ABOARD THE SHIP.
I'M SCARED ANOTHER CHAIR'S
GOING TO COME FLYING MY WAY,
IF WE TRY.
- WELL, YEAH.
- THE RAMEN'S COLD.
RENTON...
- WOW!
- SO, BOY, WOULD YOU LIKE TO
CALL RAY, MAMA? AND ME PAPA?
- HUH?
- WELL, RAY SAID
IF YOU'D LIKE...
I MEAN IT WAS HER IDEA!
- OH, NO, HONEY, YOU AGREED!
- ( laughing )
NOW, RENTON!
CALL US PAPA AND MAMA,
AND USE A BIG VOICE, OKAY?
HUH? UH, HEY, WAIT A SEC.
- I GUESS THIS WAS
ALL TOO SUDDEN!
OH, RENTON, I'M SORRY!
IT'S OKAY, YOU DON'T NEED TO
DO IT UNLESS YOU REALLY WANT TO.
AND YOU ONLY NEED TO DO IT,
WHILE WE'RE ABOARD THIS SHIP.
- BUT...
BUT, I...
I DID SOMETHING
STUPID IN OLPASA,
AND GOT IN THE WAY OF YOUR WORK!
( crying )
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF YOU KICKED ME OUT
OF HERE, RIGHT NOW!
- DON'T BE DUMB.
YOU DID THE BEST, YOU COULD!
IF YOU WANT TO, YOU CAN STAY
ABOARD THIS SHIP FOREVER!
OKAY, RENTON?
- BALANCE?
- I WANT YOU TO
LISTEN TO THIS IDEA,
THOUGH IT'S NOTHING MORE
THAN A HYPOTHESIS.
WHAT SEEMS TO SPARK
THE AMITA DRIVE
TO RESPOND IS A BALANCE.
BETWEEN THE MENTAL SIGNS
OF EUREKA AND THOSE OF RENTON.
- BOTH OF THEM?
- RIGHT.
EUREKA ALONE CAN'T DO IT,
AND NEITHER CAN RENTON.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT IS THE
BALANCE BETWEEN THE TWO.
- HUH?
- ( sighs ) JUST DISBAND IT,
ALREADY!
DISBAND THE GEKKOSTATE!
IT'S USELESS TO
KEEP GOING LIKE THIS!
SOMEONE HERE IS
CREATING A BAD ATMOSPHERE!
- WAIT, A MINUTE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
- WELL, I HAVEN'T!
- LET GO OF ME!
- WHY DID THINGS
END UP THIS WAY?
BECAUSE, ALL YOU'RE DOING RIGHT
NOW, IS BEING JEALOUS OF RENTON!
YOU'RE POUTING BECAUSE HE
TOOK EUREKA AWAY FROM YOU!
WHY, HOLLAND?
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME HELP YOU?
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME
INTO YOUR HEART?
- Renton: IT WAS SWEET.
AND WARM. AND IT SMELLED GOOD.
BUT THE WORDS WERE
SLIGHTLY TICKLISH.
PAPA... MAMA...
( chuckling )
- REMEMBERING WHAT YOU DID, HUH?
IT'S SOMETHING THAT ONLY
YOUNG ONES CAN GET AWAY WITH.
- SO, WERE YOU THINKING
ABOUT YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
- NO, I WASN'T!
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO HIDE IT!
- YOU WERE THINKING ABOUT HER?
- JUST STOP IT, CHARLES.
THAT'S NOT IT!
UH...
I MEAN, PAPA...
- ( laughing )
NORMALLY PEOPLE HAVE
TROUBLE SAYING THINGS,
WHEN THEY ARE TOLD THEY HAVE TO.
I KNOW, I COULDN'T DO IT.
- WELL, UH, CAN'T I START OUT
JUST CALLING YOU GUYS
MOM AND DAD FOR A WHILE?
- HMM?
- YOU SEE, I WAS NEVER ABLE TO
CALL FOR MY FATHER OR MOTHER.
SO USING PAPA AND
MAMA IS A LITTLE
TOO HIGH OF A HURDLE
FOR ME RIGHT NOW.
- ( gasping )
- I JUST WORKED UP
A LITTLE SWEAT AT THE GYM
SMELL BAD?
WELL RENTON,
THIS IS HOW YOUR DAD SMELLS.
- IT REALLY DOES SMELL GOOD.
- ( dings )
- I SEE, YOUR SKILLS ARE
AS A MECHANIC.
- GRANDPA POUNDED ALL
THIS KNOWLEDGE INTO ME.
HE WAS AN OLD MAN
WITH A HUGE MOUTH.
AND I THINK HIS HOBBY
WAS BEING BULLHEADED.
- NOW, DONT SAY THAT.
HE COULDN'T HAVE BEEN THAT BAD.
HE DID RAISE YOU.
- THOUGH I GUESS, HE WASN'T
GET TO RAISE ME,
ALL THE WAY TO MANHOOD.
BUT HE MADE SURE THAT MY
MAINTENANCE SKILLS WERE GOOD.
JUST BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
I ACCEPTED AN URGENT REQUEST,
TO TUNE THE LEGENDARY LFO,
IT WAS THE NIRVASH.
- THE NIRVASH? THE TYPE ZERO?
- YUP!
- WOW! THATS AMAZING.
I'LL HAVE TO GO SAY HELLO
TO HIM SOME TIME.
YOU SEE RENTON,
IF YOU'RE REALLY MY SON,
THEN YOUR GRANDPA
MUST BE MY PAPA!
- ( laughing )
- THE FACTORY,
IS IT FAR FROM HERE?
- IN BELL FOREST!
IT'S JUST A LITTLE PLACE
CALLED GARAGE THURSTON.
- THURSTON?!
WAIT A MINUTE, THEN THAT
MEANS YOUR DEAD FATHER WAS...
- YES, HIS NAME WAS
ADROC THURSTON.
- ( gasps )
- IF RENTON AND EUREKA
WERE TOGETHER,
SOME DAY THEY WOULD
CAUSE A TRAGEDY.
- YEAH? WELL, THAT WOULDN'T
HAVE CHANGED EVEN IF YOU
WERE THE ONE
CHOSEN BY EUREKA,
AND YOU DAMN WELL KNOW IT!
AND IF IT WAS YOU, YOU'D BE
PLUNGING FORWARD, RIGHT?
- YOU'RE RIGHT, TALHO.
I GUESS I AM GOING TO HAVE TO
ACCEPT HIM FOR WHAT HE IS.
- YOU JUST DON'T GET IT!
WHAT YOU HAVE TO ACCEPT,
IS THAT, YOU WERE NOT THE ONE
CHOSEN BY EUREKA!
YOU HAVE TO ACCEPT THE FACT
THAT WE HAVE TO BELIEVE
IN THE TWO OF THEM!
- ( sighs ) YES, I KNOW THAT.
I REALLY DO, TALHO.
- IF IT'S A TEST, THEN I DONT
HAVE TO GO WITH YOU.
- IT'S JUST A FLIGHT
TO SEE HOW IT'S DOING.
BESIDES, THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT TO SHOW YOU.
- ( screams )
( gasps )
THAT'S AMAZING!
I'VE ALWAYS LOOKED UP TO THE
LFO'S THAT COULD FREELY FLY
AROUND THIS WONDERFUL WORLD,
LIKE A SKYFISH.
I LOVED THEM. BUT NOW...
- YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY ARE
A WONDERFUL MECHANIC!
IT'S AS IF YOU KNOW JUST HOW
THE MECHS FEEL!
HUH?
- THIS IS A TOOL THAT'S USED
TO MURDER PEOPLE.
I DON'T CARE HOW IT FEELS.
- CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- MMM-HMM.
THIS WORLD IS SUCH
A BEAUTIFUL PLACE,
WHY DO PEOPLE
HAVE TO FIGHT EACH OTHER?
- THERE'S SOMETHING I'VE BEEN
A BIT CURIOUS ABOUT.
EXACTLY WHAT KIND OF LFO
WAS THE TYPE ZERO?
IT IS A LEGENDARY SHIP.
IT WASN'T NORMAL, WAS IT?
- NO, IT WASN'T NORMAL...
THE NIRVASH DOESN'T
BOOT PROPERLY
WITH JUST AN ORDINARY
COMPAC DRIVE.
YOU NEED A SPECIAL ATTACHMENT
CALLED THE AMITA DRIVE.
- THE AMITA DRIVE?
- RIGHT. THE AMITA DRIVE,
WORKING IN CONJUNCTION
WITH THE COMPAC DRIVE,
BECOMES THE KEY TO
LAUNCH THE SATORI PROGRAM.
- THE SEVEN SWELL?
- YEAH.
HOWEVER, ONCE THEY ARE COMBINED,
THE TWO DRIVES CAN'T BE
TAKEN OFF AGAIN.
I DONT KNOW WHY, THOUGH.
- I HEARD THAT THE TYPE ZERO
HAD A STRANGE PILOT AS WELL.
- IS THAT TRUE?
- YEAH, VERY STRANGE.
BUT THEN AGAIN, THE
VERY FIRST MOMENT I SAW HER,
THERE WAS SOMETHING ABOUT HER
THAT REALLY STRUCK ME.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY IT WAS
A CASE OF LOVE AT FIRST SIGHT.
BUT, THE FEELINGS I HAD
NEVER GOT THROUGH TO HER,
AND I FINALLY BAILED
OUT OF THE GEKKO,
THE FIRST CHANCE I GOT.
- WAIT, THE GEKKO?!
- OH, SORRY, I GUESS
I HADN'T TOLD YOU THAT YET.
YOU SEE, BEFORE I BOARDED
THIS SHIP WITH YOU,
I WAS A MEMBER OF GEKKOSTATE.
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
- ( beeping )
- DON'T BE MAD, CHARLES.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO HIDE IT FROM YOU!
BUT, I COULDN'T BRING MYSELF
TO START THIS CONVERSATION.
I'M SORRY.
- I SEE. SO, IS HOLLAND
DOING WELL NOWADAYS?
- HUH?
- ( beeping )
- MON-SOONOS? THIS IS BAD!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
IF WE DON'T MAKE A MOVE FAST,
THEY'RE GOING TO SHOOT US DOWN.
CHARLES!
- FREEDOM IS SOMETHING THAT
YOU NEED TO ACTIVELY ACQUIRE.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT'S GIVEN
WITH NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
TO BE FREE MEANS
TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY,
AND PREPARE YOURSELF
FOR WHAT'S TO COME.
UNDERSTAND, RENTON?
- ( gasps )
( grunting )
- I HAVE NO INTENT TO RESIST.
PLEASE STOP THE ATTACKS NOW.
I'M A FREELANCER
FOR THE FEDERATION.
I'M CHARLES BEAMS.
- Milton: CODE CONFIRMED.
SORRY TO HAVE BOTHERED YOU.
I'M FIRST LIEUTENANT MILTON
OF STATE ARMY 87KSQ.
WE ENCOUNTERED THE GEKKO IN
THIS AREA, A FEW DAYS AGO,
SO WE'VE BEEN ON CLOSE ALERT.
WE WERE PATROLLING,
WHEN WE SPOTTED YOU.
- YEAH, DON'T WORRY,
I KNOW WHERE YOU GUYS STAND.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
BUT YOU'RE A SUBCONTRACTING
COURIER, AREN'T YOU?
- I GUESS WE'RE EVEN, RENTON.
WE'RE REALLY FREELANCERS,
WORKING UNDER A RESERVE
UNIT OF THE FEDERATION ARMY.
AT THE MOMENT, WE'RE ON A
MISSION TO TAKE BACK EUREKA,
AS WELL AS THE TYPE ZERO.
- TELL ME, YOU'RE JOKING.
- I CAN'T.
- BUT IT'S A LIE!
- NO, IT ISN'T.
- IT'S A LIE!
- IT'S NOT A LIE.
- RENTON!
- TELL ME, IT'S A LIE!
PLEASE, CHARLES!
I'M BEGGING YOU!
I PROMISE, I'LL PRACTICE!
I'LL DO MY BEST TO CALL YOU
GUYS, PAPA AND MAMA!
SO, PLEASE,
TELL ME IT'S NOT TRUE.
TELL ME, IT'S A LIE.
IT'S A LIE!
- GEEZ, I'M SO PATHETIC!
- YOU FINALLY CAME OUT.
IDIOT, MY LEGS ARE
TOTALLY NUMB ALREADY!
HAP SAID HE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GET SOME INFORMATION,
ON WHERE MASTER NORB IS.
- Charles: THE STATE AND
THE FEDERATION ARMIES
ARE WORKING TOGETHER TO
FORCE THE GEKKO TO A PLACE
WHERE IT CAN BE SHOT DOWN.
THE COORDINATES ARE
ON PAGE 286 ON THE JACKSON MAP.
WE BEGIN IN SEVEN DAYS.
I DONT CARE IF YOU
GO BACK TO THE GEKKO
AND TELL THEM THIS INFORMATION.
IF YOU WANT TO KEEP IT IN
THE CORNER OF YOUR HEART,
YOU'RE FREE TO STAY
ON THIS SHIP.
YOU ALSO HAVE THE OPTION OF
RUNNING AWAY FROM BOTH SIDES.
IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
- ( Ray sobbing )
- Charles: THE ASSAULT LOCATION
AND DATE WILL NEVER CHANGE.
WE WILL MAKE SURE TO
TAKE THE GEKKO DOWN
AT THAT TIME AND PLACE.
SO, I WANT YOU TO PROMISE
ME SOMETHING.
IF WHAT YOU DECIDE
TO DO IS BASED ON
YOU BEING HONEST WITH YOUR
FEELINGS, WE'LL ACCEPT IT.
PROMISE ME, YOU'LL
SEE IT TO THE END.
- ( grunting )
- CAN I ASK YOU ONE THING?
DID YOU APPROACH ME, KNOWING WHO
I WAS FROM THE VERY BEGINNING?
- OF COURSE, WE KNEW!
( crying )
- THEN, I GUESS,
I'LL BE GOING NOW.
MR. CHARLES AND MRS. RAY,
I WANT TO THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING!
- ( sobbing )
- THAT BOY...
I WONDER IF HE WILL,
GO BACK TO THE GEKKO?
- I'M CERTAIN OF IT.
AFTER ALL, THAT BOY,
I MEAN RENTON, IS OUR SON.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- ( screaming )
- NO MATTER HOW HOARSE I GET,
IF THIS SCREAM OF MINE CAN
MELT AWAY INTO THE DARKNESS,
THERE'S JUST ONE THING THAT
I WANT TO TELL SOMEONE.
EUREKA, RIGHT NOW,
I REALLY NEED TO SEE YOU!
- PLEASE! I HAVE TO GO
WHERE RENTON IS!
YOU NEED HIM TOO,
DON'T YOU, NIRVASH?
NIRVASH!
- EUREKA...
I WANT TO SEE YOU.
AND I WANT YOU TO HEAR
ABOUT THIS FEELING OF MINE.
( grunts ) BUT...
HOW DO I DO THAT?
- PLEASE, NIRVASH,
MOVE FOR ME! NIRVASH!
( crying ) PLEASE! MOVE!
PLEASE MOVE!
- Holland: I'LL GO.
- ( gasps )
- I'LL MAKE SURE
TO BRING HIM BACK TO YOU.
SO, PROMISE YOU'LL WAIT!
- Renton: TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ BE TOGETHER
YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE! ♪
♪ FLY AWAY! FLY AWAY! ♪
- ♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE.
TAKE IT EASY. ♪
♪ FLY AWAY! FLY AWAY! ♪
♪ TAKE MY CHANCE
BELIEVE IN MYSELF ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
- Ray: THE BOY SEES AN ILLUSION
IN A VOICELESS CONVERSATION
WITH THE EARTH.
HE NOW FLIES INTO REALITY,
WITH HIS CONFIRMED
EMOTIONS IN HIS HEART.
NEXT EPISODE,
WORLD'S END GARDEN.