- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
- ( humming )
OH, WHAT IS IT?
- I WAS JUST ADMIRING WHAT
A HARD WORKER YOU ARE, BOY.
- WELL, I GOT TO CARRY
MY WEIGHT.
HUMANS ARE TRULY AMUSING BEINGS.
I'M DOING THE SAME THINGS,
BUT THE REACTIONS I GET
ARE SO DIFFERENT.
OVER THERE, THEY YELLED AT ME
AND TOLD ME I WAS BEING SLOW.
BUT OVER HERE,
THEY ASK IF I'M DONE,
AND ARE SURPRISED AT THE SPEED.
THERE I WAS TOLD
THAT I WAS INCONSIDERATE,
HERE THEY LAUGH AT ME AND SAY
THAT I DON'T HAVE TO DO SO MUCH.
HONESTLY, THIS PLACE
IS VERY COMFORTABLE.
I MEAN, WHEN I WAS
WITH THE GEKKOSTATE,
I WAS JUST A...
- HOMESICK?
- HUH?
- NO, NOTHING LIKE THAT!
- OH, DO YOU MISS
YOUR MOTHER THEN?
- HUH?
( gasps ) WELL...
- ( laughs ) I'M JUST KIDDING!
I CAME HERE TO CALL YOU
WE'LL BE LANDING SOON.
GO ON, TAKE A LOOK.
YOU REALLY CAN'T TELL
THAT MUCH FROM UP HERE.
- IT'S A JOB, ISN'T IT?
- YES. WE WANT YOU TO COME.
I'M PRETTY SURE THAT
WE'RE GOING TO BE
SPENDING TONIGHT IN THE CITY.
OH, AND YOU CAN JUST TOSS ALL
OF THE LAUNDRY INTO THE DRYER.
I GUESS THERE'S
A BOY AROUND NOW,
I'LL HAVE TO BE MORE CAREFUL.
SORRY!
- ( sighs )
THIS PLACE IS SO COMFORTABLE!
- PURPOSE OF YOUR VISIT?
- WORK.
I'M A COURIER,
HERE TO PICK UP CARGO.
- WE HAVE AN ANTI-TERRORIST
ALERT, IN EFFECT RIGHT NOW.
WHEN YOU STEP OUT,
MAKE SURE THAT YOU KEEP
YOUR PASSPORT WITH
YOU AT ALL TIMES.
IT'S ALMOST CURFEW,
SO YOU REALLY DON'T
HAVE A LOT OF TIME LEFT.
- YOU SHOULD HURRY.
- THEN LET'S GO.
- HEY, YOU.
- UH, YES?
- YOUR PARENTS WENT ON AHEAD.
- OH...
SOMEHOW, IT MADE ME HAPPY.
- ( siren wailing )
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S THAT?
- THIS IS IT.
- THIS PLACE?
- ( people groaning )
- IS IT THE WAR?
- NO. TERRORISM.
- TERRORISM?
- DO YOU WANT TO WAIT HERE?
- NO, I'LL GO!
- ( knock on door )
- HUH?
- I'M BEAMS.
I RECEIVED A COURIER REQUEST.
- I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
PLEASE, COME IN.
- SHE'S THE ONE?
- MAY WE ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- I GIVE NO GUARANTEES
ON WHETHER OR NOT I CAN
GET YOUR DAUGHTER
TO THE VODARAC SANCTUARY
BEFORE SHE PASSES AWAY.
- IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER.
RATHER THAN DYING HERE,
I'M SURE THAT MY
DAUGHTER WOULD PREFER
TO BECOME ONE WITH THE VODARAC,
BY HEADING TO THE SANCTUARY
OF HER OWN WILL,
TO GAIN AN ETERNAL LIFE.
BESIDES, WE CAN'T EVEN PRAY,
AS LONG AS WE STAY HERE.
- ( alarm sounding )
- Ray: IT'S AN ALARM,
WARNING PEOPLE TO STAY INSIDE.
- WHAT ARE YOUR WISHES?
IT WOULD BE TOUGH GOING BUT
THERE IS A WAY TO
TRANSPORT HER RIGHT NOW.
- NO, I DON'T WANT
MY DAUGHTER TO FACE
ANY MORE HARDSHIPS OR DANGER.
TAKE HER IN THE EARLY MORNING
WHEN THE BAN LIFTS,
WHEN SHE WON'T CATCH
ANYONE'S EYE.
- Renton: SO, IT'S NOT THAT
HER LIFE CAN'T BE SAVED?
- NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID.
I DID SAY SHE WON'T
BE ABLE TO STAY ALIVE
WITHOUT LIFE SUPPORT.
- SO, IF SHE HAD
A LIFE SUPPORT SYSTEM,
SHE'D BE ABLE TO STAY ALIVE?
- WELL, YEAH.
IF THIS HOSPITAL DOESN'T
HAVE SUCH A SYSTEM,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY WE DON'T
TAKE HER TO A HOSPITAL THAT DOES
INSTEAD OF TAKING HER
TO THE SANCTUARY?
- IT'S NOT THAT THEY DON'T
HAVE A SYSTEM HERE,
THEY JUST CAN'T USE IT.
- WHY?
- BECAUSE THEY ARE
WITH THE VODARAC.
- ACCORDING TO THE GOVERNMENT,
THE TERRORIST ACT WAS CAUSED
BY A GROUP OF RADICAL VODARAC.
THE VICTIMS FAMILIES FIERCELY
OPPOSED THE CONTINUATION
OF TREATMENTS FOR SOMEONE
OF THE SAME BELIEFS
AS THE TERRORISTS.
- Renton: BUT, IT'S NOT LIKE
SHE WAS DIRECTLY RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE TERRORIST ACT!
- JUST BECAUSE
SHE'S A VODARAC--
- LOOK, I FEEL THE SAME WAY!
BUT, HER PARENTS DECIDED THEY
WOULD ACCEPT THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
- Renton: THAT THE GIRL
IS GOING TO DIE?
- Charles: PERHAPS
FOR THE VODARAC,
IT IS SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT
FROM DEATH, AS WE SEE IT.
- Renton: THERE IS NO SUCH
THING AS AN ETERNAL LIFE!
IF YOU DESTROY A HUMAN BEING,
THEN HE WILL NEVER COME BACK!
THAT'S WHY...
EVERYTHING IS OVER
WHEN SOMEONE DIES!
I'M CERTAIN THAT SHE...
- THAT'S SOMETHING THE VODARAC
CAN DECIDE ON THEIR OWN!
IT'S NOT FOR US
TO BE MEDDLING IN.
- CHARLES, YOU'RE MUCH MORE
COLD-HEARTED THAN I THOUGHT.
- WOW, I GUESS IT'S NOT
THAT EASY TO RAISE
AN ADOLESCENT SON.
- THAT GIRL'S PRIMARY PHYSICIAN?
I THINK HE'S IN THE WEST WING.
- DOCTOR!
- UNFORTUNATELY,
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- WELL, WHY IS THAT?
- THANKS TO HER
PARENTS KINDNESS,
THE LIFE SUPPORT SYSTEM HAS
BEEN TRANSFERRED TO THAT BOY.
- YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY MORE OF THOSE?
- NO. NOT HERE.
IF WE HAD MORE, THEN MAYBE.
- WE NO LONGER HAVE TO ALLOW HER
ANY MORE HARDSHIPS IN HER LIFE.
- YES.
I'M GOING TO GO FIND THE DOCTOR
AND THANK HIM FOR
EVERYTHING HE'S DONE.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT? IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- MMM-MMM.
- GOOD. YOUR BRAIN WAVES
ARE NORMAL.
STARTING TOMORROW,
I'LL LET YOU LEAVE THE ROOM,
BUT YOU HAVE TO
STAY ABOARD SHIP.
HOWEVER, THE HANGAR
IS OFF LIMITS.
- HEY, MISCHA...
- HMM?
- I'M CURIOUS. HOW IS RENTON?
- I'M PRETTY SURE,
HE'S DOING FINE.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
TODAY, THOUGH.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
- WHAT IS LOVE?
MISCHA?
- OH, SORRY.
I DIDN'T HEAR WHAT YOU SAID.
COULD YOU TELL ME AGAIN, DEAR?
- All: LOVE?
- LOVE, LIKE IN ROMANCE?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- WHOA, THIS IS A BIGGER SHOCK
THAN WHEN SHE SAID,
SHE WAS GOING TO BE
THE MOTHER OF THOSE KIDS.
- WELL, SHE JUST
ASKED WHAT LOVE WAS,
SO THAT DOESN'T NECESSARILY
MEAN THAT SHE'S IN LOVE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT IT MEANS.
BUT I'VE GOT TO ADMIT,
I WAS SURPRISED.
- NO WAY!
- YES, WAY.
CAN'T YOU SEE,
IT ACTUALLY HAPPENED?
- IS THE GUY WHO I THINK IT IS?
- AS I SAID,
WE CAN'T BE SURE OF ANYTHING.
- BUT SHE DID ASK WHAT LOVE
WAS, RIGHT AFTER SHE ASKED
HOW RENTON WAS
DOING, DIDN'T SHE?
THE POSSIBILITY IS HIGH
THAT RENTON IS THE ONE
AND NOT HOLLAND.
- THAT'S NONSENSE.
- IN ANY CASE, ONCE EUREKA
STARTS WALKING AROUND SHIP,
SHE'LL REALIZE IN AN INSTANT
THAT RENTON IS NO LONGER HERE.
PERHAPS IT WOULD BE
BETTER TO HURRY UP
AND TELL HER THE
TRUTH, RIGHT NOW.
- HOLLAND WILL.
- HEY, WHY ME?
- WELL, WHO ELSE SHOULD DO IT?
- HUH?
- MR. BEAMS!
- WHAT?
- IT'S MY DAUGHTER.
MY DAUGHTER IS MISSING!
SOMEBODY TOOK HER.
- ( both gasp )
- CAN SOMEONE HAVE TAKEN HER
BECAUSE SHE'S A VODARAC?
- ( gasps )
- NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
I THINK IT'S OUR YOUNG GUEST.
- IT COULDN'T BE!
- ( gasps )
- JEEZ! DAMMIT!
HAVING AN ADOLESCENT
AROUND IS A REAL PAIN!
- I'M NOT SURE WHAT TO TELL HER.
( gasps )
- OH, HOLLAND.
- OH, WELL, EUREKA,
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M DOING MUCH BETTER.
- I SEE. WELL, SEE YA.
- HOLLAND, WAIT.
RENTON, IS HE IN HIS ROOM?
DO YOU THINK HE'D MIND
IF I VISITED HIM RIGHT NOW?
- HE'S...
OUT SHOPPING RIGHT NOW
WITH TALHO AND HILDA!
HE'LL BE GONE FOR DAYS.
- I SEE. THANK YOU, HOLLAND.
- IDIOT.
- IF I HEAD IN THE DIRECTION
THAT THE CAR WENT THEN...
IT'S COLD!
- ♪ I'M SO HAPPY
I'M WITH MAMA! ♪
♪ I'M SO HAPPY!
I'M SO HAPPY! ♪
- WOW, LINCK!
THAT'S A NICE SONG.
- HEY, MAMA, I CAN SING A SONG
LIKE THAT, TOO YOU KNOW!
- ♪ I'M SO HAPPY
I'M WITH MAMA! ♪
- Both: ♪ I'M SO HAPPY!
I'M SO HAPPY! ♪
♪ I'M SO HAPPY!
- HEY, KIDS. WHAT...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( hushing )
- ♪ I'M SO HAPPY ♪
- HEY THERE, HAP!
- HEY, GUYS.
WHAT'S THAT SONG YOU'RE SINGING?
- IT'S MY SONG. I MADE IT!
- NUH-UH, I DID!
- HEY, HAP. HAS HILDA'S
GROUP COME BACK YET?
- NO, NOT YET.
DO YOU NEED SOMETHING?
- NO, IT'S OKAY. LET'S GO.
- ♪ I'M SO HAPPY
I'M WITH MAMA! ♪
- WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
- WHAT? HE HASN'T TOLD HER YET?
I DON'T GET IT.
- HE JUST KEEPS CHICKENING
OUT EVERY TIME.
- BUT THE REASONS
WHY RENTON LEFT,
AREN'T EXACTLY HOLLAND'S
RESPONSIBILITY, ARE THEY?
- HE'S TOO AFRAID OF HOW
EUREKA WOULD FEEL TO TELL HER.
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
I THINK WE SHOULD SIT BACK,
AND WAIT UNTIL HOLLAND
TELLS HER ON HIS OWN.
- ( alarm wailing )
- IT'S ONLY
A LITTLE WAYS FARTHER.
- ( all murmuring )
- ( gasps )
HEY, YOU WORK HERE, RIGHT?
THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT I WANT TO ASK YOU!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT'S THE MEANING OF ALL THIS?
WHY DID YOU BRING A VODARAC GIRL
IN DEATH GEAR TO THIS PLACE?
- WHAT THE HELL IS DEATH GEAR?
- LOOK, KID, BEFORE
IT CAUSES A PROBLEM...
- Man: WHY THE HELL DID
YOU COME HERE?
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO PLAY DEAD, VODARAC!
- DON'T JUST SIT THERE!
SAY SOMETHING!
- STOP IT! LEAVE HER ALONE!
SHE'S SICK AND...
( grunts )
- GIVE MY BABY BACK TO ME!
HE WAS SO INNOCENT!
GIVE HIM BACK TO ME!
- ( gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE WAS THE ONE
THAT WAS BEHIND THE TERRORISM!
WHAT ARE YOU
ACCUSING HER OF DOING?
- WHAT AM I ACCUSING
HER OF, YOU ASK?
WELL, I'LL ASK YOU IN RETURN.
WHAT DID THE TWO OF YOU
COME HERE FOR?!
DID YOU EVEN THINK
ABOUT THE FEELINGS,
OF THOSE WHO LOST THEIR FAMILY
MEMBERS TO THESE TERRORISTS?
- ( overlapping chatter )
- OH MAN, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW WE GOT TO THE POINT
WHERE I HAVE TO SNEAK
AROUND MY OWN HOME.
( sighs in relief )
UH...
- WELL, WELCOME BACK, HILDA.
- I GUESS I'M BACK.
- Charles: HAVE YOU
FOUND RENTON?
- Ray: NOT YET.
THE GIRL'S WITH HIM,
SO I REALLY DON'T THINK
HE CAN GO TOO AWFULLY FAR.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
- Charles: I DIDN'T SEE ANY
COUPLES THAT LOOKED LIKE THEM,
INSIDE VEHICLES OR BOATS
THAT WERE LEAVING THE TOWER.
- Ray: IF THEY MADE THEIR
BACK TO THE HOSPITAL,
I'M SURE THAT THE GIRL'S PARENTS
WOULD HAVE CONTACTED US ALREADY.
- HEY, SAM!
LOOKS LIKE MITCH AND THE GANG
CORNERED THAT KID FROM EARLIER.
THE VODARAC CHICK
IS STILL WITH HIM.
- Charles: WHAT'S WRONG? WHAT?
- I THINK I FOUND HIM.
- ( car engine starts )
- DAMN YOU.
IS IT FUN FOR YOU TO DO THIS?
- IS IT FUN?
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH WHETHER OR NOT
ANY OF IT IS FUN.
- THEN, WHY DO YOU DO IT?
- THIS IS REVENGE.
REVENGE FOR THE MASSACRE
OF OUR FAMILIES!
- I'M SORRY,
BUT CAN YOU CALL IT A DAY?
I DON'T WANT
ANY MORE PEOPLE INJURED.
- HMM...
THE STATE ARMY HAS CAUGHT ON!
- ( all gasping )
- SO?
- RELEASE THIS MAN'S
RESTRAINTS IMMEDIATELY.
- SEE, I WASN'T LYING TO YOU.
WELL, I'LL BE GOING NOW.
- HEY! SIT DOWN.
- SORRY FOR THE TROUBLE, SIR.
- WHAT'S THE STORY HERE?
- I ASKED HEADQUARTERS
FOR IDENTIFICATION,
JUST LIKE HE TOLD ME TO,
AND I WAS CONNECTED
TO CAPTAIN DOMINIC.
FROM MISSION HEADQUARTERS
INTELLIGENCE PRECINCT SEVEN.
I WAS TOLD TO ACT AS THOUGH
NOTHING HAD HAPPENED.
- I WON'T CONDEMN YOU FOR
THE ACTIONS THAT YOU TOOK.
IN FACT, I BELIEVE WHAT YOU DID,
WAS THE RIGHT THING TO
DO AS A HUMAN BEING.
BUT WHETHER OR NOT THAT GIRL,
REALLY WISHED FOR SUCH A THING
IS A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT MATTER.
MOREOVER,
THERE'S NO WAY TO KNOW,
AS WE NEVER SPOKE
A SINGLE WORD TO HER.
- JUST A FEW MINUTES AGO,
SHE PASSED WAY.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT TO DO NOW?
WE WILL TAKE HER TO THE
DESTINATION OF YOUR CHOICE.
OF COURSE, I WON'T
ASK FOR ANY MONEY.
- SANCTUARY.
I'M SURE THAT IT IS WHAT SHE
WOULD HAVE WISHED FOR AS WELL.
- ( gasps )
- NO, WAIT.
FOR WHAT YOU DID, THANK YOU.
- ( crying )
- WE'RE GOING TO GET IN TROUBLE
IF WE DON'T DO SOMETHING.
I MEAN, HOW LONG ARE WE GOING
TO KEEP IT A SECRET FROM EUREKA?
- THERE ARE LIMITATIONS
TO HOW MANY LIES WE CAN PILE UP.
- AH, YEAH MAN, EVEN I'M
STARTING TO AVOID EUREKA.
- SO, WHAT'S THE REASON
BEHIND OUR LEADER
NOT BEING ABLE TO TELL
HER WHAT'S GOING ON?
- BECAUSE OF ROMANCE.
- WHAT ROMANCE?
- THE STORY ABOUT HOW EUREKA
IS IN LOVE WITH RENTON.
- WHAT? IS THAT FOR REAL?
- I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE!
I'M LONELY!
- HEY GIDGET, YOU TOLD?
- I DIDN'T TELL ALL OF THEM.
JUST YOU, DOGGIE.
- I'M WONDERING IF RENTON
KNEW ANYTHING ABOUT THAT.
- IF HE HAD KNOWN,
HE WOULDN'T HAVE LEFT.
- LET'S GO LOOK FOR HIM.
- I'M SOUNDING LIKE
A BROKEN RECORD,
BUT THE FACT HE LEFT A NOTE
ASKING US NOT TO LOOK FOR HIM...
- MEANS HE WANTS US
TO LOOK FOR HIM,
AS WELL AS WORRY ABOUT HIM.
- SPEAKING FROM PERSONAL
EXPERIENCE, MATTHEW?
- DAMN STRAIGHT.
I CONTACTED SOME
OF MY DJ FRIENDS,
AND THERE HAVE BEEN
A COUPLE OF SIGHTINGS
OF SOMEONE THAT
RESEMBLES RENTON.
- HOW DID THEY KNOW IT WAS HIM?
- THE WHEEL, MAN, THE WHEEL!
- I SEE.
- I THINK YOU SHOULD
GO PICK HIM UP.
- YOU'RE LIKE HIS OLDER
BROTHER RIGHT?
- I'M NOT HIS BROTHER.
- THE METHOD BY WHICH
WE PICK HIM UP
NEEDS SOME CONSIDERATION.
- THAT'S RIGHT. THE FIRST
WORDS WE THROW AT HIM,
CAN BE A KEY POINT WHEN DEALING
WITH AN ADOLESCENT FUGITIVE!
- SPEAKING FROM
EXPERIENCE, AGAIN?
- SHUT YOUR DAMN MOUTH,
ALL OF YOU!
RENTON DIDN'T LEAVE
THE GEKKO IN ORDER TO
MASK HIS STUPID WHIMS
OR HIS LONELINESS!
HE JUST WANTED TO LEAVE!
- ( all gasp )
- OW! WHY DID HE DO THAT?
- WE SCREWED UP.
HE WAS SERIOUSLY THINKING
ABOUT RENTON'S WELL-BEING.
- Holland: I THOUGHT
THAT I UNDERSTOOD
ALMOST ALL OF WHAT GOES
ON INSIDE HIS HEAD.
I'M SO PATHETIC.
- I'VE HEARD THAT A LOT LATELY.
- BUT WHY? WHY DID RENTON
DECIDE TO LEAVE THE GEKKO?
IS IT BECAUSE I DID AWFUL
THINGS TO HIM THAT RENTON LEFT?
- EUREKA...
- COME ON, HOLLAND! IS IT TRUE?
AM I THE REASON HE LEFT?
ANSWER ME!
- Renton: I'M SURE SHE'S HOLDING
A GRUDGE AGAINST ME.
I DIDN'T THINK ONE BIT
ABOUT HER FEELINGS,
AND THOUGHT SELFISHLY
THAT I HAD TO PROTECT HER.
I DIDN'T EVEN PAUSE
TO THINK WHETHER OR NOT
IT WAS THE RIGHT
THING TO DO FOR HER.
IN THE END, WHAT I DID
DIDN'T PROTECT ANYONE.
IN FACT, WHAT I DID
WAS HURT THEIR FEELINGS.
PEOPLE WHO DIDN'T
NEED TO GET HURT.
PEOPLE WHO HAVE
ALREADY BEEN HURT ENOUGH.
I ONLY MADE THEIR WOUNDS
EVEN WORSE THAN BEFORE.
AND I'M SURE THAT MY PAST WAS...
( crying ) I'M SO SORRY!
- WHERE IS HE?
- HIS ROOM. YOU KNOW,
RAISING AN ADOLESCENT SON...
- IT'S NOT TOO BAD.
- YEAH.
NOT BAD AT ALL.
- OH, RENTON...
I WANT TO SEE YOU.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ BE TOGETHER,
NOW YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE ♪
♪ FLY AWAY! FLY AWAY! ♪
♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE
TAKE IT EASY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY! FLY AWAY! ♪
♪ TAKE MY CHANCE
BELIEVE IN MYSELF ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
- Ray: THE HEART
SEEKING A PARENT,
AND THE HEART SEEKING A CHILD.
TIMES FULL OF WARM
DREAMS COME FORTH.
ALONG WITH THE TRUTHS
BEHIND EACH OF THEM.
NEXT EPISODE, "PARADISE LOST."