( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
♪ SO ♪
- ♪ YOU GOTTA REMEMBER ♪
- ♪ COME ON ♪
- ♪ GAME OVER ♪
♪ WE WANNA MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE ♪
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
♪ SO ♪
- ♪ YOU GOTTA REMEMBER ♪
- Renton: ( voice over )
SIS, DO YOU REMEMBER
THE CITY OF CONTRORADO?
IT'S A CITY THAT'S HOME TO MANY
SANATORIUMS RUN BY THE MILITARY.
OUR FATHER, ADROC THURSTON,
THE MAN SAID TO HAVE SAVED
THE WORLD FROM DESTRUCTION,
MET OUR MOM AND FELL IN LOVE
WITH HER IN THIS CITY.
AND WHAT EXACTLY
ARE WE DOING HERE? WELL...
ARE YOU READY, MR. MATTHIEU?
PLEASE DON'T DROP IT!
- LEAVE IT TO ME!
IT MAY NOT LOOK IT,
BUT MY HAND-EYE
COORDINATION IS...
( grunts )
( gasps )
HMM? YECH!
WHAT IS THIS RANK STENCH?
- MR. MATTHIEU,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHAT AM I DOING?
YOU WANNA EXPLAIN
TO ME WHAT THIS THING IS?
- OH, COME ON! DON'T TELL ME
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ONE!
I MEAN, EVERYONE KNOWS
THAT'S CALLED A PUNCHA NUT!
- OH, YEAH? WELL, DO ALL
PUNCHA NUTS SMELL LIKE THIS?
- NEVER MIND THAT!
JUST MAKE SURE
YOU CATCH IT THIS TIME, OKAY?
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD...
EVEN ONE OF THESE THINGS
CAN GET US ALL IN TROUBLE.
( screams )
- Man: FREEZE!
FACE DOWN ON THE GROUND AND
SPREAD OUT YOUR ARMS AND LEGS!
I SAID, FACE DOWN ON
THE GROUND AND SPREAD OUT
YOUR ARMS AND LEGS, YOU THIEVES!
- WAIT! HOLD ON A MINUTE, UNCLE!
I-IT'S ME, YOUR NEPHEW,
RENTON THURSTON.
- YOU'RE RENTON?
YOU'RE REALLY RENTON THURSTON?
- WHAT?
- ( birds chirping )
- HMM.
- Renton: ( voice over )
THE REASON WE'RE HERE IS BECAUSE
HE ALL OF A SUDDEN BECAME
ALL CONSCIOUS OF HIS HEALTH
AFTER HIS CLOSE ENCOUNTER
WITH THE CORALIAN.
- I STARTED TO FEEL IT
WHEN I GOT FACE TO FACE
WITH THE CORALIAN.
NATURE IS SO AWESOME!
AND SINCE ALL OF US WERE BORN
FROM THAT NATURE,
I'VE DECIDED
I'M GONNA RESPECT IT!
- Renton: I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT KIND OF AGREEMENT
WAS REACHED BETWEEN THOSE TWO,
BUT WHATEVER IT WAS,
IT IGNITED A MAJOR
HEALTH-CONSCIOUSNESS FAD
WITHIN THE GEKKOSTATE.
THE FAD QUICKLY SPREAD
THROUGHOUT THE SHIP,
AND THE JUNK FOOD,
WHICH WE NEVER HAD
AN AMPLE SUPPLY OF
TO BEGIN WITH,
COMPLETELY DISAPPEARED
FROM THE GROCERY AREA.
INSTEAD THERE WERE FRESH FOODS,
SUPPOSEDLY SHIPPED STRAIGHT
FROM WHERE THEY WERE GROWING.
GOD ONLY KNOWS
WHERE THEY ACTUALLY CAME FROM
BUT OUR EATING HABITS IMPROVED.
- All: HMM.
- AFTER ALL,
WE'RE NOT DONE UNTIL
WE EAT ONE OF THESE, RIGHT?
- Renton: WELL, FROM THAT POINT,
THERE WAS ABSOLUTELY
NO REASON FOR THEM
NOT TO SHOW AN INTEREST
IN THE PUNCHA NUT,
WHICH IS SAID TO BE
ONE OF THE THREE
HEALTHIEST FOODS
TO EAT ON THE PLANET.
- HEY, MAMA?
- YES?
- MAMA, YOU WANT TO TRY
THE PUNCHA NUT TOO, RIGHT?
- Renton: EUREKA STILL SEEMED TO
NOT BE FEELING WELL, BUT...
- MM, I GUESS.
- Renton: SINCE I HADN'T BEEN
ABLE TO TALK TO HER MUCH LATELY,
I WANTED TO GET HER ATTENTION.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I ATE A LOT OF PUNCHA NUTS
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE KID.
( sighs )
- HEY, RENTON.
- HUH?
- I WANT YOU TO TELL ME
ALL OF THE DETAILS.
- MY UNNECESSARY COMMENT JUST
POURED GAS ONTO THE FLAME.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT KIND OF PLACE
CONTRORADO IS SINCE
THAT'S WHERE THE NUTS ARE?
LOOK, WE DIDN'T HAVE THAT
MUCH MONEY TO BEGIN WITH
AND YET WE STILL
WENT OUT AND BOUGHT
ALL SORTS OF REALLY
EXPENSIVE FRESH FOOD
SO OUR WALLET IS TOTALLY EMPTY.
BESIDES THAT...
- HOLLAND WAS PRETTY MUCH
AGAINST THE IDEA AT FIRST,
BUT HIS ATTITUDE CHANGED
RIGHT AWAY WHEN I TOLD HIM
THAT IT WAS THE PLACE
WHERE MY SISTER AND I
SPENT OUR CHILDHOOD DAYS.
- JUST BE BACK BEFORE 3:00.
- ALL RIGHT!
- Renton: AND SO, WE GOT IT,
THE SPECIAL EXCEPTION
FROM HOLLAND.
WE GOT PERMISSION TO HEAD OUT.
AND THAT'S WHEN UNEXPECTED
THINGS STARTED TO HAPPEN.
- Eureka: RENTON.
- HUH?
- I WANNA GO WITH YOU.
- BUT, EUREKA, I THOUGHT THAT
YOU WEREN'T FEELING WELL.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
RENTON, I WANT TO GET IN
THE NIRVASH RIGHT NOW!
- Renton: ( voice over ) I WAS
CONVINCED THAT SHE REALLY
WANTED TO GO BY THE VERY
SERIOUS LOOK IN HER EYES,
AND EVERYTHING
WAS GOOD AS WE TOOK OFF.
OF THE LITTLE
VALUABLE TIME WE HAD,
WE SPENT OVER AN HOUR AND A HALF
PERFORMING A TEST DRIVE
OF THE NIRVASH.
- COME ON. FOR PETE'S SAKE,
WE'RE IN A HURRY HERE,
YOU KNOW?
- OH, WHY?
- HEY, EUREKA.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT
HOW MUCH TIME WE HAVE LEFT.
LET'S GET DOWN AND DO IT AGAIN.
- HMM.
- HEY, RENTON.
COME ON, LET'S GO!
- Renton: ( voice over )
EVENTUALLY, WE ARRIVED
IN DOWNTOWN CONTRORADO.
BUT ON TOP OF THE FACT THAT
THINGS THERE ARE
EXPENSIVE TO BEGIN WITH,
THIS YEAR'S CROP OF PUNCHA
NUTS HASN'T BEEN VERY GOOD.
THE PRICE WAS
GOING THROUGH THE ROOF
AND EVEN WITH
EVERYONE'S DONATIONS
AND ALL THE MONEY
MR. MATTHIEU WAS CARRYING,
WE COULDN'T EVEN BUY ONE NUT.
I KINDA FELT BAD FOR EVERYONE.
- AND SO YOU CAME HERE
TO STEAL A NUT.
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
- SO HOW ARE YOUR TWO
ACCOMPLICES HERE RELATED TO YOU?
- THEY'RE FRIENDS, YOU KNOW,
CLASSMATES OF MINE
FROM MILITARY SCHOOL.
- WHAT?
- BOTH OF YOU!
IS WHAT HE SAID THE TRUTH?
- MM-HMM, MM-HMM.
- HMM.
( thumping )
- HUH?
- YOU! YOU BIG FOOL!
- ( Renton groaning )
- IF THEY ARE YOUR FRIENDS AND
CLASSMATES FROM MILITARY SCHOOL,
THEY'RE VALUABLE PEOPLE
YOU'LL ENTRUST YOUR DEAR,
LITTLE LIFE TO IN THE FUTURE!
AND WHAT DO YOU DO?
YOU MAKE THEM COME HERE
AND STEAL PRODUCE?
PLEASE FORGIVE HIM
FOR ALL THE RUDE THINGS
HE'S DONE.
HE IS STILL VERY YOUNG.
ALLOW ME TO INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I'M YUKATAN IGLACIAS,
AND I'M RENTON'S UNCLE.
NOW, PLEASE, STAND UP.
IF YOU ARE FRIENDS
OF MY NEPHEW, RENTON,
I CONSIDER YOU MY
FRIENDS AS WELL.
I KNOW THAT I HAVEN'T
GREETED YOU PROPERLY,
BUT PLEASE DO MAKE
YOURSELVES AT HOME.
HEY! SOMEONE GET
SOME SPIRITED DRINKS
AND FOOD OUT HERE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE!
- ( clock chimes loudly )
- ( all gasp )
- Renton: IT'S 3:00.
- Matthieu:
THIS ISN'T LOOKING GOOD.
- Yukatan:
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE SEEN HIM IN QUITE A WHILE,
YET THIS NEPHEW OF MINE ALWAYS
CAUSES SO MUCH TROUBLE FOR ME!
- OF COURSE! NOTHING LESS
SHOULD COME FROM
THE SON OF OUR HERO, ADROC!
- THAT'S RIGHT, HE HAS TO BE A
LITTLE BIT OUT OF THE ORDINARY!
( laughs )
- Man: I'M ENVIOUS.
IF YOU ASK ME,
MY GRANDCHILD'S WAY TOO QUIET.
I WISH HE'D CAUSE A LITTLE
MORE TROUBLE ONCE IN A WHILE.
( all laugh )
- I HAVE A QUESTION.
YOU MEANTIONED ADROC.
DID YOU MEAN THE ADROC THURSTON?
- OF COURSE. ARE THERE
ANY OTHER ADROC THURSTONS?
- WHAT? SO YOU'RE
ADROC THURSTON'S SON?
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- Man: WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
SOMEONE WHO WOULD ACTUALLY
HAVE TO ASK THAT AT THIS POINT?
- OH...
- WHAT IS IT?
- UH-HUH...
- YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH IT?
- IT'S NOT A BAD THING AT ALL,
BUT... WOW!
- OH, YOU'RE JUST PLAIN JEALOUS,
AREN'T YOU? I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL!
- OH, NO, I REALLY DIDN'T
MEAN IT THAT WAY.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, DRINK UP.
GO AHEAD. DON'T BE SHY.
- NO. NO, THANKS.
- AH, COME ON.
- ( sighs )
- ( Man 1 laughs )
TELL ME NOW, YOUNG ONE,
IS THIS LOVELY LADY OVER HERE
YOUR GIRLFRIEND
OR PERHAPS YOUR FIANCEE?
- ( gasps )
( stuttering )
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- BUT, UNCLE...
- I CAN'T GO INTO ANY DETAILS
JUST YET,
AS IT'S STILL TOO EARLY TO MAKE
THE OFFICIAL ANNOUNCEMENT,
BUT SHE'S THE DAUGHTER
OF A CERTAIN COMMANDER
OF THE TOWER STATE AND
HER MARRIAGE TO MY NEPHEW
HAS BEEN ARRANGED
BY THEIR PARENTS.
I HEARD SHE CURRENTLY ATTENDS
THE NORTH SHORE UNIVERSITY'S
GIRLS' MAGNET SCHOOL.
- HOLD ON A SECOND, UNCLE!
- ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- UH...
( groans ) YEAH.
- Man 1: OH, YOU GOT ME THERE.
WOW! NORTH SHORE UNIVERSITY!
- NORTH SHORE UNIVERSITY
IS THE ELITEST OF THE ELITE,
ALWAYS FIGHTING FOR THE POSITION
OF TOP SCHOOL IN THE FEDERATION.
I HEAR THAT IT'S ESPECIALLY HARD
FOR GIRLS TO BE ADMITTED.
- MR. YUKATAN, YOU MUST BE
ONE HAPPY PERSON!
- ( sobbing )
- IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- I APOLOGIZE.
I KNOW IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH ME,
BUT IT MAKES ME SO HAPPY.
ALL THE BEST, MY BOY.
- YEAH, THANKS.
- ♪ AND SO,
WE ALL HEAD OFF TOGETHER ♪
- Yukatan and friends:
♪ TO THAT LAND OF OLD ♪
♪ THROUGH THE VORTEX
OF THE TRAPARS ♪
♪ THE WILDERNESS OF THE SCUBS ♪
♪ PROTECT OUR CAPITAL ♪
♪ THE HAPPINESS OF ALL ♪
♪ SING AND REJOICE TOGETHER ♪
♪ FOLLOW, FOLLOW, EVERYONE ♪
♪ FOLLOW US
IN ADROC'S FOOTSTEPS ♪
♪ TO THE LANDS OF OLD ♪
- ( Matthieu moaning softly )
- EXCUSE ME.
- RENTON?
- HMM.
- THEY'RE LATE!
- ( birds chirping )
- ALTHOUGH THIS ISN'T
THE FIRST TIME THAT
MY UNCLE HAS
TALKED ABOUT STUFF
AND SLIPPED IN A COUPLE LIES
IN THE PROCESS,
IT STILL MAKES ME TIRED.
I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT MY DAD
WAS MY UNCLE'S PRIDE AND JOY,
BUT IT HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
OF COURSE, THERE'S NO WAY
THAT I CAN TELL ANY OF THEM
THAT I'M A MEMBER
OF THE GEKKOSTATE.
I WONDER IF SIS
WOULD GO THROUGH THIS
IF SHE WERE IN MY SHOES,
THINKING THAT WOULD HELP
MY UNCLE OUT IN THE PROCESS.
BUT, I...
WOW! THIS IS GREAT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT MY UNCLE
ACTUALLY KEPT THIS AROUND.
- ( door opens )
- EUREKA.
- WHAT IS THIS ROOM?
- THIS IS WHERE I USED TO SLEEP
WHEN I CAME TO VISIT
MY UNCLE WHEN I WAS YOUNG.
- I SEE.
- I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED EARLIER.
- EARLIER?
- YOU KNOW, HOW MY UNCLE
SAID SOMETHING ABOUT
YOU BEING MY FIANCEE
AND ALL THAT STUFF.
- YOUR FIANCEE?
- HUH?
- OH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
- I'M SORRY, I REALLY WASN'T
LISTENING TOO MUCH.
- OH.
- WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT ARE YOU HOLDING?
- OH, THIS THING? IT'S A TOY
THAT I USED TO PLAY WITH.
THIS IS HOW I'D PRETEND
TO BE RIDING THE WAVES
BACK WHEN I USED TO PLAY AROUND.
YOU KNOW, LIKE PRETEND
TO DO A CUTBACK DROP TURN.
YOU REMEMBER THE COMIC CALLED
"AT THE BEACH," DON'T YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- OH...
WELL, IT WASN'T A COMIC
THAT GIRLS WOULD
NORMALLY BE READING.
- HEY, RENTON, HOW LONG
ARE WE GOING TO STAY HERE?
- WHAT?
- WE REALLY HAVE TO GET BACK
TO THE GEKKO PRETTY SOON.
I MEAN, YOU PROMISED TO BE BACK
BY 3:00.
- YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
BUT CAN YOU PLEASE
JUST WAIT A LITTLE BIT LONGER
BEFORE WE GO BACK
TO THE GEKKO?
- UH, WHY?
- WELL, AS YOU CAN SEE, MY UNCLE
IS KIND OF A HARDHEAED GUY
AND IT'S HARD TO COME UP
WITH A PROPER TIMING
TO TELL HIM THINGS.
- THAT, AND WE STILL HAVEN'T
GOTTEN THE PUNCHA NUT
THAT WE PROMISED
TO BRING BACK WITH US.
- OH.
OKAY, I'LL GO TALK TO HIM
FOR YOU.
- NO! HOLD ON A SECOND!
WAIT, WAIT, I'LL TELL HIM!
I PROMISE! I PROMISE!
I'LL TELL HIM MYSELF.
- WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
( gasps )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- ( Matthieu moaning )
- MR. MATTHIEU!
WHO DID THIS TO YOU?
- Yukatan: THIS IS THE WAY
TO DO IT, RIGHT?
- HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UNCLE, WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
- I'M SURPRISED YOU WERE
ABLE TO INFILTRATE
THE ENEMY SYNDICATE
THIS WELL AS A SPY.
WELL DONE.
- WHAT?
- Old man: THAT'S ENOUGH
PRETENDING, YOUNG ONE.
I HEARD ALL ABOUT YOUR BRAVERY
FROM YOUR UNCLE HERE.
YOU FACED SUCH A TOUCH MISSION,
THOUGH IT WAS A
VERY SPECIAL ONE, I UNDERSTAND.
YOU HAVE MY RESPECT
AND GRATITUDE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
RENTON IS NOT A SPY AT ALL.
HE'S ONE OF US.
- EUREKA, WAIT...
- HE'S A FULLY-FLEDGED MEMBER
OF THE GEKKOSTATE.
- ( sighs )
- Old man: MR. YUKATAN,
WHAT'S THE MEANING OF THIS?
- THIS IS WHY I WAS AGAINST IT
FROM THE BEGINNING.
I DIDN'T WANT HIM TO BE JOINING
SUCH A DANGEROUS MISSION
JUST BECAUSE HE'S ADROC'S SON.
EVERYONE, IT LOOKS LIKE
MY YOUNG NEPHEW HERE
HAS BEEN BRAINWASHED
BY THE ENEMY.
- BRAINWASHED?
- Man: YEAH, I'VE HEARD OF THAT.
SOMETHING ABOUT THEM USING
NARCOTICS TO MAKE PEOPLE
LOSE THE ABILITY TO
TELL THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN GOOD AND EVIL.
- NOW, LISTEN
VERY CAREFULLY, RENTON.
YOUR FRIENDS HERE ARE FOOLING
YOU. BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOUR UNCLE WILL FIND YOU
A VERY GOOD DOCTOR.
I'M SURE HE'LL BE ABLE
TO GET YOU BACK TO NORMAL.
- THIS ISN'T RIGHT!
- HUH?
- SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT
ABOUT YOU, UNCLE! I'M NOT...
- ( door opens )
- HUH?
- WHO IS THE INFORMANT?
- I AM, SIR.
- HUH?
- ( exhales heavily )
- LOOKS LIKE THERE IS NO DOUBT
HERE. TAKE THEM AWAY!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR YOUR COOPERATION.
GOOD DAY!
- ( Renton trying
to say something )
- WE'LL TAKE THIS GIRL
WITH US AS WELL.
AFTER HER!
- ( screams )
- HOLD IT!
- ( all gasp )
- DAMN IT.
THIS IS A BUNCH OF CRAP!
I HAVEN'T BEEN BRAINWASHED
BY ANYBODY!
IT'S YOU, UNCLE,
AND ALL OF YOUR BUDDIES HERE
THAT HAVE BEEN BRAINWASHED!
I ALWAYS LOOKED UP
TO THE GEKKOSTATE
AND DECIDED TO
JOIN THEM ALL ON MY OWN!
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH MY
FATHER NOR YOU NOR MY SISTER!
- ( all gasp )
- I AM WHO I AM!
- I'M SURE SOMETHING
HAPPENED TO THEM!
HOLLAND, PLEASE,
LET ME GO OUT WITH THE 808!
- LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
IF THIS HAS ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THEM COMING BACK
REALLY LATE OR NOT,
BUT THE TRAPAR DENSITY
IS RISING AT AN ABNORMAL RATE.
- Girl: HOLLAND.
- ( retching )
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
OH, MAN,
WE'RE REALLY IN TROUBLE.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THIS.
- ( tires screeching )
- ( groans )
- Soldier: IT'S AN AMBUSH!
I SPOTTED ONE ENEMY LFO!
- Soldier 1: SQUAD, SWITCH OVER
TO HUMANOID MODE!
- IT'S THE NIRVASH?
- ( gunfire )
- WHO'S OPERATING IT?
- ( crash )
- ( groans )
( screaming)
- ( banging )
- ( gasps )
- AMAZING. IS THAT HOLLAND
IN THERE?
- CAN'T BE. NO. THAT'S...
IT'S RENTON.
IS THAT REALLY THE NIRVASH?
BUT THAT'S NOT LIKE THE NIRVASH
AT ALL.
- WHAT A GREAT FEELING!
- YEAH!
ANYWAY, IT WAS JUST AMAZING!
- Renton: OH, STOP THAT,
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME!
IT WAS JUST A REALLY GOOD WAVE
AND NOTHING MORE THAN THAT.
- DON'T BE SO HUMBLE.
YOU'RE STILL A KID!
YOU GET THE RIGHT TO BRAG!
- ( laughing )
WOULD YOU CUT IT OUT ALREADY?
- HEY, YOU TWO,
CAN I ASK SOMETHING?
WHERE'S THE PUNCHA NUT?
- ( chuckling ) OH, YEAH,
THAT THING? IT SMELLED AWFUL!
- IDIOT! NOBODY HERE GIVES
A DAMN WHAT YOU THINK OF IT.
AND BY THE WAY,
WHAT THE HELL TIME DO YOU
THINK IT IS RIGHT NOW ANYWAY?
- OH, HONEY, THERE'S A REAL GOOD
REASON WHY WE'RE LATE.
( hiccups )
- UGH!
YOU REEK OF BOOZE! COME WITH ME!
- OW! OW! STOP IT!
STOP IT, THAT HURTS! FEELS LIKE
YOU'RE RIPPING MY EAR OFF!
- UH...
- Holland: RENTON.
- HUH?
- MAKE SURE THAT YOU TAKE CARE
OF WHAT YOU STARTED.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OF COURSE I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT!
- Renton: ( voice over )
IN THE END,
MR. MATTHIEU TOOK ALL THE
BLAME BECAUSE THEY SAID THAT
HIS SUPERVISION
WAS WOEFULLY INADEQUATE.
AT THE SAME TIME, THE BIG
HEALTH FAD THAT HAD BEEN
GOING AROUND THE GEKKO
QUIETLY FADED AWAY.
SINCE THAT INCIDENT,
EUREKA ALWAYS STANDS
IN FRONT OF THE NIRVASH,
BUT NEVER EVEN TRIES
TO TOUCH IT ANYMORE.
NOT ONLY THAT, SHE SEEMS
TO BE AGAINST THE IDEA
OF ME APPROACHING THE NIRVASH
AND KEEPS PUSHING
ME BACK WITH A GLARE,
AS IF I WAS SOME STRANGER.
HONESTLY, THAT DEPRESSES ME,
AND IT PISSES ME OFF,
BUT ONLY A LITTLE.
I MEAN, EUREKA'S MAD BECAUSE
I MANIPULATED THE NIRVASH
WITHOUT HER CONSENT, RIGHT?
IT'S BECAUSE I WAS ABLE
TO CONTROL THE NIRVASH
BETTER THAN SHE
COULD. THAT'S WHY.
I ALWAYS WANT TO BE
AT EUREKA'S SIDE.
I WANT TO BE HER STRENGTH.
THAT THOUGHT CHANGED ONE BIT.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I WANT TO
STAY IN THE
PASSENGER'S SEAT FOREVER.
I HAVE A DREAM, TOO.
I HAVE THINGS THAT I WANT TO DO.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE
INTERFERING WITH THAT
AND I DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO SAY
ANTHING NEGATIVE ABOUT IT.
I AM WHO I AM.
I WANT TO PILOT THE NIRVASH
A LOT MORE.
I WANNA TEST MY POWERS
TO A MUCH, MUCH BIGGER EXTENT.
BECAUSE, RIGHT NOW, I FEEL LIKE
I CAN DO ANYTHING!
( reading on screen text )
TO BE CONTINUED!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE! ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE,
TAKE IT EASY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ TAKE MY CHANCE,
BELIEVE IN MYSELF ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
- Girl: THE BOY
CHOOSES THE GIRL,
THROWING AWAY HIS PAST
IN A NOSTALGIC LAND
WHERE HE SPENT
HIS CHILDHOOD DAYS.
THE NIRVASH
FLIES THROUGH HE SKY,
AND ANSWERS THAT RESOLVE.
NEXT EPISODE, "HUMAN BEHAVIOR."