- ( theme music playing )
- ( vocalizing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: HONEY, YOU'RE PLAYING
WITH STATS AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
- Man:
SORRY, IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
HOW MUCH MONEY DO
YOU THINK IT COSTS
FOR TREATMENT OF THE
DESPERATION DISEASE?
- BUT--
- IT'S SO THAT WE CAN CURE
HER ILLNESS.
TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
- I ALWAYS KNEW.
- ( both parents gasp )
- I KNEW ALL ALONG,
MOMMA AND POPPA,
THAT BOTH OF YOU WORRIED
ABOUT ME ALL THE TIME.
BUT, THE BUS IS ABOUT
TO ARRIVE.
- JESSICA!
- ( gasps )
LOOK OVER THERE!
- Parents:
HUH?  AAH!
- ( explosions )
- ARE THOSE SHOOTING STARS?
DEAR GOD!
- THANK YOU FOR THIS TIME.
- ( parents gasp )
BUT WE'LL BE TOGETHER
FOREVER NOW.
POPPA, MOMMA...
I LOVE YOU!
- WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT-- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
( giggling )
- A FALLEN DEBRIS
TARGETED THE TOWERS?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- NO IMPOSSIBILITIES
ABOUT IT.
I'LL SEND YOU
THE DATA RIGHT NOW.
TAKE A LOOK!
OF 157 TOWERS
LEFT STANDING,
31 WERE DESTROYED BY DIRECT
IMPACT OF THE DEBRIS.
- ( gasps )
- BUT THAT'S--
A THING LIKE THAT
CAN'T POSSIBLY HAPPEN.
- NO!  I THING THEY'RE RIGHT!
- ( both gasp )
- I COMPARED THE VALUES
WITH CALCULATIONS
FROM THE CENTRAL SYSTEM.
RIGHT WHEN THEY ENTERED
THE TRAPAR LAYER
ALL THE DEBRIS RADICALLY CHANGED
THEIR TRAJECTORY ANGLES.
IF DR. BEAR'S HYPOTHESES
ARE CORRECT,
THE SCUB CORALS
CAN SIGNIFICANTLY CHANGE
THE LAWS OF PHYSICS
BY FORCE OF WILL.
AND IF THAT'S THE CASE--
ARE YOU SAYING THAT ALL OF THIS
WAS CAUSED BY THE SCUB CORALS?
- I HAVE ONE MORE
BIT OF BAD NEWS.
- WHAT?
- A HOLE'S BEEN CREATED
IN THE TENSION MOUNTAINS.
- Woman: THIS IS FOOTAGE
OBTAINED BY HACKING
INTO THE MILITARY
OBSERVATION SATELLITE
"HUMMINGBIRD."
THE TENSION MOUNTAIN RANGE
HAS HAD A CAVE-IN
100 KILOMETERS IN DIAMETER.
WE FOUND A SPACE BENEATH
THE CAVE-IN
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO ANALYZE.
WE BELIEVE THAT THIS SPACE
HAS SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE MICROWAVE WEAPONRY
THAT IS CURRENTLY
RAINING DOWN AS DEBRIS.
- THERE YOU HAVE IT.
YOU WANNA TELL ME
WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON, HOLLAND?!
- DAMMIT!
DEWEY-- THIS IS PART
OF HIS PLAN.
HE TOOK OUT RENTON'S GROUP
ALONG WITH THE CENTRAL CORE
OF THE SCUB CORALS.
- Talho: THAT HASN'T BEEN
DETERMINED YET.
- ( both gasp )
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I'M NOT GIVING UP HOPE.
EVEN WITH A SITUATION
AS BAD AS THIS,
WE CAN'T JUST WALK AWAY!
CAN'T.
- YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
- ALL RIGHT, CONTACT THE CREW
ABOARD THE IZUMO.
TELL THEM TO GET READY!
ON MY ORDER WE WILL ATTEMPT
TO DIVE DIRECTLY
INTO THE TENSION MOUNTAINS.
- All: ROGER THAT!
- WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
NOW, MOMMA?
- WHAT HAPPENED
TO THOSE PEOPLE?
- THE WORLD IS COMING
TO AN END, ISN'T IT?
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE AT ALL.
DON'T WORRY, IT'S ALL
GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
- I COULDN'T DO ANYTHING.
- HUH?
- I-- I SAID THAT I WOULD
PROTECT THE CONTROL CLUSTER.
MY DAD!  AND MY SISTER!
( crying )
- RENTON, DON'T CRY.
- YEAH, PLEASE, DON'T CRY.
- YEAH, IF YOU CRY
EVERYONE WILL BE SAD.
- THANKS.
THANKS ALL OF YOU.
- ( sniffling )
- WHAT ABOUT YOU, EUREKA?
ARE-- ARE YOU HOLDING UP
ALL RIGHT PHYSICALLY?
- PHYSICALLY?
WELL, I--
- SO NOTHING'S WRONG
WITH YOU, EUREKA?
- MM-MM.
- WHAT ABOUT
THE NIRVASH?
IS THE NIRVASH
SAYING ANYTHING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
OH, RENTON,
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I CAN'T HEAR ANY
OF THEIR VOICES ANYMORE!
( crying )
- EUREKA!
- I CAN'T HEAR THEM!
I CAN'T HEAR ANYTHING!
NOT NIRVASH'S VOICE,
NOT ANYTHING!
- CALM DOWN, WE HAVE TO HOLD
OURSELVES TOGETHER RIGHT NOW.
- MOMMA, RENTON--
THE COMPAC DRIVE IS
DOING SOMETHING.
- ( gurgling sound )
- Eureka:
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- ( all screaming )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU, NIRVASH?
HEY, NIRVASH!
- Dewey: LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WE HAVE ARRIVED
AT THE FINAL PHASE
OF THE BATTLE
FOR THE SURVIVAL
OF ALL MANKIND.
I WOULD LIKE TO EXPRESS
MY GRATITUDE
FOR ALL OF YOUR
OUTSTANDING WORK
AND THE COURAGE
OF YOUR CONVICTIONS.
THANK YOU ALL.
NOW THE REAL BATTLE
IS JUST ABOUT TO BEGIN.
THOUGH WE HAVE SUCCEEDED IN THE
DESTRUCTION OF THE CENTRAL CORE
OF THE CORALIANS,
ENEMIES AGAINST MANKIND,
IT WAS MERELY THE DESTRUCTION
OF THEIR CONTROL HEADQUARTERS.
NOW THAT THEY HAVE LOST
ALL ORDER,
THEY WILL BEGIN TO ATTACK
INDISCRIMINATELY
ACROSS THE LAND.
HOWEVER, 1246 SECONDS--
THAT IS THE MAXIMUM TIME
THAT THE ANTIBODY CORALIANS
CAN REMAIN ALIVE.
NOW THE FLAGSHIP
OF THE GINGA FLEET
WILL INVADE DEEP
INTO THE CORALIAN LAND
TO CONFRONT OUR FATE.
YOU ALL MUST WITHSTAND
THE 1246 SECONDS
THAT WILL ENSUE.
THE FATE OF ALL MANKIND
RESTS ON YOUR SHOULDERS.
THAT IS ALL.
- DID YOU HEAR THAT?
- Holland: YEAH.
THOUGH IT WAS A VOICE
I DIDN'T WANNA HEAR.
- ( chuckling )
- BUT THIS PUTS EVERYTHING
INTO FOCUS.  THE FLAG SHIP
IS DIVING INTO THE GAP ALONE.
- YEAH.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING IN THERE
THEY REALLY DON'T WANT
OTHER PEOPLE TO SEE.
- IN OTHER WORDS... NIRVASH
IS STILL UP AND RUNNING!
- HUH?
- BUT WHAT CAN WE DO
ABOUT IT?
- IN FRONT OF US,
DIRECTLY IN OUR PATH,
13,000 SHIPS OF THE UNITED
FEDERATION FORCE ARE WAITING.
- YEAH, BUT WE CAN'T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT NOW.
SO WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO IMPROVISE.
TRY TO MAKE A MIRACLE.
- I SEE.
MIRACLE, HUH?
THAT'S A GOOD WORD.
AND I HAVE A FAVOR TO ASK,
ASIDE FROM THAT MIRACLE.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I WANT THE GEKKO TO DIVE
INTO THE HOLE ALL BY ITSELF.
- ( gasps )
DAMN YOU!
WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- THERE'S NOT A CHANCE
IN A MILLION WE'LL WIN THIS.
- WHAT?
- UNLESS WE STAY BEHIND
AND ACT AS YOUR SHIELD.
DON'T WORRY, THE FIREPOWER
OF THE SUPER IZUMO
IS FIVE TIMES
THAT OF THE GEKKO.
IT WILL TAKE A LOT
TO BRING HER DOWN.
SO... DOMINIC AND ANEMONE
ARE IN YOUR HANDS.
- JURGENS, I--
- THE TWO OF THEM
ARE OUR COMRADES.
IT'S ALWAYS A GOOD THING
TO CUT A PATH THROUGH DANGER
FOR OUR COMRADES.
- HA, YOU'RE JUST A SHOW-OFF.
IF YOU DIE OUT THERE,
I'LL KILL YOU.
- Renton: WE STOPPED.
BUT... WHY DID NIRVASH
STOP HERE?
- Eureka: HE'S CRYING.
HE'S... IN TEARS.
NIRVASH IS BEARING
EVERYONE'S PAIN.
AND THEIR WORDS OF PAIN
AND HE'S CRYING.
HE THOUGHT THAT HE'D BE ABLE
TO FULFILL THE MISSION.
BUT BECAUSE HE DIDN'T HAVE
ENOUGH POWER,
HE MADE EVERYONE DISAPPEAR.
AND THAT'S WHY HE HAS
TO TAKE THEIR PLACE.
WHAT A KIND CHILD.
- Renton: THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- RENTON?
- IT'S NOT BECAUSE
THE NIRVASH WAS POWERLESS.
IT'S FRUSTRATING,
BUT IT'S THE RESPONSIBILITY
OF ALL OF US.
AND SO, YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY
SAD THINGS LIKE THAT,
OKAY, NIRVASH?
- RENTON.
- MOMMA...
- WHAT IS IT?
- A MOUNTAIN IS FALLING DOWN
FROM THE SKY.
- ( gasps )
RENTON!
THE SKY!  LOOK AT IT!
- ( gasps )
WHAT IS THAT?
- Woman: CONFIRMED TypeZERO
AT THE EXPECTED LOCATION.
IT SEEMS TO HAVE SUFFERED
SOME DAMAGE,
BUT I BELIEVE THERE'LL BE
NO PROBLEMS
WITH CARRYING OUT YOUR PLAN.
- I'VE WAITED A LONG TIME
FOR THIS MOMENT.
SO, LET'S BEGIN.
- ( screaming )
- DOMINIC...
- THE COLONEL
IS A REAL BASTARD.
ANEMONE?
- ( alarm buzzing )
- EARLY WARNING ALARM
IS ACTIVATED!
ONE UNKNOWN SHIP
IS APPROACHING FAST
FROM DIRECTLY ABOVE US.
- THERE CAN'T BE.
- ANTI-AIR UNIT, DEPLOY!
- ( grunts )
WAIT!  ISN'T THAT... ?
THESE BASTARDS ARE--
- Eureka: RENTON!
LOOK!  THERE!
- HUH?
THAT'S... THE GEKKO!
- IT'S THE TB303 "DEVILFISH."
I SEE.
IT'S YOU, YET AGAIN!
HOLLAND!
- THE ANTIBODY CORALIANS
APPEARED AS IF THEY WERE
TIMING IT TO THE GINGA
PLUNGING INTO THE GROUND.
IT WAS A GOOD THING
WE WERE ABLE TO SEE
THE GEKKO OFF
IN THE CONFUSION.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- WELL, IT ALMOST SEEMS
TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.
I MEAN, THE ONLY REASON
WE'RE STANDING HERE ALIVE
LIKE THIS IS BECAUSE
THE ENTIRE ARMY
IS BUSY BATTLING
THE ANTIBODIES.
HOWEVER, IF THIS
SITUATION WAS
SOMETHING THAT HAD BEEN PLANNED
IN ADVANCE BY SOMEONE, THEN--
- Man: CAPTAIN!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- AN EMERGENCY CALL
FROM A CIVILIAN SHIP.
- IN A COMBAT SITUATION?
WHO IS IT?
- WAIT, THIS IS--
- THIS IS THE APECUMA,
A HIGH-SPEED SHIP
FROM THE TRESOR LABORATORIES.
I HAVE PRESSING INFORMATION
THAT NEEDS TO BE RELAYED
TO THE GEKKO.
I NEED TO KNOW WHERE
THE SHIP HAS GONE.
- I SEE.
SO THIS IS WHAT YOU GUYS
DECIDED?
- YEAH.
- Renton: BUT HOLLAND,
RIGHT NOW, UP ABOVE--
- DON'T WORRY.
WE HAVEN'T REACH
THE LIMIT OF QUESTIONS.
ARE YOU GUYS SURE ABOUT THIS?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE THE FIVE
OF US CAN DO IT.
- YEAH, AND BESIDES,
WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE
NIRVASH HERE ALL ALONE.
- JEEZ, IT'S SO SOON.
YOU ALREADY
HAVE A GOOD FAMILY.
DID YOU HEAR THAT, TALHO?
COVER ME!  I'M GOING IN
ON THE 303.
AND I'M GONNA
TAKE OVER THEIR BRIDGE!
- WAIT A MINUTE, HOLLAND.
DON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID!
- TALHO, PLEASE,
I'M THE ONLY ONE
THAT CAN STOP MY BROTHER
AND YOU KNOW IT.
- PREPARE TO LAUNCH
MAIN CANNONS.
- Man:
PREPARING MAIN CANNONS.
CORRECTING MARGIN OF ERROR
TO THREE DEGREES.
FIRE THEM ALL!
- A BARRIER?
- IT'S THE ARMY'S NEWEST
UNMANNED WEAPON.
- AS LONG AS THEY HAVE
THAT THING, RAISED ATTACKS
ARE PRETTY MUCH USELESS.
- SO IT'S JUST
AS HOLLAND SAID.
- GIVE UP, HOLLAND.
NOT MATTER HOW MUCH
YOU FIGHT BACK,
IT'S STILL TOO LATE.
BUT IF YOU NEED
TO HAVE A FINAL SCORE...
I WILL LET YOU HAVE IT!
- HUH!
YOU'RE GOING TO BECOME
THE CONTROL CLUSTER
WITH THE NIRVASH?
- SORRY, IT'S WHAT
WE ALL DECIDED.
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU GUYS THINKING?
- I SAW MY SISTER, HOLLAND.
IN THE CONTROL CLUSTER.
I SAW SIS, AND DAD TOO.
AND WHILE I WAS THERE,
I LEARNED
THAT AS LONG AS
THE CONTROL CLUSTER EXISTS,
THE SCUB CORALS
WILL NOT AWAKEN.
IF THE HUMANS WILL CEASE
THEIR ATTACKS,
THE SCUB CORALS
WON'T ATTACK EITHER.
WE'RE GONNA GO BACK
AND TALK TO THE SCUB CORALS
ONE MORE TIME.
WE HOPE TO GET ADVICE
ON FINDING A WAY
THAT EVERYONE CAN LIVE
ON THIS PLANET TOGETHER.
THERE IS THE CHANCE
THAT WE WON'T MAKE IT BACK
HERE EVER AGAIN.
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT.
INSIDE THE SCUB CORALS,
HUMANS CAN ACTUALLY EXIST.
BESIDES, IT'S NOT LIKE
ANY OF US ARE GONNA HAVE TO GO
THERE ALL ALONE.
- FORCING KIDS INTO
DECISIONS LIKE THAT,
AND EUREKA CHANGING HER SHAPE
INTO SOMETHING STRANGE...
IS THIS... WHAT ADULTS
SHOULD BE DOING?
( yelling )
DEWEY!
- ( alarm blaring )
- MULTIPLE LEVEL TWO ALERTS!
DAMAGES UNKNOWN.
- NO ANSWER
FROM THE CENTRAL COMPUTER.
- BRIDGE NUMBER THREE'S BEEN
DESTROYED AND IT'S ON FIRE.
- WE'RE UNABLE TO SHIFT
FLIGHT SYSTEMS.
- THAT WASN'T JUST A RANDOM
BLITZ HE PULLED OFF.
WOW!  THAT'S HIS TRAINING.
JUST WHAT YOU WOULD EXPECT
FROM COLONEL DEWEY'S
YOUNGER BROTHER.
- ( blaring continues )
- THE BATTLESHIP IS GETTING
FURTHER AWAY.
- Renton: IT'S HOLLAND.
HE'S HELPING US.
EUREKA!
- LET'S BEGIN.
- All: RIGHT.
NOW LET'S GO.
NIRVASH!
- THERE'S A SUDDEN INCREASE
IN TRAPAR LEVEL RESPONSES.
- WHAT?
- COULD IT BE THE typeZERO?
- CALM DOWN, EVERYONE.
ALL CREW, ABANDON SHIP.
- ( all gasping )
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
COLONEL, ARE YOU GOING
TO ABANDON US?
- NO, I'M NOT.
ALL RIGHT, PLEASE
LISTEN CAREFULLY
TO WHAT I'M GOING TO SAY.
- CONFIRM THE EJECTION
OF NUMEROUS ESCAPE PODS
FROM THE GINGA.
- THE GINGA HAS COMPLETELY
CEASED ALL ATTACKS.
- ANY CONTACT FROM HOLLAND?
- THE JAMMING IS SO BAD
I CAN'T FIND HIS SIGNAL.
- HOLLAND,
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE, RIGHT?
- EMPTY?
- ( shouting )
- IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
YOU'RE LOOKING QUITE WELL.
- HMM, I'M NOT READY TO LOSE
TO A BUNCH OF KIDS JUST YET.
- OLD MEN SHOULD KNOW
THEIR LIMITS!
- YOU MEAN THIS STUPID
SWORD IS FAKE TOO?!
- DO YOU EVEN KNOW OR CARE
WHAT THE HELL YOU'RE
DOING RIGHT NOW?!
- I AM JUST TRYING TO
PROTECT HUMAN DIGNITY!
- YOU'RE DESTROYING THE EARTH.
HOW CAN YOU TALK ABOUT
HUMAN DIGNITY?!
( gasps )
WHAT THE HELL?
WHERE IS HE?
- ( grunts )
- ( groans )
- I PHRASED THAT WRONG.
- WHAT?
- I AM TRYING TO ATONE
FOR OUR MANY SINS.
BY MY ATONEMENT, WE PROTECT
THE DIGNITY OF MANKIND,
AS WELL AS THE SOLEMN DIGNITY
OF THIS ENTIRE PLANET.
WHY CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
- THE MAN WHO CLIMBED
HIS WAY UP TO
THE HIGHEST OFFICE
IN THE ARMY...
ISN'T MEASURING UP AT ALL!
- 10,000 YEARS AGO,
THE PEACE OF THIS PLANET WAS
SHATTERED BY THE SCUB CORALS.
INDIVIDUAL BODIES WERE LOST
AND HUMAN DIGNITY WAS DESTROYED
PAST THE POINT OF NO RETURN.
WHAT REASON DOES THIS PLANET
HAVE TO LIVE ON
AFTER RECEIVING SUCH TREATMENT?
- HA!  IF YOU WANT TO
HURRY UP YOUR DEATH,
DO IT ALL BY YOURSELF!
- I'M SORRY, BUT I AM SOMEONE
WHO GETS RATHER LONELY.
- ( rumbling )
- ( gun cocks )
- ( Dewey screams )
- CONFIRM OUR STATUS.
- MISS TALHO!
- WHAT?
- WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY MESSAGE
FROM THE IZUMO.
- THE IZUMO?
- THIS IS JURGENS.
YOU MUST STOP
ATTACKING IMMEDIATELY.
- Talho: WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE JUST GAINED CONTROL
OF THEIR BRIDGE.
- WHAT?
THEN WHERE'S THE COLONEL?
COLONEL DEWEY IS--
- THIS WHOLE THING'S
JUST A BIG TRAP.
YOU CAN'T KILL DEWEY!
- DAMN.  TALHO REALLY
GETS RECKLESS SOMETIMES.
OH, MAN.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
SHE'S QUITE RECKLESS.
YOU SEE, I HAVE A SPECIAL
KARMA IMBEDDED WITHIN ME,
TO PURGE THIS RECKLESSLY
DISTORTED WORLD
AND PROTECT ITS DIGNITY.
OBSERVE...
MY KARMA!
- BROTHER!
YOU COULDN'T HAVE!
- BY DOING THIS,
I'VE BECOME ONE WITH THE WORLD.
AND WITH THIS SACRED PLANET,
MY LIFE IS THIS PLANET'S LIFE.
THE TWO OF US ARE ONE
AND THE SAME.
IF YOU WANT TO RESIST,
THEN GO AHEAD!
HOWEVER, I WILL DIE TOGETHER
WITH THE DIGNITY OF THE PLANET!
SO CRY ALL YOU WANT!
THIS IS THE BEGINNING
OF A BRAND-NEW EARTH.
- BROTHER, DON'T, NO!
- ( gunshot )
- COLONEL.
- NO!
- ( gasps )
ANEMONE!
HUH?
WHAT THE--?
- ( stammering )
DOMINIC...
( screams )
DOMINIC!
- HOLLAND, DON'T DO IT!
YOU CAN'T KILL HIM.
YOU CAN'T KILL
COLONEL DEWEY!
( gasps )
- IT WAS TOO LATE FOR ME
TO REALIZE IT.
I WASN'T ABLE TO SAVE
MY OWN BROTHER.
EVERYTHING I DID WAS
DONE TOO LATE.
- YES, EVERYTHING WAS
TOO LATE.
EVERY SINGLE THING WE DID
WE DID TOO LATE.
OH, HOLLAND.
- ( whirring )
- ( all scream )
- WHAT HAPPENED, NIRVASH?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- AH, MOMMA!  LOOK!
- ( gasps )
- ( groaning )
AAH!
- EUREKA!
- Kids:
MOMMA!
- NO!
BUT THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
I'M BEGGING YOU, NIRVASH!
YOU HAVE TO SAVE EVERYONE!
- EUREKA, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU?!  COME BACK!
- I'M SORRY.
( zapping )
I CAN'T--
I CAN'T KEEP MY PROMISE.
I'M SORRY, RENTON.
( weakly )
BYE-BYE.
( groaning )
- EUREKA!
EUREKA!
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator:
THE JOURNEY OF THE BOY
WHO JUMPED OUT OF
HIS HOMELAND A YEAR AGO
COMES TO AN END.
AT THE EDGE OF THE WORLD
THAT HE HAS REACHED,
WHAT DID THE BOY WIN
TO HIS HANDS?
NEXT EPISODE--
THE FINAL EPISODE--
"WISH UPON A STAR."