- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ I WANNA FLY AWAY ♪
♪ I CAN FLY AWAY ♪
- Dominic: THE WORLD HAS
STARTED TO CHANGE.
THE TECTONIC SHIFTS THAT
HAPPENED TOO FREQUENTLY.
THE FEDERATION COUNCIL,
ACTING TOO LATE.
THE PEOPLE MIRED
IN DISSATISFACTION,
AND THE RESULTING
RESTRUCTURING OF THE ARMY.
EVERYTHING IS MOVING ALONG
ACCORDING TO
THE COLONEL'S PLANS.
RENTON THURSTON.
HOW WILL YOU BE
INVOLVED IN ALL OF THIS?
YOU, THE SON OF THE HERO.
( gasping )
( sighs )
HUH?
- Dominic: BELL FOREST.
DESPITE BEING IN THE OUTLANDS,
IT CAN BE SAID THAT
THE REVOLUTION CURRENTLY
TAKING PLACE ON THE WORLD,
ALL STARTED HERE.
THE TYPE ZERO,
FOLLOWING THE PIVOTAL BATTLE
FOUGHT IN THIS TOWN,
MASSIVELY IMPROVED ITS SPECS.
NOT ONLY THAT, WHAT SHOULD BE
ESPECIALLY NOTED HERE
IS THE FACT THAT THE SEVEN SWELL
EFFECT HAS BEEN CONFIRMED
FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE THE SUMMER OF LOVE.
- ( girl chuckling )
- ( exclaims )
( groans )
- ( crying ) MAMA.
- Dominic: SO MUCH THAT HAPPENED
SEEMED COINCIDENTAL.
HOWEVER, THANKS TO THE FACT
THAT THE BOY WAS THE
SON OF ADROC THURSTON
EVERYTHING WAS STARTING TO SEEM
AS IF IT WAS MEANT TO HAPPEN.
Oh, hey, you guys!
- HUH?
DO YOU KNOW WHERE
I CAN GO AROUND HERE
TO GET MY BIKE FIXED UP?
- YOUR BIKE?
- Dominic: I MUST KNOW.
RENTON THURSTON...
WHAT MEANING DOES
THAT BOY CARRY?
WHAT WAS HE ENTRUSTED WITH?
AND TO KNOW THAT...
- Girl: OH, THERE HE IS.
- HUH?
- AXEL, YOU'VE GOT A CUSTOMER.
- Axel: DON'T CALL AN ELDER
BY HIS FIRST NAME.
GEEZ, CHILDREN NOWADAYS
HAVE NO MANNERS. HMM?
- Dominic: I HAD TO MEET HIM.
I JUST HAD TO
MEET THIS MAN.
AXEL THURSTON.
- Renton: I'm sorry.
ABOUT LEAVING WITHOUT
TELLING YOU.
I HADN'T APOLOGIZED
FOR THAT YET.
- YOU WERE STAYING
WITH RAY AND CHARLES
DURING THAT TIME, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- THE INSIDE OF RAY AND
CHARLES' SHIP WAS REAL CLEAN!
I MEAN IT WAS TOTALLY SPOTLESS.
- REALLY?
- I'D GET UP EARLY
IN THE MORNING
AND HELP CLEAN THE ENTIRE SHIP
FROM STEM TO STERN
UNTIL IT SHINED.
SHE SAID IT WASN'T HARD
IF YOU DID IT EVERY DAY,
'CAUSE THE DIRT
DOESN'T EVER BUILD UP.
WE DIDN'T SKIP EVEN ONE DAY.
- MMM.
- AND WHEN WE WERE
DONE CLEANING UP,
WE'D ALL WORK TOGETHER
TO MAKE BREAKFAST.
WE'D ALWAYS HAVE
FRESH FRUIT JUICE,
HOT BUTTERED BREAD,
A BIG TOSSED SALAD.
ALL OF IT GOOD AND FRESH
AND REALLY TASTY.
- MMM.
- THE TWO OF THEM
WERE BOTH REALLY CONSCIOUS
OF THEIR HEALTH AND STUFF.
WHY DO YOU THINK
THAT WAS, EUREKA?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- IT WAS SO
THE TWO OF THEM COULD
MAKE THEIR LIVES TOGETHER
LAST FOREVER.
ISN'T THAT AWESOME?
"OUR FAMILY IS MADE UP OF
JUST THE TWO OF US,
"SO IF ONE OF US WERE TO LIVE
AN UNHEALTHY LIFESTYLE THEN...
"THEN, SEVERAL DECADES,
"ONE OF US WILL BE BURDENED
WITH THE MISFORTUNE
OF LIVING OUT OUR LIFE ALONE."
"THAT'S WHY...
THAT'S WHY THE TWO
OF US, TOGETHER..."
DAMN IT!
WHY DID THE TWO OF THEM
HAVE TO DIE LIKE THAT?
WHY DID THEY HAVE TO
FACE SUCH TERRIBLE DEATHS?
IT'S SO CRAZY!
WHY DID THOSE TWO HAVE TO COME
HERE TO FIGHT AGAINST HOLLAND?
HOLLAND SAID HE DID IT
TO PROTECT ME.
BUT I DON'T GET IT.
WHY DID HE WANT TO
PROTECT ME IF IT MEANT
KILLING RAY AND CHARLES?
- Eureka: IT'S BECAUSE
I CHOSE YOU.
IT'S BECAUSE
I CHOSE YOU, RENTON,
INSTEAD OF CHOOSING HOLLAND.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY
HE WENT AS FAR AS HE DID
WHILE HE WAS
TRYING TO PROTECT YOU.
- EUREKA...
- OH, RENTON, I...
I...
- IF IT'S HARD FOR YOU
TO TALK NOW, THEN,
YOU CAN JUST TELL ME
ABOUT IT SOME OTHER TIME,
WHEN YOU'RE FEELING
MORE COMFORTABLE.
- RENTON...
- EUREKA, IF YOU
CHOSE ME LIKE YOU SAID,
LET'S ALWAYS STAY TOGETHER.
WE'LL PICK UP WHERE
RAY AND CHARLES LEFT OFF.
- YES.
- YOU SAY YOU'RE
RENTON'S FRIEND?
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
- OH, YEAH? WELL, WHERE DID
YOU MEET HIM THEN?
- HUH? OH, AT SALISA ORNE.
- I KNOW WHERE THAT IS.
TA-DA!
IT'S HERE, RIGHT?
- ( chuckles )
YOU SURE KNOW A LOT.
- Girl 1: IT'S MY FAVORITE MAG.
- SO, TELL ME,
HOW IS RENTON DOING?
- Girl 2: OH, I HAVE A QUESTION.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU'RE A MEMBER
OF GEKKOSTATE, MR. DOMINIC?
- Girl 3: WHAT?
OF COURSE HE'S NOT.
LOOK AT WHAT HE'S WEARING.
IT'S ALL WRONG.
- ( chuckling nervously )
- THIS QUESTION HAS BEEN
NAGGING ME FOR A WHILE.
WHAT'S THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN RENTON AND TALHO?
- WELL, I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
- Girl 3: OH, IT'S BEEN
ON YOUR MIND?
- Girl 1: WHAT OF IT?
- YOU ALWAYS SAID
THAT YOU THOUGHT
RENTON WAS REALLY GROSS.
- THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID!
I WAS JUST SAYING THAT TALHO
MUST BE TROUBLED BY HIM.
- Axel: BE QUIET!
- ( all gasping )
- ENOUGH OF THIS.
I CAN'T GET A WORD IN AS WAS.
- Girls: Okay.
OH, I SEE,
SO RENTON SENT YOU HERE?
- YES. HE SAID IF I CAME
TO BELL FOREST,
I SHOULD STOP IN HERE AND SEE
IF YOU'RE DOING
ALL RIGHT, MR. THURSTON.
- ( laughs ) THAT KID...
- Girl: GOOD FOR YOU, AXEL.
I'M SURE THAT RENTON WAS
REALLY WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( grunts ) GIRLS TALKING
AS IF THEY KNEW IT ALL.
- YOUR NAME IS DOMINIC?
- YES!
- YOU SAID THAT YOU TRAVEL
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
WHERE ARE YOU HEADED NEXT?
- WELL, SIR, I REALLY
HAVEN'T DECIDED YET.
- WILL YOU CHOSE A HOT PLACE
OR PERHAPS A COLD PLACE INSTEAD?
- UH, I SUPPOSE IF I HAD TO
CHOSE A PLACE RIGHT NOW,
I'D CHOSE HOT.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
I'LL GET TO THE
REPAIRS RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
HELPING ME, RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'D BE HONORED.
- ( yawning )
( gasps )
WHAT? WOW!
( exclaims )
( screaming )
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHAT? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I'M CLEANING. CAN'T YOU TELL?
- ( exclaims ) GONZY!
I JUST FINISHED MOPPING UP
THAT PART OF THE FLOOR.
- WOW, THIS LOOKS
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT NOW.
- MAKES ME FEEL UNEASY.
- YOU KNOW, WE'VE HAD QUITE
A FEW SMOKY AFFAIRS RECENTLY,
SO THIS FEELS REFRESHING.
- Hap: IN ANY CASE, WHAT GOT
ALL THIS CLEANING STARTED?
- WELL, RENTON AND EUREKA
STARTED CLEANING FIRST.
- WHAT?
- WHY DID THEY DO THAT?
- WHO KNOWS?
- HUH?
- Hilda: I GUESS
I'LL HELP OUT, TOO.
- OH, COME ON.
- THE WAY THINGS ARE GOING,
EVEN IF WE CALLED ALL HANDS,
THEY WOULDN'T GATHER.
AND STONER'S PHOTO DEVELOPMENT
IS GOING TO TAKE A WHILE, TOO.
LET'S GO, MATTHIEU.
- ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU LATER.
- ( sighs )
- TORQUE WRENCH.
- HUH?
OH, UH...
HMM...
- Axel: WHAT'S WITH YOU?
THE TORQUE WRENCH!
- AS IF I KNEW.
- HMM?
- OH, NO, NOTHING AT ALL,
REALLY.
- ( gasping )
- THIS IS FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
IF YOU RIDE BIKES,
YOU SHOULD KNOW THIS.
- YES, SIR.
- LOOKS LIKE THINGS
AREN'T GOING SMOOTHLY.
- WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
I DON'T THINK IT SHOULD BE
TOO TOUGH A REPAIR.
- ( laughs ) NO, I MEAN
ABOUT THE OLD MAN.
- OH.
- YOU SEE, WHEN THEY START
FIDDLING WITH MACHINES,
THEY DON'T STOP UNTIL
VERY BIT OF IT IS FIXED.
ALL THREE GENERATIONS OF 'EM,
THEY'RE ALL THE SAME.
- "THREE GENERATIONS OF THEM"?
DOES THAT INCLUDE
ADROC THURSTON?
- OH, YEAH. OF COURSE, IT DOES.
- HEY, COME ON GIRLS, WAKE UP.
IT'S TIME TO GO HOME.
YOUR MOMMAS HAVE YOUR
SUPPERS WAITING FOR YOU.
( laughs )
- ABOUT WHAT YOU JUST SAID...
- WHAT ABOUT IT?
- THE THREE GENERATIONS
BEING THE SAME?
- YEAH.
- SOUNDS LIKE AN
INTERESTING STORY.
I WOULD LIKE TO HEAR
MORE DETAILS ABOUT IT.
- ( metal clanking )
- UH. HUH?
- HEY, WHERE YOU
HEADED, OLD MAN?
- I NEED A GYRO.
I'M GONNA HEAD OVER TO
SCRAP METAL OZZY'S.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I HEARD A BLIZZARD
IS ABOUT TO HIT US HERE.
- Girls: HUH?
- UH, I'LL GO TOO.
- WELL, OF COURSE YOU'RE GONNA
GO. IT'S ALL FOR YOU, ANYWAY.
- ( grunts )
- ( beeping )
- ( door opening )
- Woman: HOW LONG ARE YOU
PLANNING TO DO THAT?
IF YOU DON'T GET
A LITTLE REST SOON,
YOU'RE GONNA END UP WITH
AN IV TUBE STUCK IN YOU, TOO.
- DID THE SCOUTING ALL GET DONE?
- YEAH. I'LL WRITE YOU A REPORT.
- HOLLAND WAS...
HOLLAND WAS CONFRONTING
HIS PAIN, TOO.
- I'LL JUST LEAVE
YOUR MEAL RIGHT HERE.
EAT UP WHILE IT'S WARM.
RENTON AND EUREKA
WORKED TOGETHER TO MAKE IT,
AND IT'S REALLY TASTY.
- ( door closing )
- I'LL CARRY A BIT
OF IT FOR YOU.
YOUR TROUBLES, I MEAN.
- ( all exclaiming contentedly )
- OH, WOW!
- I'M IMPRESSED. THIS FOOD
SURE IS SOMETHING ELSE.
- YEAH. IT'S YUMMY, MAMA.
- YAY!
- HEY, EUREKA, DID YOU MAKE
ALL OF THIS BY YOURSELF?
- MMM-MMM.
Renton AND I MADE IT TOGETHER.
- ( chuckling )
I'M SORRY I DID THIS
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
I THOUGHT THAT AS LONG AS
I'M ON BOARD THIS SHIP,
WAITING TO TALK TO HOLLAND,
I'D TRY TO MAKE GOOD
USE OF MYSELF.
- COME ON, RENTON.
DON'T BE SAYING DEPRESSING
STUFF LIKE THAT.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'VE DETERMINED
TO DO WITH YOUR LIFE,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA
GET IN YOUR WAY.
IN FACT, I...
I'D LIKE TO CHEER YOU ON
BECAUSE YOU'RE ONE OF
OUR DEAR FRIENDS.
- THANK YOU, HAP.
- RENTON.
- YES?
- WE DIDN'T CREATE GEKKOSTATE
IN ORDER TO PRETEND
WE'RE SOME SORT OF AN
EXTENDED FAMILY. YOU UNDERSTAND?
- HEY, TALHO, THERE'S NO REASON
FOR YOU TO PUT IT THAT WAY.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST
SHUT UP, HAP?
- YES, I KNOW.
I THINK THE REASON THIS SHIP
EXISTS IS IN ORDER TO GO A WAR.
- HMM?
- BY ANY CHANCE, DO YOU HAPPEN
TO KNOW WHY WE'RE AT WAR?
- NO, I DON'T.
- SO YOU CAN FIGHT WITHOUT
KNOWING THE REASON WHY?
- I CAN'T FIGHT AT ALL.
AND I DON'T HAVE
THE WILL TO FIGHT, EITHER.
- REALLY? EVEN IF
THIS WAR WAS STARTED
BY THAT FAMOUS FATHER OF YOURS.
ADROC THURSTON WHO
SAVED THE WORLD?
- ( gasping )
- ADROC WAS WORKING AS
A TECHNICIAN FOR THE ARMY
WHEN ONE DAY HE MADE
THE SHOCKING ASSERTION
THAT THIS LAND, SCUB CORAL,
WAS ACTUALLY A CORALIAN,
A SENTIENT BEING.
HE TRIED TO PROVE
HIS ASSERTIONS,
BUT IN THE PROCESS OF THE
INVESTIGATION AT THE GREAT WALL,
ADVERSE AFFECTS ON HUMANS
BELIEVED TO BE FROM SCUB CORAL
EXPANDED AMONG THE RESEARCHERS
AND ARMY ASSOCIATES.
THE ARMY OFFICIALS
HEARING OF THIS,
DECIDED TO GET
RID OF THE CORALIAN,
AND ADROC IN THE END
WAS AGAINST IT.
HE WAS CONVINCED,
HE WAS ABSOLUTELY CONVINCED,
THAT THE CORALIAN WAS
AN INTELLIGENT LIFE FORM.
THAT WAS WHY HE HAD SEARCHED
FOR A WAY TO COEXIST.
HIS CONVICTION WAS CEMENTED
BY THE EMERGENCE
OF A HUMAN SHAPED CORALIAN.
THE NAME OF THE HUMANOID
CORALIAN IS EUREKA.
- ( gasping )
- SHE'S PART OF THE CORALIAN?
YOU MEAN THE CORALIAN?
- I HAD MY HUNCHES, BUT...
- BUT, WAIT. HOLD ON
A SECOND HERE. WHAT?
- Talho: I'M NOT DONE
WITH THE STORY YET.
NOW, HAP, TELL THEM
WHAT WE FOUND OUT
WHEN WE STARTED TAPPING
THE COMMUNICATION LINE.
- UH...
THE DETAILS ARE STILL UNCERTAIN,
BUT APPARENTLY THE STATE ARMY
HAS RECONSTITUTED AN
ANTI-CORALIAN SQUADRON.
ITS NAME, SIZE AND EVERYTHING
ABOUT IT IS A MYSTERY.
HOWEVER, AS PROOF THAT
THE SQUAD HAS REFORMED,
THEY'RE CURRENTLY DEVELOPING
A WEAPON CAPABLE OF
ATTACKING DEEP
BENEATH THE GROUND.
- THIS IS PROOF OF THAT.
- ( gasping )
- THERE'S ONLY ONE REASON THAT
HOLLAND CREATED GEKKOSTATE.
TO FOLLOW ADROC'S WILL
AND PROTECT EUREKA,
THE ONLY BEING ALIVE THAT
CAN ACCESS THE CORALIAN.
HOWEVER, THAT MEANT
FROM THEN ON
THE ENTIRE WORLD
BECAME HIS ENEMY.
CAN YOU BE RESIGNED
TO ACCEPT THAT FATE?
- YES, I CAN.
- ( sighs )
LET'S HEAD TO TRESOIR.
- TRESOIR? YOU KNOW, THAT PLACE
IS ONE OF THE ARMY'S...
- THE GUYS WHO WORK THERE
ARE THE ONLY ONES
THAT ARE CAPABLE OF
REPAIRING THE NIRVASH NOW.
- BUT...
- HOLLAND WOULD HAVE
DONE THIS TOO.
- ( sighs )
- EXCUSE ME.
RENTON, I'D LIKE TO HAVE
SOME MORE OF THIS LATER ON.
SO, CAN YOU SAVE ME SOME?
- OH, SOME FOR ME, TOO!
- I'D LIKE SOME MYSELF.
- ( grunts ) AH, GEEZ!
MATTHIEU, YOU AND STONER
TAKE THE 606.
HILDA, YOU FOLLOW
CLOSE BY IN 808.
- All: ROGER.
- Hap: GIDGET, CONTACT
TRESOIR ON CODE CURE.
- ROGER THAT.
- NOW, YOU GUYS
SHOULD COME WITH ME.
WE'LL EAT OVER THERE.
- BUT WHY?
WE'RE FINE HERE.
- COME ON, LET'S JUST GO.
- HEY, MISCHA,
IS MAMA'S NAME CORALIAN?
- UH...
- I DIDN'T ASK HER TO DO THAT.
- HUH?
- I KNEW I HAD TO
TELL YOU MYSELF.
BUT WHEN I THOUGHT THAT
YOU MIGHT HATE ME FOR IT,
RENTON, I...
( sobbing )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
MUCH OF IT.
I MEAN, WHENEVER
I TOUCH YOU LIKE THIS,
IT'S OBVIOUS TO ME
HOW SPECIAL YOU ARE.
- RENTON...
- FROM THE VERY BEGINNING,
YOU'VE BEEN DIFFERENT
FROM EVERYONE ELSE
I'VE EVER MET.
OH, EUREKA,
YOU ARE UNIQUELY YOU.
- ( Axel grunting )
BOY, IT'S ALREADY THIS LATE?
- ARE YOU ALL DONE?
- ( exclaiming )
- ( engine revving )
- SOMEHOW I THINK THE
GLIMMER OF THE COMPAC DRIVE
HAS INCREASED A BIT.
- THIS OLD BOY IS REALLY HAPPY
ABOUT IT. THAT'S FOR SURE.
- DOMINIC.
- YES?
- DO ME A FAVOR.
PLEASE KEEP BEING A GOOD FRIEND
TO RENTON FROM NOW ON.
THAT BOY'S FATHER WAS TOUTED
AS THE GREAT HERO OF THE WORLD.
BUT I SAY THAT IT WAS
NOTHING MORE THAN
A DESPERATE FABRICATION
OF THE STATE ARMY.
PLEASE, JUST ALWAYS
TRY TO SEE RENTON
FOR WHO HE REALLY IS.
FROM THE FIRST TIME I SAW YOU,
I HAD A FEELING
THAT YOU WERE LIKE ME.
I WANT YOU TO FEEL FREE
TO DROP BY WHENEVER YOU LIKE.
AND IF IT'S FOR
REPAIRING YOUR BIKE,
THIS OLD MAN WILL BE
MORE THAN HAPPY
TO DO IT FOR YOU ANY TIME.
- HUH?
THANK YOU. THANK YOU SO MUCH.
DAMN IT! DAMN IT!
WHAT THE HECK AM I DOING?
I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T GIVE A REPORT
OF THIS TO THE COLONEL.
( exclaims )
DAMN IT, OLD GEEZER.
WHO TOLD YOU TO DO SUCH
A PEAKY TUNE-UP OF MY BIKE?
- REPORT THAT SPEC OPS
CAPTAIN DOMINIC
IS LEAVING BELL FOREST.
- HOW ARE THE CONDITIONS?
- THEY'RE GOOD.
SEND THEM OUT ANY TIME.
- WOZ?
- ALL GOOD HERE.
- JOBS?
- EVERYTHING IS A GO HERE.
- Hap: GIDGET, WHAT ABOUT LFOS?
- COMMUNICATIONS FOR BOTH
THE 606 AND THE 808,
INDICATE THERE ARE NO
ENEMY SHIPS IN OUR AREA.
- Hap: PREPARE TO IGNITE
BOOSTERS. COMMENCE COUNTDOWN.
- COUNTDOWN COMMENCING.
- OH, LOOK, HOLLAND WOKE UP.
- MISCHA!
- FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
- IGNITION.
- TO BE CONTINUED
- TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WHY SO WHY ♪
♪ JUST YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ JUST A CHILD ♪
♪ ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ WHY SO WHY ♪
♪ JUST YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ SO I SAY ♪
- Narrator: THE GEKKO HEADS
TO THE MILITARY LABORATORY,
IN ORDER TO HEAL
ITS BATTLE SCARS.
THEY SHOW NEW
EXPRESSIONS ON THEIR FACES,
ONCE THEY STOP
FEARING CHANGE.
NEXT EPISODE,
"CHANGE OF LIFE."