- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THIS IS DEWEY NOVAK
THE CHIEF COMMANDER
OF THE UNITED
FEDERATION FORCE.
PLEASE STAY CALM
AS YOU LISTEN
TO MY FOLLOWING ANNOUNCEMENT.
WE WILL NOW ATTEMPT TO REBEL
AGAINST THE SCUB CORALS.
- ( angry shouting )
- THE SURVIVAL
OF THE HUMAN RACE
DEPENDS UPON THE OUTCOME.
I AM CERTAIN THIS OPERATION
WILL BE A SUCCESS.
SOON THE CONTROL OF EARTH
WILL BE IN HUMAN HANDS.
- ( beeps )
- ORATORIO NUMBER EIGHT.
FIRE!
- Anemone: WELL, YOU KNOW,
A LOT OF DIFFERENT THINGS
HAPPEN IN LIFE. ANY REGRETS?
OF COURSE IF I SAID
THAT I DIDN'T HAVE ANY,
IT WOULD BE A LIE.
I'M STILL VERY,
VERY YOUNG.
I WANT TO GO OUT SHOPPING,
AND EAT A LOT MORE
OF DIFFERENT
YUMMY FOODS OUT THERE,
AND LISTEN TO MUSIC
AND STUFF, YOU KNOW?
OH YES, AND OF COURSE
EVEN A WONDERFUL ROMANCE--
IF I COULD HAVE THAT,
IT WOULD REALLY
BE THE BEST.
REALLY THE BEST.
BUT THE WAY
I FEEL RIGHT NOW,
"OH BROTHER"
IS ALL I CAN SAY.
- ( alarm buzzes )
- Anemone: REALLY, OH BROTHER.
- Man: A GIANT HOLE
IN THE GROUND?!
- I INTERCEPTED A REPORT
FROM THE GINGA.
APPARENTLY,
THE EARLIER ENERGY WAVE
PENETRATED DEEP
INTO THE SCUB LAND.
I'LL LINK YOU TO IT.
- TheEND IS MOVING.
IT APPEARS SHE'S GOING
INTO THE SCUB'S OPENING.
- SHE'S WHAT?
- Anemone: SOMEONE ON MY MIND?
I HAD SOMEONE.
YEAH, PAST TENSE.
I THINK ABOUT HOW
I SHOULD HAVE TOLD HIM
HOW I FELT.
I KIND OF HATE MYSELF
A BIT FOR THAT.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT IT NOW.
THE NEXT TIME
I'M BORN INTO THIS WORLD--
IF THAT'S EVEN POSSIBLE,--
I'D LIKE TO BE BORN
AS SOMEONE WHO'S MORE CLEVER
THAN I AM NOW.
WELL, I REALLY CAN'T
DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
I FEEL THIS SELF-HATRED.
- I'M TAKING THE 303!
- BUT HOLLAND!
- I CAN'T LET TheEND
GET IN THE WAY
OF WHAT RENTON AND EUREKA
HAVE TO DO.
- HEY, GUYS,
THE OPENING LOOKS LIKE
IT'S STARTING
TO REPAIR ITSELF.
- TALHO, HURRY UP!
- COMMENCING FINAL
ENTRY SEQUENCE.
DOGGIE, TAKE US DOWN JUST
A FEW METERS OFF THE GROUND.
- YOU MEAN AT THIS SPEED?!
- IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO KEEP US FROM
GETTING CAUGHT
BY THE MILITARY'S
OPTICAL ENEMY-SPOTTING SYSTEM.
- HMM.  CAN YOU KEEP
UP WITH ME, SLOWPOKE?
- JUST WATCH ME.
- WELL, I GUESS
I'LL BE GOING NOW.
- ( Gulliver warbles )
- ( grunts )
- ( trills )
- ( sighs )
WHAT?
- ( trills )
- HMM, I SEE.
( chuckles )
WE'LL GO TOGETHER.
- Holland: TALHO, RIGHT AFTER
THE LAUNCH OF THE 303,
THE GEKKO NEEDS TO ESCAPE
THE BATTLEFIELD
BY A POWER TRAJECTORY FLIGHT,
ALONG WITH THE IZUMO.
- HOLLAND, PLEASE.
- APOLOGIZE TO DOMINIC.
BUT I CAN'T LET ANYONE
GET IN THE WAY
OF RENTON AND EUREKA.
- RIGHT NOW, THE SCUB'S OPENING
IS MEASURING TEN.
SEVEN MINUTES
UNTIL IT CLOSES!
HURRY, HOLLAND!
- COMMENCING MY RUN!
- OPTICAL SENSORS
HAVE SOMETHING.
THE TARGET APPEARS
TO BE THE GEKKO
ALONG WITH ONE UNKNOWN SHIP.
- HMM.
- INTERFERENCE WAVES SPOTTED.
THE GINGA FLEET
HAS CAUGHT UP TO US.
- HMM.
- CAPTAIN.
I SHOW A BREACH ALERT
ON THE PORT-LAUNCH DOOR.
- WHAT?!
- Dominic: I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
- Jurgens: DOMINIC!
- DON'T WORRY,
I'LL STOP TheEND.
I'LL JUST CONVINCE THE PILOT
TO STAND DOWN.
- HEY, CALM DOWN. THIS IS
NO TIME FOR PERSONAL INTERESTS.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH
PERSONAL INTERESTS?!
- ( gasps )
- LOOK, I DON'T CARE
IF YOU CALL ME A SNOB
FOR THIS,
BUT I WANT TO DO IT.
I WANT TO BE THE ONE
TO STOP THE ONE I LOVE.
SO PLEASE, LET ME GO!
- THE OPENING IS CLOSING FAST.
- OH NO, KLFs ARE COMING IN
FROM THE GINGA FLEET.
HOLLAND!
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL KEEP
THE KLFs AT BAY!
DOMINIC, GO!
( screams )
- 15 SECONDS LEFT!
- AH!
- ( metal clanging )
( clanging )
- ( alarm buzzes )
- WE--
WE'VE LOST THE SIGNAL
FROM THE HIGH-SPEED SHIP.
- NO!
- WE'VE LOST COMMUNICATION
WITH THE LIEUTENANT.
- AFTER CONFIRMING
THE GEKKO'S RECOVERY
OF THE 303,
IGNITE THE BOOSTERS.
WE'RE LEAVING
THE FRONT LINE.
- CAPTAIN.
- DIDN'T YOU
HEAR MY ORDER?!
- THE GEKKO AS WELL
AS AN UNKNOWN SHIP
ARE LEAVING THE LOCAL AIRSPACE.
SHALL WE HAVE
THEM FOLLOWED, SIR?
- NO, JUST LEAVE THEM ALONE.
HMM.
- Renton: HEY, DID YOU KNOW
THAT ALL OF THE FINGERS
ON OUR HANDS
HAVE SPECIAL NAMES?
THE THUMB IS THE DAD,
THE INDEX FINGER
IS THE MOM.
- YES, I KNOW.
THE MIDDLE FINGER'S
THE BIG BROTHER.
THE RING FINGER
IS THE BIG SISTER,
AND THE PINKY,
THE LITTLE BROTHER.
IT'S JUST LIKE OUR FAMILY,
ISN'T IT?
- ( both gasp )
- HUH?
NIRVASH?
- WHAT'S WRONG, NIRVASH?
ARE YOU OKAY?
- WHAT'S THAT UP THERE?
WAIT, THAT'S--
- ( gasps )
- IT'S THE BLACK LFO!
( grunts )
( straining )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?!
HEY, NIRVASH,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
- WHOA!
- ( both gasp )
( gasping )
- AH, DAMN IT!
- RENTON, YOUR LEFT!
- NO WAY IN HELL!
- ( gasps )
OUCH.
- RENTON, WAIT A MINUTE!
NIRVASH SAYS
THAT SHE'S IN PAIN.
HE'S TELLING US TO LISTEN
THE WHAT THE VOICE
BEHIND THE PILOT
OF THAT THING IS SAYING.
- YEAH, BUT--
BUT, NIRVASH,
THAT LFO IS THE ONE
THAT ATTACKED
THE CONTROL CLUSTER!
- RENTON, PLEASE LISTEN.
- Anemone: IF--
EVEN AFTER THIS BATTLE--
THEY TELL ME
I CAN LIVE ON...
- ( gasps )
- I'LL GO AND BUY
A SMALL MIRROR SOMEWHERE
AND PRACTICE SMILING.
- ( gasps, cries )
- SHE HAS A SAD VOICE.
- DON'T CRY.
- RENTON.
- HUH?
- LET'S SAVE HER.
- Anemone: I'LL PRACTICE
OVER AND OVER
SO THAT I CAN
SEE HIM ONCE AGAIN.
- I CAN HEAR IT.
I CAN HEAR YOUR VOICE!
- Anemone: IF THEY TELL ME
THAT I CAN LIVE
WITHOUT HURTING
ANYONE ELSE,
I'LL LET MY HAIR
SWAY IN THE WIND,
TAKE A GIANT STEP
ONTO THE EARTH,
AND GO SEE HIM.
I WANT TO LIVE
TO SAY MY THANKS.
TO GIVE SO MANY
FEELINGS TO PEOPLE.
- BUT YOU CAN!
- I WANT TO LIVE.
I WISH I DIDN'T REALIZE
I HAD FEELINGS LIKE THIS.
- Eureka: IT'S ALL RIGHT
FOR YOU TO LIVE!
NOBODY HAS EVER SAID THAT
YOU HAD NO RIGHT TO LIVE!
- ( sobs )
BUT I'M IN SO MUCH PAIN!
HE'S NOT WHERE--
WHERE I CAN SEE HIM.
AND THAT'S--
AND THAT'S WHY...
( gasps )
- YOUR FEELINGS WILL
BE PASSED ON, ANEMONE.
- THEY WON'T, EUREKA.
THEY WON'T BE
PASSED ONTO ANYONE NOW.
- VASCUDA!
- Dominic: ANEMONE!
- ( gasps )
- ANEMONE!
ANEMONE!
- ( gasps )
- RENTON.
- TheEND, NO!
- ( grunts )
( screams )
- ( whimpers )
DOMINIC, NO!
- RENTON, LOOK.
- THE LFO IS AMAZING.
IT'S JUST LIKE THE NIRVASH.
- WE SHOULD GO TOO.
- RIGHT.
- DOMINIC! DOMINIC!
DOMINIC!
- AH!
ANEMONE!
WELL THEN, HI, THERE.
WELL, LONGTIME NO SEE.
- IDIOT!
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING
LETTING YOURSELF FALL
INTO A PLACE LIKE THIS?
- I-- I'M SORRY.
- IT'S OKAY.
I'LL MAKE AN EXCEPTION
AND FORGIVE YOU.
- HUH?
- YOU CAME TO FIND ME
AND YOU SAVED ME.
- I DON'T THINK
I REALLY SAVED YOU.
- YOU TRIED TO SAVE ME.
- THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
YOU'VE EVER GIVEN ME
THAT EXPRESSION.
IT'S QUITE WONDERFUL.
- ( gasps )
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
- HUH?
I'M TELLING YOU
THAT I LOVE IT!
- THIS IS MY FIRST TIME TO
HAVE SUCH A WONDERFUL FEELING.
I WOULDN'T CARE
IF I DIED RIGHT NOW.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
I WANT TO LIVE ON TOGETHER
WITH YOU, DOMINIC, FOREVER.
- THEN THAT'S WHAT WE'LL DO.
- HEY, RENTON.
- HMM.
I PROMISE YOU WE'LL LIVE
ALL OF US TOGETHER.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY, GUYS?
- HM, ALL TOGETHER.
- ALL TOGETHER!
- Man: ATTENTION!
PREPARATIONS FOR
ORATORIO NUMBER EIGHT'S
ULTIMATE IRRADIATION
OF THE TARGET BEACON
ARE NOW COMPLETE.
THERE ARE NO OBSTACLES.
- Ageha #1: IT SEEMS THAT TheEND
HAS DONE ENOUGH WORK
TO WARRANT THE EXPANDED BUDGET
WE COMMITTED TO IT,
BUT IS IT REALLY
ALL RIGHT, SIR?
AT THE ULTIMATE OUTPUT,
THE BODY WILL
QUICKLY SELF-DESTRUCT.
- BUT WILL THEY
REALLY BE NECESSARY
IN THE FUTURE WORLD
THAT WE LONG FOR?
- ( children whimper )
- WHAT IS IT?
( gasps )
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
TheEND!
NO, STOP!
NO, TheEND!
- ANEMONE.
- DOMINIC.
TheEND IS DEAD.
HUH?
TheEND?
- TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THE FINAL HOUR OF THE PLANET
IS FAST APPROACHING.
THE BOY AND HIS ENTOURAGE
BELIEVE IN
THE SLIM CHANCES OF HOPE,
WHILE THE MEN PUT THEIR
DIGNITY ON THE LINE
AS THEY HEAD FOR THE FINAL
SHOWDOWN. NEXT EPISODE...
"SHOUT TO THE TOP."