- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
♪ SO YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
♪ COME ON ♪
♪ WE WANNA MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE ♪
♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
♪ SO YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
♪ COME ON ♪
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
DINNER IS TONIGHT?
- SAME THING AS LUNCH,
I SUPPOSE?
- WE'VE GOT TO EAT THAT
AWFUL THIN SOUP AGAIN?
- WE'RE ALL GONNA STARVE!
- DON'T WORRY.
HILDA TOOK EUREKA
AND THE KIDS SHOPPING,
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
- YOU MEAN WE'RE GOING TO GET
A JUICY MEAL AT LAST?
- WELL, WHEN I SAW HILDA
A FEW MINUTES AGO,
SHE WAS HAPPY THAT
SHE FOUND SOME
HARD BREAD WITH
A LONG SHELF-LIFE.
- IT FIGURES.
SHE SURE ISN'T EASY ON US.
- YEAH.
- I'M THINKING THREE MORE DAYS.
- YEAH. I THINK EVERYONE'S GOING
TO BE AT THEIR LIMIT BY THEN.
- WELL, IT'S BETTER THAN NOT
HAVING ANYTHING TO DO.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ENOUGH WORK FOR TODAY!
- WE'RE DONE, WE'RE DONE!
- ( chattering )
- HEY, COME ON, KIDDO,
WE'RE GOING BACK.
- OH, RIGHT.
OH, NO, NO, I GOTTA...
( grunts )
- ( urinating )
- ( sighs )
- ( man shouting indistinctly )
- ( gasps )
I MUST BE HEARING THINGS.
- ( shouting continues )
- WAIT A MINUTE, ARE YOU GUYS
MESSING WITH ME AGAIN?
- Man: GET OUT!
- ( gasps )
- EVERYONE THAT MAKES
THE SCUBS DIRTY, GET OUT!
- ( gasping )
- Man: WE DIDN'T MEAN
TO SOIL THE SCUBS.
MORE OVER, IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE USING THE PLACE
TO HOLD BIG PARTIES EVERYDAY.
- WE'LL LEAVE WHEN WE FINISH
THE REPAIRS. I PROMISE YOU.
- THREE DAYS.
AFTER THREE DAYS, YOU GET OUT.
- I WONDER WHAT ONE WOULD
DIG UP IN A SITE LIKE THAT?
- THAT SCUB IS STILL KICKING!
JUST THREE, NO,
TWO MORE METERS OF DIGGING,
AND THOUSANDS OF
GALLONS OF TRAPARS
WILL SPRING FORTH,
I'M ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN.
- WHAT WAS THAT GUY?
- HE'S JUST SOME OLD DIGGER.
- I THOUGH HE WAS ULTRA SCARY.
- WOULDN'T IT BETTER
TO BE FRIENDLY TO HIM?
IN THE WORST CASE SCENARIO,
WE COULD BE HERE WITH HIM
FOR MORE THAN A MONTH.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
- GOOD EVENING.
MR. BRITTANY?
A MAP.
FOURTEEN YEARS AGO.
THE SAME YEAR I WAS BORN.
- YOU SURE HAVEN'T BEEN
DISCIPLINED AT ALL, HAVE YOU?
- I'M SORRY I JUST CAME IN,
BUT IT WAS OPEN.
- YOU'D GO ANYWHERE AS
LONG AS THE DOOR IS OPEN?
- WELL, I UM...
- WHAT IS IT YOU WANT?
- I JUST WANTED TO COME AND
APOLOGIZE ABOUT EARLIER.
- WHY?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- DID YOUR HIGHER-UPS
TELL YOU TO DO THIS?
- NO, IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT.
- OH, THEN WHY?
GO HOME.
- ( metal clanking )
- Brittany: I'M GONNA DO IT!
I SAID, I'M GONNA DO IT!
DAMN IT!
- YOU KNOW,
HE'S VERY NOISY.
- VERY.
- HEY, RENTON!
- YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
- GO COMPLAIN ABOUT THE NOISE.
- OH, OKAY!
- ARE YOU SURE?
- YEAH, I DON'T MIND.
I'M USED TO DEALING WITH
STUBBORN OLD MEN.
- ( grunting )
- SOMETIMES, HE'S AMAZING.
- THAT BANGING NOISE
FINALLY STOPPED.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK IT WAS?
WAS IT FROM THE EXCAVATION SITE?
- LET'S GO LOOK!
LET'S GO LOOK!
- NOW, MAETER,
YOU GUYS ARE STILL
IN THE MIDDLE OF YOUR JOBS.
- WHAT? BUT, I WANNA GO SEE!
- WHY DON'T YOU ASK YOUR MOM?
I'M POSITIVE SHE'LL SAY NO.
- MAMA, YOU WANT
TO GO SEE, DON'T YOU?
- NO, I THINK I'LL PASS.
- OH! COME ON. LET'S GO.
- DON'T ASK FOR THE IMPOSSIBLE.
- LET'S GO!
- I DON'T WANT TO!
- ( gasps )
( crying )
- I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
- OH, THERE, THERE.
ALL RIGHT, MAETER, LET'S GO.
YOUR MAMA'S REALLY TIRED,
SO YOU'LL HAVE TO
COME WITH ME, OKAY?
- Holland: WHAT HAPPENED?
- ( sighs ) I DON'T KNOW.
BUT, IT SEEMS LIKE SHE IS
EXPERIENCING SOME KIND OF STRESS
FROM THAT EXCAVATION SITE.
- ARE THE SCUBS AFFECTING HER?
- OR, IS IT...
- THE NIRVASH?
RIGHT NOW,
ALL I CAN SAY IS THAT
IT CAN BE EITHER OF
THOSE TWO POSSIBILITIES.
HOLLAND, HOW MANY DAYS
HAS IT BEEN,
SINCE SHE STARTED TO LIVE
AWAY FROM THE NIRVASH?
- NINE DAYS.
OR MAYBE, TEN.
- IN EITHER CASE,
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME.
I'M SURE THIS IS
THE FIRST EXPERIENCE
OF THIS KIND IN HER LIFE.
- SO, WHAT HAPPENED
TO THAT BREAD YOU GOT?
- HONEY, CAN WE HAVE SOME BREAD?
- NO, NO BREAD!
- WHY?
- SOMEONE HERE ATE SOME
WITHOUT ASKING.
UNTIL THE CULPRIT CONFESSES,
NOBODY GETS ANY!
- IT'S JUST LIKE HER.
BOY, SHE'S TOUGH.
- WAIT A SECOND,
WHO DID IT?
COME ON, FESS UP,
OR WE'RE ALL GONNA STARVE!
- PLEASE!
- TALHO, DO YOU THINK
EUREKA IS ALL RIGHT?
- WHY DO YOU ASK?
- WELL, MISS MISCHA
WAS HERE EARLIER TODAY,
SAID SOMETHING TO
HOLLAND ABOUT EUREKA,
AND HE RUSHED OUT.
- IF YOU'RE
THAT WORRIED ABOUT IT,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO
CHECK UP ON HER?
- NO REASON.
( knocking on door )
- Brittany: WHO IS IT?
- Renton: UM, IT'S ME.
- YEAH, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I THOUGHT THAT MAYBE
YOU HADN'T EATEN YET.
- HUH?
- EVERYONE TOLD ME
TO GIVE THIS TO YOU.
I'LL CARRY IT INSIDE FOR YOU.
- HEY! WAIT A MINUTE.
I FOUND IT.
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT IS SO FUNNY?
- OH, NOTHING.
- ( clock dinging )
- ( clock whirring )
- I'M IMPRESSED.
- YEAH? WELL, MY GRANDFATHER'S
A GREAT MECHANIC.
SO, I LEARNED TO BE ABLE
TO DO ALL SORTS OF THINGS
JUST BY WATCHING HIM.
THERE, IT'S ALL DONE.
- I GUESS,
I MADE A MISTAKE.
- HUH?
- ABOUT YOU NOT
BEING DISCIPLINED.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT. THAT KIND OF
STUFF DOESN'T REALLY BOTHER ME.
- YOUR NAME?
I ASK, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- I'M RENTON.
MY NAME'S RENTON THURSTON.
- YOU'RE A THURSTON?
THAT GREAT MECHANIC
GRANDFATHER OF YOURS,
ISN'T BY ANY CHANCE
NAMED AXEL THURSTON, IS HE?
AND LIVES IN BELL FOREST?
- OH, YES.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
SOMEONE DIDN'T ASK ABOUT
ADROC THURSTON AFTER
HEARING ME SAY MY NAME.
- WELL, ALL DIGGERS,
UNLESS THEY'VE COMPLETELY
SHUT THEMSELVES OFF
FROM THE WORLD,
FIRST THINK OF AXEL WHEN
THEY HEAR THE NAME THURSTON.
IT'S THE DREAM OF EVERY DIGGER
TO BE ABLE TO DIG UP SOMETHING
THAT MEETS THAT
MECHANIC'S CRITERIA.
- OH, I WISH GRANDPA COULD
HEAR WHAT YOU SAID!
SEE, THE NUMBER OF DIGGERS
HAS REALLY BEEN DECREASING
OVER THE LAST FEW YEARS.
ALONG WITH PEOPLE WHO
SAY THAT KIND OF STUFF.
SO, HE'S LIVING ALL LONELY,
I GUESS.
- YOU MEAN,
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN HOME?
- I CAN'T GO HOME YET.
I'M STILL IN TRAINING,
SO UNTIL I LEARN WHAT I'M
SUPPOSED TO, I...
- ( sighs ) SAME HERE.
- PUT IT ON.
- WHAT?
- UM, HOW FAR ARE WE
GOING TO GO?
ACTUALLY, I NEED TO
GO TO THE BATHROOM.
- WE'RE HERE.
- ( Renton grunts )
- TURN YOUR LIGHT OFF.
- HOW COME?
- YOU'LL SEE
WHEN YOU TURN IT OFF.
- WOW!
AMAZING!
- JUDGING FROM THE DEPTH HERE,
THESE LFO's ARE PROBABLY SOME
OF THE OLDEST IN THE WORLD.
AND I'M SURE THIS IS THE
ONLY PLACE
THAT SO MANY OF THEM ARE
GROUPED TOGETHER LIKE THIS.
- UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS IS AMAZING, MR. BRITTANY!
WAIT.
WHY ARE THEY DISAPPEARING?
- THEY'RE ALL DYING.
- HUH? BUT WHY?
- I GUESS THIS IS
AS GOOD A PLACE AS ANY.
- ( machine whirring )
- ALL RIGHT.
- Man: THAT HARD-HEADED
OLD MAN'S NOT HERE TODAY.
- HMM?
- MAYBE I SHOULD GO TAKE A LOOK.
- WHY?
- OH, I JUST FEEL LIKE IT.
- HEY, RENTON, CAN YOU GET
THE NIRVASH MOVE IN A BIT?
- SURE!
- ( tires screeching )
- HEY WOZ,
IS THIS ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
- MR. BRITTANY!
- HMM?
( gasps )
- Renton: MR. BRITTANY!
GOOD MORNING.
OH, I MEAN,
GOOD AFTERNOON.
- IS THAT...
- OH, YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
OF COURSE.
YEAH, THAT'S THE
TYPE ZERO OF THE NIRVASH,
ITS THE OLDEST LFO IN THE WORLD.
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- NO, NOTHING.
- All: THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD.
- Eureka: RENTON.
- HUH?
- EUREKA. ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I HAVE SOMETHING TO ASK YOU.
- WHAT IS IT?
- IS THE NIRVASH ALL RIGHT?
- EUREKA.
- YOU SEE,
I CAN'T GO OVER THERE, SO.
- I'M GOING INTO THE
DIG SITE RIGHT NOW.
DO YOU WANT TO COME WITH ME?
I HAVE TO SAY SOMETHING.
THIS IS MY CHANCE FOR ME
TO MAKE UP WITH HER.
I HAVE TO DO MY BEST.
YOU KNOW, YESTERDAY...
- I CAN'T GO, AFTER ALL.
- HOW COME?
- WELL, I CAN'T
PUT IT INTO WORDS.
- THAT'S OKAY. WE HAVE TO
GET UP EARLY TOMORROW, ANYWAY.
IT'S NOT TOO EARLY.
I SHOULDN'T RUSH.
IN ANY CASE, I HAVE TO
PATCH THINGS UP WITH HER.
- RENTON?
- YES.
- I'M HEARING SOMETHING.
- ( clanking indistinctly )
- OH, THAT'S MR. BRITTANY.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT, YOU HAVEN'T
MET HIM YET, HAVE YOU?
HOLD ON A SECOND. I'LL GO
DELIVER THIS TO HIM FIRST.
- ( clanking continues )
- Renton: MR. BRITTANY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THAT?
- ( gun cocking )
- BUT WHY?
- THIS IS BETA.
ALPHA, DO YOU COPY?
- ALPHA HERE. GO AHEAD.
- NOTHING TO REPORT
BETWEEN FAC 40 AND 49.
- ROGER THAT.
- THEY'RE HERE.
- CONTINUE YOUR PATROL.
- WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
- THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
BUT, I HOPE THE DON'T SPOT US,
AND MOVE ON TO THEIR
NEXT SEARCH AREA.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- RENTON'S IN TROUBLE!
- SO I GUESS,
YOU GAVE UP ON DIGGING?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO,
NOW THAT YOU'VE STOLEN THIS?
ARE YOU REALLY SATISFIED
WITH WHAT YOU'VE DONE?
- WHAT DOES A DUMB KID
LIKE YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
THERE'S NO MEANING IN DIGGING,
IF YOU DON'T FIND ANYTHING
WORTH DIGGING FOR.
IT'S JUST PLAYING IN THE SAND,
UNLESS YOU STRIKE
SOMETHING GOOD.
- DOES THAT GIVE YOU
AN EXCUSE TO STEAL?
DOESN'T STRIKING SOMETHING GOOD
MEAN THAT YOU HAVE
TO EXCAVATE IT?
- THIS IS JUST LIKE
ME DIGGING IT UP.
- HUH?
- AS FAR AS THE REST
OF THE WORLD KNOWS,
I FOUND THIS
LFO BECAUSE I WAS
WORKING THERE
FOR OVER A DECADE.
- THAT'S COMPLETELY RIDICULOUS.
NOBODY WOULD BELIEVE THAT STORY.
- MY SON WILL BELIEVE IT.
I'M POSITIVE, HE WILL.
- YOU LEFT HIM ALONE
FOR FOURTEEN YEARS,
SO YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- IF I WAS YOUR SON,
I WOULD NEVER BE HAPPY
ABOUT ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
- HMM?
- ( gasping )
- ( both grunting )
- Man: THIS IS THE HACIENDA
STATE FORCES KLF SQUAD!
THE PILOT NEEDS TO
IMMEDIATELY DISEMBARK.
- Eureka: THERE IT IS. THE
NIRVASH AHEAD AT TEN O CLOCK!
- Man: CHECK IT OUT,
I SEE A BIT OF TROUBLE AHEAD.
- ( screaming )
- NO GOOD. LEADER, NO GOOD.
IT'S OBVIOUS TO THEM IT'S US.
- YOU FORGOT THE SAFETY.
- HUH?
- IT'S NOT WORTH IT FOR US
TO KILL YOU RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN RUN OFF TO WHEREVER
YOU PLEASE. JERK.
- HOLLAND, STOP IT.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
- I'M NOT THROUGH WITH HIM.
I DON'T LIKE HIS
CHILDISH LITTLE ATTITUDE.
- SO, YOU THINK
YOU'RE SHOWING OFF,
TAKING THE NIRVASH AND
TRYING TO MOVE IT BY YOURSELF?
ARE YOU LISTENING?
( grunts )
OW. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- GETTING YOU ATTENTION,
SINCE YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO'S NOT LISTENING HERE.
IF YOU WERE,
YOU'D KNOW HE'S NOT
AT FAULT FOR THIS.
- YOU KNOW WHAT, HOLLAND?
WHY DON'T YOU STOP USING HIM
AS A MEANS TO ESCAPE?
- ( grunts )
- ( door slamming )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M FINE, REALLY.
I DIDN'T CARE AT ALL.
OR RATHER,
I WASN'T LISTENING AT ALL.
I WAS THINKING MORE ABOUT
WAS WHY MR. BRITTANY
HAD STOPPED HIS EXCAVATIONS.
WHY HE HAD GIVEN UP?
IS THAT MINE REALLY DEAD?
AND IF SO, WHY DIDN'T HE
JUST START TO DIG THE NEXT ONE?
WAS THIS SOMETHING
THAT WAS IMPOSSIBLE
FOR A KID LIKE ME TO UNDERSTAND?
WHAT DID HE HOPE TO ACCOMPLISH
BY STEALING THE NIRVASH?
AND SHOWING IT TO HIS SON.
SIS, WHY DID DAD
LEAVE ME THE AMITA DRIVE?
WAS IT SOMETHING THAT DAD
REALLY FOUND IN AN OLD MINE?
IS IT SOMETHING THAT I SHOULD
BE PROTECTING WITH MY LIFE?
IF IT ISN'T SO, SIS,
THEN WHY AM I HERE?
- Eureka: RENTON.
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR PROTECTING THE NIRVASH.
FOR NOW,
I THINK YOU SHOULD BE OPERATING
THE NIRVASH BY YOURSELF.
I JUST CAN'T DO
ANYTHING RIGHT NOW.
IT'S WHAT HE WANTS AS WELL.
I'LL TALK TO HOLLAND AND
MAKE HIM UNDERSTAND
THAT IT'S THE BEST THING
FOR BOTH OF US.
HEY, RENTON?
- I'M SORRY, NOTHING'S GONNA
STICK IN MY MIND NOW.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ TAKE A CHANCE ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN MYSELF ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
- Narrator: THE RELATIONSHIP
STARTS TO CHANGE.
THE HEART BEGINS TO FALTER.
IN FRONT OF THE GIRL WHO WAS
READY TO BE SWALLOWED
UP BY THE WORLD,
THE ADULTS ARE ALL
FACING DESPAIR,
AND THE BOY IS SCREAMING.
NEXT EPISODE,
"ACPERIENCE 2."