- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
- ♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
- ♪ COME ON ♪
- ♪ GAME OVER ♪
- ♪ WE WANT TO MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE ♪
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
- ♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
- ♪ COME ON ♪
- HOW LONG HAD IT BEEN
SINCE I LEFT CHARLES' PLACE?
SEEM LIKE FOREVER.
I KEPT WALKING FOR THE PROMISE.
THE PROMISE OF
GETTING TO SEE EUREKA.
BUT...
BUT NOW, I COULDN'T
GET MYSELF TO EVEN WALK.
AND I WAS BEGINNING TO
LOSE SIGHT OF THE REASON.
WHY I KEPT ON WALKING.
( gasps )
( groans )
SIS...
MAYBE...
MAYBE I...
- NIRVASH...
DO YOU FEEL LONELY
WHEN NOBODY IS ABOARD?
DO YOU FEEL A GAPING HOLE
RIGHT HERE IN YOUR HEART?
PLEASE, SAY SOMETHING TO ME.
- ( gasps )
( groans )
- SO, YOU'VE COME TO?
ARE YOU SURPRISED?
YOU WERE LAYING OUT
THERE UNCONSCIOUS,
SO I JUST BROUGHT YOU
BACK TO THE HOUSE.
I TELL YOU,
YOU SURPRISED ME, TOO.
I WAS LOOKING AT A PERSON
COLLAPSED THERE, OF ALL PLACES!
I THOUGHT THAT THIS WAS AN AREA
THAT NOBODY WOULD EVER COME.
AT FIRST, I THOUGHT
IT WAS SOMETHING LIKE
AN OPTICAL ILLUSION.
OR A GHOST THAT
THE TRAPPERS WERE SHOWING ME.
- Renton:
THE PERSON THAT SAVED ME
SEEMED LIKE HE WAS VERY KIND BUT
HE WAS ALSO VERY TALKATIVE.
- AM I BEING TOO TALKATIVE?
MY NAME IS WILLIAM B. BAXTER.
BUT YOU CAN CALL ME WILL.
OH, AND PLEASE DON'T ASK ME
WHAT MY MIDDLE INITIAL
"B" STANDS FOR.
IT'S AN EMBARRASSING NAME THAT
MY DAD PICKED WHEN HE WAS DRUNK.
( laughs )
- OH, I...
( coughs )
- OH, I'M SORRY!
NO, DON'T TRY TO SAY ANYTHING.
THAT WAS MY FAULT.
OH, NO!
I FORGOT THAT YOU'D PROBABLY
BE BOTH HUNGRY AND THIRSTY
AFTER BEING OUT LIKE THAT!
I'M REALLY SORRY!
I'LL BRING YOU SOME SOUP
RIGHT AWAY.
HERE, YOU BETTER DRINK IT SLOW.
YOU DON'T WANT TO CHOKE ON IT.
- Renton: IT WAS ONLY
A SPOONFUL OF SOUP.
BUT THAT SPOONFUL
WAS MORE DELICIOUS
THAN ANYTHING I'D EVER
EATEN IN MY LIFE.
- DO YOU LIKE HOW IT TASTES?
- ( stomach grumbling )
- I'M SURE THAT YOU'RE
REALLY HUNGRY
AND THAT YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU COULD EAT AN ENTIRE HORSE
FROM HEAD TO TAIL IN ONE BITE.
BUT DON'T FORCE YOURSELF.
YOU WERE SHOWING
SIGNS OF DEHYDRATION.
SO, FOR NOW,
YOU BETTER EAT JUST THE SOUP.
- THANKS A LOT, YOU'RE KIND.
- NO, I'M THE ONE WHO REALLY
OUGHT TO BE THANKING YOU.
I'M HAPPY THAT YOU CAME HERE,
NO MATTER WHAT
THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
BECAUSE I DIDN'T HAVE ANYONE
TO TALK TO AROUND THIS PLACE,
OTHER THAN MARTHA.
- HUH?
- OH, I HAVEN'T
INTRODUCED YOU YET.
MY WIFE, MARTHA.
- ( gasps )
DESPERATION DISEASE.
- MARTHA, THIS IS...
- RENTON. MY NAME'S
RENTON THURSTON.
- RENTON THURSTON.
MARTHA, WE FINALLY
HAVE A VISITOR. EXCITED?
MARTHA, YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME
IN FRONT OF OUR NICE GUEST!
I UNDERSTAND THAT
YOU'RE HUNGRY, DEAR,
BUT RENTON HERE HASN'T QUITE
FINISHED HIS MEAL YET.
AND THEN OF COURSE,
I HAVE TO ENTERTAIN HIM, TOO.
MARTHA, PLEASE BE UNDERSTANDING.
- OH, LOOK,
I'LL BE JUST FINE, REALLY.
- I DON'T KNOW, RENTON.
- I'LL BE ALL RIGHT
BY MYSELF NOW.
IF IT'S JUST SOUP.
- I'M SORRY.
IT'S TOUGH WHEN YOU HAVE A VERY
DEMANDING WOMAN AS YOUR WIFE.
I'M KIDDING!
SO DON'T BE MAD AT ME, OKAY?
HEY, HOW ABOUT SOME SOUP?
- SORRY ABOUT ALL THIS.
- SURE.
- IT'S PUMPKIN SOUP,
YOUR FAVORITE.
COME NOW, YOU KNOW YOU HAVE
TERRIBLE TABLE MANNERS.
BUT, IN A TATTERED HOUSE LIKE
THIS, MANNERS MEAN NOTHING!
( laughs )
- ( grunts )
THE DAMN STATE ARMY'S
BLOCKED THIS LINE AS WELL.
I WONDER WHAT'S GOING ON TODAY?
- ( exclaiming in pain )
( groans )
PAIN WAS RUNNING
THOUGH MY ENTIRE BODY.
BUT THANKS TO
THE LITTLE BIT OF SLEEP I GOT,
I WAS ABLE TO MOVE AROUND.
TWO BEDS.
TWO CUPS.
TWO PLATES.
TWO CHAIRS.
IT WAS A HOUSE
THAT HAD TWO OF EVERYTHING.
( gasps )
I DON'T THINK SHE'S BREATHING!
- ( inhales )
( exhales )
- ( both exhale )
- ( gasps )
( exhales )
IS EVERYONE WHO HAS
DESPERATION DISEASE LIKE THIS?
HUH?
- OH!
BE CAREFUL!
I PLANTED MY POTATOES THERE!
AND CARROTS OVER THERE!
AND THERE...
I FORGOT WHAT I PLANTED THERE.
ANYWAY, BE CAREFUL
NOT TO STEP ON THE CROPS.
- I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE
ANYTHING IS PLANTED!
- WELL, YOU CAN SEE
MY FOOTSTEPS, CAN'T YOU?
JUST TRY AND FOLLOW THEM
OVER HERE?
- THE GRASS IS SO THICK
I CAN'T SEE THEM!
- I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE!
YOU THINK IT'S ALRIGHT FOR YOU
TO BE UP SO SOON?
- YEAH, I'M OKAY MR. WILLIAM.
- HEY, I SAID THAT YOU SHOULD
JUST CALL ME WILL, DIDN'T I?
- ( chuckles )
WELL THEN, WILL, I REALLY
WANT TO THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR SAVING MY LIFE.
- NO THANKS REQUIRED.
BESIDES, IF YOU'RE
GOING TO SAY THANKS,
YOU SHOULD SAY IT TO MARTHA.
SHE WAS THE ONE WHO TOLD ME
THAT YOU HAD COLLAPSED
AND EXACTLY WHERE
I WOULD FIND YOU.
- HUH?
HOW DID SHE...
- WELL, WE SHOULD
PROBABLY EAT SOON.
- WILL, CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- HMM?
- UM, I WAS WONDERING WHAT
YOU WERE DOING OVER THERE?
- I WAS PULLING OUT
THE PILE BUNKERS.
- WHAT?
( gasps )
BUT HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
THEY ARE ALL SO GIGANTIC!
- OH, IT'S NOTHING.
YOU CAST A SMALL
HOCUS-POCUS SPELL.
- HUH?
PULLING THEM OUT CAUSES
SOMETHING SERIOUS, DOESN'T IT?
ISN'T THIS WHOLE AREA STABLE
BECAUSE SO MANY OF THEM
CAN BE FOUND HERE
PLUNGED INTO THE GROUND?
- NO, YOU'RE WRONG!
IT'S THE OPPOSITE.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- SEE? IT DOESN'T EVEN
SHAKE ONE BIT HERE.
- BUT HOW'S THAT?
I MEAN, WHEN YOU PULL THEM OUT,
THEY RESULT AS A HUGE
TECTONIC SHIFT,
AND THEN IT...
THAT'S RIGHT!
IT SWALLOWS UP AN ENTIRE TOWER
BEFORE IT'S THROUGH.
- TAKE A LOOK AT THAT TREE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK HAPPENS
WHEN THE WIND BLOWS?
- HUH?
- WHAT WOULD HAPPEN
IF THE WIND BLOWS?
- WELL, IT WOULD SWAY,
OF COURSE.
- WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF
A STRONGER WIND WERE TO BLOW?
OR A WIND THAT WAS
EVEN STRONGER THAN THAT?
- IT WOULD SWAY MORE AND MORE,
AND IN THE END IT
WOULD FALL DOWN.
- GOOD, YOU UNDERSTAND IT WELL.
IT'S THE SAME THING AS THAT.
IF YOU FIGHT THE FORCE
OF THE WORLD WITH FORCE,
SOMEDAY YOU WILL FALL.
EVEN THE TOWERS THAT ARE STABLE
NOW THANKS TO THE PILE BUNKERS,
CAN'T FIGHT AGAINST
THE FORCE OF THE WORLD.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- NOW, WHEN THAT WIND
BLOWS STRONG ENOUGH
TO MAKE THAT BIG TREE
THERE FALL DOWN,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HAPPENS TO THE GRASS?
- THE GRASS WILL
MOST LIKELY FALL, TOO.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
IT WILL FALL OVER.
BUT IT WILL RISE AGAIN
GIVEN A FEW DAYS.
I TELL YOU, THIS LAND IS
A LOT LIKE THE GRASS.
I WANT YOU TO BREATHE IN.
WHAT? YOU'VE NEVER
BREATHED IN BEFORE?
- OF COURSE I HAVE!
- THEN JUST BREATHE IN!
( inhales )
- ( exhales )
THE WIND THAT I
BREATHED IN WAS SWEET,
FULL OF THE SMELL OF THE GRASS.
- YOU SEE?
YOU KNOW, THE WIND CAN
TEACH YOU MORE THINGS
THAN ALL OF THE WORDS
I CAN POSSIBLY LINE UP FOR YOU.
- HMM?
- BUT, BE CAREFUL.
BREATHING IN MEANS THAT YOU'RE
THAT MUCH CLOSER TO DEATH.
- HMM?
- YOU KNOW, RENTON, I THINK
PEOPLE SHOULDN'T USE
UP ANY MORE ENERGY
THAN IS PROVIDED BY THE SUN
THAT SHINES ON US.
- OH?
- SEE, THE PROBLEM IS THAT WHEN
YOU TRY TO USE UP MORE THAN THAT
YOU END UP DIGGING FOR SCUBS
IN ORDER TO DRAIN
ENERGY FROM THEM,
OR BUILDING ENORMOUS TOWERS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
PEOPLE CAN SURVIVE JUST FINE
ON WHAT LITTLE LAND
IS GIVEN TO THEM.
- BUT THERE ARE TIMES WHEN
THE CROPS DON'T GROW, RIGHT?
- THERE ARE.
BUT NOT SO BAD THAT YOU'D DIE
OF HUNGER, OR ANYTHING.
YOU SEE, THIS WORLD IS GIVING
US PERMISSION TO LIVE HERE.
- ( groans )
A BEAUTIFUL FOXY WOMAN AND A
GUY THAT LOOKS LIKE A RACCOON?
IT CAN'T BE RAY AND CHARLES,
CAN IT?
- COME ON, HOLLAND!
COME ON, HOLLAND!
ADROC IS CALLING
FOR YOU, HOLLAND.
- ( gasps )
DAMN IT, THE STATE ARMY
HAS GOT THIS LINE BLOCKED, TOO?
IF THIS LINE HERE AND THIS
ONE HERE ARE BOTH BLOCKED...
DAMN IT!
THIS IS NO TIME
TO LOOK FOR RENTON!
- Renton: WATCHING THEM
WAS HARD ON ME,
AND I WAS NOTHING MORE
THAN AN OBSERVER.
- HEY, WILL.
- YES, RENTON?
- I DON'T WANT TO SAY THIS,
BUT MARTHA HAS
DESPERATION DISEASE.
- NO, SHE DOESN'T.
- BUT, WILL...
- RENTON, DO YOU KNOW WHY PEOPLE
CALL IT DESPERATION DISEASE?
IT'S CALLED THAT BECAUSE
PEOPLE AROUND THE PATIENTS,
NOT THE PATIENTS THEMSELVES,
FALL INTO DESPAIR.
AND SINCE I HAVEN'T
FALLEN INTO DESPAIR,
THIS CAN'T POSSIBLY BE
DESPERATION DISEASE.
- BUT THAT'S...
THAT'S NOTHING MORE THAN
A SILLY PLAY ON WORDS.
- LISTEN TO ME, RENTON.
YEARS AGO,
I MADE A PROMISE TO MARTHA.
- ( gun firing )
- ( gasps )
- ( sobbing )
- I PROMISED THAT
I WOULD SHOW HER
THE PLACE WHERE I WAS BORN.
I TOLD HER THAT SHE SHOULD
THROW AWAY THAT THING,
BUT BECAUSE SHE WAS AN ENGINEER,
SHE COULDN'T BRING
HERSELF TO DO IT.
YOU KNOW, I REALLY WISH
THAT I COULD SHOW YOU
HOW IT WAS THAT SHE WALKED.
IT WAS TRULY BEAUTIFUL.
BUT THEN...
WE ARRIVED AT MY BIRTHPLACE
TO DISCOVER THAT IT HAD
BECOME A WASTELAND.
BUT MARTHA WAS
CAPTIVATED BY THE PLACE.
AND SO, I BUILT A HOUSE HERE.
AND DID EVERYTHING JUST LIKE
MARTHA TOLD ME TO.
I CULTIVATED, PLANTED FLOWERS
AND BUILT A LIFE.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
- BUT ISN'T IT
DIFFICULT FOR YOU?
- DIFFICULT?
WHY DO YOU THINK THAT?
NOTHING IS DIFFICULT
WHEN YOU LOVE EACH OTHER.
SO MUCH SO THAT
THE ANGELS ARE JEALOUS.
SO, DO YOU HAVE SOMEONE?
A PERSON THAT
YOU WANT TO BE WITH,
EVEN IF THE WORLD
WOULD'VE CAME TO AN END.
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
- SO, DO YOU HAVE SOMEONE?
- I DO.
- GREAT! I THINK
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
- ALRIGHT, I REALLY
HAVE TO GO NOW.
- YOU SHOULD.
YOU HAVE A SOLEMN PROMISE TO
FULFILL AS WELL, DON'T YOU?
- HUH? YES.
IS THERE A PLACE CALLED GEARNUS
ANYWHERE CLOSE TO HERE?
- MMM-HMM, IT'S NOT TOO FAR,
YOU'LL HAVE NO PROBLEMS
BUT SHE WON'T NECESSARILY
BE THERE JUST WAITING FOR YOU.
EVEN SO, WILL YOU GO?
- YES!
- HMM, SEEMS LIKE A GOOD BOY.
- EUREKA, PLEASE WAIT FOR ME.
- RENTON...
- A BULLETIN FROM
THE STATE ARMY.
THE HUNTING DOGS
HAVE BEEN PUT INTO PLACE,
AND IT'S TIME TO CORNER THE FOX.
WE'RE DOING IT?
- YEAH. I MADE AN UNBREAKABLE
PROMISE TO RENTON.
- SOMETIME YOU'RE SO CRUEL,
CHARLES, I LOVE IT.
- I'M GOING TO GO
BACK TO THE GEKKO!
I'M GOING TO SEE EUREKA!
TO BE CONTINUED!
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ BE TOGETHER,
NOW YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY! FLY AWAY ♪
♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE
TAKE IT EASY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ TAKE MY CHANCE
BELIEVE IN MYSELF ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
- Ray: THE UNAVOIDABLE
BATTLE BETWEEN THOSE
THAT CANNOT ACCEPT EACH OTHER.
THE HEARTS OF THE BOY AND
THE GIRL SEEKING ONE ANOTHER.
CREATE A RAINBOW
COLORED MIRACLE.
NEXT EPISODE, "MORNING GLORY."