- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Mischa: ALL RIGHT.
NEXT I WANT YOU TO GIVE ME THE
UNBALANCED FEEDBACK RESPONSE.
I'LL LEAVE THE PROGRAM
UP TO YOU.
FOR NOW, MANEUVER
AS MUCH AS YOU WANT TO
UNTIL YOU REACH YOUR LIMITS.
- Eureka: ROGER.
- Renton: THE DATA IS RECORDED
ON A SEPARATE TRACK?
- Mischa: I DON'T MIND
IF YOU HAVEN'T CONNECTED.
JUST KEEP ENTERING THE CODES.
- ALL RIGHT.
- ( scanning sounds )
- Eureka: I'LL START WITH A
ROLL-IN INTO A CURVING TURN.
IF I DON'T LOSE SPEED, I'LL GO
ON FROM THERE INTO AN AERIAL.
- VERY GOOD, EUREKA.
THANKS.
- RIGHT, HERE GOES.
- WAIT A MINUTE!
THE CODES AREN'T-- AH!
AHHH!
AHHHH!
- Mischa: I KNEW THERE WAS
SOMETHING DIFFERENT ABOUT IT,
BUT I DIDN'T THINK
IT WOULD BE SO OBVIOUS.
EUREKA'S CONDITION
HASN'T FULLY NORMALIZED YET.
THESE NUMBERS
COMING FROM THE typeZERO ARE--
IS THE AMITA DRIVE
REALLY SPEAKING TO THE typeZERO?
OR COULD IT BE--
- Renton: DR. MISCHA?
I'VE REACHED MY LIMIT.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT IS IT?
ARE YOU HAVING TROUBLE?
- Eureka: DOCTOR?
RENTON IS WIGGLING AROUND
IN HIS SEAT.
- WIGGLING?
- ( thinking )
SIS, I'M GONNA LET IT GO.
( vomiting )
- EW.
- ( Renton grunting )
- Renton:
I CAN'T BELIEVE I DID IT AGAIN.
THE OTHER DAY I OVERTURNED
ALL THE BOXES IN THE WAREHOUSE.
YESTERDAY I ACCIDENTALLY
ERASED ALL THE DATA
ON MR. HAP'S COMPUTER.
AND TODAY--
AHHH!
OF ALL THE PEOPLE
IN THE WORLD,
WHY DID I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
SO GROSS IN FRONT OF HER?
I'M SURE SHE THINKS
I'M JUST A STUPID,
WORTHLESS GOOD-FOR-NOTHING.
( sighs )
- HE'S SLACKING AGAIN.
- WHAAA!  HEY, NO WAY,
I'M NOT SLACKING AT ALL!
I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO GET STARTED.
- HEY, MAMA?
- WHAT IS IT?
- MAMA, WHO IS IT
YOU LIKE BETTER,
GUYS THAT THROW UP
OR GUYS THAT DON'T?
- ( bucket clanging )
- YEAH, MAMA, 'CAUSE SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T SMELL LIKE THROW UP
IS BETTER THAN SOMEONE
THAT DOES.
- THAT'S TRUE. SOMEONE WHO
DOESN'T SMELL IS BETTER.
- ( bucket clanging )
- YEAH.  WELL, YOU KNOW,
LISTEN, ABOUT THAT--
SEE, THE REASON
I THREW UP
IS I'M STILL NOT USED TO
RIDING IN THE L.F.O. JUST YET.
AND BESIDES, YOUR TIMING FOR THE
CUTBACKS AND OTHER MANEUVERS
IS KIND OF DIFFERENT
FROM THE TIMING I USE MYSELF.
SO I CAN'T QUITE GET IN SYNCH
WITH THE L.F.O.'s MOVEMENTS.
- IN OTHER WORDS, YOU JUST DON'T
GET ALONG WITH MAMA VERY WELL.
- IS THAT SO?
RENTON AND I AREN'T COMPATIBLE?
- NO, WAIT A MINUTE!
- OF COURSE IT IS, MAMA.
IF HE GOT ALONG WITH YOU,
THERE'S NO WAY
THAT HE'D THROW UP
RIGHT NEXT TO YOU.
- HMM?  RENTON, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE DON'T GET ALONG VERY WELL.
- ( bucket clamoring )
- NOW HOLD ON!
WHETHER OR NOT WE GET ALONG
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
IN THE FIRST PLACE,
THAT WAS ONE OF THE FIRST TIMES
I'VE EVER LIFTED IN AN L.F.O.
BESIDES THAT, EVERY PERSON
HAS THEIR OWN TIMING
FOR LIFTING MOVES.
AND IT'S NOT THAT EASY
TO SYNCH UP WITH THE RHYTHM
OF SOMEBODY ELSE'S TIMING.
RIGHT?!
ISN'T THAT TRUE?
- ISN'T THAT WHAT GETTING ALONG
IS ABOUT?
- ( grunting )
- Girl: MAMA, LET'S GO!
IF YOU STAY CLOSE
TO A THROW-UPPER,
YOU'LL BECOME
A THROW-UPPER TOO, MAMA.
- YEAH, LET'S GO, MAMA.
- MAMA, CAN WE EAT?
I'M HUNGRY.
- WHOEVER SAID
THAT YOUR FIRST LOVE
IS SWEET AS WELL AS SOUR
IS A BIG LIAR.
ALL IT IS IS BITTER.
- Talho: OH, IS THIS A TRIAL
THAT GOD HAS GIVEN ME
BECAUSE I FELL IN LOVE
WITH AN ANGEL?
THIS BIT OF DOWN
THAT FLOATS AWAY IF I CHASE IT
WEIGHS HEAVILY
UPON MY HEART.
- HUH?!
- AHA!
- MISS TALHO!  WAIT A MINUTE.
PLEASE DON'T TELL ANYONE.
PLEASE, MISS TALHO!
- "IT'S JUST A BIG LIE!
ALL IT IS IS BITTER!"
( giggling )
- YOU'RE GONNA
TELL THEM, AREN'T YOU?
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL THEM
ABOUT MY SWEET LITTLE ROMANCE?
- ( laughing )
- YOU'RE GONNA USE IT
AS SOMETHING TO LAUGH ABOUT
WHEN YOU'RE DRINKING TONIGHT!
- ( laughing )
- MISS TALHO, PLEASE,
I'M BEGGING YOU!
PLEASE DON'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT THIS TO THEM.
COME ON, I PROMISE
I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU SAY.
- OH?
SO YOU'RE GOING TO DO
ANYTHING I SAY?
- HUH?
- Holland: OTHER THAN THAT,
A LIFT TETHER AND
A COUPLING CARTRIDGE.
- 500.
OR MAYBE EVEN 550.
THAT'S IT FOR THE NIRVASH.
WHAT ABOUT EVERYDAY ITEMS?
- WE NEED FOOD,
MEDICINE AND GROCERIES.
- 200 TOTAL.
- GIDGET'S REQUEST IS
FIVE DOZEN SPARE TOOTHBRUSHES.
- Talho: JOHN HENRY'S
REISSUED SILVER.
- DENIED.
- OH, COME ON.
WE MADE A LITTLE MONEY
FROM THE DELIVERY
TO STROHOLM, DIDN'T WE?
I NEED IT FOR THE PHOTO SHOOT
WE'RE DOING FOR "ray=out."
- THE PARTS FOR
THE NIRVASH ARE GOING TO
TAKE A BIG CHUNK OF IT.
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT
NEXT TIME WE MAKE SOME MONEY.
- BUT IT'S A LIMITED EDITION.
I WANT THE SERIAL NUMBER
TO BE ONE DIGIT.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
STUFF CONCERNING EUREKA
HAS TOP PRIORITY.
OH, AND BY THE WAY,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M NOT DOING THIS
BECAUSE I WANT TO!
- YOUR FIRST LOVE...
- AH!
- ...IS SWEET AND YET SOUR.
- WHOA WHOA WHOA!
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
TALHO, YOU HEAD DOWN
IN MATTHIEU'S 606 WITH HILDA.
I'LL HEAD DOWN WITH EUREKA
IN THE NIRVASH.
- WAIT A MINUTE!
HOLLAND, I'D LIKE TO KNOW
WHY EUREKA HAS TO BE THE ONE
YOU GO DOWN THERE WITH!
- SINCE THEY'RE GOING TO TRY
AND FIND PARTS FOR THE NIRVASH,
HE'S GONNA NEED HER INPUT,
RIGHT?
- YEAH YEAH.
IT'S ALL ABOUT EUREKA.
COME ON,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE, RENTON.
- WHAT?! WHY ME?
- WHO'S GONNA
HOLD ALL THE STUFF I GET
IF YOU DON'T COME WITH ME?
- ( laughs nervously )
( sighs )
- HMM.
- THE GEKKO SHOULD JUST HANG OUT
ON TOP OF THE LEY LINE
AND CIRCLE WHILE WE'RE GONE.
- HEY.
THINK WE SHOULD
LEAVE THEM ALONE?
- HMM?
I'M SURE RENTON WILL
FIGURE IT OUT SOONER OR LATER,
THAT THEY'RE JUST FOOLING AROUND
WITH HIM TO HAVE SOME FUN.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I MEAN TALHO.
- HMM?
- ( whirring )
- ( beeping )
- I THINK YOU KNOW BY NOW,
BUT DON'T TOUCH ANY OF
THE WEAPONS CONTROLS, OKAY?
- UH, YEAH, I UNDERSTAND.
- COME ON,
SCOOT OVER A LITTLE MORE.
- THIS IS AS FAR
AS I CAN GET.
- I THINK YOU JUST WANT
TO PRESS YOURSELF UP AGAINST ME.
YOU ARE SO PERVERTED.
- HUH?  WHAT?  I AM NOT!
- ARE YOU SAYING
THAT I'M NOT ATTRACTIVE?
- JEEZ.  I CAN'T WIN TODAY.
HOW ABOUT LETTING ME FLY,
MISS HILDA?
AFTER ALL,
YOU AND MISS TALHO GET ALONG,
AND YOU'RE BOTH
THE SAME GENDER.
- NO, THANKS, RENTON.
MATTHIEU WILL BE IN TEARS
IF SOMEONE THROWS UP
ON THE FRONT SEAT.
- ( grumbles )
- WAIT, HE'S ALREADY IN TEARS.
- HMM.
YOU SERIOUSLY WANT A BATTLE
REPORT ABOUT BELLFOREST?
I DON'T REMEMBER
THAT FAR BACK.
- 606 HEADING OUT.
- ( panting )
( grunting )
MAN, THAT WAS CLOSE.
- Hilda: I'LL GO GET THE TOILET
PAPER AND THE TOOTHBRUSHES.
- Talho: OKAY,
THEN I'LL JUST TAKE OUR
TRUSTY BAGGAGE HOLDER WITH ME.
- ( grunts )
OOH!
MISS HILDA!
- LET'S MEET BACK
AT THIS RESTAURANT
AFTER WE'RE DONE SHOPPING!
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
IT'S THE THIRD WEDNESDAY
OF THE MONTH,
AND THAT MEANS THAT MY FAVORITE
MARKET IS HAVING A SALE.
- I'M TELLING YOU, IT'S NOT EASY
TO GET AN INERTIA PUMP
THAT'S AS GOOD
AS THIS ONE HERE.
- WELL?
- NO GOOD.
THAT ONE HAS ALREADY DIED.
YOU'VE WORKED VERY HARD.
NOW YOU CAN REST.
- YOU HEARD HER.
- HUH?
OH, MAN!
FIVE OR SIX BLADES ARE BUSTED.
SORRY, MAN.
BUT HOW THE HELL
DID YOU FIGURE THAT OUT?
DID THE PARTS TALK TO YOU?
- ( music playing )
- UH, MAYBE I SHOULD JUST WAIT
FOR YOU OUTSIDE?
- HEY, RENTON?
- YES?
- WHICH ONE IS BETTER?
- OH!  EITHER ONE IS FINE.
- ( laughs )
COME ON, WHICH ONE?
- WELL, I CAN'T REALLY SAY
IF ONE OR THE OTHER IS BETTER.
THEY BOTH LOOK
SO WONDERFUL. AND, UM--
- COME ON NOW,
LOOK OVER HERE.
- YES?  OH!
STOP IT!
- ( laughing )
EXCUSE ME?
I'D LIKE TO TRY THIS ON.
- Woman: GO RIGHT AHEAD.
- ( thinking )
IT'S TRUE THAT I WAS SO NERVOUS,
I THOUGHT MY HEART WAS GONNA
BURST OPEN RIGHT THERE.
BUT, SIS, THAT ISN'T
THE ONLY REASON
MY HEART IS RACING LIKE THIS.
YOU SEE,
THE EXPRESSION THAT
WAS ON MISS TALHO'S
FACE JUST NOW--
FOR SOME REASON, IT LOOKED
JUST LIKE YOUR FACE, SIS.
- LOOK, IF YOU DON'T LIKE THIS,
I CAN ALWAYS GO OUT
TO LOOK FOR
THE PARTS YOU NEED
ALL BY MYSELF NEXT TIME.
- NO, I WANT TO GO WITH YOU.
- HMM?
- THE LITTLE ONE--
I MEAN NIRVASH--
I WANT TO MAKE SURE
I TAKE PROPER CARE OF HIM.
- HMM.
- RENTON SAYS HE UNDERSTANDS.
- HOW MACHINES FEEL?
HA! WELL, I'M NOT SURPRISED.
HE IS THURSTON'S KID.
HUH?
HEY, I FORGOT SOMETHING.
SORRY.
- BUT WE'VE GOT
ALL THE PARTS WE NEED.
- I'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
- ( all screaming )
- ( grunting )
- UM, MISS TALHO,
COULD YOU MAYBE THINK
ABOUT LETTING ME OFF THE HOOK?
- OH!
JOHN HENRY'S REISSUED SILVER,
WITH A ONE-DIGIT SERIAL NUMBER.
- BUT HOLLAND TOLD YOU
WE COULDN'T GET IT.
- I'M JUST LOOKING!
- ( sighs )
- Man: I'M TERRIBLY SORRY, MISS.
BUT THE LAST ONE OF THOSE
WE HAD IN STOCK
WAS JUST PURCHASED BY ANOTHER
CUSTOMER A FEW MINUTES AGO.
- OH.  OH, I SEE.
- I'M REALLY VERY SORRY.
- MISS TALHO,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- ( sighs )
WE'RE GONNA
BUY SOMETHING HEAVY!
WE'RE GONNA PUSH YOUR MUSCLES
ALL THE WAY
TO THEIR LIMIT, RENTON.
- EEK!
- ( all shouting, clamoring )
- ( grunting )
- ( music blaring )
- Talho ( slurring ):
I CANNOT BELIEVE
THAT YOU CAN'T EVEN
LIFT ONE OR TWO REFRIGERATORS.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- MISS TALHO?
ARE YOU HAVING A LOT OF FUN
HARASSING ME?
- ( laughing )
OH, I'M NOT HARASSING YOU,
RENTON,
JUST MAKING FUN OF YOU.
- ARE YOU ENJOYING
MAKING FUN OF ME?
- I DO NOT ENJOY IT AT ALL!
BUT IT IS AMUSING.
- YOU THINK IT'S AMUSING
MAKING FUN
OF SOMEBODY LIKE ME?
- IT'S GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
HOLLAND AND THE OTHER GUYS,
THEY DON'T CARE ABOUT ME.
RENTON, YOU PROMISED
THAT YOU WOULD DO ANYTHING
THAT I TOLD YOU TO, RIGHT?
THAT'S WHY...
- BUT I LIKE EUREKA.
WELL, I SUPPOSE
THAT EVEN SOMETHING LIKE LOVE
NEEDS SOME SORT OF A LESSON.
SO PLEASE JUST BE GENTLE
WITH ME, OKAY?
( grunting )
THAT HURTS.
- ( laughing )
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
DID YOU SERIOUSLY THINK
I WAS GONNA KISS YOU?
ANYWAY, A KID LIKE YOU
WHOSE HAIR
HASN'T EVEN ALL GROWN IN
HAS NO BUSINESS
TALKING ABOUT LOVE.
- I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT HAIR YOU MEAN,
BUT I DON'T SEE HOW IT MATTERS.
- I'M TALKING
ABOUT HAIR DOWN THERE!
- YEAH, WELL,
IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS
WHO I FALL IN LOVE WITH
OR ANYTHING ELSE, MISS TALHO.
- YES, IT IS MY BUSINESS,
EVEN IF IT ISN'T YOURS,
EVEN IF YOUR HAIR
HASN'T ALL GROWN IN.
- HMM?
- WHY DID YOU HAVE TO
COME ABOARD THE GEKKO?
I MEAN, YOU'RE...
HOLLAND...
- HMM?  MISS TALHO?
HEY?
- ( music blaring )
- ( music continuing )
- HEY, YOU PUNKS!
ALL THAT NOISE
IS REALLY PISSING ME OFF.
- HUH?
- HEY, ISN'T THAT TALHO?
- THAT CHICK IN ""ray=out"?
REALLY?
- MAN, DID WE TOTALLY LUCK OUT
OR WHAT?
- HUH? YOU THERE--YOU JUST
TOOK A PICTURE, DIDN'T YOU?
- WAIT!  I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A VERY GOOD IDEA.
- WAIT!  SIR, YOUR BILL?
- HUH?
- YOU TOOK A PICTURE
OF ME LOOKING BAD.
AND YOU USED A FLASH TOO!
- SHE'S THE REAL THING.
- HA!
- AH!
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
- ( all grunting )
- WHA-- LET GO OF ME.
- HEY, YOU JERKS
LEAVE MISS TALHO ALONE.
- RENTON!
- ( grunting )
- AH!
- RENTON!  RENTON!
- WELL, I THINK MISS TALHO
WILL HAVE TO PAY
FOR THAT CAMERA.
- I TOLD YOU NOT TO TOUCH HER!
( thinking )
CAN I REALLY DO THIS?
I HAVE TO
TO HELP MISS TALHO.
- ( laughing )
- RENTON!
- HERE GOES!
- AH NO!
- WAIT A SECOND.
WHAT'D YOU JUST SAY?
- ( grunting )
- WAIT!  LET ME GO!
STOP IT!
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'LL BE FINE.
I'M REALLY PRETTY GOOD
AT THIS KIND OF THING.
AH!
( crying out )
- LISTEN, PUNK,
WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO
TO OUR GIRL HERE?
- IT'S HOLLAND!
- AHH!
- IF YOU WANT TO GET
TO MISS TALHO,
YOU'VE GOT TO GO
THROUGH ME FIRST!
AND THAT'S
A REALLY LAME-ASS PUNCH.
- ( laughing )
THAT'S IT FOR YOU!
- AH!  HUH?
HUH?  HUH?
AHH!
- NO, THAT'S SOMETHING
ONLY BAD CHILDREN DO.
- SO IS THIS AN ANGEL
COME DOWN FROM HEAVEN...
FOR ME?
- AHHH!
- DAMN IT.  WHY ARE YOU
PUSHING YOUR LUCK AGAIN?
- ( grunting )
JERK.
- ( whimpering )
- OH MAN.
HMM.  HUH?
- ( whirring )
- ( grunts )
- AH!
THAT HURT. ( gasps )
( grunts )
AHHH!
NOT EVEN IN 100 MILLION YEARS
COULD YOU GET
ANYWHERE WITH TALHO!
- AH!
( man screaming )
- YOU AWAKE?
- MISS TALHO?
OH JEEZ!  I'M SORRY.
- WHAT ARE YOU APOLOGIZING FOR?
- HUH?
- MAN, YOU'RE SO STUPID,
YOU KNOW THAT?
I'VE NEVER SEEN A KID
ACT SO RECKLESS BEFORE.
BUT THANKS.
- WHERE IS EVERYONE?
- Hilda: EVERYONE'S OKAY.
NIRVASH SPED OVER TO HELP
AND IT'S FINE.
WE'RE ALL MAKING OUR WAY
BACK TO THE GEKKO NOW.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- HUH?  HEY, TALHO,
DON'T SUDDENLY SWITCH OVER
TO CLEAR MODE LIKE THAT.
- OH, IT'S FINE.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'VE GOT ENEMY
COMING THIS WAY.
BESIDES, DON'T YOU WANT
TO SEE SUCH A BEAUTIFUL SUNSET
WITH YOUR OWN EYES?
BECAUSE OTHERWISE,
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
START FEELING SUFFOCATED
IF YOU'RE ONLY WATCHING
THROUGH A MONITOR.
- MMM.
- IN ANY CASE, RENTON,
YOU DID A REALLY GOOD JOB TODAY.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN THROW UP.
- OH, COME ON,
I DON'T FEEL ANY MOTION SICKNESS
WHEN I LIFT BY MYSELF.
- AH.
- ( Renton gagging )
- ( women screaming )
- AH?  ( chuckles )
- HMM.
( sighs )
- AND SO YOU SCRATCHED UP
MY 606
AND THEN VOMITED
ALL OVER THE CABIN,
AND YET I HEAR
YOU REALLY MADE THE DAY.
IS THAT ABOUT RIGHT?
- YEAH, WELL, I GUESS SO.
- WELL, WITH ALL THAT
UNDER YOUR BELT,
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO GO AFTER
EUREKA FAIR AND SQUARE NOW.
- HUH?
- WHAT?  THAT THING
ABOUT YOU LIKING EUREKA?
( laughing )
EVERYONE KNOWS ABOUT IT.
- WHAT?
- ( laughing )
- WAIT A MINUTE, MISS TALHO!
YOU TOLD THEM EVERYTHING,
DIDN'T YOU?
EVEN AFTER YOU PROMISED
YOU WOULDN'T!
- NO WAY.
I HAVEN'T SAID A THING
TO ANYONE.
- HEY, WHERE'D YOU GET THAT?
- ( laughs )
- Mischa: TO MAKE A WOMAN HAPPY,
YOU SHOULD START WITH A GIFT.
YOUNG HOLLAND DID QUITE WELL.
- HUH?
WAIT, HOLLAND GOT IT?
BUT I THOUGHT HE SAID NO?
- SO WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- OH, YOU MEAN A GIFT
FOR EUREKA?
WELL, YOU SEE,
I DON'T THINK I HAVE MUCH
OF A CHANCE WITH HER ANYWAY,
SO IT ALL SEEMS
PRETTY HOPELESS.
- FOR GOODNESS' SAKES,
DON'T WHINE AND COMPLAIN.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GIVE HER ANYTHING.
ALL THAT REALLY MATTERS
ARE YOUR ACTIONS,
LIKE WHEN YOU PUT YOURSELF
IN DANGER TO PROTECT TALHO.
- ( thinking ) WELL,
WHEN ALL WAS SAID AND DONE,
IT WAS HOLLAND
THAT PROTECTED MISS TALHO.
- WHAT?!
THAT THROW-UPPER GUY?
- THAT'S A LIE, MAMA!
- SOMEDAY WHEN MY HEIGHT
GETS A LITTLE CLOSER TO HIS,
I WOULD REALLY LIKE
TO ASK HOLLAND...
- ( yawning )
...WHEN IT HAPPENED TO YOU,
WHAT WAS YOUR TASTE
OF FIRST LOVE LIKE?
TO BE CONTINUED!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator: THE BOY COMES
TO A REALIZATION
WHILE BATTLING
WITH THE CHILDREN
AND PROCEEDS
TO TAKE DECISIVE ACTION.
HOWEVER, WHAT HE DOES
IS ALSO PROOF
THAT HE IS STILL
A CHILD HIMSELF.
NEXT EPISODE, "CHILDHOOD."