- Eureka: I HAVE PEOPLE
THAT ARE DEAR TO ME.
LINCK, MAETER,
MAURICE,
AND RENTON.
I LIKE THEM A LOT.
I LOVE THEM.
PEOPLE DEAR TO ME,
MY FAMILY.
THEY TAUGHT ME
ALL SORTS OF THINGS
WHEN I REALLY DIDN'T
KNOW ANYTHING.
THEY ACCEPTED
EVERYTHING ABOUT ME
BEFORE EVEN I DID.
THEY LET ME BE
WHO I AM.
I WANT TO BE WITH
THOSE THAT I LOVE,
THAT I WANT TO PROTECT.
I WANT TO BE WITH LINCK.
I WANT TO BE WITH MAETER.
I WANT TO BE WITH MAURICE.
AND OF COURSE,
WITH RENTON.
BUT IF WISHING SO
CAUSES THOSE THAT ARE
DEAR TO ME TO BE LOST,
IF WISHING SO MAKES THE PLANET
WHERE THEY ALL LIVE DISAPPEAR,
I WILL STOP WISHING.
BUT IF IT CAN BE ALLOWED,
I WOULD LIKE TO
SEE THEM ONE MORE TIME.
I WANT TO SEE YOU.
I WANT TO SEE YOU,
RENTON.
- HERE YOU ARE.
- HMM?
- YOU THINK IT'S GOOD
FOR THE LEADER TO BE
SITTING AROUND,
WASTING TIME LIKE THIS?
- YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
A PILOT WITHOUT HIS L.F.O.
IS KIND OF LIKE
A FISH OUT OF WATER.
- I SEE.
- I APOLOGIZE FOR TAKING
THE SUPER IZUMO'S
FUEL LIKE THIS.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'M JUST TRYING TO DO
THINGS THE BEST I CAN.
I'M A MILITARY MAN.
- THANKS.
WHAT'D YOU DO
TO YOUR HAND?
- HMM?
OH, THIS?
DEWEY'S KIDS GOT AT ME.
- THE COLONEL TOLD US
THAT WE NEED TO SURVIVE
AND BECOME THE FOUNDATION
FOR THE ORDER OF THE NEW WORLD.
HE WASN'T LIKE
ANY OF YOU GUYS.
THE COLONEL WAS
REALLY NICE TO US.
EVEN THOUGH ALL OF US
HAVE SUCH FILTHY BODIES,
THE COLONEL SAID
WE WERE ALL BEAUTIFUL!
- THOSE CHILDREN WERE
PICKED UP AT RANDOM
FROM THE REFUGEE CAMP
IN WARSAW.
- THE TERRIBLE THINGS THAT
CAME OUT OF ETHNIC CLEANSING
ALMOST DON'T SEEM REAL.
- HUMANS ARE SUCH THAT IF THEY
DON'T SEE SOMETHING ON THE NEWS,
THEN THEIR MINDS AT LEAST
HAD NEVER REALLY EXISTED.
- SO I'VE NOTICED.
- HE WAS BORN INTO
THE WORLD CURSING IT.
- HUH?
- THE ONE WHO SAVED
THOSE UNWANTED CHILDREN
FROM DESPERATION
WAS A MAN WHO, LIKE THEM,
CURSED THE WORLD
AROUND HIM.
- I WONDER...
WHY DID MY BROTHER GO SO FAR
AS TO CURSE THE WORLD?
- WHO KNOWS?
YOU SHOULD PROBABLY ASK
A THERAPIST ABOUT THAT.
- ( chuckles )
TRUE ENOUGH.
- I'M THINKING ABOUT
ADOPTING THOSE CHILDREN.
- HUH?
- ATONEMENT FOR THOSE
WHO CREATED THIS WORLD,
AND THE ONES WHO
DESERVE TO BE CURSED.
- HMM.
ATONEMENT, HUH?
WELL, GOOD OLD DEWEY SURE
LEFT A LOT TO ATONE FOR.
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT.
- A LOT MORE THAN I THINK
ANY ONE INDIVIDUAL CAN HANDLE.
- GUESS I'LL HAVE TO
CARRY IT ON MY SHOULDERS.
- HMM?
- I'LL CARRY THE WEIGHT.
EVEN IF I HAVE TO SPEND
THE REST OF MY LIFE DOING IT.
- HOLLAND!
YOU'VE GOT SOME GUESTS.
- THE COLORS ON EUREKA
AND ANEMONE
WERE IN SOME UNKNOWN WAY
FULLY LINKED
TO THE CARDIO PULMONARY
FUNCTIONS OF COLONEL DEWEY.
- I'M AFRAID THAT IT'S
A CLEVER ADAPTATION
OF THE C.F.S. SYSTEM.
A SYSTEM THAT REVERSE TRANSFERS
TRAPAR WAVES.
HE SET THE WHOLE THING UP
SO THAT HIS OWN DEATH
WOULD FUNCTION
AS THE TRIGGER.
- THE COLONEL WISHED THAT
THE LIMIT OF QUESTIONS
NOT BE REACHED AFTER HIS PLAN
TO BREAK THROUGH THE ZONE
AND DESTROY THE CONTROL CLUSTER
WAS FULFILLED.
- EVEN IF THE PEOPLE PANICKED
AND THERE WAS A BRIEF MOMENT
WHERE THE LAWS OF PHYSICS
SEEM TO HAVE NO MEANING,
EVERYTHING WOULD CALM DOWN
RELATIVELY QUICKLY.
- BECAUSE THE SCUB CORALS
ALL WANT TO SURVIVE AS WELL.
- AND SO THE COLONEL
SET IN MOTION
A COMPLEX PLAN TO SET UP
EUREKA ABOARD THE NIRVASH,
OR MYSELF ABOARD THE END
AS A SUBSTITUTE
CONTROL CLUSTER.
- HE THEN PLUGGED IN AN
AUTOMATIC SELF-DESTRUCTION
PROTOCOL WHICH WAS
PROGRAMMED INTO THE COLLARS
THAT THE TWO OF THEM
WORE ALL THE TIME.
- SO IT TURNS OUT ALL OF US
WERE WRAPPED AROUND
HIS LITTLE FINGER
FROM THE BEGINNING.
- DAMN.
WHAT A BASTARD.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT DOESN'T EXPLAIN WHY
DESPITE EVERYTHING
WE STILL HAVEN'T REACHED
THE LIMIT OF QUESTIONS.
- I THINK IT'S
THANKS TO EUREKA.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- I'M PRETTY SURE THAT
EUREKA IS REFUSING
TO BE THE SUBSTITUTE
CONTROL CLUSTER.
AND SO...
- THAT MUST BE WHAT'S BEHIND
THE GLIMMER OF THIS COMPAC.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THE INTERVAL BETWEEN
ITS GLIMMERS,
AND THE INTERVAL
BETWEEN THE SIGNS
FROM THE SPHERE LOCATED
ABOVE THE TENSION MOUNTAINS
ARE AN EXACT MATCH.
- IN OTHER WORDS,
EUREKA IS...
- MM.
STILL ALIVE.
- ( door opens )
- Kids: HUH?
- TALHO.
- Kids: TALHO!
- WELCOME BACK, KIDS.
YOU ALL DID GREAT.
YOUR MAMA WOULD BE
SO PROUD.
OH.
- ( door opens )
- HEY, HOLLAND?
- STAND UP.
I JUST TOLD YOU
TO STAND UP!
- HOLLAND,
I COULDN'T DO
ANYTHING TO STOP IT.
I TRIED, BUT THERE WAS
NOTHING THAT I COULD DO!
( grunts )
- HOLLAND, HASN'T HE
GONE THROUGH ENOUGH?
- PLEASE, PUNCH ME.
PLEASE, PUNCH ME.
I COULDN'T SAVE MY FATHER.
I COULDN'T SAVE MY SISTER.
AND I COULDN'T PROTECT
EUREKA WHEN IT MATTERED.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
JUST A BRAT
WHO COULD NEVER
DO ANYTHING RIGHT.
I'M JUST THE VERY
WORST KIND OF LOSER.
ONE THAT TALKS BIG
BUT CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
- ARE YOU THROUGH?
- HUH?
- THEN GET YOURSELF
READY TO LEAVE RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE GOING.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"WE'RE GOING"?
WHERE?
- THAT SHOULD BE
FAIRLY OBVIOUS.
TO WHERE EUREKA IS.
- ( gasps )
- ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE ONLY ONE OBJECTIVE NOW.
TO CONTACT EUREKA WHO HAS
BECOME THE CONTROL CLUSTER,
AND CONDUCT AN ARBITRATION
BETWEEN HUMANS AND SCUB CORALS
ONE MORE TIME.
HOWEVER,
THERE IS A PROBLEM.
THE SIGNALS COMING FROM
EUREKA'S LOCATION
ARE GRADUALLY WEAKENING
AS TIME GOES ON.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP
CALLING OUT TO EUREKA
SO THAT SHE CAN STAY CONSCIOUS
UNTIL WE CAN GET THERE.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT
ONLY YOU CAN DO.
ARE WE READY?
- EVERYTHING IS READY
ON THIS END.
WE CAN LAUNCH ANYTIME.
WOW, RENTON.
YOU'VE TURNED OUT TO BE
AN ATTRACTIVE GUY.
- YEAH.
- Holland: GOT IT?
THIS COMPAC DRIVE
IS USING A SPECIAL SYSTEM
TO DISPLAY ALL
THE TRAPAR INTERFERENCE
CAUGHT ON THE GEKKO'S
TRAPAR RADARS.
LOOK HERE.
USING THIS SYSTEM,
WE'RE GOING TO ATTEMPT TO START
COMMUNICATING FROM OUR END.
I BELIEVE THAT IF
SHE REPLIES TO ANYONE,
IT'LL BE YOU GUYS,
EUREKA'S FAMILY,
AND NOBODY ELSE.
- HOLLAND,
WHAT I WANT TO KNOW IS
WHEN WE FINALLY
REACH THE PLACE
AND FIND EUREKA,
WHAT IS IT THAT WE'RE
SUPPOSED TO DO THEN?
- UHH-- SORRY, BUT I REALLY
DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA.
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
- HUH?
- NEVER BEG.
AND EARN BY WINNING.
OR ELSE YOU WON'T
GET ANYTHING.
THAT'S RIGHT.
ISN'T IT, HOLLAND?
- UH-- HMM.
I DON'T THINK THOSE WORDS
WERE AIMED AT ME.
- HUH?
- I'M SURE IT WAS A GIFT TO YOU.
IT JUST HAPPENED TO
COME THROUGH ME.
FROM ADROC THURSTON
TO RENTON THURSTON.
- RIGHT.
- I'M JEALOUS OF EUREKA.
SHE HAS SO MANY PEOPLE THAT
WOULD RISK THEIR LIVES FOR HER.
- DON'T BE UNGRATEFUL.
YOU HAVE SOMEONE THERE FOR YOU.
A MAN NAMED DOMINIC.
- ( gasps )
CAPTAIN!
- ( giggles )
YOU'RE RIGHT.
- HUH?
- I DO HAVE
DOMINIC AT MY SIDE.
- SOMEONE WHO'S
MUCH MORE HANDSOME
THAN EUREKA'S BOYFRIEND.
- HMM.
WELL, I SUPPOSE THIS TIME
I'LL HAVE TO LET
RENTON THURSTON
PLAY THE ROLE
OF THE HERO.
- APPROACHING TARGET.
THERE ARE ONLY 250 METERS
IN THE SMALLEST GAP.
- THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
DOGGIE, TAKE US UP!
- Moondoggie:
ROGER THAT!
- RETURNING THE GEKKO TO
STANDARD PARALLEL FLIGHT.
- CHECKING WHICH TRAJECTORY
FLIGHTS ARE POSSIBLE.
IF WE USE CORRIDOR 999,
WE CAN REACH IT
IN FOUR HOURS.
IT'S SIX HOURS TO
THE BIAS POINT.
- IT'LL TAKE SIX HOURS?
THAT'S REALLY PUSHING IT.
- I JUST HOPE THAT SHE CAN
KEEP IT UP FOR THAT LONG.
- NOT GOOD.
CONFIRMED ANTIBODY CORALIANS.
THEY'RE AT OH-100
AND OH-140.
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF CORRIDOR 999.
- BUT HOW CAN THAT BE?
IMPOSSIBLE.
IT'S OUR SHORTEST ROUTE.
- WE'VE GOT TO
GO THROUGH ANYWAY.
- YOU DON'T THINK
I KNOW THAT?
EVERYONE,
RIG THE SHIP FOR COMBAT.
AFTER FIRING THE MAIN CANNONS
AND THE A.A.M'S,
WE'LL USE OUR BOOSTERS
TO BREAK RIGHT THROUGH
THE MIDDLE OF THEM.
- All: ROGER THAT!
- DIRECT HIT ON
THE STARBOARD REAR.
- REAR BOOSTER PRESSURE
IS FALLING.
NO GOOD. WE WON'T MAKE ESCAPE
VELOCITY IF THIS KEEPS UP.
- ( groans )
- I'LL FIGHT THEM WITH YOU.
- ( gasps )
- DON'T WORRY, RENTON.
YOU JUST LEAVE
ALL THE FIGHTING TO US.
- BUT HOLLAND--
- THE ONLY THING
YOU NEED TO DO NOW
IS TO KEEP YOUR MIND
ON EUREKA.
YOU'VE GOT TO TRUST US.
OKAY?
- ALL RIGHT, HOLLAND.
- Kids: MAMA!
MAMA!  ANSWER US.
MAMA!  MAMA, PLEASE.
WE'RE SCARED.
- Maeter:
IT'S NO GOOD.
SHE WON'T ANSWER US
NO MATTER WHAT.
- DON'T WORRY, MAETER.
I'M POSITIVE
MAMA'S LISTENING TO US.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
- MAURICE.
- HUH?
- I WANT YOU TO HOLD
ONTO THIS FOR AWHILE.
IT'S SOMETHING
IMPORTANT TO ME.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I'M GONNA GO DOWN
AND WORK ON THE NIRVASH.
- HUH?
- MAYBE IF I USE
NIRVASH'S AMITA DRIVE
I CAN MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN.
MAYBE IT WILL START TO MOVE.
AND IF SO...
ALL RIGHT, MAURICE,
LISTEN UP.
YOU'RE THE BIG BROTHER
IN THIS FAMILY.
SO YOU HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF MAETER AND LINCK.
- MM.
- GOOD.
THEN I'LL HEAD OUT.
- Maurice: OH, WAIT.
- HUH?
- RENTON, TAKE THIS.
I WANT YOU TO HAVE IT.
A GOOD LUCK CHARM.
- HEY, WAIT.
ISN'T THIS EUREKA'S?
- YOU'RE GOING, RIGHT?
BECAUSE THE NIRVASH WON'T
MOVE WITHOUT OUR MAMA.
- ( sighs )
THAT'S RIGHT.
ZERO AMMO LEFT
IN THE A.A.M.
- THAT MEANS ALL WE HAVE LEFT
ARE THE HOMING LASERS.
DOGGIE, MAKE THE HIGH SPEED
EVASION EVEN FASTER!
- IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HALF OUR ENGINES ARE DEAD.
- Holland:
DON'T GIVE UP!
IF WE LET OURSELVES
GET DISCOURAGED, IT'S OVER.
THE ANSWER'S OUT THERE.
THERE'S AN ANSWER
SOMEWHERE OUT THERE!
- Renton: NIRVASH,
LISTEN TO ME.
YOU AND I,
WE'VE BEEN TRAVELING TOGETHER.
EVER SINCE YOU FELL DOWN
ONTO MY HOUSE.
WE'VE MET ALL
SORTS OF PEOPLE,
AND THEN PARTED
WITH THEM.
THEY'RE ALL VERY SPECIAL
MEMORIES TO ME.
BUT THROUGH ALL THIS JOURNEY,
EUREKA HAS ALWAYS
BEEN AT MY SIDE.
WE'VE BEEN TRAVELING TOGETHER
ALL THIS TIME,
AND I WOULDN'T TRADE
A SINGLE MINUTE OF IT.
OH, PLEASE, NIRVASH!
I DON'T WANT EVERYTHING
TO END LIKE THIS!
I REALLY NEED EUREKA
AT MY SIDE!
- ( shouting )
- A DIRECT HIT?
- NO, THIS EXPLOSION
CAME FROM INSIDE.
FROM INSIDE!
- NO WAY.
- HOLLAND, TALHO,
I'VE GOT AN UNKNOWN TRAPAR
SIGNAL FROM THE UPPER DECK.
- WHAT?!
- Kids: WHOA.
- WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- IT'S THE NIRVASH.
- BUT HOW DID IT
GET THAT WAY?
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON HERE?
- Maurice: IT'S RENTON.
- HUH?
- HE'S THE ONE
MAKING IT ALL HAPPEN.
WE KNOW IT FOR SURE.
RENTON AND NIRVASH
ARE GONNA SAVE MAMA.
IT'S RENTON.
- WE GOT A CONNECTION.
RENTON, WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON?
- THE AMITA DRIVE
IS RESPONDING TO ME.
- WHAT?!
- I DON'T EXACTLY KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON,
BUT IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
I CAN MAKE IT.
- YOU MEAN BY YOURSELF?
- NIRVASH FINALLY ANSWERED
YOUR CALLS, DIDN'T HE?
- THAT'S RIGHT, MAURICE.
- PLEASE, YOU GOTTA
GO AND SAVE MAMA.
OUR PAPA'S THE ONLY ONE
IN THE WORLD
THAT CAN SAVE OUR MAMA!
- ( exhales )
YEAH, I THINK SO TOO.
- Holland:
YOU'D BETTER GO, RENTON.
- HUH?
- IF SHE'S THE ONE YOU LOVE,
GO GET HER BACK.
YOU'RE A MAN, RIGHT?
- ( grunts )
I...!
CAN...!
FLY!
I'M SORRY, EUREKA.
I HAVE DEFEAT SOME OF
YOUR FELLOW CORALIANS.
AND IF YOU TELL ME
THAT'S A SIN,
THEN I'LL JUST HAVE TO CARRY
ITS WEIGHT ON MY SHOULDERS.
BECAUSE NO MATTER WHAT,
I HAVE TO GO WHERE YOU ARE,
EUREKA!
( shouts )
- AND THERE HE GOES.
- YEAH, THERE HE GOES,
ALL RIGHT.
- AW, DRAT.
- HMM?
- JEEZ, IT WENT BY TOO FAST.
IT WAS MY LAST CHANCE, TOO.
- THAT'S TOO BAD.
- HUH?
- WELL, YOU'LL HAVE
PLENTY OF TIME
WHEN HE GETS BACK.
- YOU GUYS DON'T GET IT.
- WHAT?
- BEFORE ALL THIS,
HE WAS SOMEONE WHO COULD
NEVER REALLY FIT
WITHIN A FRAME.
BUT HE FINALLY GREW UP ENOUGH TO
JUMP OVER THE FRAME CALLED US.
- THERE'S NO WAY THAT RENTON
WILL BE RETURNING.
RENTON HAS FLOWN
OUT OF THE NEST.
THE NEST CALLED
GEKKOSTATE.
ALL OF US NEED TO
LET HIM GO.
OUR SON.
- IT'S JUST LIKE HIM
TO GRADUATE WITHOUT CONSENT.
I'LL TAKE GOOD CARE OF
THE LITTLE ONES FOR YOU.
JUST MAKE SURE TO WIN
EUREKA BACK, RENTON.
- ( gasps )
EUREKA.
PLEASE WAIT FOR ME,
I'M COMING!
( shouts )
( gasps, shouts )
( grunting )
- Eureka: RENTON.
- ( grunting )
- RENTON.
- ( gasps )
EUREKA!
( screams )
( gasps )
DON'T JUST SAY BYE-BYE.
DON'T TRY TO GO
BY YOURSELF, EUREKA.
- YOU CAME, RENTON.
( crying )
YOU REALLY CAME.
- I PROMISED YOU,
DIDN'T I?
THAT I WOULD MAKE SURE TO
ALWAYS PROTECT YOU, EUREKA.
AND THAT I WOULD ALWAYS
BE TOGETHER WITH YOU.
- BUT YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I CAN'T GO BACK ANYMORE.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA
MAKE THE CHOICE
TO NO LONGER BE A CORALIAN
IN ORDER TO
SAVE THIS PLANET,
THEN I CHOOSE TO
NO LONGER BE A HUMAN.
- ( gasps )
- I TRULY
CHERISH THIS PLANET
WHERE I WAS ABLE
TO FIND YOU.
AND EVERYONE WHO LIVES HERE
ON THIS PLANET ARE DEAR TO ME.
BUT I'M JUST NOT WILLING
TO LOSE YOU FOR THEIR SAKE.
- ( gasps )
- LOOKS GOOD ON YOU.
- RENTON.
- EUREKA,
LET'S BECOME ONE.
BECAUSE I WON'T LET YOU
BE ALL BY YOURSELF.
- IF I'M TOGETHER
WITH YOU, RENTON,
I CAN DO ANYTHING.
- MAMA.
- All: AND RENTON!
- Nirvash: THANK YOU.
- NIRVASH?
- RENTON, EUREKA,
YOUR EMOTIONS HAVE BEEN
ENGRAVED FOREVER
INTO MY COMPAC.
FINALLY, I WILL BE ABLE
TO OBTAIN ENLIGHTENMENT.
NOW LIVE ON THIS PLANET.
- Both: HUH?
- GO AND LIVE TOGETHER,
AND SHOW THE WAY TO ALL
THAT LIVE ON THIS
PRECIOUS WORLD,
USING THE BRILLIANT LIGHT
NAMED HOPE.
- NIRVASH.
( grunts )
- NOT ALL OF THE BEINGS
CAN REMAIN ON THIS LAND.
HALF WILL DEPART
TOGETHER WITH US.
HOWEVER, RENTON,
EUREKA,
IF ON THIS PLANET
AN EVOLUTION TAKES PLACE
FOR THE BETTER,
AND THE TWO ARE ABLE
TO BECOME ONE,
WE WILL RETURN
AND SHOW OURSELVES
IN FRONT OF YOU ONCE AGAIN.
I BELIEVE THAT SUCH A DAY
WILL SOME DAY COME.
- Eureka:
THANK YOU, NIRVASH.
- THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
- RENTON,
LET'S GO HOME.
- YEAH,
HOME TO OUR PLANET.
- Holland:
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- CAN IT BE THAT THIS IS--
- THIS IS THE SECOND
SUMMER OF LOVE.
- All: HUH?
- FROM HERE ON,
YOU WILL USE THIS UNIVERSE,
AND WE WILL USE
A SEPARATE UNIVERSE
TO SEEK OUT A WAY THAT
SCUB CORALS AND HUMANS
CAN COEXIST SIDE BY SIDE.
- WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THERE REALLY IS NO REASON
WHY THERE CANNOT BE MORE THAN
ONE PATH OF EVOLUTION.
IT WAS FUN BEING WITH YOU
ALL THIS TIME.
YOU HAVE MY THANKS.
- BUT GONZY, IT CAN'T BE
THAT YOU'RE A--
( gasps )
OH, BROTHER.
TO THINK THAT A CORALIAN
HAS BEEN WATCHING OVER US
THE ENTIRE TIME.
- HEY, HOLLAND?
DO YOU THINK THAT MAYBE...
- I THINK IT'S OBVIOUS.
RENTON CHOSE TO BECOME
ONE OF THEM.
A TRUE HERO.
MORE SO THAN HIS OWN FATHER.
- Kids: WOW!
- THANKS FOR THE FOOD.
- HEY, WIPE YOUR HANDS
BEFORE YOU EAT.
- Linck: IT'S OKAY.
- Maeter: NO, IT'S NOT.
- Linck: HEY, DON'T TELL ME
WHAT TO DO.
- Maeter: THAT'S NASTY.
COME ON, LINCK.
- HMM.
- Maurice: GRANDPA?
- HUH?
- AREN'T YOU GONNA EAT?
YOUR FOOD'S
GONNA GET COLD.
- OH, YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I GUESS I'LL HAVE TO
EAT IT QUICKLY.
- WAS IT A LOT OF
TROUBLE FOR YOU?
I MEAN,
THE FACT THAT WE CAME HERE?
- TO EAT A BIG BURG.
- HUH?
- IT HAS LONG BEEN
THE TRADITION OF THE
THURSTONS TO HAVE A BIG BURG
WHEN WE HAVE CONFIRMED
OUR FAMILY TIES.
NOW, LET'S EAT.
YOU'D BETTER HURRY UP.
IF WE DON'T,
THE MOON WILL RISE.
- MM!
- Grandpa:
EVERY MEMBER OF MY FAMILY
LEAVES THIS TOWN.
BUT YOUR PAPA, RENTON,
WAS THE ONLY ONE THAT
ACTUALLY CAME BACK.
- Maurice: REALLY?
- I NOW HAVE THREE INCOMPARABLE
GREAT GRANDCHILDREN,
AND THAT IS PROOF
MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
- Maeter:
HEY, GRANDPA!
OH, NO, LOOK!
THE TRAIN IS PULLING UP.
- OH, LET'S HURRY.
- ( kids giggle )
- COME ON NOW, CHILDREN.
YOU GOTTA SLOW DOWN.
YOU SHOULDN'T MAKE
AN OLD MAN RUN SO MUCH.
HUH?
- MAETER, WHY DO YOU HAVE
YOUR HANDS LIKE THAT?
- I'M WISHING ON A STAR
AS HARD AS I CAN
FOR MAMA AND RENTON
TO COME BACK
AND FINALLY
BE WITH US AGAIN.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- AND ME.
- YES, HURRY AND COME BACK
WITH THAT YOUNG LADY
OF YOURS, RENTON.
YOUR LOVELY CHILDREN
ARE WAITING FOR YOU.
- Renton and Eureka:
THE END.