- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- YOU KNOW, THIS PICTURE
IS KIND OF EMBARRASSING.
- IF YOU HAVE ENOUGH TIME
TO BE EMBARRASSED,
YOU SHOULD CHECK OUT THE OTHER
PHOTOS I HAVE OF YOU GUYS.
- SURE, WHY NOT?
BUT WHY RUSH ON
GETTING THROUGH ALL THIS?
- SOON, THE GEKKO WILL ARRIVE
AT THE VODARAC HEADQUARTERS,
THE VODARA SHRINE.
- VODARA SHRINE?
- IT'S WHERE THE ONE
THAT NORB CALLS SAKUYA IS.
WHEN WE FINALLY GET THERE,
WE WON'T HAVE TIME
FOR YOU TO CHECK
THESE PICTURES OUT.
- WE HAVE TO GET THIS PUBLISHED
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE
USING ANY MEANS WE CAN.
I FEEL BAD THAT AS A RESULT
OF EVERYTHING RIGHT NOW,
WE HAVE TO USE YOU
AND EUREKA LIKE THIS.
BUT IN ORDER TO GET OVER
THE CURRENT SITUATION,
WE NEED AN ABUNDANCE OF SPEED
AND THE REAL TRUTH.
YOU CAN REST ASSURED
WHEN YOU COME BACK,
BOTH OF YOU WILL BE FAMOUS.
- Renton:
IT'S ALL RIGHT WITH ME
IF WE NEVER END UP
FAMOUS AT ALL.
- Woman:
WELCOME BACK, MASTER NORB.
- ( groans )
I APPRECIATE
THE GREETING,
BUT YOU DO KNOW WHAT JOB
COMES WITH THE FACT
THAT I'VE RETURNED,
DON'T YOU?
YOU HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN?
- NO, WE HAVEN'T.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
THAT LAND HAS ALREADY
BEEN TAKEN OVER
BY THOSE THAT ARE EVIL.
- SO YOU BELIEVE
THEY'RE EVIL, HUH?
THOSE MEN
BELIEVE IN THEIR HEARTS
THAT WHAT THEY KNOW
IS THE TRUTH.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU'RE
DOING WELL, OLD LADY.
- YOU SEEM TO BE
DOING WELL YOURSELF.
WHERE ARE THOSE CHILDREN?
- Renton: MA'AM.
- OH?
THERE YOU ARE.
- ( laughing )
- I WANT TO DRINK
THAT TEA AGAIN.
- YEAH, THAT SWEET RED TEA.
- OF COURSE.
YOU'VE ALL GROWN UP
IN THE SHORT WHILE
THAT I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU.
- OH, BOY.
DON'T SAY THAT.
YOU SOUND LIKE A RELATIVE
I HAVEN'T SEEN IN AWHILE.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
I MEAN IT.  SEE?
- YOU THINK SO?
I GUESS.
- I GREW TALLER TOO,
DIDN'T I?
- ME TOO, ME TOO!
- YES, YES.
ALL OF YOU HAVE GROWN
SINCE WE WERE
LAST TOGETHER.
NOW, I HAVEN'T SEEN
YOUR MAMA YET.
WHERE IS SHE HIDING?
- I UNDERSTAND THAT IT'S HARD
FOR YOU TO SEE HER AGAIN.
IF I WERE IN YOUR SITUATION,
I'M SURE I'D BE FEELING
THE SAME WAY RIGHT NOW.
IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO SEE HER,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
BUT EUREKA,
I REALLY THINK
IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT YOU MEET
THESE PEOPLE AGAIN.
- I KNOW,
BUT TALHO, I'M...
- NOT A HUMAN BEING?
THAT DOESN'T MATTER AT ALL.
LISTEN TO ME, EUREKA.
- ( gasps )
- IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF YOU'RE HUMAN
OR CORALIAN.
WE'RE BOTH CREATURES WHO
LIVE TOGETHER ON THIS PLANET.
AND I WANT YOU TO MEET
THE PEOPLE OF THE VODARAC.
I KNOW THEY'LL TREAT YOU
JUST LIKE RENTON HAS.
IT'LL BE FINE.
- ( sighs )
I CAN'T DO IT, TALHO.
YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY ARE
A BLOCKHEAD SOMETIMES.
- IT'S BEEN 40 YEARS.
- HAS IT REALLY
BEEN THAT LONG?
- HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO GET IN THERE?
THAT PLACE IS...
- CONTROLLED BY
THE MIYOTO SECT.
- THEY ARE THE ONES THAT FOLLOW
A TERRIBLE EVIL TEACHING.
THOSE THAT FOLLOW
THE TEACHINGS OF MASTER NORB
HAVE BEEN OPPRESSED,
AND SPEND THEIR DAYS WISHING
ONLY FOR THE MASTER'S RETURN.
- DON'T THEY KNOW THAT
IT'S MUCH BETTER TO LIVE ON
THAN TO DIE
FOLLOWING MY TEACHINGS?
- SO HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO TAKE THIS FILTHY OLD MAN
INTO A PLACE LIKE THAT
WITHOUT GETTING CAUGHT?
- CURRENTLY
IN THE VODARA SHRINE,
MANY REFUGEES
ARE FLOODING IN.
- ALL THANKS TO THE BATTLES
AGAINST THE ANTI-BODY CORALIANS?
- YES.  TAKE A LOOK.
- OH-- OH, MAN.
- THEY'RE REFUGEES
HEADING TO THE VODARA SHRINE.
THE OPPRESSION AGAINST
THE BELIEVERS OF THE VODARAC
HAS BECOME WORSE
THAN EVER BEFORE.
THE ONLY PLACE WHERE
THEY CAN ESCAPE TO
IS THE VODARA SHRINE.
FURTHERMORE, MUCH TO
OUR GOOD FORTUNE,
THE SHRINE IS HOLDING
A FESTIVAL.
- WAIT, YOU DON'T MEAN...
- YES.  A BRAND NEW
SAINT HAS BEEN BORN.
- A SAINT?
THEY'RE STILL DOING THAT?
THEY'RE ALL A BUNCH OF IDIOTS.
- AND SO WE'RE GOING
TO USE THIS FESTIVAL
TO QUIETLY ENTER
THE VODARA SHRINE
NIRVASH AND ALL?
- MM-HMM.
- YEAH, THAT COULD WORK.
- BUT BEFORE THAT...
- HUH?  WHOA!
- HUH?
- HEY, LET GO!
LET GO OF ME!
I ORDER YOU TO LET GO.
DAMN IT, KEEP THOSE
IMPURE HANDS OFF ME!
I AM MASTER NORB!
STOP-- AAH!
YOU GOT SOAP IN MY EYE.
ALL OF YOU ARE GONNA
GO TO HELL FOR THIS.
- Eureka: HEY.
- Talho: WHAT?
- I WAS JUST WONDERING,
WHY ARE THERE CREATURES
LIVING IN THIS WORLD?
- THAT'S A DIFFICULT
QUESTION TO ANSWER.
- I'M SORRY.
- I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT
VERY WELL,
BUT I DON'T THINK
YOU HAVE TO THINK ABOUT
THE WORLD AND THE CREATURES
ON IT AS SEPARATE THINGS.
- OH?
- THE WORLD IS ITS CREATURES,
AND THE CREATURES
ARE THEIR WORLD.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT
THIS KID HERE
IS TRYING TO TEACH ME.
- OH?
ARE YOU HAPPY
YOU'RE HAVING A BABY?
- ( chuckles )
( sighs )
HALF AND HALF I THINK.
AFTER ALL, I'M GONNA HAVE TO
DEAL WITH TWO KIDS NOW.
- YOU MEAN, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TWO BABIES?
- NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
SOMETIMES HOLLAND IS
LIKE A YOUNG KID,
JUST LIKE RENTON IS.
- I DON'T THINK RENTON'S
A YOUNG CHILD ANYMORE, TALHO.
- WHAT?  YOU'RE MAD AT ME?
- I'M NOT MAD.
- OF COURSE YOU'RE MAD.
- I AM NOT, TALHO.
- YOU'RE SO CUTE.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
I SEE.  PILLOW FIGHT!
- ( grunts )
- ( chuckles )
( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( both chuckling )
- WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING?!
HONESTLY, I WAS WONDERING
WHAT YOU WERE DOING
INSTEAD OF
EATING YOUR SUPPER.
LOOK HERE, TALHO,
YOU'VE GOT TO ACCEPT
THAT YOUR BODY
IS NOT JUST FOR
YOU ALONE ANYMORE.
- YEAH.
OH, WELL.
WE BETTER GO EAT.
- HUMAN BEINGS ARE
REALLY AMAZING.
- ( gasps )
- HMM?
- I MEAN, YOU CAN ACTUALLY
CARRY A WHOLE NEW LIFE
INSIDE OF YOU.
- EUREKA,
BIOLOGICALLY,
YOU'RE AS CAPABLE
OF BEARING CHILDREN
AS ANY HUMAN IS.
- WHAT?
- WITH 40 YEARS
OF DIRT OFF MY SKIN,
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA
CATCH A COLD.
- ( laughing )
- WELL, WE'VE TAKEN CARE OF
THE BIGGEST OBSTACLE
TO GETTING IN.
- NOW WE JUST NEED
TO TAKE EUREKA--
- ( door opens )
- Kids: MAMA.
- ( gasps )
WAIT.
SO, THIS IS THE PATH THAT
YOU HAVE CHOSEN FOR YOURSELF.
- ( gasps )
OH, MA'AM.
( crying )
- IT'S JUST ABOUT TIME.
WE ALL NEED TO GET READY.
- HMM.
- Renton: HOLLAND.
- YEAH?
- WHAT NOW?
WHAT IS IT THAT
WE'RE GONNA BE DOING?
- WE'RE GOING TO INFILTRATE
THE VODARAC HEADQUARTERS.
- ( gasps )
- I'M GONNA HAVE YOU GUYS
MEET WITH SAKUYA.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
THAT WE'RE EVER GOING TO
BE ABLE TO SAVE THIS PLANET.
- WE'RE MEETING SAKUYA?
WHAT SHOULD WE DO THEN?
- DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S FOR
THE OLD MAN TO SAY.
- JUST BE THERE.
WHEN THE DECISION
HAS FINALLY BEEN MADE,
ALL WILL BE
SET IN MOTION.
FROM THAT POINT ON,
THERE WILL BE NO TURNING BACK.
- ( sighs )
- MM.
- ( murmuring )
- Maeter:
IS MAMA GONNA GO AWAY SOMEWHERE?
- I DON'T WANT THAT.
I DON'T WANT MAMA
TO LEAVE WITHOUT US EVER.
- ME NEITHER.
- Dominic:
THE LIMIT OF QUESTIONS.
IT'S JUST A HYPOTHESIS FOR
INFORMATION QUANTUM MECHANICS.
- ACCORDING TO ANALYSIS
BY THE MEMBERS OF AGEHA,
IT SEEMS THAT IT IS
NOT JUST A THEORY.
THIS MEANS THAT WE ARE
ON THE EDGE RIGHT NOW.
HOW THINGS WILL TURN OUT
FROM HERE ON,
WHETHER OR NOT
THE WORLD WILL END,
EVERYTHING DEPENDS ON WHAT
WE DO AT THIS VERY MOMENT.
AND HOW WE ALL ACT.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( chuckles )
SCUB CORALS COPY
EVERYTHING THAT EXISTS
AND TURNS IT INTO INFORMATION.
THEN AFTER
THE MATERIAL PLAIN COLLAPSES,
THEY WILL HEAD TO THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE EVENT HORIZON
TO BEGIN AN ENTIRELY
NEW EXISTENCE.
- THE LAST CHAPTER
OF THE AGEHA PROJECT.
RIGHT, SIR?
- IT JUST MEANS THAT ADROC
FORESAW WHAT WAS COMING.
EVEN HOW THE SCUB CORALS
WILL FINALLY DECIDE
UPON THE MOMENT
WHEN WE HAVE SURPASSED
THE ABSOLUTE LIMIT
OF QUESTIONS.
- HUH?
- UTTER NONSENSE.
- FIRST OF ALL,
THE LIMIT OF QUESTIONS
WOULD NEVER HAVE BEEN REACHED
IF THE SCUB CORALS
HAD NOT ARRIVED
ON THIS PLANET.
WHY SHOULD I HAVE TO BOARD
AN ARK TOGETHER WITH INTRUDERS
THAT NEVER ONCE APOLOGIZED
FOR THEIR ACTIONS?
I CHOOSE TO LIVE
ON THIS LAND FOREVER.
EVEN IF IT MEANS
DESTROYING THE ARK.
- HUH?  COLONEL...
- WHAT IS THE CURRENT
STATUS OF OUR TROOPS?
- SIR!  THE ATTACK SQUAD
IS ALREADY ON ITS WAY
TO THE VODARA SHRINE.
- THE GALAXY WILL
GO THERE AS WELL.
I HAVE SOMETHING SPECIAL
THAT I WANT IT TO DO.
- I MAY BE OUT OF LINE...
BUT PLEASE STOP REFERRING
TO ANEMONE AS AN "IT."
SHE HAS A PERSONALITY
OF HER OWN, YOU KNOW.
- ( laughing )
THAT'S TRUE.
IT'S JUST AS YOU SAY,
SHE HAS A PERSONALITY
OF HER OWN NOW.
I WAS ABOUT TO
FORGET THAT.
THANK YOU.
- ( gasps )
GULLIVER?
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
- SO THIS IS THE HEADQUARTERS
OF THE VODARAC.
- WHERE MISS SAKUYA LIVES.
- ( camera shutter clicking )
- I REALLY WANTED TO
SEE THIS ONCE IN MY LIFE.
AMAZING.
- DO YOU MEAN THE LOVE PARADE?
IT'S FROM AN ANCIENT STORY.
- THE ONE THAT WAS BORN IS NOT
A TRUE SAINT OF THE VODARAC,
AND YET THEY DO
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
- Norb:
DOESN'T THE MIYOTO SECT REALIZE
THAT THE REASON WHY SAKUYA
CLOSED HER HEART
WAS TO PROTECT THIS PLACE?
THEY REALLY ARE IDIOTS.
- A HUGE WALL.
- Eureka:
ON THE OTHER SIDE...
- Renton:
MISS SAKUYA IS WAITING.
- Both: HMM.
- LADY SAKUYA,
BLESSED ONE WHO CARRIES
THE BURDEN OF ALL OUR SINS
UPON HER WISE SHOULDERS,
THE SAINT, NEWLY BORN,
WILL ARRIVE
AT YOUR EXALTED FEET.
- ( gasps )
- WOW.
- GEE, I WONDER WHERE
WE ARE RIGHT NOW.
- LET'S JUST TAKE A LOOK.
- Maurice:
LEAVE IT ALONE, LINCK.
- I'M JUST GONNA TAKE
A PEEK OUTSIDE.
- ( gasps )
- SIT STILL.
WE'RE GONNA GET CAUGHT.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
- NO, I DON'T WANNA!
( shouts )
- ( gasps )
- HUH?
- ( all gasp )
- HMM?
- ( crowd gasping,
chattering )
- WHAT THE--?
- Woman:
IT'S THE WHITE DEVIL!
- RUN FOR IT!
- ( crowd screaming )
- THIS IS ALICE-1.
CRESCENT RABBIT,
TEA TIME, TEA TIME!
- ( screaming )
- THIS IS RED QUEEN,
ROGER.
- THE KING'S WITH YOU TOO.
- THIS IS CRESCENT RABBIT,
ROGER THAT.
HUMPTY, DON'T YOU BE
RUNNING LATE. YOU COPY?
- YEAH, I WON'T.
- ( gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- SORRY, MAMA.
- LEAVE THAT FOR LATER.
LET'S GO.
MASTER NORB!
- ( grunts )
- ( grunting )
- ( all gasp )
- IS THAT WHERE WE'RE GOING?
- YEAH.
- I'M SCARED.
- IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- ( tires screech )
- THIS IS ALICE-1.
WE'RE GOING TO CREATE
A DEFENSE LINE HERE.
- HOLLAND!
- RENTON, GET GOING.
UNTIL THEY BRING US A RESULT,
WE'RE GONNA DEFEND THIS PLACE.
GOT THAT?!
- THOSE ARE...
- SOME MISGUIDED FOOLS.
THEY ALL MELDED WITH
COMPAC DRIVES
TO TRY TO OPEN
SAKUYA'S HEART BACK UP,
AND DIED IN THE PROCESS.
- ( gasps )
- NONE OF THEM COULD
POSSIBLY BE SAINTS.
THIS IS A COLLECTION OF FOOLS
WITH NO VALUE.
- THEY'RE A BUNCH
OF DEAD PEOPLE?
- EW, THIS IS REALLY GROSS.
- I'M GETTING SCARED.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, LINCK.
- ( tires screech )
- ( grunts )
( gasps )
WE'RE AT A DEAD END.
THERE'S NO PLACE TO GO.
- HOLD ON A MINUTE.
- ( all gasp )
- OKAY, BETTER HOLD ON TIGHT.
- ( gasping )
- ( screaming )
- ( gasps )
IT'S GOTTEN BRIGHTER.  HUH?
- ( whimpering )
- LISTEN, EVERYTHING IS
GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
PLEASE DON'T CRY.
- ( grunts )
HEY, MASTER NORB,
WOULD YOU MIND
WARNING US NEXT TIME?
HUH?
HEY, UM, WAIT, MASTER NORB.
DON'T DO THAT.
IT'S DANGEROUS.
THIS DEEP DOWN UNDERGROUND,
THE TRAPARS COULD--
- DON'T WORRY.
THERE ARE NO TRAPARS DOWN HERE.
- HUH?
BUT WHY?
- RIGHT NOW IN THAT FORM,
TRAPARS ARE
NOTHING BUT POISON.
AT LEAST FOR SAKUYA.
- EUREKA.
- MM.
- WHAT IS IT?
- Norb: SAKUYA'S BEDROOM.
- ( gasps )
- SAKUYA IS SLEEPING
DEEP INSIDE THAT SPHERE.
NOW LET'S GO.
MOVE THE NIRVASH FORWARD.
- Both: MM.
- ( all gasp )
- IT'S PITCH BLACK.
UM, I CAN'T SEE
ANYTHING IN HERE.
- SAKUYA.
- ( gasps )
CAN IT BE THAT SAKUYA
IS REALLY...
- I'M BACK, LADY SAKUYA.
- Renton and Eureka:
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator:
THE GLIMMERING FLOWER BUD
SHOWS THE STORY THAT
UNITES MAN TO HIS LAND.
THE BOY AND THE GIRL
SEEK THE FUTURE
AND RESOLVE TO GO
ON THE JOURNEY.
NEXT EPISODE,
"ACPERIENCE THREE."