- ( theme music playing )
- ( Renton groaning )
( screaming )
- HMM?
- HUH?
- ( laughs )
OH!  AHH!
- HUH?
- NOW LOOK HERE!
- OH, HEY,
IT'S ONLY YOU, RENTON.
- "LOOK HERE" MAKES YOU SOUND
LIKE AN OLD GUY TALKING.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT, RENTON?
- DON'T YOU
"WHAT DO YOU WANT" ME!
THIS IS ALL YOUR GUYS' DOING,
ISN'T IT?!
- ( all laugh )
I TRY TO STAY CALM,
BUT YOU KEEP SETTING TRAPS
AND DOODLING ALL OVER ME.
- YEAH, AND PUT ROACHES
IN YOUR POCKETS.
- PRANK PHONE CALLS TOO.
- IT WAS SO FUNNY WHEN WE SEWED
UP THE ZIPPER ON YOUR PANTS.
- ( sighs )
YOU KNOW, BIG BROTHER
IS VERY MAD AT YOU RIGHT NOW.
WITH YOU GUYS PLAYING PRANKS
LIKE THIS ALL THE TIME,
I CAN'T KEEP BEING ADULT
ABOUT IT.
- Boy: BUT YOU'RE A KID, RENTON!
- Girl: A KID, A KID, A KID!
AND I HEARD MISS TALHO SAYING
YOU STILL DON'T HAVE YOUR HAIR.
- ( all chuckling )
- ( grunting )
AHHH!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- MMM.
- RENTON, WHAT'S WRONG?
- AH!  OH, WELL, I--
- ( all laughing )
- SEE, IT'S JUST--
HEY, EUREKA,
YOU HAVEN'T EATEN YET,
HAVE YOU?
- NN-NNH.
- HOW ABOUT WE
GET SOMETHING TOGETHER THEN?
I KNOW A PLACE WHERE WE CAN
GET A GREAT VIEW OF THE OUTSIDE.
- HOLLAND CALLED FOR YOU
A FEW MINUTES AGO.
- IT LOOKED LIKE
HE WAS IN A HURRY.
- YOU BETTER GET GOING, RENTON.
- ( sighs )
- YOU'VE GOT TO WORK.
WE CAN'T
DO ANYTHING ABOUT THAT.
- ( Renton thinking )
WELL, SIS, IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY DECLARED WAR ON ME
BEFORE I EVEN REALIZED IT.
- All: NYAH!
- THE ATTACKS HAVE GOTTEN BOLDER
AND MORE FIERCE
SINCE THIS TIME
LAST WEEK.
AND NOW WITH ALL THIS,
THEY'VE COMPLETELY
CROSSED THE LINE.
BUT THEY'RE EUREKA'S CHILDREN,
SO I CAN'T FIGHT BACK
AND I CAN'T MAKE PEACE.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
( sighs )
RENTON, REPORTING FOR DUTY,
JUST AS YOU REQUESTED.
- NOT BAD.
THAT WAS PRETTY QUICK.
- RENTON, YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE CARGO
WE'RE CARRYING
ONBOARD RIGHT NOW?
A LOAD OF WAX, RIGHT?
THE KIND YOU PUT
ON REF BOARDS AND STUFF.
- I WANT YOU TO TEAR OFF
ANYTHING THAT CAN IDENTIFY
THE SENDER OR THE RECIPIENT
FROM THE CONTAINERS.
- YOU WHAT?!
BUT HOW COME?
- THE RECIPIENT VANISHED.
- IN OTHER WORDS,
THEY WENT BANKRUPT
AND RAN OFF LAST NIGHT.
- IT'S BECAUSE WE KEEP
ACCEPTING SHADY CARGO.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE, RENTON.
IT WASN'T THAT THE CARGO
WAS SHADY THIS TIME.
IT WAS THE RECIPIENT
THAT WAS SHADY.
- WE CAN'T KEEP
SOMETHING THAT HUGE
STORED ON THIS SHIP FOREVER.
SO WE DECIDED TO SELL THEM
ALL OFF IN BURDETH.
- KEN-GOH'S
GONNA THROW ANOTHER FIT.
- I'LL SELL 'EM
BEFORE HE GETS PISSED.
- YEAH, BUT ISN'T BURDETH--
- WELL, AT LEAST YOU KNOW
HOW TO READ A MAP.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'LL HAVE TO PASS RIGHT
IN FRONT OF A MILITARY BASE.
- THAT SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
- HMM?
LOADED INTO THE CENTRALIZED
COMPUTING SYSTEM ON THE GEKKO
IS A DEVICE CALLED
THE COMPAC INTERFERENCER.
THIS DEVICE THREE-DIMENSIONALLY
SCANS THE SKY
FOR THE TRAPAR WAVES
THAT ARE CREATED
WHENEVER A COMPAC DRIVE
IS IN OPERATION,
ALLOWING US TO USE IT
AS A KIND OF RADAR
TO SEARCH FOR ENEMY SHIPS.
OF COURSE, WE CAN ALSO
CANCEL OUT THE FREQUENCY
OF THE TRAPAR WAVES
EMITTED FROM OUR DRIVES.
- THAT'S IT!
THAT'S WHY WE DON'T SHOW UP
ON THE RADAR.
- HMM.  VERY GOOD, RENTON.
- I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT AN
AWESOME SHIP THE GEKKO IS.
SO I GUESS THAT'S WHERE
IT GOT ITS NICKNAME.
- Jurgens: AH, THE EVER-ELUSIVE
GEKKOSTATE, HUH?
- Man: I'M SURE THERE'S NO
MISTAKE ABOUT THE INFORMATION.
THEY'RE HEADING DIRECTLY
TOWARDS OUR MILITARY BASE.
- HA!
THEY'RE SO FULL OF THEMSELVES.
ALL RIGHT THEN, EXTEND THE
RANGE OF OUR RECONNAISSANCE.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT
OUR RESERVE FORCES?
- I DON'T CARE.
DON'T HOLD ANYTHING BACK!
- I NEED TO BORROW THIS,
OKAY?
- RENTON, WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
YOUR FACE IS A MESS.
- WHEN I LEFT THE BRIDGE,
FOR SOME REASON, I FELL DOWN!
- ( all sighing )
- AH, THEM AGAIN.
THEY'RE SURE GIVING YOU
A HARD TIME.
- THEY AREN'T OLD ENOUGH
FOR YOU TO REASON WITH YET.
JUST GIVE 'EM A WHACK!
- NEVER HAPPEN.
WITH HIS DEAR EUREKA
AS THEIR MOMMY,
HE CAN'T REALLY
GET MAD AT THEM.
- Woman: TRYING TO WIN THE MOM
THROUGH HER KIDS.
- IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT, OKAY?
- YOU SHOULD JUST GIVE UP.
I TOLD YOU, DIDN'T I?
EUREKA PREFERS OLDER GUYS.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
- I'M POSITIVE.
- WELL, UM,
EXACTLY HOW OLD IS EUREKA,
ANYWAY?
- HOW OLD IS SHE?
- HEY, DON'T ASK ME.
- I'D SAY AROUND 15 OR 16,
JUDGING FROM
THAT BEAUTIFUL FIGURE OF HERS.
- OH, MISS HILDA! MATTHIEU'S
LOOKING AT YOUNG GIRLS
LIKE A DIRTY OLD PERVERT.
- IDIOT, WOULD YOU STOP THAT?
- YOU WANT EUREKA AS THE COVER
GIRL FOR NEXT MONTH'S ISSUE?
MAYBE WE'LL GET
SOME BRAND-NEW FANS.
- Stoner: YEAH, WELL,
WE DON'T NEED FANS LIKE THAT.
- Gidget: MATTHIEU
HAS A LOLITA COMPLEX!
- HEY, YOU WANT ME
TO PUNCH YOU, GIDGET?!
- WHAA!
- ( thinking )
HE'S ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I'M IN LOVE WITH EUREKA.
THAT'S WHY I WANT TO BE
ON GOOD TERMS WITH THE KIDS.
SO I DON'T GET MAD AT THEM
AND THEY
DON'T TAKE ME SERIOUSLY.
THEN THE PRANKS CONTINUE AND
I CAN'T BE ALONE WITH EUREKA.
IT'S A VICIOUS CYCLE.
AHH!
HUH?
CUT-- CUT IT OUT!
- ( kids giggling )
RENTON,
YOU'D BETTER HOLD ON TIGHT
'CAUSE IT'S DANGEROUS
UP THERE!
- WAIT!  STOP THAT!
WHAAAA!
YOU GUYS
ARE SO OUT OF CONTROL.
IF YOUR MOM WASN'T EUREKA,
I WOULD WIPE YOU OUT.
- WANT SOME HELP?
- YEAH, THANKS.
A LITTLE HIGHER UP, PLEASE.
- YOU MEAN HERE?
- OH, YEAH, RIGHT THERE.
AY!
THAT'S COLD.
HEY, THANKS A LOT.
EEK!
- DID THE CHILDREN
DO THIS TO YOU?
- NO!  I MEAN, THAT'S NOT IT.
IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT.
DON'T WORRY.
- REALLY?
I'M GLAD.
DO YOU THINK THAT I'M
DOING A GOOD JOB AS A MOTHER?
- HUH?
YEAH, YOU'RE DOING JUST FINE.
AT LEAST I THINK YOU ARE.
- I REALLY AM TRYING.
I'M DOING EVERYTHING
EVERYONE TOLD ME I SHOULD DO.
IT'S A PARENT'S JOB
TO SCOLD THEIR CHILDREN.
- HUH?
- THAT'S WHAT
THEY CALL DISCIPLINE.
RENTON, HOW DID YOUR PARENTS
DISCIPLINE YOU?
- BY THE TIME I WAS OLD ENOUGH
TO NEED DISCIPLINE,
BOTH MY PARENTS WERE DEAD.
- I SEE.
- SO WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
MY OLDER SISTER TOOK OVER
THE JOB OF BEING MY PARENT.
I REALLY LIKED
BEING WITH MY SISTER.
SHE SMELLED SO NICE.
- Newscaster:
AND NOW FOR OUR NEXT STORY.
THERE'S BEEN AN UPDATE
ON THE EXPLOSION AT KAPEL BASE
THAT HAD OCCURRED IN THE EARLY-
MORNING HOURS OF THE 16th.
THE UNITED FEDERATION'S FORCE
HAS DETERMINED
THE CAUSE OF THE ACCIDENT
TO BE THE EXPLOSION
OF AN OLD-STYLE WEAPON.
HOWEVER, NO DETAILS
HAVE BEEN DISCLOSED,
INCLUDING THE EXACT NATURE
OF THIS WEAPON.
THE OPPOSITION PARTY IS SEVERELY
CRITICIZING THE HANDLING OF...
- ( Holland thinking )
THE ONE THAT KILLED THE KING.
BUT THAT KING IS ALREADY--
- ...SERIES
OF UNEXPLAINED ACCIDENTS.
- THAT'S NO GOOD, MAURICE.
IT'S NOT LONG ENOUGH.
- SHOULD WE ATTACH ONE MORE?
- WON'T IT JUST BREAK
IN THE MIDDLE?
IT'LL BE PRETTY HEAVY
WHEN WE ADD WATER TO IT.
- HEY, I KNOW!
- HMM?
- JUST USE A LONGER CORD!
( laughs )
- HEY, RENTON,
HOW YOU DOIN'?
SO HOW'S YOUR WAR
WITH THE LITTLE BRATS GOING?
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU--
I'M NOT GONNA GET INTO A BIG
FIGHT WITH THOSE THREE KIDS.
UNLIKE THEM,
I'M AN ADULT WHO KNOWS HOW--
- OOOH!
- ( grunting, screaming )
THOSE BRATS!
- Maeter:
THIS IS GONNA REACH IT EASY.
LINCK, YOU'RE GREAT.
- ( Linck giggling )
- CAN YOU CARRY IT?
- YEAH, I'M FINE.
- BE CAREFUL YOU DON'T TRIP.
- 'KAY.
AHH!
- ( whirring )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- HE TRIPPED ON SOMETHING!
( grunting )
- ISN'T IT THIS OVER HERE?
WHAT DO WE DO?!
- NOISY!  I DON'T LIKE IT!
- LINCK, WHICH ONE OF THESE
DID YOU PUSH?
- ( grunting )
- ( whirring dies down )
- Maurice: IT STOPPED.
- IT'S NO GOOD IF IT STOPS
BECAUSE IT WAS MOVING BEFORE!
SHOULD WE TELL MAMA?
- NO, WE'LL TELL HOLLAND
ABOUT IT.
HE'S THE CAPTAIN OF THE SHIP.
- YOU'RE RIGHT,
WE SHOULDN'T TELL MAMA.
- WE CAN'T!
- HUH?
- IF WE TELL HIM, HOLLAND
WILL KICK US OFF THE GEKKO.
- IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT IF WE
JUST APOLOGIZE FOR DOING IT.
- IF WE GOT SEPARATED FROM MAMA,
WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT.
- NO.
- I DON'T WANT TO BE
SENT AWAY FROM MAMA!
WE MADE A PROMISE, DIDN'T WE?
THAT WE WOULDN'T LET RENTON
OR ANYONE ELSE HAVE MAMA.
SHE'S OUR MAMA!
( crying )
- I'M SORRY, LINCK.
WE DID PROMISE, DIDN'T WE,
THAT WE'D GET RENTON
OFF THE SHIP
AND PROTECT MAMA TOGETHER?
- ( Linck crying )
- ( thinking )
OH MAN.
I KNEW THAT WAS IT.
I KNEW THAT WAS IT ALL ALONG.
THAT THEY DIDN'T
WANT EUREKA,
THEIR MOM, TO BE
TAKEN AWAY FROM THEM.
I WAS LIKE THAT TOO.
- Diane: RENTON!
I HAVE A VERY IMPORTANT
APPOINTMENT TO GO TO.
GIVE THAT BACK TO ME!
- YOU CAN'T HAVE IT!
NO WAY.
YOU'RE SO UGLY, SIS!
( snorting )
- COME ON!
GIVE THAT BACK!
- ( Renton thinking )
I COULD KIND OF TELL
WHEN SIS WAS GOING OUT
WITH SOMEONE.  SO I KNOW.
- ( alarm sounding )
- Holland: THE COMPAC
INTERFERENCER JUST SHUT DOWN?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- FOR NOW, THE MILITIA
SHOULDN'T BE ABLE TO FIND US
BECAUSE WE'RE HIDDEN
BEHIND THE MOUNTAINS.
- BUT WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
WE CAN'T JUST STOP
AND HIDE INSIDE THESE CANYONS
FOREVER!
- Stoner: BUT IF WE TRY TO FLY
NOW, THEY'LL SPOT US, RIGHT?
- ( alarm continues )
- HEY.
- ( gasps )
HUH?
- SHH.
- ( ship whirring )
- MATTHIEU, HAVE YOU SEEN
THE CHILDREN ANYWHERE?
- YEAH, I SAW THEM WITH RENTON
HEADING TOWARDS THE HANGAR.
WHAT ARE YOU--
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
THE NIRVASH HAS JUST LAUNCHED?
- Maeter: HEY, RENTON,
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU KNEW HOW TO PILOT AN L.F.O.
- YEAH, IT WAS MY JOB TO
MOVE THE L.F.O.s WHERE THEY
NEEDED TO BE WHEN I WORKED
IN MY GRANDPA'S FACTORY.
- SO YOU'VE NEVER LIFTED BEFORE?
- DON'T WORRY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'VE WATCHED EUREKA HANDLE
THE CONTROLS LOTS OF TIMES.
- MMM.
- Man: CONFIRMED, AN UNKNOWN
CONTACT MAKING A FAST APPROACH!
IT'S A SINGLE SHIP.
- IS IT THE GEKKOSTATE?
- THAT'S STILL UNCLEAR.
- HA!
I WONDER.
- IT MIGHT BE A DECOY,
COMMANDER.
- YES, IT MIGHT.
- HEY, HOW COME
THEY'RE NOT SHOOTING?
- I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT IT'S PERFECT FOR US.
AH!
WHAT THE--
- ( both whimpering )
- MAN, THAT'S NOTHING!
- All: HUH?
I'LL SHOW YOU GUYS
HOW TO PULL OFF
A REAL PRACTICAL JOKE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO!
- All: OKAY!
- Jurgens: WHAT IS THIS?
- I'M UNABLE TO OPERATE
THE RADAR-GUIDED MISSILES.
- COUNTER-ATTACK EFFECTIVE
IS DOWN TO 40!
- WHAT'S THE CAUSE?
- I BELIEVE IT'S WAX
USED FOR LIFTING.
- THEY CAME
TO TAKE OUT OUR RADAR.
- GET THE RECON SQUADRON
BACK HERE!  AND MAKE IT QUICK.
- Maeter: AH, THEY'RE SO SLOW!
- Linck: YOU CAN'T GET US!
- HEY, RENTON, WE'RE ALMOST
OUT OF THE LIFTING WAX.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
TIME FOR THE FINISHING TOUCH!
- All: PERFECT!
- LOOK AT THAT.
- All: WOW.
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- THIS IS AMAZING!
IT FEELS REAL GOOD.
- ( giggling )
( laughing )
- ( all laughing )
- ( alarm sounding )
- HMM?  OH NO.
- LOOKS LIKE THE AIR FORCES
HAVE COME BACK.
- ALPHA AND CHARLIE
HAVE NOW RETURNED TO OUR SECTOR.
- BRAVO WILL ARRIVE BACK HERE
IN TWO MINUTES.
- I HOPE THEY ENJOYED
THEIR FUN AND GAMES.
BECAUSE NOW IT'S TIME
TO PAY.
- HEY, RENTON!
THEY'RE GOING TO GET US.
- THERE'S ONE BEHIND US.
( gasping )
- DAMN IT!
AM I JUST
COMPLETELY HELPLESS HERE?
HUH?
THEY CAME FOR US.
606, MATTHIEU,
IS THAT YOU?
IT'S EUREKA!
HUH?  WHAT WAS THAT?
- RIGHT AWAY, MAMA!
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AH!
YAH!
- MAMA!
- IS EVERYONE HERE ALL RIGHT,
MAURICE?
- YEAH, MAMA, WE'RE ALL FINE.
- IT WAS SCARY. WE WERE
REALLY, REALLY FRIGHTENED.
- RENTON?
- HUH?
- SLIDE BACK IN THE SEAT, OKAY?
- UH, RIGHT, NO PROBLEM.
- ( all shouting )
- HOLD ME STILL.
- HUH?
- HOLD ME STILL
SO I DON'T SHAKE SO MUCH.
- UH, BUT THAT MEANS--
- HURRY!
- OKAY.
- HOLD ON TO ME
AS TIGHT AS YOU CAN!
- RIGHT.
I WON'T LET GO EVEN IF I DIE.
AND I DON'T WANT
TO LET GO EITHER.
- WHY ARE WE HAVING
SO MUCH TROUBLE
AGAINST ONLY FOUR CRAFTS?
TAKE THEM OUT NOW!
- IT EVEN MOVES DIFFERENTLY.
I GUESS THAT MEANS
THEY REALLY DO MAKE A GOOD TEAM.
- MAMA, THERE'S ONE COMING
FROM THE BACK!
- I THINK IT'S THE LAST ONE!
- LET'S GO GET HIM, MAMA!
- Children: CUTBACK!
DROP TURN!
- Maurice: ALL RIGHT!
- Maeter: AMAZING, MAMA!
- CUTBACK TURN DROP!
- ( all laughing )
- Maeter:
NO, LINCK, THAT'S NOT IT.
IT'S A CUTBACK DROP TURN!
- A CUTBACK DROP TURN?
CUTBACK TURN DROP!
- CUTBACK DROP TURN!
- CUTBACK TURN DROP!
- CUTBACK!
- Matthieu: AREN'T YOU BEING
A LITTLE TOO ROUGH ON HIM?
THROWING HIM
IN THE LOCK-UP LIKE THAT?
- Holland: UNAUTHORIZED USE
OF THE NIRVASH,
MAKING A SOLO LAUNCH,
AND TAKING THE KIDS
ABOARD WITH HIM?
NONE OF THOSE CAN BE EXCUSED
AS JUST CHILDISH PRANKS.
- YEAH, BUT HE WAS JUST
COVERING UP FOR EUREKA'S KIDS.
- I KNOW THAT!
HE'S HAD NO ADULTS
TO SUPERVISE HIM.
AND THERE WERE NO ADULTS
WHO WOULD REALLY PUNISH HIM.
SO THAT'S WHY
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO IT.
AS THE ADULTS IN HIS LIFE,
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE
RENTON IS PROPERLY PUNISHED.
- ( door unlocking )
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL THEM,
RENTON?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL THEM
THAT THE KIDS BROKE THE SYSTEM?
BECAUSE YOU'RE AN ADULT?
BECAUSE YOU'RE A MAN?
- BECAUSE I'M RENTON THURSTON
AND THAT'S WHAT I DO.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- ME NEITHER.
HMM?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- THEY WANT TO TAKE THEIR
PUNISHMENT FOR WHAT THEY DID.
- HMM.
- I'M SORRY, RENTON.
- HMM?
THANKS A LOT.
AH!
BUT, EUREKA, WHY YOU?
- I'M HERE
BECAUSE I'M THEIR MOTHER.
IS THAT STRANGE?
- NNN!  NO, IT'S NOT.
I DON'T THINK
THAT IT'S STRANGE AT ALL.
- IT'S COLD IN HERE,
ISN'T IT?
IT'S REALLY NOT THAT BAD.
TO BE CONTINUED!
- ( theme music playing )
- Narrator:
WITH THE PREMONITION
THAT SOMETHING BIG
IS ABOUT TO HAPPEN,
RENTON IS ASSIGNED
AN IMPORTANT MISSION.
WHAT AWAITS HIM
AS HE FIGHTS TO DO HIS BEST?
NEXT EPISODE, "ABSOLUTE DEFEAT."