( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
♪ SO ♪
- ♪ YOU GOTTA REMEMBER ♪
- ♪ GAME OVER ♪
♪ WE WANNA MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE ♪
♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
♪ SO ♪
- ♪ YOU GOTTA REMEMBER ♪
♪ COME ON ♪
- ( engines roaring )
- Hilda: ( on wireless channel )
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE'S
NOBODY IN THE CITY RIGHT NOW.
- Holland: ( on wireless
channel ) HOW ABOUT THE
ARCHAEOLOGICAL DIG SITE?
- I'M GOING TO GO IN RIGHT NOW.
EUREKA?
- Renton: ( on wireless
channel ) UM, YEAH, ROGER THAT.
HEY, EUREKA?
( gasps )
AMAZING. WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
- Hilda: TRAPAR DENSITY, 8%.
LOOKS LIKE EVERYTHING'S
COMPLETELY DRIED UP OUT THERE.
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT,
THERE'S NOBODY IN HERE.
- Holland: ( on wireless
channel ) ROGER.
- Renton: ( voice over ) THE
DAMAGE INFLICTED ON THE GEKKO
WAS MUCH WORSE
THAN WE'D FIRST THOUGHT.
FOR SOME REASON, EVER SINCE
THE INCIDENT WITH THE CORALIAN,
DENSE TRAPAR FIELDS DID NOT
REGENERATE LIKE THEY HAD BEFORE
AND WE HAD TO FIND
SOME PLACE TO HIDE
WHILE WE DID ALL
THE NECESSARY REPAIRS.
- Maeter: MAMA, WELCOME BACK!
- Mischa: FEELING UNEASY?
- THIS AREA'S
UNDER GOVERNMENT JURISDICTION.
A PATROL UNIT COULD SPOT US
AT ANY TIME.
- THAT'S NOT ALL, IS IT?
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
- ( sighs )
HEY, WHAT'S THE STORY
ON THE DAMAGES?
- Man: ( over wireless channel )
QUITE A BIT OF THE
REFLECTION FILM
HAS PEELED OFF THE SHIP.
IT'S GONNA TAKE A WHILE
TO FIX.
- ( sighs )
- I'M GONNA GO OUTSIDE
AND SCOUT THE AREA.
MAYBE THE MILITARY
LEFT SOME FOOD
STASHED SOMEWHERE AROUND HERE.
- LOOK FOR ANY MATERIALS
WE CAN USE.
- Matthieu: WE'RE TAKING RENTON
WITH US.
- HEY.
SO WAS IT
REALLY THAT SHOCKING TO YOU
THAT I WAS ABLE TO OPERATE
THE NIRVASH
A LITTLE BETTER THAN
YOU USUALLY COULD?
( stiffled sob )
SAME FOR ME!
I WAS PRETTY SURPRISED
BY ALL OF IT, TOO, YOU KNOW?
BUT THE FACT IS
THAT I DID OPERATE IT.
DO I HAVE TALENT?
UH... NAH, I DON'T.
IT COULD JUST BE THAT
I'M AN UNUSUALLY GOOD MATCH
FOR THE NIRVASH OR
SOMETHING STUPID LIKE THAT.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
MAYBE THE NIRVASH IS SAYING
IN ITS OWN WAY
THAT I'M BETTER AT IT THAN YOU.
NO WAY,
THAT CAN'T POSSIBLY BE IT!
( sighs )
- Hap: COME ON, RENTON,
LET'S GO.
- HUH? UH...
- YEAH, KID,
WE'RE GOING ON AN ADVENTURE.
( chuckles )
- HURRY UP, LET'S GO!
- ( footsteps retreating )
- ( sighs )
- Hap: IT'D SAVE OUR REARS
IF WE COULD FIND
SOME SPARE REFLECTION
FILM AROUND HERE.
- Matthieu: BUT FIRST,
WE HAVE TO FIND A POWER PLANT
AND RECHARGE OUR ENERGY PODS.
- Man 1: THIS WAS A PRETTY BIG
MINE BACK IN ITS DAY.
- ( camera clicking )
( camera clicking )
- OH, MAN,
THIS PLACE REALLY REEKS.
- MATTHIEU, CAN YOU CHECK
WHAT'S DOWN BELOW?
- SURE.
- GIDGET AND MOONDOGGIE,
YOU GUYS GO OVER THERE
AND LOOK AROUND, ALL RIGHT?
STONER, WHY DON'T YOU
GO THAT WAY?
- HUH?
( gasps )
( sighs )
- ( children laughing )
- Linck: HEY, WAIT!
WAIT!
- I...
I'M VERY SLEEPY.
- Renton: MAN,
I'M REALLY GETTING HUNGRY.
WONDER IF THERE'S ANY FOOD
LEFT AROUND HERE.
( gasps )
( gulps )
- ( speaking inaudibly )
- ( mechanical whirring )
- OH, IT'S ON.
OH, WOW!
THIS PLACE IS UNBELIEVABLE!
WHOA!
WHAT?
WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THIS?
- IT LOOKS LIKE ALL THE
POWER SYSTEMS ARE STILL OKAY.
- I WONDER IF THIS SPRING REALLY
DRIED UP LIKE THEY SAID IT DID.
- IF WE WERE HERE
WITHOUT PROTECTION
BACK WHEN THEY WERE
STILL DIGGING IN THIS MINE,
WE WOULD HAVE ALL GONE
COMPLETELY INSANE.
- WE'RE ALL INSANE ALREADY,
AREN'T WE?
NOWADAYS, WE ALL THINK
IT'S PERFECTLY NORMAL
TO USE THE LFOS WE DIG UP
TO FLY THROUGH THE SKIES
AND TO USE THEM AS WEAPONS
TO KILL EACH OTHER.
HOLLAND, HAVE YOU
EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
WHY THE LFOS ARE
SHAPED JUST LIKE HUMANS?
- TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
IT'S ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT
WHEN I'M MOVING FAST THREE
CLICKS UP AND RIDING A BIG WAVE.
I WONDER IF ADROC
WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO ANSWER THAT QUESTION.
- ( children laughing )
- HMM? HEY, WHERE'S EUREKA?
- MAMA IS LAYING DOWN
AND TAKING A NAP.
- Maeter: LINCK!
- OH!
- ( children laughing )
- TAKING A NAP?
- ( footsteps )
OH, I SEE.
THE GUYS WHO DUG THIS MINE
TRIED DIGGING AROUND
ALL THE WAY BACK IN HERE.
( gasps )
- NO! NO! NO! NO!
- ( cooing )
- ( screams )
- ANEMONE! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- NO, LEAVE ME ALONE!
DON'T TOUCH ME!
NO!
- ( groans )
ANEMONE! SETTLE DOWN! STOP IT!
- ( screams )
- ( groans )
YOU REALLY NEED TO LEARN
A LITTLE TOLERANCE.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
IN MUCH MORE PAIN
IF YOU BECOME RESISTANT
TO THE MEDICATION!
- ( panting )
( hyperventilating )
- OW.
- HEY. DID YOU FIND ANY FOOD?
- UNH-UNH.
- ( door opens )
- MOONDOGGIE?
HEY, I JUST THOUGHT
OF SOMETHING. WHERE'S RENTON?
- EXCUSE ME,
IS THERE ANYONE AT HOME?
HELLO?
PLEASE PARDON ME
FOR INTRUDING.
( footsteps )
- ( toilet flushing )
- ( footsteps )
MM.
WOW!
- ( microwave dings )
- ( sighs )
( drowsily ) MAN, THAT PIZZA
WAS REALLY TASTY. WOW!
THERE'S STILL SOME OF IT LEFT,
SO I GUESS I SHOULD
TAKE IT BACK FOR THE GUYS.
FOR EUREKA, TOO.
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
IF I FALL ASLEEP
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS,
I CAN'T IMAGINE
ALL THE MISFORTUNE I'LL BE IN.
- ANY SPARE BATTERIES?
- Hap: ( over wireless channel )
JUST A COUPLE,
BUT AT LEAST I FOUND SOME.
- HAVE YOU FOUND ANY FOOD?
- Gidget: ( over
wireless channel ) NONE.
ABSOLUTELY,
POSITIVELY, NOTHING.
- ( sighs )
- WHY DON'T YOU HEAD BACK
TO THE SHIP AND TAKE A BREAK?
- Hap: HOLD ON A SECOND.
RENTON'S NOT HERE.
- RENTON? WHERE DO YOU THINK
HE RAN OFF TO?
- ( snoring )
HUH?
- ( people chattering )
- Renton: SOMEONE'S HERE.
IT'S... IT'S LIKE... OH, NO.
I SHOULD APOLOGIZE FOR EATING
THEIR FOOD WITHOUT ASKING.
BUT, SEE, I'M STILL JUST A KID!
( gasps )
WHAT? WAIT A MINUTE. THIS IS...
- ( girl screaming )
- ( Anemone groaning in pain )
( exhales heavily )
- PLEASE, GO TO SLEEP NOW.
SLEEP IS THE ONE THING
THAT SEEMS TO GIVE YOU PEACE.
- ( girl screaming )
- WHAT WAS... WHAT WAS THAT?
THOSE WERE SKY FISH!
( running )
( gasps )
EURE...KA?
EUREKA. YOU CAME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE.
YOU KNOW, EUREKA,
ABOUT EARLIER... I...
I HAVE TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU.
I'M REALLY, REALLY SORRY.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT HOW
I MIGHT HAVE HURT YOUR FEELINGS,
EVEN THOUGH I WOULD NEVER DO
ANYTHING AT ALL TO HURT YOU.
YOU KNOW HOW I SAID
THAT I COULD UNDERSTAND
EXACTLY HOW MACHINES
FEEL, RIGHT?
AND YOU SAID THAT
THAT WAS NORMAL.
I WAS HAPPY THAT WE HAD
SOMETHING IN COMMON.
BUT IT'S NOT THE SAME.
I JUST THINK I UNDERSTAND
HOW MACHINES FEEL.
MAYBE IT'S JUST ME BELIEVING
THAT I REALLY CAN DO IT.
BUT I'M POSITIVE THAT
YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE
WHO COULD EVER BE TRULY
HEART-TO-HEART WITH THE NIRVASH.
SOMETIMES I THINK THAT
I'VE BEEN TOGETHER WITH YOU
FOR MORE THAN
A LITTLE WHILE NOW,
BUT I JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND ANYTHING ABOUT YOU
OR ABOUT HOW YOU MIGHT FEEL.
I WANT TO UNDERSTAND A LOT
MORE ABOUT YOU THAN I DO NOW.
THAT'S BECAUSE...
HEY, YOU KNOW, DON'T YOU
THINK IT'S A BIT LITTLE CRUEL
TO IGNORE EVERYTHING I SAY?
WAIT! HEY,
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
EUREKA?
- RENTON!
RENTON! WHERE ARE YOU?
- Renton: A BLINK?
EUREKA'S BLINKING HER EYES.
BUT WHY SO SLOWLY?
IS THIS A DREAM?
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT IF I'M FLOATING AROUND
INSIDE THAT CORALIAN AGAIN?
EUREKA. WHAT IS IT
YOU'RE LOOKING AT?
- ( ragged breathing )
- ( gasps )
- STONER, YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
RENTON ANYWHERE, HAVE YOU?
- NO. SORRY.
- HEY, IT'S STARTING
TO LOOK LIKE HE'S NOT
IN THE MAIN BUILDING ANYMORE.
- GEEZ, WHERE DID THAT BRAT GO?
I'M GONNA KILL HIM.
- STOP IT! NO!
- ( groaning )
- Renton: THIS IS A DREAM!
IT HAS TO BE!
BUT EVEN IF IT IS A DREAM,
IS IT ALL RIGHT FOR ME
TO JUST WATCH IT?
ARE YOU SATISFIED
WITH THAT, RENTON?
( screaming ) STOP THAT!
- ( girl screaming )
- ( screaming )
- I'M SORRY. I'VE DONE
EVERYTHING THAT I CAN
DO FOR YOU RIGHT NOW.
JUST TRY AND GET SOME REST.
IN THE FUTURE,
I MIGHT END UP PUTTING YOU
IN A MORE PAINFUL SITUATION.
BUT AT LEAST FOR THE MOMENT,
SLEEP TIGHT, ANEMONE.
- ( footsteps )
- SO, THIS IS WHERE
HE'S BEEN HANGING OUT.
HEY, RENTON, YOU SHOULDN'T BE
SLEEPING IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
- HMM?
- ( grunting )
- HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- Renton: EARLIER IN MY DREAM,
I MADE UP MY MIND
AND APOLOGIZED.
I KNOW I SHOULD DO IT ALL AGAIN
IN THE REAL WORLD.
- WHEN I'M HERE,
WHEN I'M INSIDE THIS CAVE,
I BECOME VERY SLEEPY.
- UH-HUH.
YOU KNOW...
EARLIER, I, UM...
I MEAN, I TRIED.
I THINK I HAVE TO APOLOGIZE
TO YOU.
- I HEARD ALL OF THAT
WHEN YOU SAID IT BEFORE.
- RIGHT, YOU DID!
( sighs )
( gasps )
HUH?
( reading out on screen text )
TO BE CONTINUED!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE,
TAKE IT EASY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ TAKE MY CHANCE,
BELIEVE IN MYSELF ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
- Woman: ( voice over ) THE
GEKKO IS STILL UNABLE TO FLY.
IN ORDER TO FIX ITS WINGS,
THEY CATCH SOME SKY FISH.
AS THE BOY'S HEART RACES,
THE WORLD SILENTLY RESONATES
TO HIS HEARTBEAT.
NEXT EPISODE, "SKY ROCK GATE."