- ( theme music playing )
- Man: HEY, ARE YOU LISTENING?
- Man #2: DO I HAVE A CHOICE?
- I WAS SAYING THAT IF YOU THINK
ABOUT MUSIC AND MOVIES,
INSTEAD OF REMEMBERING
WHAT THEY WERE ABOUT,
YOU'RE MORE LIKELY
TO BE REMINDED OF THE MEMORIES
YOU HAVE OF THAT TIME
AND THE PEOPLE YOU KNEW THEN.
- COULD YOU JUST SHUT UP FOR
A WHILE? I CAN'T CONCENTRATE.
- AW, COME ON, I WAS JUST
GETTING TO THE GOOD PART.
- YEAH?  WELL, YOU COULD TRY
CONCENTRATING ON YOUR JOB.
HEY, FEARLESS LEADER,
CAN'T WE GET OUT OF HERE YET?
- Man over radio: SHUT UP!
WE'RE ALMOST DONE.
THERE'S A HUGE WAVE
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
25 SECONDS TO ENGAGEMENT.
- WOW.
THEY'RE REALLY GOING AT IT.
HEY, STONER,
IT'S ALMOST TIME.
- THAT'S RIGHT. IN OTHER WORDS,
THAT WHICH WE CALL MEMORY
IN NO WAY EXISTS
ALL ON ITS OWN,
WHICH MEANS
IT IS INEXORABLY CONNECTED
TO THE ENVIRONMENT
SURROUNDING IT.
DO YOU KNOW WHO IT WAS
WHO SAID THAT, MATTHIEU?
- I HAVE NO CLUE.
- MAN,
YOU ARE REALLY UNEDUCATED.
I SAID IT.
- ( grunting )
THEY'RE HERE!
NOW WE'RE GOING
TO SEE SOMETHING REALLY GOOD.
- ( gunfire )
- Matthieu: HA!
YOU'RE ON FIRE TODAY.
- Stoner: HOLLAND,
IF YOU SHOW OFF TOO MUCH,
THE L.F.O.'s BATTERIES
ARE GOING TO CUT OUT.
- HUH?
WILL THE TWO OF YOU BE QUIET?
I ALREADY KNOW ALL THAT.
- THAT WAS SWEET.
- A FULL CUTBACK DROP TURN.
HUH.
- THIS IS MATTHIEU 606.
CONFIRMED,
ENEMY UNIT WITHDRAWN.
- Woman: THIS IS THE GEKKO.
ROGER THAT.
THE NIRVASH HAS PASSED
THROUGH POINT E62,
RIGHT ON SCHEDULE.
CONTINUING WITH THE MISSION.
- Matthieu: 606, ROGER THAT.
- Woman: 909.
HOLLAND, DID YOU COPY THAT?
- I DON'T WANT TO GO.
- WHAT?! WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT? YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO SUDDENLY ANNOUNCED
YOU WERE GOING TO BELLFOREST.
THAT'S WHY
EVERYONE TAGGED ALONG.
- YEAH YEAH, FINE.
FINE, I'LL GO ALREADY!
JEEZ.
WHAT A MONDAY.
- Newscaster: WEST BELLFOREST,
SOUTHERN WINDS,
WIND FORCE THREE,
TRANSPARENCE LIGHT PARTICLES,
36,
LATER INCREASING TO 56.
NORTH BELLFOREST,
SOUTHEASTERLY WINDS,
WIND FORCE ONE,
TRANSPARENCE LIGHT PARTICLES,
11,
LATER INCREASING--
- YEAH!
Boy: 14 YEARS HAVE PASSED
SINCE I WAS BORN.
IT'S ALREADY BEEN 14 YEARS.
IT'S BEEN 14 YEARS
SINCE I WAS BORN
AND NOTHING EXCITING
HAS HAPPENED TO ME.
BUT THEN AGAIN,
I DON'T GET THE FEELING
THAT ANYTHING EVER WILL HAPPEN.
MY LIFE JUST SUCKS.
- Man: LISTEN, I'M TELLING YOU,
THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN DO IT.
- HEY, DON'T SAY THAT TO ME.
I'M A SMART YOUNG MAN
WITH A BRIGHT FUTURE, YOU KNOW?
- IT'S NOT THE FIRST TIME
I'VE SAID IT, RENTON.
YOU REALLY DON'T BELIEVE
IN THE WAVES, DO YOU?
AND BECAUSE
YOU DON'T BELIEVE IN THEM,
YOU CAN'T RIDE THEM WELL.
AND SO IT'S IMPOSSIBLE--
IMPOSSIBLE FOR YOU
TO DO A CUTBACK DROP TURN.
- YEAH, BUT THEY SAY
THAT HOLLAND WAS ABLE
TO PULL OFF A FULL-SPEED
CUTBACK DROP TURN
WHEN HE WAS 14 YEARS OLD.
I'M SURE I CAN TOO.
- OH, HOLLAND, HUH?
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
I MEAN, HE'S A GENIUS, YOU KNOW?
HE'S NOT THE SAME AS US.
AND DON'T FORGET, HE WAS BORN
UP IN THE NORTH SHORE.
HE GREW UP IN
A TOTALLY DIFFERENT ENVIRONMENT.
- HMM!  YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT HOLLAND SAYS ABOUT THAT?
WHERE YOU WERE BORN
DOESN'T MATTER MUCH.
THE SPOT
A PERSON REALLY NEEDS
IS ALWAYS
RIGHT IN FRONT OF THEIR EYES.
I'M GONNA GET BIG,
RIGHT HERE ON THIS SPOT.
YOU SEE, I'M GONNA
EARN MYSELF A REALLY BIG NAME,
AND THEN I'LL PULL OFF
A CUTBACK DROP TURN ON AN L.F.O.
JUST LIKE HOLLAND.
- HERE, TAKE THIS.
IT'S ON THE HOUSE.
- WHAT?  NO WAY!
YOU REALLY MEAN IT?
- IT'S A GOING-AWAY PRESENT.
- YOU'RE GOING AWAY?
- YEP, I'M GETTING OUT
OF THIS PLACE.
- WHAT? WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- OUT TO A BIGGER CITY
THAT GETS MORE WAVES.
LET'S FACE IT--I'M NOT DOING
ANY BUSINESS HERE AT ALL.
YOU ARE MY ONLY CUSTOMER.
AND YOU JUST LOOK AT THE STUFF.
YOU DON'T BUY ANYTHING.
- THIS TOTALLY SUCKS.
HE'S RIGHT.
THIS CITY COMPLETELY SUCKS.
IT'S A HOPELESS CITY.
IT'S LIKE THE DEFINITION
OF "SUCKS."
EVEN IF I WANT A LIFT,
WE DON'T GET
ANY DECENT WAVES HERE.
IF YOU WANT ANY KIND OF LIFE,
YOU GOTTA JOIN THE MILITARY.
BUT THEN I DON'T KNOW HOW IT IS
I'M GONNA BE ABLE
TO GET OUT OF THIS CITY.
I'M TOO YOUNG TO KNOW THAT.
I MEAN, I'VE ONLY BEEN ALIVE
FOR 14 YEARS.
SO I'LL I CAN DO
IS STAY HERE
IN A CITY THAT TOTALLY SUCKS.
- Teacher: AND SO THE SUDDEN
AND UNEXPECTED EMERGENCE
OF NUMEROUS
TRANSPARENCE LIGHT PARTICLES,
TRAPARS FOR SHORT,
CAUSED THE COMPAC DRIVES
TO GO OUT OF CONTROL,
PLUNGING THE WORLD
INTO CHAOS
AS A RESULT OF THE PHYSICAL
DESTRUCTION THAT FOLLOWED,
AN EVENT NAMED
"THE NEW ERA SUMMER OF LOVE."
AND THE MAN WHO STOPPED
THIS CATASTROPHE
BY SACRIFICING HIS OWN LIFE
WAS THE LEGENDARY HERO
OF OUR COUNTRY, ADROC THURSTON.
AND OF COURSE,
AS MANY OF YOU KNOW,
THE SON OF ADROC THE HERO
IS ONE OF OUR CLASSMATES,
RENTON THURSTON.
- ( all laughing )
- ( thinking )
THIS REALLY SUCKS.
- ( explosion )
- ( all scream )
- ( all clamoring )
- Teacher: UH, QUIET STUDY!
THE TEACHERS
WILL DEAL WITH THE SCUBS.
ALL OF YOU SHOULD STAY INSIDE.
- COME ON,
TELL US ALL ABOUT IT.
WE'RE REALLY CURIOUS
TO KNOW--
DID ANYONE ACTUALLY SEE
YOUR DAD SAVE THE WORLD?
- AND YOUR SISTER--
SHE RAN AWAY FROM HOME
TO TRY TO PROVE IT, DIDN'T SHE?
SAYING SHE GOT A MESSAGE ON
HER COMPAC DRIVE OR SOMETHING.
- ( both laughing )
- AH!
- Girl: HEY, DID YOU SEE IT?
DID YOU SEE
THIS MONTH'S "ray=out"?
- Girl #2: OF COURSE!
ISSUE 17, RIGHT?
MISS TALHO WAS SO PRETTY!
- YEAH, BUT ISN'T
THE GEKKO STATE REALLY
JUST A BUNCH OF CRIMINALS?
- MY MOM TOLD ME
THAT ALL THEY REALLY ARE
IS A GANG OF KILLERS
AND GOOD-FOR-NOTHINGS.
AND YOU SHOULDN'T
TRUST ANYTHING THAT THEY SAY.
- WHAT, REALLY?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT.
- Diane Thurston:
REMEMBER THIS, RENTON.
AS LONG AS YOU BELIEVE,
WE WILL SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN.
- Young Renton: REALLY?
- YES.
IF YOU CAN
TRULY BELIEVE IN SOMETHING,
THEN THE POWER OF YOUR BELIEF
WILL MAKE IT REAL.
THEN I KNOW YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO FLY INTO THE SKY,
HELP THE PEOPLE DEAR TO YOU,
AND SEE ME
AT ANY TIME YOU WANT.
SO PLEASE
JUST BELIEVE IN ME.
BELIEVE IN ME
AND BE A GOOD BOY.
- SURE.  I WILL, SIS.
- ( girl chuckling )
- HUH?
- DON'T YOU THINK RENTON
IS A BIT DISGUSTING?
- HE'S, LIKE, TOTALLY GRINNING,
STARING AT HIS COMPAC DRIVE.
- YEAH!
- ( Renton thinking )
THIS TOTALLY SUCKS.
HUH?
- AND WHERE
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
- GRANDPA?
- Teacher: I'M SORRY TO
SAY THIS, BUT WITH HIS GRADES,
NOT ONLY WILL HE NOT MAKE IT
INTO THE MILITARY ACADEMY,
HE MIGHT NOT PASS AT ALL.
- THAT DOESN'T MATTER!
- HOWEVER, HE IS THE SON
OF MR. ADROC,
THE RENOWNED HERO
OF THE MILITARY--
- IT DOESN'T MATTER!
THIS BOY IS GOING TO TAKE OVER
THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
NO MORE MILITARY PERSONNEL
WILL BE CREATED IN MY HOUSEHOLD.
- Renton: AWESOME!
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS,
GRANDPA?
TIME TO EAT!  EH?
- ( sighs )
WHY DID IT HAVE TO END UP
THIS WAY?
OH, RENTON,
HOW AM I EVER GOING TO BE ABLE
TO EXPLAIN ANY OF THIS
TO YOUR LATE MOTHER?
- IT ALL SUCKS.
THIS TOWN SUCKS.
MY LIFE SUCKS.
BUT AS LONG AS I GOT WAVES,
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
AS LONG AS I CAN LIFT,
IT'S NO PROBLEM.
SO YOU SEE?
I'M OKAY, SIS.
GOT MY LIFTING, AND AS LONG
AS I CAN KEEP LIFTING,
NO MATTER WHERE I AM,
EVERYTHING'S GREAT!
- ( exploding )
- AH!
NO WAY.
THAT'S MY FAVORITE SPOT.
A MILITARY L.F.O.
DAMN IT!
THIS JUST-- THIS JUST--
THIS CITY JUST SUCKS!
EVEN THOUGH IT MIGHT BE TRUE
THAT HOLLAND IS A CRIMINAL,
I'M REALLY JEALOUS
OF A GUY LIKE HIM.
HOLLAND GOES
ALL OVER THE WORLD,
ANYWHERE HE WANTS,
JUST LOOKING FOR WAVES.
I WANT TO DO
WHATEVER I WANT TOO,
DO WHATEVER I WANT
AND BECOME A PROFESSIONAL
LIFTER, JUST LIKE HOLLAND.
AND THEN--
AND THEN SOMEDAY
I'M GONNA BECOME A MEMBER
OF THE GEKKOSTATE.
- ( Compac beeping )
- HUH?
MAN, WHAT'S WITH THIS?
IT SAYS "EUREKA" AGAIN.
THAT'S GOT TO BE
THE THIRD TIME THIS MONTH.
( sighs )
( laughing )
I WONDER WHAT THIS COULD BE.
HEY, WAIT,
AM I THE ONLY ONE IT COMES TO?
I WONDER IF IT'S SOME SECRET
MILITARY CODE OR SOMETHING.
OR MAYBE, JUST MAYBE, IT'S A
MESSAGE FROM THE GEKKOSTATE.
THAT WOULD BE SO COOL,
IF THE PERSON WHO RECEIVES
THIS TRANSMISSION
COULD BECOME A MEMBER OF
THE GEKKOSTATE. I WISH! HMM?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE?
- AW, MAN! HOW MANY TIMES
DO I GOTTA TELL YOU
NOT TO BARGE IN HERE
WITHOUT ASKING.
- FOR GOODNESS' SAKE,
ALL YOU DO IS COLLECT
USELESS JUNK UP HERE.
- WHO CARES?
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU.
- YES IT DOES!
SOMEONE WHO CANNOT
EVEN DO SIMPLE ORGANIZING
WILL NEVER BECOME
A GOOD MECHANIC.
- WAIT JUST A MINUTE!
WHEN DID I SAY THAT I WAS GOING
TO BECOME A MECHANIC?
- IT WAS DECIDED FOR YOU.
- DON'T I GET TO DECIDE?
- WHAT OTHER OPTIONS
DO YOU HAVE?
LISTEN TO ME, RENTON.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT FASCINATES YOU.
YOU CAN EVEN RIDE THOSE BOARDS
IF YOU WANT TO.
BUT YOU HAVE TO FACE REALITY.
EVEN THOUGH YOUR FATHER DIED
AND BECAME A HERO,
AND EVEN THOUGH
DIANE LEFT THIS HOUSE
IN SEARCH
OF HER IMPOSSIBLE DREAMS,
NOTHING AT ALL HAS CHANGED
IN THIS WORLD.
THOSE WHO BELIEVE
IN THEIR DREAMS AND IDEALS
ARE ALL IDIOTS!
- I UNDERSTAND.
- HUH?
- YOU'RE A LOT MORE WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT'LL HAPPEN TO YOU
AFTER YOU RETIRE
THAN YOU ARE ABOUT
WHAT I WANT TO DO
WITH MY LIFE, GRANDPA.
WELL, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT!
I'M GONNA MAKE TONS OF MONEY
AND MAKE SURE TO PUT YOU
IN A NICE RETIREMENT HOME!
- ( grunting )
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
- ( alarm sounding )
- ( grunts )
- ARGH!
THIS THING!
I'M SICK OF IT.
IT'S GOT YOU LIVING
IN A DREAM WORLD!
- NO!  COME BACK!
CRAZY OLD MAN!
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
THAT'S A REPLICA
OF THE ONE HOLLAND USES.
YOU CAN'T GET 'EM ANYMORE!
WHAAA!
AN L.F.O.?
A CUTBACK DROP TURN?
NO WAY!
IS THAT HOLLAND?  HUH?
WHAT'S HE DOING?
- Both: AHHH!
- WHAA!  OH NO.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT KIND OF L.F.O. IS THIS?
I'VE NEVER
SEEN ONE LIKE IT BEFORE.
- IT'S THE NIRVASH TYPE ZERO.
- YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
- OF COURSE.
THIS IS THE OLDEST-EXISTING
L.F.O. IN THE WORLD.
I JUST NEVER THOUGHT
I'D GET TO SEE THE REAL THING.
- SO THIS IS THE NIRVASH?
- HEY!
- Both: HMM?
- THIS LITTLE ONE
DOESN'T SEEM TO BE FEELING WELL.
CAN YOU PLEASE
TAKE A LOOK AT IT FOR ME?
- ( gulps )
SHE'S SO CUTE.
- Grandfather: SORRY TO
BOTHER YOU LIKE THIS AGAIN.
- Man over radio:
AH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE DIGGERS
COULDN'T DO OUR JOBS
IF IT WEREN'T FOR MECHANICS
LIKE YOU, OLD MAN.
- LOOK, ABOUT THE STATE ARMY--
- OH, THAT'S TAKEN CARE OF.
I TOLD THEM THAT I UNEARTHED
A SCUB AND BROKE IT.
THEY WERE ALL LAUGHING
ABOUT THAT.
LISTEN, UH, ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO COME?
- YEAH.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
- ( phone hangs up )
- ( sighs )
WHAT A PAIN.
IF ONLY YOU HADN'T FOUND
THIS STUPID THING.
- ( thinking ) SO THIS--
THIS IS THE NIRVASH, HUH?
THE MYSTERIOUS CRAFT THAT
WAS THE FIRST TO BE DISCOVERED.
THE ONE THAT BECAME THE BASIS
OF ALL THE L.F.O.s EVER MADE.
THAT'S WHY IT'S TYPE ZERO,
THE ORIGINAL
OF ALL THE ORIGINALS.
WAIT, THEN THAT MEANS--
( thinking )
I AM SO SMART!
IF THIS
WAS THE ORIGINAL L.F.O.,
THEN IT MUST HAVE
THE ORIGINAL COMPAC DRIVE IN IT.
AND THAT WOULD HAVE
THE ORIGINAL DATA
FOR ALL THE L.F.O.s
THAT FOLLOWED.
WHAT?
HUH?  HUH? HUH?
THE COMPAC DRIVE IS MISSING.
THAT'S WEIRD. IT'S GOT A TWO-DIN
UNIT-TYPE ATTACHMENT SOCKET.
AND IT'S THE NEWEST MODEL TOO.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
THERE'S NO COMPAC DRIVE IN HERE.
HUH?  GRANDPA?
THIS L.F.O. IS KIND OF--
- EXCUSE ME, I NEED A FAVOR.
CAN YOU PLEASE LEND ME
THAT FLAMETHROWER
THAT'S SITTING BACK
BEHIND THE FACTORY?
THE ONE THAT'S USED ON
ALL THE SCUBS? - ( grunting )
WHAT-- WHAT'S WRONG?
- OH, THIS?
LOOK, I'M REALLY SORRY THAT
I BROKE YOUR ROOM ALL TO PIECES.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
IT WAS A VERY HURTFUL THING
TO DO.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING TO MAKE UP FOR IT.
- AMAZING!
SHE IS SO NICE.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- UH, OH YEAH!
IT'S THIS L.F.O.
IT DOESN'T SEEM TO HAVE
A COMPAC DRIVE INSTALLED IN IT.
SEE? THE ONLY THING HERE
IS THIS EMPTY SOCKET.
- OH. THERE WAS NEVER ONE THERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I DON'T NEED IT
BECAUSE IT'S USELESS.
- WELL, YOU SEE--
YOU KNOW, YOU--
YOU'RE WRONG.
IN ORDER TO MAKE AN L.F.O. MOVE,
YOU NEED A COMPAC DRIVE,
A DEVICE THAT ALLOWS PEOPLE
TO COMMUNICATE WITH MACHINES.
WITHOUT IT,
PEOPLE CAN'T CONTROL THEM.
YOU DID KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
- HUH?
- THIS IS SO GREAT!
ALL RIGHT THEN, I'VE GOT IT.
HOW ABOUT WE TRY PUTTING MINE IN
AS AN EXPERIMENT?
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I MAY NOT LOOK IT,
BUT I'M
A PROFESSIONAL MECHANIC.
SEE, WHEN YOU BECOME
A MECHANIC OF MY CALIBER,
YOU CAN SENSE THAT MACHINES
HAVE FEELINGS TOO.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THAT'S JUST PLAIN COMMON SENSE,
ISN'T IT?
WELL, I'LL GO BORROW
THAT FLAMETHROWER NOW.
- ( thinking )
SIS, THIS IS AMAZING.
SHE'S THE IDEAL GIRL
THAT DOESN'T THINK
THE THINGS THAT I SAY
ARE STRANGE.
SURE, SHE'S A LITTLE WEIRD.
BUT SHE'S SO WORRIED
ABOUT HAVING TRASHED MY ROOM,
SHE WANTS TO USE A FLAMETHROWER
TO BURN-- BURN--
BURN?!
- ( exploding )
- ( panting ) AHHH!
WHAT-- WHAT--
WHAT EXACTLY
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- A FUNERAL.
- A FUNERAL?!
BUT NOBODY AROUND HERE
HAS DIED.
WAIT A MINUTE. THERE ARE STILL
THINGS I CAN USE IN THERE!
( gasping )
HOT! OH, NO, MY CLEAS
ARE BEING SENT TO HEAVEN.
MY CLEAS! MY CLEAS!
( sobbing )
- NOW HOLD ON.
SHE'S LAUGHING.
- Matthieu: YOU KNOW, HOLLAND?
- HMM?
- WHY DO WE HAVE TO GO
THROUGH ALL THIS TROUBLE?
WHY CAN'T WE JUST GO FACE-UP
TO THE OLD GUY
AND ASK HIM TO FIX THE NIRVASH
BECAUSE IT ISN'T WORKING RIGHT?
YOU KNOW HIM, DON'T YOU?
- Stoner: WELL,
I WOULDN'T MIND DOING THAT,
BUT IT SEEMS
WE'VE GOT SOMEONE HERE
WHO DOESN'T WANT TO MEET HIM
FACE TO FACE.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- YEAH, WHAT'S UP WITH THAT,
HOLLAND?
IS THAT YOUR WEAKNESS?
IGNORING ME, EH?
- ( Holland yawns )
MAN, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HE'S REALLY
STARTING TO LOOK LIKE HER.
HUH?  DON'T LIKE THE LOOK
OF THE CURRENT.
- ( beeping )
- Renton: HUH?
WOW, THAT'S REALLY STRANGE.
- ON SECOND THOUGHT,
TAKE IT OFF.
- WHAT?  BUT WHY?
- IT WORKED ALL RIGHT
ALL THIS TIME WITHOUT IT.
BESIDES,
I CAN'T BELIEVE IN THINGS
THAT I DON'T
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT.
- YOU MEAN
YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME?
DON'T SAY THAT.
- ANYWAY, JUST BECAUSE
YOU BELIEVE IN SOMETHING,
IT DOESN'T MEAN
THAT ANYTHING WILL COME OF IT.
SOMETIMES YOU SUFFER
GREAT MISFORTUNE
FOR BELIEVING IN SOMETHING
TOO MUCH.
THERE ARE TIMES THAT IT'S TOUGH
TO BELIEVE IN ANYTHING AT ALL.
- BUT--
BUT DON'T YOU--
- Grandfather: YOU'RE ONE OF
HOLLAND'S FRIENDS, AREN'T YOU?
- GRANDPA?
NEVER MIND.
IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER NOW.
I PLANNED TO HAND THIS OVER
NO MATTER WHO CAME.
- HEY, GRANDPA,
WEREN'T YOU GOING TO
GO DOWN TO CITY HALL
OR SOMETHING?
- THIS IS IT, RIGHT? TAKE IT--
THIS IS WHAT YOU CAME HERE FOR.
MY FAMILY WAS TORN TO PIECES
BECAUSE OF THIS DAMNABLE THING.
IF YOU WANT IT, TAKE IT.
AND THEN--AND THEN DO ME THE
COURTESY OF NEVER COMING BACK!
- GRANDPA!  DON'T YOU THINK
YOU'RE BEING A LITTLE BIT HARSH?
WHAT'S WITH YOU ANYWAY,
BUTTING IN LIKE THAT?
- ( gasps )
YOU'D BETTER HANG ON!
- WHY?  WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( both grunting )
- Renton: WHAAA!
- HUH?
- ( grandfather grunting )
- ( grunting ) OH!
- GRANDPA!
- WHY DO THEY HAVE TO COME HERE
AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
- Man: WHY DID YOU FIRE?!
- Man #2: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
WHY DID I FIRE?
I DON'T THINK WE WERE ORDERED
TO PROTECT TYPE ZERO, WERE WE?
- AS A MEMBER
OF THE INTELLIGENCE BUREAU,
I CANNOT LET THIS PASS.
- ARE YOU SAYING WE SHOULD BRING
EVEN MORE SHAME UPON OURSELVES?
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I--
- WATCH YOUR MOUTH,
INFORMATION OFFICER DOMINIC!
UP IN THE SKY, ORDERS FROM
AIR FORCE OFFICERS
ARE GIVEN HIGHER PRIORITY.
DIDN'T YOU LEARN THAT
IN CADET SCHOOL?
- IMBECILE.
- ( beeping )
- ( grunting )
RENTON!
- GRANDPA!
- ( grunts )
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE NIRVASH?
RENTON?
I NEED YOU TO TAKE THIS
TO THAT GIRL NOW.
IT'S AN EXPANSION PART
FOR THE COMPAC DRIVE--
THE AMITA DRIVE.
- DID YOU SAY THE AMITA DRIVE?
- WHEN YOU ATTACH THIS
TO THE COMPAC DRIVE,
THE L.F.O. WILL REALIZE
ITS FULL POTENTIAL
AND TRULY AWAKEN.
THAT IS WHAT YOUR FATHER
TOLD ME.
- WHAT?  MY FATHER?
- RENTON, GET GOING!
USE THIS THING
TO MAKE THEM ALL GO AWAY!
- Renton: I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING, SIS.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE I'M TRYING
TO PULL OFF THIS CRAZY STUNT
JUST BECAUSE GRANDPA TOLD ME TO.
IT'S JUST-- IT'S JUST
THAT I HAVE TO TELL THAT GIRL
WHAT I WASN'T ABLE
TO SAY TO HER BEFORE--
THE THINGS YOU TOLD ME
WAY BACK THEN
AND THE THINGS I HAVE COME
TO BELIEVE IN NOW.
SO LET'S GO, RENTON!
COME ON, LET'S GO!
I'M TAKING OFF AFTER THAT GIRL!
AHHH!
WAIT--
WAS THIS REALLY A GOOD IDEA?
AM I GONNA BE ALL RIGHT?
AREN'T I A LITTLE TOO HIGH?
AM I REALLY ALL RIGHT?
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator: RENTON,
WITH AMITA DRIVE IN HAND,
FLIES THE SKIES
TOWARDS THE NIRVASH.
THE MOMENT HE ARRIVES,
THE SATORI PROGRAM STARTS UP.
WHAT RENTON SAW
IN THE RAINBOW OF LIGHT.
NEXT EPISODE,
"BLUE SKY FISH."