- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Female Aide:
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
THINKING TOO MUCH
ABOUT THINGS
WILL RESULT IN YOU LOSING
YOUR GOOD HEALTH, LADY CODA.
- IF MY HEALTH IS GOING TO FAIL,
I WOULD LIKE ALL OF YOU
TO BE KINDER TO ME.
- ARE YOU GOING TO MEET
WITH COLONEL DEWEY?
- I'M BEGINNING TO UNDERSTAND
WHY THE OTHER SAGES,
KUZEMI AND BRAYA, FEAR HIM
WITH SUCH INTENSITY.
AT TIMES, EVEN I
DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT IS GOING THROUGH HIS HEAD.
- A SQUADRON LED BY SUCH A MAN--
- YOU MEAN AGEHA?
IT'S SUCH AN IRONIC NAME.
I ADMIT THAT RIGHT NOW,
I'M SIDING WITH DEWEY.
BUT WHAT EXACTLY DOES THAT MAN
HAVE IN MIND FOR THE FUTURE?
I'M CURIOUS AS TO THE REASON
BEHIND THAT MAN WANTING
TO SEE THE PLANET
CONTROLLED BY SOMETHING SO EVIL
AND OLD AS THE SAGE COUNCIL.
WHAT IS HE ATTEMPTING
TO BRING TO THIS PLANET
AND THE HUMANS LIVING ON IT?
BEINGS WHO ARE TIED DOWN
BY THEIR SINS TO SUCH AN EXTENT,
THEY CAN'T EVEN MOVE
FREELY ANYMORE.
- ( royal music playing )
- I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
I NEEDED NO ONE TO GREET ME.
- BUT THIS IS
A SPECIAL OCCASION.
THE SAGES ON THE MOVE
HASN'T HAPPENED IN A DECADE.
WE CANNOT TAKE
YOUR VISIT LIGHTLY.
I KNOW THAT YOU MUST BE
TERRIBLY BUSY, LADY CODA.
BUT IF YOU COULD GRANT US
A COUPLE OF KIND WORDS
AT THE COUNCIL MEETING,
WE WOULD ALL BE HONORED
FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
- ARE YOU ACTUALLY DARING
TO GIVE ME, A SAGE, AN ORDER?
- OF COURSE NOT!
- I HAVE NO TIME.
BRING COLONEL DEWEY
HERE TO ME IMMEDIATELY.
- RIGHT AWAY!
- ( door opens )
- HAVE YOU GUYS SEEN HOLLAND?
- HE WAS ON THE BRIDGE EARLIER.
- IDIOT.
IT'S NOT LIKE HE'S
IN ANY CONDITION
TO FREELY MOVE AROUND.
- SHE CHANGED HER HAIRDO.
- PUT STRAIGHT-- SHE GOT DUMPED.
- EVEN HER OUTFIT IS DIFFERENT.
- OH, PUT STRAIGHT--
SHE JUST REALIZED HER REAL AGE.
- ( wrench turning )
- Talho:
AM I SOME STRANGE BEAST?
EVERYWHERE I GO,
PEOPLE LOOK AT ME
LIKE I'M SOME STRANGE CREATURE.
- PEOPLE CAN'T HELP IT,
WHEN YOU LOOK LIKE THAT.
- IT'S NOT LIKE I'VE MADE
A DRAMATIC CHANGE OR ANYTHING.
- YOU HAVE CHANGED.
- YEAH?  YOU TOO.
- YOU TOO.
SO WHY DID YOU TELL HIM?
IF HE REALIZES
THAT EUREKA IS A CORALIAN--
- IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
THOSE TWO WILL BE FINE.
- EUREKA, DID YOU MAKE
THE SCRAMBLED EGGS
FOR BREAKFAST THIS MORNING?
- YEAH.
- THEY WERE DELICIOUS.
- THANK YOU, RENTON.
- RIGHT NOW, ALL OF MY NERVES
ARE CONCENTRATED ON MY ARM.
NO, NO, MY ARM
IS MY ENTIRE SELF!
- I REALLY LIKE BEING WITH YOU
THIS WAY, RENTON.
- REALLY?
- WHEN I'M WITH YOU, RENTON,
I CAN ALMOST FORGET
THAT THESE HANDS OF MINE
ARE STAINED WITH INNOCENT BLOOD.
- EUREKA...
- ( crying )
- Eureka: ARE YOU HAPPY
WHEN WE'RE LIKE THIS?
- YEAH.
- ME TOO.
THAT'S WHY I CAN FORGET
ABOUT THE PAST
AND THE HORRIBLE THINGS
I DID BACK THEN.
- EUREKA--
- AND NOW I'VE SOILED
YOUR HANDS AS WELL.
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
- IT IS NOT!
IT IS NOT ENOUGH.
NIRVASH IS REALLY ANGRY.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
- WAIT!
- ( shouting )
- Eureka: STOP IT!
NIRVASH DOESN'T LIKE
WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
HE DOESN'T WANT TO GO BACK
TO THE WAY HE WAS BEFORE.
- YOU REALIZE THAT OUR OBJECTIVE
THIS TIME IS RESTORATION, RIGHT?
- EUREKA.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- Eureka:
HE DOESN'T LIKE IT.
HE WANTS YOU TO ACCEPT HIM
FOR WHAT HE IS RIGHT NOW.
- AND SO, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WE HAVE TO COMPLETELY RECONSIDER
THE FUNDAMENTAL SHELL DESIGN.
- YOU THINK YOU CAN DO IT?
- WE'D HAVE TO ASK GREG EGAN
TO HELP US OUT ON THIS ONE.
- DR. BEAR!
- All: HUH?
- WHO'S THAT?
- THE PREEMINENT MAN
IN THE RESEARCH OF ARCHETYPES?
YOU DON'T KNOW HIM?!
- SORRY, BUT I'VE
NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
- GREG EGAN, WHOSE NICKNAME
IS DR. BEAR,
NEVER STEPS OUTSIDE OF HIS LAB
AND ONLY RESEARCHES THINGS
THAT SPARK HIS INTEREST.
HOWEVER, EVERY PAPER
THAT HE PUBLISHES
IS ALWAYS TOP-NOTCH,
OR RATHER HE GOES FAR BEYOND
CURRENT THINKING, AND NOT MANY
PEOPLE CAN UNDERSTAND HIM.
- IN OTHER WORDS, A LOONEY.
- Jobs:
W-WHAT WAS THAT?!
YOU'LL GET CURSED
FOR SAYING THAT.
- THERE'S A-- THERE'S
SOME BIG GUY I DON'T KNOW
SITTING OVER THERE
DRINKING TEA WITH GONZY.
- ( gasps )
- Mischa: IT'S GREG!
- DR. EGAN!
I'M SO HONORED TO MEET YOU,
I'VE READ EVERY PAPER
THAT YOU'VE PUBLISHED, SIR.
- HERE.
- MY LITTLE CUB!
GIVE ME A HUG.
- YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED, HAVE YOU?
WE DIVORCED A LONG TIME AGO.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
- WHAT?!
- MISCHA, YOU WERE--
- YOU AND HE WERE MARRIED?
- ( camera snaps )
- YOU'RE STILL
AS BEAUTIFUL AS EVER.
BUT YOU--
YOU HAVE CHANGED
QUITE A BIT, YOUNG LADY.
WHY DON'T YOU
COME OVER TO MY LAB
AND WE'LL GET STARTED, HM?
- Eureka: BE CAREFUL.
- HUH?
- RIGHT.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'M FINE.
- Holland:
COME ON, LET'S GO.
- Dr. Egan:
YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS?
IT'S THE FIRST MESSAGE
SENT INTO OUTER SPACE
BY THE PEOPLE
OF OUR ANCESTOR PLANET, EARTH.
IT'S A REPLICA OF WHAT WAS
ABOARD WHAT THEY CALL VOYAGER.
IT'S SO PRIMAL.
BUT AT THE TIME,
IT WAS STATE-OF-THE-ART
TECHNOLOGY.
- YEAH, WELL WE DIDN'T COME HERE
TO GET A LECTURE ON HISTORY.
- WHAT I'M SAYING IS,
MAYBE EUREKA IS A VOYAGER.
- WHAT?
- PERHAPS SHE IS
SOME SORT OF A MESSAGE
FROM THE SCUB CORAL.
- THAT THEORY ABOUT
THE INTELLIGENCE
OF SCUB CORAL, AGAIN?
LOOK, GREG--
I'VE SAID THIS
MANY TIMES BEFORE,
FOR IT TO BE
AN INTELLIGENT LIFE-FORM
IS JUST TOO
LOGICALLY INCONSISTENT.
- LET'S LEAVE THAT ASIDE,
WE'LL JUST END UP ARGUING.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT ALL THIS?
- NOT A THING.
- THAT'S RIGHT, YOU WERE
PROBABLY SENT OUT HERE
NOT KNOWING ANYTHING AT ALL
ABOUT YOUR PAST.
NO, THE FACT
THAT YOU DON'T KNOW,
ITSELF IS THE MESSAGE.
THAT THEY DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT US,
THAT THEY KNOW NOTHING.
- SO THE MESSAGE
IS A BLANK SHEET OF PAPER?
- THAT'S RIGHT, AND WE'RE FREE
TO WRITE WHATEVER WE WANT ON IT.
WHAT DID YOU WRITE ABOUT?
TRUE LOVE?  UGLY HATRED?
THE QUESTION IS, CAN
SO MANY INTELLIGENT LIFE-FORMS
EXIST ON A SINGLE PLANET?
OF COURSE, I'M REFERRING
TO HUMANS AND THE SCUB CORAL.
- SO WHAT COULD HAPPEN?
- THE WORLD COULD BE
COMPLETELY ERADICATED.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
TOO MUCH ABOUT THIS.
THERE IS JUST
FAR TOO LITTLE DATA HERE.
IF ONLY I COULD
ACCESS THE SERVER
AT THE INFORMATION DEPARTMENT,
I WOULD BE ABLE
TO LEARN A LITTLE MORE.
- YOU CALLED US OVER HERE,
AND THAT'S YOUR REPORT?
- WELL, YEAH.
BUT I THINK WE NEED
TO TAKE A MORE ACTIVE INTEREST
IN THE CHANGES HAPPENING
TO THE ARCHETYPE
AND TO THE GIRL.
I BELIEVE WE SHOULD
TAKE THIS AS SCUB CORAL
TRYING TO SEND US A MESSAGE.
- HUH?
- IN OTHER WORDS,
THE CURRENT RESTORATION PROJECT
IS NO GOOD.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND?
WELL THEN--
THE SHAPE THAT IS
MOST BEFITTING
THE CURRENT MEASUREMENT DATA
SHOULD LOOK SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
I SUPPOSE YOU
COULD CALL IT
A SORT OF HIGH-SPEED
FLIGHT CONFIGURATION.
IT SEEMS TO ME
THE ARCHETYPE WANTS TO FLY.
THE ARCHETYPE WANTS TO FLY...
...AND SO DO YOU.
- Lady Coda:
WHO ARE THOSE PEOPLE
- THE AGEHA SQUAD.
- AH, THE AGEHA SQUAD.
THEY ARE ALL
BEAUTIFUL CHILDREN, COLONEL.
THIS LOCATION IS UNSUITABLE
FOR OUR TALK.
SOMEONE IS SURE TO LISTEN.
- DON'T WORRY, LADY.
- ( whistling )
- ( screaming )
- Dewey: I BELIEVE
THAT WAS SOMEONE
THAT BRAYA HAD CONTROL OF.
- YOU ASSERT THAT THE JAMMING
SIGNALS ARE IN ORDER?
INGENIOUS TECHNIQUE,
AND COLD-HEARTED ENOUGH
TO KILL SOMEONE WITHOUT
ANY CHANGES IN EMOTION.
YOU BREED BUTTERFLIES OF POISON.
THERE IS NO OTHER REASON
WHY I'VE CHOSEN
TO COME DOWN HERE RIGHT NOW.
THE SITUATION CALLS FOR SPEED.
BEAR CHILDREN, MULTIPLY,
FILL THE LAND,
THIS WORLD HAS BEEN POPULATED
IN ACCORDANCE WITH THOSE WORDS.
NOW THAT THE LAND ITSELF IS
BEGINNING TO REVOLT AGAINST US,
RETURNING TO OUR SPACESHIPS
IS NO LONGER AN OPTION.
WHAT DO YOU INTEND TO DO
WITH THE SITUATION?
- WHAT TO DO?
TOTAL ANNIHILATION
IS THE ONLY WAY LEFT
FOR US TO TRULY SURVIVE.
WE MUST DESTROY THE CORALIAN.
THE KUTE-CLASS
IS NOTHING BUT A GATE.
SOON, I'M SURE, WE WILL SEE
BEINGS CALLED ANTIBODIES
APPEARING HERE.
AND THE ANNIHILATION
OF HUMANS WILL BEGIN.
WE NEED TO CRUSH THEM FIRST.
IF WE DON'T, HUMANS WILL NOT
BE ABLE TO SURVIVE LONG.
THIS IS A WAR, THAT PUTS
AT STAKE TOTAL CONTROL
OF THE ENTIRE PLANET!
- THOSE WHO HAVE NO POWER, CAN
NEVER ASSERT CONTROL, COLONEL.
- ARE YOU SAYING
THAT I AM POWERLESS?
ARE YOU SAYING I AM POWERLESS?
- Renton: HE LOOKS
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
FROM HOW HE WAS BEFORE.
- Eureka: YES, BUT NIRVASH
IS STILL NIRVASH.
- THE COCKPIT IS BEING
REDESIGNED AROUND
A COMPLETELY NEW CONCEPT, RIGHT?
- NIRVASH IS VERY HAPPY
ABOUT IT.
- Renton: I SEE.
MR. MORITA!
- YES, WHAT IS IT?
- THERE'S NO REF BOARD.
- I KNOW THAT, IT'S UNFORTUNATE
BUT WE WERE UNABLE TO DESIGN
AND MAKE ONE IN THE TIME WE HAD.
- HUH?
- BUT DON'T WORRY.
I'VE ALREADY ASKED
AN INGENIOUS MECHANIC
TO WORK ON IT, EVEN THOUGH
HE'S AS GOOD AS RETIRED.
HE'S A MEAN, OLD MAN.
YOU KNOW WHO, RIGHT?
- GRAMPS!
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT DEWEY
IS DOING RIGHT ABOUT NOW?
HE'S SEEING THAT MEAN,
OLD LADY NAMED CODA.
I CAN TELL
THESE THINGS, YOU KNOW.
♪ NO ONE KNOWS NOTHING
KNOWS NOTHING ABOUT ME ♪
♪ EVERYONE IS WATCHING
JUST WATCHING A LIE. ♪
- ( door opens )
- ANEMONE.
- DOMINIC, I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE STUCK
BABYSITTING ALL OF THOSE KIDS.
- WHAT A GROUP THIS IS.
WHAT IS THE COLONEL
PLANNING ON DOING NOW?
- DID YOU SAY, "WHAT A GROUP?"
WHAT?! DID YOU GET
KICKED OUT OF THE BRIDGE, TOO?
ARE YOU STUPID OR SOMETHING?
- Ageha Member #1: A BLUEPRINT
CHANGE FOR THE REDESIGN
TO MINIMIZE
THE ENTRY SURFACE AREA
JUST GOT HERE
FROM TRESOR LABS.
- Ageha Member #2:
WE'LL PUT IT ON HOLD.
- Ageha Member #3:
YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
THEY'RE NOT TOTALLY UP
ON HOW WE'RE USING IT,
SO WE'LL HAVE
TO CHECK EVERYTHING OUT.
COMMUNICATION
FROM HEADQUARTERS--
THE AFX HAS REACHED
THE TARGETED ALTITUDE,
THERE ARE NO CHANGES
IN THE OPERATIONAL PLANS.
- Ageha Member #1:
TECTONIC AND ELECTROMAGNETIC
SENSORS ARE ONLINE.
- Ageha Member #2:
COMMENCING COUNTDOWN--
- Ageha Member #1:
FINAL CHECK, ALL SYSTEMS ARE GO.
- ATTENTION, ALL OBSERVERS,
WE ARE ABOUT TO BEGIN.
- THREE, TWO--
- ONE--
- ZERO!
- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- Ageha Member #2:
ALL RIGHT, YOU DID IT!
- Ageha Member #3:
RIGHT ON TARGET.
- WITH A MARGIN OF ERROR
LESS THAN 0.5!
- Ageha Member #3:
THAT'S JUST AMAZING.
- CONFIRM SEVERANCE
OF THE STREAM.
- HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
- IT'S COMING.
- THE WEAK CORAL SIGNALS
ARE CONFIRMED.
- ITS LOCATION?
- IT CAN'T BE DETERMINED YET.
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
THEIR LOSSES WERE?
- SEVERAL THOUSAND, I THINK.
I JUST HOPE THAT THIS FITS
INTO OUR PROJECTED RANGE.
- PLEASE, ANEMONE.
CALM DOWN, ALRIGHT?
- IT'S COMING.
- EUREKA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
EUREKA, TALK TO ME!
- IT'S COMING!
- SIR, A KUTE-CLASS CORALIAN
HAS BEEN CONFIRMED.
- WHERE'S IT LOCATED?  HOW FAR?
- DIRECTION ONE, THREE, ZERO.
DISTANCE 720 KILOMETERS.
IT'S FERES CITY!
- ( screaming )
- HELP ME!
- ( crying )
- ( whispering )
- WHAT IS SHE? LOOK AT HER.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
GET OVER TO FERES?
- ANOTHER SQUADRON HAS
ALREADY BEEN CALLED OUT.
BUT IT'S IMPORTANT FOR YOU
TO MAKE A GOOD SHOWING AS WELL.
AND PLEASE, TELL
MY CHILDREN THIS--
IT'S ALL HAPPENING
AS I EXPECTED.
- I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S FERES.
- 200 KILOMETERS NORTH
OF WHERE WE EXPECTED.
- WE'LL HAVE TO CHANGE
THE PARAMETERS
AND RECALCULATE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- Dewey:
THAT'S ALL.
- COLONEL!
- WHAT IS IT?
- ANEMONE'S CONDITION
IS NOT VERY GOOD, SIR.
- THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
THERE SHOULD BE
SUFFICIENT MEDICATION THERE.
- SIR!
- I'M TRUSTING YOU WITH
EVERYTHING ABOUT HER, DOMINIC.
BE SURE YOU DON'T LET ME DOWN.
- UNDERSTOOD, SIR.
- Eureka: EVERYONE,
EVERYTHING--THEY'RE CRYING.
- SO HAS IT BEGUN?
IS THIS THE AWAKENING?
- I DON'T KNOW,
THERE'S TOO LITTLE DATA.
WE HAVE TO GET THE SPECS
UP ON THE NIRVASH PRETTY FAST.
- WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
- IF THE TRUE AWAKENING
IS APPROACHING,
GETTING THE SPECS
UP ON THE NIRVASH HAS PRIORITY.
LET'S HEAD TO BELLFOREST.
WE'RE GETTING THE BOARD.
- Gidget:
BUT HOLLAND, THERE ARE PEOPLE
ASKING FOR HELP
OVER THERE, RIGHT?
- Talho: DON'T TALK LIKE
YOU KNOW ANYTHING.
THERE ARE THINGS
THAT WE CAN DO,
AND THINGS
THAT WE CAN'T, GIDGET.
THERE ARE TIMES WE'RE FORCED
TO MAKE DECISIONS
WE DON'T WANT TO MAKE.
- HOLLAND, WHAT ARE YOU
PLANNING TO DO
ABOUT THE RESTORATION
OF THE NIRVASH?
- I'LL HAVE YOU FINISH IT
ABOARD THE GEKKO.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
- HURRY UP, WE'RE DEPARTING NOW!
- Eureka and Renton:
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Talho: THE BOY AND
THE GIRL REACH FOR THE SKY,
WITH BELIEFS IN THEIR HEARTS.
THE NIRVASH, ACCEPTING
DEAR EMOTIONS,
EMITS TRUE RADIANCE
IN THE FAR REACHES OF THE SKIES.
NEXT EPISODE, "START IT UP."