- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Renton: EUREKA,
WHAT'S BEYOND THE GREAT WALL?
- Eureka:
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT THERE IS ONE WORD
I KNOW OF TO DESCRIBE IT.
- WHAT IS IT?
- FUTURE.
THAT IS WHAT IS BEYOND
THE GREAT WALL, RENTON.
ADROC SAID THAT TO ME.
- MY DAD DID?!
- MM-HMM.
- WAIT, YOU MEAN YOU KNOW
ALL ABOUT MY DAD?!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- YOU SHOULD HAVE TOLD ME
THAT YOU KNEW.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- ABOUT MY DAD!
- Eureka: WELL, I DIDN'T
THINK THAT YOU WOULD WANT
TO HEAR ABOUT HIM THAT MUCH.
WAS I WRONG?
- HE'S MY FAMILY!
JEEZ, ANYONE WOULD WANNA HEAR
ABOUT THEIR FAMILY,
WOULDN'T THEY?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
THAT, RENTON.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND?
IT'S THE NATURAL WAY
FOR PEOPLE TO THINK.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- WHAT'S WRONG,
IS THAT I'M NOT HUMAN.
- ( sneeze )
- News Reporter: AND NOW THE
LATEST NEWS FROM CAPITOL HILL,
WHICH HAS ONCE AGAIN
SEVERED ALL COMMUNICATIONS.
OUR CAPITAL CITY IS EXPERIENCING
THE GREATEST CRISIS
IN THE HISTORY OF OUR WORLD.
SIX HOURS AFTER THE BEGINNING
OF THE FIERCE BATTLE
BETWEEN THE CORALIANS AND
THE UNITED FEDERATIONS FORCES...
- HE'S MAKING THE CORALIANS
APPEAR, AND THEN PRETENDING
TO BE THE MESSIAH.
HIS PLAN IS WORKING PERFECTLY.
LOOK, HOLLAND,
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
BUT WE NEED TO THINK ABOUT
WHAT WE'RE DOING RIGHT NOW.
AND ABOUT WHAT WE
SHOULD BE DOING.
- DAMN!
- YEAH, WHAT WE CAN DO
RIGHT NOW... RIGHT.
- Master Norb:
DOES SOMETHING LIKE THIS
HAPPEN OFTEN BETWEEN YOU?
- Renton: WELL, I CAN'T SAY
THAT IT NEVER HAPPENS.
- HMM...
- "HMM," THAT'S ALL
YOU'VE GOT TO SAY?
- YOU WANNA HEAR SOMETHING ELSE?
- I MEAN, EUREKA AND I
ARE GONNA GET PAST
THE GREAT WALL, AREN'T WE?
- YOU AND EUREKA, HUH?
- IF YOU COULD JUST GIVE ME
SOME ADVICE OR SOMETHING--
- WHAT, EXACTLY,
DO YOU WANT TO DO?
HOW DO YOU WANT THINGS
TO END UP WITH HER?
- Hilda:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M NOT DOING
ANYTHING AT ALL, REALLY.
- SUSPICIOUS, VERY SUSPICIOUS.
- OKAY...
- Renton: NO!
I WASN'T READING THAT.
IT-- IT WAS A MISUNDERSTANDING!
- WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
- ( lighter flicking )
- Stoner:
WHAT CAN I BE DOING RIGHT NOW?
WHAT CAN I DO,
CONSIDERING I CAN'T OPERATE
AN LFO NOR THE SHIP.
THE ONLY THING I CAN DO
IS TELL WHAT TO US,
IS THE OBVIOUS TRUTH.
HOWEVER RIGHT NOW,
THE INFORMATION
FROM THE MASS MEDIA
IS FLOWING PAST EVERYONE'S EYES.
AND THAT'S WHAT'S SINKING
INTO PEOPLE'S HEARTS,
IS THE TRUTH.
IT'S POSSIBLE TO SET UP
A COUNTERATTACK AGAINST IT,
BUT IT WOULD BE
NOTHING MORE THAN THAT.
ON TOP OF THAT, DEWEY HAS
ALREADY LAUNCHED AN ATTACK
AGAINST THE OLD REGIME,
THE SAGE COUNCIL.
I'VE MISSED MY CHANCE.
FROM HERE ON I NEED TO COME UP
WITH A DIFFERENT WAY TO FIGHT.
THE UNSWAYING TRUTH,
SOMETHING THAT SURPASSES
ALL OTHER ATTACKS.
EUREKA, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- IT'S ADROC.
- News Reporter: WE ARE ALL
NOW STANDING IN A TIME
OF MOMENTOUS DECISION.
DO WE GO ALONG WITH THE COURAGE
THAT OUR HERO, ADROC THURSTON,
HAS SHOWN US AND STAND UP
WITH COLONEL DEWEY
TO FIGHT THE CORALIANS?
OR DO WE NOT FIGHT AT ALL?
THAT IS THE DECISION TO BE MADE.
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- WHAT DO WE THINK OF THAT?
I, UH...
- WELL, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU GUYS,
BUT I'M REALLY STARTING
TO FEEL SORRY FOR RENTON.
AND I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO ABOUT IT.
GUYS, YOU KNOW WE'RE
JUST ABOUT TO HAVE THEM
TRY AND GET PAST
THE GREAT WALL.
IF SOMETHING BAD
WERE TO HAPPEN BETWEEN THEM--
- WHY DON'T YOU LEAVE HIM ALONE?
- YEAH, I AGREE WITH HIM.
ANY WAY YOU LOOK AT IT
RENTON IS JUST AN ORDINARY BOY.
SO IT'D BE STRANGE FOR HIM
NOT TO THINK OF THAT STUFF.
- I THINK THE THING
THAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT HERE
IS HOW EUREKA
FEELS ABOUT IT ALL.
- RIGHT, GIDGET.
OF COURSE, THAT'S A GIVEN.
- UM, GUYS?
I HAVE A QUESTION THAT WE
SHOULD KEEP JUST BETWEEN US.
- WHAT IS IT?
- UH... WELL, NEVER MIND.
IT WAS JUST A STUPID THOUGHT.
- COME ON, MOONDOGGIE.
YOU CAN'T SAY THAT
AND THEN DROP IT.
IT'S GONNA DRIVE ME CRAZY.
- OH, WELL ALL RIGHT.
ARE THOSE TWO ABLE... TO DO IT?
- YOU'RE SUCH A JERK,
MOONDOGGIE!
- YOU CAN JUST GET OUT OF HERE,
RIGHT NOW!
- HEY NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
HOLD ON HERE.
THIS IS A QUESTION THAT COULD BE
IMPORTANT FOR RENTON.
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
I WAS A FOOL TO COME
AND ASK YOU GUYS FOR ADVICE.
LET'S GO, GIDGET.
- Stoner: A FAMILY, HUH?
I SEE, THAT'S A TOUGH QUESTION.
- Eureka:
WHY IS IT TOUGH?
- BECAUSE THERE'S
NO RIGHT ANSWER.
BESIDES, I'M LIKE RENTON,
I DON'T REMEMBER
MY DAD'S FACE ALL TOO WELL,
IF AT ALL.
I'M ONE OF THOSE
SO-CALLED WAR ORPHANS.
- A WAR ORPHAN?
- YEAH, SO I CAN UNDERSTAND
HOW RENTON WOULD GET
ALL WORKED UP ABOUT IT.
AND AT THE SAME TIME,
I CAN APPRECIATE HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT NOT UNDERSTANDING
WHY HE'S UPSET.
- STONER, IS IT ALL RIGHT
FOR ME TO STAY BY RENTON'S SIDE?
IS IT ALL RIGHT FOR ME TO KEEP
STAYING ABOARD THIS SHIP?
- ( door opens )
- EUREKA?
- Gidget:
WHAT'S THE MATTER, EUREKA?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ALL RIGHT NOW,
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- SHE'S HAVING
TROUBLE ESTABLISHING
A LINE OF COMMUNICATION
WITH RENTON.
- YOU MEAN THEY'RE NOT...
COMMUNICATING?
- YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
- IF YOU DON'T WANT TO DO IT,
IT'S ALL RIGHT
FOR YOU TO SAY NO.
- IF HE'S PERSISTENT ABOUT IT,
YOU CAN JUST PUNCH HIM!
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, GIDGET?
- UM... WHY DON'T WE GO BACK
TO MY ROOM AND TALK, OKAY?
- BUT, GIDGET--
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, THINGS
LIKE THIS SHOULD BE TALKED OUT
BETWEEN JUST US GIRLS.
- ( door closes )
- WHOA, WHAT WAS
ALL THAT ABOUT?
- I NEVER THOUGHT
ABOUT HOW I'D LIKE THINGS
TO END UP WITH EUREKA.
I WONDER, HOW DID
DAD AND MOM HIT IT OFF?
I MEAN, IF THEY DIDN'T
GO OUT AND GET MARRIED
AND DO STUFF LIKE THAT,
I WOULDN'T HAVE EVER BEEN BORN.
THAT'S RIGHT, NEVER BORN.
- ( door opens )
- MISTER MATTHIEU,
BROTHER DOGGIE, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( gasps )
- REALLY, IT'S NOT HOW IT LOOKS!
- REST ASSURED.
BOTH OF US ARE ON YOUR SIDE.
- Talho:
THIS IS THE SHORTEST ROUTE
TO THE LOCATION THAT NORB
GAVE US OF THE VODARAC SHRINE.
- OF COURSE, THE PROBLEM IS
STOPPING ALONG THE WAY
TO REFUEL.
- IN A PINCH, I KNOW
SOME PLACES WE CAN STOP.
BUT I'M WORRIED ABOUT HOW
THE ARMY'S MOVING AROUND
IN THAT AREA.
- IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE HE TAKES OVER
THE CAPITAL,
USING THIS RIOT
AS A JUSTIFICATION.
- Man: MAYBE, BUT NOT EVERYONE
IN THE ARMY'S GOING TO AGREE
TO GO ALONG
WITH A COUP D'ETAT.
- BUT ANYONE OPPOSING HIM
WILL BE PUT AWAY IN A HURRY.
THAT'S OBVIOUS, CONSIDERING
HOW FAR HE'S GONE
TO ENGINEER THIS COUP.
- I'D SAY TWO WEEKS,
AT THE MOST,
FOR HIM TO REPLACE EVERYONE.
ALL THE WAY OUT TO
THE RURAL STATE ARMY
COMMANDERS IN THE FIELD.
- SO THEN WE NEED
TO ARRIVE THERE
BEFORE THAT HAPPENS.
- Mischa ( intercom ):
TALHO, COULD YOU COME
TO MY OFFICE
WHEN YOU HAVE A CHANCE.
- ROGER THAT,
I'LL BE RIGHT OVER.
- Mischa ( intercom ):
YOU TOO, HOLLAND.
- WHY DO I HAVE TO GO?
- YOU'RE THE FATHER, AREN'T YOU?
- ( laughing )
- HEY, HOLLAND!
- EUREKA, WHAT'S WRONG?
HOLLAND, IS IT TRUE
YOU WERE A DAD?
NO, BUT PRETTY SOON
I'M GONNA BECOME ONE.
- OH REALLY, HOW?
- WAIT, YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW?
YEAH, HOW?
- DO HUMANS REALLY NEED
TO HAVE A DAD AROUND?
DADS ARE REALLY IMPORTANT,
AREN'T THEY?  AREN'T THEY?
- WELL, I WON'T KNOW
UNTIL I BECOME ONE.
- OH, SO MAYBE THAT'S WHY
RENTON WAS SO AGGRESSIVE.
- WHAT?
- MAYBE RENTON WANTS
TO BECOME A DAD HIMSELF.
- RENTON!
WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?!
- Stoner: EVERY WAVE STARTS
FROM THE MOST PETTY OF THINGS.
- HOT!
- Renton:
UM... HEY GUYS?
WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU JUST LEAVE IT TO US.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- DAMN YOU!
WHAT THE HELL
DID YOU DO TO EUREKA?!
- Stoner: AND WHEN THEY
FINALLY GET TOGETHER,
PERHAPS THEY WILL
BECOME A GIANT WAVE
THAT TURNS OVER THE WORLD.
I GUESS.
- SO THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON.
- Renton:
YOU SEE...
MY SISTER AND MY GRANDFATHER
ARE THE ONLY FAMILY MEMBERS
THAT I'VE EVER KNOWN.
AND I NEVER THOUGHT THAT EUREKA
WOULD KNOW DAD,
SO I GUESS I GOT CARRIED AWAY.
MY WHOLE LIFE I'VE ALWAYS
THOUGHT THAT I HATED MY DAD.
HE JUST TOOK OFF
AND ABANDONED HIS FAMILY.
AND SPENT ALL HIS TIME
DOING RESEARCH.
I'VE NEVER EVEN SEEN HIS FACE.
BUT SUDDENLY,
SUDDENLY I REALIZED HOW MUCH
I WANTED TO KNOW ABOUT HIM.
HOW MUCH I LONGED FOR HIM.
- THEN YOU HAVE TO GO
AND TALK TO HER ABOUT HIM.
YOU SHOULD HEAR IT
FROM HER DIRECTLY.
ALL ABOUT YOUR DAD--
THE HERO, ADROC THURSTON.
- IT'S GOING WELL.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE FREE
TO GET UP NOW.
- HOW STRANGE.
- YES, BUT THAT'S FAMILY.
EVERYONE STARTS WITH THE FEELING
OF DEEP AFFECTION.
- AFFECTION.
- YEP, AND THEN WHEN IT
TURNS INTO TRUE LOVE,
A BRAND NEW LIFE
COMES INTO BEING.
- AMAZING.
HUMANS ARE SO AMAZING.
- ( door opens )
- EUREKA...
- I CAN'T HEAR ANYTHING.
- THEY HAVEN'T STARTED
TALKING YET.
- I'M SORRY.
- SORRY.
- SORRY ABOUT YELLING
AT YOU EARLIER.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT, RENTON.
- BUT IT IS
ALL MY FAULT, EUREKA.
- IT'S NOT.
I'M THE ONE TO BLAME.
- EUREKA...
- IT'S BECAUSE-- IT'S BECAUSE
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
FAMILIES, FATHERS,
BROTHERS, SISTERS.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THINGS LIKE THAT.
THAT'S WHY
I DIDN'T REALIZE
THAT ADROC WAS SUCH
AN IMPORTANT PERSON TO YOU.
I SWEAR I DIDN'T KNOW!
AND SO--
- I SUCK.
- WHAT?
- I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
THAT YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
AN UNDERSTANDING OF THINGS
LIKE PARENTS AND FAMILIES.
I'M SO SORRY,
I REALLY DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE
YOU FEEL BAD LIKE THIS.
- RENTON?
- I ACTED SO HIGH AND MIGHTY.
AND SAID I WOULD
ALWAYS PROTECT YOU.
BUT I FAILED.
I DON'T HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO SIT NEXT TO YOU
IN THE NIRVASH.
- MANY YEARS AGO, ADROC
SAID THE SAME THING TO ME.
- MY DAD DID?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
IT WAS BEFORE I WAS ASSIGNED
TO WORK WITH THE S.O.F.
ADROC WAS THE LEAD RESEARCHER
IN THE PROJECT
THAT WAS ASSIGNED TO ANALYZE
ME AND THE NIRVASH.
HE WAS ALWAYS AT MY SIDE.
I DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT ANYTHING.
SO HE TAUGHT ME HOW TO TALK,
HOW TO ACT,
HOW TO CONTROL THE NIRVASH,
AND LOTS OF OTHER THINGS.
RENTON, HE TAUGHT ME SO MUCH.
AND HE-- HE WOULD SAY TO ME,
"I'LL ALWAYS
PROTECT YOU, EUREKA.."
- DAD SAID THAT?
- BUT THEN ONE DAY,
ADROC SAID TO ME,
"I'VE FAILED, EUREKA."
- WAS THAT THE SUMMER OF LOVE?
- MM-HMM.
- Eureka: BACK THEN,
I DIDN'T REALIZE THE MEANING
OF THE WORDS THAT ADROC SAID.
BUT EVEN NOW, I REMEMBER
IT CLEARLY.  HE SAID,
"I DON'T HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO SIT NEXT TO YOU.
I HAVE CHILDREN, AND I NEED
TO PROTECT THEM
AND THEIR FUTURES.
AND SO, I CAN'T STAND BY AND LET
THIS WORLD COME TO AN END.
I'M SORRY."
THAT WAS THE LAST DAY
I SPENT WITH ADROC.
BEFORE I REALIZED IT,
IT WAS ALL OVER.
SO YOU SEE, RENTON?
ADROC PROTECTED EVERYONE.
HE PROTECTED THE WHOLE WORLD
THAT DAY.
AND I'M SURE THAT I
WAS A PART OF IT.
- WHY ARE THE TWO
OF THEM CRYING?
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT'S GOING ON IN THERE?
- WOULD YOU KEEP STILL?
- HEY, LEADER?
- JEEZ, SHUT UP.
- MY DAD HAD BEEN
THINKING ABOUT US AFTER ALL.
DAD DIDN'T FORGET ABOUT ME
OR SIS, OR GRAMPS,
OR ANYONE ELSE.
- NO HE DIDN'T.
- DAD REALLY DID IT!
HE SACRIFICED HIMSELF
AND SAVED US ALL!
- I'M CERTAIN THAT I WAS
ABLE TO MEET YOU
BECAUSE MY DAD DID WHAT HE DID
AND PROTECTED YOU.
BECAUSE MY DAD WAS THERE,
I MET YOU.
- RENTON, I JUST NOW
FIGURED IT OUT.
TO PROTECT YOUR CHILDREN,
EVEN IF IT MEANS
SACRIFICING YOUR LIFE,
THAT'S WHAT BEING
A DAD IS ABOUT.
AND THAT'S WHAT A FAMILY IS.
- EUREKA...
- IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
ADROC IS--
IT'S LIKE HE WAS MY DAD!
- ( laughing )
- WAIT A MINUTE,
NOW THEY'RE LAUGHING.
- WHAT IS GOING ON?
- Stoner:
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- LEADER, I HAVE TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
ACTUALLY, I WANT TO USE
THIS AS THE COVER SHOT
FOR THE FIRST RENEWAL ISSUE
OF ray=out MAGAZINE.
I BELIEVE THAT IN THIS PHOTO,
IS WHERE THE TRUTH LIES.
EUREKA AND RENTON,
A CORALIAN AND A HUMAN,
RIDE TOGETHER, SHARING THE JOY
OF THE EXPERIENCE.
I BELIEVE THAT THIS
IS THE TRUTH
THAT MAY BECOME HOPE
FOR THE PEOPLE.
A TRUTH THAT IS
NEITHER THE HARD-LINE
NOR THE RESISTANCE.
HOWEVER, I DON'T WANT TO HURT
EITHER OF YOUR FEELINGS
BY USING THIS
AS THE COVER OF THE MAGAZINE
IF YOU DON'T WANT ME TO.
- NO, IT'S FINE.
I'M ALL RIGHT WITH IT.
I'M HAPPY.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU, RENTON?
- YEAH, I'M ALL RIGHT
WITH IT, TOO.
PLEASE, GO AHEAD AND USE IT.
- GOOD, THEN IT'S DECIDED.
- SO, YOU'RE FINE
WITH IT TOO, LEADER?
- FINE OR NOT, YOU'RE THE ONE
IN CHARGE OF ray=out.
AREN'T YOU?
Linck:
WHAT'S GOING ON? WHATCHA DOING?
- OH, HI MOMMA!
THERE YOU ARE.
- HEY, WHAT'S THAT PICTURE?
- LET ME SEE, LET ME SEE!
- Linck:
NO, LET ME SEE!
- FAMILY, HUH.
- I HAVE AN URGENT REPORT.
THE REBEL FORCES LED
BY DEWEY NOVAK
HAVE DEPLOYED POISONOUS GAS
ON THE LOWER FLOORS.
REGARDING THE THREE OF YOU,
WE FEEL IT'S ESSENTIAL
THAT YOU EVACUATE
FROM HERE IMMEDIATELY!
- TO THINK THAT HE'D EVEN USE
THE CORALIANS LIKE THAT.
- HE NEVER EVEN CONSIDERED
WHETHER A BLOODLESS REVOLUTION
WAS POSSIBLE.
- THIS IS ALL HAPPENING
BECAUSE YOU DECIDED
TO KEEP THE SECRET
HIDDEN FROM ALL OF US.
- Braya: TO EXPLOIT THE TRUTH
IS NOT THE ONLY WAY
FOR ONE TO GAIN HAPPINESS.
THE REVERSE CAN ALSO HAPPEN.
- Kuzemi:
THE INFORMATION CAME TOO LATE.
WHEN THE AGEHA REPORT
FINALLY CAME IN FOR US TO SEE,
THERE WERE ALREADY
TOO MANY PEOPLE ON THIS LAND.
- SO MANY, THAT WE COULD NOT
ALL FIT ABOARD THE GIANT ARK
THAT HAD GUIDED US
TO THIS PLANET.
ARE YOU GOING TO RELEASE US
FROM THE ENDURING PAIN
OF HAVING HIDDEN THE WHOLE TRUTH
ABOUT THIS LIVING PLANET
FROM THE TEEMING MASSES?
- IF YOU MANAGE
TO DEFEAT US,
YOU WILL CARRY THAT BURDEN
WITH YOU FOREVER.
- IF THAT IS YOUR POSITION--
- ( gunshots )
- FROM THE MOMENT I LET YOU
OUT OF YOUR CELL,
I KNEW THAT THINGS
WOULD HAPPEN AS THEY DID.
DEWEY NOVAK.
- Eureka and Renton:
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Talho:
THE STORY MOVES ON
WITH THE ENTIRE WORLD
NOW INVOLVED.
WHAT DID GEKKOSTATE ACQUIRE
IN THE HARSH PATH
OF THEIR JOURNEY
TOWARDS THE GREAT WALL?
NEXT EPISODE--
"JOIN THE FUTURE."