- Stoner: ABOUT 10,000 YEARS AGO
ON OUR MOTHER PLANET EARTH,
A MAJORITY OF THE PLANET'S
SURFACE WAS COVERED
IN SALT-FILLED WATER
CALLED OCEAN.
ONE OF THE SPORTS THAT TOOK
PLACE ON THAT PLANET
WAS AN ACTIVITY
CALLED "SURFING."
THEY SAY IT WAS A SPORT
THAT RESEMBLED LIFTING,
A PASTIME THAT WE WHO CURRENTLY
LIVE ON THIS PROMISED LAND
LIKE TO DO.
THOSE THAT PERFORMED
THIS SURFING
WERE WIDELY KNOWN AS SURFERS.
THEY RODE THE WAVES IN THE
OCEAN, COMMUNICATED WITH NATURE,
AND FELT THE EXISTENCE
OF THAT PLANET, THAT WORLD,
WITH THEIR ENTIRE BODIES.
YES, IT WAS VERY
MUCH LIKE HOW WE,
PEOPLE BORN ON THIS PLANET
WITH A SKY FILLED WITH TRAPARS,
THROUGH WAVE RIDING KNOWN
AS LIFTING,
FEEL WITH OUR ENTIRE BEINGS
THE EXISTENCE OF THE SCUB CORALS
AND OF THE VERY SOURCE
OF THE PLANET ITSELF.
- Renton:
THIS IS NIRVASH.
CURRENTLY WE ARE FLYING
THE SKIES OVER GREMIKOWA.
- Talho: ANY SIGNS OF LIFE?
DO YOU SEE ANYTHING MOVING?
- I SEE NOTHING.
IT'S NOTHING BUT RUINS.
- UNDERSTOOD.  COME ON BACK.
- ROGER THAT.
EUREKA, TALHO'S TELLING US
TO GO BACK.
- ( sobbing )
- EUREKA.
EUREKA.  EUREKA!
LET'S GO BACK TO
THE GEKKO, OKAY?
- BUT WHAT IF THERE'S STILL
SOMEONE INJURED BUT ALIVE?
- WE'VE BEEN HERE FOR HOURS.
LET'S GO BACK.
- RENTON.
- EUREKA.
WE HAVE TO GIVE UP.
WE GOT HERE TOO--
TOO LATE.  THAT'S ALL.
- I'M SORRY, RENTON.
- CONFIRMING THE ARRIVAL
OF THE NIRVASH
AND THE CLOSING
OF THE MAIN HATCH.
- FOR NOW, HAVE THEM TAKE IT
EASY AND GET SOME REST.
AFTER ALL, THEY JUST CAME BACK
FROM SEEING A GRUESOME PLACE.
DON'T BE SO DEPRESSED.
- HUH?
- SEE, IT WASN'T THAT
WE ARRIVED HERE TOO LATE.
THEY JUST ARRIVED HERE
TOO EARLY.
WOZ AND HAP ARE DOING
THE CALCULATIONS
IN THE CENTRAL COMPUTING ROOM.
MOST LIKELY, THE AREA OF DAMAGE
HAS GOTTEN BIGGER THIS TIME.
IN OTHER WORDS,
THEY'RE GETTING MORE ACCURATE.
THIS ISN'T COINCIDENCE.
YOU COULD SAY THIS IS PROOF
THAT IT'S SOMETHING ARTIFICIAL.
IT'S ALL RIGHT FOR YOU
TO WORRY ABOUT IT.
AS A FULL-TIME MEMBER OF THIS
SHIP, I'LL MAKE ONE REQUEST.
LET YOUR CREW
GET SOME REST.
EVERYONE'S EXHAUSTED.
- ALL RIGHT,
BUT NOT ALL AT ONCE.
STAY IN PATROL MODE
AND GIVE HALF THE SHIP A BREAK.
- ROGER THAT.
- THE INTELLIGENCE DEPARTMENT'S
FIREWALL HAS BEEN FORTIFIED,
AND THEY'VE SET DECOYS,
WHICH EXPLAINS THE FAKE
INFORMATION HAP FOUND
ON MASTER NORB.
IS THE MILITARY'S INFO
MESSED UP, TOO?
NO, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
COME ON, AT THE LEAST HE--
- Holland: YOU SHOULD GET
SOME REST, TOO.
YOU HAVEN'T GOTTEN
ANY SLEEP SINCE TRESOR.
- IDIOT, I'M BETTER OFF
THAN YOU ARE.
YOU'RE STILL INJURED.
- I HAVEN'T DONE MUCH
BUT LAY AROUND LATELY.
YOU SHOULD TAKE
CARE OF YOURSELF, TALHO.
- HEY, HOLLAND.
- HMM?
WHAT?
- NOTHING.  NEVER MIND.
- REALLY, I'M COMPLETELY
ASTOUNDED.
THE DATA WE DOWNLOADED
IMPLIES THAT
THE AIRBORNE FORM OF NIRVASH WAS
PLANNED FROM THE BEGINNING.
- DIDN'T I TELL YOU THAT?
RENTON, WHAT'S YOUR
IMPRESSION AS A PILOT?
- WELL, I THOUGHT
IT WOULD TAKE A LOT MORE TIME
THAN IT DID FOR ME
TO GET USED TO IT,
IT FEELS STRANGE THAT IT WAS
SO MUCH EASIER THAN
I HAD IMAGINED IT WOULD BE.
- THAT'S MY POINT.
THIS IS THE RESULTING SHAPE
THAT YOU TWO WISHED FOR.
WAIT, WHERE'D SHE GO?
- OH.  EUREKA WENT BACK
TO HER ROOM TO REST.
I THINK WHAT HAPPENED DOWN
IN GREMIKOWA WAS A SHOCK TO HER.
BESIDES, SHE'S--
WELL, I THINK WE JUST NEED
TO LEAVE HER ALONE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO BE EUREKA'S PARTNER.
WHY AREN'T YOU AT HER SIDE?
- WELL, I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT TO SAY TO HER.
- YOU JUST DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU?
HERE.  THIS WILL DO IT.
- STRAWBERRY CANDY?
- RIGHT.
IT DOESN'T REALLY HAVE TO
BE THIS.
YOU JUST NEED A REASON
TO START TALKING.
- WHY WON'T YOU GIVE IT TO ME?
- HAVING THIS IS A NO-GO
FOR YOU, KID.
( grunts ) THIS IS
A SMALL PIECE OF MEMORY
THAT THE LITTLE CUB
AND I SHARE TOGETHER.
- BUT EUREKA AND I DON'T
HAVE ANY LITTLE ITEMS LIKE THAT.
- THESE THINGS REQUIRE MEMORIES
ATTACHED TO THEM.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE
FOR YOU TWO.
GO FIND A MEMORY THAT
YOU TWO CAN SHARE.
- Talho: SO NOSTALGIC.
BOTH OF US ARE SO YOUNG HERE,
IT'S DISGUSTING.
WE TALKED TOGETHER
ABOUT ANYTHING
AND EVERYTHING BACK THEN.
THIS WAS WHEN I TOLD HIM THAT
I'D NEVER BEEN ON A BOARD BEFORE
AND HE IMMEDIATELY
HAD TO.
THAT'S HOW HE ALWAYS IS.
HOLLAND ALWAYS GIVES
ME ALL SORTS OF THINGS,
BUT HE ALWAYS KEEPS QUIET
ABOUT THE TRUTH
AND WHAT HE HAS PRESSING
ON HIS MIND,
THINGS THAT HE NEEDS
TO GET DONE,
WHAT HE REALLY WANTS,
HOW HE REALLY FEELS.
ALWAYS ACTING SO TOUGH.
UNFAIR.
YOU'RE SO UNFAIR, HOLLAND.
- Stoner: THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO CONFIRM WITH YOU.
OUR OBJECTIVE HAS BEEN
TO DO RESEARCH ON CORALIANS
AND TO GET IN CONTACT
WITH THEM,
TO PREVENT THE GOVERNMENT
FROM HIDING THEIR EXISTENCE
AND TO STOP THE MILITARY
FROM SECRETLY ERADICATING THEM.
- BECAUSE THAT WOULD MEAN
A BATTLE TO THE DEATH
BETWEEN THE CORALIAN RACE
AND THE HUMANS WHO MOVED
ONTO THIS PLANET AFTER THEM.
- Matthieu:
SO HOW ABOUT IT, LEADER?
IF WHAT YOU SAID WAS TRUE,
AND EUREKA WAS SOMEONE
THAT THIS PLANET
THAT THE SCUB CORALS CREATED,
DO YOU REALLY THINK WE STILL
KEEP DOING WHAT WE'VE BEEN DOING
FOR ALL THIS TIME?
IT'S NOT JUST THE GOVERNMENT
AND MILITARY NOW.
DON'T WE GO UP AGAINST
MONSTERS, TOO,
LIKE THE ONES THAT SHOWED UP
NEAR GREMIKOWA?
AND UNDER CONDITIONS LIKE THAT
CAN WE REALLY AIM
FOR COEXISTENCE BETWEEN HUMAN
BEINGS AND THE CORALIANS?
- SORRY. I NEED SOME TIME.
TO THINK IT OVER.
I KNOW THAT AS A RESULT
OF EVERYTHING,
OUR OBJECTIVES ARE
STARTING TO CHANGE.
I ALSO KNOW THAT AT THIS POINT
WE CAN'T GO BACK
TO BEING THE PEOPLE
WE USED TO BE.
ALL THE MORE REASON I NEED
MORE TIME.  PLEASE.
Man: SHONAN EAST.  SOUTHERLY
WINDS, WIND FORCE ONE.
TRANSPARENCE LIGHT PARTICLES,
18, LATER 16.
- Renton:
IT'S NO GOOD.
I CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING.
IN FACT THE TRUTH IS
I DON'T HAVE ANY ITEMS AT ALL.
- RENTON, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- HUH?
- WHAT'S WITH THE BIG MESS?
AND JUST LOOK AT YOU.
DID YOU STAY UP ALL NIGHT?
- MISS TALHO!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT GOOD
MEMORABILIA IS.
- MEMORABILIA?
( laughs )
- COME ON, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO LAUGH ABOUT IT.
- IT'S FUNNY.
- CUT IT OUT.  I'M SERIOUS.
I'M SERIOUSLY THINKING
ABOUT EUREKA.
- YOU IDIOT.  THE ITEM YOU PICK
ISN'T WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
SO WHAT, YOU WERE RUMMAGING
THOUGH BOOKS IN SEARCH
OF SOMETHING THAT YOU COULD USE?
- YEAH, WHY NOT?
THE ONLY KIND OF STUFF
I'VE GOT IS LIFTING GEAR.
- IT'S NOT LIKE YOU CAN
GET HER ATTENTION
WITH SOMETHING FROM A BOOK.
IN THE END, IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER WHAT THE ITEM IS.
WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT
ARE THE MEMORIES
OF THE GOOD TIMES YOU'VE HAD
WITH THAT PERSON.
IN FACT, THAT'S THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING OF ALL.
THE TRUTH IS, RENTON,
HOW YOU SPENT THE TIME THAT YOU
HAVE WITH THE PERSON YOU LOVE,
HOW WONDERFUL THAT
TIME TOGETHER WAS,
THAT'S WHAT'S MOST IMPORTANT
TO PEOPLE.
MEMORABILIA ARE NOTHING
BUT THINGS THAT JUST HAPPENED
TO BE LYING AROUND
AT THAT POINT IN TIME.
- ( sighs )
( screams )
I GET IT!
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU CAN'T MAKE SPECIAL MEMORIES
WHEN YOU'RE TRYING
TO USE SOMETHING THAT YOU
DON'T HAVE IN COMMON
WITH THE OTHER PERSON.
MISS TALHO, WHAT IS
THAT OVER THERE?
- WHAT?
- LOOK DOWN THERE.
WHAT IS THAT SHINY STUFF?
- HMM.
OH, THAT'S TRAPAR DUST.
- TRAPAR DUST?
- RIGHT.  IT'S A PHENOMENON
THAT HAPPENS ONCE IN A WHILE
WHEN THERE'S A REALLY DENSE
TRAPAR WAVE NEARBY.
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN
IT BEFORE, RENTON?
- I'VE NEVER EVEN HEARD
OF IT BEFORE.
WOW, AMAZING!
THIS MEANS THERE'S A REALLY GOOD
TRAPAR WAVE CLOSE TO US NOW.
TRUE.  WE'RE FAIRLY CLOSE TO
A PRETTY FAMOUS SPOT.
HOW ABOUT IT, RENTON,
DO YOU WANT TO GO LIFTING NOW?
- LIFTING?
- WHY NOT?
- Man:
OH, MAN, THAT WAS SO CLOSE.
IT'S A GOOD THING THE
MALFUNCTION OF THE FLY-BY-WIRE
LINK DIDN'T HAPPEN DURING
THE BATTLE WITH THE IZUMO.
- Man #2: YES, REALLY.
OF COURSE IF WE HAD PASSED
THROUGH THIS AREA,
THERE WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
ANY PLACE TO STOP
FOR AT LEAST TWO MORE DAYS.
- ALL RIGHT,
SYSTEM CHECKS COMPLETE.
I CAN'T FIND ANY PROBLEMS
WITH THE CONTROL UNITS.
- THAT'S WHAT I WAS
AFRAID OF.
- I THINK IT'S THE CENTRAL
COMPUTING SYSTEM.
- THIS IS A PAIN.
- WHERE DID TALHO GO?
SHE'S THE ONE THAT
REPORTED THE MALFUNCTION
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- MISS TALHO, ARE YOU SURE IT
WAS ALL RIGHT TO LIE
AND SAY THAT THE FLY-BY-WIRE
SYSTEM WAS BROKEN?
UM, SO WHAT IS IT YOU WANTED
TO SHOW ME?
OW!  SORRY, MISS TALHO.
WHAT IS THAT THING?
MISS TALHO?
WOW!  AMAZING!
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S SO COOL.
I'VE NEVER SEEN A LONG BOARD
LIKE IT.  IS IT REALLY YOURS?
- YEAH, I'LL LEND IT TO YOU.
- YOU REALLY MEAN IT?
- BUT YOU CAN'T GO ON IT
BY YOURSELF.
I WANT YOU AND EUREKA TO RIDE
THIS BOARD TOGETHER.
USE YOUR FEELINGS FOR HER
TO REACH OUT
AND PUT HER GRIEVING MIND
AT EASE.
- I JUST HAVE NO IDEA HOW
TO EVEN BRING IT UP TO HER.
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
FIGURE THAT OUT FOR YOURSELF.
- HEY, WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
- NOW LISTEN UP, RENTON.
LOVING SOMEONE FROM AFAR
IS A BIG LIE.
IF YOU REALLY LOVE HER, THEN YOU
HAVE TO SHOW HER HOW YOU FEEL.
ALL RIGHT, RENTON,
GO GET HER!
- CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
DID YOU TELL THAT LIE
FOR ME AND EUREKA?
- DON'T BE SO CONCEITED.
SEE YOU LATER.
NOW I THINK I'LL JUST GO DEAL
WITH A BIG BABY OF MY OWN.
- WILL I BE ALL RIGHT?
I'VE NEVER RIDDEN ANYTHING OTHER
THAN SHORT BOARDS BEFORE.
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
- WHAT THE HELL DOES IT LOOK
LIKE WE'RE DOING?
WE'RE GOING LIFTING.
- YES, I CAN SEE THAT MUCH.
I'M ASKING HOW YOU GUYS CAN
BE SO AT EASE ABOUT EVERYTHING.
SONIA, MAYBE YOU'RE NOT GETTING
ENOUGH CALCIUM IN YOUR DIET.
- YOU'RE AS BAD AS THEY ARE. HOW
CAN YOU JUST SUNBATHE SO CALMLY?
- RELAX.  I JUST HAPPEN TO BE
SITTING HERE READING MY REPORTS
WHILE GETTING A LITTLE
FRESH AIR.
YOU SEE?
- WELL, WE'LL BE GOING NOW.
- HEY, WAIT!
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
- SO WHAT ARE YOU
PLANNING TO DO FROM HERE ON?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE NOW FOR YOU
TO CONTACT THEM MERELY
BY WAITING FOR THE CORALIAN
TO REAPPEAR, RIGHT?
AND YOU FINALLY HAVE YOUR TRUMP
CARD, EUREKA AND RENTON.
YET, IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO GET CLOSE TO THEM
WITH THE ANTIBODY CORALIANS
AROUND.
FURTHERMORE, THE ANTIBODIES
AND THE DESTRUCTIVE WEAPON
OF THE MILITARY--
- THERE IS A WAY.
I'M OUT OF TIME,
BUT THERE IS A WAY.
IF RENTON AND EUREKA CAN
CONTACT MASTER NORB.
- THERE YOU ARE.
JEEZ, WHERE DID YOU
WALK OFF TO?
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU.
- TALHO.
- ( screaming )
- ( laughs )
- WHOA!
- Renton: EUREKA.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO SAY TO YOU,
BUT IF YOU FEEL EVEN
THE SLIGHTEST BIT AT EASE
BY MY BEING HERE AND IT HELPS
YOU SORT THINGS OUT,
THEN I THINK IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT CRUEL THINGS
ARE AWAITING US IN THE FUTURE,
BUT THIS IS ABOUT ALL
I CAN DO FOR YOU
RIGHT NOW, EUREKA.
SO IF YOU'RE UP TO IT,
WILL YOU COME OUTSIDE WITH ME?
- YOU DON'T THINK
I'M TOO TROUBLESOME?
YOU DON'T THINK THAT I'M SOME
KIND OF NUISANCE, DO YOU?
- NO, EUREKA.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THERE'S NO WAY THAT I'D
EVER BE THINKING THAT.
LOOK, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
TRUST ME, OKAY?
- RENTON, I CAN TRUST YOU?
- OF COURSE.
- Woman:
I DON'T LIKE THIS AT ALL.
AT THIS POINT IN TIME,
EUREKA'S VALUE
AS A CORALIAN IS ON THE RISE.
I JUST WONDER IF IT'S
BECAUSE OF THOSE THINGS
CALLED THE ANTIBODIES?
OR IS IT--
MY LITTLE CUB.  HEY, WHAT ARE
YOU READING SO SERIOUSLY?
- I REALLY WISH YOU WOULD STOP
CALLING ME THAT STUPID NAME.
SO HAVE YOU BEEN
SPEAKING WITH HOLLAND?
- OH, WELL, I THOUGHT
ABOUT TALKING TO HIM,
BUT THOSE TWO SEEMED TO BE
IN A GOOD MOOD,
SO I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE BEST
NOT TO INTERRUPT THEM.
- YOU LANDED US HERE ON PURPOSE,
DIDN'T YOU?
- LATELY, YOU'VE LOOKED SO DOWN
AND IN PAIN ALL THE TIME.
GO LIFTING.
IT'LL DOUBLE AS YOUR REHAB.
YOU WANT TO, RIGHT?
- OF COURSE I DO,
BUT WHEN I THINK
THAT THIS WILL BE
MY LAST LIFT.
- ( gasps ) YOUR WHAT?
- I WON'T HAVE
ANY MORE OPPORTUNITIES
TO LIFT AFTER THIS.
THIS IS MY LAST RIDE.
I WANT YOU
TO WATCH ME GET THROUGH IT.
OKAY, TALHO?
HOLLAND.
- HEY, STONER.
- YEAH.
- OUR LEADER'S LIFTING STRAIGHT
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN A WHILE.
SHOULDN'T YOU TAKE PICTURES
OF IT?
- I WOULDN'T MIND TAKING
PICTURES OF IT,
BUT I DON'T KNOW ABOUT RECORDING
A MAN TOUTED AS A GENIUS
LOOKING LIKE THAT
- IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
AFTER A CRITICAL INJURY
LIKE HIS,
IT'S A MIRACLE
HE CAN LIFT AT ALL.
- ( grunting )
- HOLLAND, PLEASE!
THAT'S ENOUGH ALREADY.
PLEASE, STOP IT NOW.
PLEASE, HOLLAND.
YOU GOTTA STOP THIS!
- SHUT UP!
- I UNDERSTAND YOU.
I UNDERSTAND YOU,
SO PLEASE STOP IT, HOLLAND.
HOLLAND.  HOLLAND.
GET UP, HOLLAND.
SPEAK TO ME.
- I'M SO PATHETIC, TALHO.
I'M PATHETIC, AREN'T I?
I'M SORRY.
THE ONLY THING I HAD ANY TALENT
FOR WAS LIFTING.
- BUT YOU STILL LIKE IT,
DON'T YOU?
YEAH, I LOVE LIFTING,
AND THIS PLANET
THAT LETS ME LIFT.
THAT'S WHY I CAN'T FORGIVE
THE EXISTENCE OF BEINGS
THAT WANT TO DESTROY IT.
TALHO, NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS
FROM NOW ON,
I WANT TO PROTECT THIS PLANET
THAT I MET YOU ON.
AND YOU, FOR LOVING ME
DESPITE BEING SO PATHETIC.
- IDIOT! ( crying )
YOU'RE MAKING ALL MY MAKEUP
RUN OFF OF MY FACE.
- HOLLAND, WHAT?
- SORRY, BUT CAN I BORROW
THIS FOR A WHILE?
JUST FOR A WHILE.
COME ON.  OH.
- OH, IT'S OUR LONG BOARD.
I LENT IT TO RENTON
AND EUREKA.
- I HOPE THIS TURNS OUT TO BE A
GOOD MEMORY FOR THE TWO OF THEM.
- JUST LIKE IT WAS FOR US.
- UNTIL NOW
I'VE BEEN LIVING MY LIFE
BY USING ALL SORTS
OF THINGS.
TO SURVIVE, I'VE USED LIFTING
AND THE ENTIRE COUNTERCULTURE
SURROUNDING IT.
WHAT I DIDN'T REALIZE WAS THAT
I HURTING THEM
EVERY TIME I USED THEM.
AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
SAYING I WAS PROTECTING
SOMETHING IMPORTANT
I ALSO HURT A LOT OF PEOPLE,
LIKE EUREKA AND RENTON.
I'M SORRY
FOR WHAT I DID TO YOU TWO.
FORGIVE ME.
- HOLLAND.
- BUT THAT'S NOT
WHAT I CAME HERE TO SAY.
AS OF THIS MOMENT,
THE GEKKOSTATE IS DISBANDING.
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT'S WITH THIS
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- WE KNOW WHERE MASTER NORB IS.
- WHAT?
- ONE OF THE ASSISTANTS
FROM MY INTELLIGENCE DEPARTMENT
DAYS FOUND HIM.
APPARENTLY, MASTER NORB HAS
APPEARED ALONE IN THE CAPITOL
SEEKING AUDIENCE
WITH THE THREE SAGES.
- THE CAPITOL?
- WE DON'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME.
NORB WHO HAS BEEN IN COMPLETE
HIDING FOR THE PAST THREE YEARS
SHOWED UP IN THE ENEMY
HEADQUARTERS OF ALL PLACES,
WHICH MEANS HE'S RESIGNED
HIMSELF TO THE SITUATION.
THE THING IS WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO LOSE HIM RIGHT NOW.
LOSING HIM MEANS
LOSING THE POSSIBILITY
OF HUMANS AND CORALIANS
COEXISTING ON THIS PLANET,
LIKE WHAT WE HAVE RIGHT HERE
IN FRONT OF OUR EYES.
I'M GOING TO GO INTO THE CAPITOL
TO RESCUE MASTER NORB.
I PROBABLY WON'T MAKE IT OUT
IN ONE PIECE.
I'VE DECIDED TO DO THIS
FOR MY OWN PERSONAL REASONS
AND NOTHING ELSE.
I CAN'T FORCE ANY OF YOU
TO FOLLOW ME.
THOSE THAT WANT TO GET OFF
THIS SHIP SHOULD GET OFF
OR STAY IF YOU WISH.
NO MATTER WHICH CHOICE YOU MAKE,
I WILL HONOR IT
AS YOUR DECISION.
THAT'S THE LAST ORDER I GIVE YOU
AS THE LEADER OF GEKKOSTATE.
THAT'S ALL.  DISBAND.
- Ken-goh: IT'S BEEN
THREE YEARS, HASN'T IT?
- SINCE WHAT?
- SINCE YOU TOOK CONTROL
OF THE GEKKO
AND ESCAPED OUT OF THE MILITARY.
COME TO THINK OF IT, IT WAS JUST
THE THREE OF US BACK THEN.
RIGHT, TALHO?
- YEAH.
I KNOW IT'S TRUE THAT
WE DON'T HAVE ANY TIME LEFT,
BUT WE CAN JUST START OVER
FROM SQUARE ONE.
- THANKS, TALHO.
- Woz: I THINK THAT'S
THE FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER HEARD
YOU SAY THAT WORD.
JEEZ, YOU AND I HAVE BEEN
TOGETHER
SINCE WE WERE THREE YEARS OLD.
I HOPE YOU SAY THAT TO ME
ONCE BEFORE I DIE.
- I WILL.
- LEADER, YOU'VE GOT
A MESSAGE FROM STONER.
HE'S DEVELOPING FILM RIGHT NOW,
SO HE DOESN'T WANT YOU
TO MAKE ANY SUDDEN MOVES.
- OKAY, GIDGET.
- ENGINE ROOM HERE.
ENGINES ARE GOOD.  ALL SYSTEMS
SHOW NO MALFUNCTIONS.
WE CAN GO ANY TIME.
- THIS IS CATAPULT CONTROL.
RIGHT NOW WE HAVE THE 606
ON THE TURNTABLE.
THE 606 IS FORMALLY REQUESTING
CLEARANCE FROM THE BRIDGE
TO RELEASE THE CATAPULT
FOR A SCOUTING MISSION.
- THIS IS THE 606.
LEADER, YOU KNOW YOU'RE
GONNA NEED AN LFO
IN THE AIR FOR WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO DO RIGHT NOW.
RIGHT, MATTHIEU?
- THAT'S RIGHT, LEADER.
- I'M NOT SEEING ANY ENEMY
BOGIES ON THE RADAR.
THE CENTRAL COMPUTER IS BACK UP
AND RUNNING,
JUST LIKE OUR LEADER.
- YOU GUYS, GEKKOSTATE IS--
- Renton: WE'RE NOT GONNA
LET YOU DISBAND US.
WE ALL TALKED IT OUT.
LET'S FACE IT, HOLLAND.
ALL OF US CAN SEE THAT WHAT
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO RIGHT NOW
IS NOTHING DIFFERENT FROM WHAT
WE'VE BEEN TRYING ALL ALONG.
AND THAT IS WHAT THE GEKKOSTATE
IS ALL ABOUT.
- RENTON.
- NOW, LEADER,
HURRY UP WITH YOUR ORDERS.
EVERYONE HERE IS WAITING
FOR YOU TO TELL THEM WHAT TO DO.
- ALL HANDS, THE GEKKO'S MISSION
NOW IS TO INVADE THE CAPITOL.
OPERATIONAL DETAILS
WILL FOLLOW,
BUT FOR NOW,
LET'S CHANGE COURSE.
HEAD FOR THE POINT WHERE WE CAN
PERFORM TRAJECTORY FLIGHT.
GOT THAT?
- All: ROGER!
- ( grunts ) HEY, COME ON,
WASN'T ANYBODY LISTENING
TO MY REQUEST?
I GUESS THIS TIME
I'LL LET IT GO.
CONSIDERING I'VE JUST FINISHED
CREATING THE BEST PIECE
OF MY LIFE.
THE TITLE FOR THIS ONE IS,
HMM, LET'S SEE.
HOW ABOUT...
SOMETHING LIKE "PACIFIC STATE"?
- Renton and Eureka:
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ WHY, SO WHY... ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: SEEKING THE KEY
FOR THE DOOR TO THE FUTURE,
THE ADULTS HAVE GONE
ON THE MOVE.
THE STORY CONTINUING ON FROM THE
PAST IS HANDED DOWN TO THE BOY.
NEXT EPISODE-- "INNER FLIGHT."