- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( grunting )
- Moondoggie:
THERE, GOT IT.
- WOW.
- HELP HIM.
- ALL RIGHT.
- YOU KNOW GUYS,
THIS THING IS PRETTY HEAVY.
- QUIT YOUR COMPLAINING.
- Stoner:
GOOD, LET'S GO.
- Renton: RIGHT NOW, I'M KIND
OF GOING ABOUT EVERYDAY LIFE
AS A MEMBER OF THE GEKKO CREW,
JUST LIKE I DID BEFORE.
THE THING THAT TALHO MENTIONED,
ABOUT EUREKA ACTUALLY BEING
SOMETHING CALLED A CORALIAN--
HONESTLY, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND MUCH OF IT.
TO ME, EUREKA'S NOTHING
MORE THAN JUST A GIRL.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE WHAT HOLLAND
TOLD ME IN THE PAST,
I THOUGHT ABOUT TAKING
EUREKA WITH ME,
AND RUNNING
TO SOMEWHERE FAR AWAY.
I THOUGHT THAT SEARCHING
TOGETHER FOR A PLACE
WHERE WE COULD LIVE IN PEACE
WAS A GOOD IDEA.
BUT--
BUT I DON'T THINK
THAT WAS QUITE IT AT ALL.
I WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING
THAT I DON'T ALREADY KNOW ABOUT.
AND ONCE I KNOW EVERYTHING
I DON'T ALREADY KNOW ABOUT,
EVEN THEN, I'M GOING
TO GO THROUGH WITH IT.
I'M GOING TO PROTECT
YOU, EUREKA.
THAT'S THE PROMISE
I MADE WITH CHARLES AND RAY,
RIGHT BEFORE I LEFT THEM.
I GUESS I HAVE TO TELL
HOLLAND ABOUT THIS.
- HOLLAND'S SLEEPING.
- HM?
- HOLLAND'S ASLEEP.
- TALHO, YOU DON'T--
YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
DO YOU, TALHO?
ABOUT MY BLOOD FLOWING
THROUGH HOLLAND'S BODY.
- HOLLAND NEVER FORGETS
ABOUT PEOPLE
HE USED TO CARE ABOUT.
ABOUT DIANE,
WHO'S NO LONGER HERE,
ABOUT YOUR SISTER.
- WAIT, WHY WOULD HOLLAND
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT MY SISTER?
- BECAUSE HE'S JUST
THAT KIND OF GUY.
HE CAN'T FORGET
ABOUT THE WOMAN WHO DUMPED HIM.
HE'S UNFASHIONABLE, STUPID,
CLUMSY, AND NOTHING BUT A FOOL
WHO KNOWS ONLY
HOW TO ACT PHYSICALLY.
HE REALLY IS A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING.
- ( crying )
I'M SORRY, RENTON--
THAT HOLLAND IS
SOMEONE LIKE THIS.
- TALHO, IT'S TRUE OF COURSE,
I REALLY DID LIKE MY SISTER.
BUT I'M--
I'M NOT HER.
I AM WHO I AM.
BESIDES, I THINK YOU'RE
THE ONLY ONE THAT CAN
SUPPORT HOLLAND RIGHT NOW
AND GIVE HIM
EXACTLY WHAT HE NEEDS.
- IDIOT.
- Matthieu: WE'RE HEADING
TOWARDS AN ARMY LABORATORY?
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS, ARE YOU?
- Hap:
WE CAN'T HELP IT.
THE ONLY PLACE THAT WE CAN
GET THE NIRVASH REPAIRED
IS THE TRESOR LABORATORY
WHERE IT WAS MADE.
- AND YET YOU PULL OUT
ALL THIS SCARY STUFF
LIKE WE'RE GOING
TO GO OUT AND ROB SOMEONE.
- BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY,
I ALWAYS SAY.
A FAKE ID CODE
HAS BEEN SENT OUT.
- WE'LL GO IN FAST.
MAKE SURE TO GRAB ONE PERSON
TO BE A HOSTAGE.
- Woz: HEY, I DON'T THINK
THERE WILL BE A NEED FOR THAT.
- YOU SEE, IT'S TRUE
THAT THEY'RE AN ARMY FACILITY,
BUT THE PEOPLE WHO WORK THERE
ARE RESEARCHERS
BEFORE THEY'RE
ARMY EMPLOYEES, RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
IF THEY'RE RESEARCH GUYS,
ALL WE'VE GOT TO DO
IS SHOW THEM THE NIRVASH.
ESPECIALLY IF THAT'S THE PLACE
WHERE HE WAS MADE.
- Stoner:
I SEE, WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
THE SAME KIND OF GUYS HERE.
- THAT'S WHY I DON'T THINK
ANY OF YOU WILL BE NEEDING GUNS.
- Matthieu: IT'S ALl RIGHT, I
WON'T BE HURTING ANYONE WITH IT.
- Hap:
WE'RE JUST BEING CAREFUL.
- Holland:
I'LL DO THE DIRECT NEGOTIATIONS.
- Talho: HOLLAND!
WAIT A MINUTE, WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- I'M FINE.
- BUT HOLLAND, ISN'T TRESOR
WHERE YOUR LEAST FAVORITE--
- Holland:
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'VE GOT TO TRUST ME.
- Renton:
I WONDER IF HE'S ALRIGHT.
- Hap: YEAH, I REMEMBER
THAT MORITA, THE LAB CHIEF,
AND HOLLAND DIDN'T
GET ALONG VERY WELL.
WAIT!
THE TECHNICAL NERDS
ADMIT DEFEAT.
- THIS IS--
IS THE ARCHETYPE
REALLY CHANGING SHAPE?
- Job?????:
YES, NOTHING FITS
THE PREVIOUS
STANDARDIZATIONS NOW.
- THIS SIMPLY CAN'T BE!
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- PERHAPS, BUT IT'S SITTING
IN FRONT OF US.
- WHO ARE THE PILOTS FOR THIS?
- Holland:
THEY'RE BEHIND YOU.
I WANT YOU TO MAKE NEW PARTS
FOR THE MOTION
AND SIGNAL RELAYS.
AND HOW ABOUT A NICE NEW COWL
WHILE YOU'RE AT IT?
- YOU'VE GOT SOME NERVE
ASKING THAT, AFTER STEALING
MILITARY EQUIPMENT
AND GOING AWOL.
- Renton:
PLEASE, HELP HIM!
PLEASE, YOU HAVE
TO SAVE NIRVASH.
- Eureka: ONLY THE
PEOPLE HERE CAN SAVE HIM.
PLEASE DON'T TURN US AWAY.
- BUT IF THE ARMY
FINDS OUT ABOUT THIS--
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT A THING.
I'LL JUST THE FORGE
THE REPORT DOCUMENTS.
- ( sighs )
- Morita: RIGHT NOW, THIS LAB
IS CONFUSED ENOUGH AS IT IS
WITH THE PREPOSTEROUS ORDERS
COMING FROM THE ARMY'S
NEW SQUADRON.
EVERY LAB RESEARCHER
IS STRETCHED TO THEIR LIMITS.
- I GUESS I'LL HAVE
TO ASK SOMEONE ELSE.
- HOWEVER, THAT'S ALL
THE MORE REASON OUR RESEARCHERS
COULD USE A BREAK.
A BREAK CALLED A typeZERO.
- THANK YOU, SIR.
- SORRY.
- TECHNICIANS LIKE US
ARE ALL LIKE THIS, YOU KNOW?
ATTENTION, PLEASE.
WE'RE GOING TO CHANGE SHIFTS
AGAIN TODAY.
I REPEAT, WE'RE GOING TO CHANGE
SHIFTS AGAIN TODAY.
I'LL RELAY THE DETAILS
TO ALL DEPARTMENTS
IN 35 MINUTES.
- EXCUSE ME, CHIEF?
I HAVE A FAVOR TO ASK.
- Morita: ALL SHIFTS WILL BE
EXTENDED BY EIGHT HOURS
FOR DESIGN OF CIRCULAR SPECIAL
AS WELL AS PROTOTYPES FOR RAPID.
DETAILS WILL BE SENT TO ALL
DEPARTMENTS IN 45 MINUTES.
MOVE THE CIRCULAR SPECIAL
FROM THE HANGAR
TO THE P-WING, AND START
MEASUREMENTS IMMEDIATELY.
- Eureka:
POOR THING, HE'S ALL NAKED NOW.
- I WOULDN'T WORRY
ABOUT HIM, EUREKA.
THE PEOPLE HERE ARE
ALL JUST LIKE MY GRANDPA.
- HUH?
- THEY'RE ALL SLIGHTLY STRANGE,
BUT I CAN BELIEVE IN THEM.
- Sonia: OH, SO THIS IS
WHERE YOU'VE BEEN HIDING.
- Eureka: SONIA!
- IT'S BEEN
QUITE A WHILE, EUREKA.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN WELL.
- YOU KNOW HER?
- YEAH.
- YOU SEE, THIS WAS
THE FIRST PLACE
THEY BROUGHT ME TO,
BACK WHEN THEY FOUND ME.
I'VE KNOWN SONIA
SINCE THAT DAY.
- FOUND?
THAT'S RIGHT, EUREKA
WAS FOUND AS A CORALIAN.
EUREKA IS--
- Sonia: SO THIS MUST BE
THE MUCH-RUMORED RENTON.
NICE TO MEET YOU,
I'M SONIA WAKABAYASHI,
HEAD OF THE TECHNICAL
RESEARCH TEAM.
I'M SURE WE'LL GET ALONG.
- NICE TO MEET YOU,
I'M RENTON THURSTON.
- YOU SHOULD GET SOME REST,
YOU MUST BE TIRED.
- YEAH I AM,
THANKS TO A VERY SELFISH LEADER.
- BUT THINGS ARE DIFFERENT
THIS TIME AROUND.
HOLLAND MADE UP HIS MIND
IN HIS OWN WAY AND IS
TRYING TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THE SITUATION.
THAT'S WHY YOU WERE CONVINCED
ABOUT EUREKA AS WELL.
- I'M NOT SURE
IF I CAN BE CONVINCED
OF EACH AND EVERY THING.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT HOLLAND
RUNNING AWAY
FROM THE TRUTH ANYMORE.
BUT IT'S NOT BECAUSE I WANT HIM
TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR IT OR ANYTHING.
I JUST WANTED HOLLAND
TO STAY THE HOLLAND
THAT I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN.
AND THAT'S ALL.
- ( sighs )
- IF THAT'S WHAT YOU'VE
REALLY BEEN THINKING ABOUT,
THEN TALHO--
- WHAT?
- YOU SHOULD PROBABLY STOP
DRESSING LIKE THAT ALREADY.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE'S TOO DENSE, AFTER ALL.
- Morita:
IN 120 SECONDS,
WE WILL CONDUCT
AN EXPERIMENT FOR ORANGE.
- Gidget:
THIS IS WHERE THEY DESIGN
THE ARMY KLFs AND STUFF, RIGHT?
THAT'S SO STRANGE, BECAUSE
IT SEEMS NICE AND PEACEFUL HERE.
- I AGREE.
- THE GUYS HERE ARE AWARE
OF HOW THE WEAPONS
THEY MAKE ARE USED.
I MEAN, THEY HAVE TO KNOW BEFORE
THEY CAN EVEN DESIGN THEM.
IT'S WHAT THEY DO HERE.
- ORIGINALLY THIS WAS A LAB
OPEN TO EXPERIMENT
WITH THE UNEARTHED ARCHETYPES.
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY'VE
BEEN MAKING WEAPONS
TO KILL PEOPLE WITH
FROM THE GET-GO.
- ( rumbling )
- WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
- Morita: THE ENTRY SURFACE
AREA IS STILL TOO LARGE.
- HELL OF A WEAPON,
THAT'S SO UNLIKE YOU.
- YOU CAN STAY ASLEEP.
- THAT WEAPON HAS SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THE NEW SQUADRON
THE ARMY'S FORMING, DOESN'T IT?
- THAT'S CONFIDENTIAL.
- IT'S DEWEY, ISN'T IT?
- I DON'T KNOW.  IN ANY CASE,
WE HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA
HOW THE GROUP THAT ORDERED IT
WAS CREATED.
OR WHO'S ACTUALLY IN IT.
IT'S A MYSTERY SQUADRON.
IT'S THE AGEHA SQUAD.
- AGEHA?
- THE OBJECTIVE IS TO DELIVER
AS STRONG AN IMPACT AS POSSIBLE
TO THE DEEPEST AREA OF SCUBS.
WE PUT IT ON THE AFX,
A REMOTE-CONTROLLED BOMBER
THAT USES TRAJECTORY FLIGHT.
THE  MISSILE ITSELF
IS 24x DENSER THAN USUAL.
FURTHERMORE, THE WARHEAD WE'LL
BE USING ON THE FINAL VERSION
IS AN ANTI-RELATIVITY BOMB.
- POLLUTED AIR
ACROSS A DYING WASTELAND.
I GUESS THEY'VE GOT SOME
PREPOSTEROUS
FANTASIES OF THE FUTURE.
- ATTENTION ORANGE TEAM,
BEGIN ENTRY SURFACE AREA
RECALCULATION IMMEDIATELY.
- ONCE THE GEKKO
IS FULLY REPAIRED,
WE'LL GET OUT OF HERE.
- HEY, IMPROVING THE SPECS
OF THE TYPE ZERO
IS GOING TO BE A PIECE OF CAKE.
YOU JUST WORRY ABOUT HOW
TO REPAIR THAT BODY OF YOURS.
- IN THE END, I GUESS I
WAS RUNNING AWAY AS WELL.
I HAVE TO CHANGE, TOO.
- Sonia:
THIS IS AMAZING.
THE ARCHETYPE HAS
EVOLVED CONSIDERABLY.
THIS DOESN'T INVOLVE
JUST THE OUTER HULL PARTS,
IT MIGHT REQUIRE A COMPLETE
MAKEOVER OF THE LAYOUTS.
- WILL THAT TAKE MUCH TIME?
EVEN IF WE GET A MOLD USING
THE LIGHT MOLDER WE HAVE HERE,
THE TOUCH-UPS ARE
ALL DONE BY HAND.
IT COULD TAKE 10 DAYS.
- Mischa:
I GUESS WE'RE TROUBLING YOU.
- WE NEED EVENTS LIKE THIS
EVERY SO OFTEN.
- HEY...
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
ANYWHERE AROUND HERE TODAY.
- HE'S ON
AN ON-SITE RESEARCH TRIP.
HE'LL BE BACK IN NO TIME.
- OH, BROTHER.
DOES HE HAVE
REALLY AWFUL TIMING, OR WHAT?
- Eureka:
SEE, IT'S RIGHT OVER THERE.
LOOK CLOSELY AT THE COCKPIT
ON THE BACK.
- Renton:
WOW, YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF
HE'S TRYING TO TELL US
TO MAKE TWO SPACES THERE.
- SEE?
- THAT WAS WHAT SEPARATED
THIS FIRST ARCHETYPE
FROM ALL THE OTHERS
THAT CAME LATER.
ALL OF THE ARCHETYPES
THAT WERE UNEARTHED LATER ON
MAY HAVE LOOKED SIMILAR
ON THE OUTSIDE TO THE typeZERO,
BUT THIS WAS THE ONLY ARCHETYPE
THAT HAD BEEN STRUCTURED
FOR TWO SEATS
FROM THE BEGINNING.
WHY WERE THERE TWO SEATS
PREPARED ON THIS ONE?
AND WHY WERE THE ARCHETYPES
ALWAYS MADE IN THE SHAPE
OF GIANT HUMANOID CREATURES?
DEBATE OVER THE MEANING
OF THIS STRUCTURE
CONTINUES TO RAGE ON.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN NICE
IF EUREKA COULD HAVE
ANSWERED THESE QUESTIONS.
- I'M SORRY, BUT I JUST DON'T
HAVE ANY MEMORIES
FROM WHEN I WAS CREATED.
- Sonia: I KNOW!
OUR CHIEF MADE A MOVIE
ALL ABOUT THIS SUBJECT.
YOU WANT TO WATCH?
- MOVIE?
- ( music playing )
- Narrator:
THE UNEARTHED ARTIFACT
WAS IN THE SHAPE OF A HUMAN.
AND IT WAS UNKNOWN
EXACTLY HOW LONG AGO
IT HAD BEEN CREATED.
FORTUNATELY, AS ITS CONDITION
WAS EXCEPTIONALLY GOOD,
AND THANKS TO THE SUPERIOR
TECHNICAL SKILLS
OF THE TRESOR LABORATORY
RESEARCHERS,
THE ARTIFACT WAS ABLE TO BE
ALMOST COMPLETELY RECONSTRUCTED.
IT WAS DISCOVERED THAT WHEN
AN ELECTRIC CURRENT WAS APPLIED
TO THIS ARTIFACT,
IT COULD BE DIRECTED
TO MOVE EACH OF ITS PARTS.
THE CIRCUITS THAT WERE
BELIEVED TO BE
THE NEUROLOGICAL
TRANSMISSION SYSTEM
WERE CONCENTRATED ON ITS BACK.
INDICATING THAT
THE ARTIFACT'S COMMAND POINT
HAD BEEN PLACED
THERE BY ITS DESIGNERS.
UPON THE ADDITION OF
THE MOTION TRANSMISSION SYSTEM,
THE ARTIFACT WAS CONFIRMED
TO BE IN THE SHAPE OF A HUMAN
AND WAS ABLE TO MIMIC
THE MOVEMENTS OF HUMANS AS WELL.
HOWEVER, THE AUTONOMOUS SYSTEMS
COULD NOT BE LOCATED
AND ITS OPERATION
WAS TOUGH, AT BEST.
BUT WHEN EUREKA,
THE GIRL WHO WAS RESCUED
FROM THE EXCAVATION SITE
AT THE SAME TIME
AS THE ARTIFACT,
OPERATED IT-- AS SHOWN HERE,
IT BECAME SOMETHING
AKIN TO A CAR.
IT WAS THE MISSION
OF THE TRESOR LABORATORIES,
KNOWN FOR ITS HIGH
TECHNICAL SKILLS,
TO DRAW OUT,
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE,
THE HIDDEN POWERS
OF THIS ARTIFACT.
WE DISCOVERED THAT USING TRAPARS
AS ITS ELECTRICAL POWER SOURCE
WAS OPTIMAL.
AND TO MAXIMIZE ITS POTENTIAL,
WE ADDED A FUNCTION SIMILAR
TO THE POPULAR SPORT OF LIFTING.
THE CREATION
OF THIS GIANT REF BOARD
PROVED TO BE AN ENORMOUS
TECHNOLOGICAL CHALLENGE
FOR THE TRESOR
RESEARCH DESIGNERS.
- GRANDPOP...
- I REMEMBER A FEW THINGS
ABOUT THAT TIME.
- Narrator: THE ARTIFACT WAS
CHRISTENED, THE NIRVASH.
AND BECAME THE PERMANENT
TEMPLATE FOR ALL THE LFOs
THAT WERE LATER FOUND OR CREATED
BY THE EXPERTS
HERE AT TRESOR LABORATORIES.
- ( clapping )
- THAT WAS PRETTY STRANGE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- MM-HMM... OH, IT'S LINCK!
- YOU GUYS WERE HERE, TOO?
- HEY, RENTON, WHY ARE YOU
FIDGETING LIKE THAT?
- Maeter:
YOU WERE TRYING TO TOUCH MAMA
WHILE IT WAS ALL DARK,
WEREN'T YOU?
- WHAT?! THAT'S NOT TRUE!
WHY DID YOU SAY THAT?
- HEY, WHERE'S MAURICE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- ME NEITHER.
- YOU THREE DIDN'T
COME HERE TOGETHER?
- UH-UH.
- MAURICE HAS BEEN
ACTING REAL FUNNY.
HE'S TRYING NOT TO LOOK
AT YOU ALL THAT MUCH, MAMA.
- RENTON, MOVE!
- WHAT?
- Maeter and Linck: MAMA!
- EUREKA!
- Eureka: MAURICE!
MAURICE, WHERE ARE YOU?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- YOU'VE CHANGED.
TALHO, YOU'VE CHANGED!
- NO, I DIDN'T.
I JUST WENT BACK.
YOU KNOW, FOR A WHILE THERE,
I THOUGHT ABOUT THROWING
IT ALL AWAY.
I MEAN, IT WAS
REALLY TOUGH ON ME.
BUT THE WAY THINGS TURNED OUT
GOT ME THINKING.
IN THE END, NOTHING HAD CHANGED.
HOW I FELT BEFORE,
MY EMOTIONS FROM MY PAST,
EVERYTHING WENT BACK
TO HOW IT USED TO BE.
IT'S SO STRANGE.
- I THINK IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I MEAN, FROM MY POINT OF VIEW,
YOU'VE CHANGED, TALHO.
I WENT THROUGH SOME CHANGES
MYSELF WITHOUT REALIZING IT.
AND NOW YOU'VE
CHANGED AS WELL, TALHO.
BUT YOU SHOULDN'T THINK ABOUT IT
AS A SCARY THING.
- OH, BROTHER.
CAN'T SEEM TO WIN,
NO MATTER WHAT.
I'M REALLY JEALOUS.
- ( phone clicks )
- OH, MAN.  HE'S STILL STUBBORN
AND OLD-FASHIONED.
- Renton:
EXCUSE ME, CHIEF?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I SAW THE MOVIE.
I WAS REAL SURPRISED TO SEE
THAT MY GRANDPA WAS IN IT.
SEE, MY GRANDPA IS...
- YOUR GRANDPA AXEL IS WHAT YOU
WOULD CALL A MENTOR TO ME.
- WHAT?!
- Morita: YOUR GRANDPA IS
A VERY FORCEFUL MAN.
HE HAD A HUGE ARGUMENT
WITH THE BUREAUCRATS
OF THIS DEPARTMENT AND QUIT.
AFTER THAT, I VISITED HIM
IN HIS BELLFOREST GARAGE
ONLY ONCE.
I COULDN'T GET THE REF BOARD
FOR THE typeZERO
TO WORK THE RIGHT AWAY.
I BOWED MY HEAD DOWN
TO OLD THURSTON,
AND HAD HIM FINISH IT UP.
YOUR HOMELAND,
IT'S A VERY NICE PLACE.
- IT'S BORING, IT DOESN'T HAVE
MUCH OF ANYTHING.
- ( sirens )
- Morita: ATTENTION,
WE ARE ENTERING
THE CIRCULAR SPECIAL SHIFT.
- HEY, HEY, HEY, YOUR MIC'S
FEEDING BACK, YOU KNOW?
- WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO NOW?
- ( loud dance music playing )
- ( cheering )
- WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON HERE?
- WHAT IS UP WITH
THIS OLD-FASHIONED MUSIC?
IT PUTS ME IN A BAD MOOD.
- Talho:
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED A BIT.
YOU'VE ALWAYS HATED
OLD MUSIC LIKE THIS.
AT LEAST SINCE I'VE KNOWN YOU.
- SHUT UP, WILL YOU?
- WE SAY ALL THIS STUFF NOW,
BUT SOMEDAY, WE'RE GOING
TO BE OLD MEN AND WOMEN, TOO.
- I SAID, SHUT UP.
- EUREKA!
DID THEY ALREADY START
MAKING IT?
- YEAH, YOU SEE?
NIRVASH IS HAPPY, TOO.
I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU, NIRVASH!
IT'S ALRIGHT FOR YOU
TO CHANGE, TOO.
JUST LIKE ME!
- Renton and Eureka:
TO BE CONTINUED!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Talho:
ARROWS OF LIGHT PIERCE THE LAND.
TO COERCE THE WORLD TO AWAKEN.
THEIR AWAKENING TRAPS PEOPLE
IN THEIR WORST NIGHTMARES.
- NEXT EPISODE,
"ANIMAL ATTACK."