- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Hap:
THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
THE GREAT WALL IS ONLY
A SHORT DISTANCE FROM HERE.
AND YET-- AND YET...
WHY THE HELL
DO WE HAVE TO STOP HERE
AND PLAY
A GAME OF SOCCER?!
- Hilda: HOLD ON.
ARE YOU SERIOUS ABOUT THIS?
- Stoner: YEAH.
SERIOUS AS I CAN BE.
DEAD SERIOUS.
- Hilda: ARE YOU NUTS?
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN THAT WE'RE
ON THE WANTED LIST RIGHT NOW?
YOU GUYS DO KNOW THAT
WE CAN'T STAY HERE
FOR VERY LONG, DON'T YOU?
- I WONDER IF THERE'S
A CORRELATION BETWEEN SOCCER
AND THE MYSTERIES OF
THE GREAT WALL.
- NOBODY WOULD BE AGAINST
THE IDEA IF WE COULD FIND ONE.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
- THE BIG PROBLEM IS
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR RENTON
AND EUREKA TO PLAY SOCCER
ALL BY THEMSELVES,
EVEN IF IT'S ONLY A GAME
OF FUTSAL.
- I DON'T WANNA PLAY!
I'VE NEVER EVEN DONE IT BEFORE.
- I'LL PASS TOO.
- Holland: I THOUGHT SO.
IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
- MM?
- BECAUSE MASTER NORB SAID
THAT DOING THIS IS PART
OF THE PATH TO THE GREAT WALL.
- HOLLAND, COME ON,
YOU REALLY BELIEVE HIM?
I DON'T WANNA SAY THIS
SO FAR INTO THINGS,
BUT MAYBE THAT OLD MAN ISN'T
THINKING ABOUT ANYTHING AT ALL.
- NOW THAT'S EVEN MORE
RIDICULOUS.
THIS IS MASTER NORB--YOU SAW
THE COMPAC ON HIS CHEST, RIGHT?
- YEAH, BUT STILL...
- COME TO THINK OF IT,
YOU WERE NEVER ANY GOOD
AT SPORTS WITH BALLS.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
LOOK, I'M JUST SAYING--
- Renton: COME ON, GUYS!
LET'S DO IT!
FOR A WHILE NOW
I HAVEN'T SEEMED TO BE ABLE
TO SIT STILL AND STAY CALM
NO MATTER HOW MUCH I TRIED.
I MEAN, I'VE REALLY WANTED
TO MOVE AROUND
AND GET IT
OUT OF MY SYSTEM.
- I SEE...
SO YOU WANNA KNOW WHY?
YOU'VE GROWN UP.
- REALLY, HOLLAND?
- LISTEN, RENTON.
IN A VERY SHORT TIME,
YOU AND EUREKA
ARE GONNA HAVE TO WORK TOGETHER
TO GET PAST THE GREAT WALL.
THIS IS ONE OF THE CHALLENGES
LEADING TO IT.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
I WANT YOU TO PASS IT.
THINK YOU CAN DO IT?
- YEAH!
- THAT'S A GOOD ANSWER.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO
A QUICK WARM-UP.
- RIGHT.
- ( both panting )
- THERE ARE TWO IDIOTS HERE.
HEY, NORB!
I WANNA TALK TO YOU.
WHERE ARE YOU?!
WHAT THE HELL
DID YOU SAY TO THEM?!
- ( snoring )
- ( ball bouncing )
- ( groaning )
- AMAZING!
- HUH?
- THAT WAS A REALLY NEAT TRICK.
- OH, WELL, IT'S NOT
REALLY SOMETHING
THAT YOU WOULD CALL A TRICK.
- GIVE IT TO ME!
LET ME TRY!
- WHY?  YOU'LL NEVER BE
ABLE TO DO IT.
- I SEE.
SO YOU'VE DONE THIS BEFORE?
- YEAH, A LITTLE,
BEFORE I STARTED TO LIFT.
BUT THEY DIDN'T HAVE
A TEAM AT BELLFOREST.
AND NOBODY AROUND THERE
LIKED TO PLAY.
SO I WAS ALWAYS HAVING
TO PLAY ALL BY MYSELF.
- OH, I SEE.
- IT SEEMS LIKE
THINGS ARE BEGINNING
TO GET KIND OF STRANGE.
- YEAH.
- HEY, I FORGOT TO ASK.
HAVE YOU EVER PLAYED SOCCER
BEFORE?
- NO, I HAVEN'T.
BUT IF I'M WITH YOU, RENTON,
I'M POSITIVE THAT
I'LL BE ABLE TO LEARN HOW.
WILL YOU PLEASE TEACH ME?
- YEAH, OF COURSE!
HEY, GIVE ME THE BALL!
GIVE ME THE BALL!
- ( kids groan )
- WHAT IS IT, RENTON?
- I'LL TEACH ALL OF YOU GUYS
TOGETHER.
COME ON OVER HERE.
COME ON.
- REALLY?
ALL RIGHT!
- ( clears throat )
NOW, THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
TO KEEP IN MIND WHEN IT COMES
TO PLAYING
THE GAME OF SOCCER IS THIS--
- Man: HEY!
- HUH?
- ( sighs )
HOLLAND'S CALLING FOR YOU.
- HOLLAND IS?
( sighs )
- Hap: WHAT IS THIS?
- YOU CAN SEE FOR YOURSELF.
IT'S A SPECIAL SCHEDULE.
- HEY, COME ON NOW.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
I'M ONE OF THE PLAYERS,
YOU KNOW?
- LIKE I SAID TO YOU EARLIER,
I'VE NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE.
- HEY, HOW COME OUR LEADER'S
NAME ISN'T ON THE LIST?
- WHAT'S A SUPPORTER
SUPPOSED TO DO?
- APPARENTLY, TEND TO
THE PHYSICAL AND MENTAL SUPPORT
OF ALL THE PLAYERS IN THE GAME.
- I KNOW.  WHAT I'M ASKING IS
WHAT I NEED TO DO FOR THAT.
- HEY, HOLLAND,
CAN I ASK ONE THING?
- HMM?
- YOU WROTE HERE THAT
WE'RE GONNA RUN
AND DO MUSCLE
TRAINING AND STUFF,
BUT YOU NEGLECTED TO SAY
FOR HOW LONG.
- ( groans deeply )
- ( snoring )
- ( sighs )
SO ARE YOU GUYS UP FOR IT
OR NOT?!
- WE'RE TRYING TO TELL YOU
WE'RE NOT.
- LOOK, LEADER, I
REALLY DIDN'T WANNA
HAVE TO SAY THIS TO YOU,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
YOU'VE GOT MORE THAN A
PRETTY GOOD REASON TO ASK NORB
WHY IT'S SO DAMN IMPORTANT
FOR ALL OF US TO PLAY SOCCER?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
EVERYTHING WE'RE
DOING IS SO THAT
WE CAN GET OVER THE GREAT WALL.
- NO GOOD.
HE TOTALLY BELIEVES IT.
- NORB!
- HMM?
- YOU GOTTA TELL US.
WE HAVE THE RIGHT TO KNOW
WHY YOU SAY
THAT ALL OF US
HAVE TO PLAY SOCCER.
- I TOLD YOU.
IT'S TO GET OVER--
- HOLLAND,
JUST BE QUIET, ALL RIGHT?!
NOW, I WANT YOU TO
ANSWER US, NORB!
GIVE US A REASON
THAT'LL SATISFY ALL OF US.
- ( snoring softly )
( chuckles )
- All: HUH?
- I DON'T GET IT.
WHY ARE YOU GRINNING?
- IT MEANS,
"BEST NOT TO ASK."
- ( techno music playing )
- ( panting )
( grunts, shouts )
- ( shouts )
- NO!
- ( whistle tweets )
- ( cheering )
- ALL RIGHT!
- OH.
- WOW, DON'T YOU THINK
RENTON IS AMAZING?
- HE'S REALLY GOOD.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
- NO GOOD.
I CAN'T KEEP UP
WITH HIM.
JEEZ, SOMEONE HURRY UP
AND TAKE OVER ALREADY!
- YOU KNOW EVERYONE IS SAYING
THAT YOU'RE GOOD, RENTON.
- IT'S REALLY NOT TRUE.
I MEAN, I WAS PLAYING AGAINST
MISS HILDA AND MR. JOBS.
THEY'RE BOTH COMPLETELY NEW
TO THIS.
LET'S FACE IT--
ANYBODY COULD GET PAST THEM.
- ( giggles )
- WHAT?
- NO, IT'S NOTHING, REALLY.
- COME ON!
DON'T LEAVE ME WONDERING.
- I TOLD YOU, RENTON,
IT'S NOTHING.
- HEY!
IT'S ABOUT TIME TO BEGIN.
- ( whistle tweets )
- ( growls )
- HEH.
- ( laughing )
- GIDGET, LOOK OUT!
- AAH!
- REALLY BIG PANTHER SHOT!
- ( whistle tweets )
- ( gasping )
- HEY, RENTON,
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
( laughs )
( humming a tune )
( giggling )
- OH, DON'T MIND HIM, RENTON.
- ( growls )
- RENTON?
- ( whistle tweets )
- THIS IS NOT GOOD.
- NOT GOOD, HUH?
- YEAH, NOT GOOD.
- WELL, HOW IS IT NOT GOOD?
- I'VE DONE A THOROUGH
ANALYSIS OF WHAT NORB IS TRYING
TO ACCOMPLISH
WITH THIS PLAN OF HIS.
I THINK WHAT HE'S TRYING
TO DO IS HELP RID RENTON
OF ANY EVIL THOUGHTS
THAT MIGHT ENTER HIS MIND
AND HINDER HIM WHEN HE TRIES TO
ENTER THE GREAT WALL.
- EVIL THOUGHTS?
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
- YOU KNOW,
THE KIND OF THOUGHTS YOU GET
BECAUSE YOU'RE A TEENAGER.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
THOSE THOUGHTS.
- OH, NOW I GET IT.
WE HAVE TO DO THIS
SO THAT RENTON CAN GET RID OF
THAT THING YOU FEEL
WHEN YOU'RE YOUNG
BY GETTING IT OUT
THROUGH SPORTS.
- THAT'S MOST LIKELY IT.
- AND I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS IS NOT LOOKING GOOD
AT ALL.
RIGHT NOW, RENTON IS
MENTALLY CORNERED,
ESSENTIALLY BEING FORCED
TO FACE OFF AGAINST DOGGIE
WHO'S OBVIOUSLY
MUCH BETTER THAN HE IS.
- THE PRESENCE
OF NEGATIVE EMOTIONS
THAT ARE UNCONSCIOUSLY
TURNED AGAINST ONESELF
INCREASES PHYSICAL
PERSISTENCE THAT CAN
STUNT HEALTHY
EMOTIONAL GROWTH.
- YEAH, AND IF
THAT'S NOT ENOUGH,
HE'S STARTING TO GET A LOT OF
EMOTIONAL PRESSURE FROM EUREKA.
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE SOMETHING
WILL HAPPEN AS A RESULT.
- YOU THINK SOMETHING
WILL HAPPEN?
- YOU BET.
THE CHANCES ARE VERY LIKELY
THAT SOMETHING WILL.
- ( groans deeply )
- ( all panting )
- I'M GONNA TAKE
ALL OF MY PAST ANGER
OUT ON HIM RIGHT NOW.
AAH!
- ( guys grunt, groan )
- OH.
- ( cheering )
- RENTON!
- OH...
- RENTON, PASS IT TO ME!
- RENTON, PASS IT!
- YOU'RE HOLDING THE BALL
TOO LONG!
PASS IT RIGHT NOW!
- HAVE YOU CONSIDERED
THE POSSIBILITY?
- WHAT?
- THAT RENTON DOESN'T KNOW
HOW TO PASS THE BALL?
- AAH!
GOLDEN FALCON SHOT!
- ( whistle tweet )
- WHOO-HOO!
( laughing )
- JEEZ, WHAT THE HELL DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING, RENTON?!
- ( breathing heavily )
- RENTON.
STOP JOKING AROUND.
- HERE'S TO RIGHT NOW.
- CHEERS, GUYS.
- AHH!
- MAN, IT'S GOOD.
- YOU KNOW, IT'S ALWAYS NICE
TO HAVE AN ICE-COLD BEER
AFTER YOU SPENT
MOST OF THE DAY
WORKING UP A SWEAT
ON THE SOCCER FIELD.
- OR YOU COULD END UP
WITH THE GOUT.
- WELL, THAT WOULDN'T BE
GOOD AT ALL.
- MM.  ANYWAY,
WHAT ABOUT RENTON?
- WE WERE EXPECTING THIS
TO HAPPEN, BUT STILL,
IT'S NOT GOOD NEWS.
- SO I GUESS IT'S BAD
ALL AROUND.
- LET'S FACE IT--
NOTHING GOOD COULD POSSIBLY COME
FROM MAKING HIM LOSE
HIS SELF-CONFIDENCE NOW.
- YOU KNOW, I'M STARTING TO
REALIZE WHAT NORB'S THINKING IS
REGARDING ALL THIS.
- OH, YEAH?  DO TELL.
- IT'S ENTIRELY POSSIBLE
HE JUST WANTS TO SEE
HOW EUREKA AND RENTON
WORK AS A PAIR.
- OH, THAT'S VERY DIFFERENT.
- BUT THE OLD MAN WAS ASLEEP
THE WHOLE TIME.
- THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
- YEAH, GOOD POINT.
- ARE YOU GUYS
THE ALL GEKKO TEAM?
- ( crying softly )
- I DON'T GET IT.
DID I DO SOMETHING BAD?
- NO, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
DOGGIE.
- ( panting )
WHERE'S HOLLAND?
- A GAME?
- MM-HMM.
- YOU DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING ABOUT THIS!
- YEAH, AND WHERE DID YOU GET
THESE GUYS FROM, ANYWAY?
- SO, HOLLAND,
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- PLAY THE GAME.
- WHAT?  ARE YOU NUTS?
- WE ONLY HAVE
ONE PATH LEFT TO US
FOR GETTING THROUGH
THE GREAT WALL.
RIGHT, NORB?
- ( chuckling softly )
- ( grunts )
- NOW WAIT JUST A MINUTE!
DON'T BE FOOLED BY
THAT STUPID GRIN OF HIS.
- I'M ANNOUNCING
THE STARTING LINEUP.
- All:
HEY HEY HEY HEY!
YEAH!
- WHAT'S UP WITH THEM?
- Holland: LISTEN UP.
SINCE WE DECIDED
WE'RE GOING TO DO THIS
NO MATTER WHO WE'RE UP AGAINST,
WE WILL WIN!
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, CIRCLE UP!
ALL GEKKOS!
FIGHT ON! FIGHT ON! FIGHT ON!
- ( Gekkos sigh, groan )
- KEEP YOUR HEADS IN THE GAME.
DON'T LET THEM PSYCH YOU OUT.
- HEY, HOLLAND, HOW COME YOU'RE
NOT IN THE STARTING LINEUP?
- HE'S JUST THAT KIND OF GUY.
- HAVE FUN, MAMA!
- PLAY GOOD, MOM!
- ( groans softly )
- I'M SORRY ABOUT EARLIER.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO BE SO HARSH.
- ( chuckles weakly )
- DON'T WORRY, RENTON.
I'LL DO MY BEST TO
COVER FOR YOU.
- GAH!
- ( whistle tweets )
- ( all shout )
- AAH.
- ( grunting )
- AAH!
EUREKA, TAKE IT.
- ( screams )
- EUREKA!
- HEY, DID YOU GUYS SEE THAT?
WASN'T THAT TACKLE
AGAINST THE RULES?
- NO, IT JUST LOOKED THAT WAY
BECAUSE EUREKA'S SO SMALL.
THE TACKLE WAS NOT
AGAINST THE RULES.
THAT'S WHY THIS SPORT'S
OFTEN BEEN CALLED
MARTIAL ARTS
IN A GRASS FIELD.
- MARTIAL ARTS, HUH?
- WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING TO EUREKA?!
- ( chuckles smugly )
WHOA!
- ( whistle tweets )
- WHAT?
- HAS HE BECOME
A COMPLETE IDIOT?
- YOU'RE IN, STONER.
- I'M WHAT?
- HEY, YOU SAID
THIS WAS MARTIAL ARTS.
- I REALLY DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
- ( whistle tweets )
- ( all scream )
- ( whistle tweets twice )
- ( both sigh )
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I'M GOING IN.
- ( whistle tweets twice )
- ( all groaning, panting )
- I'M SORRY. I SHOULD REALLY BE
DOING A MUCH BETTER JOB AT THIS.
- THINGS NEVER TURN OUT THIS WAY
WHEN YOU'RE PLAYING
ALL BY YOURSELF.
- YEAH, REALLY.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
LOOK, GUYS, THIS ISN'T JUST
RENTON'S PROBLEM
OR EUREKA'S PROBLEM
ANY LONGER.
THIS CONCERNS THE PRIDE
OF GEKKOSTATE AS A WHOLE.
- MAKES SENSE.
- NOBODY HERE IS
GOING TO BE SATISFIED
UNTIL WE GET
AT LEAST ONE GOAL
- OKAY, I'M CHANGING PLANS.
- I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD
A PLAN IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- SO, WHAT IS IT?
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO, LEADER?
- WE'RE NOT GOING TO DEFEND!
- ( helicopter overhead )
- ALL RIGHT,
BRING IT ON!
- HEY, RENTON.
- ( whistle tweets )
- I BELIEVE IN YOU.
- HUH?
EUREKA!
- WE'RE MOVING UP.
- RIGHT!
- EUREKA, OVER HERE!
- DOGGIE!
- ( all grunting )
- RENTON!
- BROTHER DOGGIE!
- OH, NO, HE'S DOING
THAT THING WITH THE BALL AGAIN!
- RENTON!
PASS!
PASS THE BALL TO ME!
IT'S ALL RIGHT, RENTON.
YOU CAN DO IT IF YOU TRY.
- WHOA...
- RENTON PASSED
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME.
- ( shouting )
- EUREKA, OVER HERE!
- RENTON!
- ( growls )
- RENTON, BEHIND YOU!
- ( shouts )
- ( growls )
- ( grunts )
- THAT'S THE BALL THAT
EUREKA PASSED TO ME!
( shouts )
- ( panting )
- ( shouting )
- ( grunts )
- NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES!
- Eureka:
HOLLAND!
- HUH?
- I'M NOT GONNA GIVE UP THIS
BALL NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS!
( grunts )
- ( groans )
- ( shouts )
- WHAT THE--?!
- ( both shout )
- ( cheering )
- ALL RIGHT!
- YEAH!
- ( both laughing )
- ( siren blaring )
- HUH?
- FREEZE!
- All:
HUH?
- Holland:
WHAT ABOUT REFUELING?
- IT'S ALL DONE.
- WE'RE GONNA USE THE BOOSTERS.
WHAT ABOUT ALL THE GUYS OUTSIDE?
- Gidget: ALL WORKERS
HAVE ALREADY EVACUATED.
- ALL RIGHT, LAUNCH!
SO WHAT DID NORB WANT TO
ACCOMPLISH WITH ALL THIS?
- MAYBE ALL HE WANTED TO DO
WAS TEACH US THE TEAMWORK
THAT WE'LL NEED IN ORDER
TO GET PAST THE GREAT WALL.
- NO, PERHAPS IT WAS SO THAT
WE'D BE PREPARED IN CASE
SOMETHING UNEXPECTED WERE TO
HAPPEN TO US ON OUR JOURNEY.
- ISN'T WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
DIFFERENT THAN BEFORE?
- SO, NOW THAT ALL IS
SAID AND DONE,
WHAT WAS IT?
- HMM?
ALL IS WELL IF YOU LEARN
SOMETHING ABOUT YOURSELF
AND ALL IS STILL WELL EVEN IF
YOU COULDN'T LEARN ANYTHING.
AND BESIDES ALL THAT...
IT WAS FUN, WASN'T IT?
- ( sighs )
- ONE DAY...
- HMM?
- ...WE'LL COME BACK HERE AGAIN.
AND WE'LL GO UP AGAINST
THOSE GUYS WE PLAYED TODAY
ONE MORE TIME,
WITH NOT ONE PERSON
OUT OF THE PICTURE.
THE ENTIRE GEKKOSTATE
AS A WHOLE!
- ( all softly groan )
- ( chuckles )
- I'M SORRY YOU'RE HAVING TO
STICK AROUND HERE
WORKING LIKE THIS.
- NO, I STEPPED ON
HOLLAND'S FACE TOO.
IT'S ONLY RIGHT.
- ( laughs )
- ( both laughing )
- BY THE WAY, WHAT DID YOU
SAY TO ME ON THE FIELD,
WHEN THE SECOND-HALF WHISTLE
WAS BEING BLOWN?
- OH.
"I BELIEVE IN YOU."
- WHAT?
- I REMEMBERED THAT IN
IMPORTANT SITUATIONS,
YOU ALWAYS SEEM TO BE ABLE TO
CREATE MIRACLES
AND SAVE THE DAY.
SO...
- ( giggles )
- FROM THE CORALIAN ATTACK
OF OUR CAPITOL,
WE LOST TWO OF
THE GREAT FOUNDATIONS
OF OUR TROUBLED WORLD.
THEY WERE KILLED BY
THE CORALIANS,
WHOSE EXISTENCE
THEY KEPT HIDDEN.
IN A WAY,
YOU COULD SAY THEY EACH
GOT WHAT THEY DESERVED.
HOWEVER-- HOWEVER,
I HAD NOT WISHED FOR THEM
TO BE MURDERED
IN COLD BLOOD.
THEY, THE SAGES, SHOULD HAVE
APOLOGIZED TO ALL OF US.
THOUGH COME TO THINK OF IT NOW,
THEY MIGHT HAVE BEEN AGONIZED
BY THE GREAT REGRET THAT THEY
MOST CERTAINLY WERE FEELING.
NOW I HAVE BEEN GIVEN
A DIRECT ORDER BY CODA,
THE SOLE REMAINING SAGE
OF OUR WORLD.
TO STRIKE,
TO STRIKE IMMEDIATELY
AND DECISIVELY.
AND SO I ASK AGAIN
FOR THE FULL DEPLOYMENT
OF THE AGEHA SQUAD.
WE SHALL ATTACK DEEP INTO
THE HEART OF THE GREAT WALL,
WHERE THE CORALIAN BASE
IS LOCATED
AND EXTERMINATE THEM
FROM EXISTENCE!
- ( cheering )
- Renton and Eureka:
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator: THE GEKKO ARRIVES
AT THE GATE
THAT LEADS TO THE FUTURE.
IN A LIGHT THAT SHINES
UPON THE SHADOWS,
THE BOY AND GIRL ENCOUNTER
THEIR DESTINED RENDEZVOUS.
NEXT EPISODE...
"THE COSMIC TRIGGER."