- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
♪ SO YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
♪ COME ON ♪
♪ WE WANNA MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE ♪
♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
♪ SO YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
♪ COME ON ♪
- Mischa: EUREKA, HURRY UP.
- Eureka: DO WE REALLY
HAVE TO GO BACK?
I DON'T WANT TO GO
INTO THAT CAVE AGAIN.
- IT'S MUCH SAFER
INSIDE THE GEKKO,
THAN IT COULD POSSIBLY BE
AROUND THIS PLACE.
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
I REALLY AM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
CAUSING YOUR CONDITION,
AND SO I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW I SHOULD TREAT IT.
RIGHT NOW,
ALL I CAN TELL YOU IS...
PLEASE, TRY TO BEAR
WITH IT, EUREKA.
- NO GOOD.
PUKEY-FACE WON'T COME OUT.
- CRYBABY!
- ( knocking on door )
- Mischa: RENTON,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE'VE GOTTA GET BACK
TO THE GEKKO.
RENTON! RENTON!
- THOSE THAT PUNCH,
THOSE THAT GIVE UP.
THOSE THAT LEAVE ME BEHIND.
EVERYONE IS SELFISH.
EVERYONE SAYS WHAT THEY WANT,
AND THEN DESTROY
MY FAITH IN THEM.
SAME GOES FOR EUREKA.
SHE DOESN'T SEEM TO
REALIZE HOW I FEEL
WHEN I PILOT THE NIRVASH
ALL BY MYSELF.
I'M ONLY PILOTING
THE NIRVASH FOR HER SAKE.
BUT, EUREKA DOESN'T BELIEVE ME.
- ( car approaching )
- ( banging on door )
- RENTON, I'M TELLING YOU,
HURRY UP AND GET
BACK ON THE GEKKO!
- WHAT AM I DOING?
IT'S NO TIME TO BE
THINKING STUFF LIKE THIS.
- UH...
- RENTON, LISTEN TO ME.
NEXT TIME YOU TAKE
YOUR TIME LIKE THAT,
WE GONNA LEAVE YOU
BEHIND, YOU GOT IT?
HAP, HOW'S THE GEKKO?
- Hap: DOING WELL.
IT TOOK A WHILE
TO INSTALL THE VRFS
THAT WE BOUGHT
FROM THE JUNK SHOP,
BUT THERE ARE NO GLITCHES
IN THE TIME SCHEDULE.
RIGHT NOW, WE'RE GETTING
THE OF LAST FILMS SECURED.
BUT THANKS TO ALL OF THAT,
OUR FATIGUE IS ALSO AT ITS PEAK.
I THINK THAT'S A BIGGER PROBLEM
THAN THE LACK OF
TRAPARS IN THIS AREA.
- RENTON!
WE'VE GOT IT HERE.
YOU CAN GO PREPARE MEALS
FOR EVERYBODY.
- O-OKAY.
- ( whimpering )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HURRY UP AND GET GOING.
YOU DO REALIZE WHAT KIND OF
SITUATION WE'RE IN NOW, RIGHT?
HEY, HAP. WHERE'S HOLLAND?
- UH? OH, YEAH.
I SAW HIM HEAD TOWARDS
THE JUMP CATAPULT.
HE SAID HE WAS GOING
TO GO READ THE WAVES.
- ( wind blowing )
- ( door opening )
- Talho: DO YOU BELIEVE HIM?
- Holland: BELIEVE WHO?
- Talho: YOU KNOW.
THAT DIGGER NAMED BRITTANY.
THAT THE SCUB DOWN THERE
IS STILL ALIVE,
AND THAT THERE'S A
MASSIVE TRAPAR SPRING
DEEP UNDERNEATH THIS CAVE.
- Holland: WHO KNOWS?
- Talho: WHAT ARE YOU
PLANNING ON DOING NOW?
- NO IFS, ANDS OR BUTS.
WE GOTTA GO OUT
AND CRUSH THEM.
- AND THE NIRVASH?
WHAT ABOUT IT?
ARE YOU SENDING IT OUT?
- WITH EUREKA IN THE
CONDITION THAT SHE'S IN...
- YOU ARE FULLY AWARE
THAT RENTON IS GOOD ENOUGH
TO COVER US IN COMBAT, RIGHT?
- JUST SHUT UP!
- DO YOU WANT ME TO
SOUND LIKE A BROKEN RECORD?
DON'T RUN AWAY.
- ( scoffs )
- ( gasping )
PLEASE, WAIT.
I'M SORRY.
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE'S
SOMETHING WRONG WITH ME.
DO ALL OF YOU HATE ME NOW,
AS MUCH AS THE NIRVASH DOES?
- UH...
- ( crying )
- WHAT'S UP, YOU GUYS?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( grunting softly )
( screams )
- WHY DID YOU ASK ME?
ALL RIGHT.
EUREKA, MAETER AND THE KIDS
WANT TO SIT AND EAT A PIZZA
TOGETHER WITH YOU.
UH, YOU DON'T MIND, RIGHT?
IS IT ALL RIGHT
FOR ME TO COME IN?
EUREKA?
- Eureka: WHAT SHOULD I DO?
IT SEEMS THE KIDS
HATE ME NOW, TOO
I WISH I KNEW WHY.
WHY DID THINGS END UP THIS WAY?
I GUESS,
IT'S BECAUSE I'VE CHANGED.
IF THAT'S THE REASON,
I WISH I HADN'T CHANGED AT ALL.
- ( machine starting )
- FINAL SHEET APPLICATION
IS COMPLETE.
ALL THE WORK IS NOW DONE.
- ( all sighing )
- I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
WE ARE FINISHED.
- THE PROBLEM IS,
WE HAVE NO TRAPARS,
WE JUST CAN'T
LIFT OFF FROM HERE.
- ( tires screeching )
- CAN IT BE? EUREKA?
- Holland: IT HEADED TOWARDS
THE DEEP END OF THE CAVE?
WHAT THE HELL FOR?
- LIKE I WOULD KNOW.
I DIDN'T SEND IT THERE.
- HEY, DO YOU THINK
RENTON'S IN IT?
- OF COURSE HE IS.
EUREKA WOULD NEVER DO
SOMETHING STUPID LIKE THAT.
- Renton: ALL RIGHT,
YOU GUYS WAIT HERE, OKAY?
I'LL FIND SOME WAY
TO BRING EUREKA
AND THE NIRVASH BACK HERE.
- BUT, THE TRAPARS ARE DENSE
DEEP IN THE CAVE.
SO, IT'S DANGEROUS, RIGHT?
- I'LL BE FINE. I'M SURE
EVERYTHING WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
- Pilot: ENEMY SHIP
HAS CROSSED THE PERIMETER.
IT'S PROBABLY A SCOUT SHIP.
- WELL, THEY'RE FINALLY HERE.
- ( beeping )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- NEW DATA.
IT'S THE INTERFERENCE NUMBERS,
THEY'RE INCREASING RAPIDLY.
- THE TOTAL NUMBER IS...
A HUNDRED?
- WHAT THE...
THE MILITARY MUST HAVE DECIDED
TO FIGHT US WITH QUANTITY.
- (screaming)
- IT'S JUST THE FIRST WAVE.
DECLARING AN EMERGENCY
FOR ALL SHIPS.
ALL LFOS, PREPARE FOR LAUNCH,
AND BRACE FOR THE SECOND ATTACK.
- Man: THE OBSERVED QUANTA
LEVEL HAS DROPPED.
WE SEE NO SIGNS OF THE GEKKO
LAUNCHING FROM FAC51.
- EXACTLY AS I EXPECTED.
THEY CAN'T ESCAPE AS LONG
AS THERE ARE NO TRAPARS.
- PREPARE TO FIRE
THE NEXT SHELL.
- YES, SIR!
ATTENTION ALL AUTOMATIC
CANNONS AND SQUADS,
CHARLIE, BACKWORM AND ECHO,
OPEN FIRE!
- Holland: WOZ, DO YOU KNOW
HOW MANY ARE OUT THERE?
- Woz: I CAN'T FIGURE OUT
THE EXACT NUMBER
BECAUSE THEY DESTROYED THE
SENSORS THAT WE PUT OUT THERE.
BUT, WE STILL DON'T SHOW ANY
ATTACKS FROM THEIR KLF SQUADS.
IT LOOKS LIKE WITHOUT BOARDS
THEY CAN'T APPROACH US, EITHER.
- HEY, HAP, WHAT'S THE DEAL
WITH THE TRAPARS?
- Hap: THE NUMBERS
ARE STILL REALLY LOW.
THEY'LL SHOOT US DOWN
IF WE DO A NORMAL LAUNCH.
- KEN-GOH, REMOVE THE SAFETY
LOCKS FROM ALL WEAPONS.
- WAIT, DO YOU REALIZE HOW
OUT-GUNNED WE ARE RIGHT NOW?
- ALL WE NEED IS A DISTRACTION.
TALHO, WE'RE GOING TO USE
THE BOOSTERS TO LAUNCH US.
- START THE COUNTDOWN.
- Talho: HOLD ON JUST A SECOND.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
ABOUT THE NIRVASH?
BY THE WAY, RENTON'S IN IT
RIGHT NOW, IN CASE YOU FORGOT.
- I NEED TO
CONCENTRATE MORE ON
OURS AND EUREKA'S SURVIVAL
THAN THE NIRVASH'S.
- AND YOU'RE OKAY WITH THAT?
- IF EUREKA'S SAFE,
WE CAN GO GET THE NIRVASH LATER.
- THAT'S NOT IT!
I'M TALKING ABOUT...
ISN'T RENTON THE YOUNGER
BROTHER OF YOU-KNOW-WHO?
- Gidget: WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- GIDGET, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WELL, MISCHA JUST SAID
EUREKA IS MISSING.
- WHAT?
- ( gasping )
- THAT'S RIGHT. THE KIDS
WERE IN THE WAREHOUSE,
SO I ASKED THEM WHAT HAPPENED.
IT SEEMS THAT EUREKA IS THE ONE
WHO TOOK THE NIRVASH.
- ( gasps )
- THEN, WHERE'D RENTON GO?
- Mischa: THEY SAID HE WENT
TO GO AFTER EUREKA.
- HOLLAND!
- WE'LL WAIT, UNTIL THE
LAST POSSIBLE MOMENT.
- ROGER THAT.
- ALL HANDS, STAND BY IN
EMERGENCY LAUNCH MODE.
- WHAT?!
- KEEP THE SAFETY LOCKS ON ALL
WEAPONS SYSTEMS IN OFF POSITION.
START THE
BOOSTER FLYWHEELS NOW.
AND ONCE THAT'S ALL DONE,
WE'LL WAIT AS LONG AS WE CAN
FOR RENTON TO FIND EUREKA.
- Renton: THE TEMPERATURE
TOPPED THIRTY DEGREES.
AND I'VE JUST PASSED BELOW
EIGHT HUNDRED METERS.
EUREKA, WHERE ARE YOU? EUREKA!
- ( gasps )
- WHAT IS THAT?
( gasps )
- RENTON.
- ( gasps )
THAT WAS CLOSE.
HUH?
THE NIRVASH.
- THEY JUST HIT
THE JUMP CATAPULT.
- NOT GOOD. AT THE RATE
THINGS ARE GOING,
IT'LL BE IMPOSSIBLE,
EVEN WITH THE BOOSTERS.
HOLLAND, WHAT DO WE DO?
- Renton: THE AMITA DRIVE
HAS BEEN TAKEN OFF.
WHO THE WORLD WOULD DO THAT?
EUREKA!
EUREKA, WHERE ARE YOU?
EUREKA! EUREKA!
WHERE ARE YOU, EUREKA...
( gasps )
EUREKA?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I WAS LOOKING FOR A BOOK.
I HAVE TO FIND IT.
I HAVE TO FIND THE BOOK.
IF I DON'T HURRY,
THE BUS WILL LEAVE WITHOUT ME.
THE SUN WILL SET.
I HAVE TO HURRY
AND FIND MY BOOK.
IF I DON'T HURRY,
THE NIGHT WILL MELT ME AWAY.
I FOUND IT.
(gasps)
THIS IS ME,
A BOOK WITHOUT WORDS.
A BOOK WITH NOTHING
WRITTEN IN IT.
THIS IS ME.
THERE IS NOTHING TO ME.
I AM NOTHING AT ALL.
I COULDN'T FIND WHO I REALLY AM.
MELTING, MELTING.
I'M MELTING AWAY.
SCARED. I'M SCARED.
SOMEONE... SOMEONE, HELP ME.
PLEASE, SOMEONE...
SOMEONE HELP ME.
HELP ME, RENTON.
- (grunts)
- I'M SORRY.
I TOOK THE AMITA DRIVE,
AND THIS IS WHAT I DESERVE FOR
DOING SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- EUREKA!
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT IS
GOING TO BECOME OF ME?
- LET'S GO BACK.
LET'S GO BACK TO THE GEKKO NOW.
- I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
- I'M SO SORRY.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I PROMISE...
I PROMISE I'LL PROTECT YOU.
- OH, NO. WE'LL BE BURIED
ALIVE IF WE DON'T MOVE.
- BUT WE...
- Holland: LAUNCH.
GEKKO WILL DO A
HIGH-SPEED LAUNCH.
PREPARE TO FIRE THE BOOSTERS!
- BUT, WHAT ABOUT RENTON AND...
- LAUNCH.
HURRY UP, TALHO.
- HOLLAND.
- Renton: I'M SORRY,
I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S ME WHO NEEDS
TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU.
IT'S ME WHO WAS
ACTING SO SELFISH.
YOU WERE DESPERATELY
TRYING, EUREKA.
REACHING OUT,
WHEN YOU TOLD ME YOU WERE
ENTRUSTING ME WITH THE NIRVASH.
BUT I JUST DIDN'T...
I COULDN'T.
PLEASE, NIRVASH,
PLEASE HELP ME!
GIVE ME POWER! GIVE ME THE
POWER TO PROTECT EUREKA!
- Man: BOOSTERS AND
FLYWHEEL ARE STABLE.
COMMENCING THE COUNTDOWN.
- ALL CREW MEMBERS,
STRAP YOURSELVES IN NOW.
- ALL CIRCUITS ARE STABLE.
WE'RE ABLE TO FIRE
THE MAIN CANNONS NOW.
- Hap: EVERYTHING IS
IN POSITION.
WE'RE READY FOR LA--
HEY, WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- THE TRAPAR VALUES
ARE SKYROCKETING.
- HOW IS THAT?
- THERE IS A GIANT WAVE,
RIGHT BEHIND US.
- WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WAIT, THIS IS
A TRAPAR SOURCE STREAM?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
EUREKA, YOU'VE GOT TO ANSWER ME!
COME ON, ANSWER ME!
- Woz: A SHOCK WAVE
HAS BEEN CREATED
WITH THE SECOND TRAPAR WAVE!
OH, NO, IT'S A BIG ONE.
- FIRE THE BOOSTERS.
EMERGENCY LAUNCH!
- Officer: WHAT? WHAT IS THIS?
RETREAT. ALL SHIPS, RETREAT.
- EVERYBODY PULL BACK
TO THE DEFENSIVE LINE.
- ROGER!
- Hap: I'VE CAUGHT TRAPARS
IN THE VRF.
THE SHIP IS STABLE.
WE'LL BE ABLE TO GO BACK TO
THE LEY-LINE IN 30 SECONDS.
- OH, HOLLAND.
- Woz: I'VE GOT AN LFO SIGNAL
FROM RIGHT ABOVE FAC51.
- WHAT? WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE NIRVASH IS STILL...
CAN IT BE?
THAT THE HUGE TRAPAR WAVE
WE JUST SAW WAS A SEVEN SWELL?
WHAT DOES ALL OF THIS MEAN?
- Renton: I DON' T KNOW.
- YOU WERE THERE,
WEREN'T YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW! I WISH I DID.
I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON, TOO.
- I WON'T ACCEPT THAT.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
WHAT DID YOU DO TO EUREKA?
HOW DID YOU COME BACK
FROM DOWN THERE?
- I DON'T KNOW THE ANSWER
TO ANY OF THAT.
BY THE TIME I FOUND EUREKA,
SHE WAS ALREADY LIKE THIS.
- AND THEN EUREKA PASSED
OUT IN THE MIDDLE AND--
- WHAT?
THEN, YOU DID THIS
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- YES, BUT ONLY
BECAUSE EUREKA...
BECAUSE EUREKA ENDED UP
IN THAT CONDITION.
- LISTEN UP, RENTON.
YOU ARE NOT TO GET
ON THE NIRVASH ANYMORE.
GOT IT? AND IF YOU TELL ANYONE
WHAT HAPPENED TO EUREKA...
I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT I'LL DO TO YOU.
- TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ TAKE A CHANCE ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN MYSELF ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
- Narrator: IN THE FACE
OF THE GIRL'S DISFIGUREMENT,
FEELINGS AND EMOTIONS
ARE SHUT OUT.
THE BOY'S HEART,
OUT OF CONTROL,
CREATES AN
UNFORGETTABLE TRAGEDY.
NEXT EPISODE,
SUBSTANCE ABUSE.