- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YOU GOTTA REMEMBER ♪
- MAMA IS GOING TO BE
OKAY, RIGHT?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE IT'S NOTHING BAD.
HOLLAND SAID SO, DIDN'T HE?
- YEAH.
- SLOWLY, TALHO.
TAKE HER TO THE REAR EXAM TABLE.
- GOT IT.
- ( grunts ) HEY! WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT YOU DO THAT FOR?
- NO IFS, ANDS OR BUTS.
- YOU'RE STAYING OUTSIDE!
- ( sobbing )
- ( beeping )
- SO CAN YOU HELP HER, MISCHA?
- NO, I CAN'T.
RATHER, MODERN MEDICINE
CAN'T PEEL THIS SCUB OFF HER
WITHOUT CAUSING DAMAGE.
HOWEVER, HER CARDIOVASCULAR
FUNCTIONS SEEM TO BE STABLE,
AND HER VITAL SIGNS ARE GOOD.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE ANY PROBLEMS
IN SUSTAINING HER LIFE.
- BUT I...
- FINE! I GOT IT!
FOR THE TIME BEING,
WHAT HAPPENED TO EUREKA
STAYS BETWEEN US.
GOT THAT?
- ALL RIGHT.
- WELL, WHAT ABOUT RENTON?
- HMM?
- WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING
TO TELL RENTON ABOUT THIS?
- ( kids gasping )
HOLLAND!
- HOW'S EUREKA?
- HOW IS SHE?
- HOW'S MAMA?
- MAMA'S OKAY, RIGHT?
- All: RIGHT?
- SHE'S JUST FINE!
NOTHING SHE CAN'T HANDLE.
- I'M SO GLAD.
- SEE, GUYS, IT'S JUST
LIKE I TOLD YA.
MAMA'S GOING TO BE FINE.
- YOU ARE SUCH A LIAR!
YOU WERE ALL
TEARY EYED, LIKE US.
HEY! THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I WAS NOT.
- UH-HUH, I SAW YOU!
- YOU'RE A TADDLE TALE!
- IS SHE REALLY ALL RIGHT?
I THINK WE NEED TO TAKE
HER TO A PROPER HOSPITAL!
THE CITY OF LIEVELVILLE
HAS A BIG HOSPITAL.
- YOU NEED TO SHUT YOU MOUTH!
I'M TELLING YOU,
EUREKA IS JUST FINE!
ARE YOU DISSATISFIED
WITH WHAT I AM TELLING YOU?
- IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU!
IT'S ABOUT EUREKA'S WELL BEING!
- STOP IT! BOTH OF YOU.
- DAMN YOU!
- Man on Loudspeaker:
HOLLAND! TALHO!
COME TO THE BRIDGE.
WE HAVE A CALL FROM
MASTER DELGEL OF THE VODARAC.
THERE'S SOMETHING URGENT
HE WANTS TO ASK YOU.
WE GOT A MESSAGE
FROM THE VODARAC
VIA CODE JIG
AT 12:30 TODAY.
IT WAS A REQUEST TO RESCUE
A CERTAIN HIGH PRIEST X.
- HIGH PRIEST X?
- THAT JUST MEANS THEY CAN'T
DISCLOSE HIS NAME.
- YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
RIGHT NOW, HIGH PRIEST X
IS LOCKED UP
IN A DOVE GRAVE PRISON
ACCUSED OF A POLITICAL CRIME.
IT'S APPARENTLY A FALSE CHARGE,
BUT X HAS BEEN UNABLE
TO GET A PROPER TRIAL,
AND IS ABOUT TO BE EXECUTED.
- AND THEY WANT US TO
GO IN AND SAVE HIM?
- YEAH, YOU GOT IT.
HOW LONG BEFORE
THEY EXECUTE HIM?
- WELL, JUST TWO HOURS.
- OH, MAN! ALL THINGS
CONSIDERED, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- BUT IN RETURN,
THEY'LL PAY US 50 MILLION.
- HUH? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- IT MEANS NOBODY
WOULD ACCEPT THE JOB
IF THEY DIDN'T OFFER THAT MUCH.
IF I RECALL, THERE'S A STATE
ARMY BASE RIGHT NEAR THERE?
- YEAH, A HARD PLACE
TO GET PAST.
- ALL LFOS OTHER THAN THE
NIRVASH ARE DISCHARGED,
AND ONLY ONE OF THE BATTERIES
HAS COMPLETED RECHARGING.
OUR LACK OF MONEY IS SERIOUS,
BUT WE HAVE TO LET
THIS ONE PASS.
- WAIT. I'LL GO.
IN ANY CASE, THIS IS
A COVERT OPERATION.
A SINGLE BATTERY
SHOULD BE ENOUGH.
AND IF I GO IN VEHICLE MODE,
I WON'T SHOW UP ON THEIR...
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING!
YOU CARE MORE ABOUT
MONEY THAN ABOUT EUREKA?
ISN'T TAKING HER TO A HOSPITAL
MORE IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW?
- MONEY IS IMPORTANT.
SO IS WATER, FUEL AND FOOD.
AND YOU KNOW IT'S NOT FREE
TO GO SEE A DOCTOR.
- BUT, EVEN SO!
- I'M THE LEADER HERE.
YOU'RE JUST A LITTLE KID.
YOU WERE ABLE TO ESCAPE THANKS
TO THIS LITTLE KID, WEREN'T YOU?
IF IT WASN'T FOR MY NIRVASH,
THAT OPERATION...
- OH, RIGHT.
I NEARLY FORGOT.
THANKS FOR ALL
THE HARD WORK, KID.
- YOU SURE SAVED US,
DIDN'T YOU?
- ( slams )
- OH, AND ANOTHER THING.
WHERE DO YOU GET OFF
CALLING THE NIRVASH YOURS,
- YOU LITTLE TWERP?
- EUREKA TOLD ME
THAT IT WAS MINE!
SHE SAID THAT IT WAS
BETTER FOR ME
TO BE PILOTING THE
NIRVASH RIGHT NOW!
( grunts )
- ALL RIGHT, HOLLAND.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
- STAY OUT OF IT, HAP!
HE'S GOTTEN FULL OF HIMSELF!
- I SAID, THAT'S ENOUGH!
YOU'RE THE LEADER OF THE
GEKKOSTATE, FOR CRYIN' OUT LOUD!
YOU REALLY THINK
YOU SHOULD BE
VENTING YOUR FRUSTRATIONS
ON RENTON?
GEEZ, HE'S AN UNRESISTING CHILD.
IT'S EMBARRASSING!
- I'M GOING TO PROTECT HER.
I'M GOING TO PROTECT EUREKA.
SINCE YOU WON'T DO IT,
I'M GOING TO TAKE EUREKA TO A
HOSPITAL TO GET HER SOME HELP!
DAMMIT, DAMMIT, DAMMIT!
JUST BECAUSE YOUR BODY
IS A LITTLE BIGGER THAN MINE
DOESN'T MAKE YOU BETTER
THAN ME.
- I DON'T LIKE YOUR ATTITUDE.
- PRETENDING YOUR SOME KIND
OF KNIGHT OR SOMETHING.
- I'M NOT PRETENDING!
- SOMEDAY, I'LL BECOME
A REAL KNIGHT, YOU'LL SEE!
I'M NOT GOING TO HELP YOU OUT.
DO THE RESCUE MISSION YOURSELF.
I'LL NEVER HELP YOU
AS LONG AS I LIVE!
- YOU ARE SO FULL OF IT!
I DON'T NEED YOU, YOU JERK!
I CAN TAKE CARE OF IT BY MYSELF!
( groans )
I CAN DO THIS THING,
ALL BY MYSELF.
- HEY! ARE YOU ALIVE?
- Holland: I'LL HAVE ONE CHANCE
FROM 15:00 to 15:20.
EVEN IF I GO THROUGH
THE DRY VALLEY OVER HERE,
I SHOULD HAVE PLENTY OF TIME.
- YOU'RE IMMATURE.
- HUH?
- BEING SO SERIOUS GOING
AGAINST A LITTLE KID.
- I WASN'T DOING THAT.
- YOU WERE TOO.
- I WAS NOT!
I'M AN ADULT!
- THE FACT THAT YOU
SAY YOU'RE AN ADULT
JUST PROVES THAT
YOU'RE STILL IMMATURE.
- DO YOU HAVE A MINUTE, HOLLAND?
I HAVE SOMETHING
I WANT TO ASK YOU?
- YEAH? RENTON IS MORE THAN
ENOUGH FOR THAT KIND OF STUFF.
- DON'T BE SUCH AN IDIOT.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
I WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT.
- I'M BUSY RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO FINISH DISCUSSING
MY PLANS WITH HAP.
THE VODARAC'S REQUEST.
WHY DID YOU ACCEPT?
A HIGH PRIEST OF THE VODARAC
MIGHT BE ABLE TO CURE EUREKA?
- IS THAT IT?
- I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
WE'LL DISCUSS IT
WHEN I GET BACK.
- ( metallic clanging )
- STOP RUNNING AWAY LIKE THAT.
YOU USED EUREKA AS A MEANS
TO GET AWAY FROM THE ARMY
AND THEN TO GET AWAY
FROM YOU KNOW WHO.
- NOT TRUE.
- OH, YEAH? WHAT PART?!
WHEN IT COMES DOWN RIGHT
TO IT, YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING
WITHOUT PUTTING THE
BLAME ON SOMEONE ELSE!
- THAT'S NOT TRUE!
I'M NOT LIKE THAT.
I'M REALLY NOT
LIKE THAT AT ALL.
- ( water splashes )
- HEY RENTON, ARE YOU OKAY?
- I'M SURE HOLLAND JUST
GOT TO HIM AGAIN.
- YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
- HOLLAND?
- HEY, RENTON, WHERE
ARE YOU GOING?
- Linck: ARE YOU GOING
TO GO FIGHT BACK?
- Maeter: DON'T DO IT.
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'D WIN, YOU KNOW.
- AREN'T YOU GUYS EVEN A LITTLE
BIT WORRIED ABOUT EUREKA?
- NO WAY! CAUSE HOLLAND TOLD US
THAT OUR MAMA WAS ALL RIGHT.
- YOU SEE, RENTON, HOLLAND
HAS ALWAYS BEEN THE ONE
WHO PROTECTED MAMA FOR US.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT. FROM WAY,
WAY BEFORE SHE BECAME OUR MAMA.
- GET OUT!
- Renton: NIRVASH.
WHAT IN THE WORLD ARE YOU?
IT'S NOT THE SAME
AS WITH EUREKA.
NO MATTER HOW I TRY
I CAN'T HEAR YOUR VOICE.
- I'M GOING TO TAKE
PHOTOGRAPHIC EVIDENCE.
YOU'VE BEEN PROHIBITED FROM
PILOTING THE NIRVASH,
HAVEN'T YOU?
- YEAH, SO WHAT?
I'M JUST SITTING HERE!
DO YOU THINK IT'S ALL RIGHT?
- YOU KNOW...
- THE SEVEN SWELL?
- YEAH. EVEN THOUGH WE
WERE SAVED BECAUSE OF IT,
IT'S STILL TOO DANGEROUS.
BESIDES, I CAN'T REALLY
PUT IT TO WORDS BUT...
BUT IT JUST DOESN'T FIT IN
THE CAMERA FRAME TOO WELL.
- Holland: I'VE JUST PASSED
POINT I 509.
NO SIGNS OF THE ENEMY.
EVERYTHING IS GOING
ACCORDING TO PLAN.
- Hap: HEY, HOLLAND.
IF YOU GET IN A BIND,
YOU HIGH TAIL IT BACK HERE.
- TRUST ME, HAP.
MISSIONS LIKE THESE ARE NO...
- NO BIG DEAL.
YOU'VE DONE IT A LOT, RIGHT?
- YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT STUFF
THAT HAPPENED THREE YEARS AGO
WHEN YOU WERE STILL AN
ACE PILOT WITH THE SOF.
- I'M ALMOST THROUGH THE FOREST.
I'LL BE SEVERING
COMMUNICATIONS SOON.
BELIEVE IT.
I CAN STILL PULL THIS OFF.
- ENJOY IT.
THIS IS THE LAST TIME
YOU GET TO LOOK AT THE SKY.
- Prisoner: I GUESS
HE REALLY IS A PRIEST.
HE DOESN'T SEEM WORRIED AT ALL.
TOO BAD BELIEVING ALONE
WON'T SAVE YOU HERE.
- HEY, LOOK AT THAT.
- ( yawns )
- HEY WHAT'S HE DOING?
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
WHEN YOU PRAY LIKE THAT,
GOD WILL COME DOWN
TO WHERE YOU ARE.
- THAT'S AN LFO.
- SHOOT IT! NOW!
DAMMIT! THEY'RE GETTING AWAY!
- Holland: GET IN THE BACK SEAT!
I WAS SENT HERE BY
MASTER DELGEL OF THE VODARAC!
- EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENS,
HAPPENS AS GUIDED
BY THE VODARAC.
- I HAVE A GIRL THAT I WANT
YOU TO SAVE SOMEHOW,
USING THAT GUIDANCE
THAT YOU GUYS TALK ABOUT.
- A SCUB...
- ( beeping )
- KLFS?
I GUESS I HAVE BEEN
FORCED INTO A RUT HERE.
- ( instrument beeping )
- MISS TALHO.
- DAMN!
HEY, MISTER PRIEST!
CAN YOU USE THAT
TO TIE MY HEAD UP?
BLOOD'S GETTING IN MY EYES!
HURRY UP!
- YES, OF COURSE.
- Talho: WHY DID YOU COME HERE?
- I JUST THOUGHT I'D TAKE
A GLIMPSE OF HER FACE.
- HMM. YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
DOING LEWD THINGS
TO HER WHILE SHE
WAS SLEEPING, RIGHT?
- AND WHAT WERE YOU
DOING HERE, MISS TALHO?
- I WAS THINKING
ABOUT KILLING HER.
- ( gasps )
- IT'S A JOKE.
- EACH AND EVERY ONE
OF YOU PISSES ME OFF.
EVERY GUY OPENS THEIR MOUTH
AND IT'S EUREKA THIS,
AND EUREKA THAT.
I COULD COMPETE IF SHE
WAS A NORMAL GIRL.
BUT I'M...
I'M GOING AGAINST THE WORLD.
- HMM? THE WORLD?
- ( beeping )
- Hap on loudspeaker: EVERYONE!
GET TO YOUR STATIONS!
HOLLAND IS IN TROUBLE!
- COME ON, HOLLAND!
THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME
YOU'VE FACED THIS MANY KLFS!
- ARE WE UNABLE TO
MAKE OUR ESCAPE?
- YOU STAY QUIET!
- WE'RE GOING TO
TAKE A NOSEDIVE!
- MAKE SURE YOU HOLD ON TIGHT!
- OH, RIGHT!
- OKAY, WHAT DO I DO?
WHAT DO MY INSTINCTS SAY?
DO I GO LEFT?
OR TURN RIGHT?
GO LEFT?
OR GO RIGHT?
LEFT!
- ALL RIGHT, I'VE
DESTROYED HIS BOARD!
NOW ALL HE CAN DO IS CRAWL
AROUND ON THE GROUND!
I'LL TAKE HIM DOWN AND SLOWLY.
HE WON'T BE ABLE TO RUN NOW.
- Renton: IT SERVES HIM RIGHT.
IT'S BECAUSE HIS EYES WENT
STRAIGHT FOR THE MONEY.
HE CURSED HIMSELF BECAUSE HE
DIDN'T TAKE HER TO THE HOSPITAL.
HE DIDN'T CARE ABOUT EUREKA!
- DO YOU REALLY THINK THAT
HE WOULD DO SOMETHING
JUST FOR THE MONEY?
HE'D NEVER DO THAT!
HE... HE...
HE WENT SO HE CAN
TRY AND SAVE EUREKA!
BECAUSE THAT THING ON EUREKA
CAN'T BE FIXED BY ANY DOCTOR!
BECAUSE IT CAN ONLY BE FIXED
BY A VODARAC PRIEST!
FOR MONEY? THAT COULD
NEVER BE THE CASE.
THAT IDIOT ALWAYS TAKES CARE OF
EUREKA MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
MORE THAN ANY WAVE.
MORE THAN ME!
MAYBE EVEN, MORE THAN HIMSELF!
- ( grunting )
- Ken-Goh: JOBS! I DON'T CARE
WHICH LFO, GET IT MOVING ASAP!
IT'S GOING TO BE
DAMNED DANGEROUS,
BUT WE'LL HAVE TO SHOW OURSELVES
IN FRONT OF THE ENEMY.
- KEN-GOH.
- TAHLO, DON'T JUST STAND THERE!
IT'S YOUR JOB TO BE
STEERING THIS SHIP,
SO HURRY UP AND GET TO IT!
- Hap: FLY WHEELS, TO GO.
READY FOR CATAPULT RELEASE.
WHOA, GIDGET, GET UP
TO THE BRIDGE.
- HAP, ESTABLISH COMMUNICATION
WITH THE VODARAC.
DON'T USE NORMAL CONNECTIONS.
- BEARING IS 1-2-0-6!
PREPARE TO LIGHT
UP BOTH BOOSTERS.
- I...
- IF ANYTHING BAD SHOULD
HAPPEN TO HER,
I'LL KILL YOU,
YOU UNDERSTAND?
- I...
- SEE THERE IS NOTHING ELSE
THAT I CAN REALLY BELIEVE IN.
OTHER THAN THE NIRVASH
AND HOLLAND.
- Renton: HOLLAND HAS ALWAYS
BEEN THE ONE TO PROTECT EUREKA.
- YOU SEE, RENTON, HOLLAND
HAS ALWAYS BEEN THE ONE
WHO PROTECTED MAMA FOR US.
- BUT... BUT, I...
I'M SUCH A KID.
I'M JUST AN IMMATURE KID,
WHO DOESN'T KNOW ANYTHING!
( breathing deeply )
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( screaming )
THE FORMER ACE PILOT OF THE
SOF FIRST MOBILE SQUADRON
ENDS UP LIKE THIS?
IT'S JUST LIKE HAP SAID.
GEEZ, WHAT THE HELL AM I DOING?
I REALLY AM PATHETIC.
- Ken-Goh: CAPTAIN! DON'T PANIC!
KEEP YOUR DISTANCE!
AS LONG AS WE SURROUND HIM
THERE'S NOTHING TO FEAR.
WAIT A MINUTE! THAT'S...
THE TYPE ZERO!
ZERO THREE!
- THAT KID.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT HE'D
BUST THROUGH ALL BY HIMSELF?
YEAH, WELL...
HE'S STILL JUST A KID.
- Ken-Goh: THE SKULL KLF
SQUADRON HAS BEEN ANNIHILATED.
- Hap: HOW MANY ENEMY SHIPS?
- I BELIEVE IT IS ONE LFO.
- WELL DONE.
YOU GOT THEM, RENTON!
TALHO, LOOKS LIKE HE
MADE IT IN TIME.
- I'M A KID. THAT'S ALL.
I'M JUST A LITTLE KID THAT
CAN'T DO A DAMN THING. BUT I...
- ZERO THREE TO ZERO ONE.
WE HAVE ONE LFO COMING IN FAST!
- I... I DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING.
NOTHING ABOUT HOLLAND.
NOTHING ABOUT EUREKA.
NOTHING AT ALL!
- ALL SHIPS, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
ZERO-TWO TO ZERO-ONE!
THE SQUADRON CASUALTIES
WILL INCREASE
IF WE ENTER CLOSE RANGE
COMBAT RIGHT NOW!
- WHEN THE SMOKE CLEARS,
WE'LL ALL FIRE AT ONCE!
- ROGER!
- DAMN IT!
( panting )
- Holland: THANKS FOR PICKING
ALONG FOR ME.
RENTON, THAT'S ENOUGH.
- DAMN IT.
DAMN IT!
DAMN!
- Holland: RENTON,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
ENOUGH! WE NEED TO GET BACK.
HEY, RENTON!
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
RENTON! RENTON!
ANSWER ME!
RENTON!
- OM MANI DARAM,
OM MANI DARAM...
- RENTON, YOU GOTTA CALM DOWN.
YOU'RE GOING TOO FAR.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
- IT'S ALL OVER!
- DAMN IT, DAMN IT!
DAMN IT! DAMN IT! DAMN IT!
- ( delirious laughter echoing )
- ( screams )
- Hap: HOLLAND!
WHAT'S GOING ON THERE?
EXPLAIN THE SITUATION.
- IT'S RIDER'S HIGH.
NO, HE'S GONE WAY BEYOND THAT.
IF RENTON IS REALLY
PILOTING THAT THING,
THE NIRVASH IS...
- ( Renton breathing heavily )
( screams )
- ( panting )
- ( closing theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE.
♪ FLY AWAY! FLY AWAY!
♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE.
TAKE IT EASY.
♪ FLY AWAY! FLY AWAY!
♪ TAKE MY CHANCE.
♪ BELIEVE IN MYSELF.
♪ TAKE IT EASY. ♪
- Talho: EVERYDAY LIFE
CRUMBLES AWAY,
AND THE TRUTH SURFACES.
THE BOY, LOSING SIGHT OF
WHAT HE SHOULD BELIEVE IN,
HEADS DOWN TO THE WILDERNESS
WITH NOTHING TO TURN TO.
NEXT EPISODE, "RUNAWAY."