- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YOU GOTTA REMEMBER ♪
♪ WE ARE GONNA MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE ♪
♪ YOU GOTTA REMEMBER ♪
- Priest: DISATOPAA RAJUNAPALA
SLITCHERVILA TITAVARANA.
TITAPATRA STVARYASA
KURASABODI.
- ( moaning in pain )
- ( chanting )
- Holland: IT PROVED USEFUL,
AFTER ALL.
- ARE YOU DONE?
- HOW IS SHE?
WHEN A BEING WHO HAS GONE TO THE
VERY END OF THE EIGHTH REALM,
IS RETURNED TO THE WORLD,
WE KNOW THE WORLD OF
THE THIRD REALM,
IT IS SAID THAT THEY ALWAYS
END UP LOOKING LIKE THIS.
- SOMEONE WHO TOUCHED
THE END OF THE WORLD?
I HAVE PERFORMED
THE RYOJU RITUAL
THAT HAS BEEN GIVEN
TO ME BY MASTER NORB.
NOW, WE CAN ONLY
WAIT AND SEE
WHAT KIND OF GUIDANCE
THE VODARAC WILL SHOW
TO THIS GIRL'S IMPRISONED SOUL.
- ( gasps )
( breathing heavily )
( screams )
IT WAS A DREAM.
- ( beeping )
- Holland: SORRY TO TROUBLE YOU.
- NOT AT ALL, I WAS THE ONE
THAT WAS RESCUED.
- IS EUREKA ALL RIGHT NOW?
- MOST LIKELY.
- HOWEVER, DON'T LET THE CAUSE
OF ALL THIS GET CLOSE TO HER.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THEN EVERYTHING IS AS
THE VODARAC GUIDES IT TO BE.
- YOU ALL HEARD HIM.
THE HIGH PRIEST SAID
HE'S DANGEROUS.
- COME ON, HOLLAND.
DON'T YOU THINK YOU ARE JUMPING
TO CONCLUSIONS A LITTLE BIT?
- WHO ELSE COULD HAVE CAUSED
ALL THIS TO HAPPEN?!
EVER SINCE HE GOT HERE,
EUREKA HAS BEEN BECOMING
STRANGER AND STRANGER EVERYDAY.
- BUT HOLLAND,
YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR THAT.
- OH, YEAH? HOW IS THAT?
- YOU BROUGHT HIM HERE.
- YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE
FOR BRINGING HIM ABOARD,
KNOWING THAT HE WAS DIANE'S
YOUNGER BROTHER.
- WHERE IS HE?
- HE'S COOPED HIMSELF UP
IN HIS OWN ROOM.
- WITH THESE HANDS,
I KILLED SOMEONE.
OF COURSE, IT SEEMS I HAVE
BEEN KILLING PEOPLE ALL ALONG.
- ( stomach grumbling )
- SIS, EVEN WHEN
THEY'RE IN PAIN,
PEOPLE STILL
BECOME HUNGRY.
( munching loudly )
- MY HUNGER DISAPPEARED
WHEN I ATE,
BUT, THE PAIN IN MY HEART
DIDN'T GO AWAY.
- I'M SORRY,
BUT CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR
AND PUT THIS ON MY TAB? THANKS.
- I'M IN SO MUCH PAIN,
YET NOT ONE PERSON HERE GIVES
ME EVEN THE TINIEST KIND WORD.
- WHY ARE YOU HERE, RENTON?
- YOU GO AWAY, PUKEY.
- YEAH, GO AWAY.
- IT WAS YOU WHO DID
THAT AWFUL THING TO MY MAMA.
- HOLLAND TOLD US ALL ABOUT IT.
- WHAT'S ALL
THE COMMOTION ABOUT?
- THERE ARE NO
VISITS ALLOWED,
BUT RENTON'S KEEPS TRYING
TO GO IN TO SEE MAMA.
- MISS MISCHA...
HOW'S EUREKA?
- THANKS TO THE VODARAC PRIEST,
SHE IS STARTING TO
STABILIZE PHYSICALLY.
HOWEVER, SHE'S
MENTALLY UNSTABLE.
IT'S NOT JUST YOU.
NO VISITORS ARE ALLOWED.
- SO, I CAN'T SEE HER?
- I'M SORRY.
- ( munching loudly )
- IS SOMETHING WRONG, RENTON?
GEEZ, I WONDER
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
- WAIT A MINUTE,
DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- NOTHING. I BEHAVED JUST LIKE
I ALWAYS DO AROUND HIM.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- OF COURSE, I AM.
- I'M REALLY GOOD AT THAT
KIND OF STUFF, YOU KNOW?
- I DOUBT THAT.
- COME ON, IT'S TRUE.
- ( humming )
- HUH? HEY, RENTON,
GOOD TO SEE YOU BACK UP.
BY THE WAY, DID THE PACK
OF SILK UNDERWEAR
I ORDERED COME IN YET?
I'M DOWN TO MY LAST GOOD PAIR.
HEY, RENTON,
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
- ( mumbling )
- THAT'S GREAT.
DIDN'T YOUR MOTHER
EVER TEACH YOU
NOT TO TALK WITH YOUR
MOUTH FULL OF FOOD?
ESPECIALLY POTATO CHIPS.
- ♪ UNDERWEAR, UNDERWEAR,
WHERE'S MY UNDERWEAR? ♪
HMM? WHAT'S THIS?
( chuckles )
WHO'S GOING TO WEAR
SOMETHING THIS HUGE?
- MR. MATTHIEU.
- WHAT, I AM?
- EVERYONE KNEW ALL ALONG.
- WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
EVERYONE KNEW ALL ALONG,
AND THEY ARE STILL DOING IT.
EVERYONE HERE KNEW.
EVERYONE KNEW THIS IS A WAR.
WE'RE KILLING PEOPLE!
- ( sighs ) YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THINK ABOUT IT, RENTON.
ALL KLFS ARE PILOTED
BY PEOPLE.
AND WHEN WE DEFEAT THEM,
THOSE PEOPLE DIE.
I MEAN EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT.
- WHY DO YOU DO IT?
- JUST WHO DID
YOU THINK WE WERE
WHEN YOU JOINED UP WITH US?
A BUNCH OF CAREFREE GUYS WHO
DID NOTHING BUT RIDE TRAPARS?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
THERE'S NO WAY
A BUNCH OF REF BOARDERS
COULD HAVE EQUIP THEMSELVES
WITH WEAPONS AND LFOS.
IN ORDER FOR US TO SURVIVE,
SOMETIMES WE HAVE
TO KILL PEOPLE.
THAT'S THE DESTINY OF
SOMEONE WHO FIGHTS
AGAINST THE GOVERNMENT
AND SOCIETY.
IF WE DON'T FIGHT, THEY'LL JUST
COME AND HUNT US DOWN.
IF YOU WANT TO GO
AND CALL THAT A WAR,
THEN I GUESS WHAT WE ARE DOING
IS FIGHTING A WAR.
- THEN, HOW COULD YOU DO IT?
HOW CAN YOU BEHAVE NORMALLY
LIKE NOTHING IS HAPPENING?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BEHAVE NORMALLY?
I MEAN, COME ON, THIS IS
EVERYDAY LIFE FOR US HERE.
AND YOU KNEW THAT ALL ALONG
WHEN YOU JOINED GEKKOSTATE.
- ( gasps )
- MAN, THIS SURE IS A HUGE
PAIR OF UNDERWEAR.
- NOW, I'M TRUSTING YOU, KIDS.
- LEAVE IT TO US.
- HUH? A RAT?
- A RAT? A RAT.
- IT WENT THAT WAY.
- All: WAIT.
- ( beeping )
- RENTON.
- EUREKA.
- WHAT?
- GOT A MINUTE?
- Eureka: I WAS TOLD THAT I
WASN'T SUPPOSED TO SEE YOU.
- THAT'S WHAT THEY TOLD ME, TOO.
- THEY SAID THAT IF
I GET CLOSE TO YOU,
YOU COULD BECOME UNSTABLE AGAIN.
- THEY'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
I MEAN,
I CAN ALREADY FEEL MY HEART
STARTING TO SPEED UP.
- ( beeping )
- I FINALLY UNDERSTAND.
- UNDERSTAND WHAT?
- THAT WE'RE FIGHTING.
- I HONESTLY THOUGHT
I HAD UNDERSTOOD IT
BACK WHEN YOU TOLD ME,
THAT WE ALL WERE IN A WAR.
THAT WE WERE
ACTUALLY FIGHTING.
BUT I DIDN'T.
- ( sobs ) IT DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE IT WAS REAL.
IT JUST DIDN'T SEEM LIKE,
LIKE THERE WAS REALLY SOMEONE,
INSIDE THAT KLF.
- YOU WERE FIGHTING
WITHOUT REALIZING THAT?
- ( gasps )
I...
YOU KNOW, EUREKA, I WANT
YOU TO KNOW ONE THING.
THE WHOLE TIME I WAS ONLY
FIGHTING TO PROTECT YOU.
- BUT, IF YOU DESTROY A HUMAN,
THEN HE'LL NEVER COME BACK.
- ( gasps ) THAT'S A
CRUEL WAY OF PUTTING IT.
YOU REALLY DIDN'T
HAVE TO SAY IT THAT WAY.
I DID IT ALL FOR YOU.
BECAUSE I THINK THAT YOU
ARE SOMEONE I CAN MAYBE...
- NO!
- ( beeping rapidly )
- ( crying ) I'M SORRY.
THIS SUCKS. I'M SUCH A JERK.
( exclaims )
IT WASN'T ABOUT A WAR
OR HOW THE PEOPLE
OF GEKKOSTATE LIVE.
I WAS HERE BECAUSE
I WANTED TO PROTECT EUREKA.
BUT... BUT NOW,
EUREKA HATES ME.
THIS IS THE WORST.
- ( gasps ) THE AMITA DRIVE.
DOESN'T MATTER, IT'S OVER.
- HELLO, THERE. CARE FOR TEA?
- ( wind blowing )
- WELL, GIVE EVERYONE MY BEST.
THERE'S NOWHERE FOR ME
TO STAY ON THE GEKKO ANYMORE.
BUT THE SKIES I JUMPED INTO,
SEEMED ALL WARPED
BECAUSE OF MY TEARS.
- ( siren blaring )
- COME ON, CHARLES,
WE'VE GOT A JOB.
- HMM? BUT MY PIZZA
IS GOING TO GET COLD.
- I'M SURE YOU CAN GET
RID OF THE PIRATES
BEFORE THAT HAPPENS.
- YEAH, YEAH. I GUESS
I HAVE TO DO IT
FOR A CUTE LITTLE RAY.
- ( chuckles )
HEY, DON'T SWEET TALK ME.
NOW, COME ON, LET'S GO.
- ( burps ) AH, PIZZA.
- ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH OF THAT.
WE'RE JUST ABOUT
IN RANGE, CHARLES.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
THIS IS PERFECT
FOR A PRE-MEAL EXERCISE.
- I'LL BE DAMNED.
I GUESS THAT BOARD
WAS A DECOY.
- ( loud explosion )
- MAN, I HOPE THAT PIZZA
IS STILL HOT.
- WAIT A MINUTE, DON'T WE
HAVE TO PICK UP THE LOOT
FROM THE FALLEN SHIP?
- I DON'T KNOW. DO WE GET
TO CHARGE EXTRA FOR THAT?
WELL, WE GET A BONUS FOR THIS.
SO, I GUESS WE SHOULDN'T
BE TOO GREEDY.
- ( giggles ) I LOVE YOU.
- ( grunts )
- BORING! BORING! BORING!
IT'S ALL BORING!
WHY WON'T YOU LET ME
GET ON THE END, HUH?
HE'S CRYING OUT FOR ME,
YOU KNOW.
- ANEMONE, PLEASE CALM DOWN
AND TRY TO LISTEN
TO WHAT I'M SAYING.
- I DON'T GET IT.
- ( grunts )
- THE AGEHA PROJECT IS COMING
TO A CRITICAL STAGE.
IT'S ABOUT THE GEKKOSTATE.
WE CAN'T LEAVE THEM ALONE NOW.
- THAT'S WHY I'M GOING TO USE
THE END TO CRUSH THEM,
TYPE ZERO AND ALL!
ANEMONE, THE COLONEL SAID THAT
JOB IS TOO MUNDANE FOR YOU.
TOO EASY.
- DEWEY SAID THAT?
- YEAH, HE DID.
AND THIS VERY MOMENT,
HE'S CONTACTING SOMEONE
TO DO THAT JOB FOR YOU.
- I'M AFRAID THAT
THIS WAS THE ONLY WAY
FOR ME TO CONTACT
THE TWO OF YOU.
PLEASE DON'T THINK BADLY OF ME.
- DON'T YOU THINK
IT'S A LITTLE SAVAGE
FORCING A
DOCKING LIKE THAT?
WELL, I SUPPOSE THAT'S
THE WAY YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN.
- SO, WHAT DOES A HIGH-RANKING
ARMY OFFICER WANT FROM ME?
COMING OUT HERE WITH
A HIGH-SPEED SHIP AND ALL?
- YOU STILL USE THIS?
- IT'S WHAT I GOT
INSTEAD OF DISCHARGE PAY.
- DO YOU KNOW THE ORIGIN
OF THE TERM FREELANCE?
- HUH?
- COMES FROM FREE LANCE.
- IN OTHER WORDS, A SPEAR.
A SOLDIER FOR HIRE.
A CUTTING EDGE AIMED
AGAINST ANYONE
AND GIVEN MONEY IN RETURN.
I'D BE HAPPY TO
GIVE YOU THAT MONEY.
- YOU WANT ME BACK
IN THE MILITARY?
YOU ALREADY KNOW MY ANSWER.
I WON'T DO IT.
THE CAREFREE LIFE OF A
MERCENARY FITS MY PERSONALITY.
I CAN'T GO BACK
TO AN UPTIGHT ARMY, NOW.
BESIDES, THIS WAY
WE CAN LIVE IN PEACE.
- AND THAT'S THAT.
AND NOW, WILL YOU
GO HOME, PLEASE?
- I'LL LET YOU SETTLE
YOUR SCORE WITH HOLLAND.
- ( gasps )
- DO YOU STILL DECLINE?
- DON'T BEG FOR THINGS.
DO IT YOURSELF.
- THEN IT WILL BE GIVEN TO YOU.
- ( sneezes )
SOMEONE'S SPREADING
RUMORS ABOUT ME.
- OH, YEAH?
AN OLD GIRLFRIEND MAYBE?
- WELL, YOU SOUND
AWFULLY IRRITATED.
- AND YOU'RE TREATING
RENTON PRETTY BADLY.
- IT'S NOT BAD TREATMENT.
IT'S JUST HE IS...
HE'S DANGEROUS, THAT'S ALL.
- AND WHICH FOOL DID THAT
DANGEROUS BOY SAVE?
- HUH?
- YOU WENT OFF AND TRIED
TO SAVE EUREKA.
BUT, AT THE SAME TIME,
RENTON WAS TRYING
TO SAVE HER, TOO.
YOU HAVE TO TRY AND UNDERSTAND
HIS FEELINGS FOR HER.
- WHY, HE'S DANGEROUS!
- YOU REALLY ARE IMMATURE.
- ( door closes )
- ( grunts )
- HEY, DO YOU KNOW
WHERE MY BAG WENT?
- YOUR BAG?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU SEE, MY FAVORITE ONE
IS MISSING.
- LOOK, I'M NOT IN CHARGE
OF REMEMBERING
WHERE YOU PUT YOUR STUFF.
- ( sobbing )
- HMM.
- ( all giggling )
- HUH?
- DID RENTON STOP BY?
- WE SHOOED PUKEY AWAY.
- Linck: WE WON'T LET HIM
ANYWHERE NEAR MAMA.
- I SEE.
- ( beeps )
- DID SOMEONE JUST STOP BY?
- DON'T KNOW.
WHY DO YOU ASK, DEAR ?
- I HAD A FEELING
THAT RENTON MIGHT COME VISIT.
- WHY DID YOU THINK THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- HEY, RENTON?
- CARE FOR SOME TEA?
- UM, DO YOU KNOW
WHERE RENTON WENT?
- RENTON LEFT.
HE SAID TO GIVE HIS
BEST REGARDS TO EVERYONE.
- THAT DAMN BRAT.
WITHOUT ANY PERMISSION,
HE JUST...
WHEN HE COMES BACK, I'M GOING
TO GIVE HIM A GOOD SPANKING.
- ( sneezes )
- I GUESS I REALLY JUMPED
OUT OF THE SHIP.
NOW, WHAT DO I DO?
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( closing theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ TAKE MY CHANCE ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN MYSELF ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
- Girl: THE BOY SEES DREAMS
OF A WARM FAMILY,
INSIDE A COUPLE
WHO MET IN A STRANGE LAND.
MEANWHILE, THE GIRL STARTS
TO SENSE THE FEELINGS
THAT ARE AWAKENING
INSIDE OF HER.
NEXT EPISODE, "CRACK POT."