- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ I JUST FLY AWAY ♪
♪ I JUST FLY AWAY! ♪
- ( sighs )
THIS IS HORRIBLE.
- Woman: HURRY UP AND GET US
THE NUMBER OF FATALITIES.
- BUT THERE ARE SO MANY BODIES
THAT HAVE BEEN DAMAGED SO BADLY.
- COUNT ONE HEAD, ONE BODY,
TWO ARMS AND TWO LEGS
AS ONE PERSON.  THAT'LL HAVE TO
DO UNDER THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
- COLONEL DEWEY HAS ORDERED
THE CAPITOL SQUADRON
TO TEST LAUNCH THE SECOND
ORANGE-ZERO MISSILE.
WE WILL NOW HEAD
TO THE OBSERVATION POINT
OF THE SECOND MISSILE LANDING.
PLEASE, HURRY.
- Man: THE SO-CALLED
ANTIBODY CORALIAN
SUDDENLY STOPPED MOVING, BUT
IT WASN'T GIVEN A FATAL BLOW.
THE REASONS BEHIND THE STOP
ARE UNKNOWN.
CALCULATING BACK
FROM ITS SIZE AND ACTIVITY AREA,
IT WAS ON THE MOVE
FOR 1,246 SECONDS.
HUH?  1,246 SECONDS?
- Man: THE CONTROL
STICK HAS CHANGED.
STROKES FOR EACH PART WILL NOW
BE DIFFERENT FROM BEFORE.
- EUREKA.
EUREKA, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- RENTON, LOTS OF PEOPLE
DIED AGAIN.
I'M SORRY.  I'M SORRY.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
- PLEASE TELL ME, RENTON,
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
TELL ME WHAT TO DO, PLEASE.
- EUREKA.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
A DISTRESS SIGNAL?
A REFUGEE SHIP FROM FERES.
- YOU MEAN SOME CIVILIANS
ESCAPED?
- WE'LL RENDEZVOUS.  REPLY
WITH A CONFIRMATION SIGNAL.
- RIGHT.
- YOU REALLY DO A GOOD JOB.
- THIS IS THE ONLY TYPE OF WORK
I'VE EVER BEEN ABLE TO DO.
THIS IS PROBABLY THE LAST
THING I'M EVER
GOING TO BE ABLE
TO DO FOR HIM.
- Girl: WOW!
- HUH?
- AXEL, DID YOU REALLY
MAKE THIS BY YOURSELF?
- DON'T YOU GO TOUCHING IT NOW.
THE FILMS HAVEN'T
FINISHED DRYING.
- AMAZING!
- HEY, WAS SOMEONE HERE
UNTIL JUST A FEW MINUTES AGO?
- SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
- SEE, I TOLD YOU.
- WAS SOMEONE SNOOPING
AROUND HERE?
- UH-HUH,
SOME CREEPY LOOKING GUY.
- HE WAS SNEAKING
ALL AROUND HERE.
- THIS ISN'T GOOD.
I THINK MAYBE THEY'RE ON TO US.
HMM?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
IF THEY COME IN HERE BEFORE
THE GEKKO ARRIVES, IT'S OVER.
GIRLS, I WANT YOU TO LEAVE
AND GO STRAIGHT HOME.
- WHAT?
BUT WE ALL JUST GOT HERE.
SO WHAT?  GO HOME AND NEVER
COME NEAR THIS GARAGE AGAIN.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING
THAT WENT ON HERE.
YOU DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING AND YOU
DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING, EITHER.
GOT THAT?
- BUT, AXEL.
- HEY, WE'LL SEE YOU
AGAIN, RIGHT?
IT'S JUST A HUNCH.
BYE, AXEL.
- YEAH.  SEE YOU LATER.
- Man: IT WAS ALL WE COULD DO
TO ESCAPE FROM THE CITY.
I THANK YOU FOR YOUR KINDNESS.
- Holland: WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
- I SAW WHAT LOOKED LIKE
AN ARROW OF LIGHT FALL
IN THE DISTANT SKIES.
- ARROW OF LIGHT?
- THERE WAS A HUGE EXPLOSION,
AND THEN SUDDENLY,
WE HAD A TECTONIC SHIFT
IN THE CITY.
A HUGE, ROUND CLOUD
SUDDENLY POPPED UP
ALONG WITH A TREMENDOUSLY
DENSE STREAM OF TRAPARS.
( sobs ) AND THEN
EVERYTHING WENT CRAZY.
- WAIT A SECOND.
THE CLOUD APPEARED RIGHT AFTER
THE ARROW FELL TO THE GROUND?
- BEFORE WE KNEW IT, THOSE
THINGS WERE ALL OVER THE CITY.
- ANSWER ME!
THOSE THINGS ATTACKED THE CITY
AFTER YOU SAW THE EXPLOSION?
- HOLLAND.
- ( crying )
- SORRY.
- THE ARROW OF LIGHT,
THAT THING AT TRESOR, HOLLAND.
- WE CAN'T PUT IT OFF NOW.
WE NEED TO GET THAT SPEC
TWO BOARD IN RIGHT AWAY.
DEWEY'S GETTING SERIOUS.
HE'S STARTING UP.
- ( chattering )
- ( grunts )
( sighs )
- HERE, I GOT IT.
- HEY, YOU DID REALLY WELL.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME, KID?
- THAT CHILD HAS LOST HIS VOICE.
- HUH?
- BOTH HIS PARENTS WERE KILLED
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HIM,
BY THOSE FILTHY MONSTERS.
- OH, I SEE.
- ( clattering )
- WHAT HAPPENED
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT THERE?
- EUREKA!
EUREKA, STOP.
YOU'RE STILL NOT FEELING WELL.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HELP OUT.
- LET ME DO THIS.
- ( gasps )
- PLEASE, LET ME HELP OUT.
I CAN'T STAND DOING NOTHING.
THANKS A LOT.
- ( whimpering )
- HEY, KID.
- ( screaming )
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
HOW CAN I BE EVER FORGIVEN
FOR WHAT I'VE DONE?
PLEASE, SOMEONE TELL ME.
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- DON'T, EUREKA.  HEY.
- AFTER ALL, I'M A HORRID
MONSTER TO THEM.
- MISS TALHO.
- GO BACK TO THE SHIP, EUREKA,
RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW IT'S HARD FOR YOU,
BUT TRY TO REMEMBER ONE THING.
YOU HAVE ALL OF US
AT YOUR SIDE.
- THE TEST MISSILE LAUNCH
WILL BE IN THREE HOURS.
THE MISSILE'S PRIMARY TARGET
WILL BE GREMIKOWA.
THIS SHIP SHOULD APPROACH
THE KUTE-CLASS TO THE LIMIT
OF THE ABSOLUTE SAFETY ZONE
AND ENTER A STANDBY ORBIT.
THE CLOSE-RANGE OBSERVATIONS
WILL BE HANDLED BY THE END.
- YOU'RE GOING TO
CRUSH ANOTHER CITY?
- COLONEL DEWEY IS CONCERNED
ABOUT THE FUTURE OF THIS PLANET.
UNFORTUNATELY, SACRIFICING
A CITY OR TWO IS UNAVOIDABLE.
CHANGE COURSE TO 003.
DESTINATION: GREMIKOWA!
- THIS ISN'T EXACTLY
AN ATMOSPHERE
WHERE WE CAN TOAST
WITH BEERS IN HAND.
- ( camera shutter clicks )
- I SEE.  I'M SORRY I'VE MADE
SUCH DEMANDING REQUESTS.
I AM TRULY GRATEFUL
FOR THIS, DR. GREG.
- Axel:
GEKKO, DO YOU COPY?
THIS IS AXEL THURSTON
REPORTING FROM BELLFOREST.
I WILL BE ABLE TO DELIVER
THE BOARD.
ACCORDING TO MY CALCULATIONS,
CONTACT WITH THE GEKKO WILL BE--
- OLD MAN, THEY'RE HERE.
- APPARENTLY, THE MILITARY
POLICE HAVE CAUGHT ON.
HE SAID THAT HE'S GOING TO
DELIVER THE BOARD BY PUTTING IT
UP ON THE LEY LINE.
- ON THE LEY LINE?
- WHAT ABOUT HIM?
WILL HE BE ALL RIGHT?
- GRAMPA.
I'M TAKING THIS SHIP TO WHERE WE
CAN TRY TO MAKE CONTACT
WITH THE BOARD.
AND THAT'S IN GREMIKOWA.
- ( feedback whining )
- ( screaming )
- OLD MAN!
- HURRY UP.  AFTER HIM!
- HERE GOES.
- RIGHT.
- ISN'T IT ABOUT TIME
TO CUT THE CABLES?
- ( clicking )
- ( grunting )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
BACK THERE, OLD MAN?
- THE CABLE'S NOT COMING OFF.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
DAMN IT, WHAT DO WE--
THIS IS BAD, OLD MAN.
- WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF ROAD.
- DON'T STOP!  KEEP IT MOVING.
IF YOU PUT THE BRAKES ON,
THE KITE WILL LOSE SPEED.
IF THAT HAPPENS, I WON'T GET
THE BOARD UP TO THE LEY LINE.
- THAT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
- UNTIL VERY RECENTLY, THAT BOY
WAS STILL WETTING HIS BED.
SINCE WHEN HAS HE BEEN
ABLE TO WALK ON HIS OWN
WITHOUT ME HAVING TO
PULL HIM ALONG BY THE HAND?
IT WAS AN INSTANT.
IT REALLY WAS
NOTHING MORE THAN AN INSTANT.
- HEY, HEY, OLD MAN!
- IN TIME,
HE'LL GROW TO BE AN ADULT.
HE DOESN'T NEED ME
TO HELP HIM ALONG WITH THAT.
THIS IS THE LAST TIME I'M GOING
TO MESS IN THAT KID'S AFFAIRS.
MY LAST JOB IS
TO DELIVER THIS BOARD.
AND I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
IT GETS DELIVERED.
- OLD MAN!
- CATCH THIS, RENTON!
- Man: FINAL ADJUSTMENTS
SHOW ALL BLUE LAMPS.
ZERO NUMBER TWO ORANGE, YOU HAVE
THREE SECONDS TO LAUNCH.
TWO, ONE...
- ( gasping )
- FIFTEEN SECONDS SINCE ZERO
NUMBER TWO ORANGE'S LANDING.
SIXTEEN, 17 SECONDS.
- Anemone: I DON'T WANT TO.
MY HEAD HURTS!
I DON'T WANT TO GO.  DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS, DOMINIC.
DO SOMETHING!  OH!
- DAMN YOU!
- IT SEEMED YOU WERE HAVING
QUITE A FEW PROBLEMS
WITH OUR MR. ADVISOR, SIR.
A KUTE-CLASS COULD APPEAR
ANY MOMENT.
HAVE HER REPORT FOR OBSERVATIONS
AT THE CORALIAN IMMEDIATELY.
THAT'S AN ORDER
FROM COLONEL DEWEY.
- ANEMONE.
- ( grunts )
- THE CORAL SIGNALS. THEY'RE
SUDDENLY STARTING TO SURGE.
A KUTE-CLASS HAS APPEARED.
- OF ALL PLACES,
IT HAS TO BE HERE?
HEY, GIDGET, WHERE'S THE BOARD?
- I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO LOCATE IT YET.
- EUREKA.
- I HAVE TO GO TO NIRVASH.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
- EUREKA.
- MY FRIENDS HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THIS AGAIN.
I CAN'T SIT STILL ANYMORE.
- OKAY, THEN.
ALL THE MORE REASON
TO GET THE BOARD.
- LEADER.
- IS IT THE BOARD?
- NO, ARMY SHIP APPROACHING
AT 10:00.
- A WHAT?
- YOU'RE SURE IT'S THE GEKKO?
- WE'RE ON A COLLISION COURSE.
AT PRESENT, OUR PATHS
WILL INTERSECT.
- PLEASE, YOU MUST
AVOID ALL BATTLE.
OUR MISSION IS
TO OBSERVE THE KUTE
AND ANTIBODY CORALIANS.  TELL
THAT TO THE PILOT OF THE END.
- Anemone:
OH, SO THAT SHIP IS HERE.
THAT'S EXCELLENT.
WELCOME, LOOK-ALIKE OF THE END.
I'M GONNA PUSH YOU AROUND.
- OH, NO!  IT'S THAT WEIRD KLF
THAT FOUGHT THE NIRVASH
BACK IN SALISA ORNE.
- WE SHOULD CHANGE COURSE.
- THE LEY LINE HAS A FAST FLOW.
THERE IS ONLY ONE WINDOW
OF OPPORTUNITY TO GET THE BOARD.
IF WE MISS IT, IT'S OVER.
- WE DON'T KNOW FOR SURE WHETHER
THE BOARD WILL GET HERE.
- TARGET IS APPROACHING.
THREE MINUTES TO CONTACT.
- HOLLAND, WHAT?
- Renton: NIRVASH, GOING OUT.
- RENTON!
- THAT'S ALL.  THERE ARE NO
CHANGES TO THE INTERFACE
OTHER THAN THE MODE SHIFTS.
GOT THAT?
- I KNOW THE BOARD IS GONNA
BE THERE.  I'M SURE OF IT.
HOLLAND.
- GIDGET, DO IT.
OPEN UP THE CATAPULT RIGHT NOW.
- RIGHT.
- ALL RIGHT,
IT'S TIME TO GO, EUREKA.
- DON'T BEG.  DO IT YOURSELF
OR ELSE YOU WON'T GET ANYTHING.
I REALLY HOPE YOU KNOW THAT
I BELIEVE IN YOU, GRAMPS.
I BELIEVE IN YOU!
- WHAT?  THAT THING.
COMING WITHOUT A BOARD?
ARE THEY MOCKING ME?
IF YOU WANNA DIE THAT MUCH,
I'LL BE HAPPY TO KILL YOU.
BASCUDE!
- RENTON.
- IT'S GRAMPS!
- WHAT WAS THAT?  STUFF LIKE
THAT IRRITATES ME.
- WHAT WAS THAT JUST NOW?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
DID YOU GET IT?
- NO GOOD.  IT WAS TOO FAST.
THE GUN SIGHT CAMERAS
COULDN'T KEEP UP WITH IT.
- CAN IT BE THAT THE typeZERO
HAS ACTUALLY EVOLVED?
- Renton: AMAZING!
THIS SPEC TWO IS JUST AMAZING.
- LET'S GO, COME ON.
- YEAH.
LET'S GO, TOGETHER.
- A SEVEN SWELL?
- NO, THIS IS MUCH MORE
BRILLIANT THAN THAT.
THIS-- THIS IS THE REAL.
- WHAT IS THAT?  THERE'S NO WAY
I'M EVER GONNA LET MYSELF LOSE
TO SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
DIE!  DIE!  DIE!
DIE AGAIN AND DIE AGAIN!
( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NO.  NO.  NO.  NO.  NO!
- ( crying )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- PLEASE.
HOLD MY HAND.
- THE SIGNALS FOR THE ANTIBODY
CORALIANS ARE STARTING
TO GO AWAY
AND ARE GETTING WEAKER.
- AFTER WE RETRIEVE THE NIRVASH,
TAKE THIS SHIP
TO WHERE THE ZONE EMERGED.
PERHAPS THERE MIGHT
BE A FEW CIVILIANS
WHO MANAGED TO SURVIVE.
- ROGER THAT.
- ( whimpering )
- ANEMONE, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED
OUT THERE.
- Woman:
WE TOLD YOU TO GIVE PRIORITY
TO THE OBSERVATION
OF THE ANTIBODY CORALIANS.
I MUST REPORT THIS INCIDENT
TO THE COLONEL.
- WHAT?  IF WE LEAVE THE GEKKO
ALONE, SOMEDAY IT'LL PROVE
TO BE AN ENORMOUS THREAT
TO US.  NOW WE CAN CRUSH IT.
- WHAT CAN YOU EXPECT A MERE
BUNCH OF PIRATES TO DO NOW?
THE WILL OF OUR GALLANT COLONEL
IS AS BIG AS
THIS PLANET ITSELF.
- ( whimpering )
- HELLO, NIRVASH.
- RENTON.
I SEE HIS INTEGRITY HASN'T
CHANGED ONE BIT.
- WHAT?
A SHIPPING STATEMENT?
WHY ME?
IT'S FROM GRAMPS.
- Axel: GREETINGS.  FIRST
OF ALL, ARE YOU DOING WELL?
THE TOWN YOU WERE BORN IS
WEARING A VEIL OF SNOW
WAITING EAGERLY FOR THE ARRIVAL
OF VIBRANT SPRING.
SINCE YOU LEFT HERE, YOU HAVEN'T
SENT ME A SINGLE LETTER.
IF YOU HAD RETURNED
WITH EVERYTHING UP IN THE AIR,
I WAS CONSIDERING PUNCHING
YOUR LIGHTS OUT.
BUT IF YOU STILL HAVEN'T
FOUND YOUR ANSWERS,
THAT'S FINE AS WELL.
THE CURRENT SITUATION
HAS CREATED A NEED
FOR ME TO GET OUT
OF TOWN AS WELL.
FOR A WHILE, I'LL LOUNGE AROUND
WHERE I CAN STAY OUT OF SIGHT,
BUT SOMEDAY I PROMISE I WILL
RETURN TO BELLFOREST.
I WILL RETURN AND WAIT
AS LONG AS I CAN FOR YOU
TO COME BACK TO THE PLACE
WE CALLED HOME.
OH, AND BRING THAT
NICE YOUNG LADY.
- ( sniffling )
- Man:
A CORALIAN AND A HUMAN.
- IT'S ALMOST LIKE A FAIRY TALE.
- Woman: THE ZERO NUMBER TWO'S
TEST LAUNCH WAS A SUCCESS.
THE ANTIBODY CORALIANS APPEARED
180 KILOMETERS NORTH
OF THE ORANGE IMPACT POINT.
JUST LIKE ZERO ONE, THE TARGET'S
ACTIVITY AREA IS WITHIN
THE RADIUS OF THE KUTE-CLASS
THAT APPEARED WITH IT.
OH, YES, AND THERE SEEMS TO BE
A LIMIT TO ITS ACTIVITY TIME.
- I SEE.
A VERY INTERESTING NUMBER.
1,246 SECONDS--
RECOGNIZE IT?
- YES, IT'S EXACTLY
THE SAME SPAN OF TIME
AS THE SEVEN SWELL EFFECT
TRIGGERED BY typeZERO.
- THE TIME HAS COME.
I WILL REMOVE THE "ZERO" TAG
FROM THE ORANGES.
CONTINUE WITH THE STIMULATIONS,
GATHER UP AS MUCH DATA
ON THE BEHAVIOR
OF ANTIBODY CORALIAN
APPEARANCE POINTS AS YOU CAN.
ONCE WE HAVE THAT, WE CAN MOVE
AGAINST THEIR CENTRAL CORE.
NOW LET'S BEGIN.
Renton and Eureka:
TO BE CONTINUED...
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ WHY, SO WHY... ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: WITH THE DETERMINATION
TO GO AGAINST THE WORLD,
THE MORATORIUM COMES TO AN END.
WHAT DID THE ONES
WAITING FOR THE WAVES
SEE ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE SKY?
NEXT EPISODE--
"PACIFIC STATE."