- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ I JUST FLY AWAY ♪
♪ I JUST FLY AWAY! ♪
- ( PA announcer
speaking indistinctly )
- Man: HEY, I HEARD ANOTHER
CORALIAN APPEARED.
- Man #2:
YEAH, ME, TOO.
- IN THE STATE OF GREMIKOWA,
IF I RECALL.
IT'S THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE PLANET,
SO I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
- ENOUGH.  CAN YOU JUST STOP IT
WITH THE DAMN NOISE ALREADY?
IT'S DISTRACTING.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU'RE JUST SITTING THERE
READING A BOOK FOR FUN.
- THIS IS DIFFERENT.
I'M GATHERING INFORMATION.
- ( music playing )
- OH.
THAT'S STRANGE.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- THIS BOOM BOX'S POWER
IS TURNED OFF.
- ( alarm blaring )
- UNKNOWN TRAPAR RESPONSE!
- HEY, WHAT IS THIS?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- AN UNKNOWN TRAPAR INTERFERENCE
HAS BEEN CONFIRMED.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
WHERE?
- 3:00, DISTANCE, 52.
- Holland: 606, YOU'RE GONNA
ACT AS BACKUP TO 808
AND ENTER
FROM THE 23RD DISTRICT.
MEANWHILE, THE 909 AND NIRVASH
WILL ACT AS A DISTRACTION.
AS SOON AS TALHO GETS NORB'S
LOCATION FROM THE INFORMANT,
WE'LL HEAD STRAIGHT IN
AND GRAB HIM.
- ( techno music playing )
- WE'LL FINISH EVERYTHING BEFORE
THAT OLD MAN GETS ON THE MOVE.
THE SUCCESS OF THIS OPERATION
RIDES ON NOTHING MORE THAN
OUR SKILLS AS ONE COMBINED TEAM.
DON'T BEG FOR THINGS.
DO IT YOURSELF.
OR ELSE YOU WON'T GET
ANYTHING.
WE CAN DO IT.  LET'S GO!
- THAT'S AN SL-1200 MARK II.
IMPOSSIBLE!
THIS IS THE CAPITOL.
- ( air raid sirens wailing )
- I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING YET,
YOU KNOW?
THIS WARNING SIGNAL HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
SOMEONE HAS
BREACHED THE PERIMETER
AND IS TRYING
TO INVADE THE CAPITOL.
- SOMEONE?
ARE THERE ANY
VODARAC RADICALS
WHO WOULD EVEN CONSIDER
THE IDEA
OF DIRECTLY ATTACKING
THIS PLACE?
OTHER THAN YOU, THAT IS?
- YOU KNOW, DEWEY,
I HAVE TO MENTION
THAT I'M NOT A RADICAL.
- I ONLY HAVE ONE LEAD
REGARDING THIS SITUATION.
NONE OTHER THAN THE MAN
TO WHOM YOU ENTRUSTED
THE FATE OF THIS PLANET,
TO WHOM YOU TOLD THE TRUTH.
- LAUNCH THE DEFENSIVE SCREENS.
- MASTER NORD,
ARE YOU FAMILIAR WITH THE WORDS,
"LOVE THY NEIGHBOR"?
- WHAT?
- WORDS WRITTEN
ON THE OLDEST DOCUMENTS
PASSED DOWN BY MANKIND
THROUGH THE AGES.
NOW WHY DO YOU THINK THAT
SUCH A PHRASE WAS WRITTEN
INTO THE OLDEST DOCUMENT
OF MANKIND?
IT IS BECAUSE
WITHOUT THOSE WORDS,
HUMANS HAVE LITTLE CHANCE
OF KEEPING EACH OTHER ALIVE.
HUMANS ARE SUCH
PATHETIC CREATURES,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- WHAT IS YOUR POINT?
- I ONLY THING I EVER WANTED
WAS TO WIN
USING MY OWN WORDS
AS A LIVING HUMAN BEING.
DID YOU KNOW THAT
THE PHRASE THAT WAS CONSIDERED
GOD'S FIRST REVELATION WAS
"IN THE BEGINNING,
THERE WAS THE WORD."
- OH, I SEE.
ARE YOU TRYING TO BECOME
SOMEBODY LIKE RASKOLNIKOV
OR SOMETHING?
- RENTON.
- THEY'RE COMING.
- ( gasps )
- Ken-Goh: CALM DOWN!
MAIN CANNONS LOCK ON.
FIRE!
- RENTON.
I KNOW.
AT LEAST I THINK I KNOW,
BUT I--
- SO DO I.
- ( alarm blaring )
- Holland: WE'VE GOTTEN PAST THE
MAIN DEFENSIVE PERIMETER
SURROUNDING THE CAPITOL.
THE FIRST STAGE
IS NOW COMPLETE.
ALL HANDS PROCEED
TO THE SECOND STAGE.  GOT THAT?
- All: ROGER.
- NIRVASH, WHAT'S WRONG?
- HEY, HOLLAND, WE GOTTA STOP
THIS BATTLE RIGHT HERE.
- IDIOT!  IT'S A LITTLE
BIT LATE IN THE GAME.
- I DON'T THINK THIS IS GOOD.
WE SHOULDN'T BE
FIGHTING THIS WAY.
THIS THIS ISN'T
OUR USUAL FIGHTING STYLE.
- I MADE IT CLEAR
DURING THE BRIEFING.
IF WE TURN BACK NOW, THIS PLANET
WILL LOSE EVERYTHING.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY TIME LEFT.
- BUT, HOLLAND!
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I CAN GO A LITTLE FURTHER.
BUT, RENTON,
PLEASE HOLD MY HAND.
- EUREKA.
- Man: AN EMERGENCY WARNING
HAS BEEN ISSUED.
EVERYONE,
PLEASE EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY
TO THE SHELTER TO WHICH
YOU HAVE BEEN ASSIGNED.
I REPEAT, AN EMERGENCY
WARNING HAS BEEN ISSUED.
EVERYONE,
PLEASE EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY
TO THE SHELTER TO WHICH
YOU HAVE BEEN ASSIGNED.
- ( gasps )
( groans )
- EUREKA!
- THERE WAS A CHILD THERE.
- HUH?
- I'M SO SCARED.
- ( explosion )
- ( gasps )
TRY HARDER, EUREKA.
- I KNOW.  I KNOW.
I'M TRYING,
BUT THE HARDER WE TRY
TO PRESS FORWARD
IN THIS BATTLE,
THE MORE OF THOSE PEOPLE
WE'RE GOING TO ANNIHILATE.
- I KNOW ALL THAT, BUT WE--
- I'M SCARED.
- EUREKA.
THOSE PEOPLE DOWN THERE
ARE SURE TO HAVE LOVED ONES
DEAR TO THEM.
JUST LIKE IF YOU, RENTON,
WERE TO DISAPPEAR
RIGHT BEFORE MY EYES.
IT'S JUST SO HARD FOR ANYONE
TO LOSE A LOVED ONE.
WHEN I THINK ABOUT THAT, I--
- ( screams )
- TALHO, ARE THEY?
- Talho: FIGHTING IS NOT
THE ANSWER FOR EVERYONE.
IF THOSE TWO DECIDED
TO MAKE THAT CHOICE, SO BE IT.
IF BY DOING THIS THEY CAN LOOK
INTO A FUTURE FILLED WITH HOPE,
THEN IT'S ALL--
- ( alarm blaring )
- I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING,
YOU'RE JUST TRUSTING THEM
TO DO THE RIGHT THING.
- OH!  THEY WERE HIT
BY FRIENDLY FIRE.
- CALM DOWN.
IT'S PART OF THEIR PLAN.
WEREN'T YOU LISTENING
AT THE BRIEFING?
- YEAH, BUT I--
- ( crash )
- Ken-Goh: STARBOARD AFT IS HIT.
- I'VE GOT THREE KLF SQUADRONS,
AND THEY'RE HEADED THIS WAY.
- ALL RIGHT, MOONDOGGIE.
EVERYTHING IS RIDING
ON YOUR SKILL AND DETERMINATION
ON HOW BAD YOU WANNA SUCCEED.
- RIGHT, LET'S DO IT!
- ( laughs )
THEY MAKE A GOOD TEAM.
- OH.
HEY!
YOU NEVER TOLD ME.
DID THE COLONEL READ MY REPORT?
- WHAT REPORT?
- THE ONE I GAVE YOU.
THE NEW REPORT CONCERNING
THE TYPE ZERO AND ITS PILOTS.
- WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT, I'M
CONFIDENT THAT HE'LL READ IT.
THAT IS IF IT REALLY WAS
SOMETHING TRULY IMPORTANT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "IF IT WAS
SOMETHING TRULY IMPORTANT?"
DON'T YOU GET IT?
THE TYPE ZERO'S SPECS WENT UP.
WHY CAN'T YOU PEOPLE UNDERSTAND?
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
( grunts )
ANEMONE.
- SO YOU'VE SUBMITTED A REPORT?
- UH--
- I DON'T THINK
THAT YOU WOULD HAVE,
BUT YOU DIDN'T WRITE THAT
THE END LOST, DID YOU?
- ANEMONE, THAT'S REALLY
NOT IMPORTANT HERE.
- OF COURSE IT'S IMPORTANT HERE!
DO YOU THINK HE'LL GIVE ME
ANOTHER CHANCE TO TRY?
I FAILED TWICE ALREADY.
YOU THINK DEWEY WOULD
GIVE ME A THIRD CHANCE?
WHY CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND
SOMETHING SO SIMPLE?
WHY ARE YOU SUCH
A STUPID IDIOT?!
TELL ME, TELL ME.
WHY DID WE LOSE TO SUCH
AN UNFASHIONABLE ENEMY?
- ANEMONE?
- HE'S GONNA KILL US.
I'M SURE HE'S GONNA KILL US
I'M SURE.  I'M POSITIVE.
HE'S SURE TO--
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE WE'LL WIN NEXT TIME.
- SUCH LIGHT-HEARTED WORDS.
- WASN'T IT YOUR PLAN TO MEET UP
WITH SOMEBODY HERE?
- THANKS A LOT.
NOW LET'S BEGIN.
- A MOLE.
ACCORDING TO
HIS CONFESSION,
IT CAN BE ASSUMED THAT
GEKKOSTATE KNOWS WE ARE HERE
AND WILL ATTEMPT TO ATTACK
VERY SHORTLY.
- HE USED TO WORK
IN INTELLIGENCE.
HE'S ONE OF TALHO'S PETS.
THE ENEMY IS NOT
COMING AFTER US.
THEIR TARGET IS THAT OLD MAN.
HOWEVER, EVEN IF THEY ARE ABLE
TO INFILTRATE THIS FAR,
IT DOESN'T NECESSARILY MEAN
THAT THE OLD MAN WILL
BOW DOWN TO HOLLAND.
HE'S DEBATING ON WHETHER OR NOT
TO TURN HIS OWN POWER
INTO A DESTRUCTIVE FORCE
IN ORDER TO SAVE THE PLANET,
OR TO ENTRUST THE GOOD FOR
NOTHING APPRENTICE WITH IT ALL.
LET'S WATCH IT UNTIL THE END.
WHAT CAN THEY ACCOMPLISH NOW?
THEY'VE MISSED THEIR
ONLY CHANCE.
CIRCUMSTANCES HAVE CHANGED.
WE DON'T NEED
THE OLD MAN ANYMORE
NOW THAT WE HAVE
PERFECTED THE ORANGE.
- Gidget: I'VE GOT
A TRANSMISSION FROM MISS TALHO.
SHE SAYS THAT MASTER NORB IS
IN THE TILUA GARDENS.
- RIGHT, GOT IT.
WE'LL HEAD OVER THERE.
- BUT, LEADER, WAIT,
NIRVASH IS MISSING IN ACTION.
- I'M SURE THAT
THEY'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S NO WAY THOSE TWO WOULD
GO DOWN EASILY.
IF THEY'RE GONNA CHICKEN OUT
AT THIS POINT,
IF THEY MAKE A MISTAKE AND DIE
THEN THERE'S NO WAY THAT WE WILL
EVER BE ABLE TO LIVE THROUGH
THE DESTINY THAT AWAITS US.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT WE'LL BE
ABLE TO PUSH TOWARDS THE FUTURE.
- DAMN IT, WE KEEP
HITTING THEM DOWN,
BUT THEN MORE COME OUT.
- WHAT ABOUT NIRVASH?
- I'M TRYING,
BUT THEY'RE NOT RESPONDING.
- TALHO SHOULD BE COMING OUT
THE POWER PLANT ANY MINUTE NOW.
AS SOON AS WE PICK HER UP,
WE CAN HAVE HILDA BREAK AWAY
AND HELP COVER HOLLAND'S REAR.
- ROGER.
- THERE ENOUGH TIME?
- THERE'S JUST GONNA HAVE TO BE.
HE'S THE ONE WHO I ENTRUSTED
THE FUTURE OF THE GEKKO TO.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT HE'D DIE
AT THIS POINT.
- ( screaming )
- ( grunting )
- SORRY FOR THE WAIT, OLD MAN.
- HELLO, HOLLAND.
- Dewey: IT'S ABOUT TIME.
IT'S FAIRLY LATE IN THE GAME
TO COME STROLLING IN.
YOU'RE A DISGRACE
TO THE NOVAK FAMILY.
- BIG BROTHER.
- EUREKA, LISTEN.  "SOMEONE
WILL COME HERE AND SAVE US."
"THE MILITARY
WILL STOP ATTACKING."
WE CAN WISH FOR THINGS LIKE THAT
BUT UNLESS WE DO SOMETHING,
THE FACT THAT THE GUYS
ON THE GEKKO ARE IN TROUBLE
DOESN'T CHANGE.
THINK ABOUT IT, EVEN IF WE WERE
TO STOP FIGHTING NOW,
THE MILITIA WOULD NEVER
STOP THEIR ATTACKS.
- THEN LET'S RUN AWAY.
- EUREKA!
- RENTON, I'M SO SCARED.
WE MIGHT HAVE TO FACE A LIFE
OR DEATH SITUATION AGAIN.
AND NOT JUST THE TWO OF US.
EVERYONE ON THE GEKKO.
MAURICE AND THE OTHER KIDS.
( crying )
BESIDES, I JUST DON'T WANT
TO HARM ANYTHING ANYMORE.
- RENTON.
- IF IT'S THAT TOUGH FOR YOU,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO FIGHT.
IF IT'S REALLY THAT HARD ON YOU,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
I JUST CAN'T STAND SEEING YOU
IN SO MUCH PAIN ALL THE TIME.
BUT STILL, EVEN IF WE
THREW EVERYTHING RIGHT NOW,
I DON'T THINK THIS WAR
WOULD END.
THAT'S WHY I'M GONNA FIGHT.
SO THAT I CAN TRY TO SOMEHOW
STOP THIS AWFUL BATTLE THAT'S
STARTED BETWEEN HUMANS
AND CORALIANS.
I BELIEVE IN MY HEART
THAT WITH YOU
AND THE NIRVASH AT MY SIDE,
I MIGHT BE ABLE TO PUT
AN END TO THIS BATTLE
BEFORE IT DESTROYS EVERYTHING.
- I NEED YOU TO TRUST ME,
EUREKA.
- RENTON.
- LET'S DO SOMETHING THAT
WE BELIEVE IN, ALL RIGHT?
- SURE.
- WHAT'S WRONG, HOLLAND?  WHAT
HAVE YOU COME TO BEG FOR NOW?
UNFORTUNATELY, I HARDLY
HAVE ANYTHING TO GIVE TO YOU
OR YOUR ENTOURAGE.
RELEASE THE OLD MAN.
HE'S FREE TO GO.
- ARE YOU SURE IT'S ALL RIGHT?
- I DON'T CARE.
THE ONE WHO SHOULD COMFORT
MY WRETCHED BROTHER
IS ANOTHER WHO HAS
MISSED HIS TIME.
- ( scoffs )
- DO YOU KNOW WHY THIS
OLD MAN CAME HERE, HOLLAND?
HE FINALLY REALIZED THAT
YOU WOULD NEVER BE ABLE
TO FIND SOMEONE WHO COULD
BECOME EUREKA'S PARTNER
NO MATTER HOW LONG
YOU LOOKED.
THAT'S WHY HE'S GIVEN UP.
GIVEN UP TRYING TO COMMUNICATE
WITH THE SCUB CORALS.
- I'M SORRY.
- JUST GET BEHIND ME.
THERE'S SOMETHING THAT
I WANT TO SHOW YOU.
THE GOODS I PROMISED.
- WHAT?
- Dewey: HOLLAND, YOU WILL NEVER
BE ABLE TO SURPASS ME.
IT STARTED WITH LIFTING.
YOU EVEN ENTERED THE MILITARY
IN ORDER TO FOLLOW ME.
BUT AT ANY POINT IN TIME,
WERE YOU ABLE
TO REACH MY CALIBER?
TO TOP IT OFF, YOU EVEN PICKED
UP THE WOMAN THAT I DUMPED.
SHE'S SO PERFECT FOR YOU.
- ( grunts )
- PLEASE, GET BEHIND ME.
- SAME GOES FOR THAT
SILLY LITTLE MAGAZINE.
YOU TRIED TO TELL THE TRUTH
WITH THAT MAGAZINE OF YOURS,
BUT WHAT DID YOU ACCOMPLISH,
HMM?
ALL YOU DID WAS BLATHER AWAY
IN POINTLESS EDITORIALS,
AND MADE IT AN OVERALL WASTE
OF TIME FOR EVERYONE.
I MEAN, YOU DO REALIZE
THAT THE MASSES
AREN'T INTERESTED
IN THE TRUTH, DON'T YOU?
THE MASSES AREN'T MOVED
BY THE TRUTH.
WHAT YOU NEED IS A LOUD VOICE
AND A NOBLE CAUSE TO CHAMPION.
FURTHERMORE, IF YOU POKE AT WHAT
LITTLE PRIDE THOSE FOOLS HAVE,
I GUARANTEE THEY'LL CHOOSE
A FAKE OVER THE TRUTH
EVERY SINGLE TIME.
AS YOUR OLDER BROTHER,
I'M WARNING YOU.
TRY TO LOOK MORE
AT THE BIG PICTURE.
OTHERWISE,
THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN WIN.
- YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED A BIT.
BUT I AM SLIGHTLY DISAPPOINTED.
BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T MANAGED
TO CATCH UP TO ME AT ALL.
- WHAT WAS THAT?  OH!
- BUT THAT'S--
HE REALLY FOUND THE ONE?
- HEY, YOU GUYS ARE KIND
OF LATE, AREN'T YOU?
WHAT HAVE YOU TWO BEEN DOING?
- I'M SORRY.
WE HAD TO TAKE A SLIGHT DETOUR.
NOW, MR. NORB.
- PLEASE, HURRY!
- NO.
WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT VEHICLE?
- Holland:
DON'T BEG FOR THINGS.
DO IT YOURSELF,
OR ELSE YOU WON'T
GET ANYTHING.
THAT'S WHAT
THE GEKKOSTATE IS ALL ABOUT.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL SHIPS RETREAT.
WE'RE GOING BACK
TO THE GEKKO.
- OH, I SEE.
YOU CHOSE THE POWER PLANT
SO THAT YOU COULD
DO THIS TO IT.
- I REALLY DIDN'T WANT TO
HAVE TO SEE THAT GUY'S FACE.
- ALL SHIPS ARE SECURED.
THE CATAPULT HAS BEEN
SAFELY STILLED.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO!
- ROGER.
- I'M SO GLAD THAT YOU
HELD YOURSELF BACK.
- HELD BACK WHAT, HOLLAND?
- HUH?
WELL, DIDN'T YOU COME TO
THE CAPITOL TO DESTROY THE CITY?
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU WANT TO KILL ME?
IT COULDN'T HAPPEN.
MY AGE IS CATCHING UP.
IS THERE ANY WAY
I CAN GET A SMOKE NOW?
- YOU JUST SAID YOUR AGE IS
CATCHING UP AND YOU WANT THAT?
- EUREKA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YES, I'M FINE.
THANK YOU, RENTON.
NIRVASH IS HAPPY, TOO.
- REALLY, EUREKA?
THAT'S GREAT.
- Norb: SO THIS IS THE ONE.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS ONE IS OUR HOPE.
- Renton: YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ME.
- ( laughs )
- Woman: COLONEL, WE HAVE
ANOTHER UPDATED REPORT.
THE POWER PLANT
WILL REQUIRE AT LEAST 72 HOURS
TO RESUME
NORMAL OPERATION.
ALONG WITH THAT, 30% OF
THE CAPITOL'S MAIN TRANSFORMERS
ARE IN NEED OF--
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
- ( panting ) COLONEL,
THE SAGES WOULD LIKE YOU
TO COME
TO THE VISITATION CHAMBER.
- Renton and Eureka:
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ WHY, SO WHY... ♪
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Woman: THE GIRL FASCINATED
BY THE LAND DISAPPEARED.
IN THE BRIGHT MEMORY
SHOWING IN THE MAN'S EYES,
THE BOY SEES THE TRUTH
OF THE ONE HE HAS DREAMED OF.
NEXT EPISODE-- "FANTASIA."