- ( theme music playing )
- ( rumbling )
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
- ( gunfire )
- ( all grunting )
- ( child crying )
- Voice: HOLLAND?
- STOP IT.
- ( crying echoes )
- SOMEBODY MAKE IT STOP!
I WASN'T-- I DIDN'T--
- ( rifle cocking )
- ( gunfire )
- ( gasps )
- ( moaning )
HEY, GET IT TOGETHER, RENTON.
- ( gasps )
- ( footsteps, banging )
- ( beeps )
- Newscaster: A.M. SOUTHEAST OF
NAGORIN ISLAND IN SOUTH
ARIB AT A DEPTH OF 60,
WE HAVE OBSERVED
AN ALPHA 7530 TECTONIC SHIFT.
I REPEAT, TODAY
AT APPROXIMATELY 8:48 A.M.,
SOUTHEAST OF NAGORIN ISLAND
IN SOUTH ARIB
AT A DEPTH OF 60,
WE HAVE OBSERVED--
- COME ON, HOLLAND.
WHY DO I ALWAYS HAVE TO TELL
YOU TO KEEP THE RADIO DOWN?
HMM?
- DUE TO THIS TECTONIC SHIFT...
- HOLLAND?
- ...PART OF THE LEY LINE...
- ( Hap snoring )
- Holland: HAP!  HAP!
- UGH!  WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHY ARE YOU
IN SUCH A BIG HURRY?
- ( panting )
IT'S HERE!
- ( thinking ) THE STORY THAT
EUREKA TOLD ME ABOUT HER PAST,
THAT IT WAS HOLLAND'S GROUP
THAT TURNED CIUDADES DEL CIELO,
THE CITY WHERE MISS TIPTORY
AND THE OTHERS LIVED,
INTO A PILE OF RUBBLE,
WAS HARD TO HEAR.
OF COURSE
I BELIEVE IN EUREKA.
SO I'M NOT GOING TO SAY
ANYTHING TO HER OR HOLLAND
ABOUT THE THINGS
FROM THEIR PAST THAT HAUNT THEM.
IT'S JUST THAT... ( sighs )
...WHEN I SEE EUREKA IN PAIN
AND SUFFERING LIKE THAT,
I CAN'T HELP BUT WONDER
IF THERE'S REALLY ANYTHING
I CAN DO FOR HER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE REAL TRUTH
IS ABOUT ANYTHING.
NOT ABOUT EUREKA,
NOT ABOUT HOLLAND.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I DON'T REALLY KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE WORLD.
IT'S JUST LIKE
MISS TIPTORY TOLD ME.
I MEAN,
I SUPPOSE I CAN GO ON LIVING
WITHOUT KNOWING ANYTHING.
BUT...
( aloud ) THE REAL TRUTH, HUH?
MMM!
AH!
( grunting )
OH NO.
MISS TALHO'S GONNA KILL ME.
( grunting )
( sighs )
WHAT THE HECK AM I DOING?
HOW LAME.
- HEY, RENTON?
- AH!
I'M NOT HIDING ANYTHING, REALLY!
NO, NOTHING AT ALL.
- I NEED GREEN STEPPEN BAN.
- HUH?
- BOARD WAX!
- UM, OH.
HOLD ON A MINUTE.
I HAVE SOME THAT JUST CAME IN
A FEW DAYS AGO.
- HEY, RENTON?
HAVE YOU FINISHED GETTING
YOUR BOARD READY YET?
- HUH?
- THERE'S A WAVE COMING.
AND IT'S HUGE!
- AH!
- IF WE CALCULATE IT
USING THE SOURCE
OF THE TECTONIC SHIFT
AND THE FLOW OF THE STRATA,
THEN THE BEST WAVES
ARE GONNA BE...
- ( scanning )
...RIGHT HERE.
- Matthieu: SO? HEY, THAT'S DOWN
IN THE SOUTHERN HEMISPHERE.
- THAT'S WAY TOO FAR.
- IF WE STAY ON THE LEY LINE,
WE WON'T MAKE IT IN TIME
FOR THE WAVES' ARRIVAL.
- THAT'S IF WE STAY
ON THE LEY LINE.
- UH, NO WAY.
- WE'RE GONNA DO IT?
- SERIOUSLY?
- WELL, IT HAS BEEN A WHILE.
- AW, FINE.
YOU WANT ME TO DO IT THAT BAD,
I'LL DO IT.
- All: ALL RIGHT!
GREAT!
THIS IS GONNA BE FUN!
- THIS IS GONNA ROCK!
- Stoner:
THEN THERE SHOULD BE NO PROBLEM!
- Hilda: DON'T SLAP ME,
IT HURTS.
- THIS IS GONNA BE SO GREAT.
- IT REALLY HURTS!
- Hap: WELL SAID!
- DON'T HIT ME.
- HMM.
AH!  THEY ALL
JUST THINK OF THEMSELVES.
WHERE'D YOU GO, RENTON?
ARE YOU HERE?
I WANT MY CHANGE.
HE'S AS BAD AS THE OTHERS.
I'M JUST GONNA GET IT MYSELF!
- ( dinging )
- AHHH!
WHA-- WHA-- WHA--
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?!
THIS IS MY--
I FORGOT I HAD THIS THING.
- ( children giggling )
- ( sighs )
IT JUST
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WELL, THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT A BIG WAVE,
BUT IT'S REALLY FAR AWAY.
I MEAN,
BY THE TIME IT GETS HERE,
THERE WILL BE
NOTHING LEFT OF IT.
WHY IS EVERYONE
GETTING SO EXCITED
ABOUT SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
I DON'T GET IT.
- HUH? WELL, BECAUSE--
- ( alarm sounding )
- ( gasps )
- TRAJECTORY FLIGHT?
- MAURICE,
GET IN THE COPILOT SEAT.
- OKAY.
- RENTON, HURRY UP.
YOU GET IN TOO.
- HUH? WHAT FOR?
- THE GEKKO IS GOING TO FLY
OUTSIDE THE ATMOSPHERE.
- FLY OUTSIDE THE ATMOSPHERE?
- WOZ, WHEN YOU'VE GOT
THE COURSE CALCULATED,
SEND IT HERE.
- ALREADY SENT.
- WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME
BEFORE THE WINDOW.
WE'RE GOING STRAIGHT TO
MAXIMUM LOAD. EVERYBODY READY?
- I HAVEN'T BEEN THIS EXCITED
IN A LONG TIME.
- Talho: WE START 35 SECONDS...
- ...AFTER THE TRAPAR
SITE SHUTS DOWN.
- ( tools rustling )
- Eureka: HERE, TAKE THIS.
- HUH?
- IT'S GOING TO BE
REALLY INTENSE TODAY.
- HUH?
( grunts )
- Hap: CONFIRMING THAT ALL
AIRLOCKS ARE SECURED AND READY.
CONFIRMATION COMPLETE.
CURRENTLY WE ARE CRUISING
WILL ALL CONTROL SYSTEMS
OPERATING ON MANUAL.
- Man: RELEASE VALVE,
CLOSURE CONFIRMED.
- PORTSIDE BOOSTER, NO CHANGE
IN RATE OF PRESSURE INCREASE.
STARBOARD SIDE BOOSTER,
ALSO SHOWING NO CHANGE
IN RATE OF PRESSURE INCREASE.
- BOOSTER
INTERNAL PRESSURE STABLE.
ALL AUXILIARY SYSTEMS ARE GO.
RELEASING
ALL PRESSURE LOCKS NOW.
COMMENCING FINAL COUNTDOWN.
- Talho: CONFIRMED NORMAL
OPERATION OF ALL SYSTEMS.
MOVING INTO FINAL POSITION.
FINAL CHECK OF
PLOTTED COURSE COMPLETE.
RELEASING BOOSTER LOCKS.
LAUNCHING NOW!
- HIGHER THAN THE SUN!
- ( all grunting )
- ( thinking ) ROCKET?
BUT THEY'RE ALWAYS SAYING
THAT WE REALLY SHOULDN'T USE
ANY KIND OF JET PROPULSION
BECAUSE OF THE WAY
IT POLLUTES THE AIR!
- ( all moaning )
- MAMA, THIS BELT IS TIGHT.
- ISN'T IT OKAY NOW?
- YES, IT'S OKAY.
- ( giggling )
- WOW.
- THAT WAS CLOSE.
I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO THROW UP AGAIN.
- RENTON, COME ON.
- WHAT?
- YOU CAN SEE THE PLANET
REALLY CLEARLY.
- PLANET?
- Children: WOW!
- AMAZING.
THE PLANET--
IT REALLY IS ROUND.
- All: WOW!
- Stoner: THE GREAT WALL.
- SO THIS IS THE THING
THAT MISS TIPTORY
WAS TELLING ME ABOUT.
HMM?
( thinking ) IF ONLY
I'D BEEN ABLE TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT IT WAS THAT EUREKA'S EYES
WERE SAYING AT THAT VERY MOMENT,
MAYBE--JUST MAYBE WE WOULD
HAVE BEEN ABLE TO MAKE IT
THROUGH IT ALL WITHOUT
HAVING IT END THE WAY IT DID.
YOU KNOW, SIS?
BUT-- BUT FOR NOW,
JUST LET ME SAY ONE THING.
HURRAY FOR ZERO GRAVITY.
- Dominic:
AND THAT IS THE SITUATION
LEADING UP
TO THE CURRENT STATUS
OF OPERATION SORRA 107
IN CIUDADES DEL CIELO.
SEVEN MINUTES FROM ENEMY
CONTACT, THE SQUADRON WITHDRAW.
BECAUSE THEY USED AN L.F.O.
INSTEAD OF WEAPONS
JUST AS R.P.G.s,
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO THINK
THAT THE ATTACK WAS INITIATED
BY A REBEL FORCE
LIKE THE VODARAC.
I BELIEVE
THAT SOME OTHER FORCE
MUST HAVE INTERVENED THERE.
- ENOUGH WITH THE REPORT.
- SIR?
- I WANT YOU TO TELL ME
WHAT YOU THINK, DOMINIC.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT OTHER FORCE IS?
- SIR!  ANALYZING ALL THE DATA
WE'VE COLLECTED,
IT IS HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT A GROUP OF CIVILIANS
WOULD USE L.F.O.s IN COMBAT
AS WE SAW HERE.
IN PARTICULAR, THE ACCURACY
OF THE ATTACKS
WERE VERY SIMILAR TO THOSE
OF THE OLD S.O.F.
FIRST MOBILE SQUADRON.
IN ADDITION,
THE FACT THAT EYEWITNESS REPORTS
ALSO MENTION A WHITE L.F.O.
LEADS ME TO CONCLUDE
THAT THE GEKKOSTATE
WERE PROBABLY THE ONES
INVOLVED IN THIS ATTACK.
- I SEE.
EVEN THOUGH THEY'RE NOW
MAKING BLATANT ATTACKS
AGAINST MILITARY FORCES,
THERE ARE NO SQUADRONS
CAPABLE OF
DEALING WITH THEM AT PRESENT.
I WAS GOING TO WAIT
UNTIL MY SQUADRON
WAS OFFICIALLY COMMISSIONED,
BUT HOW
IS THAT OTHER THING GOING?
- UH... YES.
RIGHT AWAY!
YOU, GUARD,
BRING THE BLACK ONE OUT FRONT!
- HOW FAR DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN STRETCH IT?
THE GEKKO CUP COMPETITION
CHEESE-STRETCHING CHAMPIONSHIP!
- ALL RIGHT! WHOO!
OH YEAH!
- AND NOW MOONDOGGIE
WOULD LIKE TO SAY A FEW WORDS!
- SO WHERE ARE WE?
- IT'S THE MONAKE BASE.
- MONAKE?
- Hilda: AN AIR FORCE BASE
THAT WAS ABANDONED
AFTER A TECTONIC SHIFT
HIT IT SIX MONTHS AGO--
THE LARGEST MILITARY TOWER
IN THE SOUTHERN HEMISPHERE.
BUT NOW
IT'S JUST AN EMPTY RUIN.
- Matthieu: I SEE.
AND WHY EXACTLY
ARE WE IN A PLACE LIKE THAT?
- WHO KNOWS?
ASK TALHO.
- MMM.
- ( grumbling )
- OH, WELL, MAYBE SHE'S
LOST HER TOUCH OR SOMETHING.
- ( groans )
- ( all snoring )
- HMM.
- Eureka: HEY!
- HUH?
- AREN'T YOU GOING?
EVERYONE ELSE IS.
YOU'RE FINISHED REPAIRING
YOUR BOARD, AREN'T YOU?
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- I THINK I'M GOING
TO BE STAYING HERE.
I WANT TO STAY HERE.
- OKAY.
THEN I WILL TOO.
- WHAT?
- IT'S JUST,
YOU SEE, TODAY IS...
WELL, HURRAY FOR ZERO GRAVITY.
- OH.
THAT'S NICE, ISN'T IT?
( straining )
- Renton: I'M SORRY.
DID I PUT THAT ON TOO TIGHT?
HERE, THIS ONE TOO.
AH!
- WHAT'LL I DO?
MY VOICE, IT ISN'T REACHING.
- JEEZ.
THEY DON'T HAVE TO FLAUNT IT
LIKE THAT.
- Talho: NO KIDDING.
AND DOING IT HERE
OF ALL PLACES, RIGHT?
- Moondoggie and Gidget:
ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
- Gidget: LOOK OVER THERE!
- A WAVE!
- Both: ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
- LOOK OVER THERE.
- A WAVE!
- Both: PAPER, ROCK, SCISSORS!
- Stoner: THE WAVE ISN'T COMING,
IS IT?
- Hilda: NEITHER IS HOLLAND.
- TAKE ME WITH YOU.
TAKE ME AWAY WITH YOU.
PLEASE, HOLLAND.
YOU'VE CHANGED.
- Renton: I'M SURE
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
I MEAN, YOU'VE REALLY
HAD TO DO AN AWFUL LOT
OF DIFFICULT MANEUVERS,
ALL IN JUST THE SHORT TIME
SINCE WE ALL TOOK OFF
FROM BELLFOREST.
OR IT COULD JUST BE
SOME KIND OF WARP
IN THE PHYSICAL STRUCTURE
OF THE SHIP.
HEY, MAYBE IT'S SOMETHING
IN THE AMITA DRIVE.
HEY, EUREKA?
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T THINK
I CAN HOLD MYSELF BACK
ANYMORE.
- MMM?
- Man: JUST SPILL IT ALREADY.
- ( gasps )
- RENTON?
- YOU KNOW THINGS WOULD BE
A WHOLE LOT EASIER
IF YOU JUST SPILL IT, RENTON.
- RENTON, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M FINE.  IT'S NOTHING.
AFTER ALL, THIS IS
ALL FOR YOU, EUREKA.
- HUH?
- YOU SEE, IT'S NO BIG DEAL
IF IT'S FOR YOU.
I MEAN,
BECAUSE OF HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
I-- I--
- YOU'LL FEEL MUCH BETTER
IF YOU JUST SPILL IT ALL OUT.
- IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SPILL OUT?
- NO, I CAN'T SPILL IT.
I CAN'T SPILL IT OUT
AFTER ALL.
- YOU'VE CHANGED, HOLLAND.
WHY WON'T YOU LOOK AT ME?
- YOU'RE BUGGING ME.
- YOU'RE RUNNING AWAY?!
- YEAH.
I WANT TO RUN AWAY.
AS IF I ACTUALLY COULD!
I WANT TO RUN AWAY
TO THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE PLANET OR ANYWHERE ELSE.
I WANT TO FORGET
THAT DAY, THAT PLACE,
AND EVERYTHING ELSE-- ALL OF IT.
BUT I CAN'T.
IT ALL KEEPS CHASING AFTER ME.
I REALLY JUST WANT
TO RUN AWAY.
- EVEN FROM ME, HOLLAND?
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
I'M BEGGING YOU.
CAN'T YOU JUST HELP ME
FORGET ABOUT IT?
- THAT'S IT.
THE WAVE NEVER CAME.
- GUESS NOT.
- AT LEAST THE PIZZA WAS GOOD.
- YEAH, WELL, NEXT TIME
TRY AND LEAVE SOME FOR US, OKAY?
- YOU LANDED US HERE
ON PURPOSE, DIDN'T YOU?
- WELL, IT DIDN'T MATTER
TO YOU ANYWAY.
THAT WAVE, I MEAN.
THERE'S NO WAY WE'LL EVER
FORGET ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW.
IT REALLY WOULDN'T BE RIGHT
TO FORGET.
AND I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF FORGETTING.
THAT'S WHY YOU BROUGHT HIM
ONBOARD THE GEKKO, ISN'T IT?
- BROTHER.
YOU REALLY KNOW HOW TO HIT A GUY
WHERE IT HURTS.
- YOUR WEAK SPOTS
ARE JUST TOO EASY TO FIND.
- ( Renton thinking ) THERE ARE
STILL A LOT OF THINGS THAT
I DON'T REALLY UNDERSTAND,
ABOUT HOW HOLLAND FEELS,
ABOUT THE REASON
MISS TALHO LOOKS AT HOLLAND
THE WAY SHE DOES,
AND ABOUT EUREKA'S FEELINGS.
- ( bird chirping )
- HMM?
- ( laughs )
- LOOK, IT'S A BIRD!
- A BIRD, A BIRD!
- OH.
- ( thinking ) THERE ARE ALL
THESE THINGS I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
BUT THE FACT THAT I'M
STANDING HERE RIGHT NOW,
THE FACT THAT I'M LOOKING
OUT AT THE WORLD RIGHT NOW,
I FELT CERTAIN
THAT WAS THE TRUTH.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
I COULDN'T HELP THINKING,
WHAT AM I HERE FOR ANYWAY?
WHY WAS I BORN
ON THIS PARTICULAR PLANET?
AND WHAT EXACTLY IS IT
THAT I'M LIVING FOR?
- PLAYING HIDE AND SEEK AGAIN?
THE LIEUTENANT COLONEL
IS COMING.  HUH?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING TO SEE THE
LIEUTENANT COLONEL FOR SO LONG.
COME ON,
STOP PLAYING HIDE AND SEEK NOW.
- NO!
- UGH!
OH!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- IT-- IT KEEPS SPILLING OUT
AND WON'T STOP.
- IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME,
HASN'T IT?
I'M GLAD TO SEE
YOU'RE DOING SO WELL.
I HOPE IT HASN'T BEEN TOO HARD,
MY SWEET LITTLE ANEMONE.
- ( gasps )
- NOW BE A GOOD GIRL.
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN THREE YEARS.
WON'T YOU SHOW ME THAT
PRETTY LITTLE FACE OF YOURS?
- SURE!  OKAY.
WELCOME BACK,
LIEUTENANT COLONEL DEWEY!
- Renton: TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator: THE GEKKO APPROACHES
AN UNKNOWN PHENOMENON
CALLED A CORALIAN.
THE BOY UNKNOWINGLY HEADS OUT
AND IS ASSAULTED
BY A BLACK K.L.F.
AMIDST THE WHITE WHIRLWINDS.
NEXT EPISODE,
"INTO THE NATURE."