- ( theme music playing )
- Grandfather: LOOK AT THIS.
IT HASN'T EVEN BEEN FIVE YEARS,
YET WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO STILL BOTHER
TO COME ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
TO VISIT HIS GRAVE.
I DON'T KNOW
IF HE'S A HERO
OR THE GRAND SPIRIT
OF OUR SOCIETY,
BUT THE USED HIM
AS MUCH AS THEY COULD,
AND THEN THEY
SIMPLY THREW HIM OUT.
THIS IS WHERE THOSE
WHO FOLLOW THEIR DREAMS END UP.
I CERTAINLY
DIDN'T RAISE YOUR FATHER
TO MAKE HIM
INTO SOMEONE LIKE THAT.
AND YET HERE HE IS,
LONG DEAD AND GONE.
HE BROUGHT SO MUCH MISFORTUNE
TO HIS PARENTS.
IT'S FAR BETTER
NOT TO DREAM AT ALL
THAN TO WORK YOURSELF
INTO THE GRAVE
FOR THE SAKE OF PEOPLE
WHO WON'T EVEN HELP THEMSELVES.
- Diane: OUR DAD--
- HUH?
- WHEN HE LEFT OUR HOUSE
FOR THE VERY LAST TIME,
HE SAID TO ME,
"DON'T BEG FOR THINGS.
DO IT YOURSELF
OR ELSE
YOU WON'T GET ANYTHING."
I KNOW WHAT GRANDPA SAYS,
BUT I STILL BELIEVE
IN THOSE WORDS.
SOMEDAY, YOU'LL UNDERSTAND
WHAT DAD MEANT.
- "DON'T BEG FOR THINGS.
DO IT YOURSELF
OR ELSE
YOU WON'T GET ANYTHING.
DON'T BEG FOR THINGS.
DO IT YOURSELF
OR ELSE
YOU WON'T GET ANYTHING.
DON'T BEG FOR THINGS.
DO IT YOURSELF
OR ELSE
YOU WON'T GET ANYTHING."
I CAN FLY!
LOOK AT THE SKY FISH.
- ( grunting )
THIS ISN'T GONNA WORK!
THE TRAPAR'S WAY TOO THIN HERE.
I CAN'T KEEP UP WITH THE SPEED
OF THE LONGBOARDS.
- DAMN!
MATTHIEU, COVER ME!
I'M JUST GONNA
HAVE TO BREAK THROUGH!
- ( beeping )
- Matthieu: HOLD IT!
YOU'RE NOT THINKING
OF USING THE C.F.S., ARE YOU?
- THERE'S NO WAY I'M GONNA
LOSE HER IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
- WAIT A MINUTE, LEADER!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS!
WHAT?
WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY?
- HMM?  WHAT'S WRONG?
( gasps )
( thinking )
THAT KID.
AND LOOK AT THE SKY FISH.
HMM!  VERY INTERESTING.
- ( thinking ) I GET IT.
I GET IT NOW, SIS.
YOU CAN'T JUST WAIT.
YOU CAN'T BEG FOR IT.
SO NOW
I'M GONNA DO IT ON MY OWN.
( gasps )
- HE JUST DID
A CUTBACK DROP TURN.
- WICKED!
HE TOTALLY NAILED IT.
- ( gunfire )
- ( grunting )
CAN'T SHAKE 'EM.
I NEED TO LOSE THEM SOMEHOW.
I HAVE TO TRY AND GET BACK
TO HOLLAND RIGHT AWAY.
- AHH!
- THAT BOY!
- AHHH!
- OH NO!
NIRVASH, HURRY!
- AHHH!
- OH, ARE YOU--
- I DID IT.
I ACTUALLY DID IT.
I WAS ACTUALLY ABLE TO PULL OFF
A FULL-SPEED CUTBACK DROP TURN.
- UH...
- IT WAS THANKS TO YOU.
I WAS ABLE TO DO IT
BECAUSE OF YOU!
YOU ARE SO AMAZING.
I THINK
THAT I'M IN LOVE WITH YOU!
- WHAT?
- YOU SEE,
I DID IT BECAUSE OF YOU.
AND I CAN'T DO IT
WITHOUT YOU.
I GUESS THAT
I'M TOTALLY IN LOVE WITH YOU!
- UH, LOVE?
- YEAH.
SO NOW I'M GONNA PROTECT YOU
MYSELF.
AND I'M NOT ONLY
GONNA PROTECT YOU,
BUT THIS MACHINE TOO,
WITH THIS AMITA DRIVE.
- THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE?
- MY GRANDFATHER
EXPLAINED IT TO ME.
WITH THIS, WE CAN OPEN
THE SATORI PROGRAM.
AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS,
THIS L.F.O. NIRVASH typeZERO
WILL TRULY AWAKEN!
SO HERE IT GOES.
AMITA DRIVE,
SET ON!
HUH?  WHAT THE--
WHAT THE HECK IS THIS?
IT'S EUREKA.
- ( sighs )
- WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
AHHHH!
- OH, CRAP!
- DAMN IT!
( grunting )
OH NO!
WHY CAN'T I MOVE THE CONTROLS?
HOW COME?
WHAT DO I DO?
- ( alarm sounding )
- THOSE ARE MISSILES!
WAIT, WHY WON'T THIS MOVE?
NO WAY THIS IS HAPPENING!
WHY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NO!  WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
IS THIS HOW MY LIFE
IS GONNA END?  NO WAY.
AT 14, IT'S ALL OVER?
WAIT!  WAIT A MINUTE!
AHHH!
- Matthieu: FORGET IT.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT HERE.
EVERYWHERE I LOOK,
THERE'S JUST PILLARS OF SALT.
I'VE HEARD RUMORS ABOUT IT,
BUT WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE LIKE THIS?!
- HEY, STONER!
ANY IDEA
WHERE OUR FEARLESS LEADER IS?
- OVER THERE.
OH!
WITH OUR PRINCESS.
- HOLLAND.
- YOU OKAY?
- MMM, YES, I'M FINE.
AND THE OTHERS?
- HMM?
OH, YEAH,
EVERYBODY'S JUST FINE.
BUT LOOK AT ALL THIS.
THAT WAS SOME TREMENDOUS POWER.
I DIDN'T THINK THAT THE SATORI
PROGRAM INSIDE THE AMITA DRIVE
WOULD BE ABLE TO
UNLEASH YOUR POWERS--
OR RATHER, THE NIRVASH'S
POWERS-- TO THIS EXTENT.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- WHAT?
- NIRVASH IS SAYING THAT IT
WAS NEITHER THE AMITA DRIVE
NOR THE SATORI PROGRAM
THAT WAS RESPONSIBLE
FOR UNLEASHING
ALL THIS INCREDIBLE POWER.
IT'S SAYING THAT THE TRUE SOURCE
OF THIS POWER
WAS THIS BOY'S STRENGTH.
- OLD MAN!
HEY, OLD MAN!  RENTON!
OH NO.
( sobbing )
POOR OLD GUY!
- Grandfather: HEY, DIGGER.
- EEK!
- SORRY TO BOTHER YOU,
BUT CAN I GET A LIGHT HERE?
IT SEEMS THIS THING GOT BUSTED
IN ALL THE EXCITEMENT.
- ( laughs )
OLD MAN.
- UH, HUH?
WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT'S THAT L.F.O. DOING?
- RENTON!
RENTON!
- HUH?
- ( grunting )
WHERE IS RENTON?!
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
IS HE ALL RIGHT?
- Dominic: ANY FURTHER COMBAT
IS USELESS.
WE SHOULD RETURN TO BASE
IMMEDIATELY.
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
I LOST TWO K.L.F. SQUADRONS!
I CAN'T POSSIBLY
RETURN EMPTY-HANDED.
- BUT SIR, NOW THAT
WE'VE CONFIRMED THE
SEVEN SWELL EFFECT, WE CAN'T
FIGHT WITH WHAT WE HAVE HERE.
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
IN CASE YOU'VE FORGOTTEN,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE A MERE
OBSERVER ABOARD THIS SHIP.
I THINK INFORMATION OFFICERS
SHOULD ACT
LIKE INFORMATION OFFICERS.
- FINE THEN.
I WILL EXERCISE MY RIGHTS
AS AN INFORMATION OFFICER.
- HMM?
- IN ACCORDANCE
WITH ARTICLE 56 OF MILITARY LAW,
I HEREBY TAKE COMMAND
OF THE SHIP'S HIGH-SPEED CRAFT.
- Man: I THINK
I COULD BUY TIME WITH THIS,
BUT IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE THE
GUYS IN THE MILITARY FIND OUT.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN TO MAKE
SURE YOU AND RENTON STAY HIDDEN,
SO HURRY UP AND GET READY
SO YOU CAN GET OUT OF HERE.
- SORRY FOR THE TROUBLE.
- OKAY, I'M GONNA
GO ON AHEAD.
- ( grandfather laughing )
JEEZ.
HE'S SLEEPING LIKE HE
HASN'T GOT A CARE IN THE WORLD.
- Eureka:
WHY DOES HE LOOK SO HAPPY?
- WHAT?
- I THINK WHAT HE DID WAS
VERY RECKLESS AND FOOLHARDY.
- THAT MAY BE SO.
BUT THEN
WHO IS GOING TO COMPLIMENT HIM
FOR WHAT HE'S ATTEMPTED TO DO
IF NOT FOR ME?
IT MAY HAVE BEEN RECKLESS,
ACCORDING TO COMMON SENSE,
BUT I'LL PRAISE HIM
FOR WHAT HE DID
BECAUSE, AFTER ALL,
HE IS MY FAMILY.
- FAMILY?
- YOU'LL UNDERSTAND
WHEN YOU HAVE
CHILDREN OF
YOUR OWN, YOUNG LADY.
- BUT, SIR, I'M--
- Both: HMM?
- I'M SORRY
I HAVEN'T KEPT IN TOUCH.
I HONESTLY NEVER THOUGHT
THAT I WOULD
EVER SEE YOU AGAIN.
- WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING HERE?
WELL, HOLLAND?
- Grandfather: SO HOW LONG HAVE
YOU BEEN LOITERING AROUND HERE?
SINCE YESTERDAY, I TAKE IT?
AND WHERE IS THAT TERMINUS
OF YOURS?
- THE 909 IS TOO EASY TO SPOT.
THAT'S WHY I CAME HERE
ON MY BOARD.
- GOD DAMN IT!
THAT'S HOW YOU ALWAYS MANAGE
TO MAKE MY LIFE
INTO ONE BIG MESS.
YOU BRING ME
NOTHING BUT TROUBLE.
- ONE THING--
PLEASE LET ME
SAY JUST ONE THING.
- HMM?
- THANKS A LOT.
- WELL, I HAVE A GOOD IDEA
AS TO WHY YOU ARRIVED HERE
WITH A NIRVASH typeZERO,
ESPECIALLY
SINCE YOU PROMISED
THAT YOU'D NEVER
SHOW YOUR FACE HERE AGAIN.
YOU MADE YOUR DECISION,
DIDN'T YOU?
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE, RIGHT?
NOW THAT ALL THIS
HAS HAPPENED,
YOU HAVE TO TAKE SOME SORT
OF RESPONSIBILITY,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS
TO US.
BUT EVEN SO,
I AT LEAST WANTED RENTON
TO HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY
TO LIVE
A NORMAL HAPPY LIFE.
- A NORMAL HAPPY LIFE, HUH?
ARE YOU SAYING THAT BOY
WANTS A SO-CALLED NORMAL LIFE?
- SOMEDAY HE'LL REALIZE
WHICH OF US IS RIGHT.
- THEN WHY DID YOU HAVE HIM
DELIVER THE AMITA DRIVE?
WHY DID YOU MAKE HIM
GO THROUGH WITH THE DELIVERY,
EVEN THOUGH IT MEANT HE HAD
TO DO SOMETHING DANGEROUS?
YOU DON'T BELIEVE ANY OF
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING, DO YOU?
NO, YOU'VE JUST
BEEN FOOLING YOURSELF
AS TO WHAT
YOU REALLY BELIEVE.
- NO!
I'M TELLING YOU
WHAT I REALLY THINK!
WHAT COULD A VAGABOND LIKE YOU
POSSIBLY KNOW ABOUT ANY OF IT?
- THEN WHY DID YOU HOLD ON TO IT
AS IF YOUR LIFE DEPENDED ON IT?
- BECAUSE, YOU IDIOT,
IT WAS MY SON WHO BUILT IT!
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
YOU'RE NOT QUALIFIED TO HAVE IT.
THE ONLY ONE THAT SHOULD
HAVE IT, OTHER THAN MYSELF,
IS RENTON!
UNDERSTAND, I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF FORGIVING YOU!
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
AT THE MOMENT,
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE AVAILABLE
THAT I CAN
TRUST THE DAMN THING TO.
( growling )
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
PLEASE GO HOME.
- I'M VERY SORRY.
- Renton: I DON'T GET IT.
I JUST DON'T GET IT.
I DON'T GET IT--
WHY DAD CREATED SUCH A THING
IN THE FIRST PLACE
AND WHY GRANDPA KEPT IT HIDDEN
ALL THIS TIME
AND WHY ALL OF THIS HAPPENED.
I-- I--
WHAT SHOULD I BE DOING?
- Holland: THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU HAVE TO DECIDE.
WHAT IT IS
YOU BELIEVE IN
AND WHAT YOU DECIDE TO DO
WITH THAT BELIEF
IS ALL
YOUR OWN RESPONSIBILITY.
IT'S UP TO YOU WHETHER TO
RIDE THE WAVES OR LET THEM DIE.
THAT IS THE MOTTO THAT ALL
LIFTERS LIVE BY, ISN'T IT?
- IT'S-- IT'S REALLY HIM.
- Woman:
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS, SIR?
- Jurgens: ABOUT SECOND
LIEUTENANT DOMINIC LEAVING?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT SEEMS THAT THE LIEUTENANT
NO LONGER WANTS TO MEDDLE
WITH THE GEKKOSTATE.
SO I'LL LET HIM GO
SINCE HE OPENED
THE INFORMATION DATABASE TO US.
- SIR, DATA VERIFIED.
- HOW IS IT?
- THERE'S A SHIP
AT THE BELLFOREST AIRPORT
THAT'S NOT ON ANY
OF THE CORPORATION FLEET LISTS.
- WHAT?  BELLFOREST?
THAT'S AWFULLY CLOSE.
CONTACT THE STATE ARMY.
ISSUE A WARNING
TO ALL SURROUNDING AREAS.
- SIR!
- LISTEN UP-- WE NEED TO GET
TO BELLFOREST AIRPORT
AS FAST AS POSSIBLE.
EVEN IF THE AVIATION CORPORATION
DOESN'T BUDGE,
I'LL JUST FORCE A LANDING.
PREPARE THE
MON-SOONO FOR LAUNCH!
- YOU KNOW ALREADY. YOU HAVE
YOUR ANSWER, DON'T YOU?
- ( gasps )
- YOU BELIEVED IN THE WAVES.
IF YOU DIDN'T,
THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD HAVE
PULLED OFF A CUTBACK DROP TURN.
AND THAT MEANS
YOU BELIEVE IN THE WORLD.
AND SO THE WORLD
KINDLY ANSWERED YOUR BELIEF.
QUITTING RIGHT NOW
IS CERTAINLY AN OPTION,
AND IT MAY ALSO BE
THE BEST DECISION.
BUT MY TEACHER ONCE GAVE ME
SOME VERY GOOD ADVICE--
"DON'T BEG FOR THINGS.
DO IT YOURSELF,
OR ELSE
YOU WON'T GET ANYTHING."
- WAIT!  BUT THAT'S--
- LISTEN, KID-- WHAT IS IT
THAT YOU REALLY BELIEVE IN?
WHAT DID YOU BELIEVE IN WHEN
YOU WERE INSIDE THE NIRVASH?
- WELL, I...
DAMN IT! ( grunting )
OH NO,
WHY CAN'T I MOVE THE CONTROLS?
HOW COME?!  WHAT DO I DO?
- ( alarm sounding )
- THOSE ARE MISSILES!
WAIT, WHY WON'T THIS MOVE?
NO WAY THIS IS HAPPENING!
WHY?  WHAT'S GOING ON?
NO!  WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
IS THIS HOW MY LIFE
IS GONNA END?
NO WAY!
AT 14, IT'S ALL OVER?
WAIT! WAIT A MINUTE!
ARGH!
- ( alarm sounding )
- Eureka: IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN BELIEVE IN ME.
- Renton: THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME.
I SAW IT BACK THEN TOO.
I'M SURE OF IT.
THE WORD "EUREKA"
WAS ON THE COMPAC DRIVE
AS I LOOKED AT IT
OVER MY SISTER'S SHOULDER.
I DON'T GET IT.
I DON'T GET IT, BUT--
BUT NOW I THINK
I KIND OF UNDERSTAND
WHAT MY SISTER REALLY WANTED
TO TELL ME BACK THEN
AND WHAT I SHOULD
REALLY BELIEVE IN RIGHT NOW.
- typeZERO HAS BAILED OUT!
- IT WAS SHOT DOWN?
- DID WE GET IT?!
- NO WAY.
- Holland: MATTHIEU, PULL BACK!
-WHY SHOULD I?
-JUST GET THE HELL OUT OF THERE!
IT'S THAT KID!
THAT LITTLE KID WAS SOMEHOW
ABLE TO DELIVER THE AMITA DRIVE
TO THE NIRVASH!
IT'S COMING.
THE SEVEN SWELL!
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- UNKNOWN PARTICLES
ARE APPEARING
FROM THE POINT OF IMPACT.
TRAPAR AREA
IS INCREASING IN RANGE.
- THEN THIS IS--
IMPOSSIBLE.
THEN THIS IS
WHAT THEY CALL
THE SEVEN SWELL EFFECT!
- ( all gasping )
- Grandfather: TO LEAVE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS BEHIND
THAT'S CAPABLE
OF CAUSING SUCH AN EVENT,
AND THEN GETTING YOUR SON
INVOLVED IN THIS AS WELL,
YOU BRING GREAT MISFORTUNE
TO YOUR PARENTS.
THIS IS A LIGHT
THAT DESTROYS US
AND THAT GUIDES US ALL
TO DEATH.
HOWEVER, IT IS SO BEAUTIFUL.
- Man: ELECTROMAGNETIC
RADIATION INCREASING!
THE TRAPAR FIELD
IS REVERSING POLARITY.
- OH NO! YOU GOTTA ORDER THE
MON-SOONO TO RETREAT AT ONCE.
IT'S IN DANGER!
- AMAZING.
- LIKE A GOD OF DESTRUCTION.
- Holland: HEY, DIANE,
THIS IS THE RIGHT THING TO DO,
ISN'T IT? IT REALLY IS.
RIGHT?
Renton:
I DON'T GET IT.  I DON'T GET IT.
BUT AT THAT MOMENT,
ALL I WANTED TO DO
WAS RESCUE HER.
AND THEN IT WAS LIKE
NIRVASH TOLD ME TO TRUST IT,
TO TRUST THAT FEELING.
THAT'S WHY I FINALLY DECIDED
TO BELIEVE IN IT.
BY BELIEVING IT,
I THOUGHT THAT JUST MAYBE
I WOULD BE ABLE
TO RESCUE HER.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT THAT
IT WOULD BE
THE PROOF OF WHAT I BELIEVE IN.
BUT...
- HMM.
YOU WANT PROOF, HUH?
IF YOU REALLY
WANT TO PROVE SOMETHING,
COME WITH US.
- HUH?
- I'M SURE THAT'S
WHAT SHE WISHES FOR TOO.
- ( air raid alarm sounding )
- THE ALERT SIREN!
- Holland: IZUMO'S FLEET!
THEY GOT HERE FASTER
THAN I THOUGHT THEY WOULD.
- HOLLAND, DID YOU SEE?
- SORRY, I GOTTA
BORROW NIRVASH'S RADIO.
- SURE.
- ( alarm continues )
- LISTEN,
YOU SHOULD COME WITH US.
- WHAT?
- IT'S JUST,
THERE'S NO ONE ELSE.
IT HAS TO BE YOU.
- Renton: IT'S TRUE
THAT THIS WAS THE FIRST TIME
A GIRL SAID SOMETHING
LIKE THAT TO ME.
BUT, SIS, THE REAL REASON
WAS SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
I THOUGHT THAT IT WAS MY JOB
TO PROTECT THE AMITA DRIVE
IN PLACE OF GRANDPA.
AND I THOUGHT THAT I WANTED
TO TRUST THIS GIRL
ONE MORE TIME.
THAT'S WHY I TOOK HOLD
OF THE HAND
THAT REACHED OUT TO ME.
TO BE CONTINUED!
- ( theme music playing )
- Narrator: REALITY GLIMMERS
IN SEVEN COLORS.
ALL THE ADULTS CAN DO
IS LOOK ON IN CONFUSION.
AMIDST ALL THAT, THE BOY CLIMBS
ABOARD THE NIRVASH ONCE MORE
TO EMBARK ON A JOURNEY.
NEXT EPISODE, "MOTION BLUE."