- ( theme music playing )
- Renton:
THAT'S MISS SAKUYA?
WELL, UM, I--
I MEAN, THAT'S A--
A FLOWER BUD.
ISN'T IT?
- Norb:
DO YOU FEEL IT?
- MM-HMM.
- ( chuckles )
LET'S GO.
- UH, RIGHT.
- ( grunts )
- ALL OF YOU, I WANT YOU
TO STAY WITH NIRVASH.
- ( whimpering )
- NO, I WANNA GO WITH YOU!
- ME TOO.
- OH?
- JUST WAIT HERE.
- ( gunfire )
- Holland: MATTHIEU, DID YOU GET
IN CONTACT WITH THE GEKKO YET?
- Matthieu: NOT YET.
- THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
ARE ALL THREE COMMUNICATORS
WE BROUGHT WITH US
BROKEN?
- NO, THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH THEM.
THIS IS WHAT'S HAPPENING
ON THE AUDIBLE FREQUENCIES.
ALL THAT I'M GETTING IS US.
AND THE NOISE FROM
THE SOLDIER MONKS'
DIGITAL ENCRYPTION SIGNALS.
- Holland:
THERE'S SOMETHING STRANGE HERE.
YOU NOTICED THAT THESE
DAMN SOLDIER MONKS
AREN'T ATTACKING US
OVER THE WALLS?
- THE WALL SEEMS TO HOLD
A SECRET AFTER ALL.
- Hilda: IT'S NO GOOD, LEADER.
- HUH?
- I SHOOT AT THEM,
BUT THEY KEEP SPROUTING.
IT'S LIKE I'M SHOOTING
INTO A PRACTICE WALL.
- I KNOW THAT! YOU'LL JUST
HAVE TO PUT UP WITH IT
UNTIL RENTON COMES BACK.
- HITTING THE WALL?
( chuckles )
MY HONEY SAYS
GOOD THINGS TO ME.
- YEAH, WHAT'S UP?
- JUST WATCH THIS.
I'M GONNA SEND
AN ENCRYPTED SIGNAL
TO THE GEKKO RIGHT NOW.
- ( beeping )
- WAIT, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I MEAN,
I'M HITTING THE WALL.
- YOU'RE WHAT?
- Matthieu:
ANY SIGNAL I SEND FROM HERE
IMMEDIATELY BOUNCES BACK
AS IF I'M HITTING
A BIG INVISIBLE WALL.
- Holland:
AN INVISIBLE WALL.
- IT IS A FLOWER BUD
AFTER ALL.
SO THEN IS LADY SAKUYA INSIDE?
( gasps )
- IT REALLY HAS BEEN
A LONG TIME,
MY LADY SAKUYA.
HMM.
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS THE NIRVASH,
BROUGHT BY EUREKA AND RENTON.
RENTON, I'M CURIOUS
AS TO WHAT YOU THINK
IS ACTUALLY
BEYOND THE GREAT WALL.
- HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE
IS WAITING THERE FOR YOU
BEYOND THAT
MYSTERIOUS DOORWAY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- IF THE SLEEPING SCUB CORALS
CREATED EUREKA
AND LADY SAKUYA
AS THEIR MAIN MEDIATORS
FOR CONVERSATIONS
WITH HUMANS,
IF THE NIRVASH
WAS A SHIP THAT APPEARED
SO THAT YOU TWO
COULD GO PAST THE ZONE
BEYOND THE GREAT WALL,
IF YOU HEARD ALL THAT,
WHAT WOULD YOU THINK?
- I-- I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
- LADY SAKUYA AND I
ONCE MADE AN ATTEMPT
TO SEE PAST THE ZONE
AND THE GREAT WALL.
BUT WE FAILED.
WE NEVER GOT THERE.
- EUREKA!
- DON'T WORRY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- EUREKA!
- SHE BEARS A STRIKING
RESEMBLANCE
TO LADY SAKUYA
WHO I LOVED.
- ( gasps )
- ( giggles )
- Man: UNDERSTAND...
YOU MUST NOT SPEAK
EVEN A SINGLE WORD
IN THE PRESENCE
OF THE SAINT.
DO NOT TAINT HER
WITH THE REFUSE
OF THIS MISERABLE WORLD.
- Young Norb:
BUT AM I QUALIFIED
TO TAKE CARE OF
THE REQUIRED EVERY DAY DUTIES?
- IT'S NOT LIKE
THE SAINT CAN'T DO
ANYTHING SHE NEEDS TO
BY HERSELF, OR SHE CAN.
WE JUST NEED SOMEONE
TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
AND IT WAS A UNANIMOUS DECISION
BY THE COUNCIL OF HIGH PRIESTS
THAT YOU WERE QUALIFIED
TO BE THAT SOMEONE.
IT'LL FEEL AS NATURAL
AS HAVING TWO EYES AND A NOSE.
I CANNOT ENTER ANY FURTHER
THAN THIS POINT HERE.
MAY EVERYTHING BE
AS THE VODARAC GUIDES US.
- ( door opens )
( door closes )
- ( gasps )
- BOO!
- HOW DO YOU DO,
EUREKA?
- PLEASED TO MEET YOU,
SAKUYA.
- Norb: I WASN'T TOLD THAT
THE SAINT WAS A YOUNG GIRL.
( chuckles )
NO.
NO, THAT'S NOT EXACTLY TRUE.
SHE WAS A GIRL
BORN FROM THE LAND.
AND SO WE SELFISHLY
SET HER UP AS A SAINT.
- Sakuya:
I'M SO HAPPY.
I MEAN, I'VE BEEN REALLY
WANTING TO MEET YOU FOR AWHILE.
YOU'RE ONLY THE SECOND PERSON
TO EVER COME VISIT ME
INSIDE OF MY HEART.
YOU'RE MY FIRST GUEST
IN 40 YEARS.
- I'VE WANTED
TO MEET YOU TOO.
- HEY, WILL YOU
LISTEN TO MY STORY?
I'VE BEEN WAITING SO LONG
TO HAVE SOMEONE
I COULD TELL IT TO.
IT'S ABOUT ME
AND NORB.
- Norb:
THE COUNCIL OF HIGH PRIESTS
APPOINTED ME CARETAKER.
BUT WHAT I WOULD BE DOING
WAS OBVIOUS FROM THE START.
CLEAN UP HER ROOM,
GET HER CLEAN CLOTHING,
CHANGE THE OIL
IN ALL THE LAMPS,
AND BRING IN HER MEALS.
IT WASN'T LIKE THERE
WAS SOMETHING SPECIAL
THAT ONLY I COULD DO.
AND I COULD DO NOTHING
OF MY OWN ACCORD.
NEVERTHELESS,
SHE ALWAYS WORE
A GLOOMY LOOK.
AND SHE WOULD ONLY EAT
ONE BITE OF HER MEALS.
NOW USUALLY YOU'D WANT TO DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT, RIGHT?
- Sakuya:
I MEAN, REALLY.
IT TASTED AWFUL.
IN THE FIRST PLACE,
I WASN'T MOVING AROUND
THAT MUCH,
SO I COULDN'T POSSIBLY
EAT IT ALL.
I HAD NOTHING TO DO
ALL DAY.
AND NO ONE WOULD
SPEAK A WORD TO ME.
IT WAS BORING.
THAT IS UNTIL...
ONE DAY, THINGS CHANGED.
- HUH?
- Young Norb: NO, DON'T!
- ( gasps )
- THAT IS A LOTUS FLOWER
FROM THE LAKE, MY LADY.
OHH!
- LOTUS?
LOTUS?
- ME?  NO, MA'AM.
I'M NORB, YOUR SERVANT.
( gasps )
( muffled murmurs )
- ( chuckles )
THANK YOU.
- HMM?
- Norb: IT WAS THE FIRST TIME
I SAW LADY SAKUYA SMILE.
AND AT THAT MOMENT...
- ( giggles )
I JUST FELL IN LOVE WITH HIM.
- REALLY?
- ( giggles )
I JUST COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
EVERY ONE OF THE MONKS
THAT HAD TENDED TO ME
BEFORE NORB GOT HERE
WERE ALL DOUR AND UPTIGHT.
BUT NORB REALLY
SWEPT ME OFF MY FEET.
NOT ONLY THAT,
NORB WAS THE ONE WHO
TAUGHT ME HOW TO SMILE.
- Hilda: YOU SURE IT'LL
BE ALL RIGHT, LEADER?
- Holland:
I DON'T CARE!
SHOOT A BEAM UP
TOWARDS THE SKY.
- GUESS I DON'T CARE EITHER.
WHAT THE--?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- IS THIS WALL ACTING AS SOME
KIND OF BARRIER OR SOMETHING?
- Holland:
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS?
UNTIL RENTON AND THE OTHERS
MAKE THEIR WAY BACK,
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS TO GUARD AGAINST ATTACKS
FROM THAT DIRECTION.
- Hilda: ROGER THAT.
- SAKUYA NEVER SHOWED
EVEN A HINT OF A SMILE
TO ANYONE ELSE
IN HER LIFE.
HER SMILE WAS SOMETHING
THAT WAS MINE
AND MINE ALONE.
- ( gasps )
- ( people gasping, chattering )
( screaming )
- Young Norb: AAH!
( grunting )
( sighs )
( gasps )
HUH?
- ( gasps )
- THE GLIMMER OF THE COMPAC.
BEAUTIFUL.
- ( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
- OH, NORB.
NORB.
- ( gasps )
- Sakuya:
HIS HAND WAS SO WARM,
SO GENTLE.
I WISHED THAT NIGHT
COULD HAVE LASTED FOREVER.
I THOUGHT THAT I WOULDN'T
MIND BEING IN PRISON LIKE THAT
IF ONLY HE COULD BE WITH ME.
( sighs )
BUT THEN...
- THE DAY FINALLY CAME.
- HUH?
- Young Norb: I AM TO GO TO
THE GREAT WALL WITH LADY SAKUYA?
- Man: I HAVE BEEN INFORMED
THAT THE SAINT TO WHOM
WE HAVE TAUGHT
NOT ONE WORD
SPOKE OUT YOUR NAME,
LORD NORB.
- ( gasps )
- THE SAINT HAS MADE
HER SACRED CHOICE.
TO HEAD TO ETERNITY,
TO PREACH OUR
DEEPEST DESIRES,
AND TO RID THE NEGATIVE
CHAINS WE HAVE WITH THE LAND.
YOU HAVE BEEN CHOSEN,
MASTER NORB.
- I'M A LINK
BETWEEN HUMANS AND LAND?
SO I AM.
- ( cheering )
- YEAH!
MASTER NORB!
- Young Norb: FORGIVE ME
FOR THE PROFANITIES
THAT WILL ENTER YOUR EARS.
IF I AM ABLE TO
ACCOMPANY LADY SAKUYA,
GET PAST THE GATES,
AND LINK HUMANS
AND THE LAND,
IT WILL BE WONDERFUL.
ESPECIALLY TO BE ABLE
TO SEEK OUT
THE MEANING OF EXISTENCE.
HOWEVER,
IF I HAD NOT SPOKEN
MY NAME BACK THEN,
LADY SAKUYA WOULD NOT
HAVE CHOSEN ME.
( gasps )
- ( sighs )
YOU'RE WRONG.
- FORGIVE ME, DEAR SAINT.
I'M NOT WORTHY.
- ( crowd murmuring )
- THIS IS THE SACRED
LIGHT OF THE LAND.
TRULY A MAJESTIC SIGHT.
- ( shouts )
- Sakuya: NORB!
NORB!
NORB, WAIT.  COME BACK!
COME BACK!
( yelps )
- ( gasps )
LADY SAKUYA!
- NORB!
- LADY SAKUYA.
( whimpers )
LADY SAKUYA.
- OH, NORB.
I LOVE YOU.
- SAKUYA.
SAKUYA.
SAKUYA!
( grunts )
( gasps )
AAH.
SAKUYA?
SAKUYA.
( yelps )
( crying )
( screams )
- Norb: IF ONLY I HADN'T
PULLED THE COMPAC DRIVE
OUT OF HER BACK THEN.
IS THAT WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
LADY SAKUYA
TURNED HERSELF INTO
THE SHAPE OF A FLOWER BUD,
AND THAT A COMPAC DRIVE
WAS EMBEDDED INTO MY CHEST.
AND THE SAD FACT
THAT SHE AND I
WERE NOT ABLE TO
BREAK THROUGH THE ZONE.
- ( giggles )
REALLY, IT WAS A BIG FAILURE.
BUT LISTEN TO THIS,
I FOUND OUT BACK THEN...
- HMM?
- THAT YOU WOULD BE BORN,
EUREKA.
- HUH?
SAKUYA.
- ( stammering )
- Norb: I'M SURE THAT
TIME WITHIN THE ZONE
REMAINS STANDING STILL
AND IS WAITING FOR
THE COMPAC DRIVE IN MY CHEST
TO RETURN TO LADY SAKUYA.
NO.
NO, IT WOULDN'T BE WAITING.
THE LAND IS JUST EXISTING.
WATCHING OVER ALL OF US
WHO CALL IT HOME.
- IT MUST HAVE BEEN TOUGH.
- HMM?
- OH, BUT I HAVE
NO REGRETS AT ALL.
WHEN I HEARD HIM CALL OUT
MY NAME LIKE HE DID,
I FELT THAT HE AND I HAD
FINALLY BECOME ONE.
I WAS HAPPY.
BECAUSE HOW I FEEL
ABOUT NORB IS...
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I MEAN, YOU AND RENTON.
( giggles )
YOU KNOW, I THINK I'M JUST
A LITTLE BIT JEALOUS OF YOU.
- YOU'RE JEALOUS?
- I MEAN, YOU HAVE
SO MANY THINGS, EUREKA.
I WISH I HAD THEM TOO.
AH, JUST KIDDING.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M SURE YOU TWO
WILL BECOME ONE.
- ( murmurs )
- IT'S NOT A SCARY THING.
IT'LL BE WONDERFUL.
YOU KNOW, HE'S HEAD OVER HEELS
IN LOVE WITH YOU.
- MM-HMM.
- I'M SURE HE'S
GONNA BE NICE TO YOU.
YOU HAVE TO BECOME HAPPY,
EUREKA.
- SO DO YOU.
- OH.
MM-HMM.
- MM.
- WELL, IT'S ALMOST TIME
FOR THE BUS TO LEAVE.
SEE YOU LATER, EUREKA.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
- HMM?
- YOU TRIED TO
GO BACK ONCE, RIGHT?
YOU WANT ME TO
FIX THE SCARS?
- THESE ARE THE OUTWARD PROOF
THAT I'VE LIVED TO THIS DAY.
- MM-HMM.
YOU'RE SO STRONG-WILLED,
EUREKA.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- I DON'T KNOW.
A TECTONIC SHIFT?
- Hilda: HOLD ON A SECOND.
LEADER!
LOOK, ABOVE US!
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
THE BARRIER.
IT DISAPPEARED.
- ( sighs )
- ( gasps )
EUREKA!
- ( sighs )
- EUREKA, YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YES, I'M FINE.
- EUREKA, WHAT DID
LADY SAKUYA SAY?
- SHE TOLD US
TO BECOME HAPPY.
- I SEE, LADY SAKUYA.
I SEE.
- Both: HUH?
- RADAR CONFIRMS
COMPAC INTERFERENCE WAVES.
BATTLESHIPS ARE APPROACHING
THE VODARA SHRINE
COMING IN FROM 9:00
AND MOVING FAST.
THREE SHIPS.
- WHERE'S HOLLAND
AND THE OTHERS?
- COM LINK RESTORED.
- PATCH THE LINE OVER HERE.
HOLLAND, WE CAN REACH
THE SKY ABOVE YOU
IN EIGHT MINUTES.
ARE YOU READY FOR PICKUP?
- Holland: NO!
RENTON'S GROUP
HASN'T COME BACK YET.
- THREE FEDERATION ARMY SHIPS
ARE APPROACHING FAST.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO,
HOLLAND?
AT THIS RATE--
- Holland: WE'LL GUARD THIS SPOT
WITH OUR LIVES.
THAT'S THE PROMISE
I MADE TO RENTON.
- I KNOW.  BUT HOLLAND--
- BE SURE YOU MAKE
THE FIRST MOVE
WITH THE GEKKO
NO MATTER WHAT!
( gasps )
( grunting )
- HOLLAND!
- WE'RE ALL RIGHT.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF DYING HERE.
GOT THAT?
WE WON'T DIE.
I WON'T LET ANYONE DIE!
- WE'LL SURVIVE.
EVEN IF WE'RE ALL
SHOT TO PIECES
AND COUGHING UP BLOOD!
- TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- Narrator: THE LAND AWAKENS
FROM THE REPEATED ATTACKS.
THE BOY AND THE GIRL
ARE ABOUT TO EMBARK
TOWARDS THE FUTURE,
AND THE ADULTS
RISK THEIR LIVES
TO SUPPORT THEM.
NEXT EPISODE,
"STAR DANCER."