- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
♪ WE WANT TO MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE ♪
♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
- WOW, WHAT A BEAUTIFUL CLOUD.
- A MACKEREL SKY.
- HUH?
YEAH, IT'S A TYPE OF CLOUD THAT
CAN FORETELL A TECTONIC SHIFT.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE
A REF BOARDER,
THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
- RIGHT.
- WRINKLES.
IF YOU KEEP THAT UP,
YOUR FOREHEAD WILL BE
FULL OF WRINKLES!
WE'RE BOTH ABOUT
TO GO OVER THE HILL.
- GEEZ, DON'T SURPRISE ME
LIKE THAT.
- ( laughs ) JUST WATCH OUT
FOR THOSE WRINKLES.
- HEY, SHUT UP. YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT NEEDS TO WORRY.
THAT'S WHY I'M TELLING YOU.
- WE BOTH NEED TO BE CAREFUL.
- I AM GOING NOW.
- LET ME REMIND YOU, YOU'RE
A YEAR OLDER THAN I AM.
AND DON'T YOU FORGET IT.
- ALL RIGHT, KIDS, IT'S FINE
TO GO IN AND SEE HER.
- ( all exclaim in joy )
MAMA!
- HI, YOU GUYS.
- I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
- HERE. THESE ARE THE INVOICES
FOR THIS MONTH.
- RIGHT, THANKS A LOT, MISCHA.
SO, I HEARD RENTON DISAPPEARED
LAST NIGHT. IS THAT TRUE?
- YES, APPARENTLY HE
SNUCK HIS WAY IN HERE
BEFORE HE LEFT AND SAW EUREKA.
SHE WON'T TELL US
ABOUT IT, THOUGH.
- AH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT KID IS SPINELESS.
SO, DOES SHE KNOW
RENTON RAN AWAY?
SHE'D BE PRETTY UPSET.
- THAT'S NOT THE KIND OF NEWS
SHE SHOULD BE GETTING FROM ME.
- THAT'S TRUE.
BUT, I HEARD HE LEFT A NOTE.
- THE FACT THAT HE WROTE
PLEASE DON'T LOOK FOR ME,
MEANS HE WANTS US
TO LOOK FOR HIM.
IN A WAY, HE'S ENTERED
SOME SORT OF REBELLIOUS PHASE.
- IT'S SOMETHING TO BE EXPECTED
FROM A BOY WHO HAS MOVED
INTO HIS ADOLESCENCE.
- THOUGH IT DID COME LATE.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- BUT FROM OUR VIEWPOINT,
GROWTH IS NOTHING
BUT A BIG HINDRANCE
TO THOSE GUYS WHO AREN'T
THERE WHEN WE NEED THEM.
- YOUR ATTITUDE IS A BIT HARSH,
ISN'T IT?
- I THINK THEY ARE COWARDS.
- LET'S FACE IT, OF ALL
THE GUYS ON THIS SHIP,
THE LEADER HIMSELF IS RIGHT
SMACK IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE INSANITY OF PUBERTY.
- SO, WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE
LEADER IS THINKING OF DOING NOW?
- I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
- HMM.
I'M THE ONE WHO
OUGHT TO BE SORRY.
- ( gasps ) IT'S GONE!
GONE! GONE! GONE!
( sighs )
- ( zipper unzips )
- ( urinates )
- ( sighs )
- Hap: WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
- YOU MADE THE FLOW STOP.
- WE HAVEN'T EVEN TOLD
EUREKA YET.
- I HAVEN'T THE SLIGHTEST CLUE.
- WE'RE COUNTING
ON YOU, OH, LEADER.
- BUT...
- HMM?
- BEING ABLE TO ANNOUNCE HIS
FEELINGS LIKE THAT IS JUST...
- YOU KNOW, MAYBE BOTH
YOU AND I WERE NUISANCES
TO OUR ELDERS AND SIBLINGS
WHEN WE WERE KIDS, TOO.
YOU KNOW, LIKE
HISTORY REPEATING ITSELF?
OH, SORRY.
THE BAD THING ABOUT
CHILDHOOD FRIENDS
IS THAT YOU DON'T
HOLD ANYTHING BACK.
- TRUE ENOUGH.
- HUH?
- THAT'S WEIRD.
IT'S UNLIKE HIM.
- ( toilet flushes )
- NOT LIKE HIM AT ALL.
- Renton: I DIDN'T HAVE A PLAN
OR ANYTHING.
I JUST WANTED TO GO
AS FAR AWAY AS I COULD.
BUT, THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT I REALIZED
AFTER I FOUND MYSELF ALONE.
SO MANY THINGS HAD HAPPENED,
AND I HAD NO PLACE OF MY OWN.
BUT THERE, ON THE GEKKO,
I WAS NEVER ALONE.
I'M SO TIRED NOW.
I CAN'T THINK ANY MORE.
- ( upbeat dance music playing )
- ( gasps )
- ( techno music playing )
- WHOO.
- ( chuckles )
- HEY, BOY. WHERE'D YOU
COME FROM?
DID SOMEONE
GIVE YOU THE FLYER?
- UH, WELL, I'M TRAVELING
WITH NOTHING BUT MY BOARD.
- OH, A HANDMADE ONE.
THAT'S A GOOD BOARD
YOU GOT THERE.
- OH, NO, IT REALLY
ISN'T NOT THAT GOOD.
- AND THE HEART WITHIN?
A SENTIMENTAL JOURNEY PERHAPS?
( laughs ) ADOLESCENCE!
HI, KID. MY NAME
IS CHARLES BEAMS.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- UH, HI, I'M RENTON.
- RENTON? THINK I HAVE
HEARD THAT NAME BEFORE?
OH, WELL, YEAH.
THAT'S A NAME YOU CAN HEAR
JUST ABOUT ANYWHERE.
( laughs )
HEY, WHAT WAS FUNNY ABOUT
ANYTHING THAT I JUST SAID.
YOU DO KNOW I WAS MOCKING YOU.
- YEAH, I KIND OF
FIGURED THAT OUT.
- HMM?
BUT, IT'S BEEN A WHILE SINCE
ANYONE SAID ANYTHING TO ME.
SO, I GUESS I COULDN'T
HELP MYSELF.
- SORRY.
- I SEE.
- LOOK, OVER THERE.
- HUH?
- NOT THE DJ.
- OH.
- DAMN, SHE'S ONE HOT BABE.
- SHE'S JUST SO CHARMING,
RIGHT, RENTON, MY BOY?
- SURE.
- THE SAME SONG,
BUT A LITTLE DIFFERENT?
- THIS SONG
IS THIS YEAR'S BIG ANTHEM.
WE ALREADY GOT
A BOOTLEG REMIX OF THE TRACK.
- BUT THE ORIGINAL VERSION
IS REALLY THE BEST.
- RIGHT.
- BUT THEY ARE SLIPPING.
THEY ARE USING
A VERTICAL FADE MIXER.
I PREFER THE OLD ROTARIES.
THE MIXING IS SO MUCH SMOOTHER.
- SURE.
- HMM?
- ( gasps )
- SOME MUDDY SOUNDS HAVE
STARTED TO ENTER THE BASS TRACK,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- ( gasps )
- IS THIS A TECTONIC SHIFT?
- RAY!
- ( screams )
( panting )
- ( all screaming )
- HUH?
- HMM? ( gasps )
- AH, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH, MISS.
- ( chuckles )
- WANT A DRINK?
- HUH?
- SO, RENTON, WE MEET AGAIN.
LET ME INTRODUCE
MY DARLING WIFE TO YOU.
- I'M RAY. NICE TO MEET YOU.
- YOU ARE GOING TO LIKE THIS.
I BOUGHT SOME SPARE LINGERIE.
EVEN IF YOU'RE NOT
FEELING WELL,
AS A GIRL YOU SHOULD
CARE HOW YOU LOOK.
- THANK YOU.
- EUREKA, YOU REALLY
HAVE CHANGED.
- YOU THINK SO?
- HERE.
- THANKS.
- YOU KNOW, YOU'VE ALWAYS
SEEMED REALLY HARD TO APPROACH.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALL COLD AND
DETACHED AND INDIFFERENT AND,
YOU DON'T CARE
ABOUT WHAT WE DO.
- INDIFFERENT?
- BUT THEN, I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO SIT DOWN
AND PROPERLY TALK IT OUT
WITH YOU, EUREKA.
- WHY IS THAT?
- WELL, YOU SEE, I REALLY
ADMIRE GIRL TO GIRL FRIENDSHIP,
LIKE WHAT TALHO
AND HILDA HAVE GOING.
IT'S SOMETHING
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED.
BUT, THE SAD FACT
IS THAT THOSE TWO
HAVE ALWAYS TREATED ME LIKE
I AM SOME KIND OF DUMB
LITTLE GIRL.
- FRIENDSHIP?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
- SO, LIKE, IF YOU HAVE
SOMETHING TROUBLING YOU,
YOU COME AND TELL ME.
WHATEVER IT IS.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT VERY BRIGHT,
SO, I AM SURE I WON'T
UNDERSTAND ALL THE REALLY
COMPLICATED STUFF,
LIKE OUR LEADERS DO.
AND MORE OFTEN THAN NOT,
I'LL BE OF NO HELP TO YOU.
HEY, YOU. SO, HOW ABOUT IT?
- HMM?
- ABOUT HIM.
- WHICH HIM?
- RENTON.
I MEAN, COME ON, THAT'S
THE ONLY POSSIBLE REASON
YOU'D CHANGE SO MUCH.
WHEN RENTON CAME,
YOU STARTED TO SMILE
A LOT MORE. I UNDERSTAND.
OH, IT'S NOT ABOUT
RENTON, THOUGH.
IT'S ABOUT HOW YOU START
SMILING JUST BY LOOKING AT HIM.
- START SMILING?
I START TO SMILE?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
NOW AS FOR ME,
IT'S TRUE THAT I REALLY
LIKE DOGGIE'S PRETTY FACE,
BUT MORE THAN THAT,
HE'S SO PATHETIC
THAT WHEN I WATCH HIM,
I JUST WANT TO SCOOP HIM UP
AND HELP HIM ALONG.
I'M SORRY, I'M DOING
ALL OF THE TALKING HERE.
WELL, GOT TO GO.
- TO RENTON.
- HUH?
- I WANT TO TALK TO RENTON
ABOUT ALL SORTS OF THINGS.
BUT, RIGHT NOW, I'M AFRAID
TO EVEN LOOK AT HIS FACE.
I WONDER WHY?
- (sighs )
- YOU KNOW WHAT, EUREKA,
YOU BETTER CURB
THAT NAIVETY OF YOURS
OR THE OTHER GIRLS
WILL HATE YOU.
I MEAN, IT'S ALL BECAUSE
YOU'RE IN LOVE.
- LOVE?
- YEAH, IN LOVE.
- Renton: AMAZING! YOU GUYS
REALLY KEEP IT NEAT.
- Ray: THANK YOU.
- THIS IS SUCH A BIG DIFFERENCE
FROM THAT OTHER SHIP.
- IF IT'S A COMPLIMENT,
IT'S UNNECESSARY.
- NO, THAT'S ISN'T WHAT I MEANT.
- HEY, KIDS WILL BE KIDS.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT BEING
SO CONSIDERATE OF ADULTS.
YOU CAN ONLY BE
A KID FOR SO LONG,
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL ENJOY IT.
- IN THE END, I TOOK FULL
ADVANTAGE OF WHAT HE SAID TO ME.
IF THAT TECTONIC SHIFT
HADN'T OCCURRED,
MAYBE I WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
AVAIL MYSELF OF THEIR OFFER.
- Charles: I WON'T GIVE YOU ANY.
THEY'RE ALL MINE.
- HUH?
- SORRY, I WAS STARING.
DID YOU START RIDING RECENTLY?
- HEY, I WAS BORN WITH
A BOARD ATTACHED TO MY FEET.
- BUT...
YOU CAN'T MAKE REALLY
QUICK MANEUVERS
WITH THE BOARD MADE LIKE THIS.
THE WHEEL'S PRETTY BIG,
SO, THE NUMBER OF TRICKS
YOU CAN DO IS LIMITED.
- I SEE.
SO, IT'S HIP FOR REAL BOARDERS
TO GO WHEEL LESS?
- WHAT?
- THAT'S WHAT THE MAGAZINES
MAYBE WRITING THESE DAYS,
BUT WHAT OTHERS THINK,
IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER IN LIFTING,
AS LONG AS YOU'RE HAVING FUN,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- ( exclaims )
- AT ANY GIVEN TIME
IN THIS WORLD,
THE ONE WHO FEELS PLEASURE
IS THE WINNER.
AM I WRONG?
- IT FELT LIKE HE WAS SAYING
THE RIGHT THING.
BECAUSE IT WAS IN RAY=OUT.
BECAUSE I LOOKED UP TO HOLLAND.
THAT'S WHY I BELIEVED THAT
EVERYTHING ABOUT THE GEKKOSTATE
WAS A GOOD THING,
WITHOUT THINKING IT THROUGH.
- HEY, BOY.
- YES?
- HOW ABOUT I SHOW YOU
SOMETHING GOOD? HMM?
- SO COOL!
- WOW.
- YOU LIKE IT?
- I WON'T GIVE IT TO YOU.
- HUH? HEY, WAIT.
I DON'T SEE
A BOARD ANYWHERE AROUND HERE.
- ( laughs ) HOW ABOUT IT?
WANT TO TAKE A RIDE?
- SURE!
THE MAIN CONSTRUCTION,
THE FRAMES, TOO,
IT'S NOT A MON-SOONO TYPE,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
OVERALL, THIS LOOKS CLOSER
TO THE TERMINUS SERIES.
- HEY, YOU KNOW A LOT.
- WELL, I LIKE THIS
KIND OF STUFF.
- HEY, BY THE WAY, WHERE'S
THE BOARD FOR THIS THING?
- THIS GUY DOESN'T NEED
ANYTHING OF THE SORT.
- IT DOESN'T?
- THEN HOW DO YOU
RIDE THE TRAPARS?
- ACTUALLY...
- ( beeps )
- WHOOPS. EXCUSE ME.
- Ray: CHARLES, I HAVE
A DISTRESS CALL.
A REQUEST FOR TRANSPORT
FROM A CARRIER SHIP
THAT GOT STRANDED
IN THE EARLIER TECTONIC SHIFT.
THEIR REFRIGERATION UNIT BROKE,
SO THEIR CARGO IS GOING TO MELT.
- THEY CAN TAKE
CARE OF IT THEMSELVES.
- THE CLIENT IS LLOYD RIGHT.
- YOU MEAN, THE PUSHER?
THAT MEANS THE CARGO IS
SOMETHING LIKE FROZEN CHOCOLATE.
THEY DON'T WANT
THE ARMY FINDING IT.
- WHAT DO WE DO? WE OWE LLOYD
RIGHT A FAVOR, YOU KNOW.
- HEY, BOY.
- HUH?
- YOU WERE JUST ASKING ABOUT
HOW THIS RIDES THE TRAPARS
WITHOUT A BOARD, WEREN'T YOU?
HOW ABOUT I SHOW YOU?
- Ray: WAIT A MINUTE, CHARLES.
YOU'RE GOING TO HANG OUT
THERE BY YOURSELF?
- Charles: IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY, BOY.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO
DELIVER THE CARGO.
- WOW, THE BOARD IS ATTACHED
TO THE BODY OF THE SHIP.
- SEE?
YOU DANCE TO MUSIC,
SOMETHING YOU CAN'T SEE,
BUT YOU FEEL IT ON YOUR SKIN.
AND YOU LIFT BY FEELING
TRAPARS WITH YOUR HEART,
ALSO, SOMETHING
YOU CAN'T SEE.
IT'S THE SAME THING.
IN THE CASE OF LFOS,
IT'S NOT WHETHER YOU HAVE
A BOARD THAT'S THE ISSUE,
THE ISSUE IS WHETHER OR NOT,
YOU CAN RIDE THE WAVES.
- HEY, THAT A BATTLE.
- YOU'VE GOT A PRETTY GOOD EYE.
- Man on radio: MAYDAY, MAYDAY!
EMERGENCY! PIRATES ARE
ATTACKING OUR SHIP!
THE CARGO IS IN DANGER. CHARLES!
- GEEZ, THIEVES TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF A DISASTER
LIKE A TECTONIC SHIFT.
- THEY USE THE CHAOS
OF THE DISASTER?
- YEAH, IT'S UNFAIR.
BUT IT'S ALSO A BATTLE
TO PUT FOOD ON THEIR TABLE
FOR BOTH SIDES OF THE CONFLICT.
- ( gasps )
- HEY, KID,
BETTER HANG ON TIGHT.
- YOU ARE GOING AGAINST THREE?
- OH, THIS IS NOTHING.
CIRCUS MANEUVERS,
GOING ALL OUT.
- ( grunts ) WOW.
- ( chuckles )
SUCK ON THIS.
CHECKMATE.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- SEE? YOU FEEL THE TRAPARS
WITH YOUR EARS, BOY.
YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT I'M SAYING?
- YES.
A BATTLE TO PUT FOOD
ON THE TABLE.
- WOW, LOOKS GREAT.
- YOU ARE LUCKY.
THAT COULD HAVE BEEN REALLY BAD.
- YEAH, YEAH.
- YOU MUST HAVE BEEN SCARED.
- NOT AT ALL. I WAS JUST FINE.
IT'S TRUE. I REALLY
DID THINK IT WAS STRANGE.
CHARLES WAS SO FORCEFUL,
UNCARING OF THE SITUATIONS
THAT I'VE BEEN IN.
AND, HE'S SO GRAND,
AND, WELL...
ON TOP OF EVERYTHING,
THE MEAL...
THE MEAL WAS SO TASTY,
IT ACTUALLY MADE ME CRY.
NATURE AND HUMANS CAN CHANGE
IN A BLINK OF AN EYE.
THAT WAS A SURPRISE TO ME.
BUT, SIS,
I THINK THAT THIS WAS MAYBE
THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE
THAT I FELT THIS PEACEFUL.
- ( engine revving )
- WELL, I GUESS,
THIS IS THE RIGHT ADDRESS.
- NOW, WHAT DO I DO?
- Renton: TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( closing theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ GO ANOTHER PLACE ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
♪ FLY AWAY, FLY AWAY ♪
♪ TAKE MY CHANCE ♪
♪ BELIEVE IN MYSELF ♪
♪ TAKE IT EASY ♪
- Girl: THE SITUATION
OF THE WORLD.
THE TRUTH ABOUT THIS SOCIETY.
WHAT IS THE CHALLENGE
THAT STANDS BEFORE THE BOY,
WHO IS NO LONGER A CHILD,
YET STILL NOT AN ADULT?
NEXT EPISODE, "DIFFERENTIA."