- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- IT'S FINALLY BEGAN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY THAT?
- THERE'S AN ENORMOUS
COMMOTION
GOING ON UP THERE.
THIS IS MOST LIKELY
A LARGE ATTACK
THAT WAS LAUNCHED BECAUSE
YOU TWO
WERE ABLE TO GET
TO THE VODARAC SHRINE.
- AN ATTACK?
BUT, FOR WHAT REASON?
IT'S THE WORK OF A MAN
WHO DOESN'T WANT
YOU TWO ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE ZONE.
A YOUNG LAD
NAMED DEWEY.
- WHAT ABOUT HOLLAND
AND THE OTHERS?
- REST ASSURED THAT MAN
IS NOT GOING TO BE
DEFEATED EASILY.
- YOU CAN TELL?
- HMM. IT'S JUST
A HUNCH.
THIS TOWER, IT WAS ONCE
WRAPPED IN A BARRIER,
USING A PORTION
OF LADY SAKUYA POWERS
TO MAINTAIN IT.
HOWEVER, NOW THAT WE'RE ABLE
TO HEAR THE DEEP RUMBLINGS
OF THE ATTACKS DOWN HERE,
IT IS A SIGN
THAT LADY SAKUYA HAS DECIDED.
THE POWER USED TO PROTECT
THIS TOWER
WILL NOW BE USED
FOR ANOTHER PURPOSE.
- ANOTHER PURPOSE?
- RIGHT NOW,
LADY SAKUYA IS SUMMONING UP
ALL HER POWERS
SO THAT TOGETHER WITH ME
SHE CAN SEND YOU TWO
TO THE GENUINE
PROMISED LAND.
- THE GENUINE--
- PROMISED LAND?
- ( siren blaring )
- Man: WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- IT'S NOT LOOKING GOOD.
THERE'S NO WAY WE CAN WIN
IF WE GOT TO GO UP
AGAINST NINE OF THEM.
- AT LEAST THE SOLDIER MONKS
HAVE STOPPED ATTACKING,
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH.
MATTHIEW,
I NEED A FAVOR.
- AHA?
- Talho:
WAIT A MINUTE, HOLLAND,
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
- I DON'T CARE!
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
FOR US TO GET THROUGH
THE SITUATION.
- LISTEN, HOLLAND,
YOU CAN'T BE RUSHED ABOUT THIS.
- I KNOW.
- HEY, DOGGIE. YOU'VE HEARD
ALL THAT, DIDN'T YOU?
- ROGER THAT.
EVERYONE BETTER HOLD ON TIGHT!
- ( children cry ) Mama! Mama!
- I'M HAPPY I WAS ABLE
TO KNOW THE TWO OF YOU.
- STOP IT! YOU'RE SOUNDING
LIKE WE'RE NEVER
GONNA GET TO SEE
EACH OTHER AGAIN.
- PEOPLE ALWAYS MEET OTHERS
VERY SUDDENLY.
BUT THOSE CHANCE ENCOUNTERS
CHANGE PEOPLE.
AS DO FAREWELLS.
BUT YOU SHOULD NOT
FEAR SUCH SUDDENNESS.
- MASTER NORB!
- THE TIME HAS COME
TO CREATE A POROROKA
WITH LADY SAKUYA.
- POROROKA?
- HMM.
I WILL MOMENTARILY
REVERSE THE BARRIER
THAT SURROUNDS
THE GREAT WALL.
THE TERM REFERS
TO THAT PHENOMENON.
FLY TOWARDS THE CENTER
OF IT ALL.
BEYOND IT IS THE ZONE
THAT LEADS TO THE GENUINE
PROMISED LAND.
- BUT WHAT OF SAKUYA?
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU,
MASTER NORB?
- ( chuckling )
JUST GO.
RENTON, EUREKA,
EVEN IF THE DARKNESS SPREADS
FAR BEYOND YOUR SIGHT,
WHERE YOU TWO TREAD
BECOMES THE PATH.
- ( firing, explosions )
- LEADER, ARE YOU SURE
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
- TALHO AND KEN-GOH HAVE BEEN
TRAINING HIM FOR A WHILE.
DOGGIE WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
CAN WE REALLY PULL THIS OFF?
- IT'S TIME.
TAKE OFF!
- DON'T BLAME ME
IF WE DIE.
- SO, ALL THE ATTACKS
HAVE SUCCEEDED?
- YES! WE'RE CURRENTLY
IN PHASE FOUR OF OUR ATTACKS.
BUT WE HAD CONFIRMED
THE DETONATION OF EVERY BULLET.
- LAUNCH AN ORANGE
ATTACK IMMEDIATELY.
- BUT LEADER, THERE ARE
STILL THREE SHIPS
FROM OUR ALLIANCE LEAGUE
NEAR THE VODARAC SHRINE.
- THE SHRINE IN THAT AREA
USED TO HAVE A BARRIER
AROUND IT.
AND THE BARRIER
DISAPPEARING MEANS--
- OH! THEY HAVE SUCCEEDED
IN MAKING THEIR CONTACT?
- HAVE THE END
HEAD OVER THERE.
WE NEED TO SEND IT
THROUGH THE WALL,
BEFORE THEY HAVE
THE CHANCE.
IF NOT, THEN--
- Both: ROGER THAT, SIR!
- SO YOU HAD EMBARKED,
KNOWING YOU WILL NOT ESCAPE,
MY BROTHER?
- HMM.
WELL, MY LADY...
WE'RE FINALLY
ALONE AGAIN.
- ( vibrating )
- ( gasps )
( gasps )
LADY SAKUYA!
- NO WAY!
YOU INJECTED THIS YOURSELF?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I DID IT,
BECAUSE I CAN'T FIGHT
WELL WITHOUT IT.
- ANEMONE, THAT'S ENOUGH.
WHAT REASON COULD YOU
POSSIBLY HAVE TO INJECT
THIS MUCH MEDICATION?
- I HAVE A GOOD REASON.
- ( sighs )
- I MEAN, IT'S WHAT DEWEY
IS WISHING FOR.
- ( gasps )
- ( thinking )
WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS THE GENUINE
PROMISED LAND?
- Master Norb: I DON'T KNOW.
I FAILED,
SO DON'T ASK ME.
- Children: MAMA!
- Master Norb: ONE THING.
- ONE THING?
- THERE'S ONE MORE THING
I WISH TO TELL YOU.
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU TWO HAVE
THAT LADY SAKUYA
AND I LACK.
HMM.
- MASTER NORB...
WAS IN TEARS.
WHAT THEY LACK?
IT WAS YOU!
WASN'T IT, NIRVASH?
- ( screeching )
- AMAZING!
WHERE ARE WE?
- ( firing, explosions )
- ( grunts )
- MOONDOGGIE!
KEEP YOUR HEAD ABOVE YOU!
- ( beeping )
- TIME TO GO!
- Woman: ROGER!
- WHERE'S THE 606?
- NOT HERE YET.
- ( grunts )
- IT'S HERE.
LAUNCH THE 909!
- DON'T DIE, LEADER!
- DON'T WORRY, I WON'T!
- ( yelling )
- ( firing, explosions )
- ( grunts )
- ( screaming )
- EUREKA!
( gasps )
- ( buzzing )
- ( gasps )
IT'S--
IT'S A KUTE-CLASS.
- EVERYONE IS...
IN DANGER.
- ( firing, explosions )
- ( people gasping )
- HOW MANY OF THESE THINGS
ARE THERE?
( screaming )
- HILDA!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
THANKS, MATTHIEW.
( gasps )
MATTHIEW!
- ( grunts )
DAMMIT!
I'M NOT GONNA MAKE IT
IN TIME!
- HOLLAND, YOU'RE HERE!
- HEY, GUYS.
SORRY I'M A LITTLE LATE.
- LEADER,
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
WE'RE A BUNCH OF MICE
CAUGHT ON A TRAP!
- PROTECT THIS PLACE.
- Hilda: HOLD ON A SECOND!
HOW CAN WE PROTECT
ANYTHING IN THESE
CONDITIONS?
WE HAVE NO CHOICE!
RENTON'S GROUP STILL HASN'T--
- Renton: EVACUATE THE AREA!
- RENTON!
- SORRY WE MADE YOU
ALL WORRY,
BUT ALL OF US ARE SAFE.
HEY, WHY ARE MAETER
AND THE BOYS WITH YOU?
- IT'S A LONG STORY.
- WE'RE REALLY SORRY.
- ( sighs )
WHAT THE HELL?
- HOLLAND, MASTER NORBS
TOLD US TO GO.
- WHAT?
- BEFORE WE LEFT, HE SAID
THAT HE WOULD OPEN UP A ZONE
IN THE GREAT WALL JUST FOR US.
- WHERE IS HE?
- WITH LADY SAKUYA.
HE CHOSE TO STAY
UNDERGROUND.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- WHAT?
- I FEEL SAKUYA'S FEELINGS.
AND ALSO MASTER NORB'S
FEELINGS, TOO.
IT'S TIME TO GO
BEYOND THE ZONE.
( gasps )
HMM.
Man: THIS IS THE 909!
TALHO, PICK UP THE 606
AND 808, RIGHT AWAY.
THE MINUTE THE ZONE OPENS
IN THE GREAT WALL,
WE'RE GOING IN.
- HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
YOU JUST SAID
WE'RE GOING IN,
BUT BETWEEN US
AND THE GREAT WALL.
- LADY SAKUYA,
I-- I AM--
WELL--
- ( snorts )
- ( gasps )
LADY SAKUYA!
IS-- IS THERE SOMETHING
THE MATTER?
AH... DO YOU FIND YOURSELF
DISSATISFIED TO BE HERE,
WITH SOMEONE LIKE ME?
I KNOW. YOU'RE STILL
NOT GOING TO FORGIVE ME
FOR LEAVING, FOR ABANDONING YOU
HERE ALL THOSE YEARS AGO.
- BACK THEN...
IF YOU HAD NOT CALLED
MY NAME LIKE YOU DID.
I'M SURE I WOULDN'T BE
HERE RIGHT NOW.
HERE, LOOK AT THIS!
IT'S MY BOOK!
- OHH!
- IT'S 40 YEARS
OF BLANK PAGES.
THE PAGES BEFORE THAT
ARE FULL.
- WHAT?
HMM.
SAKUYA...
- ( chuckling )
YOU FINALLY
CALLED OUT FOR ME.
I'M GLAD.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
A LONG TIME.
- ( gasps )
- LET'S GET STARTED,
FOR THE SAKE
OF THOSE CHILDREN.
- FOR THEM.
AND FOR OUR SAKE
AS WELL.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I THINK IT'S
THE POROROKA.
THAT MASTER NORB
WAS TALKING ABOUT.
- RENTON, LISTEN UP.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE
YOU'RE GONNA BE GOING
FROM HERE ON IN.
BUT IF SOMETHING HAPPENS,
IF YOU END UP
IN A BIND FOR SOME REASON,
USE THE THING THAT IS PLACED
BEHIND THE SUB PILOT'S SEAT.
- BUT HOLLAND,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
- IT'S SOMETHING
THAT YOU DESERVE TO HAVE
SO MUCH MORE
THAN I DO.
- HOLLAND, WAIT!
- WE'RE OUT OF TIME!
WE'VE GOT TO GET THROUGH
THE ANTIBODY CORALIANS,
RIGHT NOW!
GOT THAT, TALHO?
- LET'S GO, DOGGIE!
- ROGER THAT!
- LOOK OUT!
IT'S NO GOOD.
AT THIS RATE, BEFORE WE MAKE IT
THROUGH, ALL OF YOU ARE---
- RENTON!
LISTEN TO ME.
YOU HAVE TO GO NOW.
YOU TWO ARE THE ONLY HOPE
FOR ALL OUR FUTURES.
- TALHO--
- THE HOPE YOU'RE CARRYING
IS NOT JUST FOR US,
NOT JUST FOR MANKIND,
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
IT'S THE HOPE FOR EVERY LIVING
THING ON THIS PLANET!
- HOPE FOR EVERYTHING?
- ( explosion )
- MIS TALHO!
- WE'RE ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY, RENTON.
WE'LL MAKE SURE
TO SURVIVE
UNTIL YOU GET BACK.
WE'LL ALL BE WAITING FOR YOU,
ALL RIGHT?
HARRY UP AND GET GOING.
- ( crying )
- Holland: DON'T HESITATE!
GO!
- NO, NIRVASH, STOP!
- LET'S GO BACK.
PLEASE, WE HAVE TO GO BACK.
- IT'S IN YOUR HANDS,
RENTON, EUREKA.
- LEADER, ATTACKING ONE KLF
APPROACHING FAST.
- WE'VE GOT TO STOP IT!
- NOW WHAT'S UP WITH THIS?
YOU JUST GONNA RUN AWAY?
- I WON'T LET YOU INTERFERE
WITH THEM.
- WHAT IS THIS?
YOU'RE NOT THE ONE
I'M SUPPOSED TO FIGHT!
NOT BAD.
YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD.
- DAMMIT!
WHO THE HELL IS THAT?
WHAT THE HELL?
- BYE BYE, MR. UGLY.
IT'S YOUR FAULT
YOU GOT IN THE WAY.
- ( screaming )
- HOLLAND, NO!
GO BACK, NIRVASH!
GO BACK, PLEASE!
- RENTON, LOOK!
- SO I TAKE IT YOU WANNA
RUN AWAY FROM ME.
STUFF LIKE THAT...
PISSES ME OFF!
- RENTON!
- ( crying )
- ( inaudible )
- LET'S GO.
- ( gasps )
- LET'S GO, EUREKA.
FOR EVERYONE'S SAKE!
- ( explosion )
- OH! WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
( grunts )
WHY CAN'T I CATCH UP?
NO, NO!
I WON'T ALLOW IT!
( gasps )
( crying )
- TypeZERO HAS SWITCHED
TO SUPERSONIC FLIGHT MODE.
IT'S ENTRY INTO THE ZONE
IS CONFIRMED.
I HAVE CONFIRMATION
OF THE END'S POSITION
AS 8-2-5-2-7.
GETTING PAST THE ZONE.
- IT WAS A TOTAL FAILURE.
- YES.
- DON'T WORRY,
I HAVE OTHER PLANS.
I WANT THE END
RECOVERED QUICKLY.
WE'RE GOING BACK.
- HAVE A SAFE JOURNEY...
RENTON, EUREKA.
- MASTER NORB.
I JUST FEEL LIKE...
LIGHT REFLECTS ALL
SORTS OF STUFF BEHIND US.
- I'M NOT SCARED.
YOU KNOW WHY?
'CAUSE I'M WITH YOU,
RENTON.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- HEY, WAKE UP!
HEY, RENTON!
- MAMA, LOOK!
- RIGHT THERE!
- RENTON!
- WAIT A MINUTE.
I THOUGHT WE ENTERED
THE ZONE.
- IT'S A... TREMENDOUSLY
LARGE TUNNEL.
- I DON'T GET IT.
WHERE ARE WE?
- Woman: TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Narrator: THE BOYS AND GIRLS
ALL WANDER INTO
A NEW WORLD.
ALL OF THEM TRY
TO STEP FORWARD
IN SEARCH
OF A PLACE TO GO.
NEXT EPISODE,
"THE SUNSHINE UNDERGROUND."