- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Ageha Member #1: WHEN
ORANGE ZERO TWO WAS TEST-FIRING,
IT SEEMS THAT THE END
CAME IN CONTACT
WITH A typeZERO VERSION, TOO.
I APOLOGIZE FOR THE LATENESS
OF THIS REPORT.
- Dewey:
YOU SHOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
WITH THE SITUATION
BEING WHAT IT WAS.
- BUT WHAT ARE THEY PLANNING?
WHAT DO THEY WANT
WITH A VODARAC PRIEST,
AND WHY DID THEY TAKE HIM?
- NO NEED TO WORRY.
IT'S PERFECTLY CLEAR TO ME
WHAT THEY'RE ATTEMPTING TO DO.
THERE'S ONLY ONE PLACE
THAT THE GEKKO COULD BE HEADED.
OF COURSE, IT WOULD BE
BEST IF WE LOCATED
THE CENTRAL CORALIAN CORE
BEFORE THEY CAUSE
ANY MORE SITUATIONS.
BUT TO DO THAT,
WE NEED TO INCREASE
THE LANDING POINTS
OF THE ORANGE A BIT MORE.
I DON'T WANT TO SHED MORE BLOOD
THAN IS ABSOLUTELY NECESSARY.
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT, HOLLAND.
- ALL SECTIONS ARE
READY FOR DEPARTURE, SIR.
WE CAN BE UNDERWAY AS SOON
AS YOU GIVE THE COMMAND.
- Ageha Member #1:
WHAT WILL YOU DO
ABOUT THE VISITATION SUMMONS?
- CAN YOU RELAY A MESSAGE
TO THEM FOR ME?
TELL THEM THAT WHEN THE
TIME COMES, I WILL VISIT THEM.
SO I WISH FOR THEM TO HOLD OFF
ON THAT REQUEST FOR A WHILE.
- Holland:
RENTON IS EUREKA'S PARTNER.
YOU ALREADY ADMITTED TO THAT,
AND THAT'S THE REASON
WHY YOU DECIDED TO COME WITH US
HERE ON THE GEKKO, RIGHT?
WE GATHERED UP THE CHESS PIECES,
WHAT DO WE DO NEXT?
HOW DO EUREKA AND RENTON GET
TO CROSS OVER THE GREAT WALL?
- DO YOU GOT ANY MORE?
- THAT'S ALL YOU GET RIGHT NOW.
- RIGHT.  HIT ME, OKAY.
- I DON'T SMOKE.
BY THE WAY, THIS ROOM
IS NON-SMOKING.
- FOR STARTERS,
I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU TOOK ME BACK
TO THE VODARAC PALACE.
- THE VODARAC PALACE,
YOU MEAN YOUR HEADQUARTERS?
- ( snoring )
- ARE THOSE TWO
DRAWN TO EACH OTHER
FROM THEIR DEEPEST HEARTS?
THEN WE NEED TO HURRY UP.
- ( snoring )
- Renton: NO!
POOR THING, LOOK
AT THE BIG SCRATCH HE GOT.
AND WE JUST IMPROVED
ALL THE SPECS, TOO.
- SCRATCHES ARE... BAD?
- UM, WELL I GUESS
YOU REALLY CAN'T HELP
GETTING SCRATCHED UP IN BATTLE.
BUT IT'S BETTER TO HAVE IT
NICE AND SMOOTH.
GREAT!
IT'S BACK AS GOOD AS NEW.
SEE, I'M SURE NIRVASH
IS HAPPY ABOUT IT, TOO.
YOU CAN HEAR HIM, CAN'T YOU?
EUREKA?
WANT TO HANG OUT
ONCE IN A WHILE?
- Gidget:
DOES IT BOTHER YOU?
YOU CAN HIDE IT
EASILY WITH CONCEALER.
- CONCEALER?
- OH, YEAH.  YOU'VE NEVER HAD
TO WEAR ANY MAKEUP BEFORE.
YOU'RE LUCKY.
- WHY DO YOU WEAR MAKEUP?
- I CAN'T IMAGINE LIFE
WITHOUT MAKEUP.
BECAUSE IT MAKES ME
LOOK PRETTIER.
DOGGIE'S HAPPY
WHEN I LOOK PRETTY.
- IF YOU BECOME
PRETTY WITH MAKEUP,
DOGGIE GETS REALLY HAPPY?
- MM-HMM.  IF I DON'T
WEAR MAKEUP,
HIS ATTITUDE TOWARDS ME
GETS DIFFERENT.
- LIKE RENTON.
HE GOT VERY HAPPY, TOO,
WHEN THE NIRVASH GOT PRETTIER.
- SO, WHAT?  NOW I'M AN LFO?
- GIDGET?
- HM?
- CAN YOU PUT MAKEUP ON ME, TOO?
I WANT TO BE PRETTY LIKE YOU.
- Holland: RENTON.
- Renton: YES?
- WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG,
YOU HID YOUR SISTER'S SHOES
TO MESS WITH HER, DIDN'T YOU?
- WHY DID YOU ASK THAT?
- YOU REALLY GOT IN THE WAY
OF OUR VERY FIRST DATE.
THOUGH IT WAS STILL MEMORABLE.
I WANT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING--
YOUR SISTER, SHE WAS
MY FIRST LOVE.
- IT WOULD HAVE BEEN MUCH BETTER
IF I COULD HAVE LENT YOU MINE.
BUT YOUR SKIN'S MUCH DIFFERENT.
NOW, YOUR HAND.
- GIDGET, I--
- DON'T WORRY.
THIS COVERS REALLY WELL,
SO I THINK IT'LL DO JUST FINE.
- BUT I DON'T HAVE
THAT MUCH MONEY, GIDGET.
I CAN'T BUY IT.
- JUST PUT IT ON RENTON'S TAB.
- HIS WHAT?
- YEAH, WHY NOT?
I MEAN, YOU'RE DOING THIS
TO MAKE HIM HAPPY, RIGHT?
- I JUST WONDER
IF HE'LL LIKE IT.
- Holland: IT WAS BEFORE
YOU WERE BORN, I GUESS,
BACK WHEN I WAS TWELVE.
THE FIRST TIME THAT I MET DIANE
WAS AT BOLNATA MILITARY BASE.
THANKS TO ADROC, WE WERE ABLE
TO GO IN AND OUT FREELY.
THAT HILL ALWAYS HAD
A GOOD WAVE COMING IN.
WHEN I COULD, I WOULD RUSH OVER
TO MY SECRET SPOT TO PRACTICE.
NOBODY ELSE WAS EVER THERE
OTHER THAN ME.
OH, DAMN.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
THAT'S QUITE A BUMP.
I BET YOUR FOREHEAD
REALLY HURTS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- DAD DOES THAT TO ME.
WHENEVER I GET HURT,
OR FEEL BAD, OR WANT TO CRY.
- WHAT?  HOW THE HELL
DID YOU GET OUT HERE?
YOU'RE IN THE WAY.
GO SOMEWHERE ELSE.
- Holland:
I HEARD LATER ON THAT ADROC
HAD BROUGHT DIANE WITH HIM,
AFTER MUCH COAXING.
AND THAT SHE TENDED TO
COOP HERSELF UP
INSIDE THE HOUSE ALL THE TIME.
THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME
SHE'D COME OUT TO THAT SPOT.
SHE NEVER WENT BACK AGAIN.
AND RIGHT UP UNTIL
THE NEXT TIME WE MET,
I THOUGHT SHE HATED ME.
EVEN AFTER THE MILITARY
ANNOUNCED ADROC'S DEATH,
THEY KEPT DOING RESEARCH
ON THE DATA AND ITEMS
THAT HE LEFT BEHIND.
IT WOULD TAKE SEVERAL YEARS
BEFORE IT WAS ALL OVER.
- SOMEONE THERE?
DIANE!
DO YOU REMEMBER ME?
WE MET JUST ONCE
AT THE LIFT SPOT
OVER AT BOLNATA.
YOUR DAD'S BELONGINGS
ARE WITH THE COMMANDER.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD WAS
MY FATHER TRYING TO PROVE HERE?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT HIM.
WE LIVED TOGETHER
FOR SIXTEEN YEARS,
AND I KNOW NOTHING.
- ADROC'S RESEARCH DATA
IS ONLY OPEN
TO A SMALL PORTION
OF THE MILITARY.
- I SEE.
WHAT CAN I DO TO FIND OUT
MORE ABOUT IT?
PLEASE, HOLLAND.
I REMEMBER HOW WONDERFUL IT WAS
WATCHING YOU LIFTING.
- IF I CAN BE
OF ANY HELP, I WILL.
- CALL ME LATER.
- Gidget:
YOU GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I WANT
TO DO IT MYSELF.
- RIGHT.  WELL, GOOD LUCK!
- Holland: UNTIL THEN, I THOUGHT
THAT MAKING PHONE CALLS
WAS SOMETHING THAT WOMEN
WERE SUPPOSED TO DO.
OH, HI, DIANE!
IT'S UH-- ME, HOLLAND, CALLING.
- THERE'S NO ONE HERE
BY THAT NAME.
- ( phone clicks )
EXCUSE ME, AM I SPEAKING
WITH DIANE'S GRANDFATHER?
- THE NUMBER YOU HAVE DIALED
IS NO LONGER IN SERVICE.
AND THERE IS NO
NEW NUMBER, SORRY.
- ( phone clicks )
- ( knocking )
- HEY, WAKE UP.
YOU GOT A CALL FROM BELLFOREST.
AND IT'S A GIRL.
- ( dance music playing )
- Holland: SOUTHERN.
NO, WAIT--
TATSURO WOULD SET
A MUCH BETTER MOOD.
- I'M SO SORRY,
MY LITTLE BROTHER
HID MY SHOES ON THE WAY OUT.
- IDIOT! UGLY!
I'M GOING TO TELL GRANDPA
ABOUT THIS WHEN HE GETS BACK!
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
- DON'T BE.
- YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D ACTUALLY COME HERE.
- I WAS A LITTLE SURPRISED
YOU WERE OPTING
FOR THE MILITARY LABORATORIES.
I WISH I COULD HAVE BEEN THERE
TO CONGRATULATE YOU.
- IT'S 'CAUSE YOU RECOMMENDED
ME TO YOUR BROTHER, HOLLAND.
THANK YOU, FOR EVERYTHING.
- WELL...
- I'M SO HAPPY, HOLLAND!
I'M REALLY HAPPY ABOUT THIS.
- UH, WHAT IS IT?
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- UM, AN INTERVIEW?
- YEAH, I MEAN,
ISN'T INFORMATION PHYSICS
SOMETHING NEW?
- NO, IT'S JUST
THAT YOU'RE IGNORANT.
BUT IF YOU THINK
YOU'RE UP TO IT--
RIGHT, MY SWEET LITTLE CUB?
- IT WOULD BE BEST IF WE COULD
DO IT IN THE CONTEXT
OF A TALK WITH MASTER NORB.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- GOT IT!
- Holland:
I WAS CRAZY ABOUT HER.
I BELIEVED FROM THE BOTTOM
OF MY HEART, THAT SOME DAY,
WE'D BE TOGETHER.  BUT--
I SHOULD HAVE REALIZED IT.
THAT HER EYES WERE FIXED
ON SOMETHING ELSE.
STARING AT SOMETHING
OTHER THAN ME.
- Diane:
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
I'M DOING MY BEST, OKAY?
THERE'S ONLY A LITTLE BIT MORE.
- ( door slams )
- THAT'S ENOUGH, DIANE!
ENOUGH!
- WHY ARE YOU MAD?
ALL I'M DOING IS TRYING TO PROVE
WHAT IT IS MY FATHER DISCOVERED.
- I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
I'M JUST SAYING THAT THIS
IS GETTING UNHEALTHY.
- IT'S ALL BECAUSE
I CAN'T GUIDE MYSELF
TO THE RIGHT EQUATION.
TO THE FACT THAT THE SCUBS
ACTUALLY WANT
TO COMMUNICATE WITH US.
- OH, YEAH?
WELL THE SCUBS CAN BITE ME!
ADROC WAS KILLED
IN THAT EXPERIMENT.
HE WAS POSSESSED BY SCUBS,
AND HE DIED!
DO YOU WANT TO FOLLOW
IN HIS FOOTSTEPS?
- YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
LIVING IN A WORLD LIKE THIS,
WE COULD NEVER
HOPE TO UNDERSTAND.
RIGHT, HOLLAND?
- Holland: THAT WAS THE LAST
TIME I LOOKED INTO DIANE'S EYES.
AFTER THAT,
I NEVER SAW HER AGAIN.
ADROC HAD PASSED AWAY.
AND DIANE HAD DISAPPEARED.
RENTON, YOU'RE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE, ARE YOU?
AS LONG AS I'M IN REACH OF YOU,
I SWEAR THAT I WILL PROTECT
YOU AND EUREKA, ALL RIGHT?
- HOLLAND...
I'M REALLY HAPPY
ABOUT HOW YOU FEEL.
BUT HOLLAND,
THAT'S A BIT TOUGH ON ME.
YOU SEE, I DON'T
WANT YOU GOING OUT
AND KILLING ANY MORE PEOPLE.
LOOK, IT'S NOT THAT I THINK
I HAVE THE RIGHT
TO SAY THIS ANYMORE,
BUT EVEN THE PEOPLE WHO DIED
FOR OUR SAKE HAVE PEOPLE
WHO THINK DEARLY OF THEM.
AND HURT FROM THEIR LOSS.
EUREKA FEELS
EXACTLY THE SAME WAY.
ACTUALLY, THINGS HAVE BEEN
MUCH TOUGHER ON HER
THAN THEY'VE BEEN FOR ME.
BECAUSE EUREKA CAN
ALSO FEEL THE HEARTS
OF ALL THE MACHINES
THAT HAVE BEEN BROKEN.
- YOU KNOW THAT, TOO.
DON'T YOU, HOLLAND?
- WHAT I KNOW, IS THAT EUREKA
DOESN'T REALLY THINK
THAT MACHINES HAVE
HEARTS AT ALL.
- BUT, WHAT ABOUT--
- PERHAPS IT'S TRUE THAT SHE CAN
TALK HEART-TO-HEART
WITH THE ARCHETYPES THAT WERE
MADE FROM SCUBS, JUST LIKE HER.
BUT MACHINES MADE BY HUMANS
ARE SOMETHING ELSE.
- THEN WHY DID EUREKA SAY
THAT SHE COULD HEAR
THE MACHINE'S VOICES?
- BECAUSE SHE SAW IMAGES
OF SCUBS ON THEM.
IF YOU ARRIVED AS A CLEAN SLATE
WITH NOTHING ON IT
AND WERE THROWN
INTO A GROUP OF BEINGS
THAT WERE
OF A DIFFERENT SPECIES,
WOULD YOU REALLY BE ABLE
TO OPEN YOUR HEART
AND INTERACT WITH THEM?
EUREKA CAME
INTO THIS WORLD ALONE,
AND SOUGHT A PLACE
WHERE SHE COULD BELONG.
EVEN WITH MACHINES
THAT SPOKE NO WORDS.
EUREKA JUST COULDN'T
ACCEPT HUMAN BEINGS.
UNTIL SHE MET YOU.
- ME?
- THAT'S RIGHT, YOU.
I CAN'T CHANGE THE WAY
THAT I FIGHT.
HUNDREDS OF GALLONS OF BLOOD
FROM ALL THE PEOPLE
I'VE KILLED IN THE PAST
HAVE SEEPED INTO THIS BODY.
EVEN IF I WERE TO CHANGE NOW,
THEY WOULDN'T FORGIVE ME.
BUT YOU CAN STILL TURN BACK,
YOU HAVE TIME.
YOU NEED TO GO AHEAD WITH THE
COMBAT STYLE YOU BELIEVE IN.
SHOW EVERYONE A COMBAT STYLE
I COULDN'T GET AWAY WITH.
I'M PUTTING MY TRUST
IN YOU, RENTON.
TAKE CARE OF EUREKA,
AND MAKE HER HAPPY.
- I WILL, HOLLAND.
- SO, HOW FAR
HAVE YOU GOTTEN WITH HER?
- WHAT?
- HAVE YOU AT LEAST
KISSED HER YET?
- NOTHING LIKE THAT!
- BE HONEST ABOUT IT.
TELL ME OR YOU DON'T GET OUT.
- BUT I'M TELLING THE TRUTH.
- OUT WITH IT, DAMN IT!
- Hap: YOU WERE SOAKING
UNTIL YOU GOT DIZZY?
- HEY, WHERE'S STONER?
HE'S GOT TO GET
SOME PICTURES OF THIS.
- OH, HONESTLY.
WHAT WERE YOU TWO THINKING?
- CALL EVERYONE OVER.
YOU DON'T GET TO SEE
HOLLAND MAKING A FOOL
OUT OF HIMSELF VERY OFTEN.
- YEAH, VERY FUNNY.
- Renton:
I FINALLY HEARD IT.
THE WHOLE STORY
ABOUT YOUR VERY FIRST LOVE.
- JUST KEEP IT QUIET
FROM MATTHIEU.
- Eureka: RENTON.
- EUREKA?
- HOW...
IS IT?
- Gidget: EUREKA...
- ( children crying )
- WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR FACE?
- Gidget: RENTON!
WHAT ARE YOU JUST SITTING
THERE FOR?
HURRY UP AND GO AFTER HER!
- OH, RIGHT.  EUREKA!
- VERY NAUGHTY.
- YEAH, ROUGE MAGIC.
- OH, NO.
THEY'VE LOST IT NOW.
- WILL EVERYBODY JUST SHUT UP?!
- DID THE KIDS
PULL A PRANK ON YOU?
WELL THEN WHO DID
THIS HORRIBLE THING?
WHAT HAPPENED EUREKA?
LET ME HELP YOU WIPE IT OFF.
HEY, COME ON.
I WANT TO SEE.
- WHO CARES?!
- HEY, WHY ARE YOU
MAD AT ME?
- LET GO!
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
YOU, EUREKA!
- EARLIER TODAY
GIDGET TOLD ME,
IF I WORE SOME MAKEUP
I WOULD BE PRETTY.
I MEAN, I REALLY WANTED
YOU TO SEE ME
LOOKING ALL PRETTY
AND STUFF, RENTON.
I WANTED YOU TO BE HAPPY.
RENTON!
- OW.
- OH, RENTON,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- EUREKA.
- I WANT TO TELL YOU,
HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
I LOOK STRANGE.
- NO YOU DON'T.
YOU'RE REALLY PRETTY.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE NOT
WEARING ALL THAT MAKEUP.
YOU SEE, I--
EUREKA, I--
I LOVE YOU.
MS. TALHO.
- EUREKA, COME WITH ME.
AT YOUR AGE,
YOU DON'T NEED MUCH MAKEUP.
JUST A LITTLE BIT WILL DO.
THERE, ALL DONE.
- ( gasps )
- DO YOU WANT THIS?
HERE, IT'S YOURS.
BE ON YOUR GUARD THOUGH.
THERE'S A LOT
OF SMOOTH-TALKING GUYS OUT THERE
AND THEY'RE ALWAYS LOOKING
FOR A PRETTY GIRL
THAT THEY CAN SEDUCE
AND HAVE THEIR WAY WITH.
- SO YOU REALLY HAVEN'T?
- NO, WE HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
NOT YET.
- Dewey: I WAS WORRIED
ABOUT YOU, ANEMONE.
I HEARD THAT YOU
WERE TERRIBLY HURT
IN THE FIGHT YOU HAD
AGAINST typeZERO.
- IT'S NOT TRUE!
I WAS JUST CAUGHT
OFF GUARD, THAT'S ALL!
WAIT UNTIL THE NEXT TIME
I SEE THEM.
- SORRY TO TELL YOU THIS,
BUT PLAYING WITH THEM
WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN
FOR A WHILE.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE
AN ENTIRELY NEW MISSION.
IT'S A VERY IMPORTANT ONE.
AND I THINK YOU ARE THE ONLY
PERSON I CAN TRUST WITH IT.
- COLONEL, I MUST ADVISE YOU
THAT ANEMONE IS
IN DESPERATE NEED OF A VACATION.
THE DOCTOR HAS EVEN--
- I'M TOTALLY FINE,
I CAN GO!
LET ME GO, PLEASE.
DEWEY?
- I'M COUNTING ON YOU NOW.
MY SWEET ANEMONE.
- Eureka and Renton:
TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Talho:
WITH THE CROSSING OF TWO IDEAS
FROM OPPOSITE ENDS,
THE TRUTH ABOUT THE WORLD
STARTS TO COME OUT
INTO THE OPEN.
HOWEVER, IN THE WORLD
SWAYING UNEASILY,
A FALSE STORY IS BORN.
NEXT EPISODE--
"RAISE YOUR HAND."