- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
- ♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
- ♪ COME ON ♪
- ♪ IT'S GAME OVER ♪
- ♪ WE WANT TO MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE ♪
- ♪ BACK IN THE DAYS ♪
- ♪ YOU GOT TO REMEMBER ♪
- ♪ COME ON ♪
- THIS IS ROLF 03,
WE'VE ARRIVED AT THE
RENDEZVOUS POINT, A-557. OVER.
- THIS IS TEOS 01.
COORDINATES CONFIRMED.
ENTRY ANGLE IS GOOD.
PROCEED TO YOUR POSITIONS.
- ( humming )
- WHOA! WHOA!
- AMAZING! IT'S LIKE IT'S ALIVE!
- ( giggles ) YEAH,
IT'S PRETTY FUNNY.
SO YOU GUYS NEVER PLAYED AROUND
WITH STUFF LIKE THIS BEFORE?
- NEVER!
- I LIKE IT! DO IT
AGAIN! DO IT AGAIN!
- ( giggles )
OH, ALL RIGHT.
- HURRY! HURRY!
- GIDGET, DO YOU KNOW...
- UH, DO I KNOW WHAT?
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT LOVE IS?
- UH, WHAT?
- THE OTHER DAY YOU MENTIONED
THAT IT MUST BE LOVE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT LOVE IS.
- HMM, WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT'S LIKE...
RIGHT! IT MEANS THAT
YOU "LIKE" SOMEONE.
- LIKE?
LIKE.
BUT WHY? WE WERE
ALWAYS TOGETHER BEFORE!
PLEASE.
YOU WANT RENTON TO BE
IN THE COCKPIT, TOO, DON'T YOU?
( groans )
- HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU SHOULDN'T
PUSH YOURSELF SO HARD!
IT'S BETTER IF YOU JUST WAIT!
HOLLAND SAID THAT HE WOULD
BRING HIM BACK, RIGHT?
- MMM-HMM.
- EVEN IF HE WENT TO GEARNUS,
THE NEAREST CITY TO HERE,
IT'LL STILL GOING TO TAKE
A LITTLE BIT OF TIME.
- GEARNUS?
- YEAH. IT'S THE ONLY DECENT
CITY IN THIS WHOLE AREA.
EITHER TO WORK, OR TO LIVE.
- HEY, MAMA,
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- CAN YOU FIX THIS, MAMA?
RENTON MADE THIS
FOR US A WHILE AGO.
I CAN'T GET IT TO MOVE ANYMORE,
NO MATTER WHAT.
- WE WERE THINKING OF
ASKING RENTON TO FIX IT,
BUT HE'S NOT COMING
BACK ANYMORE!
- HEY, MAMA? IS RENTON
EVER COMING BACK HOME?
- ( gasps ) I DON'T KNOW.
- MAYBE HE'S NOT COMING BACK.
- MAURICE.
- YOU'RE KIDDING.
- HE'S COMING BACK, YOU'LL SEE!
- HOW ABOUT IT, MAMA?
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HOLLAND SAID THAT
HE WOULD BRING
HIM BACK HERE.
- REALLY?
- YES. AND HAS HOLLAND EVER
BROKEN A PROMISE TO US?
- YEAH. RIGHT?
- YEAH! A LOT OF TIMES!
- HE BREAKS MORE PROMISES
THAN HE KEEPS.
- THE OTHER DAY HE SAID TO ME
THAT HE WAS GOING TO
BUY ME LOTS AND LOTS
OF NEW CLOTHES!
- IT'S OKAY. 'CAUSE HOLLAND
HAS NEVER ONCE
BROKEN A PROMISE TO YOUR MAMA.
I'M SURE IT WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
- THIS IS CANTO 03.
WE'VE ARRIVED AT THE
RENDEZVOUS AREA. OVER.
- THIS IS TEOS 01.
YOUR COORDINATES ARE CONFIRMED.
HOLD YOUR POSITION AND STAND BY
FOR ORDERS FROM THE FLAGSHIP.
- ROGER THAT!
- ( beeping )
- HUH? THE 606?
- HOLLAND? WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
HE'S SUDDENLY GOING OFF
WITHOUT TELLING ANYONE?
- THERE'S GOT TO BE A REASON
WHY HE COULDN'T TELL US.
TALHO! OPEN UP THE HATCHES!
- WE'RE CHANGING DIRECTION.
- BECAUSE OF THE ARMY?
- NO.
- HMM?
- CHARLES AND RAY ARE COMING.
THEY'VE HOOKED UP
WITH THE STATE ARMY.
HOWEVER, THEY HAVEN'T
COMPLETED THE BARRICADE YET.
RIGHT NOW, I THINK WE CAN BARELY
SQUEEZE BY AT JACKSON 286.
- RIGHT. GOT IT.
- WE GOT TO HURRY.
- AW, DAMMIT.
- WAIT.
- HUH?
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO ABOUT RENTON?
- A RUNAWAY BOY OR THE GEKKO?
EVEN A LITTLE KID SHOULD
UNDERSTAND WHICH COMES FIRST.
THEN, I GUESS
YOU ARE LOWER THAN A LITTLE KID.
- MATTHIEU, WHERE'S EUREKA?
- I, UH...
I THINK SHE'S IN HER ROOM.
- SHE'S NOT HERE.
- ( door opens )
- EUREKA.
- ( gasps )
- WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- ( groans )
- SO, IS THAT RENTON'S?
- HAVE YOU FOUND HIM?
- I'M SORRY, BUT WE'RE
CHANGING COURSE TO I-709.
- WHAT ABOUT GEARNUS CITY?
- WE CAN REPLENISH
SUPPLIES AT KALZAS.
WE'RE FACING CHARLES NOW.
THOSE GUYS...
- BUT WHY?
- BECAUSE CHARLES AND RAY HAVE
HOOKED UP WITH THE STATE ARMY.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN!
YOU SAID YOU WERE
GOING TO GEARNUS!
THAT YOU WERE GOING TO GO
AND BRING RENTON BACK
TO THE GEKKO! WHY AREN'T YOU?
- LOOK, IT CAN'T BE HELPED!
THE GEKKO ITSELF IS IN DANGER!
- BUT YOU FACED HUNDREDS
OF MILITARY GUYS
IN THE PAST AND BEAT THEM!
- WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
CHARLES HERE!
AND YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT!
( exhales )
- DO YOU REALLY HATE RENTON
THAT MUCH, HOLLAND?
- I DON'T HATE HIM. IT'S JUST
THAT HE ACTS LIKE A BRAT.
- THAT'S WHY
YOU LEFT HIM BEHIND?
THAT'S WHY YOU PUNCHED HIM?
THAT'S WHY YOU KICKED HIM, TOO?
- THAT'S NOT IT. I JUST...
I...
YOU WERE MORE IMPORTANT
TO ME THAN RENTON, THAT'S ALL.
- WELL, I...
I JUST DON'T FEEL THAT WAY.
- ( door closes )
- STRENGTH IN NUMBERS.
HUH, HOW REASSURING.
- BUT WITH HIM AS THE COMMANDER
I JUST DON'T KNOW.
- HEY, HE'LL HEAR THAT!
- I AM THE FLEET COMMANDER,
MY NAME IS MOALUTDAR.
- LONG TIME NO SEE.
WE ARE HERE WITH
THE FEDERAL ARMY RESERVE UNIT,
CHARLES BEAMS REPORTING.
- IT'S TRULY A CATASTROPHE.
IF IT WAS ONLY 20 KILOMETERS
MORE TO THE SOUTH,
KALZAS CITY'S WOULD'VE
HAD THE PROBLEM.
SO, IS HE REALLY
GOING TO SHOW UP, BEAMS?
- THE BARRICADE
I ASKED YOU TO MAKE,
HAS A SLIGHT OPENING IN IT.
ON THE JACKSON MAP, PAGE 286.
- WON'T HE TRY TO
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT?
- WE'RE GOING TO
MAKE HIM TAKE IT.
I KNOW THIS GUY WELL,
HE WOULDN'T MISS THIS CHANCE.
THERE'S NO QUESTION,
HE'LL SHOW UP ALRIGHT.
- HEADING I-709. WE'RE GOING TO
GET AWAY FROM THIS AIRSPACE.
- YOU'RE SURE ABOUT THIS?
- IT'S ONLY A MOMENTARY EXIT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- I'LL ASK YOU ONE MORE TIME.
YOU'RE REALLY SURE ABOUT THIS?
- YEAH. I'M REALLY SURE.
- NIRVASH WON'T MOVE FOR ME.
AND I CAN'T COUNT ON HOLLAND.
THAT MEANS I...
I HAVE TO GO MYSELF!
RENTON WAS THE ONE THAT
ALWAYS STARTED THINGS OFF.
BUT THIS TIME...
( gasps )
- HELLO. CARE FOR TEA?
- PLEASE! PLEASE, WAIT FOR ME,
RENTON! WAIT FOR ME!
- JACKSON 286.
JUST LIKE CHARLES SAID.
WAIT FOR ME, EUREKA!
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE!
- HEY, HOLD ON
A SECOND, KIDDIES.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO MY REF BOARD,
I HAD IT RIGHT HERE?
- NO, I DON'T KNOW.
- I DON'T KNOW, ETHER.
- ME NEITHER!
- HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
( gasps )
- ( all gasp )
- IT'S PUKEY! IT'S PUKEY!
IT'S RENTON!
- BOOSTERS AT FULL IGNITION,
MAXIMUM THROTTLE!
KEEP GOING UNTIL
WE'RE OUT OF HERE!
- ROGER THAT.
- HEY, HAP,
YOU GOT TO STAY ON TOP OF
THE TRAPAR VALUE READINGS!
- YEAH, I KNOW.
WHAT ABOUT LAUNCH
PREPARATIONS FOR THE LFO'S?
- NO NEED! EVERYONE
JUST CONCENTRATE
ON THE GEKKO ESCAPING
FROM HERE AT FULL SPEED!
- WELL, THIS IS GOOD TIMING.
LOOK WHO JUST WANDERED
BACK IN, HOLLAND!
- WHO KNOWS WHERE THE HELL
HE'S BEEN ALL THIS TIME.
- HEY!
- RENTON!
- THE RETURN OF
THE PRODIGAL SON!
- GO ON, APOLOGIZE TO HIM.
YOU CAUSED HIM A LOT OF TROUBLE!
- HEY, MATTHIEU.
WHAT IS HE DOING UP HERE?
TAKE HIM TO THE BACK.
WE'RE BUSY RIGHT NOW.
- DON'T BEG FOR THIS,
DO IT YOURSELF.
OR ELSE YOU WON'T GET ANYTHING.
TELL ME MR. ADROC,
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE ALL OF US SEEKING HERE?
- FLAGSHIP COMMAND
CALLING ALL SHIPS!
THIS FLEET HAS ENTERED
THE SEA OF RAINBOW CLOUDS.
50 KILOMETERS TO
OPERATIONAL DESTINATION.
- HOLLAND, I FOUND
OUT THAT THE GEKKO
IS ABOUT TO COME UNDER...
- WHAT ARE YOU THINKING
BY COMING BACK HERE LIKE THIS?
I DON'T REMEMBER
GIVING YOU PERMISSION
TO COME BACK ABOARD THIS SHIP!
WELL?
- COME ON, HOLLAND,
LET'S BE HONEST, OKAY?
YOU KNOW THAT RENTON IS...
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
- I DIDN'T COME BACK.
- HUH?
- I'M NOT INTERESTED
ONE BIT IN BECOMING
A CREW MEMBER
HERE ON THE GEKKO AGAIN.
I'M NOT EVEN HERE BECAUSE
I THINK THAT, I MIGHT BENEFIT.
I CAME FOR...
EUREKA.
I CAME HERE JUST TO SEE EUREKA!
- HUH.
- ( whistles )
- ( gasps )
- SO, YOU'VE LEARNED
HOW TO TALK BIG.
- ( chuckles )
- 30 MORE KILOMETERS
TO GEARNUS CITY.
IF I CAN RIDE WELL, I CAN MAKE
IT THERE IN LESS THAN TWO HOURS.
A SWARM OF SKY FISH.
PRETTY.
( gasps ) IT'S THE STATE ARMY!
- HEY, CHARLES, COME IN.
CHARLES!
- YEAH, YEAH.
I CAN HEAR YOU JUST FINE, RAY.
- I'M GOING IN.
YOU BETTER PREPARE FOR LAUNCH!
- HEY, THE OPERATION ISN'T
SCHEDULED TO START YET.
WE DON'T NEED TO HURRY.
- BUT EUREKA IS MOVING TOWARD US
AND SHE'S ALL BY HERSELF!
- NOW, THAT'S
A GOOD REASON TO HURRY.
- GEKKO! CAN YOU HEAR ME, GEKKO?
- WHAT? WHAT WAS
THAT COMMUNICATION?
HELLO? COME IN.
- A-307, A BIG FLEET OF THE
STATE ARMY APPROACHING. HURRY!
- HELLO? HELLO?
- WHO WAS IT?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
THE NOISE WAS REALLY BAD.
BUT IT'S A VOICE
I'M SURE I RECOGNIZE.
( gasps )
I THINK IT COULD BE EUREKA.
- Both: EUREKA?
- THEY'RE SHOOTING AT ME!
THE COMMUNICATOR!
( gasps )
- THE STATE ARMY?
- YEAH! THAT'S WHAT SHE SAID
IN THE LAST COMMUNICATION!
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
THE RADAR DIDN'T SHOW
ANY SIGNS OF A LARGE FLEET!
- BUT, SHE SAID THAT
THE FLEET WAS AT A-307!
- THE SEA OF RAINBOW CLOUDS!
THE COORDINATES
ARE AT THE CENTER OF
THE SEA OF RAINBOW CLOUDS!
BECAUSE OF THE UNIQUE TRAPAR
TURBULENCE IN THAT AREA,
THE RADAR SIGNAL IS REFLECTING
BACK TO US IN A DEFUSED MANOR,
- HE'S USING NATURAL COMPAC
INTERFERENCE TO HIDE.
( grunts ) DAMN CHARLES!
- I'VE GOT SOMETHING!
- I DON'T GET IT.
WHICH ONE OF THOSE IS--?
- GIVE ME A SECOND!
- Both: AN OUTSIDE LINE?
- IT'S EUREKA!
- IT'S IN THE SEA OF CLOUDS.
SHE'S USING A
POCKET COMMUNICATOR.
- OH! THE REF BOARD I LEFT
IN THE DINING HALL!
EUREKA WAS PROBABLY
THE ONE THAT TOOK IT.
- ( grunts )
YOU WAIT TILL NOW
TO REALIZE THAT?
HEY! WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- Charles: RAY,
DON'T DO ANYTHING HARSH
BEFORE I DO, OKAY!
- Ray: I WAS
JUST INTIMIDATING HER.
I WASN'T GOING TO
HIT HER OR ANYTHING.
- Charles: WELL THEN, HOW ABOUT
WE PLAY OUR USUAL GAME?
- ( giggles ) OH, CHARLES,
I LOVE YOU!
- EUREKA! EUREKA!
EUREKA! EUREKA!
( panting )
NIRVASH.
NIRVASH, LET'S GO!
- HOLD STILL, WILL YA?
- WHERE IS HE?
( gasps )
- WHAT... WHAT WAS THAT?
HEY, RAY! THE MERMAID
HAS JUMPED INTO THE BUCKET!
LET'S KEEP HER THAT WAY.
MAKE SURE THE HATCH IS OPEN.
- ROGER!
- ( grunting )
( groans )
NO!
( screams )
- OH, NO!
GODDAMN IT!
- IN, IN THE END, I COULDN'T
EVEN KEEP ONE PROMISE.
I'M SORRY, MAETER,
LINCK, MAURICE.
I'M SORRY, RENTON!
- TEOS 01 HAS JUST
BEEN SHOT DOWN!
- WHO DID IT?
WHERE DID THEY SHOOT FROM?
- FROM JACKSON 103!
I PRETTY SURE IT'S THE GEKKO!
- THIS IS NOT THE WAY
WE PLANNED IT!
ALL SHIPS PREPARE
FOR BATTLE IMMEDIATELY!
- WE'LL USE THE SEA
OF CLOUDS AS A SHIELD!
TALHO! MAKE SURE YOU KEEP THOSE
BOOSTERS IGNITED, ALRIGHT?
- THEY CAN BE FIRED UP
AT ANY TIME!
- HAP! CONTINUE WITH
THE LAUNCH PREP!
TELL MATTHIEU AND HILDA
TO GO AND PICK UP EUREKA!
- ROGER THAT!
- CHANGE IN OPERATIONS!
THE GEKKO HAS APPEARED
IN JACKSON 103!
BEAMS, GET TO YOUR POSITION!
- HANG ON. JUST A LITTLE LONGER!
WHAT WAS THAT?
A WHITE LFO?
- EUREKA!
EUREKA!
- ( gasps ) RENTON!
( gasps )
( groans )
- BEAMS! THE GEKKO IS
ATTACKING US! DO YOU HEAR ME?
- RENTON.
- CHARLES, I...
I'M SURE YOU KNOW THAT I
WISH WE HAD A CHILD.
- YEAH, OF COURSE I KNOW.
I KNOW ALL OF YOUR WISHES.
NOW LET'S GO!
- RENTON! I WAS ABLE
TO DO IT BECAUSE OF YOU.
IT CAN'T BE ANYONE BUT YOU.
RENTON, I...
I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT I...
( gasping )
- YOU WENT OUT OF YOUR WAY
TO DO ALL THIS BY YOURSELF.
AND I'M REAL GLAD.
- I... I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
ALL THIS TIME.
- RENTON.
- ME, TOO.
THERE ARE SO MANY THINGS
I'D LIKE TO TELL YOU.
SO MUCH I WANT TO SHARE.
- WHY? WHY CAN'T I
CATCH UP TO THEM?
THE SPECS OF THIS SHIP SHOULD
BE MUCH BETTER THAN THEIRS!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- IT'S NO GOOD! THE GEKKO'S
MOVED INTO THE SEA OF CLOUDS!
AND I CAN'T GET THEIR POSITION!
- THERE'S NO NEED TO PANIC!
WE'RE DEALING WITH ONE SHIP!
THERE'S NO WAY WE'LL LOSE!
COMMUNICATIONS! WHAT THE HELL
IS BEAMS DOING?
- DAMMIT, WHERE DID THEY GO?
I'M TIRED OF THIS HIDE AND SEEK!
- RENTON, THAT'S...
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
JUST LEAVE IT TO ME.
I'M NOT GOING TO KILL ANYONE!
BUT I'LL MAKE IT
SO THEY CAN'T FIGHT.
- ROLF 01'S RIGHT ARM
HAS BEEN DESTROYED!
AND 03!
AND NOW 02!
THEY'RE ALL DEFENSELESS!
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND!
WHY JUST THE WEAPONS?
- FLYING ALL AROUND
THE BATTLEFIELD
AND SHOWING EVERYONE MERCY.
THAT WILL GET YOU KILLED.
YOU'RE WAY TOO KIND.
- WELCOME BACK.
- HUH?
- THAT'S WHAT NIRVASH
IS SAYING TO YOU.
- HMM, I'M BACK.
SORRY TO LEAVE YOU ALL ALONE.
- ( gasps )
RENTON, YOU JUST SAID "ALONE".
ABOUT THE NIRVASH!
HEY, RENTON.
LET'S DO IT TOGETHER!
- HMM!
- ALL FLEET COMMUNICATION
IS DOWN!
THE REFLECTION FILMS ON
THE SHIPS ARE ALL PEELING OFF!
- WHAT THE HELL DID
THE TYPE ZERO DO?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
IT'S LIKE A GIANT RAINBOW.
RETREAT! HURRY!
- HOLLAND, YOU THINK
THAT THIS IS...
- IT CAN'T BE.
THAT ISN'T A SEVEN SWELL.
THAT TWERP,
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S HIM.
I DON'T WANT TO ADMIT IT.
I CAN'T ADMIT IT!
WHAT IS THIS FEELING
THAT I'M HAVING?
- BOY, THEY SURE KNOW HOW
TO RETREAT AT FULL SPEED.
- THERE'S NOTHING MORE TO DO.
WE SHOULD RETREAT, TOO.
- CHARLES! REALLY?
- COME ON, RAY. WE'RE GOING TO
PULL BACK FOR NOW.
- ROGER!
- THE SON OF THE KING.
DEWEY, IS THAT WHAT
ALL THIS MEANS?
- Eureka: HEY, RENTON.
YOU KNOW, I WAS THINKING ABOUT
ALL SORTS OF THINGS
WHILE YOU WERE GONE.
- Renton: I MET ALL SORTS
OF PEOPLE OUT THERE.
PEOPLE WHO WERE STRANGE,
PEOPLE WHO WERE AMAZING,
PEOPLE WHO WERE SAD.
AND I REALIZED SOMETHING.
I REALIZED WHAT WAS
IMPORTANT TO ME.
- I THINK I REALIZED IT, TOO.
I MEAN, WHAT'S DEAR TO ME.
- ( both gasp )
- SKY FISH!
- THEY REALLY CAME BACK.
HEY, RENTON?
YOU KNOW, I'VE CHANGED.
PEOPLE SAY I'VE CHANGED!
GIDGET AND NIRVASH
BOTH SAID THAT
I'M DIFFERENT FROM
THE WAY I WAS BEFORE.
- I'VE CHANGED A LOT
FROM WHO I WAS, TOO.
EVER SINCE THAT DAY
WHEN YOU FELL INTO MY HOME.
- TELL ME,
I WANT TO HEAR ALL ABOUT IT.
- AND I WANT TO HEAR THE WAYS
THAT YOU'VE CHANGED, EUREKA.
- ( laughing )
I SEE. THAT'S WHAT
IT WAS ABOUT.
I UNDERSTAND NOW, DIANE.
WHAT IT IS
I SHOULD BE DOING NOW!
- WE'RE NEVER GOING TO GIVE UP.
NEVER.
- Both: TO BE CONTINUED!
- Ray: THOSE THAT FIGHT
LAY THEIR LIVES ON THE LINE,
FOR THE SAKE OF THOSE
THEY WISH TO PROTECT.
IN THAT BATTLE,
WHAT WILL THE ONE
WITH FREEDOM ON HIS HANDS,
SHOW THE BOY?
NEXT EPISODE, "HELTER SKELTER."