- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( grunts )
- ( laughs )
WOW, WHAT GREAT REACTION!
I JUST LOVE STUFF LIKE THAT.
AND THAT'S WHY I'M GONNA
HAVE TO KILL YOU.
- ( grunts )
- WHAT IS THIS KLF?
IT LOOKS LIKE THE NIRVASH!
- INTERESTING.  YOU REALLY
LOOK A LOT LIKE THE END.
COME ON, INTRODUCE YOURSELF!
HELLO THERE,
MY CUTE LITTLE LOOK-ALIKE.
DIE FOR ME, OKAY?
- ( gasps )
- COMMENCE BASCUDE CRISIS!
- ( screaming )
- ( grunting )
- MELT AWAY.  MELT AWAY.
YOUR BRAIN'S GONNA MELT AWAY!
- ( grunts )
STOP IT!
- HELP ME.  HELP ME.
HELP ME!
HELP ME, SIS, HELP ME!
- RENTON.
- ( laughing maniacally )
- NO, DON'T.
DON'T LEAVE ME!
- WHAT?
- ( gasps )
I WAS TERRIFIED.
SO TERRIFIED,
I COULDN'T STAND IT.
EVEN SO, IT FELT AS IF THE SCENE
THAT STRETCHED OUT BEFORE ME
WAS SOMETHING
THAT I'D SEEN BEFORE.
BUT AT THE TIME, THE ONLY THING
I WAS CAPABLE OF DOING WAS
TO KEEP ON WATCHING IT.
- WELL, LOOKS LIKE ONCE AGAIN
THE NIRVASH
WAS THE ONLY ONE
TO MAKE IT THROUGH.
MATTHIEU.
MATTHIEU, DO YOU COPY?
MATTHIEU, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- ( groans )
- HEY, MATTHIEU!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE I GOT
TAKEN OUT, BOARD AND ALL,
HOW PATHETIC! ( sighs )
- GET IT TOGETHER.
I MANAGED TO GRAB
SOME GREAT SHOTS.
HURRY, I WANNA GET
THESE DEVELOPED.
- ( alarm blaring )
- HUH?
- MATTHIEU, BEHIND YOU!
- Man: TREMORS
FROM EXPLOSIONS DETECTED.
STARBOARD HEADING 0810,
DISTANCE 18.
ALL MISSILES HAVE BEEN LOST.
- WHERE ARE THE LFO TARGETS?
- WE LOST THEM.
THE TRAPAR INTERFERENCE WAVES
ARE CONFUSING THE MISSILE
GUIDANCE SYSTEMS.
- CAPTAIN JURGENS.
- VISUAL CONFIRMATION
OF THE ENEMY.
- PREPARE TO FIRE THE LASERS.
FOCUS ALL CANNONS TOWARDS
THE CENTER OF THE TARGET.
- TARGET HEADING 0400,
RANGE IS 8,000.  DEPLOY.
- NOW FIRE.
- WE DIDN'T HIT IT, SIR.
THE TRAJECTORY TO LASERS
IS BEING DISTORTED.
- HMM.
THINK IT'LL ANGLE
IN THE SAME DIRECTION?
- PRECURSOR WAVES ARE
DEAD AHEAD.
TRACKING ANTI-SHIP LASERS.
- WHAT?
- WHERE DID IT COME FROM?
- IT CAME CURVING AROUND THE
OUTSIDE OF THE CORALIAN CLOUD.
- NO WAY!
A LASER CAN'T CURVE LIKE THAT.
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED.
DO WE ATTACK THE ENEMY SHIP
OR ARE WE GONNA DIVE IN?
I'VE GOT MY HANDS FULL JUST
KEEPING THIS THING FLYING.
- WE'VE LOST CONTACT
WITH THE NIRVASH.
MENTAL AND VITAL DATA
IS OFFLINE.
- WOZ.
- GIVE ME A SECOND.
THE COMPACT INTERFERENCER
WON'T STABILIZE.
- HEY, GIDGET.
WHERE'S THE NIRVASH NOW?
- ( whimpers )
I CAN'T CONFIRM ITS LOCATION.
- AT THIS RATE, WE WON'T
BE ABLE TO RESCUE THEM,
LET ALONE GET IN OURSELVES.
- ( grumbles )
- CALCULATING LASER
DISTORTION RATE.
- WE'LL RESUME OUR ATTACKS
WHEN THE ANALYSIS IS COMPLETE.
- WE WON'T BE ABLE TO RECEIVE
THE ID CODE FROM THE END.
WE SHOULD PULL BACK NOW.
WE NEED TO REGROUP AND REASSESS.
- AT THIS POINT, WE'VE LOST
EVERY ONE OF OUR KLF UNITS.
WINNING A SHIP-TO-SHIP BATTLE
IS OUR ONLY CHANCE.
- THE PRIORITY SHOULD BE
RETRIEVING THE END.
THE PRIMARY MISSION OBJECTIVE
IS THE MONITORING
OF THE CONNECTION BETWEEN
THE CORALIAN AND ANEMONE.
A BATTLE WITH THAT GROUP IS NOT
SOMETHING WE WANT RIGHT NOW.
- WILL YOU CALM DOWN,
SECOND LIEUTENANT?
- IF WE'RE DEFEATED BEFORE WE
CAN ACT, IT'LL BE THAT GROUP
WHO RETRIEVES THE END, NOT US.
- ( grumbles )
- ( static crackling )
- Anemone: WHO THE HECK ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S GOING ON OVER THERE?
ANEMONE.
- HEY, GIDGET, WHAT ABOUT
HILDA AND MATTHIEU?
- UM... LET'S SEE,
THE 606 IS HALF WRECKED.
OH, BUT WAIT A MINUTE, IT LOOKS
LIKE THE 808 IS RECOVERING.
- WE DON'T NEED
"UMS" OR "BUTS."
- YEAH, BUT WOZ IS HELPING
MISCHA RIGHT NOW,
SO I'M DOING COMMUNICATIONS
AND RADAR.
I CAN'T DO BOTH AT ONCE.
- ( machine beeps )
- OH, CURRENTLY THEY'RE HEADED
BACK THIS WAY.
HEADING IS 0812.
- RIGHT.  LET'S GO PICK 'EM UP.
HEY, KEN-GOH.
ONCE THE LFOs ARE ABOARD,
TAKE US TO DEFCON-1.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU, MAESTRO.
- ROGER THAT.
- HOLLAND, WATCH THIS.
LOOK.
- WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?
TWO SIGNALS FROM THE NIRVASH?
- ONE IS THE UNKNOWN SHIP
WE SAW EARLIER.
THERE IS SOMETHING THERE
INSIDE THE ZONE.
- Man: THE SWALLOWTAIL BUTTERFLY
IS ABLE TO SEE ULTRAVIOLET RAYS,
SOMETHING WE HUMANS CANNOT.
AND BASED ON THE COLOR CHANGES
CAUSED BY ULTRAVIOLET LIGHT,
THE SWALLOWTAIL BUTTERFLIES
CAN DISTINGUISH BETWEEN
THE MALES AND FEMALES.
IN A WORLD
THAT HUMAN BEINGS CANNOT SEE,
BUTTERFLIES ARE ABLE TO PROPERLY
DISTINGUISH BETWEEN GENDERS.
WHY DO YOU THINK THAT IS?
- SO THEY CAN MAKE CHILDREN.
- ( students laughing )
- THAT'S CORRECT.
IT IS AN IMPORTANT FUNCTION
THAT ALLOWS THE MALES
TO FIND THE FEMALES
AND LEAVE BEHIND OFFSPRING.
SUCH DIFFERENCES IN THE BASIC
FRAMEWORK OF THE SENSES
EXIST INHERENTLY
IN ALL LIVING THINGS.
FOR EXAMPLE,
EVEN THOUGH TRAPAR WINGS
ARE SOMETHING WE CAN'T SEE
WITH THE NAKED EYE,
SKYFISH ARE ABLE TO SEE THEM
AND MAKE USE OF THEM.
- ( gasping )
( panting )
- RECEIVING ID CODE
FROM THE NIRVASH.
LOCATION CONFIRMED.
- WHAT ABOUT EUREKA
AND RENTON?
- ALL VITAL AND MENTAL
SIGNALS ARE NORMAL.
WHAT? RENTON'S SHOWING
SIGNS OF--
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- HE'S EXHIBITING A REM PATTERN.
- A REM PATTERN?
EVEN THOUGH HIS BODY
IS SLEEPING,
HIS BRAIN IS ONLY
IN A LIGHT SLUMBER.
IT COULD BE A SIGN THAT RENTON
IS HAVING SOME SORT OF A DREAM.
- HUH.
- TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
IT'S AS IF EUREKA IS CHASING
AFTER RENTON'S MENTAL SIGNALS.
HER SIGNALS ARE
SYNCHRONIZING WITH HIS.
- YOU MEAN
SHE'S CHASING AFTER HIM?
- HERE, LISTEN TO THIS.
- ( static crackling )
- Eureka:
DO YOU KNOW WHO RENTON IS?
WHY DO YOU HAVE
THE SAME FACE?
- OH, EUREKA.
- 808 AND 606 ARE APPROACHING
FROM THE FRONT.
- I'M OPENING THE HATCHES NOW.
- PRECURSOR WAVE COMING IN
FROM THE STARBOARD
AND SOME ANTI-SHIP LASERS.
- IS IT COMING FROM THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE CORALIAN CLOUD?
- THAT WAS CLOSER THAN
LAST TIME.
LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE FACTORING
IN THE EFFECT OF THE CORALIAN.
- ALL RIGHT, HA,
GO TO DEFCON-1.
- GOING TO DEFCON-1.
- SAFETY LOCKS ON ALL WEAPONS
HAVE BEEN DEACTIVATED.
AUTO RAPID-FIRE MODE.
- 606 AND 808 ARE IN.
RETRIEVAL COMPLETE.
- ALL RIGHT.
HEADING 0300, SPEED LEVEL 2.
- ROGER THAT.
- HUGE TRAPAR WAVE INCOMING.
- DON'T LET US GET SWEPT AWAY!
- ( grunting )
- ( screams )
- LOOK, THERE THEY ARE.
- PREPARE TO FIRE
LASER CANNON.
FIRE!
- EVASIVE MANEUVERS.
- THERE'S NO TIME!
- DAMN IT!
- WE'RE IN LUCK.
KEN-GOH, FIRE THE MAIN CANNONS.
- RIGHT.  CHARGING ENERGY PODS
AND CANNONS ONE AND TWO.
ADJUSTING FIRING ANGLE 3.6
TO PORT.
FIRING NOW.
- UGH, WE MISSED IT
- I ASSURE YOU IT'S THE FAULT
OF THAT MISERABLE CORALIAN.
IT'S NOT AS IF I LOST MY TOUCH.
- I GET IT, KEN-GOH, RELAX.
- HOLD IT!
HOLD IT!  HOLD IT!
IF WE STAY ON THIS COURSE,
WE'LL COLLIDE.
- YOU'RE NOT RAMMING THEM,
ARE YOU?
IF WE ATTACK FROM CLOSE RANGE,
THE CORALIAN'S EFFECT...
- SHOULD BE MINIMIZED.
- Both: AS WE PASS EACH OTHER,
FIRE EVERYTHING WE'VE GOT.
- I CANNOT AGREE
WITH YOUR ACTIONS HERE.
ARE YOU TRYING TO TAKE
US DOWN WITH THEM?
- THE ENEMY IS THINKING
THE SAME THING.
WE GET THEM OR THEY GET US.
DEPLOY ALL MISSILE
LAUNCHERS NOW.
- ALL MISSILES ARMED
AND READY FOR LAUNCH.
- DISTANCE IS 200, 150,
100, 50
- Both: FIRE ALL MISSILES!
- ( panting )
( sighs )
- ( toilet flushes )
- UGH!
- Girl: OCCUPIED.
- Girl #2: IT'S OCCUPIED.
- Boy: THIS ONE'S OCCUPIED.
- Girl #3: CURRENTLY OCCUPIED.
- Girl #4:
OCCUPIED, MEOW.
- OH!
UGH! ( screams )
WHO-- WHO IS THAT?
- RENTON?
- WE JUST LOST
NUMBER TWO RIGHT VRF.
LIFT POWER DOWN BY 25%.
- TALHO, TRY TO MAINTAIN
HORIZONTAL BALANCE.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING.
- I HAVE A FEELING
THAT SOMEONE WAS
CALLING FOR ME.  HUH?
- PERVERT!
- ( screams ) I'M SO SORRY.
- ( gasps )
- WE DID IT.
- Anemone: WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?  PERVERT.  SICKO.
- Renton: THAT'S NOT IT.
I DIDN'T MEAN IT LIKE THAT.
- WHO IS IT YOU'RE WITH AND
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?  ANEMONE.
- RENTON,
WHERE ARE YOU?
RENTON.
- Holland:
AT THE MOMENT, WE'RE HERE.
AS LONG AS THEY HAVE
NO INTENTION
OF LEAVING THIS AIRSPACE,
WE'LL CIRCLE AROUND AND COME
IN CONTACT WITH THEM AGAIN.
THAT'S WHEN WE'LL TAKE THEM ON.
IT'S ALL UP TO YOU, KEN-GOH.
- RIGHT.
I WON'T MISS AGAIN.
- THAT'S THE--
OW, THAT HURTS, YOU KNOW?
- HEY, DID YOU KNOW THIS?
THERE'S TONS OF HATRED
IN THE WORLD AND THERE ISN'T
EVEN ANY REASON FOR IT.
SINCE IT'S SOMETHING
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND,
THERE'S NO WAY THAT YOU COULD
POSSIBLY UNDERSTAND IT.
BUT EVEN SO,
IT'S DEFINITELY THERE.
LOOK, THERE'S A BUNCH OF IT
SCATTERED ALL OVER THE PLACE.
A HATRED WITHOUT ANY NAME.
I GOTCHA.
NOW HURRY UP
AND CALL FOR ME.
JUST CALL MY NAME.
- CAPTAIN JURGENS, SIR.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I REALIZE
THAT YOU ARE DISSATISFIED
WITH THE WAY IN WHICH I'VE BEEN
COMMANDING THE TROOPS.
I'M SURE THAT'S ESPECIALLY TRUE
IN LIGHT OF PAST EVENTS.
- YOU'RE WORRYING ABOUT
A STUPID THING LIKE THAT?
YOU REALLY DON'T THINK
MUCH OF ME, DO YOU?
- HOWEVER, THIS ONCE
TO PROTECT ANEMONE
AND ALSO TO PROTECT THE END.
OBEY MY ORDER.
- YOU'RE JOKING?
- IN AN AREA WHERE THE TRAPAR
DENSITY HAS THINNED OUT,
WE'LL BE ABLE
TO RETRIEVE THE END.
- WE CAN'T RIGHT NOW.
EVEN THOUGH THEY'VE BEEN HIT,
WE STILL DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE GEKKO IS UP TO.
WE CAN'T BE CARELESS.
- ( groans )
- I'M SORRY,
BUT I REALLY
DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I CAME BECAUSE YOU CALLED
TO ME.
- NO, I DIDN'T.
YOU AREN'T THE PERSON
THAT I WAS CALLING FOR.
- OH, SO YOU WEREN'T
CALLING FOR ME.
WELL, FINE THEN.
WHO CARES ABOUT YOU?
- ( gasps )
- YOU CAN DIE!
- ( screaming )
- THERE THEY ARE
- WE'VE SPOTTED THE GEKKO.
- HUH!
SO THEY'RE STILL FLYING, HUH?
WELL, THIS TIME I'LL
PUT AN END TO THIS.
- GOOD, HERE THEY COME.
GOOD, GOOD.
NOW FIRE.
- ( screaming )
- FROM THAT DISTANCE,
THERE'S NO WAY THEY'LL HIT--
WHAT?
- WE GOT 'EM.
- AWESOME!
- GREAT AS ALWAYS, KEN-GOH.
- ( laughs )
IT'S NOTHING
- ( gasps )
WAIT, THAT'S MY SISTER.
- RENTON.
- EUREKA.
- LET'S GO BACK TOGETHER.
- YEAH, LET'S GO BACK...
TOGETHER.
- THE TRAPAR IN THIS AIRSPACE
IS STARTING
TO DISAPPEAR RAPIDLY.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
WITHDRAW NOW!
- HUH?
Renton: TO BE CONTINUED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- TWO BOYS HAVE A CHANCE
ENCOUNTER AT THE PLACE
WHERE THE CORALIAN
DISAPPEARED.
WITHOUT REALIZING
WHAT THE IMPLICATIONS ARE,
THEY BOTH FIGHT FOR THE SAKE
OF THE ONE THEY WANT TO PROTECT.
NEXT EPISODE-- "THE BEGINNING."