[SETH]
Jill could sense that Fantasia
was about to disappear
from the forest.
And knowing that,
she gathered up every
last bit she had
and used it to keep
her children safe.
They're still really little,
so they need lots of protection.
Are you okay?
[MYR]
I owe you my gratitude, Seth.
Oh. I didn't do much.
Doc's the one who found them.
[MYR] You gave me a chance to
see my children one last time.
Despite Jill's sacrifice,
this cocoon has been
drained of Fantasia.
It'll run out soon.
Sounds to me like
all you need to do
is make them a new cocoon.
[MYR]
No. That isn't possible.
It took me and Jill hundreds
of years to make this one.
Yeah, but this forest exists
outside of normal time, right?
That was back when
the forest was alive
and brimming with Fantasia.
If Jill were still here,
the two of us might've
been able to restore it,
but without her,
there's no hope.
Don't talk like that.
You can do anything, Myr.
You're the last fairy!
I'm weaker than my forbears
because I'm half human.
[NARRATOR]
"The Future Is With You."
[SETH]
What? You're half human?
[MYR]
Mhm.
My father was a real
mischievous trickster type.
He liked to transform himself
and woo women of your species.
You can imagine how
surprised he must've been
when one of those women
ended up pregnant.
I don't much care to get
into the details, but yes.
When my people decided to merge
with the greater world,
I wanted nothing more than
to disappear with them.
But hard as I tried,
I couldn't follow them.
My human half tethered
me to this body.
I wandered this land by myself
for what felt like an eternity.
Crippled by loneliness,
yearning for a way
to rejoin my people.
And when that failed,
I searched for
the beings responsible
for my people's fate.
I attacked the
humans relentlessly.
Then I met Jill, and I
wasn't alone anymore.
She showed me a
gentler way of life.
Before too long,
I lost interest in
fighting the humans.
I forgot about rejoining
my people, too.
Instead, Jill and I decided
to start a family.
Jill didn't like that I
rejected my human side.
She convinced me to start
visiting the castle area.
There, I heard the humans gossip
about my past appearances.
Their tales ranged from
ridiculous to idiotic.
But weren't the stories
based on things that you did?
Yeah.
A long time ago,
I encountered a rather
combative group of humans
trying to head into the forest.
I threw them all out
without much trouble.
I soon discovered they were
chasing another group of humans,
and that group decided I must've
shown up to protect them.
Years later, some humans
tried to buy the land
from me with gold.
I told them that the land didn't
belong to me or anyone else.
It wasn't mine to give or share.
Over the generations,
those stories turned into
the "Legend of Merlin."
A wise old sorcerer king
riding a stag,
spouting crap like, "I shall
not let this land be divided!"
or, "This is our country.
It doesn't belong to them!"
So are all the heroic
stories they tell
about you just
misunderstandings?
Yeah, pretty much
without exception.
The humans got everything wrong,
right down to my name.
It's always been Myrddin!
[ARTO] Even his hallowed
name was misremembered!
[LANDLAKE]
I suppose we'll have to swear
on Myrddin's name henceforth!
Here's the thing,
I can make mountains
or even deadwood trees
grow from the earth,
but it'll take life to
sustain these little ones,
and I lack the magic
to create life.
[SETH]
Hmm.
Jill put me in a bubble
just like that one,
treated me like her child.
Well, if that kept me alive,
could it work the other way?
[MYR]
Huh?
Just what are you suggesting?
That we could have a
human carry them to term?
[SETH]
Yeah. Does that sound weird?
Honestly, I think it
could work, Seth.
Since Myr is half human,
that means his children
are all one-fourth human,
so they would probably
adjust pretty easily.
You can't really believe--
Actually, you make a good point.
However, the young ones will
need a great deal of Fantasia,
which the human'll
have to gather.
So basically, you just need
a really powerful sorcerer
to volunteer, right?
[MYR] She would need to take
this cocoon into her body.
Finding a sorcerer who
would be able to manage
such a task could be impossible.
Don't worry, Myr. I know
someone who can do it.
[BOUDICA]
Yes.
And I want you to know, Myrddin,
I would consider it
a great honor.
[BOTH yelling]
I sense the passion
of a kindred spirit
in every stroke of your blade!
I hope you don't think you can
charm me over to your side.
We shall continue this later.
Well fought, sir. Ha!
Come back here!
That would defeat the purpose
of leaving, so I shan't.
Namely because I can't!
I must answer a call
of nature at once!
You could come back after.
[KNIGHT SORCERER B]
Lord de Gulis, we found you.
You're wanted on
suspicion of conspiracy.
We're to escort you
back to the castle.
[sighs] Oh, great Merlin.
What will become of us?
What is in store
for Cyfandir next?
[GOUDEAU]
Things seem to have calmed down.
Both sides have withdrawn
from the field.
[GARVICE] Did you know
what would happen, sir?
Because of your Lynx Eye?
I didn't.
When the monster brought its
anger to bear on our ship,
I was utterly convinced
that we were all done for.
[BOTH gasp]
That being said,
if we had turned tail
and then been killed,
our story would've
been much less noble.
Seriously, Captain?
It's time we headed out.
Inquisition ships won't
be safe in these skies
for too much longer.
Right. Understood.
Where should we go?
[DRAGUNOV]
To Bome, of course.
With all due respect,
are you sure that we can?
We drew blades against
our comrades in battle.
Do you think we can justify
such an overt mutiny?
I'm sure I'll be able
to take care of it.
On a somewhat related note,
our squad is going to be
rather busy for a while.
[GOUDEAU] Well, we weren't
expecting a holiday.
If anyone wants out,
this is the time to say so.
I'm with you, sir.
Same. Count me in, Captain!
Until I've drawn my last breath.
[DRAGUNOV] Regardless of
the justification offered,
attempting to enslave the
infected is plainly wrong.
I need to speak
with General Torque
and glean his intentions.
So you're a Thaumaturge. Huh.
We'll have to take
special measures
to keep you secured here.
[LISELOTTE]
This is humiliating.
But nothing fazes the general.
He'll know exactly what to do
when he learns of
my predicament.
[BOUDICA]
It has been three days now
since the Inquisition
interrupted
our Knight Ordination Ceremony
by sending an invasion force
to launch an unprovoked
attack on our country.
We've lost a great deal
of verdant land
and a great many
heroic soldiers.
But we drove back the foe
and our country will recover.
For now, let us mourn our dead
and tend to our many wounds.
But this time next year,
and in the years to come after,
we shall celebrate this day.
The day that Cyfandir
delivered a stern rebuke
to the self-righteous
Inquisitors
who were foolish enough to think
that they could put
us into chains!
[TOWNSPEOPLE]
All hail the queen!
Long may she reign!
[TOWNSPEOPLE cheering]
All that said, we were
ill-prepared for battle
and came far too close
to defeat as a result.
If not for the timely aid
of several outsiders
to the kingdom,
as well as the intervention
of Merlin himself,
we would've lost the war
and Cyfandir would be on
its knees as I speak.
Our enemy had a cunning plan.
They planted the seeds
of doubt in our hearts,
twisted the pride of
our lords into a tool
and used it to trick them into
attacking their own people.
But this was only made possible
by a myriad of failures
and mistakes.
I was a fool.
If I had asked for counsel
or gone out to speak
with my people,
I could've discovered this
conspiracy far sooner.
And if not for the custom
of keeping our curses hidden,
the villains who plotted
to burn our kingdom
at the pyre of profit
would've been missing
an essential piece
of their plan.
Sorcerers of Cyfandir.
The time has come for us to
bring our secrets to the light!
[TOWNSPERSON H]
That sounds fine in theory,
but it's a pretty big step.
[TOWNSPERSON J]
What's going on?
[TOWNSPERSON K] It's that
knight candidate, Ocoho!
[sighs]
Near my ear, I have a little
mark about the size of a coin.
When someone touches it,
I have no choice but
to do as they tell me.
And afterwards, I have no
memory of what happened!
[TOWNSPEOPLE murmuring]
[BRANGOIRE clears throat]
[BRANGOIRE]
I have six nipples.
Including the two that are...
uh, where they should be.
No offense, Lord Brangoire, but
I think you've said too much.
More like not enough!
Tell us where the other
four nipples are!
You got me curious!
No! That's much too personal.
[TOWNSPERSON M]
Are they under your beard?
Shut up!
I think my infection
turned my hair blue.
Yeah, uh. My Queen?
I don't think you're foolin'
anybody with that one.
Aww.
Tell us what your
real curse is, come on!
I feel like it's obvious.
[TOWNSPERSON A] Yeah, but we
wanna hear it from you!
Oh, fine.
If you must know
my true curse...
...it's that I grow more
beautiful by the day.
Yeah.
[TOWNSPERSON N]
She really does! Amazing!
[TOWNSPERSON O]
You're full of it!
Are you asserting that the queen
doesn't grow more
beautiful by the day?
[TOWNSPERSON O] No, I'm just
sayin' that's not her curse!
Watch yourself, buster!
[TOWNSPERSON B]
My curse is my hair.
It's even harder than steel!
[TOWNSPERSON P]
My curse is pretty weird.
I've got claws where
my teeth should be.
[TOWNSPERSON C]
Mine's even weirder.
I have two necks,
but only one head!
[TOWNSPERSON Q] And I have two
nostrils, but only one nose!
[TOWNSPERSON C]
That's normal, dumbass!
Think that's enough
for now. Settle down.
We have a whole lot
to discuss today.
Um, my Queen?
I'm sorry if this is rude,
but I wanted to ask.
Are you expecting?
My goodness.
Nothing gets past
my faithful subjects.
[TOWNSPERSON D] You started
showing so suddenly.
Who's the father?
The father wishes to
remain anonymous for now.
But I feel comfortable
telling you
that he's short of
stature, bearded,
and a stalwart
defender of Cyfandir,
and that he's dear to the
hearts of my people as well.
[TOWNSPERSON M]
Tell me this.
Does he have nips in his beard?
Are you crazy?!
I would never lay my
hands on Queen Boudica!
You would never touch me?
[BRANGOIRE]
Well, I mean.
If you were in danger, or
if you wanted me to-- Uh!
Ah! What I meant was I'm
at your disposal, my Queen!
[TOWNSPERSON O]
I feel like his real infection
is that he gets crazy red!
Shut your mouths!
First of all, this line
of discussion
is highly disrespectful
to the queen!
And second of all!
Well, you know...
[TOWNSPERSON O]
Huh? Speak up, we can't hear ya!
[BRANGOIRE]
Oh, yes.
Your Majesty, there's a request
I would like to make.
Go right ahead.
[BRANGOIRE]
I wish to retract my statement
from before the
ordination ceremony.
[BOUDICA]
Hm?
[BRANGOIRE]
I believe candidate Ocoho
would make an excellent knight.
Huh?
I think I understand,
but have the lords of Cyfandir
not chosen their heirs already?
[BRANGOIRE]
I chose to defer until now.
Whoa. Wait. What are you saying?
You wanna make me your heir?
I'm rather surprised that
you would ask for this,
Lord Brangoire.
The answer is no.
Please, my Queen.
It was Ocoho who exposed the
Spectral Nemesis conspiracy!
She fought a merchant
baron, a traitor,
and a ship full of foes,
and sent them all running!
She's overcome the
limits of her infection
and proven to be
a capable warrior!
I've been training
knight candidates for years
and Ocoho's Gysoni is
by far the strongest
I've ever seen!
That's true, but she also
defied your orders
during multiple battles against
Spectral Nemeses, right?
[BRANGOIRE] Yes, but only
to help our farmers.
She also slapped her
queen in the face once.
[BRANGOIRE] Only to help you
regain your conviction.
And at the Ordination Ceremony,
she all-but convinced my
most loyal knight to rebel.
Only to protect her people!
I've made my decision,
and nothing you say can sway it.
It could be hundreds of years
before we see an heir
with such talent again!
Stop, Lord Brangoire.
With every word that you utter,
you unwittingly shame both
yourself and your country.
It would be disgraceful
to dub Ocoho a knight now.
I'm grateful, but
Her Majesty's right.
I've crossed too many lines
and caused too much
harm to be forgiven.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'd like to repay your
kindness, but I can't.
[BOUDICA]
Stop right there, honey.
I've had my eye on
you for a long time,
and you're everything
I thought you were.
The truth is that despite
your aspirations,
you were never suited
to be a knight.
However...
...I believe that you're
perfectly suited to be queen.
[ALL]
Huh?
Not only due to the
accomplishments
Lord Brangoire just listed,
but because you
stood against me.
At the Ordination Ceremony,
you chose to put the people's
interest over the crown's.
Wait, really?
But at the time, you
seemed so angry with me.
Oh, I was just teasing you.
You looked so cute and brave
I could've eaten you up.
If I neglected to make
someone as brilliant
and heroically inclined
as you my heir,
why, I wouldn't be able to
look myself in the mirror.
And if I tried, I bet the mirror
would refuse to show me my face.
Uh. Uhh...?
Noble people of Cyfandir.
It's an honor to present
your future queen.
Before you stands
my chosen heir.
Princess Ocoho.
Let's hear it for Ocoho!
Woohoo! Long live the princess!
[TOWNSPERSON F]
Aw, she's embarrassed. Cute.
[TOWNSPERSON G] Long live
our cute new queen to be!
[TOWNSPERSON T]
She can rule me starting now.
Stop that! Address the princess
with respect or else!
[TOWNSPERSON M]
Or else what?
You'll show us your
secret nipples?
Stop making fun of my infection!
I can't believe this is real.
[BOUDICA]
I don't know what inspired it.
But I feel like I've gotten to
watch you come into your own
over the past few weeks.
You stopped fretting about
what your superiors thought
and acted like the brave
knight you wanted to be.
Whether someone was going to
give you the title or not.
To be honest, it was
mostly thanks to--
[MELIE]
He had it comin', Doc!
Hold up. Where did Seth go?
[music plays]
[MYR]
The future queen, eh?
Boudica couldn't have picked
a better candidate. Heh.
Ocoho probably doesn't
remember this,
but she came to the forest
often when she was a child.
I used to think that if
more humans were like her,
able to see the forest as I did,
they might make an
effort to preserve it.
But now there isn't
anything left to see.
Now that might not
always be true.
Your kids'll be able to do
all kinds of cool things.
When they're finally born,
I bet they can use magic
to bring this whole
forest back to life.
Yeah. But Jill will
still be gone.
[SETH]
If I hadn't come here,
the Inquisitors wouldn't
have come looking for me.
I'm sorry.
[MYR] No, they would've
done this eventually.
Don't blame yourself.
And honestly, if you hadn't
shown up to stop me,
I'd've destroyed everything
to do with mankind.
And in doing so, I would've
robbed my precious children
of their only chance at life.
There's no need to
look so glum, Seth.
Tell ya what.
I'll play you the song I wrote
to commemorate all the
fun I had with Jill.
I've decided to call it
"A Thousand Times at Least."
[SETH]
If this is what I think it is,
I'd rather you keep
it to yourself--
[MYR] ♪ Oh, weeks and months
and years of pleasure ♪
♪ More than I could
ever measure ♪
♪ Through all the time
I spent with you ♪
♪ Our love, it blossomed
and it grew ♪
♪ But now those days
have ceased ♪
♪ Before the beauty
of your flowers ♪
♪ The centuries flew
by like hours ♪
♪ You'd think
that an eternity ♪
♪ Would be enough,
but selfishly ♪
♪ With you,
I'd want eternity ♪
♪ A thousand times,
at least ♪
[MYR humming]
[BOUDICA]
Here you are, Seth.
Magosia's memory stone,
as requested.
Are you sure that
this is all you want?
Yeah, I appreciate it.
My friend's been
looking for this thing.
[BOUDICA]
For you, Melie.
A number of Cyfandir's
finest craftspeople
worked their hardest
to create it.
[MELIE] I'm honored,
Your Majesty. Thank you.
[BOUDICA]
Oh, stop.
You said you wanted to
leave without ceremony,
so go ahead and spare us the
formalities while you're at it.
So, uh, do I get a present?
Of course. You saved my life.
And in discovering
Merlin's children,
you also saved
our entire country.
Please accept this pendant
with my gratitude.
From now on,
you shall carry the honorary
title of knight-sorcerer.
Thanks, but... could I
ask for somethin' else?
Why would you do that, Doc?
Don't you wanna be a knight?
Honor doesn't fill my belly.
Look, what I could really use
is some gold to pay
off my debt with.
Got some?
None that I can spare.
This war-torn country will be
quite expensive to
rebuild, you see.
But Lord Brangoire
insisted on giving you
a little something extra.
Ya sure weren't jokin'
when ya said little.
You hold the armor
of Pen Draig.
--[BOTH yell]
--[ARTO laughs]
[ARTO] Should you sense
that violence is nigh...
[LANDLAKE] ...don your armor
and show us the foe!
I remember those
voices from before!
Uh-oh! It's the two memory
stones I swallowed!
You're the only person alive
who's capable of using it.
So carry it with you.
Since I won't be around,
you need to protect the
princess on my behalf.
We've prepared your
steed, Your Highness.
Huh? What's this all about?
I've stayed here my whole life
watching over my people,
but I regret that fact.
It's left me with far too narrow
a perspective on the world.
And because of that,
I failed to see the crisis
unfolding before me.
I want my heir to
be better prepared.
So go with them and see
the vast world for yourself.
Ensure that you won't
make my mistakes.
'Kay. Guess we'll
see ya later then.
But Ocoho'll stay in touch.
You be safe while I'm
gone, Your Majesty.
Sure. You do the same.
Be careful, Your Highness.
[OCOHO, BOUDICA laugh]
Go forth for Cyfandir.
May its future be bright.
Hey!
Fair warning: If I find out that
someone hurt the princess,
I'll murder them.
And then I'll murder you
for letting them touch her!
So don't let it get
to that point!
Okay, well, you'd better
take care of the queen
and those babies in her belly!
They're like my siblings,
so if you're not
careful with them...
...I'll smack your
beard nipples!
I feel like they
could've just said
that they're counting
on each other.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[MYR]
They may be like your siblings,
but remember that they
actually are my children.
So go and don't worry
about a thing.
I'll be watching over them.
[BOTH laugh]
[laughs]
This is my very first
time leaving Cyfandir!
[DRACCOON grunts]
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[MELIE chuckles]
She's acting the way
you used to, Seth.
Huh?
Feel like I might've
been a little worse.
Yeah.
But I'd say you've matured
quite a bit since then.
[SETH]
So have you.
[MELIE]
Well, we've overcome a lot.
And that's what
makes people grow.
I'm really glad you followed
me out here, Melie.
If I had been on my own,
I would've lost all
control of myself.
For the record,
I didn't come to Cyfandir
just for you, you know.
I'm well aware of that.
But still, thanks a bunch.
I'm happy to help.
And I'll be counting on you
to help me out, too.
[GRIMM]
Good evening.
[OCOHO, SETH scream]
[SETH] Don't pop up outta thin
air like that, it's creepy!
Oh, uh. Here.
[GRIMM]
Ah, Magosia's memory stone.
Thank you.
[SETH] I'd say no prob,
but it was kinda tough to get,
so you still owe me.
I want one personal
detail--spill it.
[GRIMM]
Grimm will consider it.
Ya know what sucks?
The archive didn't have
any books about Radiant.
It was all a big waste of time.
It wasn't all a waste.
What about that
amazing new friend
you got out of it named Ocoho?
Oh, yeah.
All right, people! Time to
get this adventure started!
[DRACCOON grunts]
You seem really excited.
'Course I do!
Listen, guys, my goal is to see
as much of the world as I can.
But while we're out here,
let's track down Radiant.
[giggles]
Your wish is our
command, Your Highness!
Let's go!
--[DRACCOON grunts]
--[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Can't I just relax
at home for a bit?
[ARTO, LANDLAKE]
Never!
Why is life so cruel?
[chuckles]
Okay. Look out, Radiant!
Me and my friends are
hot on your trail!