There it is. The Spectral
Nemesis we're after.
Stay in formation no
matter what happens!
And keep your distance from
the castle, all of you!
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
All right, let's begin
this battle together.
Gysoni!
[SOLDIERS]
[NARRATOR] The city of
the knight-sorcerers,
Caislean Merlin.
The city has been besieged as
of late by mysterious monsters
known as Spectral Nemeses.
These Nemeses appear not
from eggs, but from thin air.
Some of the most ancient
secrets of magic
are said to be kept
in this city.
And it's where Seth's next
adventure will begin.
[NARRATOR]
"Toward a New Adventure"
Seth defeated Konrad
and thwarted his schemes
for Rumble Town,
saving countless lives
and setting the town
on a course toward tolerance.
This was a good deed to be sure,
but it brought him
no closer to his goal.
Seth seeks to solve
the mystery of Radiant,
the source of all Nemeses,
and cause of much
human conflict.
As Seth continues his quest
for the secrets of Radiant,
he will also learn of the
secrets within himself.
[stomach growls]
[sighs]
It's Caislean Merlin or bust.
Yaga said I might find out
about Radiant there,
and that's the only
lead I've got.
I'll hop in here, find what I
need, and hop right back out!
Sure is nice to be home
after all this time.
[thud]
[ALMA]
So, you're back.
Uh. Yeah.
[DON BOSSMAN, JIJI gasp]
Huh?!
[DON BOSSMAN] Man, the air
really does start to get stale
in there after a while,
doesn't it, Jiji?
What's it gonna
take for you guys
to learn your friggin' lesson?
Hey! Great to see ya,
kid! It's been a while!
Be careful, Alma!
We're under attack!
Those are my assistants you
just punched, ya stupid dolt!
[SETH]
Why would you hire them?!
Maybe this is how they
show affection here, Jiji!
[DON BOSSMAN crying]
[DON BOSSMAN]
Lady Alma told us we needed
to hide from the locals,
so we sealed ourselves in those
barrels and stayed quiet.
How could he just attack
us out of nowhere?
On the plus side,
you were great hiders.
[SETH]
Hey!
Will someone please explain
to me what's goin' on here?
[DON BOSSMAN laughs]
Sorry if our sudden appearance
gave you a scare.
Yeah. Whatever. Why
are you here though?
Before we answer any
questions you have,
why don't we start over?
Let's hit him with intro
formation number 12, Jiji!
We are known as
the Bravery Duet!
Damn it, Jiji!
I said we were doing
formation number 12!
So why are you doing
formation 21?
You screwed it up
like you always do!
Now we're a laughingstock
'cause of you!
So you're a duet now, huh?
What happened to the other
clowns you ran with?
Well, long story short,
we got separated after
we fled from Artemis.
I wonder what they're
up to right now.
[SETH]
Huh?
In case this still isn't clear,
these two're allowed to be here,
they work for me.
Huh?!
Did you forget about how
they robbed all those
villagers before?
And I even caught them stealing
treasure from Artemis, too!
[ALMA]
I know.
[SETH]
Then why let them stay?
[laughing]
How 'bout I fill you in?
After Jiji and I
escaped Artemis,
we tried to lay low
on a deserted island.
We were hoping to give our
wounds time to heal there.
But it was infested
by the Nemesis!
Huh. 'Kay.
[DON BOSSMAN] We'd lost our
weapons, our brooms,
our underpants!
It seemed that was
the end for us!
But then Lady Alma
appeared out of nowhere
and gallantly saved
our sorry lives.
Yeah? Did you seriously
do that, Alma?
I happened across 'em
as I flew to work.
Then shouldn't you have given
them back to Artemis after?
Yeah, and at first I tried
to do exactly that.
I sent word, but no one
ever came to collect them.
So I gave them a chance.
Nobody's born human, right?
It takes work to become one.
I wasn't about to kill them
just because they'd committed
a few petty crimes.
That'd be cruel.
I get it.
And you've served her
ever since, right?
Actually, no!
We tried to give her the slip
as soon as she took
her eyes off us!
Huh?!
[DON BOSSMAN] But then she
unleashed her magic on us
at full blast.
[ALMA] I've got no mercy
for ungrateful punks
who bite the hand
that feeds them.
[SETH chuckles nervously]
[DON BOSSMAN]
But that's not all.
Suddenly, a Source
Nemesis appeared!
[SETH]
Oh!
[DON BOSSMAN]
We were defenseless.
But Lady Alma faced that Nemesis
with the bravitude of a lion
and struck the monster down!
In that moment, I had an
epiphany. A revelation!
This sorcerer had the spirit
I'd been trying to embody
my entire life.
The woman I saw before me was
the incarnation of courage,
self-sacrifice, and humility!
"Lady" Alma is an
understatement.
She's a goddess!
Yeah!
So that's why I've put my wicked
old ways behind me now!
As soon as she finished killing
that Nemesis, I bowed!
I got on my hands and
knees and begged her
to let us be her assistants.
And then...
[SETH]
Huh?
I can't even understand
a word you are saying!
Why don't you stop
with the sob-show
and go make me some dinner, Don?
[DON BOSSMAN]
As you command!
[footsteps]
What a pain.
Nice work, Alma. You've really
turned those guys around.
They're not good people yet,
they're just weirdly loyal.
If I quit Nemesis hunting and
became an organ trafficker,
I bet they'd start
kidnapping drunks for me.
I guess they'll learn more
with you then they would
if they were stuck in jail.
[ALMA]
Maybe so.
At any rate, they've been
standing by their promise
to assist me.
They do the work
of five men apiece.
[SETH]
You're kidding!
[ALMA]
I'm not.
There's no reason to worry
about them, though.
They're a couple of buffoons,
but they've decided
we're a family.
It's cute.
[SETH]
Oh, yeah. Speaking of family.
[ALMA]
Hm?
When all that stuff
happened in Rumble Town,
I met this weird guy.
What do you mean by "weird"?
[SETH] Well, he said that
he was my older brother.
And could he prove it?
Or did this stranger expect you
to take his claims
at face value?
He had horns, the same as I do.
The curse of growing horns
isn't actually as rare
as you seem to believe.
That may be, but he also
looked a lot like me.
And when I was in trouble
at Rumble Town,
I sensed him somehow.
I felt him do something
to help me fight.
You felt him do what?
[SETH] I think he cracked
open something inside me,
just enough to keep me alive.
And after the fight, I saw him.
Like in a dream.
[ALMA]
Seth, you felt him do something
during your fight
in Rumble Town?
Well, as strange as it sounds,
despite being a great
distance away from you,
I think I felt it, too.
And it felt wrong.
It was a sensation I don't
wanna feel again.
I don't have any more memory
of that time than you do,
but what if it wasn't a
Nemesis who infected you?
What if that seal is meant
to protect you from him?
I don't understand why you
would think that though.
[ALMA]
If he really was trustworthy,
I think he would've turned
up for a visit by now.
As I recall, you felt like
you "turned into a monster"
and then "went berserk."
If he helped to
make that happen,
then I consider
this man a threat.
Huh?
[ALMA]
Hiya!
Get it together,
ya gullible dork.
Ya can't go around listening
to every weirdo you run into,
understand?
It wasn't like that,
I really did feel some kind
of bond with this guy.
Sounds like the work of
an overactive imagination.
The story might've
been more believable
if you'd written
yourself some notes.
Aw, c'mon, Alma!
You need to listen now, okay?
You're going to be confronted
with a lot of strange things.
Don't let them confuse you.
Believe only what you've
seen and known yourself,
what you've learned.
If you get careless,
you will die, understand?
Yeah. I get it.
[DON BOSSMAN]
Oh, Lady Alma! Dinner is served!
Feel free to head
up there, Seth.
I bet you're even
hungrier than I am.
Yup! Don't gotta tell me twice!
[SETH laughs]
[DON BOSSMAN]
What do you think, kiddo?
Looks pretty tasty, right?
[ALMA]
His brother?
I have a bad feeling about this.
[DRAGUNOV]
Damn blizzard.
I still can't tell
if I'm close yet.
Why was I summoned
to such a place?
If they intended to punish me
for allowing Konrad
to act as he did,
wouldn't they have sent me
back to my own country?
Konrad. He had a poisoned mind.
I knew he was dangerous
from the beginning.
If I'd stood against him then,
could I have averted
that horrible tragedy?
Good show!
But stay vigilant;
there may be more hiding.
I assure each of you that
these pesky Nemeses
have made fools of us
for the final time.
Report, sir!
We've been told the Nemeses
have fled to District 13!
Then it's that much
easier to capture them!
Or it would be if we
had the means to!
Look over there, Captain.
I think I see something
coming towards us!
Is that so?
Why don't you take a look at it
with that Goat Eye of
yours, Vice-Captain?
With respect, it isn't called
a "Goat Eye," Captain.
Oh, I remember now. It's
called a dormouse eye, right?
Can we please not do this?
Was it a mushroom eye?
I don't even know why that
would occur to you, sir.
Whatever! Who even cares?
Just tell me what you see
with that stupid eye of yours!
So you know, it's
called the "Lynx Eye."
Hmm... It looks like a soldier.
Judging from his uniform,
I'd say he's a soldier
assigned to the prison.
Open fire!
But why?
He's obviously a Nemesis
in disguise! Do it!
'Kay. Well, just in case,
let's see if he can talk.
Hey! What's the matter?
There's been a
terrorist-led revolt
in the prison at District 13!
[ALL gasp]
[KONRAD] The terrorists
are holding a number
of innocent citizens hostage.
They're planning to execute
them one by one!
[CAPTAIN A]
Executing hostages?
Who stages a rebellion
at a time like this? Why?
[KONRAD] There are malcontents
lurking all over the place!
It hurts to say this...
...but Major Oxumare himself
was fighting at their side!
What? The major, a turn coat?
That can't be true.
Actually, it's starting
to make sense.
I heard a report that
he was overly friendly
with the immigrants and
sorcerers at the prison.
[KONRAD] He spoke with the
sorcerer children constantly,
and let no one else
near them, sir.
Devious traitor.
Captain, let my squad
handle this revolt.
We will free the hostages and
find out what's going on.
You cannot let him do that!
[CAPTAIN A]
Speak, soldier! Why not?
[KONRAD]
Because it's far too dangerous!
The reason being,
they've somehow gotten
all of those Nemeses
to fight at their side!
What?
Are you saying that terrorists
are using Nemeses
as weapons now?
[KONRAD]
I am, sir!
I can't be sure,
but I believe the major
used that last sorcerer
child to do it.
[CAPTAIN A]
How conniving!
Dispatch all our troops
to District 13 at once!
[DRAGUNOV]
Hold on, Captain!
This story has been
growing more far-fetched
with every addition.
How would terror--
[SOLDIER A, CAPTAIN A gasp]
[CITIZENS screaming]
[CITIZEN A]
The chains!
[CAPTAIN A] The whole
island's falling off balance!
We still have time
to save Rumble Town!
But the only way is to destroy
the last anchor-point
on Northeast Street
and sink District 13.
Is he insane?
[KONRAD]
This is our only chance.
Sacrifice a part of this
town or lose all of it!
In that case, let's move out
and start evacuating people.
There's no time for that!
We have to act now!
I completely agree, sir!
Not only could the town
fall any second,
this is also our best chance
to wipe out those Nemeses!
But, Captain,
there are civilians.
No, if I waste any more
time listening to you,
it'll be too late, you fool
of a vice-captain!
Go! Cannon crews open fire
on those damn chains!
Take that district down!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[KONRAD laughing]
[DRAGUNOV] Why am I always
just a spectator?
I knew he was corrupt,
and yet...
...I did nothing to stop him.
[DRAGUNOV]
This can't be right.
I've been walking three days
just to reach a dead end?
[LISELOTTE]
Dragunov!
I've heard a rumor or two about
a holy site of the Inquisition
hidden in a remote
mountain pass.
So then, is this where
my execution will be?
That's quite the honor.
[gasps]
Hold on a moment. Is that the
Father of the Inquisitors?
[TORQUE]
Indeed.
This is the oldest
known depiction
of the Patrem Inquisitor.
And to my knowledge,
the most accurate.
Captain Dragunov,
I bid thee welcome to
the Sanctum of Faith.
[DRAGUNOV]
Thank you, General.
I didn't realize that this
place actually existed.
[TORQUE]
That's for the best.
If its existence were known,
there'd be many who
would seek to defile it.
Since the Incident at Rumble
Town became public knowledge,
trust in the Inquisition
has plummeted.
I knew there'd be consequences
when I exposed Konrad,
but I needed to prevent the
past from repeating itself.
My intention wasn't to sully
the Inquisition's honor.
[TORQUE]
That's enough.
If my intention was to rebuke
you, I wouldn't do it here.
I would've summoned you back
to our headquarters in Bome.
Rise. I see no reason
to punish you.
The Inquisition
has been weakened,
and our many foes
are growing bold.
The foul Domitors have
come out of hiding.
The witch-knights of Cyfandir
parade their strength.
And the merchant barons
of the west plan to expand.
We must hold back
these many threats
while governing a populace
that's lost its faith in us.
My Thaumaturges are working
to secure our position
and prove that we can
still protect the people.
When maintaining this
delicate balance,
difficult choices often arise.
Choices I am burdened to make.
For example, I've decided
that the Captain Dragunov
who quietly guarded the
islands of Pompo Hills...
...is dead.
From this day forth,
you're Captain Dragunov
the Thaumaturge.
By the end of this incident,
your perceptiveness proved
to be a double-edged sword.
But if not for your
watchful eye,
Konrad might've concealed
the truth yet again.
Sir, I'm unworthy
of your praise.
I didn't stop him.
I didn't even attempt to--
I just reported what I knew.
That is because you
know your limits.
Unlike that fool Von Teppes.
He overestimated his strength
and was struck down before
he could use his miracle.
You have good judgment,
which is why I recommended you.
You're the same man that
I used to serve under.
A dedicated soldier who sees
that which slips past the rest.
I think that your astute
insights'll bolster our strength
in ways that you're too
humble to acknowledge.
[DRAGUNOV] I was fully prepared
to be executed, but this...
This I never saw coming.
Follow me.
[TORQUE]
The sorcerers with whom
we Thaumaturges
fight are powerful.
[TORQUE]
Before our order's founding,
the people of Pharenos
were subjugated
by powerful sorcerers.
Their oppression persisted,
until one man stood up and
flew the flag of rebellion.
That man, the son
of a simple farmer,
fought the sorcerers back with
nothing but a common pitchfork
and the strength of his will.
There are those who think
this story is but a legend
but I assure you, it is true.
Is that the Patrem Inquisitor's
pitchfork, General?
[TORQUE] Yes. It is one
of our sacred relics.
There's no magic in it,
nor was it designed for warfare.
It was made to pitch hay.
But in his hands,
it brought down men with
the strength of false gods.
Such a feat would
require a miracle.
Precisely so.
The strength of his will
gave him the power
to perform miracles.
But how'd he do it?
I'll tell you that when
the time is right.
You came a long way to get here.
For now, you need to rest.
We will perform the
revelation ceremony
and declare you a
Thaumaturge later.
Yes, sir.
You and Captain Liselotte will
leave together at dawn tomorrow.
With her, you'll begin your
first mission as a Thaumaturge.
You are to find that horned
sorcerer and his companions.
Huh?
[DRAGUNOV]
The boy who defeated Konrad.
And then went on to
stop the Domitor.
For the Inquisition to be this
determined to capture him,
he must be truly special.
You're the only
Inquisitor I trust
who's seen all their faces.
You can count on me, sir.
Their faces are imprinted
clearly in my mind.
Caislean Merlin
in Cyfandir, eh?
That's supposed to
be the ancient city
where magic was first
created, right?
Well, that's what
people say at least.
Seems like Yaga's
grasping at straws to me.
Say, unless I'm misremembering,
that country's protected by
flying knight-sorcerers,
which must mean
it's pretty difficult
to pull off a decent
heist out there.
[DON BOSSMAN]
So, Lady Alma,
you sure ya don't
wanna go with him?
Why should I go?
I've got my own business
to attend to right here.
[DON BOSSMAN]
Yes, ma'am!
As for Seth, the time
when I could tell him
what to do with
his life is over.
Is this what people
call a mother's love?
[ALMA]
Like hell it is!
Now that's a sight!
We've reached it.
The continent of Cyfandir.
[NARRATOR] Seth finally sets
foot in Cyfandir. Alone.
Almost immediately,
he encounters a party
of merchant barons
who wish to exploit the
continent's resources
for themselves.
After an awkward encounter
and a brief chase,
Seth escapes the barons
with the help of an old ally.
Next time on Radiant ,
"An Encounter in the Rain."