[NARRATOR] Upon their return
from Caillte Forest,
Ocoho and Melie were
summoned to the palace
and accused of insubordination.
But due to Mordred's
intervention,
they were spared
the Queen's wrath.
At the same time, Seth
was making great strides
under Myr's guidance,
though he has yet to master
the dark power within him.
Myr tells Seth of a
mysterious darkness
which tried to engulf
him in the Sidh,
and Seth's misgivings about
Piodon continue to grow.
[MYR] Ah. This is getting to be
more than I can handle.
That's enough for now.
[MYR]
So I was right.
When it can't see through the
peephole, it decides to leave.
I need to know, Seth.
If this is from your "brother,"
why would he put something
like this inside of you?
Do you really think his
objective was to save your life?
[SETH sighs]
[SETH groans]
Well, that could've gone better.
[MYR grunts]
[MYR] We've gained some
important knowledge
about this freeloader of yours,
but you couldn't quite manage
to take control of it.
I feel like I came
pretty close though.
I just need something to give me
a little bit more of an edge.
I had that exact thought myself.
Jill, why don't we whip it out?
Sure.
Huh?
[MYR] Across the line
and under the vine.
There.
[SETH]
Hmm...
Is it an armband?
Well, I'd call it a bracelet.
[chuckles]
And, um, not that you asked,
but it's made of wood and hair
from a very special
part of my body.
[screams]
[SETH]
What?!
[NARRATOR] "The Qualifications
of a Knight."
[SETH screams]
[SETH] What the heck did
you put on me, Myr?
I was just kidding, relax!
Learn to smell a joke
already, would ya?
Phew. That's a relief.
You got me good there.
So, what is it really?
Oh, just a little idea
that Jill floated to me.
It should help you keep
that freeloader at bay.
Tell me, do you feel
anything by chance?
It's really warm.
Almost like it's been
out in the sun.
It was fashioned from
the bark of a special tree
found here in Caillte Forest.
You do remember that we immersed
you in a bubble of Jill's sap
in order to bring you back from
death's door earlier, don't you?
[SETH]
Yeah.
[MYR] Well, that sap seeped
inside you through your wounds.
Which means Jill is
now a part of you.
As is the forest itself.
[JILL chuckles]
Now let's hear how
grateful you are.
Oh, yeah. I owe you
big time for this.
[MYR]
Mh-hm.
Let that band strengthen
your newfound connection
to the forest.
Whenever you fear you might
lose control to the shadow
that monitors you from the Sidh,
use that piece of the forest to
anchor yourself to this world.
I'll try that. Thanks!
Guess that's all, right?
You mind if we get
back to training now?
Mhm. Sure.
But one last thing, Seth.
I feel I should give
you a quick warning.
Huh?
Well, um, frankly,
what I saw in the
Sidh scared me.
The force of darkness called
forth by the freeloader
you described as a peephole,
you need to be wary
of it, understand?
[JILL]
Yes. Myr's right.
If that darkness engulfs
you completely,
then there's a chance
that you might never
regain consciousness again.
[MYR] Jill and I have spent a
great deal of time in the Sidh.
We delve into it every day,
and we've never encountered
something so hostile there.
So, yeah.
You just need to get that pesky
little freeloader sealed away
so as to keep it from telling
the darkness where you are,
and then you'll have
nothing to worry about!
How this goes will depend
the state of your heart.
That, and the size
of your stones.
[chuckles]
Whatever.
Look, I made a promise to Melie
and I'm not about
to break my word.
I'll get this thing
under control.
No matter how long
it takes, I'mma do it!
[MYR]
We're glad to hear that.
You've got the right
attitude, Seth.
Work hard and have fun doing it.
Totally!
I bet Melie and
Ocoho are training
with the knight-sorcerers
day in and day out.
I've gotta hustle to keep up!
[horn blaring]
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS chattering]
What's going on?
A Nemesis has appeared
in the farmland
on the outskirts of town.
[BRANGOIRE]
Is it a Spectre?
[SAGRAMORE]
No.
It appears to be the
standard variety, sir.
All right.
All knight candidates and
squires should make ready.
I want you on your dragons
in the next two minutes.
Anyone who lags behind
will be punished
first by my fist
and second by my-my--
Oh, what's it matter?
The point is, you'll
be punished severely!
Yeah. So move it!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Sir!
That order was for knight
candidates and squires,
not for you trainees.
You guys had better
stay home for this one.
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Right!
[LORD DE GULIS laughing]
You truly are a
harried creature,
aren't you, my dear
Lord Brangoire?
[BRANGOIRE]
Lord de Gulis.
You can set your
worries aside now.
Under my command, I promise
you'll find glory aplenty.
More than enough to restore
your recently sullied honor.
Ha! Uh.
My fire-kissed angel, Melie!
Tell me, my carrot.
Are you planning to join
us on this operation?
Um, I'd like to.
It seems fire has kissed
your hair and your soul!
Thou art a cruel Valkyrie!
I can picture you soaring
over the battlefield already!
I should--
And I'm certain I'm not alone
for I daresay a captivating
beauty such as yours
could beguile any hero,
living or dead.
Huh. Okay.
Ah, but wait! Battling a Nemesis
can be terribly perilous!
Knowing that,
I want you to stay in the
safest place in this world.
Yes. You'll fly
behind yours truly.
Sure. Got it.
[chuckles] Very good.
And as one last precaution, I'll
give you this protective charm.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[LORD DE GULIS screaming]
[LORD DE GULIS stammering]
[MELIE]
Oh, no. I'm really sorry!
[LORD DE GULIS]
Don't be, my dear, it's fine.
All has gone according
to plan, I assure you.
What's a thorn or three to a
seasoned warrior such as mys--?
[BRANGOIRE]
That's enough, Lord de Gulis!
We're in the midst
of an emergency--
we must move immediately.
Pha! I see that your approach
is just as graceless
as it's always been.
[BRANGOIRE]
Come again?
It's in times of urgency
that we need to relax the most.
Fear and anxiety tend to
spread like twin plagues.
A true knight-sorcerer serves
as both the people's sword
and their star of hope.
Therefore, we must be
elegant in all things.
[BRANGOIRE grumbles]
Let's just go already.
Knights, mount your
dragons at once.
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Sir!
[OCOHO]
'Kay. You ready?
Let's hunt this Nemesis.
[FARMERS yelling]
Petro!
[PETRO screams]
Whoa. How are we okay?
By Merlin's beard, we're safe.
[LORD DE GULIS laughing]
You good people had quite
the close call, I see.
I'm Lord de Gulis.
If you've heard stories about
Gulis the Nemesis Slayer,
then you know my name well!
[laughs]
[FARMER A]
Whoa. The Golden Knight!
[LORD DE GULIS yells]
[LORD DE GULIS]
What's happening?! Where am I?!
Confounded cape!
Fear not, citizens!
This is all according to plan!
[BRANGOIRE]
Lord de Gulis!
We're meant to fight
the Nemesis as a group.
Forgive me.
When I saw these helpless
villagers in danger,
my longsword all-but
moved on its own.
[growls]
Dismount!
We'll start by
assessing the damage,
then move on to cleaning
up the Nemesis corpse.
[KNIGHT-SORCERERS]
Sir!
[MELIE] Wow. He killed it
with a single strike.
That's amazing. I didn't
know he was so strong.
Although he is still weird.
Oh, yeah.
Lord de Gulis is one
of the most powerful
knights-sorcerers we have.
But you're right
that he's weird.
He has mentored both Mordred
and Sagramore though,
and look at how they turned out.
They may well be the most
promising knight-candidates
of our generation.
Those two were brilliant
to begin with though,
so that's to be expected.
Huh. But...
Even though they're both
prestigious knight-sorcerers,
Lords Brangoire and Gulis
seem kind of, well...
...they're very different.
Yeah, I'm sure you've noticed
that they don't get
along all that well.
And I wouldn't really
expect them to.
They have completely
opposite concepts
of how knight-sorcerers should
conduct themselves.
What would you say is
the main difference?
To put it sympathetically,
Lord de Gulis is kind of
a heroic individualist.
He believes that knights should
showcase their unique abilities
and behave like
champions of the people.
While on the other hand,
Lord Brangoire is a
firm disciplinarian
who values humility and
efficient teamwork.
It sorta seems like he's
the one who's actually right.
Kind of.
Teamwork is great,
but Lord Brangoire
can take it too far.
I wish he was more
flexible, you know?
Also, his gruff
approach to things
hasn't done much for
his public image.
[MELIE]
Interesting.
So even though they're
knights of the same order,
they still disagree about stuff.
Yeah, that's perfectly normal.
Is it now?
So is that why you like
to disobey your orders?
You're the one who
charged into Caillte Forest
after I warned you not to.
[BRANGOIRE] What are you
two blabbering about?
[OCOHO]
Uh-oh.
[MELIE yells]
That girl again... Honestly.
Huh? What's this?
[KNIGHT-SORCERER B]
Lord Brangoire! There's trouble!
[BRANGOIRE]
Report!
Another Nemesis
has appeared nearby!
[BRANGOIRE]
Nearby. Which way?
Just on the other
side of that hill,
near a settlement
to the north, sir!
It's much larger than
the last one was.
Cease your work
for the time being!
There's a giant Nemesis we've
gotta take out, so mount up!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Sir!
[LORD DE GULIS laughing]
Huh?
I hear that a Nemesis
of prodigious size
has just appeared.
I must ride!
If you're in the air now,
you can form my vanguard!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Sir!
Ah, crap.
Of course de Gulis would
try something like this.
The rest of you are
with me, get moving!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Yes, sir!
We should move.
Right!
[FARMER D] Ah. Those knights
are an inspiration!
I pray the great
Merlin's blessing
will ride with every
last one of them!
You've got this!
Kill the monster!
Now that was a stirring
call to action, my boy!
You've a warrior's
heart! Well said!
Drink your milk so you can grow
up strong like me, all right?
You're a fine soldier,
but as a knight-sorcerer,
you should give
more consideration
to the image you cultivate.
There's no need.
I don't care if these civilians
love us or hate us,
just so long as they're safe.
Regardless, we should
discuss our strategy
for vanquishing
that huge Nemesis.
Hmm...
This one's a real threat.
We should approach with caution.
Why don't we split up
into proper squads
and go for a pincer maneuver?
Using Gysoni, of course.
And keeping our distance.
Ah! You know what?
That gave me a splendid idea!
Why don't we have our squads
compete in a contest?
Say what?
The squad that
defeats the Nemesis
shall sit at a banquet
hosted by the losers!
No. I won't participate in
this absurd game of yours.
Brave knights of my vanguard,
we ride to battle!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Sir!
[growls]
We need to back them up.
You heard me!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Sir!
[PETRO] I know you can
beat him, Golden Knight!
You've got this!
You're the best!
[LORD DE GULIS laughs]
[LORD DE GULIS]
Thank you, son! So are you!
[BRANGOIRE] We'll do this
by the book, all right?
Gysoni!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
[OCOHO]
Hmm...
What's wrong?
We need to get moving. It'll be
tough to catch up as it is.
If they see us lagging behind,
then we'll get in trouble again.
I sense something.
Yeah?
Yeah. Whatever it is,
it's not good.
Could it be...?
[OCOHO gasps]
Look at that Nemesis.
It wasn't just one--it's an
entire group of Echoes!
[ALL gasp]
[ALL scream]
You all need to run!
[FARMERS scream]
This won't be enough
to finish them off.
The Echoes are scattered
all over now!
If we aren't careful,
these villagers could end up
caught in the crossfire!
[OCOHO]
Then we'll have to improvise!
[MELIE]
Ocoho!
I'll protect you!
Carserem!
Wow, you created a magical cage
to keep the villagers safe
while you go after the Nemeses.
Pretty clever!
That monster's leg is
trapped in here with us!
Yeah. Sorry about that.
But hey, at least you'll all
be safe in there, right?
Petro. Petro isn't here!
Have at you!
[whistles]
[OCOHO]
Take care of them!
Right!
I'll cut you to shreds!
Barely made it.
I was gonna slay that thing!
Why'd you stop me?
You thought you'd beat it?
You know that you're
an unarmored kid
with a stick, right?
Maybe I don't have a sword,
but the Golden Knight said
I had a warrior's heart!
Well, that much is obvious.
I'm sure you'll grow up
to be crazy strong.
[OCOHO] The Echoes are
trampling the fields.
I can't allow them to cause
any more damage here.
And with everyone
else so far away,
I have no choice but
to handle this myself.
Which means... my only
option is close combat.
Hey, Draccoon, I'm gonna
borrow your senses now!
Gysoni!
[OCOHO]
I'm sorry,
but I can't set you down
on the ground right now,
it's too dangerous.
[PETRO]
That's okay. Lemme at 'em!
That's not gonna happen.
But hey, I've got a
vital mission for ya,
and I think you've got
the courage to take it.
Huh?
Hold on to these reins
as tight as you can
and don't let those monsters
out of your sight.
Understood.
Good luck down there.
I'm rooting for you!
[OCOHO]
All right, I'll be back soon!
[OCOHO yells]
[OCOHO]
Dine!
[sighs]
That went all right,
but I don't know.
How many more times
can I repeat it?
[OCOHO]
Draccoon, go up higher.
Higher!
[OCOHO]
No. There are so many.
[FARMERS yell]
[OCOHO]
I have to do something.
But there's no way I can deal
with all of them by myself.
Come back here, now!
Hey! This way!
Stop with your stupid contest!
If I don't get help here,
these people are gonna die!
[gasps]
[OCOHO]
They're too far to hear me.
It's hopeless.
Thanks to Draccoon, I can see
where all the Echo Nemeses are,
but that doesn't help
me stop them.
What can I do?
Of course!
Lord Brangoire communicates
at a distance with Gysoni.
I could do the same, but...
Doesn't matter!
Let's set the record straight!
How many times do I have
to tell you that on your own,
you're nothing?!
Your personal ambitions
are just rust on the chain
your comrades have formed!
Just be very careful
from now on.
There are many actions that
men are always praised for,
but when a woman
behaves the same way,
she'll be labeled
as impertinent.
They may hold me in
the highest regard,
but the knights are
still a society of men.
And many of them do not
look upon you favorably.
Listen very carefully.
You would do well to try and
lay low until your ordination,
got it?
[giggles]
[OCOHO] I'm supposed to
lay low until I get ordained.
If I go against orders
and pull another stunt,
the knights could
flat out reject me.
I should've just
kept my head down.
followed my orders!
You've got orders?
And why the heck
should that matter?
You think that means you can
blast whatever's in your way?
[OCOHO]
No!
I have to act.
Because the knight-sorcerer
I want to become
is the kind who
protects the people.
I won't be a coward who
ignores someone's suffering
because of an order.
I'll save every life I can.
Even if I'm giving up my
shot at getting ordained!
[OCOHO]
Gysoni!
All my Gysoni bonds were
suddenly disconnected.
What could make that happen?
[gasps]
[BRANGOIRE] Where do
you think you're going?!
[BRANGOIRE] By Merlin,
they're still in Gysoni.
And it seems their flames
have gotten stronger.
What's going on here?
Okay. Fan out!
[OCOHO]
Find your targets.
Fire!
[OCOHO]
Protect the people at all costs.
Eliminate the monsters
that threaten them!
Don't let any escape!
Let's show these Nemeses
how the proud knight-sorcerers
of Caislean Merlin fight!
All that we do, we do for
the life of this land!
[growls]
Looks like we're done.
I think we got all the Echoes.
Okay. Good.
[KNIGHT-SORCERER A]
Huh?
[KNIGHT-SORCERER B]
What the heck just happened?
Well, we had entered Gysoni,
then everything got kinda
blurry all of a sudden,
and I wasn't even able to
hear Lord Brangoire's voice.
[KNIGHT-SORCERER C]
Same here.
I was with Lord de Gulis,
so I didn't even use Gysoni.
Check out all those Nemeses.
It looks like they're dead.
[KNIGHT-SORCERER F]
Who killed them? Was it us?
[KNIGHT-SORCERER G]
If it was, I don't remember it.
[KNIGHT-SORCERER B] And where
do you think all of these Echoes
came from anyway?
Look next to that building.
Do you see her?
Talkin' to you, Sagramore.
[SAGRAMORE]
Is that Ocoho?
Why is there a child
on her dragon?
Hey, knight lady! Wake up!
[DOUSSANT]
Hmm...
It would appear that the
knight-sorcerers defeated
both the Source Nemesis
and its Echoes.
I don't see any
casualties either.
All according to plan.
"According to plan"?
You can't seriously
expect me to believe
that you predicted the actions
of that knight-candidate girl.
Yes, I'll admit I was
somewhat surprised
by the extent of the
young lady's power.
But if we play our hand wisely,
her strength might just
increase our profits.
Her name is Ocoho, by the way.
She's been extremely useful
to our cause already.
And she'll continue to be
the cornerstone of our plan.
[NARRATOR] Fantasia is
the power of imagination.
A link with Fantasia is
a link to the world.
Armed with Myr's teachings,
Seth faces the shadowy monitor
within himself once more.
He attempts to control
it with Fantasia,
but its strength
is hard to match.
Can Seth evict the
freeloader at last?
Next time on Radiant ,
"Now, Feel the World."