[NARRATOR] After infiltrating
Caislean Merlin on orders
to capture Seth
and his companions,
Dragunov and Liselotte received
word from General Torque.
They were to attend
a clandestine meeting,
deep in the forest.
Waiting to greet them were
a group of merchant barons
led by Doussant himself.
The truth of the conspiracy
brewing in this land
will soon be revealed.
[LISELOTTE]
We finally got into the city
only to be ordered out of it.
Strange.
And I know they're
trying to be discreet,
but this seems like overkill.
[DRAGUNOV] These people are
either overly cautious
or up to something
truly nefarious.
Regardless, General Torque
ordered us to meet with them.
You sound reluctant, Dragunov.
I'd almost use the same word
to describe how you looked
when the general said
you were being promoted.
You seemed none too enthused.
I can assure you
that I was pleased.
I just don't express joy
as outwardly as most.
Ah. I'm glad you
managed to find us.
Forgive the rustic
nature of the venue.
I am Baron Doussant,
and you are Captains
Liselotte and Dragunov
of the Thaumaturges, yes?
[NARRATOR]
"Your Decision."
Welcome, Captain Liselotte.
We're always honored to speak
with the Inquisition,
but especially when they send
an emissary of your repute.
This goes for you as well,
Captain Dragunov.
That's enough flattery.
Why don't you state
your business?
You've the attention
of two Thaumaturges,
so you'd best have something
to say that's worth our time.
[chuckles]
Then allow me to get
directly to the point.
I invited you here to
discuss the Harmonizium.
[LISELOTTE]
And what might that be?
[DOUSSANT]
A ground-breaking device
capable of nullifying Fantasia.
The knight-sorcerers are
normally quite powerful.
But if we stripped them of
the power to use magic,
they would be quake
before the might of Bome.
What are you suggesting?
The stage is set for
an armed intervention.
You're asking us to
invade the continent?
This country's ruled
by the infected.
Which, from where I'm standing,
seems to make its very existence
an insult to the Inquisition.
Am I wrong in assuming
that General Torque
would like to finish the work
your Patrem Inquisitor began?
Perhaps he would.
With a successful campaign here,
we could restore our
damaged reputation.
Yes, indeed.
That little incident
at Rumble Town
must've hurt the
Inquisition quite a bit.
It did.
And I'm sure you'll exploit that
as you would anything else.
Listen, this is my humble
offer to General Torque.
This land is ripe
for the taking.
War could secure a wealth
of new resources for us
and a restoration
of dignity for you.
We can iron out
the details later.
Let us forge an alliance
to reshape this world.
You certainly are a smooth
talker, Baron Doussant.
Is that so?
Has something I've said
come off as insincere?
You say you want new resources.
I'd like you to be
more specific.
Dragunov the Lynx Eye,
I'm beginning to see
why you were brought
into General Torque's
inner circle.
Out of respect for your
piercing insight,
I'll speak the truth in full.
The true objective of this
merchant baron entente
is to make sorcerers hated,
remove them from any
place of authority,
and divest them of their rights
so they might be used
as our slaves.
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Ocoho,
who had learned that someone
was taking advantage
of her curse
and using her to summon Spectral
Nemeses without her knowledge,
went to confront
her chief suspect
and childhood friend, Mordred.
[SETH] A little while back I saw
you with Mordred in the stables.
To be honest, I thought he
was kissing you at the time,
but then your eyes went hollow.
[MORDRED]
What's up?
Oh. Hey, Ocoho.
Seems kinda late for a visit.
Is there something
the matter, or what?
Why don't you tell me?
Sure, come in.
What's wrong with you?
We're comrades.
Every day we fight for Cyfandir.
Every day we risk our lives
to protect the people here.
[MORDRED]
I'm sorry.
You've betrayed us.
Your country and
your fellow knights.
That's not true.
Please, just hear me out.
We're on the same
side, I promise.
Be quiet!
Foreigners are trying
to invade our country!
And you expect me to believe
those Spectral Nemeses
are protecting us somehow?
[MORDRED] We only use
them against people
who've betrayed Cyfandir.
Don't give me that crap!
Spectres hurt everyone!
They don't check your loyalty
before crushing you.
[MORDRED] We're doing this
to secure Merlin's legacy.
Please just trust me.
I did trust you, Mordred!
More than anybody else.
That's why... I knew it was you.
You're the only person I told,
so no one else could've
used me like that.
Now fess up. Tell the truth.
Why did you force me to plant
those stones for you? Why?
I promise I only did it
to protect you, Ocoho.
Don't lie to me.
I'm done playing the fool.
[MORDRED]
I'm telling the truth.
The Faithful of the Hermit
wanted to use you more directly.
They wanted to make
you their assassin.
Their assassin? Against who?
[coughs]
The same people we
use the Spectres on.
Farmers who trade
with foreigners.
Knight-sorcerers who've
turned against Merlin.
The Faithful of the Hermit
have a long list of people
they'd like to see dead.
But you're important to me,
so I couldn't let them
use you like that.
I convinced them to have you
summon the Spectres instead.
Like that's better.
And even if it is the truth,
I still can't believe
a thing you say.
[OCOHO]
I have to tell the queen.
She likes me. If I tell her,
she'll believe me.
I'm sure of it.
I wouldn't recommend
that if I were you.
To become a Faithful
of the Hermit,
a defender of the great
Merlin's legacy,
one must first swear fealty
to the queen herself.
You understand what
that means, right?
Please help me, Merlin.
You're the founder
of Caislean Merlin.
The wise guardian
of all of Cyfandir.
So please, help me
save your land.
Lend me your strength.
And your wisdom as well.
[MYR]
You know that's a rock, right?
Rocks aren't especially wise.
[OCOHO gasps]
Ah! Hey, Myr.
I know you like to pop up out of
nowhere and mess with people,
but I'm trying to pray
to Merlin right now.
Sounds pretty important.
So did he get turned into
a big hunk of unmoving stone
or was he always like this?
[OCOHO]
This isn't actually him.
It's obviously just
a statue that was made
to represent Merlin.
Yeah, I really didn't feel
like talking to it
was gonna help you before,
but this pretty much
confirms my doubts.
Back me up, Seth, what do
you think about this rock?
Huh?
You were in there with him?
What were you guys doing?
After all the time
in the forest,
I don't really like sleeping
in beds anymore.
So tired.
So how did your talk
with Marmot go?
You don't have to say.
We were childhood friends.
I remember the first time
we saw the knight-sorcerers
flying above us
on their dragons.
They looked so cool.
We decided then and there
that when we grew up,
we'd become knights just like
them and protect our country.
All these years, we've worked
hard to reach our goal.
But one of the friends that
I was chasing that dream with
used the trust I put
in him against me.
And he says he did it
on orders from the queen
I'd hoped to serve.
The Ordination
Ceremony's so close.
What am I supposed to believe?
I feel so lost.
And my feet sorta carried
me here on their own.
I guess I just wonder what
Merlin would've done.
I'll tell you one thing.
That Merlin guy,
he wouldn't walk around
asking rocks for help.
Fair point.
To be honest, I'm not sure
if I'm actually fit
to defend Cyfandir.
You know?
[SETH]
You can protect anything.
Look, Ocoho.
I heard all about how you fought
that army of Nemeses.
Most people would've
chickened out, but not you.
You fought your hardest.
Not for praise or glory.
You didn't get any.
You fought to protect
the people. And you won.
Maybe you'll become a knight.
Maybe you won't.
Either way, you've done
something to be proud of.
You can handle this. It's okay.
Just keep your eyes open
and do the next right thing.
[OCOHO]
The next right thing.
Sounds simple enough.
[PEOPLE chattering]
[LISELOTTE] Come on.
This is such a stupid idea.
[DRAGUNOV]
What is?
[LISELOTTE]
Dressing up like this.
We aren't wanted--we've no
need for these disguises.
Nothing more than
a simple precaution.
Ugh.
Bet we could've gotten through
in full Inquisition uniform.
Not a guard to be seen.
They haven't even set up
a checkpoint at the gate.
The sorcerers have
grown incautious.
It seems they've enjoyed too
much peace and quiet lately.
If only they knew
what was coming.
The merchant barons
have concocted
quite the ambitious plan.
[DRAGUNOV]
Yes.
[LISELOTTE]
They're a shady bunch,
but you made the right call
in dealing with them.
And that's not the only way
that you've done well
over the past few weeks.
You were praised by
the general himself.
[CROWD cheering]
[ALL gasp]
[MELIE giggles]
Huh? That armor.
Look! Ocoho's riding through!
[SETH]
Oh, cool!
She looks really gallant;
don't you agree?
Uh. Although she also looks
a little nervous, huh?
[SETH]
Ocoho.
Ocoho, are you okay?
[OCOHO]
Seth?
What's up? Still nervous about
the Ordination Ceremony?
No, that isn't really it.
[SETH]
Huh?
I've accepted that I might
not become a knight.
And regardless, I know
what it is I need to do.
I'm glad to hear that.
We'll talk more after.
'Kay. Best of luck to ya.
Right back at'cha, Seth.
My darling knight-sorcerer
candidates.
Each of you has fought
to defend Cyfandir.
And now for your reward.
You shall each be welcomed
into a noble family.
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
My Queen!
Now, if I'm to take the
mentor lords at their word,
then amongst this
crop of candidates
are some of the strongest
warriors this castle has seen.
I am oh so proud of you!
Always keep the teachings of
Merlin close to your hearts.
Here before the sacred tree that
has survived the flames of war,
let us spare a thought
for the events of the past
as we celebrate the present.
Now, my lords!
Before we can begin festivities,
we must carry out our duty!
Examine the candidates
and choose those
who are worthy to succeed you.
Let the first candidate
step forth.
[NARRATOR]
Elsewhere,
Seth slipped into the Castle
Archive with Doc at his side.
[SETH]
It's just like Ocoho told us.
There are barely any
guards at all today.
Can ya remind me why ya
need me to trespass with ya?
I thought you wanted to see
the books in the archive.
Yeah, but no book's worth
gettin' arrested over.
If we get caught,
it's straight to the dungeon!
I'm not crossin' any
more dangerous bridges
than I have to!
Good luck, but you're
on your own. Yeah.
Doc!
No one's gonna catch us, relax.
I need you to find the weird
rock that Grimm asked for.
Help me out.
Oh, fine.
[SETH]
See ya.
Once ya track that down,
you can do what you want.
[DOC]
Wait! Hold on a minute!
[SETH]
Huh?
Look, despite myself, I can't
help but be a little worried.
I mean, what if that
Diabal guy attacks you
with another Spectre?
I have to talk to him.
If it'll help me to
understand my power,
then it's worth taking
just about any risk.
Later.
You're just gonna go?
Well, don't get killed.
Ya big jerk.
[BRANGOIRE] Let the next
knight-candidate come forward
so the lords might
judge your worth.
[CROWD murmuring]
No one's taking her.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
This is rather troubling.
Is there no lord among you
who wishes to take on this
girl as their successor?
With all due respect,
Your Majesty.
This candidates' record
is highly questionable,
featuring a long list of
insubordinate actions.
Let us know if you disagree
with that, Lord Brangoire.
[grunts]
We have duties at home.
People to govern, fiefdoms
to protect, and more.
All that we've built for
ourselves would be threatened
should we take on such an
untamable, unreliable successor.
[CROWD murmuring]
Selection of knight candidates
is the mandate of the lords,
but please, friends, consider
reviewing her candidacy
one last time.
[OCOHO] It's fine, My Queen.
I don't need this.
[CROWD gasps]
Just what are you trying to say?
That the title of knight-
sorcerer is no longer something
I would fight to attain.
[CROWD chattering]
I'm sure that you
must be frustrated,
but bitter as this
defeat may be,
you mustn't let it demean
your honor as a knight.
[OCOHO] The honor of the knights
was already demeaned,
and the one who brought them
low was you, Your Majesty.
When you set the Spectres
loose amongst your people!
[BOUDICA]
Excuse me?
[SOLDIER A]
What's she talking about?
[SOLDIER B]
That's impossible.
The queen would never
betray her citizens.
[BOUDICA] You say I brought
forth the Spectres?
You make a grave and
unexpected accusation.
Even if it's but a joke
made in poor taste,
this isn't the time
to say such thi--
You're wrong. This is the time
to demand an explanation.
And the accusation I just
made was no joke.
I have a duty to this country.
People of Cyfandir,
you have to listen to me!
Spectral Nemeses don't
appear naturally,
they're made by people!
They're used as weapons by a
secret group of conspirators.
A group known as the
Faithful of the Hermit.
[CROWD gasps]
[OCOHO] This group has
been punishing people
who interact with outsiders by
unleashing Spectres on them.
They wish to rule us through
fear from the shadows.
They claim to uphold
Merlin's will, but...
If he were here today,
I think he'd hate everything
they stand for.
And so, I'm dragging these
cowards into the light.
The Faithful of the Hermit
are based in this castle
and their members have
infested our country
at the highest level!
[LORD DE GULIS] I think
we've heard quite enough
from this insolent child.
Guards, do your duty.
Remove her from our sight!
Gysoni!
How did she do that?
Such an incredibly
strong Gysoni.
[BANGOIRE]
None of us were open to it,
yet it took hold of
the younger lords.
I feel the grip of
her will, even now.
You truly are full of
surprises, my dear.
I hate to repeat myself,
but this is not the time.
You once said that you
have nothing to hide
from your people, My Queen.
Even now, I want
to believe in you,
but I can't while you
hide the truth.
If you actually care
about your subjects,
then tell us what you know.
Expose the villains who've been
victimizing your people
and cast them down!
Do not let this arrogant
girl's blathering sway you!
The good people of Cyfandir
have nothing to be afraid of.
The little fool's lying
through her teeth,
for no other reason than to
assuage her wounded pride.
We can only pray that
the next knight candidate
who's found unfit to
join a great family
accepts their fate
with more dignity.
I challenge this entire
assembly to search my voice
for any trace of a lie.
And then I'd ask these people
to do the same with
you, Lord de Gulis.
Because from where I'm standing,
you sound like
you're full of crap.
[LORD DE GULIS]
Be silent!
You've always been an
insubordinate wretch.
Problem children like you
need to be punished.
[gasps]
[LORD DE GULIS yells]
You raise your weapon
on the girl's behalf?
What's the meaning of
this, Lord Brangoire?
[BRANGOIRE] You're acting
rashly, Lord de Gulis.
You're only so intent on
silencing this candidate
because you're involved
in the conspiracy yourself.
And Lord de Gulis isn't
the only traitor here.
Who else among our ranks
has been preying
on your own people
while my brave soldiers fought
and died to protect them?
Huh. Looks like it's about
one fourth of you.
Citizens, what this girl
says is lamentable,
but I'm willing to vouch
for her honesty.
The Spectral Nemeses
are made by men!
[CROWD chattering]
This is disappointing.
Tell me, do you derive
some kind of enjoyment
from upsetting my people?
If you harbored such suspicions,
you should've told me
about them in private.
[BRANGOIRE]
With all due respect, My Queen,
after all that I've learned,
I don't know who I
can trust anymore.
Lord Brangoire,
I have always counted you
amongst my most loyal retainers.
So you can imagine my surprise
at seeing you turn against me
to take the side of a child.
[BRANGOIRE]
I am a knight-sorcerer.
I will oppose with all my might
anyone who threatens
my country or it's people.
Thanks for speaking up, sir.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
[MELIE]
Huh?
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[CROWD gasps]
My Queen, dire news
from the coast.
What has happened to you?
It's... the Inquisition!
[OCOHO gasps]
[SOLDIER A] They've come
with a massive armada.
It's an invasion!
[SANTORI] I've been wanting
to re-establish relations
with the knight-sorcerers,
and a war seems like
just the way to do it.
By my beard, I couldn't
be more delighted.
There's such a wonderful sense
of nostalgia in the air.
I feel like I'm heading
to a family reunion.
You're right, Santori.
I know just how ya feel.
Yes. It is like we're heading
to a family reunion.
[NARRATOR] The Inquisition
launches their invasion swiftly.
Queen Boudica swears to resist
them to the bitter end.
Meanwhile, Seth
infiltrates the castle
and confronts Diabal regarding
their similarities.
He then learns the
truth about Piodon.
Who exactly are these men?
And what is their
connection to Seth?
Next time on Radiant ,
"The Final Battlefield."