[NARRATOR]
After losing his wife,
Myr turned into a great beast
and set off on a rampage.
Without the forest
to tether him,
Seth succumbed to his inner
darkness and joined Myr.
Meanwhile, Fantasia continues
to disappear from the land.
Life continues to wither away,
and foolish humans
continue to fight.
[MELIE] Seth! Don't let
yourself lose control!
[gasps]
No!
Wait! Seth!
I know that name.
The historians say that it's
the great one's true name.
That creature is Merlin.
[SETH, MYR yelling]
[gasps]
I can feel it!
His soul's been twisted
into an exquisite knot
of boundless grief
and anguished rage.
Magnificent! Please,
let me suffer with you!
I call on you,
Patrem Inquisitor,
noble bringer of all miracles.
Let your divine
light shine forth
and guide those who are lost!
[ULLMINA]
Oh.
I've never seen such
complete and utter agony.
You poor child.
It'll be all right, dear.
Just let it out, okay?
Give it to me,
and don't hold back.
[INQUISITION CAPTAIN A]
The magic barrier's
starting to falter, sir!
We'll knock those standing
stones down soon enough!
Continue the bombardment!
[INQUISITION SOLDIERS gasping]
What the--?
[INQUISITION CAPTAIN A screams]
[GRIMM]
Greetings. Might Grimm join you?
[NARRATOR] "A Bouquet of
Flowers for This Land."
[BOUDICA]
Myrddin.
I didn't know that you lived.
I didn't know we'd be attacked.
I've been so completely
blind. And now--
My Queen.
Ocoho.
[OCOHO yells]
[OCOHO screams]
You okay? Don't be reckless.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Keel that up and
you'll be crushed.
I don't care.
[OCOHO yells]
I swear in Merlin's name,
they can wound my body,
but they will not conquer
my spirit or my country!
[yells]
[BOTH scream]
[MELIE]
Please, stop!
[BOUDICA crying]
[OCOHO]
Your Majesty, we need you.
Please help us defend this land!
No, it isn't the land
that matters.
Every living thing's in danger,
as are your loyal subjects!
All of us are in peril.
These invaders would leech
the life from our land
and enslave us!
The people's anguish
is your own, isn't it?
Well, then stand up for us.
As long as we fight,
there's still hope!
I tried to fight only
to fail completely.
I don't deserve to call
myself a queen.
[OCOHO]
That's not true.
Now get up. Like it or not,
you're Cyfandir's leader.
You don't have time
to cry right now.
Neither do I.
Please, My Queen.
Stand and fight!
The girl has grown.
[BOUDICA]
You're right.
We've no time to
languish in self-pity.
Our fate is not sealed.
Not while Cyfandir's
defenders draw breath.
All right. No one can destroy
this machine without magic.
No one but me!
[BOTH]
My Queen!
[BRANGOIRE]
The device is huge.
Are you sure you can damage it?
[BOUDICA] It almost sounds
like you're beginning
to underestimate me,
Lord Brangoire.
Our weapons have failed us,
as has our magic, but fear not,
I'm sure my bewitching body
can get the job done.
Wait, no!
[grunting]
My Queen. You have to stop!
No. Just keep going.
I know that you can do this!
Don't give up.
That hunk of scrap metal doesn't
stand a chance against you!
Destroy it! For your people!
She's right!
Metal or not, there isn't
a machine in this world
that can stand against you!
[BOUDICA] I am Queen Boudica,
Sovereign of Cyfandir!
This body is not my own!
Every hair on my head,
every drop of blood
drop in my veins,
it all belongs to my people!
If I meet my end in this
moment, then so be it.
I'll protect this land
till my life is spent!
Don't stop pushing!
Take it down!
Do it for your subjects!
Do it for the great Merlin!
[yells]
[OCOHO]
Your Majesty!
[BRANGOIRE]
Are you all right?
You have my thanks,
but there's no need
to worry, I'm fine.
Queen.
That was amazing.
Well done, My Queen.
[ARTO]
The Fantasia hath returned!
[LANDLAKE]
We're saved!
[DOC yelps]
[GUEN] Ha-ha! We've been
granted new life!
[DOC] I mean, technically,
you guys are still very dead--
[LANDLAKE]
Silence! We must away!
[DOC]
To where?
[ARTO] To track down the
great Myrddin of course!
I need you to
help me rescue Seth.
He fought as hard as he could to
protect your country's citizens,
and if the Inquisition
gets ahold of him,
they'll probably kill him!
[DRAGUNOV] And if they
ever gain the means
to mass-produce these
anti-Fantasia machines,
you sorcerers will
be made helpless.
It's you again.
[DRAGUNOV]
I've come bearing dire news.
The fighting's taken a bad turn.
If you would like,
I can take you to the
horned sorcerer at once.
He's in danger.
Wait, so do you know
where Seth is right now?
[DRAGUNOV] His rampage has
been brought to a halt
by a Thaumaturge called Ullmina.
[MELIE gasps]
Then take me to him.
If there's a chance I can
help, I have to try!
[DOC]
Wait, it's not safe.
[DRAGUNOV]
Hm?
[chirping]
Hold on tight.
[DOC]
H-Hey!
[MELIE gasps]
We'll be there shortly.
Fair warning:
Your friend isn't in his right
mind at the moment.
Do you know how
to calm him down?
No, it was Grimm
who stopped him
when we fled Rumble Town.
That sorcerer who's
covered in bandages?
Perfect. Here goes.
[GRIMM] Hmm. Grimm can
feel Fantasia returning.
Someone must've destroyed
the Inquisition's new toy.
[GRIMM]
The Thaumaturge archer.
This man isn't our enemy.
He's here to help!
[GRIMM] He shot an arrow through
Grimm's shoulder not long ago.
Why should he be trusted now?
What is your objective?
I wish to rescue the
horned sorcerer.
Can you help him?
[GRIMM]
Hmm...
[ULLMINA]
Oh! This feels incredible.
Wave after wave of black torment
is flowing from your
soul to mine.
You're the horned sorcerer.
I've heard a great
deal about you, dear.
This is wonderful.
I'm so glad you're here.
Now, I'd like to take
you to Bome with me,
what do you say?
[ULLMINA gasps]
We got him!
Return that black soul
to me at once, you fiends!
It belongs to me
and no one else!
Don't talk about Seth
like he's a thing!
He doesn't belong to
anyone, understand?!
You can't! No!
No! No! No! No, give it back!
Let's go.
[GRIMM]
Right.
I've done all that I can to
help you for the time being.
Stay alive so you can
prove your cause is just.
I'm rooting for you.
Major Ullmina, are you--? Uh!
It's gone. Without the pain,
all I feel is emptiness.
Why did the pain
have to leave me?
Bring it back to me...
[VERONE] Major Ullmina,
pull yourself together. Major.
...don't care how many sink.
I want my black-hearted...
[VERONE]
Mother!
[ULLMINA]
Huh?
[INQUISITION CAPTAIN B yells]
Compose yourself.
We have work to do.
Prince Verone, it's you.
You should know better
than to use your miracle
on a living being.
It's too dangerous.
You subdued that tainted
creature for a time,
but at the cost of
entwining your spirits.
You lose your mind.
[ULLMINA]
You're quite right.
Yes. I was driven briefly mad.
Dragged towards the pit
in that sorcerer's soul.
[ULLMINA]
But I was pulled out too soon.
One day, I will dive
into that abyss again
and drink his pain
until I drown.
[VERONE] Major Ullmina,
the Harmonizium you deployed
in the forest has been disabled.
Also, the colonel has fallen.
That's most unfortunate.
I suppose we should
take our leave.
For now, the infected
will remain free,
but we will return soon to save
them from their depravity
and guide them back
into the light.
I look forward to the day
when I can give
them my blessing.
[ORDERIC]
Look! They're turning around.
The invaders are retreating!
[SOLDIERS cheering, laughing]
[SOLDIER A]
We did it!
[GUENOLINE]
Cyfandir has been saved!
[MYR roars]
What is that?
[SOLDIER B] It sounded like
some kind of beast.
What in Merlin's
green earth is that?
[MYR roars]
[INQUISITION SOLDIERS scream]
[MELIE gasps]
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[SOLDIER B] It's attacking
the Inquisition's ships!
[SOLDIER C] Could it have been
sent by the great Merlin?
[SOLDIER D]
It must've been!
Let's hear it for
Merlin's familiar!
[SOLDIERS]
Huzzah!
Yes, let us thank
our newfound ally:
The embodiment of
Cyfandir's fury!
Please, Noble Beast, tell us
how we can thank you!
[GUENOLINE] Speak if you're
able. We're listening!
I'll slaughter them all!
[roaring]
Make a shield!
[SOLDIERS]
Sciath!
[roars]
Fall back to the castle,
but stay ready to defend!
[GRIMM] That is nature's
wrath incarnate.
Those sorcerers don't have
a chance of defeating it.
Then we need Seth.
Please, Seth, we need you to
come back to your senses!
Myr's about to kill
a lot of people
and no one else can stop him!
Come on.
[GRIMM]
Try not to excite him further.
He's grown much stronger,
which makes him
harder to restrain.
Sorry, but I have to risk it.
Seth wouldn't want
us to do nothing.
Your friend is in pain, Seth.
Wake up so you can calm him
down before people get hurt!
[roaring]
[SETH yelling]
[GRIMM]
Grimm warned you.
He'll break out of his
bonds at this rate.
[MELIE]
What can I do?
[gasps]
[MELIE] Maybe if I talk
to him through the Sidh.
Seth, if you can hear
me, we need you back.
[gasps]
What is this thing?
Hey, Seth, are you
somewhere in there?
[gasps]
Ocoho, how'd you know to come?
I heard you scream. The sound
carried through the Sidh.
So Seth is inside
this thing, right?
[MELIE]
Yeah.
This is a really crummy time
for you to get overtaken
by your inner darkness,
you know that?
I thought you'd been
training to prevent this!
Please, Seth. Listen!
Myr is on a rampage!
We have to stop him!
[roaring]
Hold on. What's that
Inquisition ship doing?
[ORDERIC]
Is it trying to help us?
Did we kill it?
[roars]
Our shots landed, but
the beast wasn't injured.
How can that be?
It doesn't matter. We just
need to slow it down.
If we keep shooting,
it'll give some soldiers
a chance to escape.
[GOUDEAU, GARVICE]
Sir!
[OCOHO]
Seth! Turn around, damn it!
Just look at us, please!
[GARVICE]
Uh! This is bad.
The beast is facing us now!
Turn us around! Hard to port!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[roars]
[GRIMM]
The bindings are coming loose.
If you're going to wake
Seth, then hurry!
Before he breaks free!
[yelling]
Look, Seth,
I know what it's like
to see a loved one die.
We understand your pain,
but we're not gonna let it turn
you and Myr into monsters!
No matter how hard it is
or how badly it hurts,
we keep our eyes open
and do what's right!
You said you'd find a way
to control this thing,
but that you'd need help.
Well, that's why I'm here.
So let me help you, Seth.
Please don't leave
me behind again!
Myr needs you, Seth. Hurry!
[roars]
This attack'll be even
bigger than the last!
Oh, no.
[SETH]
Titan... Punch!
[DRAGUNOV]
It's him. The horned sorcerer!
[chuckles]
I guess you could say
this makes us even.
So now what?
Perhaps we should flee while the
beast is distracted, Captain.
But once Cyfandir
falls, we're next.
So as long as we have the
strength to make a difference,
we'll use it.
Helping them helps us.
Let's keep up the fight!
[growls]
Listen, I need you to
calm down, okay, Myr?
[growls]
Seeing Jill like that broke me.
So I can't imagine how you felt.
But even so, we both know
that she wouldn't
have wanted this.
No. You're right.
Jill didn't want any of this.
Right.
[MYR] But... if I had crushed
your filthy brethren
when they first gathered
around the forest
and started tearing
at its edges,
none of this would've happened.
And she would still
be alive right now!
Stop! What do you think Jill
would say if she were here?
She's not here. She's gone!
[MELIE gasps]
[roars]
Here goes nothing:
Gravem Carserem!
[roars]
[GRIMM]
Nubes Spectris!
[growling]
[SETH]
Hurry.
We should be rushing
to the others
to help them stop Myr right now.
What are you doing?
[DOC]
I'm checkin' somethin'.
When I got close to Jill's body,
the memory stones
all started to glow.
[OCOHO]
Huh?
Then do you think there's
something under her?
[gasps]
[SOLDIER D]
Take shelter behind the wall!
[SOLDIER E] Trust in Merlin!
His ramparts will protect us!
Trust in Merlin?
I am Merlin, you fools!
And nothing will protect
you from my wrath!
[GRIMM] With that much Fantasia,
he'll send the walls flying.
[roars]
[MYR]
Jill.
If I had just followed
my first instinct...
If I had chased the first
settlers away from this land...
[MYR] If I had ignored your
words of kindness and mercy...
If I had unleashed my rage when
they first provoked it...
...we'd be together.
The little ones...
You and me...
You never would've
been taken from me!
[MISTER BOOBRIE yells]
[MYR]
Huh?
[gasps]
[ORDERIC]
Hm?
Hold on, where'd these vines
come from? Are they magic?
Wait... Jill?
Is that you, Jill?
[SETH]
No, Myr.
[SETH] It hurts just saying it,
but she's not coming back.
Listen.
You know this better
than I do, but still.
Your wife was stronger
than any human weapon.
The Inquisition didn't
kill her with their machine.
At least, not directly.
You see, she could've
survived without Fantasia...
...but they couldn't.
So she made a choice.
Jill chose to give her life
so they would have a chance.
[NARRATOR]
Prejudice, slavery, war.
These things prove that
humans are foolish and weak,
which is why they must
work together to grow.
The long battle
has ended at last,
and in the hopes of
a brighter tomorrow,
Queen Boudica must
make a decision.
Seth's quest, full of fast
friendships cut short,
must continue.
Next time on Radiant ,
"The Future Is With You."