[NARRATOR]
Seth went to the Luchorpan
to speak with his
estranged friends,
but he couldn't find the words
to regain Melie's trust.
The pair parted ways without
resolving their differences.
Seth then met with the
knight-sorcerer candidate Ocoho.
He agreed to help her train
in return for books
from the castle library.
Books which he hopes will
contain clues about Radiant.
[gasps]
It's strange. I keep on
having that same dream.
What's going on with me?
[NARRATOR]
"His Name Is."
[SETH humming]
That should do it!
[JIJI]
Huh?
[DON BOSSMAN, JIJI]
Excuse me, Lady Alma.
The Communication Feather
seems to be stirring!
I can hear just fine,
so stop shouting!
[DON BOSSMAN, JIJI]
Aww...
Get over it! Go fetch me a pen
and a blank piece of parchment.
--[DON BOSSMAN] Can do!
--[JIJI] Do can!
Hey, what's up, Alma!
It's good to hear from you.
This is the second time you've
reached out since you took off.
I'm glad to see you're
still alive somehow.
The last time you called me,
you said you'd convinced
the merchant barons
that you were a spy and
attacked them with magic
before fighting a
"Spectral" Nemesis
half the size of a mountain.
So what've you done since?
Crash into the castle?
Destroy an ecosystem?
Of course not, I know
how to behave myself.
[ALMA]
Oh, do you now?
I guess it must be a coincidence
that chaos follows you
everywhere you go.
[SETH]
Ah, gimme a break!
I've been good lately.
Just training with Ocoho.
She's wearing me out.
Feels like I've got
cavities in my arms.
Ugh. Listen to yourself, Seth,
it's like you've forgotten
why you went to Caislean
Merlin in the first place.
Huh?
You should be
investigating Radiant.
If you've been developing
cavities anywhere,
I'm gonna have to assume it's
in that thick skull of yours.
[SETH] I am investigating
Radiant. Relax.
Whenever I'm not
training with Ocoho,
I'm looking through the
books she brought me
from the library.
It's a lot to go through.
I haven't even found
a single lead yet.
[sighs] If Radiant's
location were in a book,
it wouldn't be much
of a quest you're on.
In that case,
I guess I'mma have to sneak
into the Castle Archives.
[ALMA] If you think that'll
help, then give it a try.
Just make sure you don't
get caught, all right?
[SETH] Don't worry about it!
I've got a foolproof plan!
Do you now?
Why do I worry that your
idea of a "foolproof plan"
is to walk in there
with your hood up
and hope that nobody
cares enough to stop you?
[SETH chuckles]
[ALMA]
Have you seen Melie?
Yeah. Pretty often.
Like every day.
She's taking a knight-
sorcerer training class
taught by these popular
knight candidate guys
named Mold-raid and Saggy-boor.
Oh.
Well, if you know all that,
I guess things have improved.
At least you see each other.
Well, I've definitely
been seeing her,
but I mostly try to look
from a safe distance.
[SETH screams]
What, are you stalking
her from the bushes?
Next time just walk up
and start talking!
Stop acting weird!
It sounds simple when
ya put it like that,
but what am I s'pposed
to say to her?
Ugh! Seth! How should I know?!
Shape up or I'm keepin' tabs
on all the smacks I owe ya!
[SETH]
By the way, I was wondering.
Have you and I ever been
to Caislean Merlin before?
[ALMA] No. Not that
I can recall anyway.
Why do you ask?
It's because of the castle.
It feels familiar.
Like I've been there.
You think you remember it?
I don't quite know.
I keep dreaming about
this stone passage.
And ever since I got
to Caislean Merlin,
these weird memories
that I didn't even
know about keep surfacing.
[door opens]
[gasps]
Someone came in
so I should get going.
I'll give you a
call again later.
[ALMA]
All right. Be careful out there.
Try not to do anything
you'll regret, okay?
And call me more often.
[SETH]
I will. Bye, Alma!
[BOTH]
Hm?
[SETH]
Ocoho and Mold-raid?
Shouldn't they be out
doing drills right now?
Weird. I wonder what
they're talking about.
[SETH gasps]
[SETH]
Oh, boy.
Did I just see something
I wasn't supposed to?
[gasps]
[SETH] Sorry, I wasn't
trying to spy on you.
It's just that I heard
somebody come in here
and I got curious, you know?
Are you okay?
What gives? Is she mad too now?
[MAN A]
Did you hear?
People are saying they saw
the Dullahan last night.
[MAN B]
Again?
[MAN A] This country's
becoming more dangerous
with every passing day.
All right, I'm gonna
head off to my class
with the knight-sorcerers.
Okay. Well, it's good to see
that you're feelin' better now.
What do you mean by that?
[DOC]
Oh, uh, nothin'!
Have fun out there, Melie.
Try to be careful.
Right! You be
careful, too, okay?
Don't eat anything weird
you find lying on the floor!
I'm not a baby anymore!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Nobody asked you!
[DOC growling]
[DOC sighs]
To be honest with ya,
Melie puts on a cheerful front,
but I can tell she's
still thinkin' about
what happened with Seth.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Well, sittin' here worryin'
about it ain't gonna help!
Ya know what? Screw it,
I'm hittin' the town!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Draccoon's such a
pain in the butt.
Ever since I gave him some
extra fruit that one time,
he's been completely insatiable.
[sighs] What a nuisance.
[SAGRAMORE grunting]
Again!
[OCOHO]
Some things never change.
Including your morning training
regimen apparently.
How are ya, Sagramore?
Fine.
I'll work on my
fundamentals every day
for the rest of my life.
That's part of being a knight.
It sounds like you're just
as serious and diligent
as you've always been.
It was the same
when we were kids.
You've always been the most
responsible of the three of us.
[SAGRAMORE] Right, well, being
a knight-sorcerer candidate
means you have to work hard.
[OCOHO]
Yeah, I'm aware of that.
Ocoho, it seems like
you've been slacking
ever since the queen
complimented you.
You're kidding, right?
Well, if that's how ya
feel, come and test me.
Bring it.
[OCOHO]
Careful what you ask for.
[OCOHO yells]
[SAGRAMORE]
Is that all you've got?
So this is the archive entrance.
A good day to you, my lords.
[KNIGHT-SCHOLAR A]
And to you.
I haven't seen the old guy
look up from that scroll once.
He won't notice me if
I'm dressed like this.
Hm?
Now's my chance.
[DOORMAN A]
A good day to you, my lords.
Good day.
A good day to you, my lord.
Right back at'cha.
Wait a moment, please.
Are you completely certain
that you have permission
to access the archives?
Your name isn't appearing
on my scroll.
Oh, yeah? Well, that's
certainly strange.
There must've been
some kind of mistake.
[SETH]
Crap!
I gotta think of an excuse fast,
or I'm gonna get
thrown into jail!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
Think of something!
Like, anything!
[screams]
What are you doing
to my poor list?
Intruder! Someone stop him!
There's an intruder in here?
Let's capture him!
[SETH]
Alma was right!
[KNIGHT-SCHOLAR D]
He came through this way!
[SETH] Wish these guys
would just give up.
Huh?
Wait a second. I've seen
this passage before.
[SETH] That's the symbol
from my dreams.
[KNIGHT-SCHOLAR D] There he is!
We've got him cornered!
[ALL gasp]
[KNIGHT-SCHOLAR E]
He vanished.
[KNIGHT-SCHOLAR C]
No. That's impossible!
[KNIGHT-SCHOLAR D] He must
be nearby. Keep searching!
[KNIGHT-SCHOLAR C]
Where's he hiding?
[sighs]
Now what are the odds of that?
I suddenly passed
through the wall
after I drew that weird
symbol I saw in my dream.
My armor's just getting
in the way here.
[SETH] So this castle has
a secret passage in it.
I wonder where it might lead.
[SETH]
Hm?
[SETH] That's cool. It looks
like I'm inside the walls.
There could be
passages like this one
running through
the whole castle.
So this might get me
into the archives.
[SETH] How's all of this
hidden inside the castle?
[SETH] Something tells
me it's been a while
since they've cleaned down here.
Okay, this place is starting
to creep me out a little bit.
Uh.
Who could that be?
That's the Nemesis from before.
Except only way smaller.
[DIABAL]
Who's there?
Not good.
[DIABAL]
Canfod!
A young man.
Average physique.
No obvious weaponry.
[SETH]
He's inspecting me.
[DIABAL] A small stone in
his left pocket, and...
[DIABAL gasps]
[DIABAL]
Horns? No. This can't be!
I should've been safe in here.
This isn't fair!
Where did I go wrong?
How did he find me?
Whoa. It's okay!
[DIABAL]
Stay back!
I guess hiding here from
the world wasn't enough.
I won't let you take me!
I would rather die!
[SETH]
Hey, calm it down!
I think you're mistaking
me for someone else.
I'm not after anyone.
I just happened to find
this passage by accident!
[DIABAL] Save your breath,
I know you're lying!
Those horns of yours are
all the proof I need to see!
I don't know how you managed
to find me down here...
...but I won't let you
capture me alive, Piodon!
What? Piodon?
[DIABAL]
Maybe I should call for backup.
I could try, but even
if I do, he's too strong!
Wait a sec. You just
called me Piodon, right?
So, do you know who he is?
[DIABAL] No. The process
has already begun.
I have no choice!
What is this?
Did you just cage me in here?
[SETH]
Hey! Hang on a minute!
I'm not your enemy, I swear!
Just talk to me, please!
Why's there a Nemesis in here?
What is this place for?
C'mon, man, don't just leave!
[FARMERS chattering]
Oh, no.
It's a Spectre! Look out!
[FARMER B]
Everyone run!
Get away from the fields!
[FURGONDE screams]
[FURGONDE]
It's a giant ghost!
If it sees us, we're done for!
What do you think we should do?
'Twas I who discovered it,
so the naming rights are mine.
I shall christen
it "Spectrolom"!
Wow. It is quite big.
But I'm sure we can catch it
for my collection somehow.
No! That's the worst
idea ever! Let's run!
Hush. We're perfectly
safe where we are.
And furthermore, this could
be what we've waited for.
The catalyst of a true crisis.
[LISELOTTE]
Look at that.
One of the Spectral Nemeses
we've heard about.
So, what do we do?
I'm not sure why you're
asking for my input on this.
You have seniority here.
We're of equal status now.
Besides, I've trusted
your judgment
ever since I served with you.
You were always on the mark.
[DRAGUNOV]
I do what I can.
The heck am I looking at?
Is that me standing there?
I get it now. This must be
where the Spectrals come from.
Whatever's within the
barrier gets projected.
[FARMERS shouting]
[FARMER C] The house!
My kids are still in there!
This is bad.
If I take so much
as a single step,
then I could end up
crushing dozens of people.
For the time being,
I need to stay still.
I can find a way out of
this mess, I always do.
[FARMER B] Look up there!
It's another Spectral Nemesis!
[gasps]
It poisoned me.
[FARMER A] Look out!
The first one's falling!
Run!
[horn blares]
[BRANGOIRE] This is an
emergency! Move it!
We've had a Spectral
Nemesis sighting
12 leagues east of Sylverive!
We're deploying in two
minutes, ready or not!
Each of you will fly
out of this stable!
Either on your dragons
or at the end of my boot!
[OCOHO] You're kidding me. We're
really deploying right now?
I'm in big trouble.
Seth still has Lulu's armor
and he's disappeared!
Don't guess you could tell
me where he went, Draccoon.
[BRANGOIRE]
Mordred!
Why have you brought a pack
of novices into my stable?
[MORDRED] They're here to
observe the operation, my lord.
And since it's an emergency,
they can also provide us
with a little support.
I won't allow it.
[MORDRED] This was an order
from the queen, sir.
Then I welcome their presence!
Where's Sagramore gone?
I don't know, but I'm sure
he'll be here any minute.
"Any minute," eh?
First the Lord de
Gulis disappears
and now Sagramore's gone?
Those Spectral Nemeses aren't
gonna give us a minute!
Nemeses?
Our guards at the watchtower
reportedly saw
two specimens at the same spot.
As if dealing with one
weren't hard enough.
[BRANGOIRE] The only
knights who've defeated
a Spectral Nemesis
are you, Sagramore,
and the Lord de Gulis.
We needed all three of
you here for this fight.
We've lost far too many of our
comrades to these monsters.
Ordained knights and
candidates alike.
I cannot assign you a new
partner. It's too dangerous.
[OCOHO]
If Mordred needs a partner...
...then I volunteer.
[BRANGOIRE]
Who are you?
I'm Ocoho and I've served under
you for the last three years!
How do you not know that?
Right.
You're the pain in my butt
that the queen's
taken a liking to.
Ocoho, I appreciate you,
but... don't do this.
I have to--we're
short on fighters!
If we can't beat these
Spectral Nemeses,
who knows how many civilians
they'll end up killing?
I've been training with you
and Sagramore all this time!
I know, but you--
[BRANGOIRE] Hmm. It's true
that this is a bad idea.
But Sagramore isn't here,
and she volunteered.
She's going with you, Mordred.
On your mounts, all of
you. It's time to fly!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Yes, sir!
Hey, is everything all
right with you, Mordred?
Uh. Yeah. I'm just fine.
Say, would you mind taking
charge of the trainees
for a couple of minutes?
I still need to get my
dragon ready for battle,
so I'll catch up
with you in a bit.
'Kay.
[TRAINEE whispering]
'Kay. Let's go. Does
everyone have their brooms?
[TRAINEES]
Yeah!
I know we're throwing you
into this kinda fast.
Just stay safe and do your best
not to fall too far behind us!
[TRAINEES]
Yes, ma'am!
[FARMER C]
Hm?
[FARMER E] I don't understand.
Wasn't it falling?
[FARMER C]
Yeah, but it stopped.
[FARMER F]
We've been saved!
[FARMER G]
The great Merlin has blessed us!
[SETH grunting]
[SETH]
I'm starting to go numb.
Before too long, my body's
gonna give out on me.
What's wrong with you?
Why don't you attack me again
and finish what you started?
[SETH]
Does it only react to movement?
[SETH] I'm slipping.
At this rate, I'll--
No. I can't let myself fall.
I have to hang on!
[GRIMM]
Look at that.
You truly do have a talent
for getting yourself
into trouble, Seth.
This is most unfortunate.
And there's nothing Grimm
can do to help you directly.
But Grimm can free you
to defend yourself
without fear of harming someone.
That projection must
be bound to an object.
If it's destroyed,
the spell will break.
So what do you intend to do
once we've arrived at the scene?
I merely aim to fulfill
my duty as an Inquisitor.
Which means saving as
many lives as I can.
The Inquisition has
no power here,
so our best chance of catching
that horned sorcerer
and his friends
is to keep a low profile
till we've found them.
Staging a mass rescue could
put that in jeopardy.
What you're suggesting right now
does everything short of going
directly against our orders.
I'd do it even if it
went against them.
[LISELOTTE]
Hmph.
You really haven't
changed a bit.
Those are dragons.
These must be the
knight-sorcerers.
[gasps]
So that's a Spectral Nemesis.
It's kinda shaped
like a human being.
Oh, wow!
These Spectrals always
look pretty strange,
but I've never seen
one like this before.
Wild.
Are you ready, Draccoon?
Let's show the world
how hard we've trained.
All the blood, sweat,
and tears we've shed
will be worth it once we've
defeated these Nemeses!
Once I knock these
Spectrals into orbit,
even Lord Brangoire will
have to acknowledge me!
[MELIE]
Ah!
[BOTH]
That's Seth!
[BOTH gasp]
[NARRATOR] A so-called Spectral
Nemesis which looks like Seth
towers over homesteads
and terrified farmers,
while the motives of the man
who created it remain unknown.
Then, a badly poisoned
Seth blacks out.
While he finds his psyche
relegated to the realm
of consciousness,
his body is at the mercy
of the dark power
which lurks inside him.
Next time on Radiant ,
"The Spectre Battle."