[NARRATOR] Seth stumbled
into a hidden chamber
in Caislean Merlin's keep.
There, he was trapped
alongside a Nemesis
within a device that projected
them both as Spectres.
Seth succumbed to
the monster's poison,
and then went berserk,
but was nonetheless bested
by Diabal and his allies.
After a rescue from Myr,
Seth began to train with
him in Caillte Forest.
By opening his
senses to Fantasia
and letting it connect
him to the world,
Seth conquered his
inner darkness
and learned to
create with magic.
Meanwhile, the citizens have
enjoyed a brief respite
from the Spectral Nemesis menace
as they prepare for the
Knight Ordination Ceremony.
However, this peace is
bound to be shattered.
For unbeknownst to the people,
a great conspiracy is
afoot in the capital.
Cyfandir will soon add a dark
new chapter to its history.
[NARRATOR]
"The Truth Is Like a Curse."
[TOWNSBOY A]
What's the party about?
[TOWNSMAN A]
Has no one told you kids?
It's for the
Ordination Ceremony.
They'll be anointing
a new group of knights.
[TOWNSBOY B]
Cool! I wanna be a knight!
Wait, how many
years has it been
since the last ceremony?
[TOWNSMAN C]
Too many if you ask me!
But with all these
people flooding in,
we stand to make a fortune!
If we do our work well,
and if Merlin wills it...
Hey. Stop that.
We can't finish cleaning if you
don't stand still, Draccoon.
[DRACCOON grunts]
[MELIE]
There ya go.
I just realized it's been
a whole week already.
You mean since we left Seth?
[OCOHO]
Yes. What's the deal?
Do you think he's actually been
training this whole time?
If he's healed up, then yeah.
He's a wild one,
but once Seth's committed
to doing something,
he always gives it his all.
Hm. I'll take your word for it.
Although I can only
guarantee that he's trying,
not that's it's gone well.
[OCOHO chuckles]
Yeah, that's fair.
Ya wanna know what I think?
I think Seth gettin' hyped
up about somethin'
can only mean more trouble!
Listen, Melie, your little
internship's over, right?
Then why don't we just
head back to Artemis?
I'm gonna stick around at
least until the festival's over.
[DOC gasps]
But hey, feel free
to go by yourself.
Are you kiddin' me?!
I can't go all that way on
my own, it's too dangerous.
I'm only a kid!
Wait, if you don't wanna be
here, then why'd you come?
[MELIE]
Good question.
It's not like I asked you to
come with, you volunteered.
I came because I was worried
about you and Seth, okay?
You act like you've forgotten,
but the two of you weren't
on the best terms!
All this worrying just
isn't good for you, Doc.
Oh! Sure!
And spendin' more time in
a place this dangerous
should totally help my nerves.
You say that, but it's
gotten a lot safer.
Nobody's seen a Spectre
since we left the forest.
[DOC] Yeah. But the culprits
are still out there.
I'll believe we're safe
when whoever's behind
this gets arrested.
Can't we tell someone
what Seth saw?
There's no one that
I'm sure we can trust.
We have no idea how
high up this might go.
Do you really think that
some are knight-sorcerers?
Could they be plannin'
a coup? [gasps]
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
I'm sorry! My hand just slipped.
[DOC]
I've had it with this place!
I'm leavin' first
thing tomorrow! Ah!
Cut that out, ya stupid monster!
Relax, Doc. You'll be okay.
Just think of it as a magic
shower that smells like wet fur.
That's Lord Brangoire. Again.
Just how many times
is that now? Ah!
[MELIE]
That's for treating me and Doc
like we're your damn servants.
Huh?!
It's your overstuffed teddy
bear that needs cleaning,
so why should we have
to help dust it off?
If ya want a real
dust up, bring it!
Guess it was about time.
Here I was starting to hope
that the other you
might take a day off for once.
[OCOHO]
Uh?
It's angry Melie!
You're so fun to fight
when you get like this!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[OCOHO] Bring it on,
ya savage little cutie!
Are ya ready?
[OCOHO, MELIE yell]
[OCOHO, MELIE grunting]
[MELIE]
You're not terrible.
[OCOHO]
Thanks. Neither are you.
[MELIE] Maybe I'll beat
you up some more tomorrow.
Cool! Lookin' forward to it.
You had better rest up though!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
What the heck is
with you weirdos?
[MELIE]
Come on. We're leaving.
[DOC]
Melie, what're you doin'?
I'll catch you two later.
[MORDRED]
Hey there.
[OCOHO]
Huh?
Have a sec? I wanted to talk.
Yeah, what's up?
Hey! Put me down this instant!
[MELIE] No can do. I need
you to be my lookout.
Uh-- What are you talkin' about?
The heck you need a lookout for?
Try using your eyes and
then give me a guess.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[gasps] Whaddaya think
he's sittin' there for?
[MELIE]
Keep struggling like you were.
If he finds out that we're onto
him, there could be trouble.
[gasps]
[DOC]
That hurts! Put me down!
You're pinchin' me! Lemme go!
Uh. He's pretty
focused on the door.
He really is after Ocoho.
[DOC]
How did you know?
Used my eyes.
He's been following us all day.
Do ya think he's with
the people Seth fought?
[MELIE]
Probably.
Listen.
What if just this one time, we
tried minding our own business?
--[MELIE] Sh!
--[gasps]
[DOC]
Huh?
Can't see her face,
but that's Ocoho, right?
My stubby little legs can't
keep up with you guys.
Why don't'cha just
leave me behind?!
Because if this group of
conspirators has any sense,
they'll come after us, too.
We had better stick
together, Melie.
I've got your back!
Stop your wailing.
You'll tip him off.
What providence that we should
happen upon each other
here and now.
And what better match for
a golden paragon of virility
than a fiery femme fatale!
We were destined
to meet tonight!
Or perhaps you chose
to make your own destiny
and came out here to find me.
Huh?
[TOWNSWOMAN A]
Oh, look! It's Lord de Gulis!
[LORD DE GULIS]
Hello there. Good evening.
It's great to meet you all.
Anyway!
I understand that you only
arrived in the capital recently.
It must be quite
confusing. Fear not.
This shining knight's about to
show you every nook and cranny.
[MELIE growls]
I've got somewhere
to be, so move it.
[LORD DE GULIS]
My cheek.
My poor cheek--
Oh! How it hurts!
And yet my beloved has placed
her hand upon my face.
Such bliss! May it bruise
into a mark of love!
[TOWNSWOMAN A]
That's our charming knight!
Even when he's getting
rejected, he's fun.
Damn. There are too many people.
You and Mr. Boobrie
need to go on ahead.
You're small enough that he
can fly you over this crowd.
What? No way! Come up
with another plan.
Hey, Boobrie.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
This is a one-time offer, okay?
If you can track down
Ocoho and Brangoire,
I'll give you the
beating of a lifetime.
[DOC yelling]
Pull up! If you
keep slippin' down,
I'm gonna get a face
full of gravel, Boobrie!
Why'd you have to
bring me with you?!
[BRANGOIRE]
By Merlin!
I will ensure that you come
to regret what you've done!
[DOC yelling]
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[DOC]
You stupid demon bird.
[BRANGOIRE]
Who are you?
Uh? [gasps]
Do you plan to stand in my way?
Oh! Nope! You do what you want!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Hey! Stop that!
Get away from me,
you little nuisance! [grunts]
Have at you, traitor!
What is this, some kind
of entrapment spell?
Worked it out, did you?
Now tell me, what
does your group want?
Why are you creating Spectres?
You used your spell
on the wrong person.
What are you saying?
Open your eyes!
Don't let her fool you!
She's the one who's been
causing the Spectres to appear!
She's betrayed us!
[ALL gasp]
Wait, Seth?
Wait a second. Where did
you even come from?
Ya know, Seth, this may
well be the first time
I've been sincerely
happy to see ya!
This isn't really the best
time to chat, you guys.
Now get up!
[SETH] What the heck's
going on with her?
Doesn't look like
she's gonna hold back.
[DOC yelps]
It's me, Ocoho.
I'm your friend, remember?
Crap, she's seriously
tryin' to kill us!
Hey! Lemme in there, big guy!
Make some room!
Let me out of here
so I can fight!
[MELIE chuckles, gasps]
[BRANGOIRE yells]
[SETH]
That's enough!
Talk to us, Ocoho.
Why are you acting
all crazy right now?
[SETH] Those eyes.
I've seen them before.
[BRANGOIRE]
It's no use.
If she won't surrender,
then I will---
Just hold on!
We still don't know
the entire story yet.
I know more than enough!
That traitor has planted a stone
that will make a Spectral
Nemesis appear!
[gasps]
[BRANGOIRE, SETH gasp]
[DOC gasps]
[BRANGOIRE]
I finally caught her red-handed,
but you got in the way! [growls]
In the name of great Merlin,
I won't let her escape!
[DOC] So Ocoho was
gonna make a Spectre?
[DOC gasps]
Has Ocoho really
been playing us all
for fools this
entire time? No way.
Look, Melie.
We need to catch her
before Lord Brangoire!
Huh?
[SETH] She isn't her
normal self right now!
[MELIE]
What does that mean?
Do you think she's
being controlled?
I've got no idea.
[MELIE]
Great.
It doesn't matter.
You just keep track
of Lord Brangoire.
I'll take care of the rest!
You don't honestly
think that you can
get ahead of us on foot, do you?
Stop acting stupid
and get on the broom.
I know a shortcut!
[MELIE]
Seth! Wait!
Hey. Did you guys
forget about me?
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[FARMER D]
All right, let's call it day.
What's the matter, boss?
Do ya see something?
[FARMER D]
Look there.
Flying just above the
road to the castle.
It looks like...
That's the Dullahan,
there's no doubting it!
Its head isn't attached
to its shoulders, you see?
What could the Headless Fairy
be doing on my land?
--We better run for it!
--Oh, no.
Wherever the
Dullahan is sighted,
a Spectral Nemesis
appears not long after!
Oh, no!
Merlin's angry with us for
taking gold from a foreigner--
He's sent his harbinger of
vengeance to punish us!
I knew I should've turned
that merchant baron away!
[SETH]
This is Caillte Forest, so...
Aha!
There. I gotcha!
Ocoho, why are you acting
so weird right now?
You've never been this quiet,
and you've never been
so friggin' murdery!
Damn it. Stop fighting me!
Just calm down, will ya?
Oh. Uh. That was
easier than expected.
[BRANGOIRE] Well done, boy!
Don't let her go!
You've been caught
in the act, traitor.
I finally have the proof
I need to expose you
for what you are.
Uh-- Lord Brangoire?
Hey. And you're
here, too, Melie?
[OTHERS]
Hm?
Wait, Seth?
Hold on. Why do you have
your arm around my neck?
Where the heck are we?
[OTHERS gasp]
Come on, guys.
You're really scaring me now.
What's going on here?
Talk to me, I'm freaking out!
Do you seriously
think I'm a traitor?
Well, that isn't true.
I would never turn against
my country, I promise!
[BRANGOIRE] You lie.
I just watched you try to
plant a stone that
would've seeded a Spectre.
[OCOHO]
I don't know what you saw,
but I would never do that!
What do you make of all this?
I got nothin'.
Although I feel like
Ocoho's telling the truth.
[BRANGOIRE] Don't be fooled.
I've been watching her for days.
I know that she's guilty!
[gasps] Sounds like you've
suspected her for some time.
I was more or less certain
that she was at
least up to something.
The girl has always been
willful and disobedient.
And when the queen spoke to us
about the Spectral Nemeses,
I saw her react strangely.
Now, put out your arms.
Huh? I'm telling
the truth, I swear!
You wanna be sure you
get this right, don't ya?
Well, then let her
explain herself.
Why do you defend someone
who attacked you
both without remorse?
[SETH] 'Cause things aren't
always what they seem.
I was suspicious of you before.
What? Why would you be?
[SETH] When I got back
from the forest today,
I saw you following Ocoho.
You were acting super creepy,
so I kept an eye on you.
I thought you might be
with the conspirators.
[MELIE] Hold on. If you were
back in town that early,
then you should've let us know!
[SETH]
Oh, yeah, I know. Sorry.
[OCOHO]
If you saw me burying
some kind of
Spectre-summoning stone,
then that must be what I did.
Yeah? Okay.
I'm gonna show you something.
It should explain how
this happened, 'kay?
[BOTH gasp]
You see this mark?
Whenever someone presses on it,
I'm forced to do
whatever they tell me to.
And afterwards, I lose
all memory of what happened.
That sounds like a pretty
terrible infection to have.
[OCOHO]
It is.
I'm a little bit confused.
[MELIE] She's saying someone
used her to do all this.
Damn it.
[OCOHO gasps]
Use this blade to
take your own life.
--[MELIE gasps]
--No, don't!
Now stop.
What happened? Am I--?
[BRANGOIRE]
It seems she told the truth.
Hey, Ocoho. Is there anyone
else that you've told?
Because if you have, then...
[OCOHO]
There isn't.
[BRANGOIRE] You see,
that's the law in this nation.
Everyone must keep their
curse secret if they can.
So if we figure out who
knows about her mark,
that'll tell us who's really
behind these Spectre attacks.
I told ya, Lord Brangoire,
it wasn't actually
Ocoho after all!
[BRANGOIRE] Ocoho.
Return to the castle for now.
Stick to your usual routine
until I can figure out
who's at fault here.
Wait, does this mean
you're letting me go?
I don't have much of a choice.
The culprits can't know
that I'm onto them.
[MELIE] Kinda seems like
you wanna use her as bait.
I'll do what it takes
to stop the traitors.
For the record, Ocoho.
I intend to keep the
secret of your infection.
[MELIE, SETH sigh]
[BRANGOIRE]
That said.
Someone who can be so
easily turned into a puppet
by the enemies of the crown
has no place in the order.
Know that I'll oppose
your ordination.
[SETH gasps]
I'm sorry, Ocoho.
Let us know if there's
anything we can do to help you.
Yeah, like givin' that guy
a swift kick in the ass.
[SETH]
So, what should we do?
[OCOHO]
I need to talk to Mordred.
[SETH, MELIE gasp]
He's always helped me
and defended me
when I screwed up.
There's something I need
to find out from him.
Uh. I don't get where
this is coming from.
But I think I might.
A little while back,
I saw you with him
in the stables.
To be honest, I thought he was
kissing you at the time. Heh.
But then your eyes went hollow.
They looked just like
they did earlier tonight.
How could you leave a
helpless kid like me alone
in a dangerous place like that?
You weren't alone,
you had Boobrie with you!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
I know that I've caused
a lot of trouble for you guys
and I'm sorry.
Nah, don't worry about it.
Me and Seth make
lots of trouble.
It's true. Chaos does
follow them everywhere.
So about this stone...
There's a whole lot of
Fantasia packed into it.
[DOC]
I guess there would have to be
for it to create one of those
enormous projections.
[SETH]
It's really weird though.
The imprint on this Fantasia is
pretty much the same as mine.
[DOC, MELIE]
Huh?
Diabal.
[MELIE]
Don't think I know that name.
He's the guy I fought
beneath the castle.
He's just like me.
I need to find him again.
[BOTH]
Hm?
But there's no way to get
past the castle guards.
Actually, there is a way.
Seth could wait until the day
of the Ordination Ceremony
and sneak in then.
[OTHERS]
Huh?
With all the public
events going on,
the guards'll be
spread pretty thin.
That works out for me.
Yeah, it ought to.
I used to sneak into the castle
that way when I was a kid.
Me and my best friends, too.
I'll track down Mordred
and make him talk.
[SETH] Hey, Ocoho,
I've got faith in you.
If Mold-raid tries to touch
your neck, you'll beat him down.
He only got you before because
you weren't expecting it.
That curse doesn't define you.
You're a top knight-candidate.
Don't let anyone
tell you different.
If you need any help,
then just say the word
and we'll come!
'Kay. Thank you.
[NARRATOR]
Dragunov and Liselotte
successfully infiltrated
Caislean Merlin.
But now, having
secretly received
new orders from General Torque,
they are on their way
to a remote location.
[LISELOTTE]
We finally got into the city
only to be ordered out of it.
Strange.
And I know they're
trying to be discreet,
but this seems like overkill.
[DRAGUNOV] These people
are either overly cautious
or up to something
truly nefarious.
Regardless, General Torque
ordered us to meet with them.
You sound reluctant, Dragunov.
I'd almost use the
same word to describe
how you looked when
the General said
that you were being promoted.
You seemed none too enthused.
I can assure you
that I was pleased.
I just don't express joy
as outwardly as most.
You say that,
but the smile you gave when
the general ordered us
to look for that horned sorcerer
tells me a different tale.
This is where you tell me
whatever you're hiding
and then assure me that
when the time comes,
I can trust that you will follow
the orders you've been given.
[DRAGUNOV sighs]
[DRAGUNOV]
All right, fine. I'll confess.
But please promise that you'll
keep this between the two of us.
I do have an ulterior motive.
I see this mission as my chance
to get closer to someone.
How's it going so far?
Wait, you...
[DRAGUNOV]
It seems that we've arrived.
Welcome, friends, I hope you
didn't have trouble finding us.
Forgive the rustic
nature of the venue.
I am Baron Doussant,
and you are Captains
Liselotte and Dragunov
of the Thaumaturges, yes?
[NARRATOR] Ocoho interrogates
her close friend Mordred.
Why did he use her as he did?
What is his is true ambition?
Who are the
"Faithful of the Hermit"
scheming in the bowels
of the capital?
Who can she trust?
On the day of the
Ordination Ceremony,
Ocoho gives the
queen some advice
in the hopes of bringing
the truth to light.
Next time on Radiant ,
"Your Decision."