[NARRATOR]
While his wounded body slept,
Seth reconciled with Melie
in a realm called the Sidh.
Once he's healed, Seth wishes to
stay with Myr in Caillte Forest
to train and learn how
to control his rampages.
[DOC sighs]
[DOC] Do ya really think
following a mushroom
is a good idea?
[OCOHO]
Don't worry!
Myr promised that
this little guy
would lead us out of the forest.
We'll be fine.
[DOC]
If you say so.
I just don't understand why Seth
would wanna stay in
this crazy forest anyway.
Seth decided that this is
what's best right now.
So all we can do
is believe in him
and hope his training
with Myr goes okay.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Yeah, I agree.
But listen, judging from
what Seth told us,
the Spectral Nemeses
we've been fighting
are just projections being sent
from beneath the castle.
Plus, Seth told her
the guy behind it
has a whole lotta scars
and couple'a ghost friends.
If that doesn't give
you the creeps,
then I don't know what will.
When we get back, we can
tell the knights about this.
We can't! Absolutely not!
What, so we're just
supposed to keep quiet
and let them get away
with everything?
No, of course not.
But for a conspiracy
this elaborate
to be kept under
wraps for so long,
the people pulling the
strings would need to have
a whole lot of influence
in the castle.
[gasps]
[MELIE] Are you're saying
there's a traitor
within the knight-sorcerers?
[NARRATOR]
"The Palace of Schemes."
[BOUDICA]
Oh, you're here already.
Well, I'm still getting dressed,
but feel free to stay.
I have nothing to hide from you.
Have any idea why we
were brought along?
You're all so lovely.
You may bow before me.
Don't be shy.
[ALL]
Your Highness!
Tell me something,
Lord Brangoire.
[BRANGOIRE]
My queen!
Do you happen to know what it is
that holds all the people
of our nation together?
It's the trust we have
for one another.
[BRANGOIRE]
Of course.
The people trust in the knights,
the knights in their queen,
and I place my trust in you,
all of my precious subjects.
These Specters are beginning to
threaten the trust we've built.
If this sacred bond we
all share is betrayed,
it will give people like
the merchant barons
the chance to steal
our land away from us.
[OCOHO]
Betrayed?
[BRANGOIRE]
Absolutely.
We've mobilized our forces to
prepare for any eventuality.
Very well. However,
the people have doubts.
Some have begun to question
your strength as a leader.
There were complaints
about your conduct
in our most recent battle.
The word "disgraceful"
came up at least once.
Your attack was delayed.
And the Spectres disappeared.
To where, you have no idea.
Well, that was because
of two insubordinates
who refused to obey my orders.
As I've been informed.
So what happened?
Why did you choose
to break formation
and attempt to prevent
an attack on Spectres
you'd been ordered to slay?
[MORDRED] Your Highness,
may I have a word?
[BOUDICA] I will allow
it this time, Mordred.
It's my opinion that Ocoho's
intervention is the reason
we're alive right now.
[MORDRED] The Spectres
started fighting each other
right after Ocoho
stopped our attack.
If we'd been allowed
to continue our charge,
I think most of us would've
been crushed between them.
Is that why you stopped them?
I'm sorry. I don't know
what I was thinking.
Yes, well, at any rate,
it would seem that the person
I actually need to reprimand
is Lord Brangoire,
for his lack of sound judgment.
[gasps]
No, Your Majesty!
[BOUDICA]
What a shame.
In your place, Lord de
Gulis will command
the knight candidates
until further notice.
You will assist him until
the ordination ceremony.
I'm sorry, sir.
I had to be honest.
[LORD DE GULIS clears throat]
[LORD DE GULIS] It just so
happened that I was passing by,
and I could've sworn
that I heard my name.
Could it be that you--?
[LORD DE GULIS yells]
[LORD DE GULIS]
Figured I would land on my nose.
[LORD DE GULIS laughs]
[LORD DE GULIS] I planned
this entrance all along!
Hail, Queen Boudica.
I dedicate that most graceful
somersault to your grace.
Wait a second.
This is Lord de Gulis, first
knight to defeat a Spectre?
Listen, Gulis,
I need you to take command
of the knight candidates for me.
Of course! Just leave everything
to me, my beautiful queen!
You know that I, Gulis,
would leap into a fiery inferno
or even thorny roses
for Your Majesty.
[LORD DE GULIS chuckles]
My, and speaking of
a prick that burns.
Your beauty has
pierced my heart.
Take this rose, I beg you.
[MELIE]
No thank you!
Come now! I must insist!
[MELIE] Your mouth is
bleeding, are you okay?
I did that on purpose!
I'll have you know
I planned this all along!
[growls]
[MELIE] I already told you
that I don't want it!
Oh, my! A fierce beauty!
That'll be all. Everyone
is dismissed and may go.
Besides, I'm busy
and have work to do.
[OCOHO yelps]
[LORD DE GULIS]
There's no need to be coy.
[MELIE] ...hole to die in,
you creepy old goat.
Not only did you
disobey orders,
you also entered Caillte Forest.
I didn't think you were the type
to go and break the rules.
This kind of behavior is
unbecoming of a future knight.
However, it is super becoming
of a badass rebel.
You go, girl.
I'm seriously proud
of you, ya know that?
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You should know that I fully
support all your efforts.
You remind me of myself
before I became queen.
[OCOHO]
Oh, yeah?
Wow. That's such an honor!
Just be very careful
from now on.
There are many actions that
men are always praised for,
but when a woman
behaves the same way,
she'll be labeled
as impertinent.
[BOUDICA] They may hold
me in the highest regard,
but the knights are
still a society of men.
And many of them do not
look upon you favorably.
Listen very carefully.
You would do well to try and
lay low until your ordination.
Got it?
[giggles]
O-Oh. Okay!
But enough of that!
What was the forest like?
Was it gorgeous?
You just have to tell me!
[OCOHO] Uh. Well, it was...
it was pretty weird.
[BOUDICA]
How was it "weird"?
Oh. Um.
For one thing, there were
walking mushrooms.
[BOUDICA]
Really? What else was there?
--[OCOHO] What else?
--[BOUDICA] Uh-huh.
[OCOHO] We did see a lot of
different colored birds
that I'd never seen before.
[BOUDICA]
Oh!
[SETH]
Where am I?
I feel like this would
be a good time
for you to pop him out of there.
He might drown if you leave him.
You think so? Humans really
are fragile creatures.
What is this?! Are you
tryin' to kill me?!
My, what an awful thank you!
For your information,
you would've died ages ago
if I hadn't placed you in there.
Jill kept you immersed
in that sap
so that your body could
completely heal itself.
I didn't know that's
what it was for.
Here ya go. Put some
clothes on, would ya?
My body feels like
it just woke up
from the longest nap
I've ever had.
Of course it does.
In your human time,
I'd say it's been...
...about two years, probably.
What?! Two years?!
[JILL] I think it's been
closer to three, honey.
My mistake.
I always lose track of the time
when I'm with my
sweet morning glory.
Oh, Myr! You sweet talker!
Would you cut that out already?!
Good grief! This can't be right!
What happened to everyone else?
[MYR] Who knows? I haven't
seen 'em for a while now.
Oh, man, oh, man, oh, man!
I'm gonna be dead meat!
If I've actually gone three
years without calling Alma,
she's gonna murder me!
This can't be happening.
Stop panicking and listen
to me. You'll be fine.
Time moves differently here--
it's not as boring as it
is in the world of man.
Time moves differently in here?
But what does that mean?
Think of it this way.
If you imagine that human time
is moving along a straight line,
time within Caillte Forest is
like a circle stuck to the line.
This place has its own
unique flow of time
that's unrelated to
the outside world.
No matter how many
years you spend here,
if you want it to happen,
you can choose to leave
the forest at a point in time
just after you entered.
So when you said it's
been two or three years
since I got here...
[MYR]
We told you the length of time
that had passed within the
forest, not outside it.
Get it? You can leave at
any point in time you please.
I don't really
understand it, but I guess!
This means I can train
as much as I want, that right?
You wish to stay here and train?
Why exactly do you think it
important that you do so?
Well, uh,
I've gotta learn how to control
this dangerous power of mine.
It's important 'cause I can't
hurt my friends ever again.
[MYR]
Mh-hm.
Okay.
Well, it really isn't
any of my business,
but feel free to
train on your own.
Hey! Would you please
hold on for a second?
You have to be the
one to train me!
You use Fantasia with your
bare hands like I do,
so it makes perfect sense!
[MYR]
Hm?
[SETH] Please, Myr!
Help me become stronger!
Teach me how to control
Fantasia like you do!
Well, you may be ignorant,
but at least you're determined.
If you really want me to train
you that badly, then, uh,
yeah, sure.
Prove your worth by
trying to catch me.
Hah! I don't think you
have it in you though!
Heh! Really?
[MYR] It's not only time
that's different here.
Space can also expand
and contract.
Be sure to look closely,
listen carefully,
and feel the very
world around you.
If you can't manage that, you'll
never be able to catch me.
Most of that sounds
like gibberish to me,
but if you wanna play
tag, I'm down.
You gotta be kidding!
[yells]
[SETH]
Ow.
[MYR] You really aren't
paying attention.
You think that everything in
this forest is your enemy.
Oh, yeah?
The land you walk on every day
and the wind that blows
through your hair.
It's important that you
open up your senses
to the things around you
and become one with the world,
instead of acting
like its enemy.
I just don't understand
what you mean by that.
[SETH yells]
[MYR chuckles]
That was pretty good for
your first time. Not bad.
But the moment you fully opened
your senses to the world,
you closed them off again.
Huh?
I was wondering, Myr.
[MYR]
Mh-hm?
What made you decide to
help him with his training?
You remember that boy Yaga?
He asked me to do it.
And he's a member of the
Thirteen Sorcerer Coven.
So that's the only reason
you're doing all of this?
I think you might just be
planning something else.
[gasps] You can't run away!
[MYR]
Hey, Seth! Put your pants on!
We're gonna go one more lap!
[SETH]
Ah, come on! Already?
[MYR]
Now don't drag your feet.
[sighs]
It feels like he's picked
up the pace today!
I managed to dodge it!
But what was that feeling?
[SETH]
It happened again.
I was able to feel them
coming somehow.
[SETH]
Water.
Wind.
What could that be?
Is it Myr?
I can sense it.
Huh?
[chuckles]
I finally caught you.
Thanks a bunch for the help!
Good work.
It would seem that you've
learned how to sense
and work with the
world around you.
And now that I've caught
you, you'll teach me
how I can control Fantasia
like you do, right?
I don't remember
agreeing to do that.
[SETH]
Huh?
It feels as though you humans
never learn anything at all.
You don't actually understand
a bit of what you
just did, now do you?
What are you talking about?
Listen carefully.
You must think of Fantasia
like it's the air we breathe.
If all you ever do is gather
a whole bunch of it
and then force it back out
all at once... it's a fart.
[SETH yells]
A fart?
So communicating with nature
and sensing your
surroundings is essential.
You were only able
to catch me earlier
because you opened your
senses up to the Fantasia
that fills this space and then
became one with all of it.
You mean I was sensing Fantasia.
Thanks to the sap that Jill used
to heal those wounds of yours,
there is now a tiny
part of this forest
residing within your body.
Because of that, you now have
the ability to sense this place
and its Fantasia as if it was
an extension of your very being.
[SETH]
That must be why.
When you're in harmony
with the world,
you can use Fantasia
to do things like this.
Uh! Wait a sec!
What're you doing, Myr?
[SETH screaming]
You can use it not just to
destroy, but also to create.
It's about more than just
making a bunch of noise
and spitting fire.
Used wisely, magic has
boundless potential.
[SETH]
Amazing.
[MYR]
But for a case like yours,
merely harmonizing with
Fantasia won't be enough.
You'll have to defeat that
which dwells within you first.
You mean the thing inside me
that makes me lose control?
Well, it's more like that
thing is a freeloader
living inside you and taking
over when things get tricky.
Then what can I do about it?
[MYR] Gather as much
Fantasia as you can.
Push yourself to your limits.
Once you do that, he'll have
to make an appearance.
He's coming now.
Be sure you're prepared to throw
everything you have at him!
[yells]
[screams]
Stay strong and don't let go.
Keep holding onto
the link you share
with the rest of the world.
I'm trying my hardest,
but it's just too strong.
[screams]
[yells]
[MYR]
Hmph.
Ah, man, my head.
You lost control
and attacked me,
so I reflexively kicked
you into the sky
and punched you into a tree.
[SETH]
I get it. The plan didn't work.
[MYR]
Tell me, what did you feel
when the freeloader
took control?
Could you see your surroundings?
[SETH]
Yeah.
I could, but I definitely
felt cut off
from the Fantasia of
the forest around me.
And also, I don't feel
anything from it.
The freeloader's pretty
much just a void.
Aren't you able to feel it
fighting you as you struggle
to keep control of your body?
[SETH]
No.
I don't know how to explain
the feeling, but I'll try.
The freeloader is like
a hole in the wall
that's built up around me.
And from time to time,
it feels like someone
is watching me
through that hole.
Let's try this one
more time, okay, Seth?
If we succeed,
you could find out
who's on the other
side of that hole.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, the mysterious man
known as Diabal and his comrades
were still searching for Seth.
What they feared most was
that the puppet master
pulling the strings
would find them.
The man named Piodon.
[SHADOW A]
It's no use.
We can't find the location
of the boy with horns.
[SHADOW B] We had the other
members help us search,
but they had no more
luck than we did.
With all the knight-sorcerers
you call your comrades,
you'd think that you could
organize a proper manhunt.
[SHADOW A]
Diabal,
you could've easily used
your power to stop the boy
when he first snuck in.
[SHADOW B] Exactly.
It's your fault he escaped.
No, Piodon might've
found me if I'd used it.
[SHADOW A] Piodon. He's the
one you're hiding from?
The one who wounded you?
That's right.
As long as I can stay hidden
within this castle's barrier,
he can never track me down.
[SHADOW B]
So that's why you want
to protect the castle so much.
Seeing as our job is to guard
this land from foreign enemies,
we're glad you
share our interests.
[SHADOW A]
Back to the boy with horns.
Do you think his appearance
here was Piodon's doing?
I'm not sure. But it
doesn't actually matter.
I'm completely certain Piodon's
using the boy to gain something.
That's just the way he works.
And if the boy should fail
to meet his expectations,
he'll be broken.
Just like I was.
You're doing well, Seth.
Before the show gets started,
I'll enter the Sidh
so I can obsesrve
what's happening to you
there in that plane.
[MYR]
Now.
It's time to take control
of this freeloader.
[SETH yells]
[MYR]
I can see it clearly.
It's stretching its feelers
out in every direction,
all to try and control the orb
that's surrounding you.
If it manages to do that,
you'll lose all
control over yourself.
But I still can't tell exactly
what this thing is.
[SETH]
Myr! What's happening?
Is something wrong?
I can see what you mean now.
Seems like you were
right about this, Seth.
This thing of yours is nothing
more than a peephole.
If the strength of
your will weakens
and you lose the
orb's protection,
I think it intends to make
you some kind of offering.
[SETH]
What do you mean?
Who would I even be
an offering for?
I'm not sure yet.
It's something that's
looking for you.
And your freeloader
is trying its best
to help that something
find you here.
Agh. This is getting to be
more than I can handle.
That's enough for now.
[MYR]
So I was right.
When it can't see through the
peephole, it decides to leave.
I need to know, Seth.
If this is from your "brother,"
why would he put something
like this inside of you?
Do you really think his
objective was to save your life?
[NARRATOR]
Lord de Gulis leads
the knight-sorcerer
candidates to battle.
He defeats a Nemesis
with a single blow,
and upon learning that
another is nearby,
challenges Lord Brangoire
to slay it before he can.
Ocoho and Melie lag behind,
which means they're alone
when they see the fallen Nemesis
split into numerous small ones.
Next time on Radiant ,
"The Qualifications
of a Knight."