[NARRATOR] Thanks to a
mischievous eccentric named Myr,
Seth met Ocoho, a
knight-sorcerer candidate.
But as they battled
a Spectral Nemesis,
Seth tried to protect Ocoho
from a powerful blow
and was knocked off
her dragon's back.
Oh, no!
Seth!
Someone just severed contact!
First reserve unit,
take their place at once!
[KNIGHT-SORCERER A]
Out of the way, Ocoho!
Wait, listen! My pilot
got knocked off our mount!
[KNIGHT-SORCERER A] You broke
out of the Gysoni spell,
so right now, you're
getting in the way!
Well, then...
[NARRATOR]
"The Bringer of Calamity."
[FARMER A]
Uh! Just look at that thing.
[FARMER'S WIFE A] Let's go.
We need to get further back!
[FARMER A] But we can't
just leave the fields
to be destroyed.
[FARMER'S SON A]
Hey, Dad, look over there!
[SETH screaming]
[ALL gasp]
[sighs] Wow.
That was a close one.
My left arm has lost the
ability to gather Fantasia.
Must be 'cause that's
where Torque hit me.
But on the plus side, my right
hand seems to be working fine.
[FARMER'S SON A] Cool!
That knight-sorcerer has horns!
There's no way they'd let
a sorcerer with horns
become a knight.
[SETH] Hey! Why haven't
you people run away yet?
Didn't you notice
a giant Nemesis?
[FARMER A]
Yeah, it's pretty hard to miss!
We were workin' the fields
when that thing popped
up outta nowhere.
Hang on.
Did any of you see something
fall from the sky
before all this happened?
We didn't see nothin' like that.
One second everythin'
was normal,
and the next, that big sucker
was towerin' over our heads!
This just gets weirder.
Well, anyway, it's dangerous
here, so you need to run!
[OCOHO]
Seth!
[SETH]
Hey, Ocoho!
You're still alive!
That's so good to see!
'Course I am! Gah!
[OCOHO laughs]
Let go of me, Ocoho!
I give, I give, I give,
I give, I give! Gah!
Why did you try to block that
Nemesis with your bare hands?
It would've been fine,
except I couldn't get
my magic to work right!
Well, then you should've
just had Draccoon dodge it!
That's what I gave
you the reins for!
I told you, I don't know how
to ride a friggin' dragon!
[ALL gasp]
What was that? Maybe an
attack from the Nemesis?
Don't think so. Look up high.
All of their assaults are going
straight through its body.
It has to be weakened
before Mordred and Sagramore
can finish it off.
No. All that grain
was ready for harvest.
It was ready.
I told you this would happen!
You brought this upon us
when you decided to
deal with that foreigner!
Look, what's done is done.
There were omens. You saw
the Dullahan, right, Dad?
This is 'cause of the curse.
The curse!
"Dullahan"?
Hey, Seth, we need to
get out of here fast.
More attacks'll be hitting soon.
[SETH gasps]
Huh?
Seth, wait!
I can't move with this on!
Repulse!
[gasps]
[SETH]
Thanks, Ocoho!
That shield is crazy awesome!
Hey, what're you doing?
Shouldn't you have at least
created a Dome of Protection?
[SETH]
Uhh... dunno what that is.
But are you saying that
there's a way to protect
the farmer's land
from all those attacks?
Maybe, but I haven't
been ordered to.
Ordered to? And why
should that matter?
Were your fellow knights
ordered to destroy this farm?
Of course they weren't,
you know that.
But we have to bring
down the Nemesis--
it's our sworn duty!
And you think that means you can
blast whatever's in your way?
I thought you were doing
this to protect the people.
If you guys destroy this farm,
you're as bad as the Nemesis.
It isn't always enough just
to save people's lives.
If they lose their
farm right now,
those people will
probably starve.
I'mma stop that.
You gonna help me, or what?
Okay, you've convinced me.
[OCOHO] But protecting an area
this large, that's tough.
I'll need some backup.
How do you mean?
[OCOHO] I can create a
Protective Dome myself.
The thing is, its size will
depend on how much Fantasia
I can put into it, and we
can gather more together.
'Kay, got it.
Here we go.
Cromen!
[KNIGHT-SORCERER A]
What's going on?
[KNIGHT-SORCERER C] All our
Fantasia's getting sucked
towards the ground!
[OCOHO] It feels as if
there's a sea of Fantasia
flowing through him.
It's like he's drawing it in
through every pore of his skin.
Who the heck is this guy?
[MORDRED] Lord Brangoire!
Our Gysoni link is going to--!
[gasps]
[MORDRED]
Seems that dome is consuming
all the Fantasia nearby.
[SAGRAMORE]
Mordred, look!
The Nemesis is disappearing!
Let's attack it while we can.
All right.
[MORDRED, SAGRAMORE yell]
[OCOHO sighs]
[SETH chuckles]
Think your chrome dome worked.
[OCOHO]
Huh?
But I've never seen a
Nemesis like that before.
[FARMER C]
The place is a mess.
Things could've been worse,
but this still isn't good.
A big chunk of our harvest
is unsellable now.
[BRANGOIRE]
Thanks to your diligent efforts,
we have successfully vanquished
yet another Spectral Nemesis.
[SETH]
Whoa!
[BRANGOIRE]
Excellent work.
I have no doubt that you'll
become fine knight-sorcerers.
Well, two of you will.
Care to guess which?
Mordred and Sagramore!
The only candidates here
who followed my orders.
All the rest of you are
just useless maggots!
I never called off the attack,
so why did you break formation?
Do you think that's how
real knight-sorcerers fight?
[KNIGHT-SORCERER B] Um, with
all due respect, Lord Brangoire,
we stopped fighting because
there wasn't enough Fantasia
to keep the confinement
spell going.
What do you mean?
[KNIGHT-SORCERER B] Well, Ocoho
cast that spell from below,
and then all the
Fantasia was gone.
[KNIGHT-SORCERER D] Yeah,
that's how it happened, sir.
Damn you! Why'd you cast
a spell from the ground?
I didn't even give you
permission to be on the ground!
Explain yourself, Ocoho!
Um, sorry, sir, but I'm Ocoho.
[BRANGOIRE grunts]
[clears throat]
Doesn't matter!
Let's set the record straight!
How many times do
I have to tell you
that on your own,
you're nothing?!
Your personal ambitions
are just rust on the chain
your comrades have formed!
But, sir, I--
[BRANGOIRE]
No more excuses!
I don't care about your
talents, your abilities,
or your family line.
If you wanna be
in the spotlight,
go become a bard, or a juggler!
Or join up with those
buffoons at Artemis!
But don't waste the
time of the Order!
Have you lost sight of
the great Merlin's teachings?
Gysoni allows us all to
fight together in harmony!
Don't forget that!
[BOUDICA] Lord Brangoire,
you haven't changed a bit.
Don't interrupt!
Oh. My apologies, Your Majesty!
[giggles]
Our wise sovereign, Her Majesty
Queen Boudica, is here!
[BRANGOIRE]
Knights! Bow to your queen!
You don't have to kneel.
But since you're
going to anyway,
I think you'd better get
down on both your knees.
[BRANGOIRE]
Oh. O-Of course.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
She's a giant. Could
that be her infection?
[BRANGOIRE]
My queen, I wasn't expecting you
to honor us with
your presence here.
If I'd known you were coming,
I would've waited
before reprimanding--
That's quite all right.
I came here on a whim,
so you couldn't have known.
Although I wish you had taken
more care with your positioning.
From where you're kneeling now,
you can see up my skirt.
[gasps]
[BRANGOIRE]
I'm so sorry! Please forgive me!
It's fine.
I came out here because I wanted
to see a Spectral Nemesis.
They have caused my people
to suffer, have they not?
[FARMER B]
Yes, my queen.
When my people are in pain,
I feel it as my own.
Please forgive me for my failure
to protect you from this threat.
Aw. No need to blame
yourself, Your Majesty.
I 'preciate your kindness
and your concern.
This was rough for us, 'n our
fields'll need time to recover.
But thanks to those brave
knights of yours,
we've got somethin'
to rebuild from.
I'm so glad to hear that.
However, I think your head
should be a bit lower.
[FARMER B yelping]
Um. Please, my queen.
Your people are afraid of more
than them Spectral Nemeses.
Who gave you permission
to address the queen directly?
I'm giving it now.
Majesty.
Your head, Brangoire.
Do remember.
[BRANGOIRE yelps]
As I was saying, the people's
anguish is my own.
Now tell me, good farmer,
what is it that so
frightens my subjects?
[FARMER B]
Well, um.
Whenever night falls, we see it.
The Dullahan stalks these hills!
The Dullahan?
[FARMER B]
It's a mighty scary spirit
that carries its head
in its arms, you see.
And believe it or not,
it started showing
up in this area
about the same time as
the Spectral Nemeses.
How horrifying.
And is there anything
else you can tell me
about this ghostly entity?
There is.
The Dullahan has also been
called the Bringer of Calamity.
Of calamity. I see.
[FARMER B]
My queen,
between the Spectral Nemeses
and the Dullahan, it's too much!
I don't understand what
honest farmers like us
could've done to deserve
such misfortune.
Noble subjects,
I ask you to listen.
Thanks to King Prasutag, my late
husband, who I still mourn,
the destructive war that
had plagued this fair land
was brought to an end.
We had finally attained peace.
I truly hoped it would last.
But regrettably,
it's proved fleeting.
Unknown forces have brought
conflict to Cyfandir once again.
The Spectral Nemeses
and the Dullahan.
I cannot yet say
what these things
will come to mean
for our country.
However, when the
earthly spirits awaken,
we must pay them heed.
The ghost of Merlin is agitated.
I can feel it in my bones.
We're his successors.
Knowing that, we must
ask ourselves daily
if we deserve to
inherit his gifts.
We must strive to be
worthy of the kingdom
he left us to protect.
We must struggle to comprehend
his brilliant words,
and then to live by them.
To defend Cyfandir every
bit as fiercely as he did.
But not just the land.
We must also protect all
of the lives within it.
The lives that depend on it.
Ocoho, as Lord Brangoire said,
your choice to break from
the group and act as you did
could've had grave consequences.
But your goal was noble,
which makes this deed
worthy of Merlin's legacy.
My queen.
Let's hope these farmers
will make good use
of the land you saved.
I'm sure they'll work
their hardest to do so.
And in time, I believe
they'll be able to make it
even more fertile than before.
Do you agree?
[FARMER B]
Uh, yes! Most definitely!
[giggles]
[BOUDICA] Now, I must return
to my many royal duties.
Forgive me, Lord Brangoire,
I'll intrude no longer.
Let me just say that you and
your soldiers all fought well.
I was thoroughly impressed.
[BRANGOIRE]
Ah!
Thank you very much, my queen!
[BOUDICA] Lord Brangoire... you
mustn't lift your face, right?
[giggles]
[BRANGOIRE] Oh, no!
My apologies! I did it again!
I'm terribly sorry.
It was an accident!
Sure it was.
I wish all of you good health.
And I pray that the great Merlin
will grant you his protection.
Her Majesty the queen
is now departing!
The queen's as beautiful
as she is kind-hearted!
She smells amazing!
I wish it was my
face she'd touched.
I'm never washing
this cheek again.
Hey! Shape up!
Stop ogling the queen,
get back on your steeds,
and fly back to the castle now!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Right, sir!
'Bout time we left. I'm hungry.
[OCOHO]
Seth!
Were you watching all that
happen? Did you see?
That was the queen herself!
And she knew my name!
I was there when she said it!
I'm very happy for you.
Lemme go, ya maniac!
Yay! She said that I was
worthy of Merlin's legacy!
That means I'm gonna be
a knight for sure, right?
[laughs]
Although Lord Brangoire
was pretty angry.
Eh, who caree? He's always
grumbling about somethin'.
And the queen
herself praised me.
She practically ordained
me right there!
Draccoon, we'll celebrate
with a double serving
of fruit tonight!
No! Make it triple!
[DRACCOON wailing]
What kinda noise is that?
You ready to head back now?
I've got a whole buncha things
I'd like to ask you about.
But before that,
let's just celebrate!
Sure.
Huh?
[OCOHO]
Seth.
[SETH] Uh, I just remembered.
I've got a nearby errand to run.
Sorry. You go on without me.
[OCOHO]
Really? Okay, see ya later!
[SETH]
Sounds good.
How's it goin', Grimm?
Ya come for any
reason in particular?
[GRIMM]
Hm. So you spotted Grimm out.
Well, ya weren't exactly
hiding, now were ya?
Ya got the giant hat,
you're covered in bandages,
and you're standing in a field
with your arms stickin'
out like this.
[GRIMM]
And yet you alone saw Grimm.
Yeah, that's true.
It's almost as if you're
invisible to anybody
who isn't out looking for you.
[GRIMM] In a field,
Grimm poses as a scarecrow.
In a graveyard,
Grimm becomes a corpse.
And on the road,
Grimm personifies
a sickly old traveler.
Would you like to know why
Grimm takes on such guises?
Yeah.
[GRIMM]
People are wont to ignore
that which offers nothing
and poses no threat.
Even when they see
such things plainly,
if they can't assess their
value, they move on.
This works well for Grimm.
Grimm is best able
to achieve his goals
by keeping a safe
distance from the world.
Do you believe that to be
your circumstance as well?
[GRIMM]
You don't need to be like Grimm.
Caislean Merlin's keep
is well-protected,
yet you've secured
access already,
and put yourself into an
advantageous position.
Sure, but what
should I do next?
There might be some
information on Radiant
stored in the Castle Archives,
but I can't get into them
unless I join those knights.
[GRIMM]
Hm. The archive, you say?
Yeah, what about it?
[GRIMM]
Grimm would ask a favor of you.
What'cha need? You've helped
me a bunch. I owe you.
If there's anything
I can do, just ask.
[GRIMM] There's an object
inside that castle
of which Grimm has need.
Hm? Wait, so you want me
to go and steal it for you?
I'm grateful and all,
but that's a little too far.
[GRIMM] Just borrow it. Grimm
only needs it for a short time.
It's a stone like this.
[SETH]
What is that?
[GRIMM]
It's called a memory stone.
Some sorcerers are in the habit
of carrying stones like
these at all times.
They allow their
bearers to record
any and all events that
they experience.
[SETH]
Oh... It's pretty.
[GRIMM]
When you go to the archive,
look for a place called
the Anmatheque.
The... Anma-what?
[GRIMM] It's a collection
of memory stones
owned by historically
important sorcerers.
Within it, is a stone
that belonged
to a female sorcerer
named Magosia.
Can you find it
and smuggle it out?
I'm not sure about this, Grimm.
You know your way around here,
wouldn't it be easier for
you to get it yourself?
[GRIMM] Grimm cannot move
beyond the castle gate.
[SETH]
No kidding. Why not?
[GRIMM] Because of reasons
that are Grimm's alone.
So mysterious.
What exactly do you need to use
that memory stone for anyway?
[GRIMM]
Something important.
[SETH]
The heck does that mean?
[GRIMM] It means something
of great import.
Okay, fine! Ugh!
Keep your dumb secrets.
And I'll do my best
to help you out,
but it might take a while.
I don't have any idea how I'm
gonna get into the archive yet.
[GRIMM]
Hm. You may get caught.
Say what?
[GRIMM] Espionage might
not be your strong suit.
Maybe you should
recruit an ally.
Consider the female trapper
you used to travel with.
Or perhaps the boy
with the man's soul.
Melie and Doc are
both great, but...
[GRIMM]
Incidentally,
I'm surprised that you aren't
traveling with them right now.
If Grimm is not mistaken,
they've already arrived in
Caislean Merlin, have they not?
[SETH]
You know everything, don't you?
I did see them in
the city earlier,
but they acted strange
when I said hi.
[GRIMM]
These things are subjective.
Grimm thinks you rather strange.
That's not the kinda
strange I'm talkin' about!
They were just
different, ya know?
It felt like there was this
distance between us.
I guess they must
be angry with me
for heading off to Cyfandir
without telling them first.
[GRIMM]
That could be.
Did you leave without telling
them anything at all?
Kind of. We didn't talk,
but I left behind a letter.
[GRIMM]
Grimm finds it reasonable
that such a drastic act
would lead to a
misunderstanding between you.
[SETH]
What do you think I should do?
[GRIMM]
Grimm cannot advise you in this.
If Grimm knew how to
avoid misunderstandings,
Grimm wouldn't be
the cause of so many.
[SETH] Yeah, you're the
last person I should ask.
[GRIMM] But honestly,
is this the kind of matter
that you should trust
to outside advice?
[SETH]
Prob'ly not.
I need to figure this thing
out all on my own, don't I?
I'll talk to 'em.
[GRIMM]
There's an affordable inn
called the Luchorpan
in the city.
You should check for
your friends there.
Everywhere else is overpriced.
Good to know.
Thanks a bunch, Grimm.
I'll go check it out later.
I've gotta ask.
Where are you getting
all this information
you have on Caislean Merlin?
You knew about the
castle, the forest,
even which inn to try.
[GRIMM]
Have a guess?
[SETH]
I'm wondering if maybe
you served as a
knight-sorcerer once.
[GRIMM]
I did not.
Of course that's all you'll say.
When are you finally gonna
tell me who you are, man?
[GRIMM]
Grimm is Grimm.
Well, once I bring ya this rock,
ya gotta show me what
your face looks like, 'kay?
Do we have a deal?
[SETH]
No! He disappeared again?
For a guy that's always
up in my business,
Grimm sure is secretive.
[sighs]
Okay.
There's a cheap inn
called the Luchorpan.
Bet Doc would like that.
[FARMER D humming]
Man, I don't feel sotally
tober right now.
This was fun.
Hm? What is it?
See that? A light!
Oh, yeah.
We've gotta run.
It's the Dullahan!
[FARMERS screaming]
[NARRATOR] After his
conversation with Grimm,
Seth decides to try and
reconnect with Melie and Doc.
But when he visits the
place they're staying,
Seth is still unable
to comprehend
the reason behind
Melie's coldness.
Melie had trusted
and relied on Seth,
believing he would do the same.
Instead, he left.
Next time on Radiant ,
"Silent Rain, Distant Hearts."