[SAGRAMORE yells]
[gasps]
--[MORDRED] Glaw!
--[SAGRAMORE] Sciath!
[SAGRAMORE yells]
[yells]
Listen, Mordred,
I don't wanna fight you.
Can't we just--?
It's just as I thought.
You might seem cold-hearted
at a glance, but in truth,
you're a nice guy, who cares
deeply for his friends.
--[thud]
--[SAGRAMORE gasps]
[MORDRED]
And it's that naive streak
that made you such an easy mark.
[OCOHO]
No.
No!
[NARRATOR]
"The Black Dragon Descends."
Queen Boudica disabled
the Harmonizium singlehandedly,
but was brought
down in the process,
leaving the knight-sorcerers
leaderless.
Meanwhile, Mordred revealed
his true allegiance
and fought Sagramore.
Mordred lost, but
Sagramore spared him,
only to be slain in cold blood.
Unaware of all this, Seth faces
Dragunov back in the city.
[DRAGUNOV] I'm afraid you
might not get the chance
to see your friend again.
But regardless, I need you
to come with me now.
Why the hell would I?
To make this invasion
even easier?
Why are you people doing this?
[growls]
In the wake of Rumble Town,
the Inquisition's position
as a trusted authority
has been greatly diminished.
The merchant barons' plan will
help us regain that authority.
Those fancy guys who chased me?
You're saying they're
the ones behind all this?
It isn't that simple.
This war was schemed up
by countless people.
You can't save the
day with your fists
the way you did in Rumble Town.
Screw that.
If there are a bunch of
Konrads behind this war,
then I'll just have
to pummel 'em all!
[yells]
You said her name was Melie?
[gasps]
Before you attack me without
considering the consequences,
spare a thought for the
reality of your situation.
What about her?
You know what? Just listen.
If you want to keep her safe,
then help me end
this war quickly.
Where did that
stupid witch run off to?
She had some nerve
mocking my disguise.
[MELIE] This Inquisitor
just won't give up!
Guess I must've made her
even angrier than I thought.
[gasps]
[MELIE yells]
Don't think for one second that
you can get away from me twice.
[gasps]
You can twirl around
as much as you want,
but it won't help you
escape from my blades.
[gasps]
[LORD DE GULIS]
Shimmering Strike!
[CRISTOLOM]
Defiant Deflection!
[LORD DE GULIS]
Ardent Advance!
[CRISTOLOM]
Capricious Counter!
[LORD DE GULIS]
Indignant Lotus!
Well played, sir.
I am truly honored to fight
a master such as yourself.
And for my part, I'm exhilarated
to face a worthy foe.
If you and I had just met...
[LORD DE GULIS]
...in a more peaceful time...
...I think we might
have become--
You mustn't say it!
Such is the nature of war!
The swordsman's path
is a lonely one.
Aptly put. And since we
have no other choice...
[CRISTOLOM] ...we shall let
our blades do the talking!
Have at you!
That I will!
[BOTH]
Gird your loins.
No, this can't be real.
Come on, Sagramore, get up!
Get up!
Look at this mess, Mordred.
This deck was made
from the finest wood,
at least try not to stain it.
I'll avoid spilling
more blood if I can.
Hey. What's with you?
After all these years,
you're gonna pretend
that we were nothing?
That we weren't all friends
since we were kids?
Oh, my. Aren't you spirited?
I doubt this firebrand
would join us.
Afraid not, Father.
That was never an option.
[DOUSSANT]
Then do away with her at once.
We're due to sail back to the
Pontanin States with all haste.
[OCOHO, DRACCOON growls]
[OCOHO]
Mordred.
Time and time again, you got
me out of so much trouble.
If not for you,
I probably would've been
kicked out of the
order long ago.
You always stuck up for me.
Now you're saying you
never really cared?
I said I didn't want to lose
you before, isn't that right?
Well, I wouldn't exactly
call that a lie.
I needed you then.
Or at least, you
were useful to me.
If I had let you get
kicked out of the order,
I would've lost access to
my dear Dullahan, remember?
That kind of infection
is insanely rare.
It's what made you the
cornerstone of my plan.
I don't get it.
Do you feel no remorse?
Not a bit.
[MORDRED sighs]
The thing is, I don't
actually feel anything.
On account of my own infection,
emotions are pretty
much a mystery to me.
[gasps]
Guess you never noticed,
but I only learned to
look like I could feel
by copying the people around me.
Sagramore didn't know it,
but he was a big help.
Sitting next to him
and his poker face,
I was able to pass for
a pretty average kid.
It's funny.
He looks more
expressive in death
than he did when he was alive.
Because his best
friend betrayed him!
Stop crying over spilt blood.
You sound like my dad.
I don't need you anymore.
[DRACCOON growling]
Stupid beast.
[DRACCOON cries]
Draccoon! No. No!
Stay with me!
Please don't leave me alone.
What did I just finish
telling you, Mordred?
No more bloodshed on
the deck of my ship.
[MORDRED]
Sorry, Dad. I forgot.
You cold-hearted creep.
I'm gonna make you
pay for all of this.
[gasps]
[MORDRED]
Jump off the ship for me.
You are sure, right?
I'll go with you,
but only if it ends the war.
Keep your eyes peeled.
We're near the front lines now.
[BOTH gasp]
What is all this? It's so--
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
I can't believe
they'd do all this,
cause all this carnage,
just to get me.
Yet that's precisely
what they've done.
You're why the Inquisition
came, at least.
The merchant barons want
something much worse.
How could this get worse?
[DRAGUNOV] They intend to make
slaves of the infected.
What? You're kidding me, right?
And even though you know that,
you're still working with them?
Can't you see how evil this is?
General Torque is
pursuing a just cause.
And I owe him my loyalty.
General Torque. You mean--?
No friggin' way. You're
loyal to that bastard?!
How righteous can he be?
He's attacking people who're
just tryin' to live their lives!
I can understand
your frustration,
but this world is more complex
than you'd like it to be.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
I concede that the Inquisition
is a deeply flawed institution,
but it exists to protect
the defenseless.
The infected may be oppressed,
but you have magic,
and the means to abuse it.
The Inquisition stops cruel
sorcerers from becoming tyrants.
Are you really speaking
for yourself?
Or are you just repeating what
you've been told to believe?
I want to end this war
before it gets worse.
That's my personal wish,
I can tell you that.
You aren't lying, are you?
You'll find out soon enough.
That's Dragunov's signal!
It seems he managed to catch
the horned sorcerer.
Oh-ho! Cease fire,
the lot of you!
They suddenly stopped firing.
[SOLDIER B] Was it in
response to that signal?
Where did that flare
even come from?
[SOLDIER D]
Hey. You see that kid?
[SOLDIER E] He looks like
that Spectre we saw.
How dare you destroy our land!
You crushed my grandfather's
field, ya damn monster!
Get outta here!
And never come back!
[SOLDIER I] Drop dead,
you ugly horned menace!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
You have a harsh rebuttal
for everything I say,
why not defend yourself
against their comments?
[SETH] There's no point
in arguing with them.
I don't know how you got there,
but you did everything you could
to minimize the damage you
caused as a Spectre, right?
Of course I did,
but it wasn't enough.
I still caused damage.
They have every
right to be angry.
If our roles were reversed,
I would feel the exact same way.
Just who are you?
Captain Dragunov has proven
to be quite resourceful.
Thanks to his and
Liselotte's efforts,
our lost lamb is
heading back home.
Go signal the ships.
[INQUISITION A] The time
has come! Assume formation!
They're forming ranks.
[SOLDIERS chattering]
What are they up to?
And what's with all
of the commotion?
Impossible.
Hey. What the heck is that?
A ship. The mightiest
to come out of Bome.
Our flagship, Uranos .
Why bring it out now?
It looks like playtime's
finally over.
It's regrettable
that we couldn't
drag the game out
a little longer,
but at the very least,
we can ensure that this
war ends with a bang.
I swear on my beard,
I shall make it happen.
[CITIZENS gasping]
They're targeting
the standing stones!
We have to hurry back!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[crying]
It's only a child.
We need to ru--
The magical barrier that's
protected Caislean Merlin
for centuries oughtta fall
within the next few moments.
I swear on the splendid
sheen of my moist beard,
I couldn't be more excited!
What a thrill it is to witness
the demise of a kingdom.
I do hope that you're enjoying
this glorious spectacle
as well, my dear queen.
Thought we had a deal, Eyepatch!
Weren't they supposed
to stop their attack?
Or did you just say that to
get me out of the castle
so your friends could destroy it
without killing their prisoner!
They aren't stopping.
[TORQUE]
We'll attack Cyfandir.
Teach its infected lords
humility and reclaim our place
as this world's enforcers
of justice and order.
But our main goal is to capture
that horned sorcerer.
I cannot stress enough
how essential it is
that we catch him.
You're conflicted. I understand.
And I have faith in your ability
to judge what is right.
[TORQUE] Perhaps you're
uncertain as to whether
the horned sorcerer
deserves to be taken.
When it comes to that boy,
I must ask that you put
your faith in my judgment.
I'm guessing you
also have concerns
about the impending campaign
in Cyfandir, is that correct?
Yes, sir.
Put your fears to rest.
I wish only to rebuild the
Inquisition's authority
so we might uphold order
throughout the world.
I hope to shed as little
blood as possible.
I understand, sir.
I wanted to trust him.
What was all that about
stopping the war?
This smells like betrayal!
That it does,
and I'm the victim.
Ah! Don't you dare make
this all about you!
Tell your soldiers
to stand down!
I can't. I don't have
that kind of authority.
Then I'll find out
who does. Jerk.
Wait. What are you planning?
[SETH] To find out
who's calling the shots
so I can beat him
to a bloody pulp.
Hold on. You shouldn't just
charge forward without thinking!
[SETH]
Right.
You want me to "calculate" how
things might turn out first.
But if I do nothing,
I'll regret it.
So I'll think as I move and
fight for what feels right.
Uh?
It's a lone enemy!
Whoa. I think it's
the horned sorcerer!
Skull Attack!
[INQUISITION screaming]
[INQUISITION E yells]
Keep going till you reach
the center of the battlefield.
You'll find Colonel
Santori there.
You're helping me now?
Old as he may seem,
he's a strong fighter.
Be careful.
While moving,
he's only able to enlarge
any one part of his body,
so don't let him stand still.
But why would you--?
What're you standing
around here for?
Charge on forward.
Make them stop.
Explain yourself,
Captain Dragunov.
What did we just witness?
A soldier realizing that
his cause was unjust.
How dare you speak such words!
What kind of
Thaumaturge would--?
You guys are here, too?
Why track me down?
You've earned our
absolute loyalty.
We'll follow you in
whatever you do, sir.
Whatever your goal,
you aren't in this alone.
Not to brag, but we've
gotten a lot stronger.
Wait till ya see us
in action, Captain!
Yeah, and we even figured out
how to make some
of your recipes.
I see now.
Not all of us were stuck
in place. It was just me.
Huh?
All right, men, here's the deal.
For the time being at least,
we'll act as an
independent company.
Now, this won't be great
for our careers, mind you,
but we have other concerns.
[INQUISITION]
Sir!
Goodbye, Ocoho. Die well.
[gasps]
Hey. What're you doing, Dracoon?
You found me in the Sidh.
I guess you wanted
to say goodbye.
[grunts]
You can pull my cape
all you want,
but it's not gonna save me.
I'm completely under
Mordred's control.
I do appreciate your
persistence, but...
Wait. I'm moving of
my own free will.
How is that?
You still have a Gysoni flame.
Oh, I get it now. I never
released you from the spell.
That left us with a
lingering connection,
which you used to save me.
Draccoon!
Huh?
[OCOHO]
Please, Draccoon!
Don't leave me!
Shouldn't you be
falling right now?
What part of "jump off the ship"
did you not understand?
Oh. You're back to your senses.
Well, that's inconvenient.
Looks like I'll have to make
another mess on the deck
and get yelled at.
Be careful, gentlemen.
This one's wild.
Don't talk.
Don't you get it?
You have no chance.
Right or wrong, you've lost.
I'm curious, how'd you manage
to break the curse?
Is it just that you care
more about your life
than some peasants?
Shut your mouth.
We were friends.
I don't wanna hurt you
more than I have to.
If you want a painless death--
[OCOHO]
Shut up!
As long as I've known you,
you've been using me.
Well, guess what? Now it's
your turn to be the puppet.
Gysoni!
[growls]
[BARON MERCHANT gasp]
I need to get out of this hole
before our bombardment breaks
down the magic barrier.
Just what are you
trying to prove?
There's a reason you're
called the infected.
It's because you
people are sick.
You think that we're all sick?
Yeah. Right.
Anyway, I have to admit,
you put up a better fight
than I was expecting.
You defended well, but a
defensive focus has its limits.
[MELIE]
Same thing goes for offense.
Here. Let me show you!
What's the matter, Thaumaturge?
Can't you fight
in close quarters?
[LISELOTTE]
What's going on with this girl?
Everything from her footwork
to her expression
has suddenly changed.
I feel like I'm fighting
a different person.
Why are our soldiers
breaking formation?
What's going on up there?
Sorry. We're getting
torn apart, Colonel!
That horned sorcerer's
on a rampage--
we can't even slow him down!
I see.
[yells]
[INQUISITION scream]
It-It looks he's heading
straight for us, sir.
Indeed it does!
Guess I'm gonna get to
stretch my legs after all.
The giantess was a big let-down,
so a spirited scrap with
the horned sorcerer
is just what this old man needs.
[INQUISITION L]
Here he comes!
[SETH]
Skull Burst!
Well, this is certainly
an enigmatic sight to behold.
It would appear to
be raining soldiers.
They're coming from over there,
but where's the brat?
[SETH yelling]
Huh?
I've got you.
Pulsar!
[SANTORI yells]
Well, this is just delightful!
You've gained considerable power
in the brief time since
our last encounter.
Estimated casualties?
That barrage wiped out
around 30% of our soldiers.
Tch.
And they've captured the queen.
We need to get her back,
no matter the cost.
The rain's concealing
her location.
Even so, I'm forming
a party to search for her.
I want half of you
to ride out with me.
Hold on a minute.
I'm picking up a Fantasia
source of unknown origin
coming from the
direction of the castle.
What could it be?
[SOLDIER M] It's moving much
faster than a dragon.
In fact, it's not
even comparable.
[ORDERIC]
There's no way.
It'll be on us in just
a few moments, my lord!
[ORDERIC gasps]
[GUENOLINE]
Huh?
Hold on. Could it be--?
That armor, it's--
[SANTORI] Lemme give you a
taste of my celestial shoe!
[laughs]
Huh?
Uh?
[SETH, SANTORI yell]
Did we get shot at?
[SANTORI]
Well, this is peculiar.
Hey, Seth! Get me outta this
crazy thing! I'm dyin' in here!
Huh?
Doc?!
[NARRATOR]
The mysterious warrior
who just landed on
the battlefield is Doc,
though he's far from alone.
He stands against
a powerful enemy:
Verone, the Prince of Convictis.
Meanwhile, Seth and Santori's
battle escalates to a new level.
Seth's rage comes to a head
as he struggles against
his strongest enemy yet.
Next time on Radiant ,
"The Will of the People
Shines Bright."