[NARRATOR] Seth bade Alma
and the others farewell
and flew to Cyfandir.
There he encountered,
fought, and narrowly escaped
from the merchant barons
with the help of Grimm.
Caislean Merlin
has been defended
by the knight-sorcerers
since ancient times.
In this mystical city
where sorcerers
and humans live side by side,
Seth is surprised to find
the cherished friends
he had left behind in Artemis.
They say that Merlin
lived near here.
Hold on. Why are Melie
and Doc out here?
They didn't come to
find me, did they?
Where should we go?
Somewhere cheap.
Melie! N' Doc!
You okay?
What's up with her?
[NARRATOR]
"The City of Knights."
[NARRATOR] In times long past,
the great sorcerer Merlin
erected five colossal
menhirs, standing stones,
in order to protect the people.
The castle of Caislean
Merlin sits in the center
of these stones, and that
is Seth's destination.
[SETH] Hey, lady.
What'cha got on Radiant?
Radiant, huh?
Yeah! Right!
Sure, would you like me
to find a map for you?
Ah!
I was joking. We don't
have anything on it.
Aww. Really?
'Cause I heard that
back in the day,
the knight-sorcerers were
all about searching
for Radiant's location!
[CLERK A]
I've heard the same,
but that was a terribly
long time ago.
No one's seriously
looked for Radiant
since Merlin tried it
with his knight-sorcerers.
[SETH]
Man, but you're my only lead!
Yes, well, these days,
our forces are occupied
with fighting the Nemesis.
I don't suppose you came
out here to submit yourself
for knight-sorcerer training.
Training for what?
The knights-sorcerers receive
countless applications
from ambitious sorcerers
just like you
who wish to join their
illustrious ranks.
A few will be selected
to train as candidates,
and a few of those will
one day be recognized
as true knight-sorcerers.
Ah.
Go ahead.
Applications over there.
But that isn't what
I came here to do.
I just need help
finding Radiant, 'kay?
C'mon, miss, can't ya
think of anything
that might turn out
to be a decent clue?
Let's see.
There may be some pertinent
records in the Castle Archives.
Huh? Seriously?
Now we're talkin!
Lemme go check 'em out!
[CLERK A]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Priceless historical
documents are kept there,
so only authorized personnel
are permitted to enter.
Aw, that sucks.
Well, how the heck am
I supposed to become
authorized personnel?
Honestly?
Without any references,
your only chance would be to
apply for employment here.
Let's see what positions
we have open.
We need a secretary.
You think you can handle
the entrance exam?
Nope! Not a chance!
Well, we're also
looking for a guard
or a new stable-hand.
Those jobs wouldn't get you
into the archive though.
Most of these jobs won't.
The knight-sorcerers
have archive access
and they're taking applications.
Fine, I'll do it!
Being a knight might
be kinda fun anyway.
This the form? 'Kay...
And there. You've been rejected.
That was kinda quick.
Knight-sorcerers need to
help the people feel safe.
With your infection,
you can't do that.
Those horns of yours
will always scare people.
Huh? Then... what if no one
has to see my horns?
Am I good now?
No. That's fraud.
[GUARDS growl]
[SETH yells]
Well, that sure
didn't go my way.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[sighs]
No, no. Come to think of it,
I'm better off havin' that brat
outta my hair for good.
I'm actually relieved.
[laughing]
[MELBA]
Are you sure you're okay?
So, he's putting up
a tough front, I see.
[PAPA]
Yeah. This one...
By the way, Doc,
you said that Seth went to a
place called Caislean Merlin,
but I was wondering if you
could tell us what it's like.
You're some kinda know-it-all
researcher, right? So tell us.
Sure. It's the capital of a
faraway land known as Cyfandir.
A long time ago, a sorcerer
named Merlin saved the people
who lived there and united
them under his leadership,
founding a powerful new nation.
Because he's so popular there,
the place has very
little prejudice.
It's a haven for sorcerers,
kinda like Artemis.
Wow. You have such a
wealth of knowledge.
Well, when you're
in my line of work,
it pays to know what's
what in the world.
It can't pay that well
or you wouldn't be always up to
your neck in debt, would you?
I'm not the one who
racked up all that debt!
Cyfandir is an ancient land
with a complex history.
Many texts concerning magic are
stored in the capital's library.
[gasps]
Plus, I hear the
knight-sorcerers there
have been enlisting young
recruits and training them
to use a combination of
magic and martial prowess
to fight the Nemesis.
[MELIE]
Is that true? Are you sure?
[DOC]
Melie.
I don't know the details,
but I'm told that anyone
who passes their training
is recognized as a
capable sorcerer
well-able to hold their own
against any Nemeses.
What is it?
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[DOC]
Hey! Melie!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
[MELIE]
Doc. Mister Boobrie.
I'm sorry. Can't breathe.
Need time to catch my breath.
Man, I'm sure lookin'
forward to the day
I get my grown-up legs back.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Did you need something?
No. I just... You know.
I thought I'd take a walk.
Nothin' beats a leisurely stroll
after a cup of coffee.
You enjoy that.
Hey. Wait!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[MELIE]
A really long time ago,
before I'd ever set
foot in Artemis,
I did something that I
can never make up for,
no matter what I do.
[MELIE]
Ever since then,
I've been trying
so hard to be better.
But honestly, I don't feel like
anything's changed at all.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
[MELIE]
I'm still a--
[DOC] What you are
is an amazing tracker.
I am?
[DOC] I wouldn't hire just
anybody as my assistant.
I picked you 'cause you're good.
It's nice of you to tell
me that. Thank you.
But, Doc... that isn't
enough for me.
[DOC]
What could she have done?
[sighs]
Looks like I'm at a dead end.
I just flew halfway across
the friggin' world...
...and I still haven't found
any clues about Radiant.
Wonder who this is.
Uh...
Oh. Right.
[SETH]
Hey, there.
So you're the legendary
sorcerer Merlin, huh?
I hear you tried to
find Radiant, too.
I could really use a hint
if you've got any.
You know what the Nemesis are?
Or if they're actually evil
like everybody thinks?
[sighs] How am I supposed to
get into those archives?
[MYR] Why don't you
just act like a vine?
[SETH]
Huh?
[MYR] Vine's creep all over the
place and no one looks twice.
Sorry, but who are you?
I'm the wise fairy
of the statue.
A fairy?!
Though there are those
who would call me an imp.
Yeah? Even so, I've never
met a magical being before.
Hey. Wait, you're totally human!
So you've figured me out, eh?
Well, I'm still a better
source of advice
than that statue you
were chatting with.
[SETH yells]
[SETH]
What do you eat?!
[SETH coughs]
How's that for some
legendary sorcery, kiddo?
You're a legendary source of
stank, I'll give you that.
I have a number of fine skills.
My talent for unlawful
entry came to mind
when I heard you
profess your troubles.
Wait. "Unlawful entry"?
Hang on a second, are you saying
that you know of a way
to sneak into the castle?
Are you asking me
to share my wisdom?
I am.
[music plays]
[MYR] ♪ Closer to a
knight there is none ♪
♪ than the horse who
he rides as it runs. ♪
♪ This is a tale
quite bizarre. ♪
♪ Of a bold young
knight named Gontar. ♪
♪ For his steed he held
quite the fixation. ♪
♪ And it grew until
they had relations. ♪
♪ Twas a secret known to some. ♪
♪ That Gontar touched its-- ♪
I think I'm gonna cut
you off right there.
Heh. Looks like that hint
was a little too subtle.
♪ If to meet a knight-sorcerer
you wish to be able, ♪
♪ then heed this song well--
get your butt to the stables. ♪
The stables?
But I doubt they'll be anywhere
near the Castle Archives.
The castle?
I would never set foot in such
a cold and lifeless place.
I always like to have a few
tender shoots of grass
pressed betwixt my toes.
[SETH yells]
Keep up. We're almost
to the stables now.
I'm grateful that
you're trying to help,
but I don't wanna see horses.
I wanna see the records
from Merlin's adventures.
Ha! Doubt you'll find anything
but fluff about him there.
[SETH]
Huh?
You saying he wasn't as
great as everyone thinks?
'Cause I heard he saved
a whole bunch of people
and basically founded
this whole country.
[MYR] He was really just
a nasty old hermit.
Oh.
If you ask me, Merlin was dirty.
Vagabonds like him don't bathe!
That doesn't sound anything
like what I heard about him.
People always believe whatever's
most convenient for--
[horn blares]
Huh?
We're late.
Come along, Seth,
we need to hurry.
Yup, right behind you!
Is this it?
'Course it is.
Now get in there. Go!
[SETH yelping]
Hey, no pushing!
[MYR]
Oops!
The place has a password.
It's "Lulu is napping," okay?
What?
[SETH] What the heck
have I gotten into?
All units ready to depart
now should do so at once!
And all units not
ready to depart now
should do it at once anyway!
[KNIGHT-SORCERERS]
Sir!
[KNIGHT-SORCERER A]
Hurry it up!
Come on, this way!
I'll hand you the
reins to the dragon
right before the
fighting starts, okay?
Yeah. I've got you.
[KNIGHT-SORCERER E]
No! Not that way!
[KNIGHT-SORCERER F] Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
[KNIGHT-SORCERER E]
I don't know! Ask this thing!
[GATOR laughs]
[KNIGHT-SORCERER E]
Somebody help me!
[OCOHO]
Huh? Hey!
[SETH]
Uh...
[OCOHO]
Guy with the saddle! Over here!
You mean me?
[OCOHO]
Yeah, you.
Are you one of the new squires?
[OCOHO] That's my saddle
you've got, isn't it?
Where'd Lulu go?
Well, um...
The place has a password.
It's "Lulu is napping," okay?
I was told that she's napping.
Again? Well, that's a pain.
Okay, then put the saddle on.
Saddle?
[OCOHO]
Yeah. The one in your hands.
Ugh. Hurry, will ya?
We're gonna be late!
Oh, uh. Sorry.
[OCOHO]
Right there. Go ahead.
[SETH]
Okay. Like this?
[OCOHO]
Uh, no. That's backwards.
[SETH]
Oh.
[OCOHO] How is turning it
upside down gonna help?
[SETH]
Prob'ly won't, huh? Heh.
[OCOHO] Oh, I didn't realize
you were this new.
Well, uh.
I'll handle the prep this time.
Just watch what I do.
Oh, and put this on.
'Kay. How's it s'posed
to work though?
You should probably set
your bag down first.
Oh, wow! That thing's
totally amazing!
Whoa.
Cool! I look awesome!
[SETH laughs]
[OCOHO]
Glad you like it.
Well, hop on.
Um, the thing is,
I'm not really a--
[OCOHO]
Tell me later.
We're the last unit
that's still here.
[SETH yelps]
[OCOHO]
Hold on tight, okay?
[SETH] Whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait a second. I'm not ready.
All right, Dracoon,
let's do this!
[SETH screaming]
Slow it down! I'm falling!
Let's fly!
Oh, no.
[SETH screaming]
[SETH]
Whoa.
Woohoo!
This is so... incredible.
[SETH] It's nothing
like riding a broom.
Lulu's such a flake sometimes.
She could've at least told me
she was gonna send a
rookie in her place today.
Hey, look, can I tell
you something?
Sure, start with your name.
[SETH]
Huh? Oh, uh, right.
My name's Seth.
It's nice to meet you, Seth.
You can call me Ocoho.
I'm a knight-sorcerer candidate.
And here we have my
Racoon Dragon, Draccoon.
[DRACCOON purrs]
Congrats on getting
into the order.
We'll all be counting on you
to help us defeat the Nemesis.
What? Did a Nemesis
show up here?
Aw, man. Lulu didn't tell you
anything about this, did she?
Ya heard the horn blow, right?
That's basically what
calls us to battle.
So that's what that was.
But okay. We just need to take
down that pesky Nemesis.
You got it.
I'll do the fighting though,
you just steer Draccoon.
Uh.
Huh?
Yeah, I've never even ridden
on one of these things before,
so I don't think I'm
ready to drive one yet.
Seriously?
I'm really good on a broom.
Though my last two crashed...
Well then, how good
can you be, Seth?
Wait, just what were you doing
with my saddle in the stables?
Uh, I got thrown in at
random by a strange old man
who wears underwear
in his beard.
When your beard is as full
as mine, it needs it.
Myr got me again?
I guess you know him?
There's no one in the castle
who doesn't know that weirdo.
The guy's constantly
screwing with us.
Ugh. You've gotta be kidding me.
At this rate, I'm never
gonna get ordained.
[MORDRED]
Ocoho, are you all right?
How goes it, Mordred?
I'm great. Focusing
on concentrating.
Gotcha. Just try to be ready
so you can act when
we're given orders.
Of course! Don't you
worry about me.
I'll definitely do
my duty this time!
That's the spirit!
Whoa.
This one's even bigger than the
one we fought the last time.
The heck is that?
It's the size of an entire city!
It's what we're calling
a Spectral Nemesis.
A Spectral Nemesis?
Are they not like regular ones?
For one thing, almost none
of our attacks affect them.
You do know why
that is, don't you?
The Nemesis can only be hurt
by attacks that use Fantasia.
Those are the attacks that
haven't been working.
Oh, crap.
[OCOHO] No one had ever
seen a Spectral Nemesis
until pretty recently,
but lately,
they've become more common
than regular Nemeses.
If they can't be
hurt with magic,
then how do we beat them?
We'll be okay.
We have Mordred and Sagramore,
and their attacks
still work just fine.
Your teammates are named Marmot
and Sakura? That's weird.
Ugh! Their names are Mordred
and Sagramore, okay?
They're knight candidates,
the same as me.
[SETH]
Huh? Oh!
I saw them ride through town!
They're really popular.
And strong.
But I know I'm good
enough to match them.
[BRANGOIRE] I want all
of you knight candidates
to listen up now!
As you can see,
we're up against
another one of those
repugnant Spectral Nemeses.
I have two pieces of advice
for each of you.
First of all, you need
to sharpen your senses
while keeping the great
Merlin's teachings in mind!
And second of all-- Hmm.
Well, second, you need to, uh...
Look sharp. Keep your chins up.
You'll be fine. Don't-Don't...
Can ya tell us the
second part again?!
That's just how
Lord Brangoire is.
It's best if you don't
comment about it.
Oh, my bad.
Now then, we're gonna launch
our attack in four stages!
Stage one: You seven will form
a circle around the beast
and cast a confinement spell.
Do not let it break!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Sir!
[BRANGOIRE] In stage two,
you six will fire a salvo
of offensive spells at the
monster's head to disorient it!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Sir!
[BRANGOIRE]
Then in stage three,
Mordred and Sagramore will
move in at close range
and deal the killing blow!
Yes, sir!
We won't let you down.
After that, we'll move
to stage four. Hmm...
Which should really
speak for itself.
All right, let's do this!
Everybody, pull your hoods up!
Take the reins, okay?
'Kay.
Here we go. All together!
Gysoni!
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
What're those flames
above your head?
It's Gysoni.
Is that a spell? What's it do?
It lets us attune our
minds to Lord Brangoire,
even from a distance.
We effectively merge our minds
into one consciousness,
which lets us channel
far more Fantasia
than any of us could on our own.
Whoa. Do you think I could
learn that spell someday?
Sure. But just shut up for now.
I don't wanna miss the signal.
Okay, I'll be quiet.
[KNIGHTS-SORCERERS]
Cyfyngu!
[laughs]
Huh? Hang on.
Nothing's happening.
Nothing has to happen.
It hasn't moved yet,
but we're using this spell
to hold it in place
in case it tries.
Guess that kinda makes sense.
What's goin' on?
This thing's being swarmed
with dragons right now,
and it doesn't seem
to care a bit!
Well, that's--
[SETH] There aren't any
pieces of egg shell
on the ground either.
Plus, it's all glowy
and see-through.
Wait, none of this adds up!
I need you to stop
talking right now!
I have a hard time
using Gysoni as it is.
If you don't cut it out,
I'm gonna lose contact with
Lord Brangoire and the others.
[gasps]
[SETH]
Ocoho! Look out!
What's up?
Get down!
Repulse!
It didn't work!
Huh? Oh, no! He's falling!
Seth!
[NARRATOR]
Lacking the ability to affect
the Spectral Nemesis
with their magic,
the knight-sorcerers are
completely at its mercy.
While helping Seth protect
the farmers below,
Ocoho learns of the immense
power that he can channel.
Then, Ocoho is denounced
before Queen Boudica
for ignoring orders.
How will she be judged?
Next time on Radiant ,
"The Bringer of Calamity."