[NARRATOR] Seth encountered
a young man named Diabal
in a hidden chamber of
the keep at Caislean Merlin.
It's clear that he and
his shadowy allies
are creating Spectral Nemeses,
but to what end?
Even when Seth went berserk,
these new enemies had
the strength to match him.
[NARRATOR]
"Seth in the Forest of Time."
[SHADOW A]
He escaped?
[SHADOW B] Impossible! You saw
the hit he took from Diabal.
[SHADOW A] We need to cover
this breach with an illusion.
[SHADOW A gasps]
[SHADOW A]
Look down there. It's Myr.
[SHADOW B]
He's but a senile old man
who thinks he can
speak with flowers.
Even if that fool
were to witness
the second coming
of Merlin himself,
no one would believe
a word he said of it.
[DIABAL]
Were you able to find his body?
[SHADOW B]
No.
[DIABAL]
Then he's still alive.
We must do whatever it
takes to finish him off.
He knows where I'm hiding!
[SHADOW B]
Before we do anything,
you'll tell us who that was.
All I know is that he's with
the man who gave me these scars.
'Kay, you can let him out now.
Thanks for helping me
stow him away, my dear.
I'll come by and make it
up to you in a few days.
[MYR] These wounds are
beyond my power to treat,
but I've yet to see an injury
my wife couldn't heal.
[gasps]
What the heck was that
weird sensation?
[MELIE]
Doc!
[DOC]
Hey, Melie.
Listen. I'm pretty sure
Seth's in trouble!
Huh? What do you mean?
Well, this is certainly
peculiar, isn't it?
This rubble looks like
a piece of the castle,
but there's no sign that
the exterior is damaged.
Could it have been
a projectile then?
What would it be fired from,
some kind of catapult?
I doubt that this lump would
even make it over the wall.
--Yeah.
--[CASTLE GUARD A] Hmm...
Good point.
All of us did hear
that explosion, right?
Of course we all did.
[MELIE]
Ocoho.
Yeah?
Oh, hey.
Why did you bring a
little kid with you?
[DOC] I'll have you know
that I'm your elder!
Anyway, who is this girl?
[MELIE] This is Ocoho,
a knight candidate.
She's been with Seth since he
first arrived at the castle.
Oh! That's right!
We need to hurry.
Have you two found any clues
to where Seth might be?
This should be near the source
of the explosion we heard.
Hopefully it didn't
involve Seth.
[DOC]
Of course it involved him!
Whenever there's a
mess gettin' made,
you can always find
Seth in the thick of it!
Yeah, Doc's right.
The trail's extremely
faint right now.
But still, I'm picking up
traces of Seth's Fantasia.
Amazing!
Yep. Melie's tracking abilities
really are top-notch.
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirps]
Huh?
Seth has to be close.
Vestigia Invenire!
[MELIE]
Come on! This way!
The tracer disappeared?
That's what happens when
magic reaches the gate.
These walls are designed
to cancel out any spell
that tries to pass through them.
Well, in that case...
I'll try again now.
Vestigia Invenire!
It went into the forest?
[DOC] I don't remember adults
bein' this hard to keep up with
when I was a real kid.
I need to take a break,
so I'm gonna!
Ow! Stupid bat! Okay,
fine, I'll keep goin'!
[MELIE]
Let's hurry.
[OCOHO]
Wait! Hold on!
Haven't you heard
the old legends?
Caillte's forest is guarded
by a powerful spell.
Whoever goes in there gets
lost for years at a time.
Some people never make it back!
[DOC]
Seriously?
No one goes in there.
Even veteran knight-sorcerers
steer clear of these woods.
Well, if you say so.
Let's look around
the edges instead.
You do that.
I'll go in alone!
[OCOHO, DOC yell]
[OCOHO]
Hey! Wait, Melie!
[OCOHO screams]
[DOC screaming]
[MELIE]
Look it. What is this place?
[OCOHO]
Idiot.
I get it now.
Of course you're
a friend of Seth's,
you're every bit as awful
at listening as he is!
How do you expect to
get out of here, Melie?
Uh, I don't feel like
it'll be that difficult.
We just turn and...
retrace our steps...?
Wait, Melie just dragged us
through a big thicket, right?
[MISTER BOOBRIE crying]
[MELIE, OCOHO yelp]
[ALL sigh]
What was that thing? Did you
feel how strong its aura was?
That monster could eat us all
in one bite! We should run!
I'm so sorry. It's my
fault that we're all--
Oh. Stop. Save that
for later, 'kay?
Apologizing won't
get us anywhere.
Let's focus on the task at hand.
We'll be fine if we
all work together.
If we must get eaten,
we'll do it as a team.
We've got two main objectives!
First, we've gotta
try to find Seth.
Then we just need to leave.
Right!
[MISTER BOOBRIE chirping]
Stop your squawkin'!
You're gonna make that
monster come back!
What do you see?
[DOC]
No monster.
[MELIE]
Where could it have gone?
The question that you
ought to be asking
is "when" could it have gone.
Give it a rest, Myr.
We don't have time for your
silly riddles right now.
Ugh. Wait!
--[MELIE, DOC scream]
--Myr?
Hello, everyone.
I take it that you three are
also out for a relaxing stroll
through this serene
little patch of garden?
[DOC] Serene garden?
It's a monster-infested jungle!
Oh my. Well, this is
certainly a surprise.
You three can see
the wildlife, eh?
[OCOHO]
Yeah, of course.
I'm also quite impressed you've
managed to avoid getting lost.
[DOC] We're actually
as lost as can be.
Are you really?
In that case, you're
welcome to come with me.
I'll introduce you to my wife.
Look, Myr, I'm sorry, but we're
really kinda busy right now.
We have to find Se--
[MYR]
Oh, he's with me.
[ALL]
Huh?!
Seth!
He looks terrible!
What happened to him?
I don't understand
these injuries either.
Which is why I'm taking
the boy to an expert.
Ah! Those birds look
just like tortibri.
Huh.
And those flowers.
I've seen them in an antique
field guide by Sextus Apuleius.
Almost every living thing out
here was believed to be extinct.
If these specimens are real,
this is a huge discovery.
Why doesn't the enchantment
of the forest affect you, Myr?
Enchantment?
You do know about it, right?
Anyone who enters
this forest gets lost.
People have ended up trapped
in here for decades.
[MYR]
Oh, yeah?
[OCOHO] The legends say
it's because of a spell
cast by Merlin himself
to protect us
from invading enemy armies.
Isn't that amusing. You people
really are quite ridiculous.
When something confounds you,
rather than confess your
ignorance about it,
you come up with a
random explanation.
It's true that many people
have been lost in this forest,
but I can assure you
that this isn't
because of some magic spell.
Here we are.
I have to say,
you're looking even more radiant
than usual, sweet pea.
[MELIE, DOC, OCOHO yelp]
Welcome home, shrubby hubby.
It's good to be back!
I brought you some
visitors this time.
A bouquet of humans just for me?
Myr, you shouldn't have!
I'll put them in the
vase straightaway!
[MELIE, DOC, OCOHO scream]
[JILL laughs]
[JILL]
Relax, I'm only kidding.
You should've seen your faces.
We would never decorate
with living humans.
We're not sadistic monsters--
we have morals.
We would never be so cruel
as to cut down a living thing
just to stick it in a vase.
We wait until you're dead first.
I'm never gonna pick a living
flower again, I promise!
Me, neither!
I'm only gonna use
rocks for decoration
from this day forward!
Jill's just teasing you a bit.
I assure you, my
adorable honeysuckle
is as gentle as a
sweet spring rain.
[BOTH giggle]
Hold on. You smell like pollen.
I'd better not find
out that you've been
hanging around those
loose city plants again.
You're the only one for me,
my succulent sapling!
[JILL]
Don't lie to me, Myr.
I can see that leaf
in your beard!
You know, it's funny you
should mention that leaf
because I bet it got stuck there
when I was leaning on a tree
as I wrote you this
new love song.
[MYR clears throat]
I call it:
Ode to my blossoming buttercup
and her soft, supple bark.
[MELIE]
Um. Excuse me!
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but my friend's badly hurt
and we heard that
you could help him.
[JILL] Oh, my. That
one's all-but wilted.
[MELIE]
I'm begging you.
Help Seth. Please
save my friend!
[JILL chuckles]
[MYR]
Right there. Can you see it?
It's almost transparent,
but there's a little
orb around him.
Tried my best to break it,
but nothing I could come up
with seemed to do the trick.
So what did you end
up doing to get in?
I caused a little tree to grow
and let it push through
with its branches.
Oh. Very clever.
Ah! What the heck are
you guys? You're so big!
Oh. Sorry about that. One sec.
Myr?
Yup. That's me.
And this is Jill, my wife.
[SETH]
Your wife?
I know. She's a hottie.
Stop it. You old charmer.
Hey, uh, could you maybe tell
me how you're inside my head?
Inside your head?
Wow, Myr. Your friend has quite
the self-centered theory.
We're drifting through
a spiritual plane
called the "Sidh" right now.
[SETH]
The "Sidh"?
[JILL]
Yes. Very good.
There aren't too many who
can awaken themselves
to this plane of existence,
but everyone has a place in it.
Once you grow accustomed
to the Sidh,
you can use it to seek
out other entities.
You can even use it
to communicate
over great distances.
Ohh.
[MYR]
Now tell me, Seth.
Who awoke you to the Sidh?
And where'd the eye come from?
I think Piodon. He says
that we're brothers.
He saved my life,
but at a price.
[BOTH]
Hmm...
[MELIE] So, um, what do you
think they're doing?
[DOC] To be honest, it looks
like they're nappin'.
[MELIE]
No. That can't be it.
[DOC]
You sure?
[MELIE]
Are they actually napping?
No, they're not!
They're talking with Seth.
Their auras are all over his.
Can't you sense it?
Their auras?
What do you mean?
Come to think of it,
I do sort of get the feeling
that they're connected somehow.
I can't normally sense
this kinda stuff,
but here in the woods,
it seems to come so naturally.
It almost feels like
the forest is helping me.
Hey! I've got an idea!
Ya ready?
Wait, what are you gonna do?
I'm pretty curious, too.
[MYR]
Hmm...
So you passed out
from the poison
and woke up inside this bubble
along with that little eyeball.
That's right.
Then the eye swallowed me up
and seized control of my body.
I couldn't stop it.
It sent me on a rampage.
I need to know--do you think
this'll happen again?
[MYR]
It seems likely.
Hard to say till we know
what this thing is.
It's possible that it's been
acting on its own accord.
And there is a chance
you've been controlling
it subconsciously.
The worst case is probably
if it's subservient
to this Piodon fellow
you told us about.
I'm holding it back
from possessing you
for the moment at least.
But without its raw
power to sustain you,
you're more or less stuck
at the brink of death.
[SETH]
What?! Brink of death?!
I'm really about to die?
Given enough time,
I can heal your wounds.
But if I were to wake you up,
you would leave the Sidh,
which could break the spell
that Myr used to trap the eye.
So you're saying that I would
lose control of myself again.
I mean, unless you can figure
out how to get a handle on it,
yeah.
[SETH]
I can't.
So... just leave me like this.
[MELIE]
Don't talk that way!
[gasps]
[SETH]
Melie?
Did you bring the two
of them in here?
Yep.
Nicely done, kid.
Does this face look
nice to you?
Just look what
you've done to me!
Ya made me an
old coot. Fix me!
Yeah, I don't know
how that happened.
But hey, you should turn right
back to normal when we leave.
[OCOHO chuckles nervously]
That's my guess at least.
Then let's leave now!
Huh? But we just got here.
I'm not staying like this one
second longer than I gotta!
So hurry up and get
me outta this place!
Aww, but--
You don't understand
what this is like!
I need to go back, now!
Okay, I'll take you back.
Just stop your shouting.
[MELIE] I can't believe
you're trying to give up.
That isn't who you are, Seth.
I'm just scared.
This monster takes over my body
every time I let my guard down.
It doesn't matter
how hard I fight,
or how loud I scream.
In fact, I feel like
it just gets stronger
the more I struggle against it.
There's nothing I can
do to make it stop.
So what's the plan?
You're just gonna mope
inside this bubble forever?
I thought you would understand.
Well, I don't, Seth.
So try explaining.
You know what it's like
to lose control of yourself.
If anyone should get what that
means for me, then it's you.
[MELIE] It means you're
gonna have to struggle.
Just like everyone else does.
Doc got turned into a helpless
infant and he didn't give up.
I've been randomly losing
my mind for years now
and I'm not giving up.
We all have things we
have to push through.
Why won't you try?
[SETH] You know what it's
like to lose control.
Now imagine if every
time it happened,
you destroyed everything
and everyone around you.
If you knew that your curse
could make you kill
Boobrie, or Doc, or me,
would you really still
let us get close to you?
Would you risk it?
You'd leave? Right?
Look, here's the deal,
this thing is a monster
and I can't control it.
Any more than you can
control your curse.
If I'm wrong, tell me.
Have you ever been
able to fight it off?
[MELIE]
No.
I can't beat it.
[MELIE]
But... you have.
You've snapped me out of a fit
more than once now, Seth.
My curse never
seemed to scare you,
or to damage the
trust you put in me.
I still don't know how
I even earned that trust.
You've always acted
as if my infection
was this insignificant thing.
You treated it like
it was just a quirk,
a part of my personality.
'Cause of you,
that's actually how I've
begun to see it myself.
[MELIE]
Look, Seth,
I know our situations
are different, but...
...just try.
I'm sure that you can find
a way to beat this thing.
I'm too weak, Melie.
[SETH]
Well, on my own at least.
So, yeah. I'm glad that
I have you around.
Do you mean--?
[SETH] I have no idea
how this thing works,
but the more I talk to you,
the more it seems to calm down.
It doesn't feel so scary now.
I thought that this
was something
I would have to take
care of by myself,
but I was wrong.
I-I do need help.
I don't wanna leave
you behind again,
but I couldn't live with myself
if I hurt you somehow.
Which leaves me one option.
I swear, I'm gonna learn
to control this thing.
No doubt.
Good news.
[SETH chuckles]
What's so funny?
I missed the joke.
I just had to get stabbed.
Huh? To do what?
To convince you to
be my friend again.
When did I ever stop
being your--? Oh.
That's right. You were so
dang worried you forgot!
I guess so. Huh.
I'm glad we can start
talkin' casually again.
I missed ya.
[MELIE] Hold on.
I'm still mad at you, Seth!
[SETH]
So you were mad!
[MELIE] No! That just
slipped out. I wasn't--!
Agh... C'mon. Gimme a break.
[SETH]
Melie.
[MELIE]
Huh?
[SETH]
Thank you.
[MELIE chuckles]
[MYR]
Ah. She woke up.
As for him, he seems a bit
less wilted than before.
[OCOHO]
So what's that mean?
Will he be okay?
Yeah, he's decided to keep
pushing forward with our help.
Well, that's a relief.
Although it seems he plans
to stay here with Myr.
He said he wanted to spend
some time training with him.
[OCOHO, DOC]
With him?
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Determined
to find a way to control
the chaotic power within him,
Seth begins a training regimen
unlike any he's been
through before,
under the tutelage
of Myr and Jill.
After learning the true
nature of Fantasia,
and how to open his senses
to the world around him,
Seth confronts the dark power
that Piodon placed inside him.
Next time on Radiant ,
"The Palace of Schemes."