[NARRATOR] After the fight
with the Spectral Nemesis,
Seth encountered
Grimm once again.
Grimm asked Seth for a favor,
then suggested that Seth
look for Doc and Melie
at an inn called the Luchorpan.
And so, Seth did exactly that.
[DOC] Who the heck's knockin'
in the dead of night?
It's you!
[SETH]
Yeah. Hey.
[DOC]
How did you know we were here?!
Let's call it a guess.
So is Melie here?
Her? Yeah, but she's
already asleep, so...
[MELIE]
Doc?
[SETH]
Then who was that?
Get outta here, will ya?
We need our rest!
[SETH]
I heard her!
Come on. Why are you
acting like this?
It sucks, but you need
to leave, 'kay?
I'm serious. This is for
your own good, Seth.
[SETH]
What?
Listen, Doc, I just wanna tell
her that I'm sorry, okay?
[MELIE]
What for? Why are you sorry?
Melie.
[NARRATOR]
"Silent Rain, Distant Hearts."
You say you're sorry,
but why would you be?
I--
[MELIE] What made you decide
to come and see us,
after what you did?
Oh, um. Well, I--
For one thing,
I want to let you know
that I still plan to pay
you guys back. I swear.
Oh, so that's what
this is about.
Well, then there's no need
for you to say sorry.
You don't owe me anything.
Stop! Please tell me
what's going on with you!
[MELIE] I have a very
busy day tomorrow.
Wait, you're angry
because I left Artemis
without warning you,
is that right?
[MELIE]
Not at all. It's fine.
Then talk to me!
I just wanna know how I
made you so angry, Melie.
[MELIE]
You haven't. I'm not.
It really seems like you are.
I can honestly say
I'm not mad at you.
But... I'll admit that
I'm a bit jealous.
What?
Seth, it must be nice for you,
to move on to the next
thing just like that.
We had lots of adventures
in Artemis, didn't we?
It was fun while it
lasted, at least.
[SETH]
Yeah.
[MELIE]
We hung out at Kettle Coffee.
Took a job from
Master Lord Majesty.
Saved Doc from a Kraken.
Good times.
Uh. Sure.
[MELIE] Actually, a lot of what
we did was scary or sad,
but we got through it
because we had each other.
We weren't together
for long. Not really.
But even so, I thought
of us as a team.
As friends.
And then you left. Because you
didn't feel the same way.
Melie.
[MELIE] We didn't mean to
you what you meant to us.
It's just that simple, Seth.
[MELIE]
Nothing to say to that?
Good. That's fine.
Must be my fault for
misunderstanding
--where you and I stood.
--It isn't true.
[SETH] You guys...
are both important to me.
Really. I care about you.
That's why I didn't
want to cause you
more trouble than I had.
You're kidding.
What kind of trouble?
[SETH] You know.
The kind that I get into.
Before you took off,
when you said you
wanted to come here,
I was so excited to see
the knight-sorcerers.
With them, I thought I'd be able
to improve my offensive magic.
It didn't even cross my mind
that you wouldn't take me.
I'm sorry. I never should've
gotten your hopes up like that.
I didn't exactly
plan all this out.
But I didn't want to
leave you guys behind.
I did it because I was
worried about you.
Look, I've got no idea why,
but those Thaumaturge guys
are still trying to catch me.
Honestly, I just--
I don't wanna put
either one of you
into any more
danger than I have.
[MELIE] Setting the state
of Doc's body aside,
we aren't children in
need of protection.
I can take care of
myself just fine.
Besides, even if something
were to happen to me,
that wouldn't be anyone's
responsibility but my own.
If you had any faith in me,
I think you'd agree with that.
But you see me as a
weakness. A liability.
So yeah. Of course you
came to this town alone.
I trust you both
completely. It's just--
[MELIE]
Go on.
[SETH]
Actually, you know what?
You're right.
It's true. I left you
behind for a reason.
It's because I didn't
want you around me.
What's with you?
That was just mean.
But it needs to be said.
I'm not just worried about the
Nemesis and the Inquisition.
I'm scared of myself.
Fact is, I don't know when
I might lose control next,
and so I'm worried
that it might happen
with you guys around.
Why's that?
You've gotta be kidding me.
Look, have you forgotten
what I turned into
when I fought against
the Thaumaturges?
Of course I remember.
I was really scared.
Okay, in that case,
you should understand!
Whenever I lose
control of myself,
I don't know what's what.
I can't tell friend from foe.
So basically, you left
me and Doc behind
because you don't feel like
we're strong enough, right?
That's not the point
I'm trying to make here!
[MELIE] You think that I'm
so useless and fragile
that all I could do
if you went berserk
is get myself killed.
I know you're tough,
and I don't think that
either of you are useless!
[MELIE] Right. You just
don't have any use for us.
You're wrong!
I'd've brought you, but I'm
not safe to be around.
When that other side
of me takes over,
there's no telling
what I might do.
So I can't just--
You can't what? Have friends?
You think that if you can't
fully control yourself,
then you shouldn't
get close to anyone?
You think that rather
than ask for help,
some people should
just be alone?
Come on, Seth. Look at
who you're talking to!
It's me. "Crazy Melie,"
the walking disaster!
I get it, the thought that
there's someone inside you
who could hurt your friends
without you even knowing
it is terrifying!
Who would even wanna be friends
with someone like that?
Not too many.
After years of searching,
I know that for a fact.
[MELIE]
Ever since I was infected,
there's been this growing
void around me.
I didn't have to decide to
keep people at arm's length
like you have, Seth, the
other Melie did that for me.
She's ruined my entire life.
But I never stopped hoping
things would change someday.
That I'd meet someone who
would stand by my side.
Someone who could stop me
if I started acting crazy.
[MELIE]
And maybe, just maybe,
if that someone
had been there...
...then it's possible
that poor Venelope
would still be around, even now.
[MELIE]
Things were better.
I'd finally found someone
who understood my pain.
Someone who accepted
me and my curse.
I had a friend I could trust.
A friend who trusted me.
At least, that's what I thought.
I'm sorry, Seth.
I didn't wanna let you
see me act so pathetic.
[SETH]
Listen--
Stop talking. Please.
I didn't say all that to
get you to comfort me,
and your pity doesn't
do me any good either.
I honestly wouldn't know,
but maybe you're right.
Maybe I should be living
the same way that you do.
If I kept people
at arm's length,
if I stopped opening my heart,
I guess I would
stop getting hurt.
But it was worth the pain.
Having a friend who
worried with me,
who wasn't afraid
to stand at my side.
Know what? Maybe this isn't
about which way is right.
Maybe we're just different.
I guess you just didn't want
the same things as me.
[SETH gasps]
Goodbye.
I was so scared I would
hurt her... and now I have.
[door opens]
[DOC]
You know, Seth.
I tried hard to talk Melie
out of coming here.
But she had already
made up her mind.
The way she put it, she wanted
to strengthen her magic
and prove that she could
take care of herself.
Apparently, she's joined up
with other teams before,
but it never lasted too long.
Each time, her curse would
take over and screw it all up.
Melie's been waiting
for most of her life
to meet someone like you.
Someone who wouldn't give
a damn what her curse was.
But then...
I left her. Just like
all the others.
Even though your intentions
were entirely different,
you ended up ditchin'
Melie in the same way
all the people before you had,
and that was rough for her.
[DOC] So maybe try not to blame
her for how she's takin' it.
There's only one person
to blame here. That's me.
I see.
Hey, Seth. Uh.
What're you plannin'
to do now?
Do you have somewhere to go?
Don't worry about it.
Might be broke, but I've
got somewhere to stay.
[DOC]
Really?
Well, hey. Good for you.
[DOC]
Anyway, headin' back in.
See ya.
[SETH]
Hm. Where should I go from here?
[stomach growls]
[chuckles]
[SETH]
This thing.
That's right.
Is anybody home, or--?
Uh.
[yells]
[OCOHO]
Only three?
Then, Deine!
That was amazing.
[OCOHO]
Huh?
Draccoon, Egwil!
Hey! I can see you tryin'
to peep through that door.
And unless you work
with the Order,
visiting hours are
way past over.
Uh. Ocoho, right?
Seth?
Hey.
[OCOHO] Look at you!
You're soaked to the bone!
Honestly, the locals here dress
warmly for a reason, ya know.
[SETH]
Heh. Right.
Uh, mind if I stay here
until the rain stops?
[OCOHO]
I guess that's fine.
Here. Dry off with this.
[SETH]
Thanks a bunch.
Ah! It smells like dragon poo!
[SETH groans]
[OCOHO]
Beggars can't be choosers!
[SETH]
Oh, also, I left my backpack
when I came earlier today,
do you mind if I grab it?
No prob. Just a second.
Where could I have
put that thing?
Oh, there it is! Lulu was
using it as a pillow.
[SETH]
Who's Lulu?
Is she why the password
was "Lulu is napping"?
You haven't actually
met her yet, have you?
She's a little busy.
But this is my squire, Lulu.
She helps me take
care of Draccoon.
She also pilots Draccoon,
maintains our equipment,
trains with me, and helps me
out in a bunch of other ways.
She's what you would call
an irreplaceable partner.
[SETH]
Huh?
[OCOHO]
Now then, just gonna yoink this.
It is yours, right?
Uh. Yeah.
[SETH] Wait, so why has she
been asleep this whole time?
It doesn't seem normal.
Unless... That must be how
her curse works, right?
[OCOHO]
Oh, um. Well, yeah, I guess so.
It's something like that.
[SETH] Huh. So, Ocoho,
what's your infection?
Huh? Say what?
Why would you ask that?
I barely even know you!
That's so rude!
Why though?
I wouldn't be mad if ya
brought up my horns.
[OCOHO]
That's 'cause you're weird!
Infections are a very
private subject!
Hey! Can I guess it?
I'm thinkin' your curse
makes you ignore
whatever anybody says
to you, is that right?
No! You just keep getting more
rude over time, ya know that?
That means I'm close.
Oh, is it--?
[OCOHO] Help me drown him out,
Draccoon. My hands are full!
Cover my ears for me!
Lemme go!
I asked you to cover
my ears, not...
That looks cozy.
Well, anyway, I think I'll
go ahead and take the hint
to stop making guesses
about your curse for now.
[OCOHO sighs]
It's clear that you
aren't used to the way
things work in Cyfandir.
So tell me, where'd
you come from?
Most recently,
I lived in Artemis.
Before I moved there,
I stayed near a place
called Pompo Hills.
And you came all the
way to Caislean Merlin
from way out there?
Why would you do that?
Mostly 'cause I'm
trying to find Radiant.
Radiant, huh? You wanna
find it for a reason?
To help fix the world.
So believe it or not,
I was told your
knight-sorcerers here
were searching for it as well.
Doesn't look like
that's true anymore.
It's not. That quest
ended a long time ago.
Which means my only chance
to find something out
is to break into
the Castle Archives.
I wouldn't recommend it.
The archives are well-guarded.
Hey, cut that out! Come on, Myr!
What's with you?
How long ago did you creep in,
and what are you always doing
here, ya sneaky little imp?
I'm just getting
out of the storm.
S'been raining hard
enough to drown a duck.
[chuckles]
[OCOHO] Hey! Get your paws
off Draccoons's food!
Stop pretending you're homeless
and go back to
your wife already!
I would if she'd have me.
But she's all kinds
of angry at me!
I got the boot 'cause
she thinks I cheated!
You? Cheat? No way!
You might try to.
[MYR]
You'd be surprised.
I'll have you know that I've
got more than one mistress.
I'm a ladies' man...
[SETH]
Maybe I'll leave and come back.
I'll play you this romantic
little number I wrote
with the girls in mind.
Ahem.
The berry first
time we did meet,
I did not believe
that melons could grow
so round as yours.
But in time we grew close,
and entwined and did greet,
your sister so sweet
as no wine e're poured.
And so I resolved to
make you both mine.
To declare you sweet
cantaloupes my little--
--[thud]
--[MYR screams]
Feel free to step in
and help me deal
with this freak anytime, Seth!
Huh? Seth?
[SETH]
Man, his songs are awkward.
[OCOHO]
Going somewhere?
Don't'cha think you've got a
little explaining to do first?
I'm sorry for causing
you trouble earlier.
It was my fault that
ya got yelled at
by the mean old dude
with the beard.
[OCOHO]
I don't care about that.
I wanna know your
secret, so spit it out!
[SETH]
What? Spit what out?
[OCOHO] The secret of how
you were able to gather
such an insane
amount of Fantasia
when we were casting
that Cromen Spell!
Well? Let's hear it!
Huh? I don't think I
did anything special.
I'm pretty sure you gathered
most of that by yourself.
Nope! No way!
Kinda hate admitting this,
but when I'm on my own,
I can't gather anywhere
near that much Fantasia.
Which means it must've
come from you!
Now tell me how you did it!
Okay, well, maybe it was me,
but that doesn't mean
I know how I did it.
So you don't know?
Right.
In that case, I think you
should be my sparring partner.
[SETH] But why? You and Draccoon
were doing fine earlier.
[OCOHO]
Draccoon isn't nearly enough.
Lord Brangoire put me
on the defense squad,
but that isn't me at all.
I'm a fighter. I'm s'posed
to be in the thick of it!
You know what I mean?
Anyway, I'm tryin' to beef
up my offensive strength
and polish my technique
so I can put on a show
and help him to see
my true potential.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
I've got my hands full
trying to deal with
my own problems.
[OCOHO]
Aw, man.
Wait, what if you
and I make a deal?
Help me train and I'll find
you books from the castle.
Wait a sec? You mean
from the archive?
I can only use the
library right now,
but it's worth a shot, right?
Think about all
those history books.
There must be one
that mentions Radiant!
I should say no.
[OCOHO] There isn't much
time before they decide
which candidates to ordain!
Please help me!
I wanna be a knight-sorcerer
more than anything!
It's been my wildest
dream forever!
And I can help you, too,
so think of this as fate!
Come on! Just please
say you'll do it!
So you think that if you
can't fully control yourself,
then you shouldn't
get close to anyone?
You think that rather
than ask for help,
some people should
just be alone?
Listen.
I really doubt that I'll be
able to do anything for you.
But...
I'm out of leads,
so I need those books.
And if there's a
chance I can help
make that dream
of yours happen--
[OCOHO]
Ah! That sounds like a yes!
Yeah. I think we may as
well give it a shot.
[OCOHO]
Woohoo! Thanks a million!
Okay, we'll get up
at five every morning
and train for two
and a half hours.
Wait. D'you say five?
[OCOHO] I've got drills
during most of the day,
but I'm totally free at night!
So we'll meet up again
and duke it out
until one of us goes down!
Say what?
You've gotta train
at least that hard
if you wanna be a
knight-sorcerer.
[SETH grunts]
Okay.
Well, if that's how it is,
I'mma get goin' and look
for a place to sleep.
Otherwise, I'm not sure
I'll wake up in time.
So do you not have
a place to stay?
Then how 'bout you crash here?
Am I even allowed to?
Of course you're not,
but make sure nobody finds
out and you'll be fine.
Draccoon's super fluffy.
I bet he'll make a great bed!
Thank you, Ocoho.
This is a huge help!
I'm looking forward
to it, Seth.
Know what? Right back at'cha!
[gasps]
That dream... I had it again.
[NARRATOR]
Seth sneaks into the castle
and is perturbed at
what he sees there.
Those halls should
be a mystery to him,
but he finds them familiar
on account of his dreams.
When he arrives at the place
where his dreams led him,
Seth meets a tortured young man
who lives in mortal
fear of Piodon.
Next time on Radiant ,
"His Name Is."