Did we get shot at?
[SANTORI]
Well, this is peculiar.
Hey, Seth!
Get me outta this crazy thing!
I'm dyin' in here!
Wait, Doc?
[NARRATOR] "The Will of
the People Shines Bright."
[ARTO]
A fine landing.
[LANDLAKE]
Verily, my friends.
Twas an entrance worthy
of a true knight.
[GUEN]
Now then, where's the foe?
[ANCESTOR A]
Take me to the rogues at once!
[ANCESTOR B]
Take me as well!
[ANCESTOR C]
And me!
So, who all's in there?
It sounds like there's
a whole bunch of you.
[ARTO]
Hm? Who's asking?
[LANDLAKE]
Be this the foe?
[GUEN]
Draw your weapon, boy.
[SETH] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hold on a second.
[DOC]
Leave him be!
Seth's a friend!
Not an enemy, got it?
[ARTO] So he's a
subject of the kingdom?
No, not exactly.
[ARTO]
Then he must be an enemy.
I just said he's not, okay?!
Life isn't that black and white!
Hey, Doc. Is that you?
Where'd you get
that awesome armor?
[LANDLAKE] The boy recognizes
greatness when he sees it.
He is a friend!
[GUEN] Tell us more about
how awestruck you are.
Seriously, how'd ya
end up in there?
Basically, I found a whole
bunch of memory stones,
but was about to get caught,
so I climbed in
this armor to hide,
but then it lit up
all of a sudden,
and the stones started talkin'!
Stop! Shut up already!
They keep fightin' for
control of this thing!
It's drivin' me nuts!
[GUEN]
You should learn some restraint.
[LANDLAKE]
What do you make of this pose?
[ARTO]
Nay! Like this!
I like 'em both?
[SANTORI] I hope you'll
forgive me for interrupting,
but I came here looking
for a slugfest!
[DOC screams]
[ARTO] At last. The enemy
has made himself known.
[SANTORI]
Impressive!
You managed to stop my projected
fist with a single hand.
I've heard that Cyfandir's
greatest heroes
are kept in memory stones.
It would appear that the
knights of Caislean Merlin
had one last trick to pull out.
[ARTO] My lords, to win this
battle, we must fight as one.
Wait a sec. You've got
a kid in here, you can't!
[LANDLAKE] Aye, we'll dispatch
the wretch together.
Are you even listening?
[GUEN]
In Merlin's name,
we shall fight till
our lives are spent!
You're dead already.
[ARTO]
Let's go!
[ANCESTORS]
Right!
Oh, yeah! You're makin'
this old man feel alive!
[SETH]
He's actually taking damage.
I'll hit him before
he projects again.
Skull Burst!
[yells]
[ARTO]
The boy has spirit.
[DOC] This is our
chance to run! Let's go!
[LANDLAKE]
Shut your craven mouth.
[GUEN]
Death or glory?
[ANCESTORS]
Both!
[DOC]
What is wrong with you maniacs?!
[GUEN]
Huh?
Don't let up on him! Pulsar!
[ARTO]
Well struck.
[LANDLAKE]
The blackguard has fallen.
[DOC] Great! Let's run then!
Come on! Chop-chop!
[GUEN] That seemed rather easy.
How disappointing.
[ARTO]
I'm sure he fought as hard
as his old bones would allow.
[LANDLAKE] Are all our
adversaries so ancient,
or might there be some
healthy ones elsewhere?
[SETH]
No way.
That bastard fell asleep
on us! Hey, Gramps!
Sorry, I was just
resting my eyes is all.
[SETH] You'd better take
this seriously, creep!
By the way, weren't you supposed
to pull your troops back
once Eyepatch found me?
[chuckles] It's funny.
I fought against the
Brotherhood of the Ashes
for seven days and seven nights.
Faced the great Albur Fendragon
in an honorable duel.
Pursued the formidable Saroumor
to the ice fields...
What's he going on about?
[SANTORI] But of all the mighty
opponents I've tussled with,
none could hold a candle to you.
You never fail to surprise me,
though we've fought many times.
[SOLDIER A]
Colonel Santori!
We were trying to
restrain the queen,
but a giant knight-sorcerer
showed up.
We can't get past him!
[SANTORI] Why are you
bothering me about it?
[SOLDIER A]
Sir?
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm busy right now!
You'll just have to find a way
to capture the queen yourselves.
[SOLDIER A]
Sir!
[ARTO]
The queen of Cyfandir?
[LANDLAKE] By Merlin,
we must rescue her at once!
[GUEN]
Away!
[DOC] Nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-no! Wait!
Hold on! Don't do this! Please!
[SETH]
Doc!
[SANTORI laughs]
[SANTORI]
Alone at last.
We can finally pick up
where we left off,
without anyone else meddling.
Come at me!
Hmm.
You seemed a little more savage
in our previous encounters.
What do you mean
"previous encounters"?
I've seen you once, above
Rumble Town's clock tower.
[SANTORI]
Oh, we met long before that.
The first time I saw those
horns was back in Vivacyne.
Oh, no. Don't you remember me?
And I thought what
we had was special.
Sure you were only a child,
and we did little more than
cross paths, but even so...
A horned child back in Vivacyne?
[DIABAL] I thought I'd lost
his trail in Vivacyne,
but then I saw someone else.
A brother who looked even
more like me than Piodon.
You're talking about Triton.
It wasn't me you saw there,
it was one of my brothers!
There's not a doubt
in my mind that it was you.
You had the same face
and the same tiny horns.
Well, we're brothers, of course
we would look the same!
Huh?
It's strange to
think of, but yes,
I suppose it could've
been a brother of yours.
Actually, it could
explain a few things.
What things would it explain?!
How ya get around so quick.
Why you're such a natural
with Fantasia.
And why my superiors are so
keen on catching the lot of you.
You and your infected
brothers are plague rats.
What's your problem?!
I'm the one you want, but you
still attacked the castle
after Eyepatch gave his signal.
He promised me you would stop!
This is just wonderful!
Keep it up, kid!
I want you fired up for this!
[SETH] If I'm your target,
then come at me.
Leave this country out of it!
There's a lot more than
you could know going on
behind the scenes here.
The main goal is to make
sorcerers look evil.
[SETH]
Huh?
[SANTORI] That'll ease the
people's collective conscience.
When they learn that
we've released your kind
from the shackles of freedom.
[SETH]
"Released from freedom"?
[SANTORI chuckles]
[SANTORI] You might not be
the reason we invaded,
but you are the reason
General Torque sent me
to lead our forces.
My orders are to beat
the fight out of you
and bring you back to the boss,
and I'm so glad to see
that you've still got the
strength for a brawl.
You're burning, old man.
[SANTORI]
You bet your horns I am!
I'm burning with the
desire to go all out
and kick your butt
in a one-on-one duel!
[SETH]
I meant that literally.
Look down, you're on fire.
Huh?
Ah!
Oh, no. What a blunder!
Think I left my
medicine in there.
Uh! Thank goodness. It's safe.
That a combat drug?
You Inquisitors seem
to like those.
Well, those merchant
baron techno-chemists
know what they're doing.
Now, as a matter of principle,
I only take their
anti-fantasia brew, myself.
I'm none too fond of
their strength enhancer.
Too many side-effects,
and too easy to get hooked.
Just look at what
it did to Konrad.
You look the same to me.
Trying to hide your weakness
with a blend of drugs and lies.
[SANTORI]
Hm?
[laughs]
I swear by my toasted beard!
I've met a whole heap of
obvious crazies in my life,
but none who sounded as ridicu--
Well done! You went and forced
me to use my left arm!
It's been ages since anyone's
been strong enough
to make me do that in a fight!
O Patrem Inquisitor,
bringer of miracles.
May your grandeur
be made manifest!
So this heathen can
be brought to heel.
Know what this calls for?
An old-fashioned
roundhouse kick!
[SANTORI laughs]
[SETH yells]
[SOLDIER B]
Careful, he's strong.
[SOLDIER C]
He can't take all of us at once.
I won't fall, not without
taking you lot with me.
[humming]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[SOLDIERS scream]
Wait, I know that suit well.
The armor of Pen
Draig, I'm certain!
[GUEN]
So this is the current queen?
[ARTO] It's heartbreaking
to see her brought so low.
[LANDLAKE] Tis unforgivable.
Let us take our vengeance!
[ANCESTOR B]
No objections!
[ANCESTOR C]
Nor from me!
[ARTO]
Good. Let's begin!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[ARTO]
Like wheat before the scythe.
[LANDLAKE] Twas quite knightly,
if I may say so myself.
[GUEN]
A stroke well-cut!
I-I feared the great
Merlin had forsaken us,
but if you're here,
he mustn't have!
[ARTO] You fought like
a true hero, my lord.
Wounded though you were.
[LANDLAKE] Fear not, we shall
carry the queen to safety.
[BRANGOIRE] Yes.
Your presence is proof enough!
I was wrong to doubt him.
Merlin was watching
over us all this time!
[ANCESTOR B]
Of course he was!
[ANCESTOR C]
Without fail!
[GUEN]
Do not doubt it for a moment!
[BRANGOIRE]
I won't. Never again!
[DOC]
Have we done enough yet?
Let's go somewhere safe!
[BRANGOIRE] Hm? I believe
I've heard that voice before.
Uh-huh! I know you.
We met when you tried
to bash Ocoho's head in
with that hammer!
So, the little boy I met
out in the field?
You're the one inside
of that armor?
[ANCESTOR A]
Along with me.
[ANCESTOR B]
And me!
[ANCESTOR C]
[DOC] As you can tell,
I've made a few friends.
Countless knights have tried
to harness that armor.
Some have even tried to do it
with the aid of memory stones.
How'd you succeed
where they failed?
I was just lookin' for a place
to hide down in the archi--
Actually, it's not important.
Let's get the queen outta here.
Hm? What was that?
I broke somethin'.
Uh! Ah! What's goin' on here?
[LANDLAKE] It seems these
soldiers were petrified.
[ARTO]
Tis an unnatural demise.
[GUEN] What black art
could've done this to them?
Somebody help me. I'm lost.
[ARTO] How strange. What's a
child doing on the battlefield?
[GUEN]
That poor thing.
[LANDLAKE]
Come here. We'll help you.
Hang on! I don't trust this kid!
[ARTO] You'd have us leave the
poor boy to fend for himself?
Is that the same
kid from before?
Hey! Don't let him get
anywhere near you!
That boy's a Thaumaturge!
I call on you,
Patrem Inquisitor,
noble bringer of miracles.
May the sound of
your truth ring out
and silence these sinners
till the end of time.
[ARTO]
Fall back!
[DOC screams]
[LANDLAKE]
Twas too close for comfort.
He's extremely powerful!
Anything that enters
that circle of his
will be turned into stone!
That's how I lost my leg!
Don't let his looks fool you,
he's a Thaumaturge, I tell you!
[ARTO] Hmm... How best
to deal with this?
I've got a great idea!
Let's run away!
If we run as fast as we can,
he'll wear himself
out by chasin' us,
and then we can run
even farther away!
[ARTO]
Out of the question!
[LANDLAKE]
A true knight flees from no foe!
[DOC]
Oh, come on!
[ANCESTOR B] Leave this
cheeky rascal to me.
[ANCESTOR C]
And me!
[DOC]
No, don't do this!
[LANDLAKE]
For the queen!
[ARTO] Forsooth, the boy
hath a fearsome power.
[BRANGOIRE]
He can even petrify Fantasia.
[DOC] That's that! We tried
our best and failed.
Let's go!
[ARTO]
Nay!
[LANDLAKE]
By Merlin.
[GUEN]
We have found a worthy opponent!
That's easy for you to say!
You're already rocks,
ya got nothin' to lose!
[ANCESTOR C]
Aye! Let's attack!
[DOC]
Would a true knight hit a kid?
[ARTO]
Hm? Surely not.
[GUEN]
Twould demean our honor.
[LANDLAKE] But our brothers
lay slain before him!
[ARTO]
Well said!
We've no choice
but to strike him down!
Now! To battle!
[DOC]
No, no, no, no!
Stop charging in,
you crazy nitwits!
[ARTO] His defenses look
to be impregnable.
I'm glad you're finally
accepting that.
Now swallow your pride
and give up!
[LANDLAKE]
By Merlin, no!
[GUEN]
We shall not retreat!
Why? This isn't fair!
[GUEN yells]
[DOC]
I'm trapped in a kid's body
in the middle of a battlefield
fightin' a friggin' Thaumaturge!
If he doesn't kill me,
I'll die of stress.
All of these problems'll
bury me alive!
[DOC]
Hm?
Stop! I've got an idea.
For real this time!
[ARTO]
Nay, we must press on!
[LANDLAKE]
We refuse!
[DOC] Okay, fine!
Ya leave me no choice!
[ARTO] Have you put us
in your mouth, boy?
That's right, and if you
don't do what I say,
I'll start chewin'!
[ANCESTOR C]
How vile!
[LANDLAKE]
Desist, I beg you!
[DOC grunts]
[ANCESTOR C] Uh! He
swallowed Lord Arto whole!
[DOC]
It's your fault for jostlin' me.
[GUEN] I can scarce believe it.
Thou art a villain!
[LANDLAKE]
What a repugnant sanction.
[ARTO]
Ugh! It reeks of coffee in here!
[LANDLAKE]
By Merlin.
[GUEN]
My deepest condolences.
All right, now listen to me!
Stop takin' turns attackin'
him with different spells!
That's nothin' but
a waste of time!
[GUEN] If we can't get close
or use magic, what can we do?
[DOC] I want ya to use magic,
but together this time.
You're gonna make the biggest
wave of Fantasia you can--
all at the same time!
[LANDLAKE]
Then form it into a spell?
[DOC]
Just release some Fantasia!
[GUEN]
That would be futile.
[ANCESTOR B]
I oppose it!
[ANCESTOR C]
I'm opposed as well!
[LANDLAKE] It's time
we staged a mutiny! Hm?
[ANCESTOR B]
Lord Landlake?
[GUEN] Did you just swallow
a second great lord?
That's right, and if
ya don't shape up,
you're all gonna join 'em!
[ANCESTORS yell]
[GUEN]
Consider us persuaded, child.
We shall give your plan
our best effort.
[DOC] You should've
done it earlier. Hurry up!
[ANCESTORS]
Right!
[DOUSSANT]
Mordred's gone rogue?
Fools! Stop him at once!
We can't without
hurting him, my lord.
The boy's obviously
lost his mind.
If he can't be spared,
then cut him down!
Kill him! Kill him!
Before he ruins everything
I've worked for!
More blood on the deck?
That's fine wood,
and it cost me a
fortune to acquire.
It's worth more than any
of your lives, understand?
Mordred!
Snap-to like the puppet you are
and clean up this mess at once!
What a worthless failure.
Ah! You hateful creature.
[OCOHO] You called your
own son a puppet.
Said this deck was worth
more than his life.
With a dad like you,
Mordred had no chance!
[DOUSSANT]
Enough.
Kill that wretched girl
and my son along with her!
[OCOHO yells]
[LISELOTTE]
You sorcerers are tainted.
By choice or not,
you cause humanity
nothing but pain and fear!
They only fear us
'cause you Inquisitors
tell 'em they should!
The fact is that you people
need to be controlled!
Why'd you ditch the witch's hat?
Was it something I said?
Don't test me!
Who are you?
I know you're not the
girl I fought before.
I'm proof that she
won't be controlled.
Pulsar!
[SETH]
He projected both arms.
If I can't get him moving,
I'll be in big trouble.
[laughs]
[SANTORI]
In a sense,
I'm here to offer
a helping hand.
I bet you Inquisitors think
you're doing us a favor,
but the infected don't
want your help!
We're not animals to be caged!
[SANTORI]
You say you're not beasts,
but you certainly look like them
as you squirm around trying
to get away from us.
You should see
yourself right now.
The harder you fight, the closer
your natural savagery comes
to taking control of you.
[SANTORI laughs]
[SETH]
He's right.
I have to finish this quickly...
before I lose control again.
[SETH]
Titan Punch!
[SANTORI grunts]
[laughs] Not bad.
[laughing]
Were you hoping that I'd
punch my own lights out?
Well, hey, between you and me,
your trick almost worked.
But if you wanna win now,
you'll have to do a lot
more than just dodge.
[SETH]
Fine, how 'bout this?
Diabal! Let's take him out!
Right!
Oh, yeah! Your antics
never fail to entertain me!
You really are amazing!
The battles we've fought have
given me no end of delight.
Every time I think
I understand you,
ya hit me with another surprise!
Not good.
Ow! That really hurt.
Gee. That's gonna
smart for a while.
I guess I went overboard.
Oh, come on! Don't tell
me that finished you!
Ya should've dodged
my face easy!
Am I about to be disappointed
twice in one day?
[yells]
Your illusions are weak.
And furthermore,
I know how they work!
[DIABAL]
He crushed the stone.
Seth.
Whoo! That was a
pretty fun tussle.
It was a bit shorter than
I've grown accustomed to,
but we've still got some time.
Now get back up on your feet
so I can knock you down again.
Stand and fight!
Do it for your friends,
or for freedom,
or for the sheer thrill of it!
[SANTORI]
There's no way you're finished.
I'm sure you've got
more fight in you.
[growls]
[SANTORI] You may look goofy
with your tiny horns,
but you're strong.
I respect your abilities.
There are many sorcerers,
but none of them can come
close to matching your vitality.
That's why I hoped you'd escape
us back in Rumble Town.
If I didn't have a sorcerer like
you to chase around Pharenos,
then I would be bored
out of my mind!
Hunting sorcerers is good sport,
plus you people need
to be controlled.
Most people live in fear of you.
They'd breathe much more freely
if you were all put in chains.
And as a Thaumaturge
of the Inquisition,
it's my duty to protect people.
Help them feel safe.
[SETH]
Do you think you sound noble
as you repeat the lies
you've been told?
You Inquisitors don't want
people to feel safe.
It's their fear that
gives you power.
Hurry up and kill them!
We'll do the same
with any other slaves
who refuse to do
as they're told!
This ends now.
We're offering your kind
a proper place in this world.
Why can't you see that?
Why can't you let us choose
what to do for ourselves?
We don't have any interest
in becoming slaves!
Oh, please! What're you
getting mad at us for?
It's the Nemeses that made
you less than human,
we're just making do
with what's left.
[SETH]
You think we're less than human?
And don't try to act like
having magic's improved you.
I've attained a power that
makes you look weak,
and I did it without becoming
a monstrous hybrid.
The pinnacle of humanity
is standing right here.
If you disagree, then lift
your head and say so.
Unless you're ready
to become a slave.
Well? Are ya gonna give me
the fight I want or not?
[SETH]
You're the real slave.
What are you mumbling?
[SETH] And I'd break
your chains if I could,
but they're in your
heart and your mind.
And you put them on!
What? How?
[gasps]
Gysoni!
[SETH] You can weigh us
down with shackles,
or toss us into cages,
but sooner or later...
we'll break free of you!
Funny thing about the infected.
We're all survivors!
You could never understand
what that means.
[SETH] But whether you
accept us or not,
we are human!
[SETH yelling]
You've got me in rapture, kid.
Somehow, I knew that you'd
be the one to give me
the fight I've always
yearned for!
I can't tell you how
grateful I am
to have finally met a monster
who can best me in battle!
I'm not your damn monster.
Just a pissed off human!
[SANTORI screams]
I wish you the best, truly!
You've fulfilled my wildest
dreams, and more!
By my beard I swear,
this is my finest day!
[NARRATOR] Shortly after
mighty Santori's defeat,
Ullmina deploys a
Harmonizium in the forest
and activates her dread miracle.
As fallen soldiers rise
to fight again,
the device rips
Fantasia from the air.
Myr loses all hope.
Sorrow turns to rage and
a primal howl is heard.
Next time on Radiant ,
"I Can't Hear Your Voice."