Cheep!
Oh crap!
I totally forgot about
that little chick!
Looks like we're cutting
straight to the carnage, huh?
It's your move, Tomoki.
Whoa! Why the
hell is it my move?
Maybe it's not, but we got do
something, and quick!
What's the plan?
If we don't stop this thing,
Sorami City won't be
worth a cluck.
Master?
Damn it all!
Fine!
If I gotta bust out
the big guns here,
then that's what I'm gonna do!
Yes, Master.
I'm ready!
We're gonna choke that chicken!
It's time to transform!
♪ opening song ♪
Hold on!
Why am I the one transforming?
You were born for
this moment, Sohara!
I believe in you!
All right, Tomoki.
If this is my destiny,
then so be it!
Pervert!
I am Daedalus.
Mother of the Angeloids.
I graced my creations
with vast potential.
That is their blessing
and burden alike.
Type Epsilon.
Chaos.
She fell into
his clutches,
and her soul was
twisted accordingly.
Luckily, Tomoki repurposed her,
just as he did the others.
Now they reside on Earth,
living out their days in
circumstances that
belie their strengths.
Type Delta, Astraea.
The master of
hand-to-hand combat.
Type Beta, Nymph.
The master of
electronic warfare.
And the mightiest and
deadliest of all the Angeloids,
type Alpha,
my darling Ikaros.
Unlike the other Angeloids
with which we have
filled the Synapse, I created
my daughters to be warriors.
I granted them
the ability to feel.
A double-edged sword
the others do not possess.
But like the others,
they do not sleep.
I denied them sleep because
there is a sweetness
to be had in living
the moments of one's life.
I did not want them
to dream their days away.
But now, I realize that,
for all my good intentions,
I may have doomed my
children to a fate most cruel.
I'm Hiyori Kazane,
a high school student.
I live in a sleepy town
tucked away up in the mountains.
It's a darling little
place called Sorami,
population seven
thousand, give or take.
There's not much in the
way of excitement here,
but that's why I love it.
Two years ago, my parents passed
away at about the same time.
Ever since then, I've earned
my keep tending to the
produce at a local
farm before school.
And there he is, Tomoki Sakurai.
He takes this road to
school every morning with
Sohara Mitsuki,
his childhood friend.
I really love working out here,
but each time they walk by,
I wanna vanish.
I mean, I get so grimy.
If he ever saw me like this, I
think I'd die of embarrassment.
But he never seems to
notice me, so I guess I'm safe.
Oh goodness!
If I don't hurry up and finish,
I'm going to be late
for school again!
I sorta depend on Tomoki.
When he walks by in the morning,
I know it's time to change
into my school clothes
and get moving.
So, how'd you do?
Not that I could ever tell him.
He'd probably think I was weird.
You are such a slacker!
I think I could
look at Tomoki all day.
Except, for being
the same grade and all,
we only have one class
together-- Home Ec.
It was my favorite,
even before I noticed him.
I was busy cleaning
veggies one day,
when suddenly he
just dropped into my life.
Aw, balls.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
I should've been watching.
Whoa!
Those green peas
look delicious, huh!
Sorry 'bout launching
'em everywhere.
Y'know, if you
weren't such a spaz,
this wouldn't have happened.
He's clumsy.
Uh, who're you?
I'm Hiyori.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm glad we got
this chance to meet,
even though it took
him running into you.
What?
No, it's fine.
Really.
Check it out, Sohara.
You ever see green
peas look this tasty?
Oh, no kidding!
They look so plump!
Did you grow these, Hiyori?
You can, hang onto that one!
If you want!
Yeah?
For real?
'Cause, you know--
I think--I think those peas
are happy they're going
to be eaten by
someone who
really appreciates them!
Huh?
Forget I said that!
I don't know if
they're happy or not.
Well, I'm pretty happy
about it, so there's that.
Thanks again!
See ya 'round!
He-- he complimented
my vegetables.
No one had ever
done that before.
The wind is good today.
Although I'm not exactly happy
with the direction it's blowing.
But it won't be a
problem for takeoff!
Don't do it!
You're insane!
You'll die!
Hello there, Ms. President.
Good morning.
Um, is someone gonna
jump off the roof?
Take a look.
Sugata?
Shouldn't you be
trying to stop him?
I could ask him to come
down but he won't listen.
I'll worry about
it after he falls.
Could you be more irresponsible?
I mean, you're student
council president,
you gotta do something!
If you're talking
about insurance,
I already bought
a whole lot of it.
Several million worth of
life insurance to be exact.
Wow, that's a lot.
Don't you stand there,
acting all impressed.
Come on, Prez.
Aren't you two like
childhood friends or something?
Shouldn't you be showing
the tiniest bit of
consideration?
Are you suggesting
I'm not worried
about him in the slightest?
No, that's not--
Are you suggesting
I believe it might
not be such a bad thing
to watch my dear friend
plummet to his death with
a big smile spread across my
face as the cherry blossoms
bloom in the background?
I didn't say that.
And are you suggesting
I'm even considering
the remote possibility
that after I've made
my claim on the insurance, I'll
travel the world on the finest
luxury cruise
liner while I mourn
my friend's untimely passing?
Are you?
What do you think?
Are you sure you
want that answer?
Uh, no.
He jumped.
Be careful!
So, you wanna head back?
Hang on, Tomo.
What about your dream?
I am so not talking to that guy!
What are you talking about?
Tomo's just being stupid.
He wants to ask
Sugata some questions.
We heard he's in
the know regarding
"out there" kinds of things.
You'd be right about that.
He's creepy,
perverted beyond belief,
weird beyond
comprehension,
and without a
doubt the freakiest
four-eyed guy I know of,
but he's dependable for
what you need.
Dependably nuts!
Well, who the hell
else are we gonna ask?
I mean you refuse to
go see a professional.
I just want to live
in peace and quiet!
Fine then.
Have it your way, jackass.
Tomoki and Sohara always seem to
have so much fun
when they're together.
Hey, Hiyori!
You don't know what we're
doing in gym today, do you?
No idea.
It wasn't too long
after that when
things started getting
a little strange.
There was this one
rumor going around school
that a girl with wings
had randomly shown up.
Sohara!
Would you at least hear me out?
What are you doing?
Don't follow me, Ikaros!
C'mere!
What?
This month I've got
four projects that I--
That very night there
was a story on the news
about people all
around the world spotting a
mysterious meteor
shower of girls' panties.
I guess they must have
been flying off the shelves,
too, 'cause when I went
to buy more the next day,
there were barely any left.
Hold up!
It's just meat and potatoes.
Huh?
That voice, it's Tomoki.
And I think I taste sugar.
It doesn't make any difference.
Meat and potatoes are the basic
ingredients of curry, right?
No, I'm pretty
sure that's curry.
Yeah, wasn't that funny, Sohara.
I know.
Sorry!
It's just, ever since
Ikaros showed up,
it seems there's always
something to laugh at.
I guess she didn't do this
to our dinner on purpose.
Pardon.
Master?
I am curious as to what
you were laughing at.
What do you mean?
We're just laughing
to have a good time!
Isn't that reason enough?
I guess that Tomoki joined the
New World Discovery Club.
I'm glad.
It looks like a lot of fun.
Maybe if I joined the club my
life would be a little more fun.
A new girl transferred in after
that summer vacation,
and the boys all went crazy
over how adorable she was.
Whoa, seriously?
That's a lot.
What are these things, Master?
They're not mine.
They're love letters.
Like from boys.
Love letters from boys?
This is just stupid.
Stop it!
Think about the
people who poured
their hearts out
in those letters.
You can't just throw them away!
But that doesn't interest
me in the slightest.
Just read 'em, or at
least take 'em home.
Would it kill you to do that?
Jeez, bug, you're
so annoying sometimes.
So, how did your
morning classes go?
Freaking awful.
How are they doing socially?
Any trouble fitting in?
Judging by the way the
boys are fawning over them,
I'd say they're
adjusting pretty well.
You see?
When did this happen?
The entire school's
talking about the
two cute transfer girls.
Sure didn't take very long
for the news to spread.
This is insane!
Listen up you disgusting bugs!
Keep the chatter down!
I'm trying to watch my soaps!
And now, just like bugs,
watch 'em scatter.
Oh!
Spank us baby, we're bad boys!
Here are those extra apples!
I hope I brought enough!
Thanks!
Y'know, for the
last-minute save,
they've been selling way
better than I thought.
Just glad I could help out.
Wow, look at all the
people here this year!
There's cotton candy!
Oh, and takoyaki
and yakisoba too!
All you ever yap about is food.
So?
What's it to you?
If you keep eating
like this you'll get fat.
Just kidding!
Forget I said anything!
Hey Nymph.
You want one?
No way!
Yo Ikaros!
Let me know if you want
anything, I'll buy it for you!
Alright.
These.
What?
I think one would suffice!
Tomo!
Come check out these
other booths with me!
Be right there!
What's all this?
What is a festival exactly?
I believe a festival
is an event that the
entire town can
enjoy together as one.
Mikako?
That's why we, the Satsukitane
family, have hired a
pro to oversee a night of fun
and danger in the woods.
Our hope is that it will
unite the entire town.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
The rules are simple.
We will play a game of
survival using these cork guns.
The last person standing will
win a truly fantastic prize!
A fantastic prize, huh?
Ten million yen in
cold, hard cash.
Hey Nymph, are you
getting cold feet?
Just not interested.
Not in the slightest.
Okay, fellow neighbors,
are you ready?
Then let's get crazy
and shoot the
living hell out of each other!
May the survival game begin!
What do I do?
I was just standing there,
and they handed me this!
Well, well.
So you're actually taking
a break for once.
Yeah.
I was here, anyway,
so I figured I'd let myself
have a bit of fun before
I head back home.
I really admire your
work-ethic, you know that?
I'm just doing my part.
Honestly...
I enjoy your
salt-of-the-earth gumption.
You're a good catch.
You just have to give boys
the chance to get to know you.
Boys like, oh-- say-- Tomoki?
You are just too adorable!
Now go and terrorize your
neighbors like a good girl.
It's not exactly Cupid's
bow and arrow,
but if you shoot
Tomoki in the heart,
I betcha he'll notice you!
Sh-shoot Tomoki
in the heart with this?
I guess Mikako's right, though.
If I shoot him with
a cork, he'll notice me.
At least right then.
I'll do my very best!
Now that's the spirit!
Have fun out there!
Raise some epic welts!
To the victor go
the spoils, honey.
My very best wasn't so hot.
The first person I
stumbled across took me out,
so I never did find Tomoki.
Turns out, everyone
really liked the
candy apples that night,
so Mikako ordered a bunch
of them for the
Cultural Fair, too.
Hey look!
It's time for the
Cultural Fair again.
Am I supposed
to know what that is?
It's something we do at the
private high school in town.
All the different classes
and clubs set up booths.
They put on plays and concerts,
ya know, stuff like that.
Oh.
Master, will you be taking
part in the fair, too?
No, it's a pain in my ass.
Only way I would is if
my class forced me to join.
Way I see it,
I'm not in any clubs so
why should I even bother?
I've been waiting
for you, Tomoki.
We have a plan in the
New World Discovery Club.
Look... We're currently
recruiting skilled pilots.
Screw you!
Don't say that.
You should be honored to
even be considered given how
many members we
have in the running.
Now wait just a damn minute!
When the hell did I
ever join your club, huh?
Well, according to the
student council registry,
we have you down as
a card-carrying member.
Conspiracy!
Someone's out to
get me, I swear!
Wow.
These poor, depraved children.
What a pathetic
excuse for an event.
Oh look, Yoshitsune, they put a
banner up for the cultural fair.
I'm surprised they
can afford that,
let alone pay for the fair.
Do they even know the
meaning of the world "culture"?
It's those face-turds
from the Academy!
They think highly of themselves.
They don't seem very friendly.
Time to watch the sparks fly.
My goodness, Tsukino.
Are you seeing this?
They're actually making
flowers out of cardboard.
It begs the question;
can these cave-people
demonstrate culture when they've
barely discovered
how to make fire?
Stupid yuppies!
If you're so great,
what the hell are you
doin' for the
festival this year?
Let me guess, something big
and flashy with no character?
We have something
in the works, yes.
We will be performing
the classics.
That's the dumbest
idea I've ever heard!
Did you hear that Sohara?
They're gonna put on some
lame-ass boring play,
as if anybody would
want to see that crap!
Why not just play a tape of
Shakespeare while you're at it?
You friggin' rich idiots!
He wasn't referring
to the theatre.
You are such a moron, Tomo.
He was talking about
doing classical music.
The poor cretin's never
heard of classical music?
It almost makes me
feel bad for him.
Come on everyone,
we'd better be on our way.
I'm afraid this lack
of civility may infect us.
Way to go, genius!
That big mouth of yours just put
an even bigger target
on our backs!
Damn!
They just declared war, Sohara.
Now we have to
do something for the fair.
Yeah, I saw that.
Any bright ideas?
Well, we could-- I got nothing.
Attention everyone.
The Prez has arrived.
As your Class President,
I cannot allow this
injustice to stand
another moment.
If they're going to
attack us with music,
then we shall
retaliate with music.
What do you say?
Wanna start a band?
A band, like with instruments?
Come on!
Hurry it up, slowpoke!
They've already started!
Sorry!
I hope we can still
find seats together.
The festival's
music competition's
been the talk of the
town for weeks!
We now give you the full
orchestra of Sorami Academy.
Please, give them
a round of applause.
If they don't realize how
poor and underprivileged
they are after this,
they never will.
This is what true
culture is all about.
Man, that was really good.
I don't know how
we're gonna top that.
Oh man.
You know what this means?
The academy's going to
make fun of us again.
Hey, don't count us out yet!
We have Tomoki's band this year.
They're bound to be good!
I didn't realize Tomoki
was so popular at school!
Our next act is a performance
by the members
of the New World Discovery Club.
Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki!
Thank you, thank you very much!
I can hear the voices.
They're calling me!
The stage is my life
and now the time
has come to show you
all how to rock!
This song is called
"My Tingly Nips"!
♪ I perk up
whenever you're near! ♪
♪ And it feels so good! ♪
♪ You perk up when
you see me, too! ♪
♪ Like I knew you would! ♪
♪ Is it something God gave
us as part of his plan? ♪
♪ I know it's hard, but
don't be afraid anymore! ♪
♪ Baby touch my tingly nips
with your gentle hands. ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
Tomoki, you know
damn well that's
not the song we decided on.
I know, I know!
But it was totally worth it!
Wow, that was an easy win.
Thanks so much for
the comedy, ingrates.
How fitting for these feeble
peasants to play a novelty song.
Unfortunately for them it
has led to our victory.
Now that they've seen what
happens, perhaps they should
shut up like the good
future laborers they are.
Sorry 'bout that.
That was a little bonus,
for the fans.
I love you guys!
What's this?
Can you believe the
nerve of this guy?
Now it's time for the real song.
Here ya go.
This one's called
"I'm Falling Down."
♪ Falling down. ♪
♪ Aaahhhh ahhh. ♪
♪ Blue. ♪
♪ The sky up above. ♪
♪ I wanna soar forever
with you, my love. ♪
♪ (You, my love) ♪
♪ But you are the
one who can fly. ♪
♪ I've fallen and
I'm stranded here. ♪
♪ It's because my-- my
wings are heavy from the ♪
♪ shame of all the ways
that I've hurt you. ♪
♪ Don't run away.
(Don't run away) ♪
♪ Don't leave me here
to cry in vain. ♪
♪ So gimme a sign,
I'll try and I'll try. ♪
♪ I know I can fly! ♪
♪ To be with you! ♪
♪ Who is the sky that
hangs above? ♪
♪ Clouds are like tears
I cry in my love. ♪
♪ I'm gonna spread
these broken wings ♪
♪ and soar back
into your heart. ♪
♪ 'Cause that's where
I'm falling all over again. ♪
♪ Falling for you. ♪
♪ (Falling down) ♪
That was amazing!
Tomoki is so talented!
What?
You don't know how to smile?
I was thinking maybe you
could give her some advice.
I guess there's
no point in asking
someone who
never smiles himself.
Come on.
Let's go, Alpha.
Oh!
I'm sorry!
I was just admiring
how straight your rows are.
I didn't know we had
any garden plots on campus.
And those aren't easy to grow!
What's your secret,
if you don't mind my asking?
Over the course of my admittedly
brief agricultural career,
I've discovered that
vegetables really flourish...
So this is Eichiro Sugata,
the head of the New
World Discovery Club.
Everybody says he's a weirdo,
but he seems to know
his way around a garden,
so he can't be that bad, right?
Besides, he's
friends with Tomoki.
I'm sure he's just fine.
Wow!
They've got so many
stands this year!
Hey, Nymph!
We got this for ya.
You did?
I promised I'd
get you something.
Remember, I said if
my booth turned a profit,
I'd buy you anything you
liked, and you like these.
Oh.
That's right.
I saw, you had your
eye on these earlier.
Plus you've been
kicking ass in the band,
so I wanted to
give you something.
Thanks for being awesome.
Thanks?
Is that what
I'm supposed to say?
Or--
Thank you, Master.
Thank you so much.
Humans are no more than bugs,
simple creatures
who we crush underfoot.
Even if he is nice to me,
he's still beneath me.
It's so good.
Isn't it?
Way to go, Tomo!
You made her cry!
You little devil.
So wicked.
N--No, I--!
What are you doing?
Look Nymph.
The sky here is so vast.
Huh? What does
that even mean?
--I don't get it.
--What the heck, Tomo?
Did you do something
to upset Nymph again?
Don't look at me!
I didn't do anything.
Why are you all looking at me?
It wasn't my fault!
This candy apple is awful!
What are you talking about?
You just said it was good!
Oh shut up!
Mikako came out here today
while they were setting up.
Said something about
getting an event ready.
Well, I'll be...
You grew all
this yourself, dearie?
Uh-huh!
Tell you what.
I'll take one of
them daikon radishes.
Great!
Thank you very much, ma'am!
Huh?
He's groping her!
Oh, the humanity!
Pants is groping Makiko!
I-- I give up!
No way!
He's already in a tight spot!
The man's face is being crushed!
This does not look good!
Flying body press!
She's reaching--oh!
To catch him mid-air-- Oh!
and performs an
Argentine Backbreaker!
--and here's your candy apple.
I hope you like it!
Thanks a lot!
Nymph is so adorable.
She reminds me of a doll.
She's not the only one.
They're all adorable.
Why would Tomoki notice
me with them around?
I hope he does, though.
I really do.
Man, a lot happened
in one night,
but the festival
was fun, wasn't it?
Are you sure that's
all you wanted?
I said I'd get you anything,
and I do keep my promises.
'Cause the last time
you had a candy apple
you said they
were gross tasting.
You remember that?
Course. You cried over
it like a baby.
But I do like them.
Candy apples.
I like them a lot.
Hey Tomoki, aren't you
going to have one, too?
Nah, I already had a bunch of
takoyaki and other junk today.
You don't eat a lot
of sweets, do you?
Not really.
First snow of the year!
Perfect day to
do absolutely nothing.
War is hell!
All students, report to the
P.E. field immediately!
Two teams--boys on one,
girls on the other!
We're going to
duke it out like our
ancestors always did
with snowballs!
Just like that, all of our
classes were cancelled.
Everyone headed outside for the
most epic snowball fight ever!
Your Lordship!
What's it gonna be?
The enemy is at Honnoji!
Ready!
Fire!
So uh-- Could you do me a favor?
Well that depends.
What do you want?
This is paradise.
I haven't relaxed in a hot
spring like this in forever!
Hiyori!
You really called it!
This place is amazing!
I found it recently.
I'm just glad you're
having a good time.
It's gonna eat me!
Why'd I even bother
coming out here, huh?
Look over there.
It's Tomoki, that
pervert from Class C.
He's always getting in
some kind of trouble!
What a pain in the ass!
Oh?
But he seems like
such a fun guy.
Whenever I see him, I just
know it'll be a good day.
I guess-- I, uh-- y'know.
I like him.
I've watched the nature channel!
I know what happens next!
This is why I said
fishing is bullshit, man!
Whenever Tomoki was around.
I just sort of forgot
about everything else.
Yeah.
I couldn't deny it anymore.
I had really fallen for him.
Air!
Uh, what are you
doing down there?
I heard that veggies get
their food from the dirt,
so I figured I'd give it a shot!
Huh?
You know, if you're that hungry
I could just give you
some vegetables.
Yeah?
Like for free?
Score!
These cucumbers are delish!
Whatcha gonna do with
all these veggies, huh?
Well, I was thinking
of giving them to the
animals at school we
keep as class pets.
Mikako's always being so nice
to me, I figured the least
I could do was help
her out with their food.
Cool!
She's my sensei!
It's like an
all-you-can-eat buffet!
What's all the fuss about?
Dude, let's go check it out.
Oh, Astraea, no.
I give it my all, but my
cooking is so plain.
I can't offer these
cookies to Tomoki.
I mean, look at them.
Just look at 'em!
Dig in.
As many as you'd like!
Thanks!
Ikaros?
Care for a cookie?
This smells like tasty!
I'm in heaven!
They're delicious.
I'm so glad.
Hey, I know!
Since you like
watermelons so much,
why don't you have
Hiyori teach you about 'em?
Her melons are radical!
Like for real!
Huh?
You said there was
stuff about growing 'em
that you still
didn't know, right?
Well, this chick is like
the produce whisperer,
so problem solved!
If I can be of use,
I'd love to help.
Change a few things in
your garden and you'll be
growing tons of
watermelons in no time!
Trust me!
Watermelons by the ton?
Yes, please.
I would like that a lot.
Hey!
What's up?
I smelled cookies and
thought I'd check it out!
Uh!
Yeah have a cookie!
Oh no!
I don't have any cookies left!
They're gone!
I'm so sorry!
Hey, it's fine.
I'm sure they were great.
See ya later!
Tomoki looked at me.
He spoke to me.
He even smiled.
From that moment on,
something inside my
heart began to blossom and grow.
Maybe Tomoki and I
could become friends.
Maybe close friends
or even more.
My wish set down
roots in my heart and
it grew little by little as
I watched Tomoki.
I watered it with hope
and he was its sunshine.
Oh, cool.
The actress on Barnyard
Sonata is getting married.
Remind me to
tell Nymph about this.
Sohara, I have a question.
Sure, what is it?
When someone proposes to you,
is marriage what
happens afterwards?
Yep.
Check it out.
After the proposal,
you have a wedding and you
get to wear a beautiful
dress like this one.
Isn't it gorgeous?
A proposal, then a wedding.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Maybe the heat's
making you lightheaded.
I know! We should
go get some ice cream.
That's the best thing to
do when it's hot outside.
Yeah!
Hiyori!
What's up?
Sohara and Ikaros.
Uh, good afternoon.
If you're not busy, we were
about to go get some ice cream.
You wanna come with?
Huh?
Uh yeah.
Thanks.
Y'know, I'm glad
we're finally getting
a chance to hang out for once.
Yeah, I'm glad also.
I've been seeing a
lot of you and
your friends around
town this year.
Honestly?
I'm jealous of how
you all get along!
You've been watching us?
Whenever you're all together,
you have a lot of fun.
Like just the other day,
when you ate curry
in the woods
down by the stream.
You were there?
Aw, how come you
didn't say something?
Because I'm not a member of
the New World Discovery Club.
Makes no difference to me!
In fact, I betcha Tomoki
would've hollered for you
to come over and
fill up a plate.
You-- you really think so?
Course I do.
Tomo's always
being nice like that.
I mean, that's basically
what he did with Astraea.
Man, that girl can
really pack it away.
I-- I knew that it was
a long-shot, but--
If I wanted him to know
I existed, I had to be brave.
So the very next day, I marched
right up to that club room.
I was nervous,
but I had to do it.
Uh.
Hi!
I'd like to join the club,
if that's okay.
There's Tomoki.
He's right in front of me.
The boy who turns each
new day into an adventure.
He's looking at me.
He sees me!
From now, until the day I die.
I'm never gonna
forget that girl.
My name is Hiyori Kazane,
and uh, I'd really
like to join the club!
Hold up.
You're not talking about
this club, are you?
Yeah, I really dunno
if you wanna do that.
As they say,
the more the merrier.
Isn't that right?
You did want more
members, as I recall.
Fair enough.
You...
Why are you here on Earth?
Just think of all the
fun we'll have with
the newest addition
to our money!
Huh?
Money?
Size matters, my little friend.
Just one more name
on the official club roster,
and Sugata's operating
budget will skyrocket.
Hiyori!
You've made the right decision.
Stop sparkling!
Whatever.
Welcome to the club.
Me, I got a whole
lotta nothing to do.
There's one tiny detail
I forgot to mention.
Huh?
To receive the extra
money for the club,
we need to prove
that it's big enough.
Sometimes, a club
will take money
that it's not entitled to,
and it's my duty as
president to destroy them.
So unless you long for death,
you're going to show up
to the New World Discovery
club every single day.
Comprende?
We've got plenty more of it,
so please drink up.
Thank you very much.
Man, I'm starving!
Hey Alpha, where are the snacks?
I will go bring them out.
Now then, I'd like to bring
Hiyori up to speed
as to what the New World
Discovery Club is all about.
Man, you guys are
harshing my mellow!
The bulk of our club activities
concern the discovery of a
hitherto-unknown land floating
in the skies above Sorami.
Damn it!
Taking over my house for the
club meeting is totally balls!
And this is just the beginning!
If I don't do something,
I'm gonna have to deal with
these chuckleheads
after school every day.
If I try to skip out they'll
just follow me home and bogart
what little peace and
quiet I have left in life!
Think, Tomoki!
Think!
Those are the basics.
That'll do for now.
Hiyori.
Uh, yeah?
So, I've been dying to ask.
Are you going out with anyone?
No I-- I'm not seeing anyone.
No one at all.
Aw, you're so innocent!
Not like that pervert,
who drools over
half-naked bimbos next to us.
Real classy.
What the hell, Sohara?
How come you're singling me out?
He's the grand
master of perversion!
Why don't you get up
in his grill for once?
Pay no mind to his lies.
Like the Holy Grail of yore,
the New World
can only be grasped by those
who are pure in heart and body!
Sure, it's an afterschool club,
but for me this
is what I live for!
As the leader of
this intrepid club,
I comport myself as
a bastion of purity!
Thank you, don't get up.
Son of a--!
What's so great
about purity, huh?
Wait!
Purity!
That's it!
Psst!
Hiyori!
Over here!
C'mere--I gotta talk to ya!
'Bout time you took the old
entrance exam, dontcha think?
I don't know what that means.
You heard Sugata
rambling on just now.
If you wanna be in the
New World Discovery Club,
you gotta have a
pure heart an' junk.
That's why I've devised
a super-scientific test
to gauge just how pure you are!
But how do you test for
something like that?
With these!
Panties are a purity test?
Huh?
Of course they are!
What, are you blind, woman?
Forged from the whitest
cotton, these panties
represent all that is good
and unsullied in the world!
That's why the pure of heart
have no problem doing this!
And this!
So, if you wanna join the club,
you gotta show these
panties just how
much you love 'em!
Never gonna happen!
Any second now, she's
gonna drop those drawers
and run screaming
for the hills.
There's no way she'll wanna be
a part of the club after this!
Soon as she's gone,
we don't get extra money--
and I can go back to doing
whatever the hell I want!
Huh?
What?
Are you outta
your friggin' mind?
Am I a member of the club yet?
Not just no!
Hell no!
Aw.
C'mon!
That was just part one!
Ahem.
Oof.
Care to tell me what
that was all about?
Master said to keep you here,
while he and Hiyori
are up in his bedroom.
What?
Tomoki.
You dog!
And he's off.
Rub-a-dub-dub,
it's chicks in the tub!
What could be more pure?
What the hell?
A white school swimsuit!
Can you handle the purity?
What the hell?
The usual.
And one for the dame.
Right away, sir.
White sushi rice on
a white dish topped
with edible white panties!
This meal is
the ultimate in purity.
Thus, it is your final test.
Bon appetite!
No way can a girl do this!
Bye-bye, Hiyori!
Psyche!
I can't make
this girl eat panties!
I mean, look at her!
She's all decent and crap!
Man, and she was
gonna do it, too!
What kind of a monster am I?
Surely you didn't
sneak out of the
club meeting to feed
this poor girl panties.
You are so dead,
you little pervert.
Would ya look at the time?
I'm gonna call it a day.
Hold on, Tomoki.
We thought of some other pure
white things you might enjoy.
Like a white soap riceball!
And a white lightbulb!
And an all-white outfit
that'll rock your world!
Yeah!
Now that's what
I'm talking about!
"Rock my world." Oh.
Purity punch!
Purity's bullshit!
Now that we've
dealt with his antics,
let's make this
official, shall we?
Welcome to the New World
Discovery Club, Hiyori.
Cheers, everyone!
Sorry about Tomo--he
is such a jackass.
That's okay, really!
So, tell me--what's
your favorite snack?
Keep it coming!
All the mackerel!
I'll eat every last one you got!
Here.
Thanks a lot.
I guess I'll be
needing these, huh?
May I?
May I ask for your
assistance sometime,
in growing watermelons?
Yeah, I would be happy to help!
Master has returned.
Hey again.
Purity can suck it.
Never mind that little perv.
Purity's fine.
Hey, Hiyori!
Do you watch "Barnyard Sonata"?
If you wanna go the
extra mile, we are looking
for someone to fill the role
of Pretty, Sugata's assistant.
You gotta try this mackerel!
Uh, okay.
Purity can suck it.
I'll get you down!
It's okay, Tomoki.
You're safe now.
Isn't she just
the sweetest thing?
Seems the new girl
upped the ante.
Yes, I daresay you're right.
Sorry 'bout dinner
running so late.
No, I-- I had fun.
Thanks for walking me home.
Hey.
So, I gotta ask.
What possessed you to join
our club in the first place?
Seriously.
I got roped into it.
What's the appeal?
I guess I just thought that--
that it might be interesting.
You know?
I mean, actually it's
kind of romantic!
There's a whole other world out
there, just waiting to be found.
Just like two people
find each other.
Uh, Tomoki?
Is it okay if we maybe
take a little detour?
This is my favorite spot
in the whole world.
Even if I feel
really sad, I look out at
the town from
here and I feel better.
I love Sorami.
I never want to
live anywhere else.
And even if I do someday, it'll
always be home in my heart.
I've been up here
before, you know.
Actually, I kinda come
up here a bunch.
I guess I always figured
nobody else knew about it.
Wow, that's neat.
Then we've been looking out from
the same spot all this time.
You're not the only
one who loves Sorami.
I've thought it was
a great place ever
since I was a little kid.
Especially up here.
Tomoki?
Um, are you okay?
Oh!
Sorry.
Just thinking back.
There's a whole
new world out there,
hiding above us in
the night sky.
Just waiting for someone
to fly up and say hello.
That's amazing.
I'd really like to see it
for myself someday.
And that was that.
Hiyori came to the club meetings
every day, like clockwork.
Meanwhile.
I kept trying to
get her to quit.
Yeah, she was nice and all, but
I wanted my afternoons back!
I'm taking a picture!
Smile, everybody!
No way is she doing this one!
Hey!
No fair!
Tomoki, it's time
to admit defeat.
What?
Unless, of course,
these incessant challenges
serve another purpose,
and you're actually
showing her that you care.
What, for her?
As if!
You're having the time of
your life up here, aren'tcha?
Uh-huh!
I really am!
I've always wanted to soar
through the air, and now I am!
It's a dream come true!
The weather today is
just perfect, isn't it?
They dug up another old
farm to build something.
I'm a little sad about
the town changing,
even though I know
it's all for the best.
The book mentions "pruning,"
but I am not sure
that I understand it.
If you really want your
watermelon to be top-notch,
you get rid of the others
that aren't doing as well
so that the good one gets
more nutrients out of the soil.
Whenever I prune,
I end up feeling kinda guilty.
I know I have to do it,
but it's not the bad ones'
fault they didn't work out.
So you understand
why I feel that way?
Oh, I'm so glad!
Sure they're plants, but I
betcha they have feelings, too!
Poor little watermelon,
all alone!
Sorry about that.
When it comes to gardening,
I get a little worked up.
Y'know, Ikaros?
Getting to sit here and
talk to you like this--
it's really nice.
Kinda feel like I'm dreaming.
Finally got those club
pics developed, huh?
That blonde with the
cans looks just like me!
That's 'cause it's you, silly!
Those two aren't dating
on the sly, are they?
I mean, they are
together a bunch.
I spotted him buying
her lipstick the other day.
What's that about?
Get a load of this!
I finally figured out what's
going on with those two!
Tomoki and Hiyori are,
like, totally going together!
If those two really are an item,
there's something
fishy about it.
Huh?
I don't know what passes
for pretty among
the girls down here on Earth,
but I'm gonna assume
Hiyori is seen as
a pretty good catch.
I caught a big fish once!
Mikako was just telling me.
On last year's "Who would you
like as a girlfriend?" survey,
Hiyori ranked number one.
Why would a girl like
that fall for a perv like him?
Maybe it's true love!
Or maybe he's got
some kind of dirt on her.
Something like--
Sure hope these cheesecake
shots never get out!
So, hey, whatcha doing tonight?
It could happen.
So, what's for dinner tonight?
I plan to make
meat and potatoes.
Hey, sounds good to me!
I forget, have you ever had
Sohara's meat and potatoes?
I have not.
She puts pickled plums
in it--it's really weird!
Hand 'em over!
I, uh-- what?
I can't believe you took
dirty pictures of Hiyori!
Yeah, and now you're
blackmailing her?
They told me you have
cheesecake, so gimmie!
Huh?
I don't know what
you're talking about!
You were real chummy going
home from school together,
weren't you?
I was gonna go
shopping--she said
she wanted to
come along, that's all!
I totally saw you buy her some
lipstick, so don't even lie!
Shows what you know,
smarty-pants!
I bought that lipstick
for me, 'cause I wanted
to turn my nipples
into eyeballs!
But I needed a girl with
me, so the makeup
counter lady wouldn't
chase me off again.
And you gave her a meat bun!
How could you?
Nah, see, 'cause it's--Wait!
You're just pissed off 'cause
I didn't give it to you, huh?
Where're the dirty pictures?
Cough 'em up!
I'm really not following!
What do I do now?
If anybody looks over here,
they're gonna see me!
Just tell me what I did
to make you mad this time!
Oh yeah, like you don't know!
Hiyori and you are
a thing, aren't you?
Huh?
Oh, Hiyori.
Hello.
You really thought that
Tomoki and I were a thing?
Hold on.
Does this mean that--?
--that you guys
aren't going out?
Wait, you three were
shouting at me 'cause of that?
Sorry.
Our mistake!
Guess we kinda
jumped to conclusions.
No, this is terrible!
He's looking at me in
my grubby farming clothes!
Now he's never gonna like me!
Man, these green peas
are making me hungry.
They look awesome.
But the stuff you grow always
looks awesome, doesn't it?
Remember when you
gave me some of the
peas you were cooking
in Home Ec that time?
Those were easily
the best I've ever tasted.
Hey, I've got an idea!
How 'bout you toss some
of those into dinner, Ikaros?
You'll join us--right, Hiyori?
Oh, maybe I shouldn't
take your peas after all.
If the others come over, we'll
only get like one pea each.
I can do it.
I can tell Tomoki
how I feel about him.
Tomoki?
I just want to let you know
that-- that I love you.
She loves me?
What do I do with that?
Think, dude!
I don't know jack about love!
I mean, I love boobs,
but that's different, right?
She doesn't love me
like I love boobs.
What if she does?
Or what if she just
plain loves boobs?
That reminds me of
a dream I had once!
Wait, that's it!
I'm just dreaming all this crap!
Ikaros!
What is it, Master?
I want you to hit me!
Huh?
I gotta be sure I'm
not dreaming all of this!
So I want you to hit me as
hard as you can, dammit!
All right.
Uh, you're doing it wrong.
Guess I'm awake.
Good times.
Huh?
Hey, Alpha, you don't think he's
going to see Hiyori, do you?
He made no mention of that.
Yeah, why would he?
Seriously, though,
Tomoki shouldn't
spend time around Hiyori.
It isn't safe.
She's not supposed
to be in Sorami.
You know that.
And you know what's at risk.
How is Chaos's
recovery coming along?
Stabilizing her is
a difficult process.
It is requiring many
subtle adjustments.
Ah, yes.
I almost forgot.
A girl by the name
of Hiyori Kazane
joined our club
the other day.
Which is odd, since I
remember seeing a girl who
looks just like her in a
capsule here in Synapse.
Care to tell me
what this is about?
Not free to tell me?
Ah.
May I ask you another
question, in that case?
Recently, I thought back, to the
day I first laid eyes on Tomoki.
There's no reason
I should have forgotten
such a day, but without
realizing it, I had.
Does the Synapse have
something to do with this?
I wish I could give
you an answer.
You deserve to know.
You don't say.
Where are you going?
Since answers aren't
forthcoming, I'll find my own.
I'm so sorry.
It's gotta be tough on you, huh?
My just saying that.
I'll wait at the overlook,
all tomorrow night.
I hope you'll come up
and give me my answer.
One way or the other!
Least I can give her these.
Nymph?
No!
This is bad!
The earthbound Hiyori--
--is dead!
She's coming!
It's beginning!
Our Hiyori will be erased!
Everything about
her will be gone!
What?
My memories of Hiyori,
they're vanishing!
I have to get inside the dome
before I forget her entirely!
That's my only chance!
This girl.
Who is she?
Look who's snooping
around again!
You're not getting away
this time, you little bastard!
Hold your fire.
He's a guest.
You must be their former master.
I saw how you ran for
this building a moment ago.
That look of panic on your
face was absolutely priceless.
You must be thinking
of someone else.
How soon they forget.
Not that you had any
choice in the matter.
It's all been purged.
What's been purged?
Guess!
Go ahead!
I've outmaneuvered you in ways
you can't even comprehend.
Hey, you two.
What's up?
I came out here to meet up
with Hiyori like she wanted,
but I haven't seen any sign of--
My head.
It's killing me!
Master, Hiyori is--
Hiyori said that she can't
make it up here today.
She'll be coming
back tomorrow, though.
And she said that
she really hopes
you'll swing by 'cause
she'll be waiting.
Huh?
That's weird.
Well, let's go.
No point in waiting
around here, right?
My head's killing me, anyway.
Why did you lie to Master?
'Cause I care about him,
and the truth would hurt.
It is, by all accounts,
a night like any other.
Foggy, yes, but not unduly
so for the time of year.
Nymph...
You told me that it would
hurt him, but I still think
that maybe we should tell
Master the truth about Hiyori.
After all, she was his friend.
Wa-- for reals?
Did you hit your head
or something?
If we tell Tomoki
the truth about Hiyori,
he's going to figure
out the rest of it.
He's not a total idiot!
I know you did it for him,
but he told me once
that lying was a
very bad thing to do.
I think he would not want me to.
So your master
ordered you not to lie?
Even if he didn't call it
an order, that's what it was.
But he's not my master, is he?
I'm unclaimed.
Nymph, I--
Okay, okay.
Even though he's just gonna
forget everything
about her tomorrow anyhow,
I guess I shouldn't
have lied to him like that.
Now you've got
me feeling all guilty!
Tell you what--I'll go and make
it up to him right away, okay?
What the hell do you
think you're doing, Nymph?
What's wrong, Tomoki?
I thought you liked this outfit.
Like it?
You damn near gave
me a heart attack!
Come to bed.
Huh?
I came here to snuggle up.
So come back.
Whatever you say.
Hey, Tomoki.
That's my name.
Remember, how you
told me that one
time that you would
become my master?
I'm ready to imprint,
if you meant it.
Don't do it.
At the end of the
day, the only one you
should have to
answer to is yourself.
That goes for
you and Ikaros both.
And even Astraea.
What kind of life
would you have if you
spend it following
someone's orders?
You deserve way better.
Freedom is pretty bitchin',
and I want you to
have that, you know?
Having masters isn't all bad.
Life's complicated when you have
to figure stuff out on your own.
Look, it's not like I want you
to be my master
because I'm an Angeloid.
It's 'cause--
'Cause I think you're amazing!
Tomoki, I think that I'm in l--
Tomoki?
What the hell!
Tomoki!
That's the pain of
memories being zapped
out of your mind by the Synapse.
By tomorrow, Hiyori will
never have existed!
Huh?
What'd you say her name was?
It's Hiyori!
Hiyori Kazane!
Geez.
All that porn's rotted
your brain, Tomo.
We don't have any new members.
I think I'd have noticed.
I've never heard that name.
And believe me,
I have dirt on everybody.
Are you sure that this
wasn't just another dream?
Oh, come on!
She bumped us into a higher
bracket for the club budget.
You practically drooled on her!
Wait, I got it!
Remember when
you took all of those
pictures of us doing like,
club stuff, Sohara?
Yeah--the album's
right over here.
What the hell?
She's gone.
Something fishy's going on here!
Uh, Tomo, where're you going?
I'm awake!
No, please!
Send me back into the dream!
I beg of you!
You wanted your dream,
and you had it.
Mewling for do-overs after
the fact is just ungrateful.
Your little charade
has come to a messy end.
You've been purged
from their memories.
You're nothing to them.
Well, it appears
you're not entirely
forgettable to one
of those insects.
Tomoki, of course.
You can see him again, you know.
So long as you don't mind
making certain sacrifices.
Hiyori, where are you?
Damn it all, Hiyori!
Where did you go?
Look at you.
You knew.
You knew that she was real.
Master, we thought that--
No-- you can't!
Tell the truth right now!
She wanted to
tell you the truth!
Don't blame her--blame me!
It's just once a human learns
the truth about this stuff,
their mind can't
be wiped anymore!
That's why you were
never supposed to find out!
About what?
Just say it!
Hiyori never really
did exist in this world,
but she's not the only one!
--Tomoki!
--Master!
How is it possible Master's
memories were not erased?
I don't know.
But the longer he retains
them, the worse off
he's going to be
in the long run.
What's that even mean?
Tomoki remembers all
the stuff about Hiyori
that the Synapse took
from everyone else.
After a while, the strain of
it's gonna break him down.
It's "when," not "if".
How come a dummy
like him can't forget?
I forget all the time.
There must be
something we can do.
What the--?
What did you pick up?
I dunno, but whatever
it is, it can't be good!
You're kidding me!
Oh, thank goodness.
I made it back
to my beloved home.
Sorami City!
It's Hiyori.
Hiyori!
She's become an Angeloid?
Engaging: Kairos.
Oh, no!
You monster!
How could you bring
her back as an Angeloid?
Are you insane?
Why should you care either way?
She was a Synapsian, but she
turned her back on the glory of
this world in
favor of that insect
and that grimy little dung-heap.
So I sent her back, as the
destroyer of all she holds dear.
I've returned, Tomoki.
What are you waiting for, Zeta?
It's time to make
your wish come true!
Hiyori!
Stop!
Crap-cakes!
Hey, Ikaros?
Stop attacking us, Hiyori!
We're your friends!
The lights are on,
but Hiyori ain't home!
Nicely done, Zeta!
Now annihilate every
human you can find!
Where are you
hiding, Tomoki dear?
We have to stop her, and quick!
The direction she's going'll
take her straight into town!
We asked nice!
So what's plan B?
We'll have to take Hiyori out.
A master's orders are absolute--
we know that better than anyone!
If we let her go, she's won't
stop 'til she kills Tomoki!
Yeah, but--!
Don't worry, Astraea.
I'll do it.
She's not sporting
any serious armor.
One blast of my Paradise
Song should be enough!
I'm sorry.
No--you mustn't!
What the hell?
If I let you destroy Hiyori,
it will sadden Master!
Tomoki has no idea what
we're up against, Alpha!
If we act now,
no one else gets hurt!
I'm not sure.
Why'd they make me so stupid?
It's like "one plus one"
all over again!
Move.
I have to do this.
Take her out.
One shout and it's done.
Quick and painless!
Don't do it, Nymph.
The one you're
gonna hurt is you.
I can't do it.
Hiyori!
I swear I'm gonna help you!
Damn you, Tomoki Sakurai!
What are you waiting for, Zeta?
Destroy him!
Aegis-L!
Tomoki!
Over here!
Sugata?
Keep her busy long as you can!
Ikaros!
What happens
if we attack all that
mechanical junk
floating behind her?
I mean, if we can
bust up all that crap,
do you think Hiyori'll
go back to normal?
I don't know,
but it's worth a try.
I'll hack her system
to immobilize her.
While I'm doing that, I need you
two to destroy that machinery!
Okay?
Go!
All right!
Now!
Hack initiated!
Nymph!
What's wrong?
Hiyori executed a counter-hack!
You rejects are so
easy to outsmart.
I equipped this one with
top-notch electronics
for just such an occasion.
Chrysaor!
You leave her alone!
Kairos.
I just got rewound!
Nymph!
So, you like to get cute with
time-manipulation, do ya?
Hacking field, maximum range!
Now, Delta!
Try rushing her again--
and this time, floor it!
Okay!
Alpha!
Fire!
If I must!
Take that stuff!
Oh, no.
It's no use!
She's an Angeloid now,
and there's no undoing that!
She chose this fate, forsaking
her very nature for the chance
to see Tomoki Sakurai again--
and now she'll kill him!
My master!
That sound.
It can't be!
That's her countdown timer!
If you tamper with time and
space too much all at once,
the temporal-spatio paradox
releases a massive energy burst!
That's smart-people talk for
"She's gonna blow
up the town," huh?
It is!
There's gotta be something
you can do to stop her!
Can't you just break
off the ticking part?
Maybe I can bypass her
command to self-destruct.
But if I fail--
Then what'll happen?
Hiyori and everything around
her will be annihilated.
I know I have to do it,
but it's not the bad ones'
fault they didn't work out.
Extend Aegis around
myself and Hiyori!
Of course!
Aegis is strong enough
to contain the blast!
The explosion won't
even reach Sorami!
Good thinking, Ikaros!
Huh?
How come she's inside it?
Get out of there, Alpha!
If she goes off while
you're both inside,
you'll be vaporized, too!
You and I are the same.
We were given powers
we never asked for,
and ordered to hurt people.
Our reactors ache
for the same person.
Hiyori.
So you understand
why I feel that way?
Sure, they're plants but I
betcha they have feelings, too!
Poor little watermelon,
all alone!
You do not have to be alone.
I will stay with you...
To the very end.
Forgive me, Master.
I cannot let
Hiyori perish alone.
Ikaros!
I ordered you not to die!
Tomoki?
Man, is he dumb!
Godspeed, Tomoki.
It's all up to you now.
Master!
Aegis power mode!
Dummy.
Why the heck were you just
going to throw in the towel?
I'm gonna save Hiyori
and the rest of us,
so don't go wussing out.
Right.
Hiyori, I know Sorami's
been changing lately,
but don't let it bum you out.
There.
You see?
That spot you love so much.
That we both love so much.
It's just fine.
Oh, right.
I forgot.
Here.
These belong to you.
They look good on you.
I've always thought so.
I--
I remember you.
Huh?
Tomoki.
Hiyori!
It's time for you to go.
If you stay any
longer the explosion
is going to destroy you both!
I know you can hear me, Ikaros.
And you were right.
We are the same.
We don't want--
--the boy we love to die.
I can't stop the process now.
But there's one
final thing I can do!
Commencing program hack.
Lowering Aegis.
Master!
Tomoki.
Thank you.
I'm sure you've long since
forgotten but the reason
I came to love Sorami so
much was because of you.
Here...
I found these!
Thanks a lot.
Now that you've got 'em back,
you don't have to cry.
Hey, come here!
Wanna see something cool?
Heh.
It's neat, huh!
Yeah!
Isn't it pretty?
Uh-huh!
Those bells in
your hair look pretty, too.
Hey, you wanna play with me?
It's way more fun than
being all alone, right?
Yeah!
At that moment, I decided
to live in your town forever.
To find my bliss
in an endless dream.
We didn't have
much time together,
but getting to know all
of you, especially you,
Tomoki, brought me
such happiness.
Hiyori!
Thank you for being my friends.
I had the time of my life.
And Tomoki,
I really do love you.
Hiyori!
Don't go!
I swore to her, Ikaros.
I swore to Hiyori
that I was gonna save her!
And now she's gone!
I know that I'll
never forget her.
You were the first girl who
ever told me that she loves me.
Thank you, Hiyori.
♪ closing song ♪