[TOHKA]
I'm so hungry, Shido.
Shido, gotta potty.
Darling. Darling.
Um, Shido, what's going on?
[overlapping chatter]
Kaguya, isn't that my candy
you're about to eat?
[chuckles]
Come on, don't sweat it.
If stupid little things
like that actually get to you,
then you might as well be
as old as you look right now.
Agree, it's much nicer to share
and you have plenty.
--Hey!
--[overlapping chatter]
Everybody, listen!
I need all of you to calm down
right this second!
[chatter continues]
[SHIDO groans]
Natsumi, what have
you done to me?
[REINE] You've got a lot
on your hands today, Shin.
[SHIDO]
Reine! Thank goodness.
I appreciate you coming.
It's hard to keep up
with all of them on my own.
Sure. I'm sorry for
having to leave them here.
House guests are a lot of work.
Hmm.
[YUZURU]
Ponder. Do I want a cookie?
[giggling]
[SHIDO]
Um...
So what happened to Natsumi?
[REINE] I deployed
observation devices to find her,
but no luck yet.
I'll let you know
if that changes.
All right, thanks.
It's strange, why would
Natsumi do something like this?
I've asked myself that.
It could have been
some sort of last resort.
Emergency measures
she used to escape.
The Spirits no longer
have the ability to fight.
It could be this is
actually a warning
not to go looking for her.
Of course, she could also
just have a grudge.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[WESTCOTT]
As far as we've confirmed,
there are six Spirits
gathered around Shido Itsuka.
So as soon as
you're feeling ready,
I'll have you make
your move, Ellen.
Right. Who shall I
start with, sir?
Ah, yes, this is the Spirit from
the AST's report the other day.
She hasn't been confirmed
lost as of yet,
and seeing as she turned up
in Tengu City,
she's our primary target.
[NARRATOR] A grand opening
amidst the chaos.
"My Own Personal Zoo."
Now, Shido's fathering skills
are put to the test.
--No way.
--Seriously?
That's so lame.
[SHIDO]
Well, at least it looks like
Natsumi spared everyone here.
--Morning, Itsuka.
--Uh...
--Hey.
--You okay?
Oh, yeah. I'm super good.
[TAMAE]
Excuse me, Itsuka?
[SHIDO]
Yes?
You have some guests here
to see you
but I'm not sure if, uh...
What guests?
Yeah, about that...
--See? I knew he was here.
--[gasps]
Hey, what did I say?
You were to stay in the office
and behave until I came back.
Well, well, what have we here?
Bother. You're blocking the way.
[KOTORI]
Shido, do you copy?
It's an emergency!
Tohka and the others
have disappeared from the house!
Yeah, that's because
they came here.
Hey, Shido, would you please
do us all a favor
and have a talk
with these teachers
and set 'em straight?
They refuse to believe
we're really Yamai.
[YUZURU] Sigh. These adults
don't have enough imagination
not to judge on appearances.
Why are you here
in the first place
when I asked you all
to wait at home?
It's a school day
so we didn't think
you actually meant it.
Yes, I know it's a school day.
--Hey, cutie.
--Wanna tell us your name?
Uh...
I'm Chiyogami Itsuka.
And I'm so happy to meet
some of Papa's friends.
--Hold up. "Papa"?
--No, no! Don't misunderstand!
These, uh... These girls are,
uh, my relative's kids!
I'm just looking after them.
Heh! You know,
"Papa," it's only, like...
I-It's their nickname for me.
Oh, now I get it.
It's funny, but knowing you,
I almost believed
the kids could be yours.
Well, that's terrifying.
Come on, everyone,
let's get you back home now.
Oh, weird. What was that?
[TOHKA screams]
Tohka, wha... [grunts]
What... What have you
done to me, Shido?!
Bastard! What the hell
did you just do?
--Uh...
--You're the worst!
That is so lame!
But I didn't do anything!
Wait, the light. Don't tell
me...
[grunting]
Come on, time to go...
Ugh! You coward!
--[KOTORI] Shido!
--What, Kotori?
--[KOTORI] The house!
--The house?
Hold on, what about the house?
Of course. Why not?
She's really done it this time.
[laughs]
Now, I wonder what I can do
to mess with these fools next.
You seriously
don't intend to react
after what Westcott did to us?
I'm not sure what to tell you.
The incident did make
one thing clear.
Westcott's on
a whole different level.
We were foolish to think
we could stand against him.
Maybe so.
But he still deserves
every single ounce
of retribution
we can serve him.
Retribution, huh?
What exactly
is it you have in mind?
Right now, as far as we know,
Westcott is in Japan, correct?
Yeah, and what of it?
I'm home, girls.
[TOHKA]
Shido. Shido!
[groaning]
Why is there so much cake?
[TOHKA]
Shido, wake up.
Are you okay? Hey, Shido?
[yawns]
These past few days have been
one thing after another.
Not again.
--Hmm?
--[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasping]
[gasps]
Eh? What's with this outfit?
[GIRLS whining]
Huh? Aw, come on!
[REINE]
Shin, do you copy?
Reine, help!
Natsumi has gone
all out this time.
Although, thanks to that,
I've been able to
track down her location.
Wow, for real?
Well, where is she?
[NATSUMI laughing]
Oh, man, this is so great.
You look ridiculous,
and it only serves you right
for embarrassing me.
What will I do next?
Shoot, who's coming this way?
Some friend of Shido's maybe?
Too bad. I guarantee you won't
be catching me this time.
[groans]
You know, I never
would have expected
such a violent greeting
from one of Shido's friends.
Sorry to disappoint,
but I wouldn't exactly
call myself a friend of his.
Oh, you must be
with the AST, then.
Not that I could
possibly care any less.
What do you want?
It's simple.
I've come here to hunt you down.
Heh. You might
find that difficult.
Well, we'll only know
for sure once I try, right?
[NATSUMI chuckles]
Where do you get
all this confidence?
From them?
[ELLEN]
No.
Well, no difference to me.
Ha!
You witch!
Haniel.
[ALL gasp]
My, my, my.
Thank you so very much
for this abundance of goodies.
Now, to return the favor!
Look what she did.
Is that Ellen?
[gasps]
I must say, I think
you're cuter this way.
[gasps]
So, exactly
what do you plan to do?
This fight
isn't over yet, Natsumi.
I'm still powerful enough
to kill you.
[NATSUMI groans]
[groans]
[gasps]
No. No! Why?!
Ugh. How could
this be happening?!
[gasping]
No! No! Please, no!
I must have missed your vitals,
but I'm afraid
your power's falling rapidly.
Now then...
Please, someone help me...
Anybody...
Please, I'm begging...
Don't you worry,
it's gonna be over soon.
[gasps]
Huh?
[grunting]
Yah!
Are you all right?
Yeah. But why are you...?
--Ah!
--Now, Gabriel, let's Rondo.
Pathetic. Look how weak you are.
Sympathy. It is a shame.
Why are they helping?
--[SHIDO] Natsumi!
--[gasps]
Wait, what are you doing?
Are you okay?
We'll patch you up in no time.
And why would I let that happen?
Hey, Ellen, think twice on this.
Your friends are
in short supply.
And you're outnumbered.
Doesn't bother me.
Truth be told, those girls were
never much help from the start.
Is that right? Well, then...
Miku!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Kotori, do it now.
[SHIDO] Hang in there
a little bit longer, Natsumi.
Shido. Why help me?
[grunts]
[ELLEN sighs]
[ELLEN] A useful pawn
could come in handy.
[MURDOCH]
Mr. Simpson.
Tell us, at this very moment,
do you know
how many DEM satellites
are in geosynchronous orbit?
--No.
--The answer is 23.
And out of those, I'm told
eight are awaiting disposal.
[SIMPSONS]
Hmm?
Hold on, back up a minute.
Where are you going with this?
I mean, what does it
have to do with...
Huh?
Murdoch, no. You can't mean--
[MURDOCH] Yes. I do.
We should dispose of them.
We can gather up
all those junk satellites
and drop them on Tengu City.
[cell phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
Yes?
Punishment? You mean mine?
What are you saying?
[ORIGAMI]
All this is to "punish" me?
What the hell is going on?
[cell phone ringing]
[WESTCOTT chuckles]
[KOTORI]
That sure was quick, Shido.
[SHIDO]
is it true? Natsumi woke up?
Just a little bit ago.
[SHIDO]
Natsumi...
[KOTORI] She took enough
damage from Ellen
that we don't have to worry
about her using her Angel.
But still,
you should be careful.
[SHIDO]
Right.
Hey, what happened to your face?
Uh, well, like I said,
be on your guard.
Oh. Wow. Okay.
Yo, Natsumi.
What the...
Would you cut that out, please?
[NATSUMI]
Don't look at me!
[SHIDO]
Come on, what's the matter?
[NATSUMI]
Why did you rescue me?
I don't get it.
[SHIDO]
Why?
Well, because Ellen
obviously had you beat.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Look, I mean, I went
around impersonating you
and then I erased
all of your friends!
I don't know what to tell you.
When we came across you
in that condition,
of course we were gonna help.
[gasps]
Stop lying to me!
Don't think you can fool me
with your smooth talk, Shido!
That's not even close
to my intention.
[NATSUMI growls]
Natsumi, listen.
What is it?
Tell me this.
Why'd you do this stuff?
Why did you erase my friends?
Why do you think?
Because you saw the real me
and know my secret, obviously.
And that secret is?
Well, that this is...
This is my true form.
Hold on just a sec.
Why does me seeing you
in this form
set you off so badly?
How can you ask that?!
Please. How could I not be
mortified looking like this?
No one should ever
see me this way.
Natsumi, listen I--
The first time you and I met,
you said I was pretty,
do you even remember that?
Would you have had
the same reaction
if I had looked like this?
The answer is no, you would've
ignored me if I'd spoken to you.
I really don't think--
Yes, you would have!
Everyone's exactly the same.
When I look like this,
nobody ever pays attention to me
and it's the worst thing ever!
In any case, that's why
I'll never be able
to forgive anyone who has
seen me in my true form.
And that includes you,
so get lost!
[sighs]
Can I ask you something?
What is it that's
so disappointing
about the current you?
[gasps]
[screaming]
Yeah, that's kinda why
I told you to be careful.
How is Natsumi's mental state?
Well, it's been
incredibly unstable.
Sealing her is out of
the question at this point.
Figured as much.
She's miserable.
She just doesn't have
any confidence
in her current state.
Obviously.
Otherwise, she wouldn't
always be changing herself.
You know, I actually think
the real Natsumi
has a charm of her own.
I just wish there was a way
for her to see it.
She'd rather transform
than to look in the mirror
long enough to see that.
[BOTH]
Transform?
[sniffs]
Uh...
[sighs]
Can I ask you something?
What is it
that's so disappointing
about the current you?
Come on.
Who would be fooled by that?
Once I can finally
use Haniel again,
I am so done with this.
[NATSUMI]
Uh. What's this?
--[SHIDO] Captured!
--[NATSUMI screaming]
[NATSUMI]
Let me go!
[SHIDO]
Okay, we're good.
[grunts]
Hey, where am I?
Hi, there.
This is a pop-up beauty salon.
You're in Salon de Miku.
Huh? What's going on?
What do you mean?
Miku just explained.
It's a day of beauty.
[NATSUMI]
No, nothing's ever that simple.
I bet you're really doing this
to make me believe
you think I'm pretty while you
laugh at me behind my back! Ah!
Whatever. Would you
lie down already?
You're really holding up
the schedule.
[NATSUMI]
Schedule...?
Natsumi,
for the rest of the day,
our goal is to transform you
in a way that makes you happy.
If we succeed,
then that's our win.
If you don't see a difference,
then we lose.
And you can do as you please.
What exactly do you mean,
"do as I please"?
Let's see.
What if we let you run away
to wherever you might wanna go?
[NATSUMI]
Hmm.
--Fine. Deal.
--[BOTH chuckle]
[SHIDO] It's about time
for you to learn.
A girl can transform
even without an Angel
if she wants to.
We're gonna start
by oiling up your skin.
[NATSUMI groans]
How could this help?
[MIKU] Now, we're just going to
warm you with some hot stones.
How does that feel?
[NATSUMI]
I mean, it's all right.
This will help any swelling
in your legs, too.
[NATSUMI]
Oh. Really?
[MIKU chuckles]
Doesn't that feel nice?
You really ought to be
taking better care
of your gorgeous skin.
Why should it matter
what I do when...
I mean, it won't change.
[snoring]
[gasps]
Somebody had a little nap.
Move along to the next room now.
--[chuckles]
--[NATSUMI] Sure, okay.
You can sit back
and trust our mad skills.
[NATSUMI]
Eh...?
[KOTORI] Clothes are important
for your confidence.
Come. Follow us.
Step right on in.
Oh, that looks awesome.
Yeah, it's really cute.
[KOTORI]
Try on this one next.
That brings us here
to the final room
of your transformative journey.
Hi, my name's Shiori.
Makeup's my thing
and you're getting a makeover.
[NATSUMI] I just... I don't
think it'll change anything.
Do you honestly believe that?
Of course I do.
[SHIORI]
What if I told you...
[SHIDO] ...underneath here,
I'm really a man?!
[NATSUMI]
Weirdo.
[gasps, groans]
[KOTORI]
Poor thing, look how hurt he is.
[MIKU]
I wouldn't worry about it.
Besides, if you ignore
the silly part
about Darling being a guy,
he's still a girl.
Yeah, anyways,
I'll be utilizing these skills--
the same technique you couldn't
see through just now--
to prove that I can
transform you.
[NATSUMI sighs]
Do whatever you want.
[GIRLS giggling]
[SHIORI voice]
I'm all finished.
How is it, Natsumi?
I don't know, is this me?
[NATSUMI] Wait. What the
heck is going on here?
And why does everyone
look so happy?
I did those terrible things.
If this is me, that means
I just lost because...
I might... I think I'm...
[screaming]
Hey. Natsumi, watch out!
[thuds]
[NATSUMI groans]
[overlapping chatter]
[cell phone buzzing]
[ORIGAMI]
Who is this?
My name is Ellen Mathers.
I'm trying to reach
Master Sergeant Tobiichi--
is this she?
Ellen Mathers, huh?
What is this about?
I like that.
Let's get straight to the point.
Master Sergeant,
I want you to consider
coming to work for me.
[ORIGAMI]
No way.
I'm not aiding any organization
that would bring harm to Shido.
[line beeps]
[MAN]
There she is! That way!
[ELLEN] Uh-oh. Looks like
you're in quite the predicament.
Five years ago,
there was a fire in Tengu City.
If you do decide
to work for me,
you would be given access
to information on that event.
You want to avenge
your parents, don't you?
I'll do it.
[thudding]
[gasps]
What the...
You're a smart girl.
Welcome to DEM Industries.