[NARRATOR]
One girl transforms,
now bright, kind, and cheerful.
But someone else changes, too,
into something dark,
fierce, and cruel.
[gasps]
I-I'm sorry.
Did it happen again?
Did what happen?
[ORIGAMI]
Nothing. My apologies.
Lately, I've been having
these blackout moments
where my mind goes blank.
It goes blank, as in...
[chuckles]
It's nothing to worry about.
I'm probably anemic
or something.
Anyway, I guess
you read your note?
The one I left on your desk?
Uh... Yeah.
Are you still free
on Saturday?
[ORIGAMI] Oh, sorry, there's
somewhere I have to be!
Kurumi, you can
stop hiding now.
[KURUMI giggles]
You know me too well.
Crazy, huh?
This really does make it
a lot harder to understand
why Origami turned inverse,
wouldn't you say?
Yeah.
But this Origami was able to
accept the death of her parents.
I don't get it.
What happened?
[KOTORI] Let me see
if I've got this straight.
So you're saying
this world exists
'cause you used Kurumi's
time travel powers.
And you did that
to save Origami's parents
who should've died
five years ago.
And the purpose
of that was to avoid
what she would've turned into.
Yeah, that's the gist of it.
[KOTORI]
Hmm. Fascinating.
I think now I get why you've
been acting a little strange
for the last day or so.
It's true.
Maybe Origami shouldn't have
inversed in this world.
Regardless, she definitely did.
And now we have Devil
to contend with.
I've analyzed her encounter
with Shin on the roof.
He's telling the truth,
believe it or not.
Origami Tobiichi
hasn't the faintest idea
that she's a Spirit.
But how can that be?
[REINE] Shin, you managed
to change the course of time.
So you and Kurumi
are the only ones
with actual knowledge
of the original world, correct?
Yeah.
And as for Kurumi,
considering her own powers
are what brought this about,
she's kind of an exception.
So if I had to guess
from everything you've told me,
in order to retain knowledge
of the original world,
two conditions must be met:
Being directly hit
by Kurumi's Yod Bet,
and having Spirit powers
flowing through one's self.
With both conditions met,
it's possible that one's memory
of the original world
may be recovered.
[KOTORI] We know that Origami
was shot by Kurumi's Yod Bet,
so the first condition was met.
Separately, she's ended up
living a peaceful life,
thanks to Shido's interference.
[KOTORI] But then, when
Phantom showed up on the scene
and gave her Spirit powers...
[SHIDO] She finally
remembered everything.
[REINE] However,
as a self-defense mechanism,
her memories were split in two.
Essentially, there's one Origami
who lives in peace,
and then there's
the Spirit hunter, Devil.
[SHIDO grunts]
[REINE] So now, as soon as
Origami senses Spirit power,
she loses control
of her mind and memory.
[KOTORI] And then
the Inverse version of her
is awakened.
The theory works and is
consistent with what we know.
The question is,
what can we do about it?
As long as Origami's a Spirit,
there's only one thing
for Ratatoskr to do.
Huh?
Make her fall for me, right?
Correct.
That's how we'll seal
her spirit powers.
You'll need to convince Origami
to go out on a date with you.
Think you can handle that,
lover boy?
Ugh. What now,
is there a problem?
Nothing, it's just...
[KOTORI]
Huh?!
You've already promised to
meet up with her this Saturday?!
So you hit on her before even
knowing that she was a Spirit?
The heck?! Dude.
--[growls]
--[SHIDO] Well, I mean,
it's complicated!
[ORIGAMI whining]
[sighs]
I can't believe
I wrote him a note.
Since when did I become
some kind of
lovesick girlie girl?
[inaudible]
I don't know. Maybe it's...
--[cell phone chimes]
--Huh?
Oh, it's from him.
Okay, gotta reply.
"Yes, thank you, that time
and date will work for me."
Is that too impersonal?
"Dear Itsuka, as I write this,
the winds of autumn fill me
with hope and anticipation.
And the moon sits like
a big egg in the sky
as I wonder
how you're faring tonight."
Who says that?! No one!
[sighs]
[ORIGAMI]
I really appreciate you
inviting me here today, Itsuka.
You okay?
Yeah, my pleasure.
Since we're hanging out,
could we maybe do
first names now?
--Pretty please?
--Oh. Of course we can.
Mm. Sounds good.
That's more like
the Origami I know.
Sorry, too fast?
Guess I'm just anxious
to say your name.
I mean, 'cause it's so pretty.
Thank you.
I've always been glad
my parents picked it for me.
If you like calling me
that so much,
say it as often as you want.
I don't mind at all.
Feel free to call me
Shido, too.
Thanks. I'll work up
the courage soon.
Kill me now. This is unbearable.
[ORIGAMI] So what do you think
we should do today?
Good question.
Here we go.
Your choices, everyone.
[KOTORI]
Mm-hmm, that seems right to me.
I hated to pass up
the first choice,
but going someplace
where they can't talk
is a pretty classic blunder.
Plus, choice number two
is a safe and versatile option.
Even if she isn't into shopping,
they'll have lots of fun.
[KOTORI]
Hmm.
All right, Shido, we're ready.
--Go with--
--[SHIDO] Hold up a sec.
I wanna test out
a different choice.
[MAN]
Oh, yeah!
[ORIGAMI gasps]
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Emotional levels are unstable.
[MIKIMOTO]
Origami Tobiichi is distraught.
Big shocker there!
What are you thinking, Shido?!
Talk your way out of it!
Right. I will.
Sorry about that,
wrong building.
Oh, so that wasn't it. Okay.
Man, I genuinely thought
Origami would go crazy for that.
You never cease to amaze me.
Look, just go with two, okay?
Take the girl shopping.
[SHIDO]
Roger.
Break it gently.
How's her happiness level?
I hope it didn't drop
too drastically.
Yeah, about that...
Her emotions are bouncing
all over the place,
but her happiness actually
seems to be rising.
Are you serious?
[ORIGAMI] Hey, where are we
gonna go shopping?
[SHIDO]
Um, let's see.
[KOTORI]
Your choices, everyone.
[SHIDO]
It's gotta be the third one.
[ALL]
Huh?!
Have you lost your damn mind?!
No way can you take a girl there
on the first date.
Yeah, but Origami
and aphrodisiacs
go together like
peanut butter and jelly.
You know what I'm saying, right?
[KOTORI groaning]
Origami, this way.
Here we are. What do you think?
[whimpering]
I'm so sorry, Itsuka,
but I have to admit,
I don't even know what
most of the stuff in here is.
Yeah, right. Very funny. Uh...
Then what's all that?
Huh?
--[alarm blaring]
--What?! What's going on?!
Why do I have all this?!
I don't understand
what's the matter with me.
What made me pick up
those things?
Don't worry about it.
It's totally my fault
for taking you
to the store
in the first place.
How would you feel
about a new outfit
as my way of apologizing?
--That sound good?
--[ORIGAMI] What?
No, I can't let you do that!
Please don't worry, I got it.
In exchange, all I ask is
that you let me be the first
to see you wearing it.
That's the only payment I need.
Tell me something,
are you kind of a ladies' man?
You're almost too good at this.
No. No, that's not true at all.
[ORIGAMI] Then I guess
I'll take you up on that offer.
And while I'm at it,
I should make sure
it's an outfit
that you'll like a whole lot.
[giggles]
[KOTORI chuckles]
Yo, ladies' man.
She really called you out,
didn't she?
Yeah, not helpful. Shut up.
[KOTORI] Hey, I don't remember
saying it was a bad thing.
[REINE] Shin, Origami just went
into a dressing room
in the back of the store.
Don't lose sight of her.
Right, thanks.
--[ORIGAMI screams]
--Origami!
Are you okay?
[ORIGAMI]
I... What am I doing?
Sorry. I'm coming in!
--[ORIGAMI] No! Please don't!
--[gasping]
[ORIGAMI whimpers]
So, let me ask.
Did you pick this because
you thought for some reason
that I'd be into it?
I don't know!
That's why I freaked out!
I mean, I don't even remember
taking these clothes
off the rack!
I'm sorry... again.
For some reason I'm weird today.
Don't let it bother you.
Nothing you've said
or done has fazed me.
[ORIGAMI]
Mm.
--Thanks for that.
--[device ringing]
Sorry, bathroom break.
I'll be right back.
Sure, go ahead.
[sighs]
Huh?
So sorry to keep you
waiting like that.
[gasps sharply]
[SHIDO]
Hey, whatcha doin'?
[SHIDO chuckles]
No, wait, this isn't whatever
you're thinking right now!
Your spoon fell off the table
so I was just picking it up!
[gasps]
Ah...
I'm so sorry!
[SHIDO chuckles]
It's nothing, don't sweat it.
It'll dry in no time.
--[shutter clicking rapidly]
--Uh...
What are you doing?
[ORIGAMI]
Ah?!
Huh? Why am I...
You have to believe me.
It's like my body's
moving all on its own!
What is going on with me?!
[MINOWA] Origami Tobiichi's
emotional levels
have now stabilized.
[KAWAGOE] Her happiness meter
still remains high.
[KOTORI]
The mood isn't bad, either.
With any luck, we could
wrap this up in one day.
Perhaps.
However, it seems clear
that she remains anxious
about something.
Could just be basic nerves
regarding whether Shin
will accept her or not.
I'm not surprised
after all she did.
I feel like it should only
take one more push, though.
Seriously? So, you mean
you're done with the AST, then?
[ORIGAMI]
Mm.
My anemia and those
blackout moments
are both pretty
solid reasons to quit.
Also, I just don't know anymore.
Is it really
the right thing to do?
Continuing to wipe out Spirits
the way that I have?
[SHIDO gasps]
Forgive me.
I forgot it was a Spirit
that was responsible
for the death
of your brother, too.
You don't have to be
sorry for that.
[ORIGAMI]
Huh?
Listen, I think you're
very smart to question it,
and I completely agree with you.
And to be totally honest,
my brother would say
the same thing.
Oh, my sweet friend,
I'm so sorry.
Thank you for telling me that.
[SHIIZAKI]
Happiness meter climbing.
[MIKIMOTO]
Maximum value has been reached.
[REINE]
Hmm.
That must have been the source
of her earlier anxiety,
so now it seems
she's turned a corner.
Shido, it's looking good.
I'd say it's time for you
to dive in for the kill!
[ORIGAMI]
Ah!
[gasps]
[screaming]
[SHIDO]
Origami!
[grunting]
[SHIDO groans]
Are you all right? You hurt?
[ORIGAMI]
No.
Shido, I'm...
[gasps]
Origami, you okay?
[ORIGAMI]
Spirit.
[alarm blaring]
[REINE]
No. Her Spirit power.
Shido, get outta there!
[SHIDO]
Uh, Origami?
[SHIDO gasps]
[screams]
What was that?
--[alarm blaring]
--[ALL gasp]
Inverse type.
Devil.
[gasps]
What's that?
What am I sensing?
Shiver. My heart is restless.
There. Look!
[SHIDO yelps]
[KOTORI] What are you thinking?!
It's too dangerous!
[SHIDO]
Origami is after me now.
Our only chance to seal her
is to do it while
her armor is incomplete!
[SHIDO groans]
[screams, groans]
[SHIDO] If I run away,
the city will be demolished.
I can't let her.
[SHIDO]
Not again. Never again.
[KOTORI]
Shido, stay back.
[SHIDO]
Yggdrafolium?
[KOTORI] We should be able
to use Fraxinus's main battery
to break her Spirit barrier
for three seconds.
You'll have to use that chance
to get close and seal her--
--[gasps]
--No, Kotori, run!
[SHIDO]
Kotori!
Please, no... Not again...
[SHIDO]
Origami!
[TOHKA yells]
Tohka.
You all right, Shido?
[KAGUYA]
We're here to help.
You guys...
Shido, fill us in,
who the heck is that?
I sense a dreadful Spirit power.
You're right. That's Origami.
The transfer student?
[SHIDO] It's far too dangerous
to fight her.
I should probably
tell you all to run away.
But I am begging you
to help me save her anyway.
--Well, isn't that obvious?
--[SHIDO] Huh?
[TOHKA] After all,
you're the one who saved me.
You're the one
who made my world possible.
So, this time, it's finally
my turn to help you.
Thank you, everyone.
[SHIDO]
Wait for me, Origami.
[ORIGAMI]
Where am I?
Did I lose...
consciousness again?
I thought I was
just with Itsuka.
Huh?
[ORIGAMI]
Are you...
...me?
[ORIGAMI]
I don't get it. What is this?
Oh, my gosh.
Are these... my memories?
[gasps]
[KAGUYA]
We'll distract her, Shido. Go!
Suggestion.
Get out while you can.
[SHIDO]
That's it. Great job, you two!
[BOTH]
We call Gabriel!
Rondo!
And March!
What the heck, Natsumi?
Why do you have to be
such a copycat?!
I've just always
wanted to try that.
[YOSHINON]
Here we go!
[YOSHINON] At this rate, he
can't even get close to her.
[YOSHINO yells]
Shido. You've got
to reach her!
Zadkiel, Shiryon!
Yoshino?
Hah!
Haah!
Now's your chance. Move!
Go save the transfer student!
You guys are the best!
Origami!
[SHIDO groans]
No! Let me in there.
[SHIDO]
Let me in!
Open your heart!
Origami!
You're looking at the one
who killed your mom and dad.
It's not true, that never
happened in this world.
'Cause Itsuka's brother...
[gasps]
No. Itsuka saved them.
And what about
my memories, huh?
Do you think I can ever
take back the truth
that I killed them?
But that's...
Ah...
[whimpers]
[ORIGAMI INVERSE]
I am you and you are me.
And even if the world's remade,
the memories will remain.
Always.
[ORIGAMI sobbing]
[ORIGAMI INVERSE] There's no
hope in the world for me now.
And that means you, too.
Stop, enough!
Please, just stop...
I can't... I can't take this.
[ORIGAMI sobs]
Please... Someone...
Somebody, please help me...
--[SHIDO] Origami!
--[gasps]
Huh?
[SHIDO]
Origami, can you hear me?
Itsuka?
What the...
What is Shido doing here?
[SHIDO] Don't carry this burden
on your own.
Like I told you five years ago,
you're not alone!
I'm always here for you!
All of your sadness
and your hate,
let me carry all of it for you!
If you're lost, I'll find you!
When something happens
and it's too much,
please come to me.
Give it all to me,
everything, it's okay.
I'll take all of it.
Do you hear me? Okay?
Don't let despair
take you over, Origami.
[SHIDO] No matter how
many worlds you try to break,
I'll fight to get to you!
I know you're in despair.
I'll never stop trying
to help you save yourself!
Shido...
My friend...
[SHIDO] Come on,
reach out to me, will ya?
I won't lose you!
Origami!
[ORIGAMI]
I...
Thank you, Shido...
[ORIGAMI]
If you hadn't been here for me,
I would've ended up
doing something else
I'd never be able
to take back.
[ORIGAMI] The fact that
I killed my mom and dad
is never going to
go away for me.
Nor will the sin
of slaying the ones
I did in the original world.
[ORIGAMI]
That will stay with me forever.
Even if... if it's changed
so that it never even happened.
Origami...
You're right.
Unfortunately,
I think that's a burden
you'll always have to bear.
[ORIGAMI gasps]
[sobbing]
[wailing]
[ORIGAMI sniffles]
Listen... I feel like
I need to apologize...
The feelings I've had
towards you
weren't actually love.
I got two feelings confused,
I think.
I felt I could rely on you.
But now I realize
that when I lost my parents,
I had no other choice
but to cling to you.
Well, I'm honored.
But it took bravery to trust me.
So you're saved because of you.
Shido...
[SHIDO]
Oh, yeah.
I've got something of yours,
and I need to give it back.
I held more than tears,
wouldn't you say?
[ORIGAMI sighs]
Shido, do we...
Ah?! Mm.
Good grief, man.
We'll never learn our limits.
Or so I hope.
--[door rattles]
--[gasps]
Good morning, Shido.
Morning, Origami.
[chuckles]
[ORIGAMI] Here. I have something
to wipe your tears with.
Thank you.
[grunts]
[gasping]
Wha...
Origami, what are you doing?!
[SHIDO yells]
[ORIGAMI]
School swimsuit.
It retains moisture well.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, I picked these up
for you, too.
Okay, I'm a little confused.
Because when all that happened,
didn't you say you never
loved me to begin with?
Yeah, which means
our real love story
can start now.
[SHIDO whimpers]
You better stay away from Shido!
--Get off him!
--[SHIDO grunts]
[ORIGAMI chuckles]