[KURUMI]
I have to admit,
I'm pretty impressed
that you were able to find me.
[KURUMI groaning]
[ORIGAMI]
It wasn't exactly my first time
tracking one of you down.
I guess it makes sense
I've gotten better at it.
Yes, but still, you weren't
exactly easy on me, were you?
I didn't kill her.
I held back.
Well, then,
what brings you here now?
I'm gonna assume you haven't
come by for a tea party.
[ORIGAMI] I have an
important question for you.
[KURUMI]
Oh, yeah? Go ahead.
[giggles]
I mean, I can't promise
I'll answer it,
but let's see, shall we?
Zaphkiel is an Angel
who manipulates time, correct?
Also, each and every
one of those 12 dials
has a different kind of power.
So my question is,
of the 12,
does one have a bullet
that'll send someone
to the past?
Just out of curiosity,
what would you say
if there was one?
That I want to borrow
your power.
My, my.
You're actually suggesting that
I use Yod Bet for your sake?
Is that really
what you're asking me?
[ORIGAMI]
Yes.
Well then, here's my answer.
It's unfortunate.
I hate disappointing people,
you know?
You may be blessed
with incredible power,
but it means nothing
if you can't hit me.
Uh-oh. I think I'm being
rather underestimated right now.
Just 'cause
I'm a curious kind of girl,
what exactly would you be doing
with Yod Bet if I had agreed?
Simple.
I want to go
to August third, five years ago.
Five years ago?
Why, though?
I have to go back there.
I have to try and fix it
so that my mom and dad's deaths
never happened.
I'll change history,
if you'll help me.
[KURUMI]
How interesting.
I have to wonder,
what is your plan
if I choose to refuse you?
[ORIGAMI] I'll make sure
you agree, any way I can.
[KURUMI] Hmph! Well, you've gone
and said it now, huh?
Well, whatever.
As a matter of fact,
I was a little nervous
about using the Yod Bet
without having tested it out
on anyone first.
So I guess I can just use you
as my guinea pig,
since you asked so nicely.
[gasps]
Seriously?
[KURUMI]
Now, come to me.
Zaphkiel!
[KURUMI]
Zaphkiel.
Let's try Yod Bet.
[KURUMI]
Go find out for me, little pig.
Prove to me how foolish
it actually is
to try and change the world,
and whether or not
God permits it.
[TOHKA]
Ugh. Shido.
I'm so hungry.
[KAGUYA]
Wait a minute,
you're not going around
giving our kinswoman
the forbidden fruit
before we get a piece, are you?
Complaint.
It would appear that Shido
is unfortunately forgetting
that he is our property,
first and foremost.
Hey! He belongs to me, too,
you know.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll grab you something,
so hang tight, okay?
Do you two want anything?
[SHIDO chuckles]
--[cell phone vibrating]
--Uh?
Is that Yoshino's phone?
[gasps]
Shido. What are you...?
Ah! No. Yoshino, this isn't...
[YOSHINO whimpers]
What's all the ruckus
when I'm tryin' to sleep?
--Gah!
--No, this isn't how it looks.
I swear.
Get off of her,
you filthy pervert!
Crap. Shido!
Gross! I can't believe
you had the guts
to do perverted things
to Yoshino
while I was literally sleeping
right beside her.
[SHIDO grunts]
No, it's a misunderstanding.
--I was just reaching for this.
--[cell phone vibrating]
Kotori?
[KOTORI]
Hello? Yoshino?
Kotori? Is that you?
I really made it.
It's five years ago.
Metatron!
Mal'akh!
Yes, this is
Tengu City's Nankou area.
Mom and Dad,
they're so close.
--[alarm wailing]
--[gasps]
Shido.
[gasps]
It's you. I found you.
I found you, I found you,
I found you, I found you!
Finally, I found you!
Metatron!
[PHANTOM] Strange, attacking me
out of nowhere like that.
I was just wondering
who you might be.
You're a Spirit, aren't you?
What about that Angel? Metatron?
Please tell me,
what is the meaning of this?
I still possess
the Sephirah crystal, you see.
So who could you be?
Where did you
come from exactly?
Why did you attack me
like that?
[ORIGAMI gasps]
[screams]
[shrieks]
--[PHANTOM] Oh, I see.
--[gasps]
So you've reversed
the flow of time
by using Zaphkiel, have you?
That's surprising,
that she would lend
someone her powers like that.
Kadour!
Not so fast.
Oh, dear.
Whatever the future me
has done,
it seems she's earned
quite the grudge from you,
hasn't she?
[growls]
[PHANTOM] I'm sorry
about whatever that was,
but I'm afraid I can't
let you kill me here today.
I have a wish that I have to
make come true, just like you.
[gasps]
A wish? For real?
You kill my mom and dad,
then you dare to have
a wish in this world?
Really?
Screw you. Screw you! Screw you!
I refuse to give you time
to make your wish come true.
I don't even plan
to give you any time to pray!
You'll die without
accomplishing anything.
Disappear,
leaving no trace behind.
You should have
nothing but regret
filling your cold, empty heart.
Nothing!
Be gone from this world!
[PHANTOM] Wait, you think
I killed your mom and dad?
I'm sorry, but maybe
you have the wrong person.
[gasps]
[growls]
[shrieks]
[PHANTOM gasps]
[screaming]
[PHANTOM]
That was truly magnificent.
I never would've imagined
you could wield Metatron
quite so well.
[panting]
[PHANTOM]
The birth of a powerful Spirit
should be celebrated.
That's what I think.
What are you?
[PHANTOM]
That brilliant attack...
I'm so glad I got to witness it.
This is all happening
so that my wish comes to pass.
Goodbye, now.
It really is about time
that I was on my way.
[gasps]
You stay here!
[PHANTOM]
There's no reason to.
Not when I've already
achieved my goal for the day.
[growls]
Yes. I saved them...
Mom and Dad...
--[alarm wailing]
--[gasps]
[whimpers]
No...
Please, no...
--[gasps]
--[wailing continues]
[YOUNG ORIGAMI]
Angel?
[ORIGAMI]
There I am.
It happened just like before.
I couldn't stop it.
I'll never forgive you.
I'll kill you.
[sobbing]
I swear that I will.
Someday, I'm gonna kill you!
[screaming]
Oh, I see.
So, Fraxinus was...
Anyway, I'm glad you're safe.
[KOTORI] We're in
Ratatoskr's underground base.
You all really
should come, too,
once your pickup arrives,
I mean.
Wait, how is it you know
where we're at?
[KOTORI]
Shido, whose phone do you think
you're on right now, anyway?
--Oh, right.
--[car approaching]
[KOTORI]
Sounds like they're there.
I can fill you in on the rest
once you get here, okay?
Hold up, one sec.
The thing is... Origami...
[WESTCOTT]
Excellent work, Ellen.
Your performance
really was superb.
[ELLEN] No.
I took one too many direct hits.
Surprisingly, the enemy had some
talented individuals with them.
Fascinating.
Well, in that case, let's hope
that a good number
of them have survived.
Wouldn't that be nice?
More importantly...
[WESTCOTT]
Yeah, I know, I know.
I didn't predict this,
though I guess that makes sense.
I mean, who would've thought
that she would become a Spirit?
Ah, it's such a pity, too.
Ike, I'm looking at you,
and you're smiling.
Oops. Well, guess you caught me.
[ELLEN]
So, where is she now?
Hard to say.
It seems like her reaction
suddenly vanished.
Do you think it's possible
she could have
Spirit wave suppression powers?
Is that what
you're thinking, too?
If she's a Spirit,
then she knows
she'll be hunted by us.
So of course
she would hide herself.
Maybe.
That would undoubtedly be smart,
but the fact that we have
such trouble
understanding their actions
is what makes Spirits Spirits,
wouldn't you say?
You never know.
She might actually be watching
over us right now as we speak.
[KURUMI]
I wonder, is it possible
that Origami was able to
achieve her goal in the end?
Because, really,
if I'm being perfectly honest,
in my dark little
heart of hearts,
I truly hope that she's able
to make that wish come true.
[KURUMI CLONE chuckles]
Wow, it's so not like me to say
something like that at all.
Have you been out in
the moonlight too long or what?
Hey, come on,
I don't have to be one thing.
Sometimes I just happen to be
in a more charitable mood
than others.
[SHIDO]
Hmm?
[gasps]
What the hell's that?!
[KOTORI]
What? What is it?
Look, the moon.
[gasping]
[ALL gasp]
Shido. What the heck
is happening out there?
Kotori, what is this?
[KOTORI]
A Spirit.
But I don't really get it.
Something this powerful
without any warning?
[SHIDO]
Kotori?
[KOTORI] Listen, this reaction
is no normal Spirit.
It's an Inverse.
[gasps]
Are you okay, Shido?
Yeah. Thanks, Tohka.
But we have to save
the other people.
Everyone, help me out, 'kay?
[SHIDO grunts]
That blast...
Where'd it come from?
[SHIDO]
Wait... Origami...?
Oh, no.
What the hell happened to you?
Origami!
[KOTORI]
Origami Tobiichi's a Spirit?
--Listen, Shido.
--[footsteps]
You need to prepare yourself
emotionally.
No matter who it might be,
a Spirit is a Spirit.
You'll have to capture
Origami Tobiichi.
[SHIDO]
Yeah. I know.
[TOHKA echoing]
Shido...
--Shido!
--[gasps]
I have no idea what's happened
to Origami, but look.
If there's one person
in this world
who can bring her back,
that person is you, Shido.
Yeah, you're right.
[KAGUYA]
I'm glad to see you understand.
If you were about to
whine and complain
about being the one to do it,
I was ready to toss you clean
through the freakin' sky.
A pledge.
Kaguya and I
will guide you there,
right towards Master Origami.
--[KAGUYA] Hmm.
--Shido, please go to her
and open up her eyes
however you can.
Hey, now, wait for me, darling.
I'd be so sad if you were to
forget me. [giggles]
--[SHIDO] Look out!
--[BOTH gasp]
[SHIDO]
Yoshino.
[YOSHINO] Um, I kind of think
we should take care
of everything on the ground.
Using Zadkiel's power, I have
a feeling I can hold her off.
Uh, I guess I might as well
help out too since I'm here.
After all, this debris
won't be dangerous
if I turn it
into cotton balls.
Natsumi.
[SHIDO]
Thank you, everyone.
Come on, let's go now.
I'll lead us
and open up the way.
--[yells]
--Gotcha.
Acknowledged. Ha!
[SHIDO grunts]
Whoa!
Mild praise.
You're pretty good at this.
I appreciate that.
[yells]
Be ready to go as soon as
I draw out her attack.
I won't last that long.
Kaguya, Yuzuru, ready?
Leave it to me.
Agreed. Let's go.
--[ELLEN] Oh, I think not.
--[GROUP gasping]
[ELLEN] We'll have no children
meddling with the Inverse.
[ALL grunt]
[screaming]
Shido!
Rescue, now.
Raphael, El Nahash!
It's a pleasure
to see you again, Shido Itsuka.
Well, the feeling
sure as hell isn't mutual.
[ELLEN]
Hmph.
She's comparable even
to Princess back in the day.
What a magnificent Inverse.
Ike will be so delighted.
[SHIDO]
Screw you!
We're not about
to let you take Origami!
[ELLEN] Barking at me
like some stupid dog
isn't going to accomplish
anything here, you know.
--Be silent--
--[yells]
Yuzuru!
Response.
[grunts]
Origami!
[SHIDO]
Origami. It's me.
Shido. Can you hear me?
[inaudible]
All right.
[SHIDO gasps]
Ori... gami...
[gasps]
[screaming]
Dammit.
What now?
I've gotta go back up.
Huh?
[SHIDO]
Fraxinus?
[KOTORI] Looks like
you really went all out.
Kotori!
[KOTORI]
I wish I could tell you
to pull back for now
and retreat.
Unfortunately, I don't think
we can afford to do that
in this situation.
Our transport device
is hanging in there, though.
So we'll go ahead and try
sending you over to Ori...
Huh?
Kotori!
[gasps, groans]
What is this?
[KURUMI giggles]
My gosh, long time
no see, Shido.
Kurumi.
What are you trying to pull
at a time like this?
Oh, my.
Could it really be possible
that the great Shido
has completely forgotten
what my personal goal
actually is?
[SHIDO growls]
[KURUMI] "At a time
like this," you say?
I mean, if you think about it,
what better time
is there, right?
I can't be expected
to let an opportunity
like this slip away.
I'm begging, Kurumi,
please don't get in my way.
I have to save them.
I have to get up there
and save Origami.
[sighs]
That one's hopeless, though.
Nobody's voice is going to reach
Origami as she is right now.
And by that, I do mean no one.
Including you, my friend.
I wonder
what she might have seen
on her recent little trip
through time.
[gasps]
Well, doesn't matter.
I think I've wasted
enough minutes
standing around talking to you.
It's about that time, Zaphkiel.
Let's get this party started,
shall we?
[gasps]
[grunting]
Oh, wait,
didn't I tell you already?
You're mine now
no matter what you try.
--[SHIDO gasps]
--[gunshot]
[whimpers]
How did it not hurt?
Hey, what did you do?
[chuckles]
What, indeed, am I right?
A good question
but it won't be answered today.
Don't...
What do you say?
I don't know about you,
but I think our date
is long overdue.
--[SHIDO gasps]
--[gunshot]
[SHIDO screaming]
[groans softly]
[insects chirping]
Cicadas?
Wait, shouldn't the buildings
be destroyed?
This is Tengu City, right?
[gasps]
Ms. Tamae!
[TAMAE]
Hmm?
Uh, hi.
How exactly is it
that you know my name?
What? Hold on.
What are you talking about?
It's me. Shido Itsuka.
Oh, wait, are you actually
trying to hit on me?
Well, that's very flattering,
but I kinda need to go now.
Sorry, have a good day.
I don't get it. That was her.
[KURUMI laughing]
--Kurumi?
--[laughing continues]
[KURUMI]
Don't waste your time looking.
You won't find me where you are.
I'm in a different time
than you now.
What are you talking about?
[KURUMI] Using Zaphkiel's
last bullet, Yod Bet,
I sent you hurtling
back to Tengu City
as it existed five years ago.
[SHIDO]
Five years ago?
You take me back
to where I belong right now!
I don't have time
to screw around like this.
[KURUMI] Are you
completely sure about that?
Because the only way
to reverse the disaster
that's unfolding
in the present,
is to deal with
the younger Origami
you'll find in the past.
Origami?
[KURUMI]
Yes.
[SHIDO] So, you're telling me
Origami asked for your help
to go back five years
and kill Phantom?
[KURUMI]
Yep. That's exactly it.
But if that's true,
why would Origami go
Inverse back in
our original time?
I mean, what happened to her
when she came here?
[KURUMI]
Believe it or not,
that's something
even I don't know.
It's your job to find out.
And then, it's your job
to reverse it.
Now, maybe you understand
why I shot you with Yod Bet
in the first place.
Yeah, I do.
But tell me something.
Why would you do this?
Why would you have
used your Angel
for someone else to begin with?
[KURUMI]
I know, right?
If I had to say why,
the simplest answer
is that I want proof.
Proof that it is
somehow possible
for history to be changed.
[NARRATOR]
She knows that she's becoming
the thing she hates,
yet she trudges on.
Crossing time, defying God.
In the end, where will
that road lead her?