[KOTORI]
It's crazy.
I still can't believe
she vanished.
And it was right at midnight.
The instant the date changed,
Yuzuru was erased.
We've got to figure out
which of these 12
Natsumi is impersonating.
Because it looks like
if I don't,
we run the risk of losing
another person each night,
one by one.
Yeah, that seems to be the case.
The process of elimination
will help.
Not much of a consolation
when friends
are vanishing, though.
[grunts]
I've gotta find out
who she is in a hurry.
Not just for us,
but for Natsumi's sake, too.
Well, in that case,
isn't it about time for you
verify my identity?
What if I'm her?
No way, you're the real deal.
At least, that's what I'm hoping
is the case with all my heart.
What the hell does it matter
what you want to believe?
Your mission is to do
what you can to verify it.
You could grill me
with questions, or...
I mean, to judge my reaction
or whatever,
you could, like, kiss me
or something dumb like that.
I see.
Then...
Well?
Oh, okay.
[whimpers]
Big brother! What are you
doing?! Give me those!
Come on, they're mine!
Give ‘em back. No fair!
--Oh, yeah.
--You're bigger than me!
--You're Kotori all right.
Natsumi couldn't play
this side of you so perfectly.
--Isn't that right, Kotori?
--[KOTORI growling]
Oh, crap.
I'm sorry? Not the face!
[REINE] I think we need to
speed up this dating process.
[SHIDO]
I agree.
I know we've already
scheduled a pretty packed day,
but I don't care.
Let's fit as many more in
as we possibly can
before tonight.
I'll leave all the
arrangements to you.
[REINE] Understood.
I'll do the best I can.
As for right now,
you're due to meet Miku.
--Better hurry.
--I'm on it. Thanks.
Thanks for coming, Miku.
But, hey, why did you
want us to wear costumes?
It's kinda weird.
Oh, it's kind of
an occupational hazard,
I'm afraid.
Being such a huge star
means having to hide sometimes.
But I don't want you to worry.
As you can see, we'll totally
blend in if we cosplay here.
We're finally on a date
by ourselves.
I just didn't want anyone
getting in the way of that.
Huh. That actually
makes sense.
--Wow!
It's Kanon Tsukishima
and Seig from Valkyrie Misty.
[WOMAN 1] And you're in
the rarely cosplayed masks
from episode six
when they saved Misty!
[BOTH]
Can we please take your picture?
Wait, what?
Oh, no, I don't think we--
Of course.
We would be delighted!
Darling, your turn. Go on.
[SHIDO]
What, me?
[sighs]
[BOTH]
There it is!
The signature
pose of our beloved Seig!
[AI] So, you gonna tell us
why we're here or what?
Because, FYI, if you're making
amends, this isn't enough.
That's so lame, yo.
Nah, this has nothing
to do with that day.
Just thought we should hang.
I mean, we're classmates,
after all.
I should know you better.
[TAMAE] So, what is it
that's troubling you, Shido?
Why is it you're
suddenly interested
in talking about the future?
[SHIDO]
Uh, well... How do I put it?
I guess I just feel like
I need to start taking
my life's path more seriously.
Oh, now I see.
Hmm.
In that case, do you remember
the promise you made me?
Because I haven't forgotten it.
--Shido.
--[SHIDO squeals]
Hai... yah!
No way!
[laughs]
Did you see that?
It was my signature move.
You just witnessed
the Dunkelheit Windhose.
--[SHIDO] Uh...
--[KAGUYA] Hmm.
You'll never beat
my crazy skills, Shido.
Not now that I have this guy.
With this legendary relic
in my possession,
you stand no chance
of defeating me.
So, there.
Wait, how is it "legendary"?
I mean, didn't you
just buy it from that lady?
Well, if I were you,
I would try to focus on my game.
Don't forget, we promised
that the loser of this match
would do whatever
the winner wants.
[SHIDO]
I'm well aware.
Get ready for a comeback!
Uh...
And Shido's out,
ladies and gents.
Come sit by me.
[SHIDO]
Yeah, okay.
My first order is,
for the next ten minutes,
you won't act surprised
or flustered.
Nor will you try to stop me,
no matter what.
And you'll promise me
to never speak of it again.
[gasps]
Right, okay. I promise.
Thank you.
--[sighs]
--[gasps]
[chuckles]
This is even more comfy
than I thought it would be.
Be good and I'll turn you
into my full-time pillow.
How does that sound?
You've got to be kidding me.
I'm sorry, are you
complaining, my pet?
Now then,
I want you to rub
my head very gently.
--As you wish, master.
--[chuckling]
[gasps]
Hold on.
[KAGUYA whimpers]
What the... What's wrong?
[KAGUYA sobbing]
Yuzuru... I miss her...
Kaguya. Of course.
[KAGUYA] I know you said
she was taking an exam,
but really,
you don't know where she is.
I can tell.
You think I'm stupid.
I would never.
[KAGUYA]
But you thought it was better
if I didn't know, right?
So, I'll trust you.
Because that fateful day,
the one who gave me
and Yuzuru a third choice,
that was you, Shido.
Kaguya...
[KAGUYA]
So, I'm begging you.
Please save Yuzuru.
[KOTORI]
"Holy crap, you pathetic loser."
Kidding.
I meant the opposite of that.
You beat the schedule
and actually went on
11 different dates in two days.
I'm exhausted
thinking about it.
Well, can't complain.
I'm the one who asked for it.
So?
Did you sense anything wrong
when you were talking to anyone?
[SHIDO]
No, nothing in particular.
There's no doubt in my mind
that Miku and Kaguya are real.
And neither my teacher
nor the girls seemed off to me.
This is hard.
I know we need
to figure it all out,
but I dread knowing
who Natsumi is.
Yeah.
Sorry, bro.
Unfortunately, I think it's time
for you to give her an answer.
I know.
Except, even if I wanted
to make some kind of guess,
how am I supposed to do that?
[KOTORI] Hmm. We don't
really know that, either.
This game seems guided
by nothing but Natsumi's whims.
She's holding all the cards.
I imagine even right now,
she's observing us
from somewhere close by.
[NATSUMI]
Right on the money!
You stay back!
[SHIDO]
Natsumi.
Ah, good evening, Shido.
Day two of the game
is now at an end.
Tell me something,
are you having fun yet?
What is this even about,
Natsumi?
I never asked to play this game.
Just bring Yuzuru back now
and we can talk about
anything you want.
Sorry, no chance.
It's a bummer if you're not
feeling up to the task,
but the cork's kinda
already out of the bottle
if you know what I mean.
So, no time
like the present, right?
Why don't you give me
your guess for today?
Who am I impersonating?
I... I don't...
Shido, some will be erased
if you don't answer her.
Even a wild guess'll do.
[growls]
I think the one
you're impersonating...
...is Yoshino.
And I'm not confident in that,
but she did seem unusually bold.
I see.
Well...
[SHIDO gasps]
Natsumi, wait!
She's gone.
Do you think you were right?
[REINE]
Shin. Kotori.
Do you copy?
Reine? We're here, what's up?
Just now,
Natsumi's Angel showed up again.
Two more people
have disappeared.
Both Ai Yamabuki and Yoshino.
[SHIDO gasps]
[SHIDO]
Two more days have passed,
and I still haven't
guessed correctly.
Ms. Okamine, Mai Hazakura,
Mii Fujibakama, and Tonomachi
have all been erased.
[REINE]
Shin, you're almost to the spot.
Sorry. Did you wait long?
[ORIGAMI]
I just got here.
[REINE] For the record,
I've been observing her.
She's been waiting there
for over an hour.
[chuckles nervously]
[ORIGAMI]
Well, what are we seeing?
[SHIDO] I don't know.
I hadn't really decided.
So in other words,
you invited me
not because you wanted
to see a specific film,
but instead because you wanted
to spend some time with me.
Uh... Um, yeah.
I mean, I guess.
Sure.
[BOTH laughing]
[WOMAN]
How far are we going?
[MAN]
As far as you want.
[SHIDO]
Origami?
[gasps]
Huh?
Shido, I want you to touch me.
No bra for easy access.
What? Here?!
You don't mean that!
[SHIDO]
Hmm?
[muffled screaming]
[SHIDO sighs]
--That wore me out.
--[footsteps approaching]
Mind, body, and soul.
--[TOHKA] Shido.
--Huh?
[SHIDO]
Tohka.
What are you doing
out this late?
I wanted to check on you.
These past few days,
you've just seemed
so preoccupied.
I've been
a little worried about you.
[gasps]
Sorry.
Oh, no,
you don't have to apologize.
You're doing something important
that you have to do,
isn't that right?
It's just...
It's sad not being able
to see you, that's all.
If there's anything
I can do to help,
just say the word, okay?
Thank you. You're so sweet.
I already feel like
a whole new man.
Yay! That makes me happy.
Me, too.
[laughing]
[TOHKA]
Huh?
I'm so sorry to bother you.
If I wanted to get
to Tengu Street,
would this be
the right direction?
Yeah, that's right.
Turn left at the second light
and you'll run directly into it.
Thanks a lot. Broken GPS.
I appreciate
that you young lovers
were willing to help me out.
[OLD MAN] What do you think?
Did I sound awkward back there?
No, I highly doubt
they suspect anything.
[OLD MAN]
Hmph.
So that's Shido Itsuka,
as well as the famous Princess.
They certainly don't seem
any worse for wear.
Well then, good night, Shido.
Natsumi.
Yeah, good night, Tohka.
[giggles]
"Natsumi."
Or in other words,
"I love you." Huh.
[chuckles]
Hey, Kotori, I'm home.
Shido! There you are!
Where the hell have you been?!
I just heard from Reine
a second ago.
She said it's Tohka.
--Tohka has vanished!
--[SHIDO gasps]
[doorbell beeping]
Please, no. Tohka!
Tohka!
[sobs]
[gasps]
[NATSUMI]
Oh?
Is that panic I hear in your
sweet little voice, Shido?
Natsumi!
Hey, now, this isn't my fault.
You're the one
who didn't come home
when you were supposed to.
I assumed you were
forfeiting your guess tonight,
so I did the thing
and erased another person,
you know how it goes.
You are the worst.
Still, though,
I'm kinda thinking
I wanna end this pretty soon.
Wanna end what?
What does that mean?
What it means is,
if you guess correctly,
I'll return all the people
who have disappeared.
Just know,
if you don't guess right,
then it's officially my win,
and I'll take the place
of every one of your
missing friends from now on.
Those 12
precious friends of yours
will unfortunately never be
returning to this world
ever again.
Since this time
is kinda special,
I'll be back at 11:30 tonight.
[SHIDO]
Natsumi, wait!
Natsumi!
[SHIDO] I'll get it right.
I'll save them.
I will.
All of them.
[NATSUMI chuckles]
That Shido...
He makes the most adorable face
whenever someone disappears.
But that's not
nearly enough for me.
I want you to show me
what true despair is!
That's the unlucky fate of those
who see my dark secret.
I'll watch you drown
in your sorrow.
And then, nobody will
be able to find me.
Not that anybody
looks for me, anyway.
[WESTCOTT]
Yo, it's been quite a while.
How long, Elliott?
Thirty years, give or take.
You seem well, Ike.
Good for you.
Okay, that's everyone, then.
Shido.
I know it's a lot,
but at least now you understand
what we're facing.
I got you all involved in this,
and I'm so sorry.
Look, don't worry about that.
I just wish
you'd told the truth.
It really would've helped,
when Yuzuru disappeared.
This is embarrassing,
but I think I'm the most sad
to hear that our date
was just a part
of a research operation.
I have a long list
of questions about this.
But for now, I'll let it go
and cooperate.
Thank you all. I mean it.
Okay, let's go
through it all again.
Natsumi is impersonating
one of these 12,
and it could be anyone.
These have been
Shido's guesses so far:
Yoshino, Ms. Okamine,
and Mai Hazakura.
I think we can
exclude these three.
In turn, Natsumi has erased
Yuzuru, Ai Yamabuki,
Hiroto Tonomachi,
Mii Fujibakama, and Tohka.
It's possible that she was
actually one of those five.
And then there are
the five of us, of course.
That makes us
strong suspects.
Although, to impersonate
one of us
might pose a little more
of a challenge for her.
Huh? Wait, What do you
mean by that?
I get it.
Our traits are too unique
and complex.
And that makes us hard
to imitate, right?
Sure, yeah. Let's go with that.
[ORIGAMI]
This Witch,
the Spirit
you're calling Natsumi,
why would she take
such a huge risk?
[ORIGAMI]
The way she's handled it so far,
every time a person disappears,
it just increases our
chances of guessing right.
So by the end,
it'll be hard for us to lose.
Which means, the Witch is
confident we won't choose her.
She knows that no matter
what we might come at her with,
it will never be
the correct answer.
For example...
[ALL gasp]
She concealed herself
inside a photo or something.
A good point.
That is exactly
the sort of creative thinking
we need right now.
Don't you think,
maybe it's possible
she isn't impersonating
anybody at all?
I really can't imagine
that's the case.
[SHIDO]
Origami is right.
Why am I trusting Natsumi
to play by the rules?
She'd do anything to win.
Which means, she could even be
one of these five.
[NATSUMI chuckles]
What a party.
[ALL gasp]
Natsumi.
--Ah! She's the one.
--[gasps]
Aww! She's so gorgeous,
it's not fair!
Thanks for that.
Now, then, It's the night
we've all been waiting for.
What do you say?
Do you think
you can finally guess
who I'm impersonating
tonight, Shido?
Yeah, I'll get it, all right.
And you know what?
It's for your sake, too.
Ha. Sure, give it
your best shot.
Now, tonight is special
because I'm gonna give you
three guesses.
You'll know right away
if you're wrong
‘cause one of your friends
here will disappear
right before your eyes.
Isn't it exciting?
Come on, Shido,
give me the first name.
Don't be shy.
Okay. Well, then for starters,
I know you can't be
one of the four people
standing in this room.
I can't imagine you'd bet
everything on a game
you had a 75 percent
chance of losing.
[SHIDO]
So in other words,
you're somewhere among the five
people that you've erased.
You made yourself safe
as quickly as possible,
as someone we'd least expect.
And that is...
Yuzuru, the one who went first.
Hmm.
Shido, what're you saying?
Yuzuru was the real deal.
I am positive
that she was my sister.
[SHIDO] Thing is, I'm not
certain about this, either.
At least, if Natsumi
actually was Yuzuru,
everything would make sense.
Oh, what a shame.
You're so wrong.
[gasps]
Origami!
You guys,
she literally disappeared!
You're kidding.
It really wasn't Yuzuru?
I've been saying that
the whole time!
What's next, my darling
little detectives?
Who are you gonna name now?
Don't take too much time,
or I'll just have to
suck someone else up.
[WESTCOTT]
Elliot is on the move, too.
It's time to fill the vacancy
in your support personnel.
The trick is, finding someone
who's worthy
of an Adeptus number.
Easier said than done.
[WESTCOTT]
Is it really, though?
What about the one
who gave you that scar?
Now, there's
an outstanding wizard.
[SHIDO]
Dammit!
[KOTORI]
Keep it together, Shido.
I think you're on
the right track here.
[SHIDO] Which one is Natsumi?
Who is she?!
Can't cope!
I have no clue who it is!
We don't know enough
to make a guess yet.
Sorry, gang,
but time's almost up.
I may just go ahead
and vanish someone
if I get tired of waiting.
Hold on. I think it's him.
Oh, too bad.
Better luck next time.
[screams]
--[GIRLS gasp]
--Kaguya!
Time for the grand finale,
so this is your last chance.
Who will you choose
to be your final guess?
I can't take this,
my darling, I can't!
To think I was lucky enough
to finally meet Shido,
and now I have to
turn around and disappear.
Keep it together, Miku.
You have to stay calm.
FYI, just 30 seconds left.
[growls]
[MIKU]
Darling, look at me.
This is for you.
I just can't bear to disappear
without leaving
a piece of me with you.
--[SHIDO] Miku--
--Because if I wear this,
then it'll only end up
vanishing together with me.
[SHIDO gasps]
[SHIDO]
Wear this?
Vanish?
What? What are you
thinking, Shido?
[gasps]
I've got it, Natsumi.
I mean, I know the reason
you're so confident.
[NATSUMI]
Hmm?
While it's true that you're
impersonating someone
in one of the 12 pictures,
it is not one of the people.
[NATSUMI grunts]
This was you. I know it.
You're Yoshinon.
[gasps]
No way.
Why in the world would she...
Now that I think back,
it was strange.
[SHIDO]
Yoshinon is Yoshino's puppet.
It shouldn't be able to see
something that Yoshino can't.
[growls]
What Miku just said
made me realize.
When Yoshino disappeared,
Yoshinon vanished
right along with her.
Well then? I made my guess.
You were impersonating
Yoshinon, right?
[growling]
[squeals]
[ALL groan]
[ALL gasp]
[SHIDO]
You guys!
Tohka!
Shido. Where are we?
--[YOSHINO] What happened to me?
--[sobbing]
[YOSHINON]
So weird.
I feel like I've been
taking the longest nap ever!
Doubt. Why exactly am I here?
You're back! Yuzuru!
Oh, thank goodness.
You all look okay.
[NATSUMI grunting]
--[SHIDO] Hey, Natsumi.
--[NATSUMI gasps]
Care to explain
why you did this?
Because we're all listening.
Holy crap. Are you Natsumi?
Huh?
[screams]
Haniel, now!
Oh, I get it.
She has this filled-out form
only after she transforms
using Spirit power.
You saw. You saw!
Damn you, you saw everything!
You've now seen my secret
not once but twice!
No, it is unforgivable.
And none of you
are getting away with it!
Huh?
I hope you enjoy
this farewell present.
We'll meet again.
Rest assured,
I'll have my revenge.
Wait. Don't go!
We can talk!
[TOHKA]
Shido.
[SHIDO]
Huh?
[NARRATOR] They say
there is only one truth,
however, the future can split
into many different paths.
Which one will you choose?
[screaming]