[MURDOCH] What the hell
were you thinking, Mr. Westcott?
Please, do enlighten us.
[WESTCOTT]
Sorry, I'm not quite sure
what you're asking, Murdoch.
Now's not the time to play dumb.
I'm obviously referring to your
many recent activities in Japan.
Interfering with
the Self-Defense Force.
Utilizing Wizards
for your own agenda, and worse,
transforming the city
into a war zone!
The Japanese government
is all over us, thanks to you.
How do plan
to rectify this mess?
Look, what does it matter?
We obviously achieved enough
to make it worthwhile.
Don't forget, we succeeded
with Princess's inversion.
Do you really not understand
what I'm saying?!
It's ludicrous!
What do Spirits have to do
with saving DEM?
The company can't afford
to take a backseat
to your selfish
little obsessions.
Everyone, I think
the time has come.
I move that
Managing Director Westcott
be relieved of his position.
--[MAN A] I agree.
--[murmuring]
[RUSSELL] Are you willing
to comply with this, sir?
Of course. Removing me
is well within your given rights
as the board of directors.
Well then, Chairman Russel,
I say we proceed
with a vote right now.
All right, all those in favor
of Wescott's dismissal?
Zero hands.
His removal is hereby rejected.
What? What are you
talking about, Chairman?!
All these people
agree with me--
--[screaming]
--[MEN gasping]
[screaming]
You'll find Realizers
ready at the infirmary.
If you get there fast,
you should be back to normal
in a few days.
[MURDOCH groaning]
And once I'm finished addressing
my "selfish little obsession,"
I shall hand over
the company, soon.
Don't worry.
At least compared to how long
we've already
been waiting, anyway.
[NARRATOR] A written challenge,
and with it, 12 photographs.
Her one question:
"Can you find me?"
[REINE] So, these must be
the photos that Natsumi sent.
[KOTORI]
"I'm here, among your friends.
Can you take a guess
which one I am?
Before everyone else
disappears, too?"
That was Natsumi's
entire message.
Well, if we take it
at face value,
then we have to assume Natsumi's
impersonating one of them.
And that if you can't
find her quickly,
they'll begin to disappear
one by one.
Does that sound right?
--[SHIDO grunts]
--[KOTORI] Most likely.
Ugh! Notice, she gives
no specific time limit
or any other rules
for this little game.
That did stand out.
Can't imagine she forgot.
And while you're sitting here
trying to figure this out,
she's probably somewhere
overseeing the entire game.
No. It's not wise
to refer to it as a game.
Those who are erased by Natsumi
may very well
never be returned to us.
[gasps]
[KOTORI] That's true.
She seems different from Kurumi.
I have a feeling Natsumi may not
be satisfied playin' around
and keepin' it light.
The fact is, someone here
may already be gone
for eternity.
[SHIDO] No. I don't think
Natsumi is like that.
If I can just guess
who she's impersonating,
I know they'll come home
in one piece.
Sounds like you are putting
a lot of faith in this witch.
Think about it.
Could you open up
your heart to someone
if you didn't think
they trusted you?
As if you know women at all.
Though, I will admit,
that was accurate.
[REINE] Mm-hmm. Whatever the
case, we need to hurry.
Sorry, Kotori.
I'm afraid you'll have to
stay away from command.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I could just as easily
be Natsumi as anyone else could.
And you, Shin,
you have an awful lot
of work ahead of you.
[SHIDO]
Hmm. Okay, what should I do?
For the time being,
I'd start by deciding the order
you'll be dating them in.
To see through
Natsumi's disguise,
be careful not to overlook
even the smallest differences
from the norm.
You'll date them one by one,
in search of anything
that seems off.
Feels wrong somehow
to go out on dates
while I'm doubting everyone.
[TOHKA]
Oh, good morning, Shido!
I'm sorry,
were you waiting long?
[SHIDO] Not at all.
You're right on time.
[TOHKA giggling]
[SHIDO] This has to be Tohka.
I mean, look at her.
[TOHKA]
Is anything wrong, Shido?
You seem a lot more quiet
than usual.
[gasps]
Oh, you think?
Nah, I'm super great. Really.
[REINE]
Try to relax, Shin.
Remember, she's good at this.
You won't see through
her disguise easily.
Let's try to shake her up a bit.
[SHIDO]
Hmm.
Hey, Tohka.
Would you remind me
when we went out last?
I can't remember.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Have you forgotten that we went
shopping just a few days ago?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
[SHIDO]
She got it. So, what's next?
[TOHKA] But I don't mind
going out again so soon,
just so you know.
It's one of the things
that makes me the happiest.
Tohka.
[SHIDO]
Ha. I'm totally onto you.
Huh?
You play Tohka well.
Right, Natsumi?
[growls]
Wait, are you not...
Shido, who the heck
is this Natsumi?!
--Eh?
--Don't try to pretend
like you didn't just blurt out
another girl's name, Shido!
You better tell me where
this other girl is right now!
No. You misunderstood.
That's a kind of a greeting.
It started in an island
down south.
And now it's caught on
in Japan, too.
Natsumi! Natsumi! See?
[TOHKA]
Is that true?
Wow, what an incredible lie.
It's so bad
it almost has to be real.
[TOHKA] Oh, okay, well,
I guess that makes sense.
So, when they use "Natsumi"
as a greeting,
what does it mean?
Um, well, I'm pretty sure
it means "I love you,"
or something close.
[gasps]
I see!
[giggles]
Oh, also, what did you mean
when you said I play Tohka well?
[SHIDO whimpers]
Wow, Tohka, check it out!
That restaurant is totally
doing a lunch buffet!
We have to get in there
and take advantage!
You wanna get lunch?
Sure, I mean, I could eat.
All right.
Let's go do it, then.
[SHIDO] Wait a minute,
what is this reaction?
Normally, one mention of food
would instantly cheer her up.
[REINE] So far we've had
no detection of Natsumi.
How has it felt on your end?
I'm thinking it's gotta be
the real Tohka.
But, we're here to eat lunch
and she seems so...
--[REINE] Problem?
--What?
Is something the matter, Shido?
[SHIDO]
Oh, no.
No way. Tohka only filled
half her plate?
Strange.
I wonder if she's sick.
That's absurd!
She's always a bottomless pit
no matter what.
Hey, were you waiting for me?
Thanks, let's eat up.
Uh... right. Yeah, we should.
[SHIDO]
Is it true?
Is Tohka really Natsumi?
--[TOHKA] Thanks for the lunch.
--Huh?
You're done?
--[TOHKA sighs]
--[stomach growls]
What's wrong, Tohka?
That couldn't have been
enough food for you.
No, it's okay.
I saw something on TV.
[TV WOMAN]
You have to be careful.
Girls who regularly eat
a lot more than guys
can sometimes
be a real turnoff.
[gasps]
See, the thing is, I didn't want
you to be turned off by me,
so I thought I would eat less.
Actually, I really prefer girls
who are happy to scarf
down lots of food.
[gasps]
Do you mean it?!
[SHIDO]
Yeah, it's definitely Tohka.
Fine. But we still
can't dismiss her just yet.
Stay with Tohka
and let her finish eating,
but make sure to get back home
by at least 3:00.
Your next date will come over
and meet you there.
[doorbell dings]
Yeah, hang on, I'm coming.
--[YOSHINON] Boo!
--[screams]
[YOSHINON] Might wanna be
more careful, Shido.
Uh, right, thanks.
I just wasn't
expecting to see you.
Then I guess today's
your lucky day!
Ah, man. [sighs]
Sorry about that, Yoshino.
Yoshinon kind of surprised me.
[gasps]
[YOSHINO]
Uh, trick or treat.
If you don't give me any candy,
I think I have to prank you.
[gasps]
[YOSHINO]
Shido, this is so...
I have to say, I never thought
you'd come here
trick-or-treating.
Afraid we're all out of candy.
I hope the hotcakes will do.
This is a first for me.
I've never had them.
I see. Well, I hope you enjoy.
[gasps]
Ah! Ah! Ah!
--[YOSHINO chuckles]
--[SHIDO laughs]
You had the same reaction
the first time
you came here, remember?
Let me see...
Remind me what it was
you ate that day.
Oh, what was it?
That's right,
you made oyakodon for me.
Ah, yes, that was it.
[YOSHINON] Huh? What are you
talking about, Shido?
That doesn't ring
a bell to me.
You don't remember?
No. I wonder, though,
do you think it could've
been during that time
when I stayed over
at Origami's?
Oh, yeah, I forgot
that ever happened.
I actually had to invade
Origami's place
to get you back, didn't I?
--[whispering]
--Uh-huh. I should?
[YOSHINON]
Come on, just do it!
What would you think
about sharing this with me?
Huh? No, that's okay.
I mean, I made those
especially for you.
Oh. All right, fine,
we can share.
Give me a bite.
[gasps]
Say ah.
A-Ahhh...
Isn't that yummy?
[SHIDO]
Mm-hmm. It really is.
[gasps]
Shido, you've got
a little syrup.
Huh? Where is it?
[YOSHINON]
Ooh!
Um, hotcakes are like halfway
between a food
and a candy, actually.
So that's why...
Why I just...
It was just a prank, okay?!
[YOSHINON]
Woo-hoo!
You go, girl!
Hey, Reine.
I think that was
the real Yoshino, don't you?
[REINE]
Well, who knows, really?
[SHIDO]
So, who's up next on the agenda?
[REINE]
Right. Hiroto Tonomachi.
Tohka, Yoshino, and Tonomachi.
We're three dates down
with no real leads
on what we're looking for.
None of their behavior
seemed any different
than usual to any of us.
I'd prefer not to call
that whole thing
with Tonomachi a date
if that's okay.
[REINE] Shin, think you can
handle one more?
Yuzuru is already
waiting for you
at the designated location.
Absolutely.
--[SHIDO] Sorry, Yuzuru.
--Offended.
Some nerve, inviting me here
and arriving late.
What do you have to say?
So sorry.
I was running a bit behind.
[YUZURU]
Hmm. Pardoned. It's all right.
You'll find I have a big heart,
so we will just call those
five minutes an anomaly.
[sighs]
[YUZURU] Are you unhappy
that I'm the only one here?
Huh?
No, that's not it at all.
I-I was just thinking
what a rare occasion this is.
Negative.
Please don't feel as if you need
to make some kind of excuse.
Kaguya and I are of
one heart and mind.
In fact, what you said,
it only serves to validate
how closely she and I
are bound together.
[chuckles]
[YUZURU]
Question.
Is there anything wrong
that I should know about?
You've never called me out
this late.
Oh, nothing.
I just thought it might be nice
to talk with you alone
once in a while.
Bad idea?
Negative. It's not bad at all.
But if that's the case...
[gasps]
Y-Yuzuru?
Selfishness. Just for tonight,
Shido is mine and mine alone.
And it's nice.
Suggestion.
Shido, shall we take
a walk together?
Whoa...
Admiration. It's beautiful.
[SHIDO]
Yeah, it sure is.
Advice. Whenever a girl says
that something is beautiful,
it's common knowledge
the only appropriate response
from a guy is,
"But you are more beautiful."
Huh? Is that really how it is?
[YUZURU] Affirmative.
That is just how it is.
Well, you are more beautiful.
[YUZURU sighs]
Happiness.
Do you mean it, though?
Uh... huh?
Confrontation.
--Shido?
--Yeah?
What is it?
Question. Answer, please.
When it comes to Kaguya and me,
which of us do you like more?
[SHIDO] I can't answer that
off the top of my head.
You're both too precious.
[chuckles]
Disdain. Good grief, Shido.
You picked the most pathetic
and lazy answer
that there ever was.
What did you expect?
You popped that question
out of nowhere.
[YUZURU]
Concession.
Okay, then,
if I gave you enough time,
do you think you would be
able to answer me?
[SHIDO]
Uh... Ah... Uh...
If I do that, which answer
are you hoping to hear?
[YUZURU]
Response.
If you end up choosing Kaguya,
then I'll agree
and you're a good person.
I'd be disappointed in you
if you chose me.
Yeah, I did not expect that.
[YUZURU]
Addition.
If you were to
choose me instead,
I'd be happy.
[SHIDO]
Hmm.
Well, which is it in the end?
[YUZURU]
Sigh. It's just like I said.
I'd be fine with your choosing
either one of us.
However, your answer
was gutless.
That was a bummer, Shido.
You're a big chicken.
[SHIDO groans]
--[YUZURU] Although...
--[SHIDO] Hmm?
[YUZURU]
Petition.
One thing. Promise me this.
If Kaguya ever comes to you
and asks you to answer
the same question that I did,
when the time comes,
I want you to tell her
that she's the one you choose.
Prediction.
Kaguya will get mad at you.
She'll want to know
why you didn't pick me.
But deep inside, she'll be
so happy that it hurts.
[SHIDO]
Yuzuru...
Confidence.
Kaguya may behave strangely,
but she really does
love you very much.
And this is me saying it,
so it must be true.
The things that Kaguya hates,
I hate as well.
And likewise.
The things that I love,
Kaguya loves just as much.
Careless.
I said more than I meant to.
Before I blurt out
anything else,
I should just go.
Come on, please stay.
Petition.
What I've said to you is no lie.
Kaguya really is
extremely taken by you.
So, please, do me a favor,
be good to her for me.
Uh... Wait, Yuzuru!
Come back!
[KOTORI] And? You just came
right home after that?
After a date, you made a girl
walk home at night
in the dark all by herself?
I gotta say,
you are not impressing me
with these choices.
Sorry. It all happened so fast.
There's not much else
that could've been done.
From start to finish,
Shin has worked very hard today.
Look, I'm well aware of that.
Going on four dates
in a single day
wouldn't necessarily be
an easy task for anybody.
So, Shido,
Tohka, Yoshino,
Tonomachi, and Yuzuru.
Any thoughts on whether
or not Natsumi
might've been impersonating
one of them?
[SHIDO]
Hmm. I just can't say for sure.
I want so much to believe
everyone was real.
Great, don't tell me
you ever thought
this would be easy.
No suspicious readings
on Fraxinus.
So I agree with Shin,
if that helps.
Until we get more data
from the next round of dates,
it's anyone's guess.
Ugh! Fine. Then go
and get some rest, Shido.
You'll be no help to us
if you're sleep-deprived.
Screw up your dates tomorrow
and it'll be a problem
for more than just you.
Thanks for that.
Reine, tomorrow starts at 10:00,
is that right?
Yes, and the first
of the day is Kotori.
Now, I see. That's why--
No. You are so wrong.
Just, as the commander,
I feel...
Ahh--
Why are you all spaced out?!
Go to bed already!
[YUZURU]
Return. Hello, I'm back home.
[KAGUYA]
Yuzuru?
Hey, what was
your urgent business?
Trivial. Just something
I needed to take care of.
It is time, Haniel.
I'll pick the first one.
Will you even be able
to guess who I am,
before every last one is taken?
[laughs]
--[doorbell dinging]
--[pounding on door]
[SHIDO yawns] What's the deal?
It's so early in the morning.
--Shido!
--K-Kaguya?
She's gone...
When I woke up, Yuzuru was gone!
[REINE]
How's Kaguya?
[SHIDO] Better than
she was this morning.
To be safe, I'm having Tohka
and Yoshino stay with her.
I think she'll be okay.
[REINE] Yuzuru had to be
taken to Ratatoskr HQ
for an urgent exam.
Or so we'll say.
Though, if Kaguya
is Natsumi disguised,
then it's a completely
pointless lie.
Reine, your thoughts?
Who could take Yuzuru?
Are we sure it was Natsumi?
Yes.
Look at this.
[SHIDO]
Is that...
[REINE]
Video from a security camera.
The 12 people Natsumi identified
with those photos
are being watched
around the clock.
This is footage
from last night.
I don't see anything
out of the ordinary here.
Keep watching.
[SHIDO]
Hey, that's Natsumi's--!
Yuzuru!
[REINE]
As you can see,
Yuzuru has been abducted
by Natsumi's Angel.
Also, it's likely that
whoever she's impersonating
has been erased this way, too.
Natsumi...
I don't understand.
Why do this?
Deciphering her intentions
can wait.
Right now, we have to focus.
Keep people safe.
I do believe in Natsumi.
I think this is
just a game to her.
Which is why I'm going
to put an end to all this.
Before anyone else disappears.
[KOTORI] I agree, Shido.
Let's not spare any effort.
So I guess it's about time
we begin our date.
[SHIDO] How can I know
that in the days that followed
I would learn just
how powerless I truly was.