Change history? Oh, boy.
[KURUMI]
Yes.
I want you to prove
whether or not it can be done.
I'm curious to know
if this unsalvageable ruin,
this tragedy
devoid of all hope,
could possibly
be prevented if we tried.
So you think
there might be a chance?
I mean, I've always
heard it said
that history
will correct itself, but...
Sure, but do the people
who say that
typically have the power
to put their money
where their mouth is?
Well, no, I guess not.
Doesn't matter how crowded
this world may get,
the only one around who can
interfere with time is me.
And don't you forget it.
A little pointer, though.
Remember that whatever you see
before you is real,
and whatever moment you're in
is the only truth there is,
so be present.
Will I really be able
to save Origami?
Hard to say.
That really depends on you.
All right.
I'm in, let's do it.
Huh?
[KURUMI] Would you care
to explain what you're doing?
Cutting through this way'll
be a lot faster.
Hmm?
[gasps]
[SHIDO]
Eek!
Who the heck are you?
Uh... Sorry. Gotta go!
Hey! You get back here.
[KURUMI]
Shido?
[SHIDO] Shoot. I can't afford
to waste time like this.
What now?
What do I do?!
[gasps]
[SUZUMOTO]
Shido?
Yep, just me.
Have you seen anyone sketchy
come through here?
Uh...
No, I haven't seen anybody.
[SUZUMOTO]
Really? That's weird.
Is it?
Huh? Oh!
Never mind,
don't you worry about it.
Tell your mom hi for me, okay?
Whew, that was a close one.
[KURUMI giggles]
Good thinking, I'm impressed.
[SHIDO]
Yeah. Never would've imagined
that I'd use Natsumi's
transformation powers,
but they came in super handy.
[KURUMI]
I'll say they did.
Looking like that,
no one will bat an eye
seeing you in the past.
Yeah, sure,
but how do I get back to normal?
[KURUMI] Aw, you're so cute,
why would you bother?
Yeah, very funny.
--[explosion]
--[screams]
That must be Kotori.
[KURUMI]
So it would seem.
Let's go!
[NARRATOR] A girl defies time
and transforms into a devil,
while a solitary boy goes up
against an impending disaster.
[PEOPLE screaming]
[SHIDO gasps]
There I am.
Phantom?
[SHIDO gasps]
[SHIDO]
Origami.
[ORIGAMI]
Metatron!
[SHIDO]
Wait, no!
[KURUMI]
Hurry, go after her.
Right.
Origami!
Stop this!
It's me! Please listen!
It's useless.
She can't hear me.
Origami! Come on!
--Origami!
[SHIDO gasps]
Mom and Dad. There you are.
[groans]
[KURUMI]
Shido?
[SHIDO]
Don't worry, I'm fine.
But did they...
Wait. No!
[whimpering]
[growls]
You did this!
[ORIGAMI]
I'll never forgive you.
Never!
I'll kill you. I swear, I will!
[ORIGAMI]
Someday, I'll kill you!
I don't believe it.
What the hell's going on?
This is insane!
[KURUMI]
Not really.
For someone like Origami to have
ended up in her current state,
I knew for a fact
something significant
had to have happened.
She's gone.
[KURUMI] Yod Bet must have
reached its limit.
She went back
to her original time.
[SHIDO]
No way.
So I guess this means
Origami wasn't able
to change history after all.
This is terrible.
Hey, Origami.
[gasps]
Watch out!
Sorry to knock you down.
Are you okay?
They're gone now...
They're both gone...
[ORIGAMI]
I don't...
[SHIDO]
Origami.
Sorry. I'm... so sorry!
Who are you...?
[SHIDO] It's all right!
It's gonna be all right!
Listen to me,
someday, you'll understand.
I promise.
All of this. The truth.
But please don't forget:
you are never alone, okay?!
I'm not... what?
[SHIDO] All of your
sadness and your hate--
let me carry all of it for you!
If you're lost, I'll find you.
When something happens
and it's too much,
please come to me.
Give it all to me, everything.
It's okay.
I'll take all of it.
Do you hear me? Okay?
Don't let despair
take you over, Origami.
[sobbing]
[ORIGAMI]
Thanks, you're very kind.
But who exactly are you, anyway?
Huh? Oh, I'm, uh...
My name is Shido Itsuka.
I just live in the neighborhood.
Shido Itsuka.
Did you really mean
everything you just said?
Yeah, of course.
I meant every word.
Okay.
Well then, this will be
the last time I ever cry.
[ORIGAMI] But... it's also
the last time I'll smile.
What?
[ORIGAMI]
All my sadness and my joy,
all the fun in my life,
I give to you.
But this anger,
this anger is mine alone.
I'm going to kill that thing.
That Angel.
No matter what it takes.
No matter how long it takes.
Origami, wait...
[ORIGAMI] So, sure, you can
carry everything for me
till I'm ready
to kill the Angel.
Until then...
[SHIDO]
Uh...
[KURUMI]
So that's what happened.
What an ironic turn of events.
How unexpected.
This is disappointing.
I'm sorry.
You used Yod Bet,
and I still couldn't
do anything to fix this.
[KURUMI] No, that's not
what I'm talking about.
What?
Shido, we just learned Origami's
the one who killed her parents,
and that means
this whole situation
wouldn't have happened
if not for my Zaphkiel.
So I have to be honest,
that's more than
a little upsetting to me.
Hold on.
I think you're being
a little unfair
to yourself, don't you?
I mean, you didn't
want this to happen.
[KURUMI]
No, of course not.
Anyway, it doesn't matter
'cause it's all over now.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[KURUMI]
Is that really what you think?
It's true, as far as
that world is concerned,
what's done is done.
Full stop.
However, I just happened to be
presented with a new method
to fix this mess
only a moment ago.
What are you talking about,
"presented"? By who?
Believe it or not, by you,
a few dozen minutes from now.
You mean the future me?
I don't get it.
Why would I do that?
[KURUMI]
Because the method future you
told me about isn't one
that the you who went
to the past was aware of.
Do you understand?
You're saying
that for this me, right now,
there's still a chance
I can save Origami?
[KURUMI]
You got it.
Apparently, this isn't over yet.
Let's go!
Indeed.
I agree, it's about time
we went ahead
and fixed this poor excuse
for a world.
Yes. I'll do literally anything
to save her.
[KURUMI]
Attaboy, that's the spirit.
[SHIDO]
So, how do we that?
It's pretty simple in theory.
Basically, we're just
going to have you try again.
[SHIDO]
Huh? What do you mean?
If you think about it,
what was the main reason
you weren't able
to stop Origami?
It was because you had no idea
what was about to happen.
Do you see where I'm going?
Yeah, I think I get it now.
The gist is that
you're suggesting
we use Yod Bet on me again,
is that right?
[KURUMI]
An interesting guess, for sure,
but I'm afraid
that's impossible.
As it stands now,
I'm simply sharing your senses,
or have you forgotten?
I can't physically interact
with you in any way.
[SHIDO]
Then... what?
There's another option.
One single method that only
I know and can make happen.
[SHIDO panting]
Is this the right place?
[KURUMI]
Oh, absolutely. Without a doubt.
I don't see anything.
--[gasps]
--Well, well, lucky me.
I will say,
it's definitely not every day
that a guest
stumbles upon us out here.
Kurumi?
When you know my name
right off the bat,
that's another story.
Who are you?
--[gun cocks]
--And what the hell do you want?
[grunts]
You, five years ago?
[KURUMI]
Yes.
It so happens
I was also near the scene
when this all occurred.
What the hell
were you doing there?
[KURUMI] Just checking out
what was up with that blaze.
I had this sneaking suspicion
that a Spirit might be part
of an inferno that size.
That makes sense.
So, then, what you
want me to do is...
Yep. You get to go
ask me to shoot you.
With Yod Bet.
[SHIDO]
Listen, I need your help.
[KURUMI] You are not to move
without my permission.
I can't guarantee
you'll survive.
I'm Shido Itsuka.
I came from five years
in the future.
And, Kurumi,
you're the one who sent me.
I swear, if this is
some kind of joke--
--This is not a joke!
--Oh?
Listen, please,
I need you to listen.
[KURUMI]
My goodness,
the old me sure was a cautious
little thing, wasn't she?
Let's try something.
Shido, do you think
you could have that me
physically touch you?
I'll try.
Did you just mumble something?
[SHIDO] Kurumi, would you
come touch my hand?
You can keep the gun on me.
Future Kurumi wants to talk.
Wait. I said that?
[SHIDO gasps]
[KURUMI]
Scale of one to ten,
how weird is it if I start with
"Long time, no see"?
Very interesting.
You definitely have my voice,
so that's a good start.
Wanna tell me
what this is all about?
[PAST KURUMI]
I see.
So you're saying
all you want me to do
is point Yod Bet at him
and shoot, is that right?
[KURUMI] Yes. I'd say
that's precisely what I want.
Very well, then.
[SHIDO]
Really?
I can't very well
refuse myself, can I?
Now, come to me!
Zaphkiel, it appears
your time is now!
Zaphkiel.
Yod Bet.
All right,
shall we proceed, then?
Yeah.
Origami, this time it'll work.
I wish you
the best of luck, stranger.
[gunshot]
[KURUMI]
Shido? Oh, Shido?
[sighs]
[humming]
[SHIDO]
Looks like it must've worked.
All right,
let's change the world.
[KURUMI giggles]
Can I assume you have
some sort of plan, then?
[SHIDO]
Hmm...
[KURUMI]
Tick-tock, time's a-wastin'.
Look, stop pressuring me, okay?
I haven't really had time
to think about it.
[KURUMI] Remember, you and I
both know exactly
what's about to happen next.
So I vote you prevent Origami
from realizing
who killed her parents.
Sound like a good plan to you?
[SHIDO]
I considered that, too.
But it doesn't address
the enormous problem
that her parents will still die.
[KURUMI]
Hmm...
[SHIDO]
Let's be real.
As long as her parents
are killed
at the hand of a Spirit--
any Spirit--
she could end up
directing that grudge
towards anyone at all.
On Kotori,
who caused the inferno.
Or Phantom, the one who gave her
the power to do that.
[KURUMI] What's going on
in that head, Shido?
[SHIDO]
Wouldn't it work out if...
If Origami appeared
but there was no enemy in sight?
Well, yeah,
it's possible, but...
Good. There's something
I wanna try.
[KURUMI]
Okay, you do realize
you're creeping around
like a pervert?
[SHIDO]
Oh, shut up.
[KURUMI] By the way,
I assume you know this,
but it never hurts to clarify,
you can't interact
with Kotori or the others.
Yeah. I get that.
I shouldn't tamper with history
any more than necessary.
The only thing I'm here to do
is to save Origami.
--[KURUMI] Shido?
--It's here.
[gasps]
[KURUMI]
Try to refrain, would you?
[gasping]
[KOTORI screams]
Kotori, I'm sorry.
[grunts]
[SHIDO]
Hey!
So you're Phantom.
Been waiting.
[PHANTOM]
You're...
It can't be. Why are you...
Wait a minute,
how do you know me?
[KURUMI]
Better hurry.
[SHIDO]
I'm on it.
[KURUMI] Didn't see
that reaction coming, did you?
Is that someone you're already
acquainted with, Shido?
Nope, can't say I know anyone
who censors their entire body.
[KURUMI chuckles]
I have to admit,
I never would've imagined
that your big plan
would basically consist
of chatting with Phantom.
Is that a problem?
'Course not,
and it's so incredibly like you
to attempt that.
But I can't say
it'd be my recommendation.
The fact is, that one
is impossible to predict.
Do you know who she is, then?
[gasps]
[SHIDO]
Phantom.
[PHANTOM]
Huh, Phantom, is it?
Am I to understand
that's the name I've been given?
I apologize for running off
like that before.
I thought it would be better
to do this away from her.
[PHANTOM] Oh, sorry.
Should've done this sooner.
Is that what you look like?
Well, no, this isn't
my real appearance.
I don't think I can show you
what I actually
look like just yet.
So do you know
who I am or something?
[PHANTOM]
I do.
Very well, yes.
[PHANTOM]
So?
Is that really all you wanted?
You went through the trouble
of using a time travel bullet
to come back here.
This isn't just
a vacation, is it?
How do you know all this...?
Fine, I'll get straight
to the point, then.
I need you to disappear
right now.
Is that your poetic way
of saying
that you're here to kill me?
[SHIDO] No, this is about
saving someone.
I just want you
to get out of sight, fast.
[PHANTOM]
I see.
--Sorry, but my answer is "no."
--[SHIDO] Huh?
I'm afraid that I still have
a few things I have to do.
Please just go!
Origami is about to...
[gasps]
[KURUMI] Shido, what's going on?
What's wrong?
[SHIDO] Wait, why does
this feel so familiar?
[PHANTOM] When the time is
right, we should meet again.
[chuckles]
I promise you,
this time, I'll never let go.
I won't make
that same mistake again.
[SHIDO gasps]
[SHIDO grunts]
[coughing]
[KURUMI]
Are you okay, Shido?
Breathe.
[SHIDO]
Yeah, I'm fine.
Who the heck was she?
[grunts]
[SHIDO]
Don't tell me...
Origami!
[inaudible]
Don't, Origami!
[SHIDO]
No!
I won't let it.
I can't let that happen
to her again.
[SHIDO]
I will change the past!
Just hold on, okay?
I'm coming!
[ORIGAMI'S PARENTS]
Origami!
Mom and Dad. There you are.
No, Origami, don't!
[KURUMI]
There's no use, it's too late.
Dammit. No, it's not!
[KURUMI]
Shido, wait!
[SHIDO sighs]
I did it...
[SHIDO gasps]
What the...
Wait. Wasn't I...
Kurumi? Kurumi!
Did it work? Did I do it?
Was I able to save them?
[SHIDO]
Origami and her parents?