Does this mean I managed to
make the world a peaceful place?
[door clicks]
Oh, cool. You're already awake.
Good morning, Big Brother.
Kotori. You're all right!
What about Fraxinus?
How's the crew?
Is everyone okay?
Is it possible
you're still asleep?
Uh, no, I'm...
Hold on. What day is it?
Huh?
It's the third of November,
don't you know that?
If it's November third, then...
It's the day after
Origami went Inverse.
[SHIDO]
Thank goodness. What a relief.
What the heck?!
What's happening?!
[SHIDO]
I did it.
I managed to change
the world, after all.
[NARRATOR]
Daily life.
On the surface,
we think we know what it is.
Then, reality rears its head
and we discover
all is not as it seems.
--Ah.
--Uh...
Hey, there you are.
Morning, Shido.
Morning. Sorry to make you wait.
Here, don't freak out,
but I brought you
one of your favorites.
[gasps] That's right,
you were gonna cook
those bite-sized cutlets
for me, weren't you?
Huh?
Uh, isn't that what you said
you'd make yesterday
or am I not remembering right?
Yesterday?
[gasps]
Oh, right, I did.
Sorry, didn't end up
having those ingredients.
So I made you a rice bowl,
with sweet eggs, too.
Oh, my God.
That sounds so good right now!
Ohh! I mean, I literally...
[SHIDO] Does this world
have a whole different history
that I'm not aware of?
Well, what a nice morning.
It was good of you
to pick me up, servant.
Salutations.
Good morning, everyone.
Shido. Tohka. Kotori.
Yeah, hey. Morning.
What's with you?
If I didn't know better,
for a second there,
I would've sworn you were
totally checking out our boobs.
Explanation.
While gross, it still isn't
an unheard-of reaction
for a man.
Care to add anything, Shido?
[SHIDO]
Nope. I'm good, thanks.
--[school bells chiming]
--[STUDENTS murmuring]
[SHIDO]
Origami hasn't shown up yet.
[TOHKA]
Hmm...
Huh? What's the matter?
I don't know,
I can't explain it.
It's as if something
is incomplete.
Just kind of a weird feeling.
--Incomplete?
--[door rattles]
[TAMAE] Welcome.
Good morning, everyone.
--Suzuhara?
--[SUZUHARA] Here.
--Setouchi?
--[SETOUCHI] Here.
[SHIDO]
Is she absent today?
Or maybe
she's just running late.
[TAMAE]
Next is Tonomachi.
[TONOMACHI] Yo. Hiroto Tonomachi
is present and accounted for
and ready to face the day,
my love.
[TAMAE] Right. So, Tonomachi
is very much present.
--Next is Nakahara.
--[gasps]
What's wrong?
Did I say something weird
or are you just having a moment?
Um, no, I'm...
Her name should come
after Tonomachi's.
Sorry, but what about Origami?
Who's Origami?
I don't think I've ever known
anyone by that name.
[gasps]
Origami?
What the heck
kinda name is that?
What, did Itsuka, like,
fold a bunch of paper cranes
for the teacher?
[gasps] Hold on, does he think
he can steal my Tammie
with arts and crafts?
That's so lame.
[SHIDO]
Now I see.
I guess, here, in this reality,
Origami doesn't live
in the city.
The Origami of this world
probably doesn't hold
a grudge against Spirits.
She's just off somewhere
living happily with her parents.
It's better this way.
This is how
it always should've been.
[TOHKA]
Shido?
[SHIDO]
What's up, Tohka?
Are you all right?
Is something bothering you?
[SHIDO]
Huh?
[gasps]
Oh, no, I'm fine.
[SHIDO]
I hope that she's happy.
Though, I would've loved
to see her again.
Even just once.
To see this
new Origami, smiling.
[tapping]
What's going on? Is he okay?
[YOSHINON] Yeah, seems like
he's in the dumps.
Look at how zoned-out he is.
Has to be a girl.
[BOTH gasp]
What do you mean?
Why do you think that?!
I mean, I might be wrong,
so don't get
your panties all in a twist.
Hey! If you know, out with it.
It's just that when it comes
to the troubles
of high school boys,
you can lay money down on it
being about some girl.
Someone treating them badly
or not reciprocating
their feelings.
Typical guys worry about
these things all the time.
Really? They worry
about that stuff, too?
Yeah, even though,
when you ask
if they want to group up
for a project,
they say "Ew,"
and try to act all disgusted.
And when you pick up
their eraser they say,
"You can just keep it now
that you've touched it,"
or something dumb.
Hold on, back up a minute.
How the heck does a Spirit
like you know
so much about
student life, anyway?
Uh... Listen, the point is,
I think it's obvious
that something happened
to him at school.
He'll probably be fine
if we give him time,
but I can't help but worry.
[sighs]
Me too. It's tough seeing Shido
acting so depressed like this.
Isn't there anything
we can do for him?
I don't know what to tell ya.
I'll say one thing,
if it's girl trouble
that's giving Shido grief,
then the only thing to heal
his heart is another girl.
Huh?
Oops, too close.
Man, I've got to focus.
[KOTORI]
Hey, Shido, need some help?
Huh? Sure, thank you.
Why don't you wash...
[SHIDO]
What kinda outfits are those?!
And what's with those bodies?!
What? We all have a body,
what's the problem?
Yeah, she's right.
Don't think
about that right now.
What's important
is that we help.
Right, it's just that, um...
Natsumi! Was this your idea?!
Maybe it was, maybe it wasn't.
Wait a damn second.
Why aren't you in a bathing suit
like the two of us?!
I thought we all agreed that
we'd get dressed up together!
It's true, we did.
But once I thought about it,
I realized that wearing that
would be super embarrassing.
I was afraid I might
feel stupid, you know?
Girl, you're the one who gave us
these stupid outfits!
You little... Get over here,
I'll dress you myself!
Kotori, you have to calm down.
Ahh! I'm being violated!
You guys, would you
please knock it off?
--[glass shatters]
--[NATSUMI yelps]
[GIRLS screaming]
--[thud]
--[GIRLS groan]
Um, ow, that was rough.
Everyone good?
[ALL groaning]
[sighs]
You guys are killing me,
you know.
[sighs]
Well, I'm sorry about that.
I apologize, Shido.
Yeah, sorry.
No worries. I'm sorry
that I had you all concerned.
Thank you.
I really am better now.
I don't mean to pry
into your business or anything,
but, man,
get a hold of yourself.
After all, you never know
when another Spirit
is going to appear, right?
Yeah.
There are Spirits
we don't know about.
Not to mention the fact that
Kurumi and Devil are out there.
Wait, who's Devil?
I don't know that Spirit.
What are you talking about?
I mean
the Spirit Hunter, "Devil."
And if you thought
that Nightmare was bad,
this one can be
every bit as dangerous.
As bad as Kurumi?
Are you for real right now?
What the heck's
with you today, Shido?
It's almost as if
you've forgotten
everything up until yesterday.
[SHIDO] Sorry, could you go
over some info again?
The stuff about this Spirit
named Devil?
[KOTORI]
Ugh. Fine.
We've confirmed she exists,
but she's an unidentified Spirit
who's evaded all attempts
at contact so far.
Also, not surprisingly, I'd say,
Devil's an Inverse.
Wait, what do you mean?
An inverse Spirit
just shows up here sometimes?
Well, I'm trying to tell you,
we don't know very much
about her, yet.
Tell me this, though.
What's a Spirit Hunter?
It's just like it sounds.
Devil never shows up
anywhere on her own.
She only appears whenever
another Spirit manifests itself.
Then, suddenly, she's there
and she attacks them.
If Tohka and the others
hadn't helped her out,
Natsumi would've been
in big trouble.
Wait a minute. Is this her?
[KOTORI]
Yeah.
[SHIDO]
Origami...
[groans, sighs]
Shido, are you still sleepy?
Nah, I'm okay.
I just didn't get
much rest last night.
Oh.
[SHIDO]
Where is Origami?
She wasn't in her apartment.
And she wasn't at the house
where she lived
with her parents, either.
Why did she become a Spirit?
Why an Inverse?
[SHIDO] By changing history
five years ago,
I should've saved her
mom and dad.
[TAMAE]
Good morning, everybody.
I have an idea,
let's go all out today.
[SHIDO] What happened
during that five-year span?
What could've changed?
Oh, I almost forgot.
[SHIDO]
I can't do much alone.
Maybe if I explain what I know,
Ratatoskr will look into it.
If I could have your attention,
today, I have a new friend
to introduce to you all.
Go ahead, come on in, please.
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[gasps]
I'm Origami Tobiichi. Hello.
It's nice to meet you, everyone.
Look at that dazzling long hair
and that pure, innocent smile.
She's cute enough to give
my honey a run for her money.
Well, let's see. It looks like
the seat next to Itsuka is open.
Please, feel free to sit there.
Sure, thanks.
--[ORIGAMI] No way.
--[BOTH] Huh?
Don't I know you?
[SHIDO gasps]
[KOTORI]
What do you mean?
What makes you think Devil
transferred to your school?
I'll explain it later,
once I'm back home.
I swear it's true.
You have to believe me.
[KOTORI]
All right.
But I admit,
I'm not thoroughly convinced.
[SHIDO]
I get it.
[KOTORI]
I'll have Ratatoskr investigate.
What's the student's name?
Origami.
--Last name, Tobiichi.
--[KOTORI] Hold on.
Do you mean
Origami Tobiichi from the AST?
Wait. Kotori, do...
Do you remember the last world?
[KOTORI]
What are you talking about?
I know her because
she fought against Tohka
and the others
a bunch of times.
But she retired
not too long ago.
Now that you mention it,
it does seem like Tobiichi
left the AST
around the same time Devil first
started appearing regularly.
[SHIDO]
Why did Origami join the AST?
I saved her parents.
[KOTORI]
Are you even listening?
--Sorry, yeah.
--[school bells chiming]
Just tell me
if you find out anything.
[SHIDO]
I don't get it.
If I changed what happened
five years ago,
then why would she...
[SHIDO] Guess I'm gonna
have to ask her in person.
Was this for me?
Did you wanna
talk about something?
Yeah, sorry to bother you,
Origami. Thank you.
Uh...
Oops. Sorry. We haven't met yet.
I guess it's kinda rude
to talk as if I know you.
No. I just wasn't
expecting my first name.
And you're... Itsuka, right?
What is this about?
A question.
When you saw me this morning,
did you try to ask me something?
Oh. Sorry if that's
been bothering you.
It's just that
I was a little surprised.
The thing is, you look just like
someone I met a long time ago.
Huh?
[SHIDO]
You mean, could we have...
No, I don't think we've met.
The person I'm referring to,
I saw around five years ago.
You would've been
in elementary school.
Besides... that person
actually passed away.
Five years ago,
right before my eyes.
[SHIDO]
Oh, my gosh. She means me.
So, shouldn't we go back
to class now?
Uh, wait. Hold on a sec.
Five years ago.
This didn't happen during
the Nankou area fire, did it?
How did you know that?
[gasps] Oh, gosh, could that
have been your older brother
that I saw that day?
Well, something like that.
[sobs]
Huh?
What is it?
Ah! I owe him everything!
Your brother saved
both of my parents' lives.
If he hadn't been there,
my mom and dad
would've both died for sure.
I'm forever grateful.
Oh, sure.
That confirms it.
Sounds like I was able to save
Origami's parents, after all.
[gasps]
Sorry for blurting that out.
No, it's okay.
I'm so thankful for what he did
for them that day.
Even though,
as fate would have it,
my parents then died
in a car accident a year later.
No...
But thanks
to your wonderful brother,
that last year they were alive,
my mom and dad
were able to give me
so much love and happiness.
Wow. I'm glad.
[SHIDO] Is that the hand
of fate at work?
Are you okay?
[SHIDO] Well, I was
kind of wondering why
you joined the AST.
I mean, since they survived.
Wait, how did you know
about that?!
Oh. I don't know. I just, uh...
Did you go outside?
In the middle of
a spatial quake alarm?
You know
you're not allowed to do that.
Uh, yeah. That's what I did.
That's very dangerous.
You always have to evacuate.
Right, sure.
Would you like to know
the reason I joined the AST?
I would. But only if you
don't mind telling me.
[ORIGAMI] So, the fact that you
know about the AST has to mean
that you know the reason
for the alarms
in the first place.
The Spirits.
During the fire five years ago,
it was actually a Spirit
that killed your older brother.
But that was...
[ORIGAMI]
I kept thinking.
I didn't want more people to
have to suffer the way he did.
[ORIGAMI]
I wanted to become a person
who could protect others
from Spirits.
[SHIDO]
She did this because of me.
Can I ask you one more thing?
Yes, of course.
I'm just wondering
why you became a Spirit.
Huh? What are you talking about?
What does this mean?
--That had to be--
--[school bells chiming]
[ORIGAMI] Sounds like
lunch time's about over.
Thanks so much, Itsuka.
I'm glad we were able
to chat like this.
Hold on. Can't we talk
a little bit more?
But I think class
is about to start.
Some other day is fine.
If you're free sometime,
can I see you?
Huh? Like on a date?
Eh? Yeah. I guess so.
Thank you.
Do you think I could have
some time to think about it?
Uh, yeah, of course.
[ORIGAMI]
Thanks. Goodbye, then.
[SHIDO] So strange,
talking to her now.
Am I too used
to the other Origami?
Shido, where the heck did you
disappear to during lunch?
Oh, I just got
a call from Kotori.
She's fine with curry
for dinner.
Ah, that's terrific news.
My mouth's already watering.
[SHIDO]
Huh?
Saturday, huh?
Guess I need to have
that talk with Ratatoskr.
[yawns]
Oh!
[gasps]
Oh, man.
[yawns]
I'm so tired.
I'll just rest a bit.
[SHIDO groans]
[KURUMI]
My goodness.
[gasps]
Big boys like you
should watch where they sleep.
Dear Shido.
[yelps]
Kurumi?!
Heh. Last I checked.
Well, that was quite
the greeting, wasn't it?
Who knew you had such
a cute little sleeping face?
Eh. Uh...
[growls]
Uh-oh, what's wrong?
You know, I'm honestly
deeply hurt
that you seem
to fear me so much.
And here I thought
we were comrades
who were
changing the world together.
Kurumi, do you...
Yes, I remember everything.
All about the original world,
and about Origami, too.
Oh. Good.
Then tell me,
why did things end up this way?
What happened to Origami
in this world?
[KURUMI]
I'm afraid that's something
even I'm not aware of, Shido.
However, with Origami
the way she is now,
there are definitely
certain ways for us to find out.
Are there really?!
[KURUMI]
Indeed.
[growls]
[giggles]
Oh, come on, there's no reason
to be so scared.
[KURUMI] All I have to do is
shoot Yod at Origami.
Once I've done that,
I'll be able to see
all kinds of things
about what sort of life
she's lived in this reality.
You have Yod. That's right.
Then, I don't understand.
Why didn't you go ahead
and use Yod on Origami before,
back when she went Inverse?
[KURUMI]
Don't be silly.
Do you actually think I could
get close enough to her
at that point?
Look, whatever, forget it.
Let's do it now.
We can still find out
why she inversed
in this world, right?
Kurumi, please,
I need your help.
[KURUMI giggles]
Whatever shall I do with you?
[ORIGAMI]
Where could it be?
I don't get it.
How could I lose
my hair clip like this?
Huh? Wait, what if...
[footsteps]
Yes, I knew it.
This is where it was.
Thank goodness.
I should be more careful.
[SHIDO]
Please I need your help.
But in that case...
[ORIGAMI]
Is that Itsuka's voice?
Itsuka and who?
--[door creaks]
--[SHIDO] Uh. Huh?
[gasps]
Origami?
Uh... No, this... I can explain.
What's she doing?
One way to find out.
Let's see, how should
I greet you here in this world?
Do I say, "Nice to meet you"?
Though, it does seem
quite possible
that we've already run
into each other several times
before this moment in time.
I will... kill you...
[grunts]
Armor? I knew it.
I knew you were Devil!
Satan.
[gasps]
[grunts]
That's a pretty violent way
to greet a person.
No. Kurumi!
How... How could you do that?
[gasps]
What's the meaning of all this?
Meaning of what?
[ORIGAMI]
Itsuka?
[gasps]
What on earth
are you doing here?
In a place like this?
[gasps]