No way, impossible!
This is unreal.
How did you do that?
Whoa. What the...
He finished before you started.
That's so lame.
How weird.
[ORIGAMI]
What's going on with him?
[groans]
[ORIGAMI, TOHKA]
Shido!
[NARRATOR]
Spirits.
Special designation
disaster beings
that exist in a critical space.
Approach 1:
Annihilate them
by military force.
Approach 2:
Date them and make them
fall in love.
[pants]
It feels like I'm on fire...
[REINE]
It seems clear from my analysis.
It's as if the connection
between you and Shin
has drastically narrowed.
Therefore, it's hindering
the circulation
of your Spirit Powers.
[KOTORI]
So basically,
all that Spirit Power
is backing up
and starting to cause
Shido's body to overheat.
[ORIGAMI]
That makes sense to me.
Since it has nowhere to go,
it's stalling out in his body
giving him incredible powers.
Yeah, and it's possible
he'll go on a rampage
with all eight
of our Spirit Powers,
which would be the worst.
That would be terrible!
So what's our plan?
How are we going to save him?
The answer is quite simple.
Kiss him.
That's it.
Like, with lips?
It'll open the path
for Spirit Power to flow.
There's just one problem.
Your deadline is 12 tonight.
So you're saying
that by midnight...
...we all have to kiss Shido?
[ORIGAMI]
I can think of worse things
than having to kiss Shido
to save his life.
[SHIIZAKI]
Commander, bad news.
Shido seems to have escaped
from the infirmary.
[ELLEN gasps]
Is that Shido Itsuka?
[SHIDO]
Huh...? A woman...?
Right, a woman.
Gotta make her fall for me.
Can't forget to do my duty.
[ELLEN]
Ah...
[gasps]
Man, I've missed you
so much, Ellen.
Uh...
What in the actual heck
happened here?
[KAGUYA]
You don't think Shido did this?
[YUZURU]
Wonder. Such Spirit Power.
Luckily, we can track
where he is with the monitor.
Got him, let's go.
I don't get it,
how are you doing this?
You're in my Territory,
after all.
Don't be hostile, my dear, 'kay?
I just want us to understand
one another.
You jerk!
If you think this is funny,
you're wrong.
I'm not joking, though.
Who cares
if we're from different sides?
We can still love
one another, right?
Ellen, it's you I want.
You've officially gone too far!
[ELLEN grunts]
[gasps]
[SHIDO chuckles]
[SHIDO]
Look, don't be difficult, okay?
--See ya.
--[gasping]
Till we meet again. Ciao.
That's so humiliating!
You'll pay for this someday,
I swear it!
Cool. My body feels
as light as a feather.
What a great day.
Everyone's power
is surging inside me
and I feel like I could sing!
♪ I love you ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ I need you ♪
♪ The sky is blue ♪
♪ And my heart
is clear and bright ♪
Shido!
Oh, hey, Tohka.
Kotori. Everyone.
To what do I owe
this pleasure, huh?
Listen up, lover boy.
We're here to save
your dumb ass.
To save me?
Seriously?
You found me so you can kiss me?
That's right!
And mine's gonna be
a big ol' passionate smooch.
[SHIDO]
All right, then.
Though, I have a feeling
I'm gonna miss all this power.
I'll do it, on one condition.
What's with that smirk?
Listening.
Come on, let's hear it, then.
Before I had to get
each one of you to fall for me
in order to seal
your powers, right?
But this time, you have
to make me fall for you.
We do?
Huh?
I'll just be honest, though.
I already like all of you
girls plenty as it is.
So to say you have to
"make me fall for you"
isn't the most accurate.
Use any method you want
but make sure
my heart skips a beat.
Just enough that I can't wait
to give you a big kiss.
Cool?
[chuckles]
Right, make his heart
skip a beat.
Got it!
And make it good,
so that he'll want to kiss.
So be it. Get ready.
Ratatoskr is gonna go all out
to make you fall for us.
I'm honored.
I'm ready to start
whenever you are.
Let's get going real soon
and begin our date.
Our deadline
is midnight tonight.
So let's not waste time.
Shido...
Huh, nice.
Let's see
what you've got, ladies.
[TOHKA]
Hello!
[YOSHINO]
Oh, good, you're here.
[MIKU]
Darling!
[SHIDO]
You look great. All of you.
You went and picked out
swimsuits just for me?
I appreciate it.
Well, yeah.
I mean, of course we did.
Caution. It sounds like
you're falling for him now.
It's Shido's turn
this time around.
What? I know that, okay?
[KANNAZUKI]
Ratatoskr presents
the one and only,
heart-throbbing,
Fall in Love Dome.
[SHIDO]
A what now?
If you would, allow me
to explain the rules.
The Spirits will go
one at a time,
each trying to make
Shido's heart skip a beat
in their own erotic way.
While that happens,
we will, of course,
be closely monitoring
Shido's excitement level
here in the control room.
And once you've inspired him
to exceed a certain level...
[fanfare plays]
...you'll hear
fanfare like this,
which indicates a clear triumph.
Please note, the actual kissing
of Shido will occur
after everyone
has completed their turn.
As you know, the deadline
is 12 o'clock tonight.
Is all of that clear?
Got it down?!
[KOTORI] Listen, I wanna get
one thing straight
before we start.
This isn't the time to screw
around with our choices, got it?
Of course not, Commander.
Your lowly, unworthy dog,
Kyouhei Kannazuki
will surmount
dear Shido's defenses
no matter what it takes!
Okay, that wording
kinda creeps me out.
I have something
I'd like to say.
If we're using a beach, anyway,
I don't understand why
we didn't choose a nudist one
like I originally suggested.
--[gasping]
--Um, 'cause it's scary?
[ORIGAMI] But if our main goal
is to get Shido excited,
it'd be a lot more effective
to catch him off guard.
Just think about it,
if everyone was naked,
we would've already heard
that fanfare by now.
[KOTORI]
Look, that might be true
but there are lines
I'm not willing to cross
and this is one of them!
While I get
what you're saying, Origami,
I feel like that might have
the opposite effect.
His shock might actually
exceed his excitement.
I see. Guess I'll strip
bit by bit, then.
That's the way to do it!
I'd argue there are
many ways to proceed.
Origami and the vice commander,
they make a pretty good team.
Yeah, it seems like
they're always on
the same wavelength, doesn't it?
Must be all those hobbies
they both share.
Everyone ready?
Then let's get this conquest
of Shido underway.
Do we any volunteers
to go first?
Duh. A true warrior is always
the first to get to a battle.
Now, let's get
this ball rolling.
Honor. Kaguya and I
can get this done.
[KANNAZUKI]
All right!
The Yamai Sisters
are the first up to bat.
That's the Hurricane Children
for you.
Rushing ahead fiercely
like the wind.
[SHIDO]
Two girls at once, huh?
Be gentle with me, okay?
Kaguya. Yuzuru.
Sure, but prepare yourself.
You're about to fall
for us so hard, dude.
There's no doubt.
A knockout in a single round.
Here we go, everyone.
Please make your choice.
Huh, should it be one or two?
Aww! Why would you
ignore option three?!
Just do it!
Strap a rope around
his neck like reins!
It's the only way, you hear me?
You have to go with option three
and ride Shido like a human--
[KANNAZUKI]
Uh, g-guys?
What are you doing?
[gasps]
Coup d'etat? Revolution?
[KAWAGOE] The commander
left orders to tie you up
if you started
screwing around.
[KANNAZUKI]
Oh, what a commander!
In that case,
you can tie me up tighter.
What's wrong with you?
The left side is way too slack.
What does that idiot
even think he's doing?
I guess that means
it'll be number two
or the squeeze attack,
which is no big shocker,
if we're honest.
So, hey, guys.
--What's goin' on?
--[YUZURU, KAGUYA growl]
[SHIDO]
Hmm...
What do you think?
Like it, Shido?
Don't our feminine charms
make your heart go a-flutter?
Agreement.
It's no point in trying
to lie to yourself, you know.
Feel. See?
Of course,
what guy wouldn't like it?
But it's a little much
with both of you at once.
I can't really focus.
[KAGUYA, YUZURU]
Wha...
Dumbfounded.
Shido doesn't seem fazed
in the slightest.
But, hey, thanks anyway.
You're putting
so much thought into this.
I want you to know,
I appreciate it.
--[KAGUYA] Wait, we failed?
--Embarrassment.
And I feel cheated
for some reason.
[REINE]
Wait, cheer up, girls.
Appearances can be deceiving.
He may look composed
but his excitement
level's climbing.
Try choice two this time.
[SHIDO]
What gives?
You only got ice cream
for yourselves?
Not gonna lie,
I'm kinda bummed out.
[KAGUYA] Hmph. That's a
hasty conclusion, Shido.
Bestow.
One of these ice creams
is all for you.
One will be plenty for us.
We're used to sharing things.
Oh, well, thank you.
[YUZURU]
So sweet.
I can't get enough.
[REINE]
Sorry to interrupt,
but weren't you supposed
to be doing that with Shin
and not with each other?
--[KAGUYA] What?
--Awkward.
Now that you mention it...
[KAGUYA]
Oops.
Uh-oh.
[YUZURU]
It's so cold.
[KAGUYA moans]
[SHIDO gasps]
[fanfare plays]
[KANNAZUKI]
Yes! Today's very first fanfare.
Yamai Sisters.
You made that boy
fall for you hard.
He's not kidding.
You two really got me good.
[SHIDO]
So, next is Natsumi, right?
You volunteered to go
next all on your own?
Thank you for that.
Are you kidding?
The rest of us drew straws.
This condition
of yours is absurd.
The others might be able
to manage this,
but to make you fall for me?
It's not even possible.
That's definitely not true.
You're plenty cute, Natsumi.
[whimpers]
I can't do this now.
Hold on a sec.
[SHIDO]
Hmm?
[NATSUMI] Hey, let's play
some multiplayer, huh?
Okay, sure.
Wait, but Natsumi doesn't
even own the game, does she?
Meh, then she can
just play by herself.
How dare they?!
You chose that game
on purpose, you jerks!
Heh. Now I've got him
in the bag, for sure.
[REINE] Natsumi, it's dangerous
to use Spirit Power right now.
Revert back to your other form.
[NATSUMI]
It'll be fine.
I'm in a real swimsuit
and everything.
My guess is, he'll fall
for me within a minute.
Sorry you had to wait.
Worth it, though.
Natsumi, you look incredible.
[chuckles]
Well, thanks, sweet boy.
I can't blame you for being
interested in a big girl's body.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[screams]
[fanfare plays]
[KANNAZUKI]
Another success!
Natsumi's baggy suit and Shido's
pervy mind for the win.
Seriously?
Yoshino, what's that?
[YOSHINON] Oh, no worries,
it's nothing, right, Yoshino?
Huh.
--[gasps]
--[fanfare plays]
[KANNAZUKI]
Yoshino scores a success!
[SHIDO] Wow, look at this.
It is quite a shift in mood.
[KOTORI] I thought you might be
bored of the beach.
From now on, it's adult time.
Elegant, grown-up time.
They say that boys grow fast,
if I'm not mistaken.
But a woman can change
the very moment you look away.
Know what I mean,
dear big brother?
--[gasps]
--[fanfare plays]
[KANNAZUKI]
That's my commander!
Success!
[MIKU]
Darling?
I'm so glad I found you here.
Tonight, I'm gonna
sing a song just for you.
--[gasps]
--[fanfare plays]
--[KANNAZUKI] Miku, success.
--Huh?
But I didn't have a chance
to perform my song.
[SHIDO] Hey. I heard
that you were up next.
Yes, that's right.
I'm not gonna drink, okay?
No problem, alcohol-free.
Something the matter?
I don't know anymore.
Don't know what?
It doesn't matter.
[BOTH]
Cheers.
Ah...! That's definitely
alcohol-free.
What's wrong? You okay?
Oh, Itsuka...
How is it you manage
to be so handsome, anyway?
Itsuka...?
Hold on, are you that Origami?
I mean, does it really
make a difference to you?
Whenever I spend time
thinking about you,
I get all warm
and tingly inside.
And my heart seems
to get all full and tight.
Itsuka, I... I love you.
[gasps]
I love you so much that I hardly
even know what to do.
--[SHIDO gasps]
--[fanfare plays]
[KANNAZUKI]
Origami, success!
Well, that's seven of us clear.
It's just Tohka now.
Something wrong?
No, it's just that
when I heard Origami
talking about how much
she loved Shido,
I felt my chest
clenching up right here.
I know saving Shido
should be my priority, but...
I'm having a pretty hard time
letting go of this feeling.
These silly thoughts
keep getting in the way.
I don't think that's a silly
thought at all, though, Tohka.
Yeah. It's probably
the most important emotion
you'll rely on to save Shido.
I don't understand. It's scary.
Go on, we're counting
on you, okay?
Ah. Right.
I feel so weird. Why, though?
Origami said that drink
was non-alcoholic.
[TOHKA]
Sorry to make you wait.
Ta-da!
Oh, wow, that looks really good.
Well, I just figured
you might be hungry.
So, I brought every tasty food
I could find with me.
Shall we begin?
[SHIDO]
Sure, yeah.
[grunting]
Thank you.
[groans]
Shido!
--[gasps]
--[SHIDO groans]
--Shido!
--What?
What's going on?
--He okay?
--[alarm blaring]
[REINE] No, it happened
sooner than we thought.
Are you all right, Shido?
--Stay with us!
--[SHIDO] Go. Get away, Tohka!
Flashing Thunder Wave!
[TOHKA]
Shido!
[SHIIZAKI]
There are abnormal Spirit waves
practically pouring out of him!
His Spirit powers
are totally off the charts.
[MINOWA] His emotion readings
don't make any sense.
He's on a rampage!
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Spatial quake alarm.
Full danger.
[KAWAGOE] At this rate, we'll
have an even worse disaster
than the one we had
30 years ago.
Kotori, what are you doing?
We need to stop him.
Panic mode. It's officially
a race against time.
All right, then.
Looks like it's up to me.
[KOTORI] Ratatoskr made
Dainsleif specifically
because of this risk,
so we could eliminate
Shido if we needed to.
I'm so sorry, Big Brother.
Forgive me for having
no other choice but this.
What are you doing?
You must never use this, Kotori.
We'll find another way together.
[TOHKA]
I agree with Origami.
You're not alone, Kotori.
There's Origami and me,
Kaguya and Yuzuru,
Yoshino, Miku,
and Natsumi, too.
If we all put
our powers together,
I'm sure that we can save Shido.
[KOTORI]
Tohka. Origami.
[YOSHINON] If we don't slow
Shido down somehow,
we're never gonna catch up!
[NATSUMI]
Is that even possible, though?
[YOSHINO]
What can we do?
[grunting]
[KURUMI giggles]
I can be so whimsical
sometimes, can't I?
[KOTORI]
What happened?
This is our chance.
Yeah, I doubt we'll have
long to make it count.
Relax. It's plenty of time
for the Yamai Sisters.
Raphael. El Re'em!
Response.
Raphael. El Nahash!
[KAGUYA]
Shido, we're here to help you.
Grateful. After all, you're
the one who saved us first,
so now it's our turn.
[SHIDO snarls]
It'll be over soon.
Please hang on.
[NATSUMI]
There. Are you happy now?
[MIKU] Aww, you didn't even
try to make it a good one.
[giggles]
Now I've shared
an indirect kiss with Natsumi.
Come on now.
[screams]
Metatron.
[SHIDO grunts]
--Kotori!
--Big Brother, I'm sorry.
[KOTORI screams]
[screaming]
[yelling]
Shido!
Shido, I am your
final opponent.
[yells]
[YOSHINO]
Oh, my gosh.
[KOTORI]
We're out of time! Hurry!
[TOHKA yells]
[gasps]
Where'd her power go?
[grunts]
--Tohka!
--Stay back.
Don't worry,
and don't interfere.
I feel like it's important
for me to do this on my own.
[growling]
[yelling]
[TOHKA]
Oh, Shido...
Is it possible
that you've had to fight
against this kind of pain
and fear the entire time?
How did you stay strong?
How were you able
to keep reaching out
through so much chaos
to save us all?
[TOHKA]
Oh, now, I see.
I think this must be the feeling
everyone calls "love."
[TOHKA] But it's different from
how I feel for the others.
It's a love
that's only for Shido.
That's why...
Shido, I'm here.
[TOHKA groaning]
Hey, Tohka, sure you don't
want me to do that?
No, thanks.
This is important,
I'm the only one who didn't
get you to fall for me.
And so...
[SHIDO]
Tohka...
[TOHKA]
All done, Shido.
Tasty, right?
[SHIDO]
Mm! Yeah, it is.
Did it work?
Did your heart skip a beat?
[SHIDO]
You know, it totally did.
[gasps]