[MURDOCH'S ACCOMPLICE]
Humpty Dumpty will reach
the target area
in approximately five hours.
[MURDOCH]
And what about Westcott?
As we expected,
he hasn't left
his hotel room in Tengu City.
[snickers]
[NARRATOR]
A girl thinks,
"If only I could be
more honest,"
and she hopes with all her heart
that she can find
the courage she needs.
Wishing on every shooting star.
[SHIDO]
Maybe we went a little too far.
I didn't realize
she'd get that upset.
[screaming]
Don't worry. It's really
not as bad as you think.
Look, that's her mental state,
mood, and happiness.
They've all risen up
to much healthier levels.
[chuckles]
She's probably not used to
being complimented and stuff
when she's in her natural form.
Seriously, for someone
who's always so desperate
to be in the center
of the action,
girl has zero self-confidence.
You know, now you mention it,
Natsumi talked about
how nobody ever paid attention
to her in her true form.
Sounds to me like
a few bad experiences
might've really done some damage
to her sense of self-worth.
Her beauty isn't
the real issue here.
I think, in general,
Natsumi just needs
to feel accepted for who she is.
Those liars.
They don't mean any of it.
Haniel, now.
I'll find out the truth.
Tohka, Yoshino.
--Huh?
Uh, hi, Kotori.
Are you taking a break, too?
[KOTORI] Hey, can I ask
you guys a question?
What do you think
about that Natsumi girl?
Think, meaning...?
You know, I mean, how gross
can you actually get?
She's so ugly that it's hard
not to pity her, right?
--Huh?
Kotori, what are you
talking about?
This isn't like you.
Uh...
Excuse me, but I don't think
Natsumi's gross or ugly at all.
[YOSHINON]
Hear, hear.
[KOTORI] Wait, what are you
even talking about?
You must be blind because
that girl is a hot mess.
She's an eyesore.
[KAGUYA]
Huh?
Hey, what's going on in here?
What's up, Kotori?
You don't seem
like yourself today.
It's not me that's off.
They've been saying
weird things.
[YUZURU] Doubt.
What kind of weird things?
Like, that Natsumi
is actually pretty
and not the pain in our
collective butts that she is.
If you ask me, the only one
saying bizarre stuff is you.
Puzzled. That doesn't sound
like something you would say.
Yeah, you really shouldn't be
talking about Natsumi like that.
--Hmph!
--[chuckles]
[KAGUYA laughing]
[NATSUMI]
No way, it can't be.
This means...
[TOHKA]
Kotori, wait.
[grunts]
Kotori? I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Uh...
You seem down. Everything cool?
[KOTORI]
I'm fine, all right? Jeez.
Hey, by the way,
I had a thought
about Natsumi earlier.
Here it comes.
At last, I'll get the truth.
I'm wondering if we should let
her out of the room for meals.
[gasps]
[SHIDO] I've just been
thinking about it a lot
and, well, she's gotta be
lonely eating by herself.
But if she got to sit down
to eat meals with everyone else,
I think Natsumi might
actually warm up to us.
[gasps]
Oh, no. Hey, what's the matter?
Did I say something
to upset you?
[NATSUMI]
Just shut up, you idiot!
[sobbing]
Wait. Kotori!
Uh...
Whoa, that girl
never leaves candy behind.
--What's going on with her?
--[cell phone ringing]
Kotori?
--Hey, what's up with you?
--[KOTORI] Huh?
What are you talking about?
Never mind,
there's an emergency.
It's Natsumi.
She's escaped from the facility.
[SHIDO]
Dammit.
I've looked everywhere,
but no sign of her.
I doubt she's here,
but it's worth a shot.
[gasps]
Natsumi!
Thank goodness, here you are.
[SHIDO]
You're...
Hello, there.
Pardon me for intruding.
Ellen? What are you doing here?
Social call?
After all, what would
the great DEM want
with little old me?
I came to ask you a question.
Something you wanna know?
Indeed.
The Spirit you took away
with you
the other day called Witch,
where is she?
We need her location.
There's no way in hell
I'd tell you that!
Is that so?
Your place is very nice.
I imagine you're all one big,
happy family together here.
[ELLEN]
That sweet bunch.
Are you prepared to lose them?
[SHIDO gasps]
I'll ask you one more time.
In return for
the continued safety
of the other six Spirits,
tell me where I can find Witch.
[KOTORI]
Any reaction from Natsumi?
[MINOWA]
Nothing at Point A.
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Same goes for Point B.
That's not good.
If she's wary of us,
she might decide to stay hidden
and refuse
to show herself again.
[MINOWA]
Hmm. This is interesting.
--Natsumi?
--No, but it's peculiar.
It could be a satellite based
on its altitude and trajectory.
That's odd, though.
Why would something like that--
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Commander.
There's magical power,
but it's faint.
It looks like explosive magic!
[gasps]
[MINOWA]
Enlarging the image.
Freakin' Bandersnatch.
Oh, joy.
[KOTORI gasps]
Don't tell me...
[cell phone buzzing]
Yes.
Very well, then.
I'll handle everything here.
Today is your lucky day,
Shido Itsuka.
[KOTORI]
Have you found Natsumi?
[SHIDO]
Nope. Had a little trouble.
[KOTORI]
Shido, I need you to listen.
You're not going to believe this
but please trust me.
In a dozen or so minutes,
a satellite will crash
into Tengu City.
[gasps]
Wait, back up for a second.
'Kay. Explain.
[KOTORI]
There's no time now.
It's dangerous
to be above ground.
Get yourself to
the nearest shelter, okay?
[SHIDO]
And the others?
[KOTORI]
Don't worry about them.
The debris won't leave a scratch
where they're at, I promise.
--Debris?
--[KOTORI] Yeah.
We're blasting it
to smithereens.
[KOTORI]
Keep searching for Natsumi
as long as you possibly can.
But if you can't find her,
you have to evacuate before
it's too late, you hear me?
[SHIDO]
Yeah. I got it.
[KOTORI]
I'm counting on you, Shido.
--Kotori.
--[KOTORI] What?
Thanks a lot.
[KOTORI]
That's my line, dork.
[line beeping]
--[screaming, shouting]
--[alarm blaring]
[SHIDO]
Natsumi! Natsumi!
Please, answer
if you can hear me!
Where are you?!
Any minute, satellite debris
is gonna come crashing down!
It's dangerous to be out here.
Let's get to
an underground shelter, okay?!
I know where to go,
just follow me!
Are you listening?
Please, Natsumi!
Look, I swear, we won't
shut you up in a room anymore.
When this is all over, you can
go wherever you want, all right?
Okay?!
[NATSUMI]
Why go this far for me?
Especially since the one
you're searching for
is the disgusting real me.
I was desperately
trying to ruin your life.
I managed to erase your friends.
And tons of other
unmentionable things.
So why is it you care
for me so much?
[SHIDO]
Natsumi!
[MINOWA]
Commander, the satellite!
It's time.
Calculate the impact area.
[NAKATSUGAWA, MINOWA]
Roger!
Ready? Let's blow
this thing out of the sky.
--[SHIDO] Natsumi!
--[alarm blaring]
[panting]
Natsumi.
Come on, where are you?
I'm right here.
I'll help you!
[KOTORI]
Mistilteinn, fire!
[ALL gasp]
How in the hell...?
Yes, that's odd.
I've never heard of anything
like that before.
Bandersnatch Territory
deflecting Mistilteinn?
--[explosion]
--[BOTH gasp]
What the...
[NAKATSUGAWA]
Incoming from 12 o'clock.
Displaying now.
--Isn't that...
--[growls]
Commander?
Well, that's a kink, isn't it?
Kannazuki,
I'm leaving you in charge.
Commander.
Now then, shall we get started?
It's time to go to war.
[KOTORI]
Camael...
...Megiddo.
And away we go.
[KOTORI]
Gungnir!
Fire!
--[KOTORI growls]
--[REINE] A hit?
[MINOWA]
Target eliminated. Success!
--Woo-hoo!
--[NAKATSUGAWA] Yeah!
[KOTORI panting]
[alarm beeping]
[NAKATSUGAWA]
I-It's a satellite.
Another satellite
has just appeared!
[growls]
Camael...
[KANNAZUKI]
Commander?
[KOTORI gasps]
[KANNAZUKI]
Commander, any more and...
[KOTORI panting]
Kotori, what are you...
[KOTORI]
A second one.
We'll recover you with Fraxinus,
so stay put for now.
And the shelter?
[SHIDO]
You can't mean...
I haven't found her.
[KOTORI]
Please.
Please save yourself, Shido.
You have to forget
about me, okay?
[gasps]
Shido, where are you?
--Shido!
--[TOHKA] Kotori.
What's going on?
[YOSHINO]
What's happening?
[YOSHINON]
In a little pinch, are we?
[KAGUYA laughs]
What a sad sight, people.
Getting all kinds of worked up
over nothing.
[YUZURU] Agreement.
Everyone try to remain calm.
[MIKU] So, wait. Is that thing
the satellite, then?
[gasps]
You guys, what are you...
Kotori, I'm not seeing
Shido anywhere.
--[KOTORI] Shido is...
--Talk to me.
What do we do?
Just say the word
and we'll help out.
[ALL]
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
So much... Everyone...
Please go and
protect my brother!
I beg you!
[SHIDO]
It's up to me, then.
Come on.
Lend me your power. Sandalphon!
[SHIDO]
Here we go.
[yells]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[SHIDO groans]
--[YOSHINO] Shido.
--[SHIDO gasps]
Wait. Tohka?
What are you doing here?
Simple. Kotori said that
you were in a bit of trouble
so we had her send us.
[SHIDO]
Oh, wow. And Kotori?
They're all busy fighting off
the enemy airship.
But don't worry,
I think they can handle it
on their own just fine.
[SHIDO] Man, I honestly thought
I'd be a goner.
[ALL gasp]
Good grief, this is
really next-level.
Outrage. Can't they just
leave well-enough alone?
Well, we won't let them
do as they please.
What are you...
[WESTCOTT]
Ellen, how nice to see you.
There's no time for this.
You need to get out of here.
Those rebels
on the board of directors
are trying to kill you.
[WESTCOTT]
I know all of that.
[ELLEN]
Then why are you--
Quite simply because
I believe they will fail.
What's wrong?
Don't you trust me?
All right, just in case,
we'll send her to the scene.
What do you mean?
[WESTCOTT] It can be
a little test of sorts.
Gabriel March!
It's incredible, isn't it?
Man, I knew I liked this song.
I am about to get
crazy pumped up.
Affirmative.
Very nice assist, by the way.
Look at it.
Tohka, help me out.
Let's destroy that hunk of junk.
We can do it together.
--[TOHKA] No, we can't.
--[gasps] Why not?
What are you talking about?
I don't know the details.
But that satellite has some kind
of explosive magic on it.
So unless we destroy it
higher in the atmosphere...
[KAGUYA laughs]
Have you forgotten who we are?
We're the Yamai sisters.
The hurricane children.
This is what we do.
Solemn pledge.
We're gonna blow it away. Ready?
--That's right.
--With all my might.
[BOTH]
Take this!
[BOTH gasp]
Ouch!
[groans]
[MIKU]
Hold on!
--Tohka, the others.
--Right.
Ragh!
--[YOSHINO] Tohka.
--You okay?
[BOTH gasp]
--Let's go.
--Got it.
[NATSUMI]
It's okay.
I know it'll all
work out somehow.
Just like it did
that other time.
[NATSUMI]
It's fine.
Someone will swoop in
and help them, I know they will.
Come on, show up, already.
Someone will. They have to.
Shido!
[gasps]
Uh, what the hell?
Natsumi!
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
Look, you've gotta
hurry it up.
Huh?
You're trying to destroy
that big thing, right?
--Yeah.
--[MIKU screams]
What you waitin' for?
Go ahead and smash
the dumb thing.
But that's really dangerous.
It's got explosive magic.
[NATSUMI]
Hmph. Haniel!
[gasps]
[SHIDO]
What the hell?
--[gasps]
--There you go.
Surely you can
manage it from here, right?
--Tohka.
--Let's go.
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH gasp]
[SHIDO]
Was that because of them?
[NATSUMI]
Kaleidoscope!
Natsumi, are you sure?
[NATSUMI] What do you think
you're doing messing with Shido?
You should know the only one
allowed to do that is me.
And don't you forget it!
[SHIDO]
You guys, thank you.
If it had just been me,
I could never have saved
everyone in the city.
Thank you for everything.
--Natsumi.
--[NATSUMI gasps]
What is it now?
Are you super disgusted
that I changed into a lollipop
and hid in your pocket?
Or are you upset
that I didn't come help sooner?
[SHIDO]
I'm glad you're okay.
That's weird.
You don't make sense.
I literally hid myself away
and just watched
as you all panicked.
[SHIDO chuckles]
And before that,
I did really terrible things
to everyone here, too.
You're nice. I don't get it.
Why? What's your deal?
Every last one of you.
[sobbing]
Such dummies...
[wails]
Hey, what's wrong?
It's okay.
I'm so sorry for doing
all those things to you...
Causing you so much trouble,
when none of you have ever been
anything but nice to me
from the start...
Which made me happy...
...but I was too proud
to thank you...
I'm so sorry.
So, thank you. Really.
--[sobbing]
--Don't worry about it.
Besides, you seriously
saved our lives just now.
Hey, don't cry.
Remember how I promised
you could go
anywhere you wanted
once this was over?
You're one of us now.
I hope you'll be my friend.
[chuckles]
[NATSUMI sobbing]
[NATSUMI wailing]
[SHIDO]
Natsumi?!
[whimpering]
Ugh, men.
Darling, whatever you're doing
is making Natsumi cry a lot.
What? Hey, I didn't do it.
Well, I can't leave Natsumi
in the hands of someone
who only makes her upset.
So I'll just have to be
friends with her, too.
That's right, there's no more
teasing Natsumi.
I'll gladly be your friend, too.
Me, too. I'd love that.
Yeah, you can be
my new kinswoman.
Agreement. And that means
we will always protect you.
Okay, wait a minute.
Why are you all making me out
to be the bad guy?
--[GROUP chuckles]
--[overlapping chatter]
[SHIDO] I wasn't teasing
anyone to begin with!
[chuckles]
[TOHKA]
Apologize to her.
[SHIDO]
Give me a break.
Good work, guys. Thank you.
Huh?
So, um, hey.
Could I just ask you...
Do you...
Do you really think
that I'm cute?
Of course I do.
You're very cute, Natsumi.
Um, thank you.
Could you teach me
how to do makeup?
Sure. I guess Shiori
could help you with that.
Okay.
Natsumi?
About sealing me,
how would we do that?
Uh...
Um, well, we'd just...
[whispering]
[screams]
'Kay, well, that's embarrassing.
I guess there's not
really a choice.
[yelps]
[NATSUMI growls]
No one thought
it was a good idea
to warn me my armor
would disappear?
Shido, what were you even
thinking in a place like this?
[YOSHINO] Um, I didn't
see anything, if that helps.
Hah! Sealing in the middle
of a city, huh?
That sure is
one interesting fetish.
Agreement.
Using an emptied-out city
to play out
your deepest, darkest desires
is quite the unique idea, Shido.
True. Darling really
is a bold one, huh?
What's wrong, Kotori?
Are you serious?!
Huh?
Hey, what's happening, Shido?
It would appear
this isn't over yet.
Another bomb
is on its way down.
[ALL gasp]
[SHIDO] I'm all out of strength,
but I've gotta try to stop it.
[ALL groan]
Now what?
It can't be. No way.
[SHIDO]
Origami...?