[beeping]
[gasps]
Kommandeur!
We're reading an unidentified
Extar over on Point 2-3-2.
You sure it's just the Extar?
No Liberators nearby?
Positive. Scans don't
turn up anything else.
[alarm blares]
[gasps]
What's that thing?
It's growing before our eyes.
I've never seen
anything like it before!
My God...
[MAMORI] ♪ This little mushroom
is a little mushroom boy. ♪
♪ Come out, come out,
little mushroom boy! ♪
♪ This little mushroom boy
is a little mushroom! ♪
♪ Come out, come out,
little mushroom. ♪
Wait, hold on!
Ah?
I bet I know what
you're thinking, Mirei.
"Mushrooms can't walk.
Why sing that silly song?"
That's why you're
staying quiet, right?
What? Um, no.
Jungle rule. It's important
that we're always singing
in order to scare off any
man-eating animals around.
For example, bears easily
frighten when they hear
high-pitched melodies,
limericks,
or commercial jingles.
--Even, a-- [gasps]
--[MIREI growls]
So it's you two.
What're you doing now?
[MIREI grunts]
Let me give you some
friendly advice:
Stay away from
this part of the island.
And now that you know better,
pass that on to the other girls
--staying with Miss Torino.
--[booming]
[gasps]
[MAMORI]
Whoa. What was that?
[ALL grunting]
[KASUMI gasps]
[gasping]
[MAMORI]
Nooo!
[NIMI sobs]
Miss... Kasumi!
[ALL grunting]
[NIMI sobbing]
[KASUMI]
I know you.
You're Miss Minimi, right?
Yeah. It's Nimi Minimi.
You know this... giant?
Uh. Sorta.
She arrived with another
girl before you two,
but she was normal size.
Not many girls arrive
here two-at-a-time,
so big or small,
she's hard to forget.
Miss Minimi, what exactly
happened to your body?
[NIMI]
So... It's a long story.
Do you have a minute?
[NIMI]
Before we were brought here,
Noe and I were on
the same softball team.
I caught and she pitched.
[NOE grunts]
[UMPIRE]
Strike three, you're out!
That's game, ladies!
Nimi!
Noe!
[NIMI giggles]
But then, I guess,
somewhere along the way,
they found out we were both
carrying the Armed Virus.
So they kidnapped us and
dropped us on this island.
[sighs]
[NIMI]
I was scared and homesick,
but I also knew that
as long as I had Noe,
as long as we remained
a team, I would be okay.
So, the other day, we
became more than a team.
We joined in body and soul.
How sweet.
They're in love.
That's right.
But no matter what she touched,
it couldn't get me to Drive!
I can't tell you how many
days we spent grinding away,
but my powers never came.
And that's when Miss Charlotte
gave us the news.
[NOE] What?! You want her
to marry someone else?
You're breaking us up?!
Another girl will
get to Drive Nimi?
That's not fair...
Don't do this...
[CHARLOTTE] I'm afraid
you've left me no other choice.
If a Liberator can't activate
her Extar's powers,
then we must re-assign her
to someone who can.
[NOE]
Give us more time!
I won't argue over
the finer points
of Liberator-Extar doctrine.
I've made up my mind,
and you two are splitting up.
[NIMI] I was so sad.
All I could think of to do
was leave the castle.
I ran deep into the woods until
I collapsed from exhaustion.
But then, when I
woke up this morning,
I was like this! A giant!
Can you help me?
I've lost everything,
including my clothes!
I'm as lost as she is.
[receiver beeps]
This is Kasumi.
Yes, that's right.
I'm at the spot where
the radar said it was.
It looks like...
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Don't tell them!
It looks like nothing
to worry about.
Just a glitch in the radar.
I'll keep searching the area
to be safe, though,
and check back in
the mid-afternoon.
[gasps]
Hey. Sleepyhead.
You think the new girls who went
looking for mushrooms are okay?
[MEIFENG]
Of course they're okay!
As long as Mirei's one of the
two girls we're talking about.
[TORINO]
'Kay...
[MEIFENG]
Who knows?
She's so powerful,
they might start looking for
bigger game than mushrooms!
Just imagine how cool it'd be if
they come back with a crocodile!
[booming]
[BOTH gasp]
[booming continues]
[MEIFENG squeals]
It's a giant girl!
[MAMORI]
Hey! We're back!
Yo!
It's... nice to meet you.
--[TORINO whimpers]
--Oh... Oh, wow,
that girl is way bigger game
than a crocodile.
--[gasping, murmuring]
--[GIRL A] A real giant!
[TORINO]
I understand completely.
If things were getting
that uncomfortable for her
at the castle, she's
welcome to stay with us
for as long as she wants.
Thanks, I owe you one.
You owe me nothing.
Protecting girls is
the purpose of this town.
It's a refuge for anyone
fleeing the Veste.
Hey, you! Your name's
Nimi, right?
Um, yes, ma'am.
I guess I'm sort of the mayor
of this little jungle town.
I'm Torino Kazami. But you
can just call me "Big Sis."
Oh, okay! My Big Sis!
[TORINO]
Well. First thing's first:
Let's find you some clothes!
We don't want you
catching cold.
Or distracting the other girls
with that body of yours.
Ah. Yes, Big Sis.
[GIRLS murmuring]
Where the heck did
you get all this fabric?
[TORINO]
Oh. A friend gave it to--
[gasps]
[grunting]
[MEIFENG gasps]
[hums]
Have we met before?
Nope, you must be
thinkin' of someone else.
I'm a wild girl who
lives in the jungle.
Got no attachments to anyone
or anything at the Veste.
[KASUMI]
Hmm...
[sighs]
All right, there's our pattern.
Now it's time to cut!
Have at it, girls!
Go do your thing!
Ah! Um... Uh, what do you
mean, "do our thing"?
Don't play dumb.
You know what she means.
Get with the kissy
--and the touchy-touch.
--[BOTH] C'mon, girls!
Start kissing!
[gasps] What does this
have to do with anything?!
[MEIFENG] It has to do with
getting her clothes
so she doesn't have to
walk around buck naked!
Yeah, that is a good
reason, I guess...
[MIREI]
Hmm.
[gasps]
[TORINO] Oh, come on,
Mamori. Just try it.
[MAMORI] Yeah, but... it's hard
when everyone's watching you.
[MEIFENG] God! Would you
quit being such a prude?!
Now, go!
Sorry, about that.
[MAMORI gasps]
[moans]
[MAMORI]
[GIRLS gasping, sighing]
[NIMI sighs]
[KASUMI grunts]
[MAMORI moaning]
[MAMORI] I wonder why
this keeps happening.
I mean, it's just a kiss,
but every time she does it,
my whole body starts tingling.
And getting hotter...
like it's about to... explode!
[MAMORI gasps]
[screams]
[MAMORI]
♪ Ahh... ♪
[MIREI grunts]
[NIMI] Heh. It's just
what I needed, guys.
But, um... do you think
it shows too much skin?
Sorry, Nimi. We did the
best we could for you
with the fabric we had.
Well, we certainly
won't forget this sight!
Cup size Triple Z!
--[loud rumbling]
--[MAMORI gasps]
Ah! Oh! Pardon me.
I haven't eaten a thing
since I left the castle.
And that was yesterday morning!
--[TORINO] Hmph!
--[MAMORI, MEIFENG gasp]
[NIMI sighs]
Wow! Thanks!
Well, girls, watching our giant
guzzle six barrels of curry
has gotten my own
tum-tum growling.
Miss Torino, you mind
making us some lunch, too?
I can't. I used up
everything here
making that supersized curry.
[gasping]
Don't worry! I'll help you!
I'll repay you for everything
you've done for me,
from bikini to food.
Okay. Just tell me
what to get and I'll get it!
Get any handsier with that oil,
and I'm gonna Drive.
[moans]
Try to hold it in.
It'll make the release
that much sweeter. 'Kay?
You're such a good Extar.
[KOUZUKI moans]
[MIYASATO]
Mmm...
Huh?
Hmm...?
What the hell is that thing?
[KOUZUKI]
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
[KOUZUKI, MIYASATO scream]
[BOTH]
Huh?!
Hey, I'm sorry if
she scared you guys!
[MIYASATO]
Huh?
[KOUZUKI] Hey! You're that chick
named "Virgin," aren't you?
[MAMORI growls] For the
last time, my name is Tokonome!
[MAMORI]
Wow! I sure do love fresh tuna!
Thanks for cooking, Miss Torino!
Ah! Anything for my girls.
[MAMORI] And thank you
for catching it, Nimi.
I'm just returning the favor!
[sighs]
It's so nice out...
If we had bathing suits, we
could spend the rest of the day
swimming in the ocean.
[MEIFENG]
Get your swimsuits!
I got all sizes,
colors, and brands!
[MAMORI]
Wow! Right on cue, Meifeng!
Ah. Oh, right. Cash money.
Not free, huh?
[MEIFENG]
Pony-up!
[MAMORI]
Well, how do I look?
Does it fit in all
the right spots?
[NIMI gasps]
It's perfect!
Too tight.
[TORINO]
Too bad, because mine has
just the right
amount of jiggling!
[BOTH laugh]
[MAMORI yelps]
[screams]
[BOTH giggle]
[GIRLS laughing, murmuring]
[MAMORI laughs]
[TORINO]
Whee!
I'm jealous...
That looks so fun.
[MIYASATO]
Awesome!
[KOUZUKI squeals]
Even those two are playing?
[KASUMI]
Anyway.
I still haven't figured out why
Miss Minimi became a giant.
Has the Armed Virus mutated?
Or is it related to her
problem with finding
a Liberator who can Drive her?
[KASUMI groans]
Oh, I'm sorry!
Are you okay, Miss Kasumi?
[KASUMI]
You wanna play ball...?
Let's play ball!
--[MAMORI yelps]
--[MEIFENG grunts]
Hey, what'd I do...?
[KASUMI] Noe Oya.
Nimi Minimi's ex-Liberator.
Refused marriage to a new
partner... put in a dungeon?
Damn you, Charlotte. Why are
you so hard on these girls?!
[NOE] Nimi, you idiot.
You shouldn't have run away...
[MAMORI groans]
I gotta go pee...
[NIMI sobbing quietly]
[MAMORI gasps]
[sobbing continues]
[NIMI]
Noe... I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
Poor Nimi...
[NIMI squeals, screams]
[BOTH gasp]
--[GIRLS murmuring]
--[NIMI sobs]
Well...
They always say a good night's
sleep makes a woman healthy.
We gotta do something!
What if she keeps growing
every night, forever?
[NIMI]
Yeah...
[ALL gasp]
Please help me...
If I don't get back to normal,
the world will treat me
like a... monster!
[NIMI screams]
--[gunfire]
--[missiles whistling]
[NIMI whimpers]
And if all that
isn't bad enough,
I'll never get to be
romantic with Noe again!
[NIMI sobs]
Hey, stop crying!
[gasping]
[MAMORI] If you want to see
Noe so bad, go see her!
No one's stopping you!
[NIMI]
It's not that I can't do it,
it's that I've gotten so big.
I don't know what I would say
without scaring her!
So just go! You'll say the
right thing once you see her!
You guys were best friends
before you came to this place!
Your connection is unbreakable!
Just go to her and
pour out your heart.
[NIMI]
Really? It's that easy?
[MAMORI]
Mm-hmm.
[NIMI grunts]
I'll do it! I can't keep
running away like this!
I'm going to see Noe!
And I'm not afraid
to let it all hang out!
[MAMORI gasps]
You sure it was okay
to rile her up?
Huh?
It's just... when she shows up
at Veste looking like that,
people will snap!
[gasps]
Wait, Nimi! Come back!
Go faster! We gotta catch up!
Come on, floor it!
I'm going as fast
as the truck will go!
[receiver beeps]
What's up? Did you find--
Kommandeur! The giant's
attacking us! It's real!
[gasps]
[GIRLS screaming]
She's gotten bigger!
[KASUMI]
If she charges us,
she could bring down
the whole castle!
I got no choice... Sorry...
[tires screech]
[growls]
[NIMI squeals]
[NIMI groans]
[CHARLOTTE coughs]
What on earth was that?!
[CHARLOTTE]
Huh?!
Huh...?
[NIMI yelps]
[CHARLOTTE grunts]
[NIMI whimpers]
[shrieks]
Nimi!
We missed our chance!
[CHARLOTTE] I don't know
how you got this big...
...but I do know why
you're attacking me!
It's all about trying
to marry you off!
No. I'm not here about that.
I just wanted to--
[CHARLOTTE]
Keep lying like that!
I don't care how big you are--
I'll crush you myself! Hah!
Ready, Miss Charlotte.
[gasps]
[SOLDIER B]
I'm ready, too, Miss Charlotte.
[moaning]
[SOLDIERS moan]
[NIMI whimpers]
All right. Let's do this.
[screams]
[KASUMI]
Stop!
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
[boom]
What's going on up there?
[MAMORI] Miss Noe? Hello?
Is there a Noe here?
Friends with a girl named Nimi?
[NOE]
I'm Noe!
[BOTH gasp]
Your partner Nimi is in trouble!
You have to come with us!
I can't! Notice the bars?
'Less you got a key, I'm stuck.
[MAMORI growls]
Wait! I know what to do.
Mirei?
[gasps]
[MIREI]
Haah...!
Let's go!
Charlotte, stop!
You'll hurt her!
[CHARLOTTE] Miss Kasumi, you're
standing in my line of attack.
Get out, or get hurt!
[KASUMI]
Charlotte!
[gasps]
That's... Sri!
[CHARLOTTE]
Gouverneur Akira's Arm!
Using force right away
is never smart management.
[NOE]
Nimi!
[gasping]
Noe, I came back!
[NOE]
Nimi, why?
[gasps]
It just happened one day.
Every morning I'm bigger
than the night before!
They tried to make me
a giant bra and panties,
but when I grew,
they snapped off.
[NOE]
I don't care about any of that!
What I was asking is
why did you leave me?!
You're mad...?
[NOE] Remember what
we promised each other
when we first got
to this island?!
No matter what happens, we'll
get through this--together.
But then... you broke that
vow... You left me all alone!
[sobs]
You're a jerk!
[gasps]
Noe...
[NOE]
But you also complete me.
Nimi, you're the only one
who can catch my fastball.
Only-- Only you can catch
my body and soul!
Noe!
[MAMORI gasps]
Nimi shrunk.
[AKIRA] So everything
worked out in the end.
[CHARLOTTE]
Gouverneur...
Miss Charlotte. You were too
quick to decide that Noe
could never activate
Nimi's abilities.
What? I didn't see
any abilities!
Nimi's Extar power is
growing to super-sizes.
[CHARLOTTE] So, what, you want
me to admit that I was wrong,
is that it, Gouverneur?
[AKIRA] Since there was
a lag in her activation,
your mistake is
somewhat understandable.
But now, having seen
what they're capable of,
I think we can both agree
that Nimi and Noe
are meant to be together.
[growls]
They do make such a cute couple.
For once, everything
worked out fine.
That's right.
[MIREI]
Hmm...
[gasps]
Oh. Mirei?
Don't worry, Mamori.
We'll see them again.
We're all here--together.
[gasps]
That's right.
[MAMORI]
"No Money, No Life."