[RESEARCHER A]
Test subject C7.
Liberator abilities are
slightly above average.
But her natural athleticism
is extraordinary.
It's for this attribute that
she's been selected
for enhancement.
[A]
And her partner?
[RESEARCHER A]
We plan to use A3.
[MOMOKA]
You must be C7, right?
It's nice to meet ya.
They call me A3, and it looks
I'm gonna be your new Extar.
I've already
finished enhancement.
It changes an awful lot,
even the color of your hair!
A3. Is that you?
Long time no see. Eh, C7?
Why... would she call you that?
Y'know, I was under
the impression that
they'd gotten rid of you.
You'd think that a secret
organization would know
how to tie up loose ends,
and yet here you are.
So how did you do it?
Ya make use of all
your physical assets?
Seduce the men with that
bikini model bod to survive?
[MIREI grunts]
Between you and me, I'm
really glad you're alive.
I really mean that...
from the bottom of my heart.
Know why?
'Cause if you're alive,
then you can still die!
And I've always wanted
to off you myself!
[MOMOKA chuckles]
I was trying to make the
most of this mission before
but now that I've got you
here, I don't have to.
Tell me, C7, do you
believe in fate?
I wasn't sure before,
but after this reunion,
how can I doubt it?
I mean...
This was destined.
You know I'm right;
you can feel it.
What does this mean? Françoise?
Miss Sagara!
Explain what you are!
You're wielding an Arm, but how?
You're an Extar, and no
one's tranced with you!
This is just one of the perks
of being Soldier class.
[KASUMI, HIBIKI scream, groan]
Miss Kasumi!
[MIREI]
Stop this, A3!
[MAMORI gasps]
Mirei...
What was that?
Why're you going
by that name now?
I see. So you've been living
it up this whole time
with a fake name, eh?
It never occurred to me
that you would end up
ditching your designation.
If I'd known you were here,
I would've come straight away!
[MIREI gasps]
And turned your
guts into jump rope!
[MIREI groans]
Mirei, no!
Someone's been naughty.
You know you can't
go all soldier-mode
without taking your
medicine first.
Oh, I forgot.
You must not have any, huh?
How many times have you done it?
How long till you fall apart
like the used up trash you are?
[MIREI groaning]
Oh, Mirei... Do you have
any idea how much trouble
I had to go through 'cause
of what you wouldn't do?
Try to think of
something more useless
than a soldier who won't kill.
[MAMORI gasps]
I sure can't.
But what about you?
Leave us alone!
What's wrong with you;
--this isn't right!
--[HIBIKI shrieks]
No! Stop it! Please!
Hibiki!
[HIBIKI]
Somebody help me!
Make it stop!
Excuse me while I shut her up.
[KASUMI gasps]
--No!
--[growls]
--[engine revs]
--[gasps]
So who are you?
Or should I say "what"?
She's a soldier.
How interesting.
So the one we were attacked
by... must've been older.
[MOMOKA]
Anyway, who the hell are you?
'Bout time you came.
They're called Lady Lady.
I just reviewed the data on the
chip we recovered from Hiiragi.
Apparently, they were agents of
the Nafrece intelligence agency.
They're hybrids, both of them.
Either one can take the
role of Liberator or Extar.
Wow... That's not too shabby
for a couple of naturals.
So then why were you sent here,
did your agency
get tired of you?
As a matter of fact, we
left of our own volition.
Rather than live there as
dogs of the government,
we took our chances here.
And do you think
it was worth it?
Yes. Because they'll
never control us again.
And we don't intend
to stay here forever.
[RAIN moans]
[LADY J moans]
Well, if you're planning
to break your quarantine,
then I suppose it follows that
you also intend to oppose us?
Why yes, we do.
Even if all of you
are soldiers...
We'll take you down the same!
[gasps]
Why didn't that disarm them?
Do you really think a natural
can stand up against a
soldier's enhancements?
[RAIN screams]
[LADY J grunts]
Lady Rain! Lady J!
She's out of our league.
So this is... what
soldiers can do.
That's what you two get for
butting into my business.
So, where were we,
girls? I forget.
Oh, right, the killing.
Restrain yourself for now, A3.
There's still a chance that
this could be our target.
She can't die until
we know for sure.
No way is that discarded piece
of junk what we're looking for.
If C7 had the stuff to
cause a Valkyrie effect,
she would've done
it way before now.
It was that one.
Who, me? No way!
This has to be a mistake.
Mamori's the target?
They're wrong.
That's impossible.
So since our mission's
accomplished,
I'm gonna get my kill on.
[D5] Our mission is to find her,
and then bring her back to HQ.
[MIREI]
No.
[BOTH]
Hm?
Whatever you're planning,
I'm not gonna let you touch her.
If only you could
back that claim.
[MAMORI yelps]
Go to sleep.
No, let her go!
A3, we need to fall
back and confirm
that this girl is our
legitimate target.
No killing till then.
Fair enough.
Stop it! Let her go!
You should count yourself lucky
that you're still in one piece.
Give her back to me.
Just give her back!
I'll do anything!
Listen to yourself.
I guess you care a lot about
her if you're that torn up.
Now I'm kinda jealous.
You didn't beg like
that to get me back!
You really have a knack
for pissing me off.
[CHARLOTTE yelps]
Françoise?
[screaming]
What's happening?
I wish I could say.
[MOMOKA sighs]
It's a real shame.
I could've made a
day of killing her,
I would've gotten
candles and everything.
[CHARLOTTE]
Françoise! I demand to know what
you're doing with that girl.
As Gouverneur of the Warter,
I demand that you
explain your intentions--
If you ever wanna make
it off this island,
then shut your mouth
and do as you're told.
I don't understand.
I thought I was...
Aw, you forgot the shut your
mouth part already! [giggles]
[MEIFENG sighs]
I made so much cash from
that match the other day.
I was gonna take a bath in it!
[sobs]
And now I'm even poorer
than I was before!
You poor thing.
We owe you one, truly.
[MEIFENG] Yeah, well,
I'm charging interest!
Your friend's leaving.
--[GROUP gasps]
--[MIREI groaning]
Mirei? Where are you going?
I think you know.
They took Mamori.
I'm gonna track them down
and bring her back.
But in that condition,
what can you--
I'm coming, Mamori.
Just hang in there, I-- [groans]
You've gotta heal up first.
Stop, A3. She isn't a fighter.
Please just leave her be.
She hasn't done anything
to deserve this.
Don't hurt her.
[E9]
This is amazing!
Her Valkyrie Effect
reaction size.
It just went over 70 somehow!
If those values are
from a natural--
There's no doubt about it.
This is our target:
Mamori Tokonome.
See? Exactly like I told you.
There's no need for
further testing.
[moans, screams]
She's at 80%; 84 now!
It just hit 90!
And the numbers
are still going up!
[laughs]
Yup, this girl is the real
deal! I finally found her!
Tell me, do you have any
idea what will happen
to the Armed Virus if the
reaction size hits 100?
Do you have any idea what this
hot little mutant's capable of?
Uh-- Yeah... No.
This has never been documented,
but theoretically the virus
should begin to
distribute unevenly.
This could cause a total
reversal of its symptoms.
So wait, A3, does this
mean what I think it does?
What it means is that
there's no need for me
to give this treasure up
to the organization.
'Cause as long as I have her...
No one can stop me!
[A] I see that your enhancement
procedure was successful, C7.
Soon you and A3
complete your training.
You'll be deployed
within the year.
Before that happens,
a word of advice.
This is an organization
that values results.
Fail to provide them,
and we will fail to have
reason to provide for you.
We do not carry dead weight.
Cease to be useful and
you will be disposed of.
Remember that.
[MOMOKA]
It's them or us, C7.
[MOMOKA] You have to
fight... to keep us alive.
[MOMOKA]
C7!
Why won't you fight them?
[sobs]
Why don't you care
enough to protect me?!
C7!
[RESEARCHER A]
She refused to fight?
Unbelievable.
[A] There is no room
for useless individuals
in this organization.
Dispose of her.
She's waste.
[DOCTOR A]
Listen, as far as HQ knows,
you're about to be
killed and disposed of.
Instead, I'll put you
into a near-death state.
It's the only way
to get you out.
I can't explain how, but I plan
to send you somewhere safe.
I've made arrangements
for you to start over.
Leave C7 behind.
And begin a new life,
as Mirei Shikishima.
I fear that this doesn't even
begin to atone for my sins.
I beg you, go and
do what I cannot.
Leave this place... and have
a full and normal life.
Please don't do this! You
wouldn't even know about her
if she hadn't been
trying to help me!
Don't interfere!
It doesn't matter what she did.
If she has the Armed Virus,
she must be quarantined.
[MIREI]
A normal life, he said.
So much for that.
I quit...
[MIREI]
There's nothing to live for.
[MAMORI]
Mirei...
Why are you so quick
to risk your life?
[whimpers]
[MIREI]
Why not?
[MAMORI]
I wanna go home.
Daddy... Mommy...
I wanna see you again.
I just wanna... go home!
[MIREI]
I understand now.
Why would you do
something this drastic,
without even telling
me about it first?
I warned you just last night
to stop being so rash!
Oh, Mirei...
You leave me no choice.
I have to... kiss you.
[MIREI gasps]
[MIREI]
That's when I realized.
I found it--My reason.
I have to find you.
[groans]
I have to get you back.
Mamori...
[MAMORI groans]
Mirei? Are you here?
She couldn't make it.
And I wouldn't expect
her if I were you.
[MAMORI gasps]
You're that girl!
My name's Momoka Sagara.
We have lots in common.
Once, I was Mirei's
partner, too.
Actually, she was the worst
thing that ever happened to me.
You mean that
Mirei got you hurt?
That's right.
Rather than let the
organization dispose of me,
I "volunteered" to take on their
newest experimental
enhancements.
They toyed with my body.
Cut into me again and again.
And turned me into a monster.
So do you understand why I feel
a little salty towards her now?
Ever since her, my
life has been about
having things taken
from me, one by one.
So...
[MAMORI gasps]
[MOMOKA]
Now I'm gonna take it all back!
What are you--?!
But in order to do that,
I'm gonna need to
use your power, kay?
There's no need to be afraid.
I've got a vested interest in
making this feel good for you.
Because the better it feels
when you Drive for me,
the stronger a weapon you'll be.
[MAMORI gasps]
What-- What is she doing?
I feel hot all over.
I can't let this feel good!
I'll turn into an Arm!
[MAMORI]
And... if that happens...
Then, she'll use me as a weapon
to do whatever she wants!
[MAMORI yelps]
[MOMOKA]
That's not a bad resistance.
You've got a stronger
will than I thought.
But the human mind and body...
It can be hard to keep 'em
both on the same page.
[MAMORI]
I can't let her make me Drive!
[MOMOKA] No matter how
noble your intentions may be,
pain can always break you,
and you can always
drown in pleasure.
That's how your body works;
it can't be helped.
[MAMORI]
No, I can't!
[MOMOKA] Once it's been driven
to the furthest extreme,
the mind will lose any
semblance of control.
--[MAMORI screams]
--[MOMOKA laughs]
I know this...
...because that's how
it happened for me!
Fan... tas... tique!
[MIREI panting]
[groans]
[AKIRA]
You're leaving, right?
To save Miss Tokonome?
That's right, but...
not only her.
I plan to free everyone who's
being held in that castle.
But that means you'll
be up against soldiers.
Soldiers who are
stronger than you.
It doesn't matter.
I'll fight.
[AKIRA]
Why?
Because of her--
Mamori Tokonome.
'Cause when you find a
reason, you keep it.
[MIREI] Mamori has a
place to go back to.
People who she loves.
Someone who she
hopes to see again.
I want to make that
wish come true for her.
If I could just do that--
It'd be enough.
[engine revving]
Hey, you need a ride?
[MIREI]
Why help me?
[RAIN]
Only reason why we do anything.
Because we decided
we felt like it.
You know that they'll kill you.
[RAIN chuckles]
I know it'll be a
show to remember.
[CHARLOTTE]
Excuse me?
That's what you are?
You're the Watchers Akira
was always talking about?
That's right, and it follows
that if you cooperate with us,
then we can help you in return!
It's not impossible for us
to get you off of this island.
You wouldn't be the first
exception to the quarantine.
How about Ange?
Can I bring the
rest of Adel, too?
That depends on the
results you bring.
Excuse me, Ma'am.
We've spotted an unregistered
vehicle approaching the castle!
A fine opportunity.
This is your chance to
demonstrate your commitment.
[MIREI gasps]
[RITTER B]
Ready to fire on your command.
You there! Stop at once!
[guns cock]
I have nothing against
you... but I will pass.
Guns down, let her through.
[MIREI gasps]
[E9 moans, gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
That insubordinate twit.
How dare she ignore the orders
of her rightful Gouverneur.
She'll be getting a stiff lesson
once I've taken care of you.
[E9 squeals]
Damn it. A Soldier Arm?
I'll take you down for Adel!
Slippery vermin!
[CHARLOTTE laughs]
That's the power
of the Watchers!
The power of a Soldier Arm!
No natural can take me on while
I've got a weapon like this.
I don't care if you've
got Lady Lady with you!
[gasps]
How did you--?
What is that?
When did they get a shield?
[RAIN]
You ready, J?
[LADY J]
I always am, Rain.
[RAIN, LADY J]
Final Mode!
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
Well, this is surprising.
[RAIN]
Like I told you...
[MIREI]
Huh?!
[RAIN] We're gonna put
on a show tonight!
[LADY J]
Go, Mirei! Now!
Just how desperate are you?!
This isn't done.
I'll leave this
god-forsaken island
no matter what I have to do!
Thank you for the help.
We're leaving the rest to you.
You can do this.
Don't let the soldiers win.
[MIREI]
Mamori... I'm coming.
Please be okay.
[MOMOKA]
I'm pretty impressed
that you made it
this far, Mirei.
[MIREI gasps]
[MIREI]
Mamori!
Talk, A3!
What the hell have
you done to Mamori?!
I have a name.
It's Momoka Sagara.
[MAMORI gasps]
[moans]
[MIREI gasps]
[MAMORI squeals]
[MOMOKA] I was hoping
you'd survive that blast.
Now I get to use
what you love most
to take everything from you.
I'll take it all...
including your life.
[MIREI, MAMORI]
"Valkyrie Drive."