--[crash]
--[CROWD chattering]
[GIRL A]
Oh, great, Kusumi's back.
What? You wanna
dance with me, bitch?
You don't scare me
anymore, Kusumi!
Hey, this is my fight.
Stay out, losers!
[MIIDERA]
Miss Kusumi, need I mention that
you just got out
of the dungeons!
You're fighting in front
of your probation officer!
Yeah! And if you're smart,
you'll stay out, too!
[gasps]
[CROWD gasps, cheers]
[CROWD screams]
They're driving in
the middle of lunch?
I was gonna sit there!
[gasps]
[KUSUMI yells]
[YOTSUYA yells]
All right, both of
you, knock it off!
[KUSUMI gasps]
[YOTSUYA gasps]
Wait, is that, Sri?
Yes, it is.
Which can only mean--
[gasps]
--[CROWD cheering]
--[GIRL B] Lord Akira's here!
[GIRL C]
I knew he'd come!
Ladies, we agreed on one thing.
No fighting in the castle!
Or did you forget?
Thank you.
[CROWD squeals]
I knew the Gouverneur
would calm them down.
Ladies!
I know we Ritter enforce
rules that can sometimes
make life in this castle
severe and unforgiving.
But such discipline
has a higher purpose
of proving to the watchers that
we are capable of civilized life
and one day returning to
our families on the mainland!
We must remain united
to achieve that goal.
Our very future depends upon it.
Another troublemaker gets out of
the dungeon and starts a fight.
By my count, it's the third time
in a month that's happened.
I want you to crack the whip
a bit. Tighten up the reins.
Miss Charlotte,
being harder on them
will only make things worse!
Gouverneur, I suggest
we go the other way,
and throw a big party
to relax everyone.
Kasumi, why've you
been so soft, lately?
Because your methods haven't
been encouraging good behavior!
All I want to do is crush
the rebels in the jungle,
is that really so wrong?
[KASUMI] Yes! When your first
and only idea is violence,
it's wrong!
[engine revving]
[gasps]
Huh?
I'm heading out
for a bit; goodbye!
Oh...
The Governeur's so handsome!
[sighs]
Now this look feels right.
[AKIRA sighs]
[TORINO]
Did you lose something, Akira?
[AKIRA]
Miss Torino.
If what I'm looking
for got through
the force field
protecting this island--
It should have washed
up right in this spot.
How've you been?
Oh, the same old, same old.
Not one message from
anyone back in my old life.
[AKIRA]
That's too bad.
[TORINO] But no news
could also be good news!
Means everything's
hunky-dory, right?
We're getting cold
standing here,
why don't you come
with me and warm up?
[AKIRA]
Hm.
[TORINO giggles]
[sighs]
Nice to see that wrinkle
between your eyebrows go away.
What?
I don't have that;
you're just being mean.
[giggles] No, you do!
Right there between your eyes!
Well, if we're being
honest with each other,
you've got some
crows' feet, too.
What?! That's not true!
I'm too young to have wrinkles!
I'm kidding.
[TORINO gasps] Hey, you!
That's not funny at all!
We should probably
get back before dusk.
Good thinkin' there.
Plus, if I stay in the water
any longer, I might faint.
[MAMORI] Look Mirei, a hot
springs right on the beach!
[giggles]
Huh?
[gasps]
[MAMORI]
My-- My body...
Just looking at her makes
me all tingly and warm.
[gasps, whimpers]
[yelps]
[AKIRA gasps]
Well, that's new.
She got excited
by the nice view.
[AKIRA grunts, sighs]
I'm sorry I lost control
when I saw you.
You don't have to
apologize for that.
It was surprising yes,
but it's natural.
So, who is your friend?
I'm sorry, this is Aki--
[gasps]
[AKIRA growls]
Eee-- Hee-- Heel?
My dear old friend,
Madam Heelhold?
Old friend?
Miss Heelhold?
Oh! With a name like that,
you must be foreign.
[AKIRA] Uh-- That's right.
My dad's foreign.
[chattering]
Thanks again.
That's the best tasting
meal I've had in months.
Hey. It's already pretty late,
why don't you stay the night?
Huh? I can't.
Oh, come on, you
deserve a break.
'Sides, no one will notice if
you're gone just one night.
I guess I can spare a
night away from the Veste.
[AKIRA]
I'll be a good guest.
I won't take up too much space.
[MAMORI] You can stay
as long as you like!
[AKIRA gasps]
[AKIRA]
Uh-- Uh...
What's wrong, Miss Heelhold?
Oh! Uh-- It's nothing. All good.
[MAMORI] Okay, cutie, since
we have a guest tonight,
you're sleeping over here.
I hope the two of us
don't have any problem
fitting in this one twin bed.
[MIREI grunts]
Huh? What's wrong
with you, Mirei?
[MIREI growls]
[AKIRA]
I can't sleep like this.
[MAMORI]
You can't sleep, either, huh?
[AKIRA gasps]
[MAMORI giggles]
It's just always hard to
sleep in a different bed.
Well...
Then how about we stay up
talking until we both get tired?
[AKIRA]
Sure.
[MAMORI] Miss Heelhold,
you've been on this island
a long time, haven't you?
That's right.
In fact, you could say
I'm one of the very first girls
who ever even arrived here.
Back then, I was so
lost and scared.
But with the years, I changed.
Both physically, as
well as... emotionally.
In all your time on the island,
have you ever known
any girls to escape?
Never. Not once.
[MAMORI]
Oh... Okay...
[AKIRA] Promise me that you
won't lose hope, Miss Mamori.
I won't.
[AKIRA] Whether the Armed Virus
makes us Extar or Liberator,
we must use our powers
safely and responsibly.
And those of us who fail
to do so, must be punished.
Whether we like it or not, that
virus made us who we are today.
If we can show the outside world
that we're able to control our
powers and use them for good,
They'll have no choice but to
welcome us back with open arms.
That is the hope that has kept
me going these many years,
and it should be your hope
as well, Miss Mamori.
Stay strong, and never give up.
Is all that just something
you tell yourself or
do you really believe
--they'll take us back--
--I really do.
One day, we will go home. I know
this because it is the truth.
So you have to believe it, too.
Please, never give up hope.
'Kay. I believe if you
believe; we're going home.
[AKIRA]
Become a man?
[YUI]
Yes.
All carriers of the Armed Virus
are biologically female.
Therefore, everyone on the
island they're sending you to
is also female... which is
why I want you to lie
about your real gender and live
on the island as its only boy.
[AKIRA]
What? Why?
If everyone there is special,
the only leverage left
is for you to appear
completely different, Akira.
Please understand.
This is the best way for you
to stay safe and strong.
Oh, Mother, no...
[door clicks]
[AKIRA]
What is that?
[YUI]
This is Sri.
The Hiiragi Group
spared no expense
in developing it just for you.
It's perfectly
calibrated in every way
to supplement your
abilities as a Liberator.
Think of Sri... as your
protector and your servant,
despite her being a robot.
Robot... Extar?
Please, dear.
This is the best I can do for
you under these circumstances.
But I will find a way to get
you out of there, I promise!
Until that day comes,
don't give up hope.
Please, believe me!
I love you, Akira!
[footsteps]
[KUSUMI groans]
[grunts]
[MEIFENG]
Crap, crap, crap!
We gotta big problem!
[gasps]
What's wrong, Meifeng? Cookie?
No, I don't want a cookie.
We've got something way more
important than your bakin'
to worry about right now!
Don't you guys watch the news?
[REPORTER]
A few hours ago,
several armed assailants
took a Ritter hostage
and locked themselves inside an
abandoned building near Veste.
According to a statement
released by the
suspected kidnappers,
they will not release
their hostage until
the Gouverneur meets
the following demands--
Protecting the right to
live outside the castle,
disclosing the statistics
for food production,
and evenly distributing
supplies among all girls.
So they don't want our
rule, but they still want
all the benefits that
come with living under it.
I don't care who
they're holding hostage,
I can't take them seriously.
Prepare a squadron to
attack the terrorists.
[KASUMI gasps]
What about the hostage in there?
Hopefully she won't
become collateral damage.
There's still time to
negotiate with them!
Oh, Kasumi. How many times
must I explain to you
the danger our rule faces
if we come across as weak?
I would have thought by now
that you'd've learned your
lesson on such matters.
[KASUMI grunts]
[CHARLOTTE giggles]
And what about the Gouverneur?
The Gouverneur's first instinct
in crisis is never to use force!
[CHARLOTTE]
Well, it's too bad for you,
the Gouverneur has been MIA
the last couple of days.
What a terrible
work ethic he has!
For all his lofty talk
about maintaining order,
he sure doesn't lead
by example, does he?
Men are so disappointing.
No, Charlotte!
If the Gouverneur's not going
to be here to keep the peace,
then he's left me no choice
but to do his job for him.
I have to go.
Huh? Wait, what's going on?
That news story.
I can't just ignore rebellion.
But the situation's
way dangerous!
Of course, you can ignore it!
I'll go with Miss Heelhold.
[MIREI]
Mamori, no.
Are you sure?
If Miss Charlotte's using
deadly force against the rebels,
we have a moral
duty to stop her.
Are you in, Mirei?
Yes.
[AKIRA] They had to pick
my secret changing spot,
of all places.
[AKIRA gasps]
[RITTER A, B grunt]
When are you gonna
meet our demands?
How long do you want
her to stay a hostage?
[muffled whimpering]
[KASUMI gasps]
The Adel? Now what's she doing?
Hold on!
Your belief in negotiation
has got us nowhere!
I should have gone in the second
they kidnapped a Ritter!
Outta my way, Kasumi!
Kommandeur, move it!
[MAMORI]
Through that?
[MEIFENG]
That's right!
This old tunnel goes directly
under the abandoned building
where the girls are holed
up with their hostage.
I even dug a vertical shaft
that'll take us right up
into the middle of the house.
When did you dig an extra shaft?
The truth is...
I sometimes use this place
to host gambling parties.
I dug it so I'd have an escape
route in case I got found.
[ALL groan]
Hey! Don't judge what I do!
You wanted a Fast Pass up
into the Haunted Mansion
and I gave you one and
asked for nothing in return!
You're right.
Thanks, Meifeng.
This does help us.
Uh-- Yeah...
Well, ladies, I'm happy to show
you the way, but I gotta jet.
I ain't gonna go stick my
neck into danger for free.
[AKIRA]
You've done more than enough.
Okay, you two,
now it's your turn!
Right!
--[MIREI moans]
--[MAMORI gasps]
[MAMORI moans]
[MEIFENG]
Wow!
I've never seen you get
into it this hot and heavy!
[MAMORI moaning]
[AKIRA gasps]
[MAMORI squeals]
Here we go!
[MEIFENG gasps]
Hey!
They didn't say goodbye.
All right, I'll go
through the trap door
and distract the rebel girls.
That's when you
rescue the hostage.
Roger that, lady.
You done this before?
When you've been here as long as
me, you've done everything once.
Let's rock 'n roll.
[KUSUMI gasps]
[HEXA A yells]
[groans]
Damnit!
[KUSUMI yells]
You good?
Yeah...
I feel great!
Heh!
[gasps]
[groans]
[AKIRA gasps]
[MAMORI yelps]
[gasps]
--[AKIRA gasps]
--[KUSUMI] Don't move!
I don't think I've
ever met you before.
Are you a Warter secret weapon?
You caught us off-guard.
But luckily, I had the
Warter paralysis spray on me.
[AKIRA]
So this was all a set up.
That's right. The "hostage"
was the mastermind.
[gasps] Why do this?
Because I'm sick of living
my life in that dumb castle!
No matter how civilized we act,
we're never getting
off this island
like our fearless leader,
the Gouverneur, claims.
That's why I teamed up with a
few of the resident bad girls
to put a big plan into motion.
A reform movement to
make over the entire Veste
into something that
offers real fun and hope.
But this isn't reform,
this is terrorism. You fool!
[MIIDERA]
As long as we get what we want,
you can call it
whatever you like.
[KUSUMI] What should we
do with her friends?
[MIIDERA] Tie 'em up and
throw 'em on the floor.
Make sure this one doesn't get
close to her Liberator, though.
We don't want her
hands to wander.
Next thing you know,
they'll be Driving indoors.
[MIIDERA sighs] All that time
pretending to be a hostage
really cramped me up.
[KUSUMI] Hey! Don't stand
there, they can see you!
[MIIDERA]
I'm fine.
Besides, if Charlotte
does storm the place,
we'll just escape
down the emergency exit
our guests gave us.
Hey, uh, Miss Heelhold?
Do you remember what
happened to me yesterday
when I first saw you at the
beach when you were in the nude?
[AKIRA gasps]
I can't.
[MAMORI]
Because of you, I have hope.
[AKIRA]
Huh?
So use me.
Now's my chance to help you.
Are you sure?
Yes.
[BOTH moan]
[gasps]
She's not your Extar!
This girl's strong!
I think she's at the
same level as Lady Lady!
[KUSUMI]
Charge!
[ALL groan]
No way...
I don't-- don't believe it!
[gasps]
You have to give up.
[MIIDERA sighs]
I almost forgot about Mirei!
That gas she got sprayed
with paralyzed her.
Go get a doctor
as fast as you can.
[MAMORI]
Right!
[MIIDERA chuckles]
It's not over yet!
Good.
[MAMORI] Hurry!
She's in here! She's frozen!
[gasps]
[MEIFENG]
Those stupid jerks.
I was kidding about
wanting money to go in.
All they had to do was
ask, and I'd have gone!
But no, they're all
like, "Later, Meifeng!"
--[enging revving]
--[MEIFENG] Whoa!
Hey, watch out!
The hostage situation is over.
But they had to take Mirei
to the castle for
medical treatment.
She got hurt?
[RAIN] Hop on. I'll
give you a ride there...
...if you wanna go.
[MEIFENG]
I do!
[sighs]
Surprise! Wallet-sized
Gouverneur pics!
Meifang called in some favors
and got them made for me!
Cute, right?
I'm gonna put them
under my pillow.
With this hottie
close to my head,
I'm guaranteed to have
some sexy dreams! [giggles]
[MIREI] Whatever gives
her hope... is good.
[MAMORI sighs]
[giggles]
I will find a way to get
you off that island, Akira.
I promise you!
Until that day comes,
do not lose hope!
Yes.
I have more hope than ever.
[MAMORI]
"Valkyrie Effect."