[CHARLOTTE]
Now I see.
It was you, Lady Lady.
I always said it
was foolish for us
to tolerate your defiance.
Destroy them!
[ANGE growls]
[gasps]
[ANGE gasps]
[KOUZUKI]
Are you okay?!
[MIYASATO gasps]
Don't go jumping to
conclusions, Charlotte.
[KASUMI] If you're innocent,
then why are you here?
Well, if I cared
to explain myself...
...I'd say it had
something to do with
this fascinating pair.
How about you, J?
[LADY J]
Agreed, Rain.
So that motorcycle
was a person?
An Arm.
[MEIFENG]
It's Rain Hasumi. And Lady J.
First Warter shows up
with Charlotte
and now Lady Lady's rolled in.
Just About every power
player on Mermaid Island's
come to fight!
Wish I could take bets...
[AKIRA]
Hello there. Enjoying the view?
Huh?
[MEIFENG gasps]
[MEIFENG]
Uh...
Gouverneur Hiiragi, hi.
[CHARLOTTE]
Lady Lady.
The most selfish-minded fools
who've ever set foot
on this god-forsaken island.
It's due to people like you
that we've been quarantined.
Unless you and every
other anarchist can be
brought to heel, the
watchers will declare us
unfit to live in society.
Heh. As if they haven't already?
The trial isn't over.
It's still possible for us to
prove they misjudged us.
If we lead orderly lives here,
we'll show that
despite our powers,
we're no threat.
Once we've proven we
can form our own society,
we'll be allowed to go home--
Hate to be rude, but
we've heard this crap before.
Yes, and we've decided
that we have our doubts.
Here's one glaring issue:
Your precious Gouverneur hasn't
given us a shred of proof
that the watchers are there.
For all we know, these watchers
are just something he made up
so everyone in Veste would go
along with his little patriar--
Stop rambling on about nonsense.
Excuse me?
What are you doing?
[MIREI]
I've never met these women--
they played no part
in this theft.
The others here
are innocent, too.
You have your
confession, it's over.
Now take me in
and leave them alone.
It isn't true. Please help her.
[BOTH gasp]
Thank you for confessing,
Miss Shikishima.
It simplifies this task
a great deal.
Please come with us
for further questioning.
--[CHARLOTTE gasps]
--[MIREI] Very well.
[CHARLOTTE] Questioning?! We
need to make an example of her!
If we let criminals like her
and Lady Lady go unpunished,
then why should
our subjects fear us?!
I won't allow your
sentimentality to ruin
the reputation of Warter!
Soldiers!
Show them how we do it!
[moaning]
[moaning continues]
[gasps, screams]
[moans, gasps]
Don't leave a single one
of them standing!
Please don't do this! I'm--
You've got the looks,
all right. How's your form?
[MIREI grunts]
[gasps]
Good.
--[RAIN grunts]
--[MIREI gasps]
[RAIN laughs]
[RAIN]
♪ Ahh... ♪
[LADY J]
Use her.
It's all right, they'll live.
Take cover!
[SOLDIER A screams]
--[grunts]
--[SOLDIER D grunts]
[SOLDIER F groans]
[MAMORI whimpers]
What is that power?
She can forcefully
revert them from arm state.
Rain's special move is quite
arousing, don't you think?
Her Disarmament Buster.
Special move?
Well, check out mine!
Charlotte! Wait!
[LADY J grunts]
[LADY J]
♪ Laa... ♪
Did you just enter Drive
without a partner?!
That's just how
powerful the bond is...
[CHARLOTTE growls]
...between me and J!
[CHARLOTTE grunts, gasps]
[RAIN chuckles]
[KASUMI yells]
[grunts]
[RAIN] You're pretty quick
on your feet, Kasumi.
But you still can't win
without your partner.
You might as well tie
an arm behind your back.
My, does she look lonely.
[RAIN] I hear your Extar
hasn't been coping too well.
Hibiki Kenjo, right?
[gasps]
You know nothing about her.
--How dare you mock her pain?!
--[AKIRA] Stand down!
[ALL gasp]
Is that the Gouverneur?
Well, what do you know?
Never would have guessed
that he'd be bothered
to make an appearance here.
[LADY J] Only one boy has ever
been sent to Mermaid Island.
[RAIN] The illustrious
Gouverneur of Warter himself.
[RAIN]
Akira Hiiragi.
[gasps]
It's Lord Akira!
Hush, I wanna hear him!
We're at your
service, Gouverneur.
What are you doing here?
I've come to tell you
the truth about this crime.
[CHARLOTTE]
The truth?
That's right. I've
determined that the person
who actually stole
from Veste isn't here.
I met her a moment ago,
on top of that cliff.
[AKIRA]
Enjoying the view?
[gasps]
I feel as if we've met before.
[MEIFENG]
Nope, sure haven't!
[AKIRA] I'm afraid
the culprit escaped though.
I must apologize.
I've brought shame
to the title of Gouverneur.
The confession was false, then.
That can't be right!
Our tracker's signaling
from inside the town!
[AKIRA]
Naturally.
The culprit must have sold
our goods to these people.
That makes them
victims, too, in my eyes.
[CHARLOTTE sighs]
Forgive me for any distress
we may have caused you.
No. You're fine.
Ah! Wait a second...
I mean-- I mean, I'm fine!
Thanks to you...
Please permit me to
issue a formal apology.
I beg your pardon.
Oh. Yeah. Okay...
And as for the supplies
that were taken,
please keep them,
as a small reparation.
Does that sound amenable?
Yes...
Well, then, if that's settled--
It's a shame, Akira.
I was looking forward to
seeing how you are in a fight.
Regretfully, I must decline.
I'm quite averse to pain.
[AKIRA]
Warter! We ride for Veste!
[KASUMI]
As you command, my lord.
Move out!
--We can't just ru--
--[KASUMI] That's enough!
Gouverneur Hiiragi's
orders are absolute.
[CHARLOTTE growls]
Goodness. That was
a close one, wasn't it?
[MIREI grunts]
What has your
panties in a twist?!
You made me kiss you.
That's what.
Truly a fascinating girl.
I like you, Mirei. Think
you'll be seeing more of us.
In fact, I know it.
Lady Lady... They're powerful.
They might be Soldier-class.
Could it be...?
Just when I needed him most,
the charming, gallant prince
I've been waiting for has come.
[MAMORI] It's him...
It has to be, I'm sure of it!
My true prince!
You handled that perfectly.
Thank you, Lord Hiragi.
It was the least I could do
to calm things down.
We had nothing to gain
from escalating that conflict.
Yes. I completely agree, sir.
[CHARLOTTE] The Gouverneur
never even should've known
we'd left the castle!
Who...? Who could've told him?!
I won't let it happen again!
[MEIFENG] Ooh, boy,
am I glad you're all okay!
It really is too bad
that happened...
I wonder what Warter
was looking for.
[RESIDENT A] What do you mean,
"You wonder"?! It was you!
Okay, yeah, I know. I'll do
better next time, honest.
[RESIDENT B]
I thought that Charlotte girl
--was gonna kill us.
--[RESIDENT A] I know, right?
Like I said, I'll do better.
[TORINO] What's all this
about a prince now?
[MAMORI] Oh, um!
The gouverneur, I mean.
You wouldn't
know him, would you?
Well, of course.
He's quite famous, you know.
Ah... Could you tell me
what he's like, please?
Yeah, I guess so.
Akira Hiiragi--slightly
over five-foot seven.
My sources tell me
he's blood type A.
As sweet as you are;
I bet you're the same.
So far, it seems like
he's the only boy
who's gotten the Armed Virus.
I don't know if that helped him
become Gouverneur or not.
What I bet was helpful is
his great power as a Liberator.
He's a Liberator, really?
Wait! So Liberators
are the ones who
turn Extars into weapons,
aren't they?
[TORINO]
They sure are!
If he's a Liberator
and I'm an Extar...
...I guess that he
and I could be...
Mr. Hiiragi, please allow me
to become your Arm only,
until death do us part!
Miss Virgin...
It's Tokonome.
Sorry, it's confusing.
I could never use a frail
beauty like you for war.
That would expose you to danger,
and I plan to keep you safe.
For the rest of my life.
[MAMORI]
Oh... Mr. Hiiragi...
[AKIRA]
Miss Virgin.
[MAMORI]
It's Tokonome...
[MAMORI sighs]
So perfect...
I see what's going on here.
You're not the first girl
to fantasize
about becoming
the Gouverneur's arm.
[gasps] No, I mean, he is
really amazing, but...
...I'm not worthy.
But you like him, don't you?
Well, um... Mm. Wait.
Mr. Hiiragi doesn't have
a girlfriend already, does he?
[TORINO] Nope, and
it'd be chaos if he did.
He's something of
an idol on this island.
[MAMORI]
Huh... Is that so?
[AKIRA] Well, Kommandeur.
How fare our wounded Ritters?
[KASUMI]
None were badly wounded.
I expect they'll be able
to resume their duties
within the next few days.
Along with Lady Lady,
Miss Shikishima could have
slain them with ease,
but It would seem
she showed some restraint.
[KASUMI]
Yes, I suspected.
Gouverneur, may I ask you
a question please?
By all means.
With all due respect, my lord,
why allow Lady Lady
to do as they will?
[AKIRA]
There are a number of reasons.
Each of them is
both Liberator and Extar.
Powerful at that.
Warter has the
strength to beat them,
but not without
becoming weakened.
There's no cause
to take that risk.
And besides, I do
harbor some hope for them.
Hope, sir? For what?
Well... Rogues they may be,
but their goal is still
to escape this island,
same as ours.
The only real difference is
in how they mean to do it.
How can you be so certain
that we'll get away
with this, Charlotte?
[CHARLOTTE] What is it
you're fretting over?
[ANGE] The Gouverneur ordered
us to withdraw. All of us.
[CHARLOTTE] Come now, Ange,
it's about interpretation.
I tried to get everyone back
to the castle as ordered.
But those armored cars get so
cramped that when
Miranda said
she'd walk, I let her,
and now I guess
she hurt her foot.
I can see her now, dragging
herself through the woods.
That poor darling.
If she does get back, I'll
make all her boo-boos better.
[MIREI gasps]
[MIREI]
What have you done?
[MAMORI giggles]
Meifeng wanted to make up
for all the trouble,
so she got these for me!
That girl really is
a jack-of-all-trades, huh?
[sighs] Now I can imagine
I'm with Mr. Hiiragi
whenever I'm at home!
What a nightmare...
[MAMORI gasps]
Sorry, did you say something?
No, ma'am.
I have nothing to say.
[MAMORI] 'Kay, well I don't know
about you, but I'm exhausted.
Could you get the light for me?
[MIREI]
Yes.
Mr. Hiiragi...
[MAMORI sobs]
[MAMORI]
I wanna go home...
Daddy... Mommy...
I wanna see you again...
[MIREI sighs]
[TORINO] Hmm... Well, we've
made it through another day,
at least.
[TORINO giggles]
[TORINO] It must be
even harder for Akira.
[AKIRA] Miss Virgin.
Hey, there, Miss Virgin.
[MAMORI sighs]
It really is Tokonome...
[AKIRA] Uh, right.
Miss Tokonome, hi.
Hey there. How are you doing?
[AKIRA]
I'm good. Wake up, now.
[MAMORI]
Hmm...?
[gasps]
My prince! You're here!
[AKIRA] If you would,
Miss Tokonome, follow me.
Uh, yeah, okay.
[MAMORI]
Hey. Where are you going?
Wait for me!
No prince. But where could
he have gone, though?
[AKIRA]
Just over here, Miss Tokonome.
[gasps]
Oh. Hi again.
Lead on, gentle prince.
Wherefore art thou,
handsome prince?
Princes aren't
supposed to tease.
[AKIRA]
Nor would I.
[gasps]
You are Mr. Hiiragi, right?
Yes, that's right.
But why're you here, though?
Shouldn't you be at Veste?
Yes, I certainly should.
It's hard to explain, but---
I've been in agony, ever since
I first laid eyes on you.
I had no choice but to sneak
back here and see you again.
I couldn't stop myself.
I had to come.
You really mean it, don't you?
Oh, I do. My heart's on fire.
And this insatiable yearning--
it can only mean one thing.
[MAMORI gasps]
It has to be love, Miss Virgin.
Yes. It's Tokonome, though.
[AKIRA]
Miss Tokonome. Forgive me.
I've wanted to
touch you so badly.
To hold you, just like this.
Yeah... Um... Me, too...
[AKIRA] Oh, but that
isn't all I yearn for.
I'd also like to go further.
[gasps] Sorry, but--It's too
soon, we just met, lusty prince.
What is time
to a love like ours?
[MAMORI gasps]
Are you ready?
I... don't know.
I think I'll take
that as a yes.
[MAMORI gasps]
[gasps]
[MAMORI moans]
Ahh! [gasps]
[moans]
[MAMORI] His hands...
They're so strong!
Finally... I'm gonna get
rid of this dumb name!
After this, no one will ever
call me "Virgin Tokonome" again!
[MAMORI moans]
[moaning continues]
Mr. Hiiragi, yes! Ah!
It feels so amazing!
[MAMORI moaning]
Poor little virgin.
She has no way to tell
he isn't the real deal.
Now then. I just have to wait
for her to get herself off.
Once she Drives, it's over.
[moaning]
Before long, I'll have a shiny,
new sword for Charlotte.
--[laughs]
--[MAMORI moans]
[MAMORI moaning loudly]
[MIRANDA]
Hmph. Took her long enough.
[gasps]
What? Why are you here?!
[MIRANDA] Impossible!
How'd you know about my plan?
I see no need to answer you.
Fine. My mistake
for underestimating
the girl who beat Saejima.
However...
...very shortly, you'll
realize that raw power
is useless against
an Arm like mine!
[MIREI yells]
[gasps]
[grunting, growls]
[MIREI grunts]
[growls]
[MIREI whimpers]
[MIREI gasps]
[MIREI panting]
[MIRANDA] Yeah. Good
luck bashing your way
through my phantasms.
There, there.
Look, I could say it'll all be
over soon, but that'd be a lie.
This hell is just beginning!
[MIREI yells]
No way!
No one's ever been able to break
through one of my illusions!
No one!
I've been to hell already.
That was nothing.
Hah...
What-- Just what are you?!
Answer!
[MIREI]
I'm not telling you.
[MIRANDA gasps]
[screams]
[MIRANDA]
You cut it?! Impossible!
What kind of monster are you?!
This can't be real!
[MIREI yells]
[MIRANDA shrieks]
[MAMORI] Up and at 'em,
Mirei! Get up, already!
How much daytime
are you gonna waste?
[MIREI groans]
Hey! Come on sleepyhead,
rise and shine!
Five more minutes?
You always seemed like
such a diligent person.
But now I'm seeing
your lazy side.
Sorry about that.
[MAMORI giggles]
[groans]
I had the most amazing dream!
I think it must be thanks
to these posters!
Sweet prince.
[MAMORI giggles]
[MIREI sighs]
Now get your lazy butt outta
there, it's time to get dressed!
Miss Torino told me she needed
our help with something.
Yes. Right away.
[GIRLS murmuring]
[HEXE A]
Whoa, what happened?
[HEXE B]
No idea.
Hibiki...
Just hang in there for
a little bit longer, okay?
I'm working my hardest.
We all are.
We're going to get you
off of this island
and back to your family.
I promise.
[MIREI]
"Giant Girl. Little Heart."