[explosions booming]
[panting]
[MIREI panting]
[rapid gunfire]
[grunts]
[SOLDIER A gasps]
[whimpers]
[whimpers, yells]
[MIREI gasps, yells]
[MIREI grunts]
[MIREI groans]
[gasps]
[MIREI gasps]
[FEMALE HEXE F]
Why's it say "virgin"?
[MAMORI]
No, no!
I know this is confusing,
but the kanji on my shirt
just looks like that word!
It's actually read as
my last name, "Tokonome."
[FEMALE HEXE F]
Her last name's "virgin?"
[MAMORI]
Oh, and for the record.
I am still a virgin, and I don't
think it's fair society shames
people who are doing whatever
they want to their own bodies.
[sighs] Once again,
I think I've said too much...
Can we just drop this?
[CHARLOTTE]
Impressive.
[MAMORI gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
For your info,
the girl you beat,
Saejima, is an A-Class.
[MAMORI whimpers]
[SAEJIMA groans]
--[screams]
--[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
You disgust me.
Arrogant in your abilities
to destroy others.
Aroused at the
thought of violence.
--[SAEJIMA yelps]
--[GIRLS whimper]
[CHARLOTTE]
You have the self-discipline
of a wild animal.
It's trash like you that make
the Hexe disrespect us.
[SAEJIMA shrieks]
Ouch. Now that's nasty.
That's too far.
Please stop hurting her!
Haven't you ever heard not to
kick people when they're down?!
How I punish Saejima is none
of your business, new girl.
Yes, ma'am, I get it.
It's just hard
to ignore is all!
[gasps]
So, please... stop
punishing her physically--
[yelps]
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
Hmph.
[gasps]
[MIREI grunts]
[ANGE giggles]
[MIREI yelps]
[MIREI grunting]
[MAMORI] Stop it!
Please stop whipping her!
[MAMORI]
Are you okay?!
[MAMORI gasps]
No!
Why do you try to kiss me
whenever things get hairy?
Last I checked,
we're both still girls.
[gasps]
[screams]
[MIREI grunts]
[MAMORI]
One day... someone will come.
Even for a silly nobody like me.
I'll have a champion.
[MAMORI] Like a fairy tale
knight on a white horse,
he'll appear and--
[MAMORI]
Wait... hold on.
That's not my fantasy!
Um, where am I?
[KASUMI]
Good. You're awake.
[gasps]
[KASUMI] Don't worry,
we didn't do anything to you
while you were out.
Um... I'm scared...
[KASUMI]
You can relax.
I have no plans to
lay a hand on you,
or hurt you in any way
while you're awake, either.
I promise.
Let's start things off properly.
I'm Kasumi Shigure.
The Commander of Wärter.
And what is your name?
Hi, I'm Mamori Tokonome.
[KASUMI] Miss Tokonome,
do you know why
we brought you here to this...
rather strange, island?
Any guesses at all?
No.
[KASUMI]
Hmm...
Then I'll try
explaining it as best I can.
This is an artificial
island called "Mermaid."
You, me--all of us--have
been brought here
because we're infected
with the Armed Virus.
[MAMORI]
I've never heard of that.
It has no known cure,
but it grants the infected
a special power.
[ANGE] Miss Charlotte,
that new Liberator transfer?
I've restrained her in the
underground disciplinary room.
[CHARLOTTE]
Thank you, Ange. Good work.
That girl not only knew
she had powers,
she knew how to use them
right off the bat.
Could she be the
long-rumored, "soldier?"
There's no proof the
soldier's real, let alone her.
[CHARLOTTE giggles] Soldier or
not, she's still a new transfer,
and new transfers
need to be broken.
Our girl may have been
special back home...
...but on this island,
she is just one of many.
Do you remember us
from the beach?
What? I don't have
any special powers.
I'm just a run-of-the-mill
teenage girl.
"Special powers,"
that's crazy talk.
[KASUMI]
I'll show you.
[KASUMI] This is footage
from earlier today
of your battle versus Saejima.
[MAMORI gasps] Oh, God!
She forced herself on me!
Trust me, I tried to stop her!
I didn't want my first kiss
to be with a girl!
I couldn't keep her
from doing stuff to me
with her hands, either.
I'm sorry! I'm weak!
[KASUMI] You're not
in trouble for any of that.
Just keep watching the film.
Miss Tokonome,
this is your power.
You're able to transform your
body into a weapon
that we call an "Arm."
And we call you girls with this
transforming power, "Extars."
In turn, the girls who
use you Extars,
or as we say, DRIVE you,
are called, "Liberators."
Every single girl you
will meet on this island
falls into one of
those categories.
They're either
Liberators or Extars.
You must have somehow
changed that footage.
Girls can't do that.
Please, tell me this is a joke.
I know it can be a lot
to swallow, but it's all true.
I wouldn't lie to you.
[MAMORI] Yeah, it's-it's just
a lot to take in all at once.
[CHARLOTTE] Are you done
bringing her up to speed?
[gasps]
[KASUMI]
Charlotte?!
Um... Where'd you take her?
The tall blonde girl
I was in the arena with.
You didn't kill her, did you?
Tall blonde girl?
[chuckles] You must mean that
Liberator who rubbed you raw.
She's not being a very good
listener right now.
[MIREI grunts]
[CHARLOTTE] So we're giving
her some obedience training.
Please don't torture her,
lady, I'm begging you!
I can't stand the
thought of violence!
You better get used to it
if you're gonna stay here.
Charlotte, no!
Uh...?
[MAMORI squeals]
[CHARLOTTE laughs]
I need you to be
naked so I can get
the most accurate
measurements possible...
[whimpers]
[CHARLOTTE]
...for your wedding dress.
[FEMALE HEXE A]
You hear the good news?
There's gonna be
a wedding today!
[FEMALE HEXE B]
It's with that new Extar, right?
She barely broke a sweat when
it came to beating Saejima.
I bet she's in high demand.
The Wärter's planning it.
Us girls who're B-Class
and below have no role.
The same as it always is.
Wow...
It's... It's the kind of wedding
dress I've always dreamed of...
Ah... This is my big day...
Sort of...
[MAMORI]
I'm getting married?
It's more like an official
matchmaking ceremony.
How is that different? I mean...
I'm only 16 years old, y'know?
[ANGE]
It's not a romantic coupling.
Though, it could be.
It's a ceremony for matching
you with the Liberator
who will best maximize
your Extar abilities.
Think of it as, finding you the
perfect partner to work with.
So all of this is
just about mastering
that super transforming
power I have?
Yes, that's it, exactly.
But, wait, hold on.
I don't wanna be a weapon.
And I certainly don't want
someone using me to hurt others!
[CHARLOTTE] You have
no choice in this matter!
If you don't go along
with our plans for you,
the person who will suffer the
most for your disobedience
is your friend, whom I would
just love to make scream.
[MAMORI whimpers]
[RITTER B]
Excuse me.
Miss Virgin?
[MAMORI]
It's "Tokonome."
Preparations for your
wedding ceremony are complete.
Please follow me.
[KASUMI] Charlotte,
don't you think you're moving
a little too fast with her?
I mean, a wedding?
On only her
second day on Mermaid?
[CHARLOTTE]
The bigger danger is letting
such a powerful newcomer
do as she pleases.
But still--
Sorry, but the Gouverneur's
given me permission.
C'mon, let's go.
I love the pageantry.
Watching a new Ritter join
the ranks of us Wärter
never gets old.
[bell ringing]
[organ plays]
[MAMORI] Well, it's
certainly the wedding aisle
I've always dreamed of.
I just didn't think the person
standing at the end of it...
[MAMORI]
...would be a girl...
Hello. I'm Tomomi Nukui.
I'm so glad to
meet you, Miss Virgin.
Um, it's Tokonome.
Nukui? She's a trainer--
why's she the groom?
Is this some kind of set-up?
I worry about Tokonome's
ability to cooperate with us.
So I'm hoping Nukui
can break her in.
How cute.
You're almost as
innocent as your name.
It's not virgin!
[clapping]
[CHARLOTTE] I congratulate
you, Miss Tokonome.
This worked out
faster than I thought.
[MAMORI]
What?
Stop, Charlotte!
Don't argue during
a wedding, Kasumi.
[NUKUI] Well, the only thing
left to do now
is to physically test
our compatibility.
What? What do you
mean by "physically"?
What do you think I mean?
Why, Driving you, of course!
Our bodies will become one.
Melting together
like sweet chocolate.
Virgin bride...
Um... It's Tokonome...
[MEIFENG]
Well, howdy, there!
Don't you go givin' me
the stink eye.
I came down here
to help get you out!
Why, you might ask?
Well, you see, I was running
bets on your fight yesterday.
And, boy, did I make
a killing on your win.
Figure I owe you
this much, at least.
Though, it wasn't as easy
getting past them
as I would've liked.
Whoa, mama, you've got
some big knockers.
Silicon or saline?
What?! All natural!
[MIREI growls]
[MEIFENG]
Oh, come on, chill out!
[grunts]
Hey, that hurt!
Is this about me
squeezin' your melons?
They're just so darn nice!
All right, fine. I'm sorry.
How 'bout I make it up
to you by telling where
they took that little
virgin girl you came with--
Tell me.
Oh, man... She's a
feisty one, isn't she?
Anyway, I did like you wanted.
Thank you.
If I let you keep my pay out
from yesterday's bet,
would that be enough to cover
what you did down there?
[gasps] Heck yeah,
that's more than enough!
Thank you!
And who, exactly, are
you betting on this time?
It's not...
[RAIN]
...obvious?
[CHARLOTTE giggles] Please don't
disappoint me, Miss Nukui.
[grunts]
[NUKUI chuckles]
Um... I think I'd like to go
back to my real home, now.
I'm sorry.
But, you're never going back
home to your old life again.
You'll spend the rest of your
life on the Island of Mermaid.
Because we're carriers
of a dangerous virus,
we've all been quarantined.
[gasps]
[MAMORI gasps, moans]
[NUKUI]
Extars activate their powers
when they have a kind of...
out of body experience.
A bit like a trance.
[MAMORI whimpers]
[NUKUI]
And then they lose control.
They become physically
aroused to the point that
their passion bursts forth
in a spasm of pleasure.
I feel it getting closer,
my darling.
[MAMORI squeals]
[moans]
[MAMORI gasps]
My hands will guide you
into paradise.
That's it...
Stop!
Get off me!
Yeah... I don't like it.
--It's gross!
--[NUKUI gasps]
[NUKUI]
It's gross?
That means you're saying
my moves don't work?
[NUKUI growls]
So, you wanna play
hard to get, do you?
Then I've no choice
but to use a more
advanced technique
to excite you!
[knuckles cracking]
A form of pleasure that
comes out of pain!
[gasps]
She repelled me!
Sometimes, if the class
difference is too great,
the Liberator can't Drive.
I'm an A-class Liberator!
There's no way you can
possibly be above that already!
It's impossible!
[NUKUI yells]
--[MAMORI screams]
--[glass shatters]
[NUKUI gasps]
[MAMORI gasps]
I know you!
[NUKUI grunts]
[gasps]
Let's go. Okay?
Yeah.
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE] And just where
do you think you're going?
You're as clever as you are
strong, I'll give you that.
However did you get out
of your dungeon punishment?
Listen. Just don't hurt her.
Are you ready?
Am I ready for what?
[gasps]
[MAMORI whimpers]
[MAMORI]
It's my dream come to life.
Every girl's dream, really.
Getting rescued from certain
doom by a handsome prince.
But why does the
handsome prince in my dream
have to be a beautiful girl?
[MAMORI moans]
[MAMORI] Her touch isn't
the same as it was yesterday.
It feels so much...
[MAMORI gasps, moans]
[MAMORI]
It feels so much better!
[MAMORI gasps]
Fusion Transform.
Liberator Arm!
Ange, go.
[ANGE grunts]
[MIREI grunts]
[ANGE gasps]
I'm not going to hurt you.
I promised her.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Look at it this way:
She found a life partner
today, after all.
Hah. In that case,
both those girls...
...are now enemies of us Warter.
Hey, um, thanks for saving me.
I'm glad I didn't marry her.
[MAMORI] Does it hurt?
Fighting like that?
[MAMORI]
You know, I'm sorry.
I don't think I've ever
introduced myself.
My name... is Mamori Tokonome.
I'm a sophomore at
Sakuragaoka High School.
And I'm 16.
[gasps]
Is, um, something wrong?
Now tell me your name and age!
My name is Mirei.
Shikishima. Fifteen.
Ah! Your first name is
Mirei, that's so pretty!
HuH?! Wait, 15?!
You're... You're... You're!
[gasps] You're a whole
year younger than me
and you look like that?!
[MIREI]
"Zero Arm."