It's no use.
I'm not surprised.
It's the same type of force
field that's around the island.
The Arms we have just
aren't strong enough.
Nimi, maybe you can break
the field by getting bigger.
But if I super-size and
don't break through,
I'll just end up
crushing everyone here!
[RESIDENT A] What's going to
happen to us, Miss Torino?
We'll be fine.
It'll all be over soon enough,
--I promise.
--[footsteps]
[TORINO]
Who are you?
What do you want from
us on this island?
Did the government
order you here, or--
[D5] I take it you're the one
they appointed "Watcher"?
[RESIDENT A gasps]
What is the Watcher?
Nice hair color you got.
I take it that means
you're Enhanced.
Which can only mean...
...you're taking orders
from one group-- Triple A.
[D5]
Yes, but not right now.
Huh?
We came here independently
of any orders.
So that our leader can
get everything she wants.
Answer me!
What have you done to Mamori?
Little Mamo is doing fine.
In fact, she's already adjusting
to being my new partner.
[MOMOKA laughs]
Oh, Mirei, you look so angry.
I'm shaking in my boots!
Scary!
[MIREI]
A3! Tell me what you want.
[MOMOKA]
I already got it!
And now that I do have Mamori.
I'll use her to take
whatever else you have left!
[gasping]
[MIYASATO]
Crap...
Whoa, hold me!
Who's that?
[BOTH]
Kommandeur?
[MOMOKA chuckles]
I'm just getting warmed up!
[laughs]
Dance for me, doggy!
[MIREI groans]
[MOMOKA]
Oh, no! Is little Mirei hurt?
Well, then.
Time...
...to die!
[MOMOKA yells]
[MIREI]
Mamori... Don't give up hope!
[MOMOKA laughing]
They'll never find
all your body parts!
What the--!
Kasumi.
Why're you--
I also have something
to prove with Momoka.
Am I right... Hibiki?
[KASUMI]
Going to Veste?
Are you sure?
The most important thing now is
no one else ends up like me.
Then we had better
be ready to fight.
Oh, Kasumi, I'm so sorry.
You shouldn't've had to
fight alone all this time.
So... from now on...
[HIBIKI]
I'll always be at your side.
All right. Let's go!
[laughs]
Wow! You've got some skills...
...for someone natural born.
But I'm a different
kind of fighter!
Ha!
[gasps]
Lady Lady...
--[MEIFENG] Don't forget me!
--[MIREI gasps]
Meifeng!
Well, Mirei... This is so nice.
There I was, spending all
that time crawling in the mud.
While you traveled around,
living the good life
and making all these
attractive friends.
I hate you!
More than anyone!
[KASUMI gasps]
[KASUMI]
Miss Saejima? Miranda?
What is this?
It's a display of
Valkyrie powers!
Something you can only dream of!
Crap! What's she doing to them?!
It looks like...
the Arm is absorbing them!
[gasps] Oh, no.
And each girl already
carries the virus.
She's absorbing them
to get more of it!
[MOMOKA]
That's right, ladies!
A fresh injection of the virus
is exactly what I'm doing.
It'll turn my Little Mamo Arm...
...into the biggest
problem you've ever faced!
[MIREI gasps]
Oh, no...
Run!
Now I wield the Valkyrie Power!
Watch... this!
[KASUMI gasps]
[screams]
[LADY J screams]
--[RAIN screams]
--[MEIFENG screams]
[gasping]
[groans]
What is that...
that bright light?
[RESEARCHER A]
It's a Valkyrie Effect!
Reaction size, 92.7.
The biggest one we've seen yet!
[A]
Momoka ignored my orders...
...so that she could steal
that power for herself.
Oh, man...
It feels like we could be
even a little more powerful.
But still... it's been more than
enough to take down you bitches.
[MIREI groans]
Mirei's alive?
Dammit.
Try this again.
I'll get medieval.
And kill you... with my hands
instead of some energy blast!
[MOMOKA gasps]
What?!
C'mon!
Hop on!
Move it!
A3...!
[gasps]
[ALL groan]
[ALL groan, scream]
[MOMOKA]
You know I could've stopped 'em
without your help, right?
[D5]
My apologies.
[MOMOKA]
Look at them.
Just like dead flies
on a pile of garbage.
[MIREI groans]
Mamori... Mamori...
Mamori... Help.
Hey. Eyes up here, pervert.
I can tell how
much you miss her.
How 'bout... you can
see her one last time.
[MIREI gasps]
[groans]
[screams]
All your cool island friends
are welcome to join you inside!
Now you won't be so
lonely in defeat.
[MOMOKA]
Best friends, together forever.
And while you girls
enjoy eternity in there,
I'll be using the Arm out here
to do what you hate most, Mirei.
Killing people. Lots and
lots of innocent people!
[laughs]
[MIREI groans]
Mamori?
Where am I?
I'm inside of her...
when she's an Arm.
So am I just a collection
of thoughts now? Am I dead?
[LADY J, RAIN yelping]
Lady Lady?
Hey! Where are you guys?
[LADY J, RAIN yelping]
Lady Lady!
[KASUMI, HIBIKI yelping]
Shigure!
[MEIFENG, AKIRA yelping]
Meifeng! Akira!
Momoka's got Mamori sucking
the virus right out of them!
[MIREI grunts]
[MIREI yelps]
[gags]
It's the virus.
Its power is flowing into me.
It feels so right.
With their power, you'll reach
levels never dreamed of!
If you're actually able to get
a Valkyrie Effect's
size over 100%...
...the virus will
evolve and transform
into an even stronger strain.
Huh?
[D5]
The force field's gone.
[E9]
Well, that's weird.
The Powers that Be finally
noticed what we've been up to.
[D5]
Satellite weapon!
[E9]
Miss A3!
Don't worry, guys, I got this.
[MOMOKA]
You're even dumber than Mirei,
if you think a space laser
is enough to stop me!
[RESEARCHER A]
The satellite's offline.
[A] That was our last,
best chance to stop them.
[laughs]
Being invincible is the coolest!
Need more...
...more power!
I'll start by sucking the virus
out of all the other
girls down on Mermaid!
Then, I'll drain everyone dry
on the other four islands.
I will take back everything
that was ever taken from me.
And then I will
have... my revenge!
A3!
You came back!
Yes...
The power of every virus
carrier will soon be mine...
...stored right here,
in Little Mamo's Arm.
[MIREI]
No.
What the--?
[MIREI]
I said, no.
[MOMOKA]
Mirei? Is that you?
[MIREI]
You can violate me...
...steal the virus
that empowers me...
but you can't defeat me.
As long as I still have a
reason to live--to fight--
I swear to you...
I will fight!
[MIREI grunts]
[yells]
[groans]
Mamori...
[hisses]
[gasps]
[MIREI]
There you are!
Don't give up hope.
Hold on.
A3... These are her bindings.
I failed you.
I couldn't stop her.
But, please, my love...
Give me another chance.
[MIREI]
I promise, Mamori...
[MIREI] I won't just
get you out of here.
I'll bring you back
to your family!
[MIREI growling]
[MIREI gasps]
Mamori!
[MIREI]
You're free.
[MAMORI]
Mirei? Is that you?
That girl, Momoka,
she captured me.
That's over with, 'kay?
Let's get out of
this awful place.
[MAMORI]
Yeah, but how?
With our love... like always.
What?!
What in the hell?!
[GROUP gasps]
[MEIFENG]
Ouchy!
How'd we... get back?
Yeah, what happened?
[LADY J]
I'll take it.
They're still there!
[MOMOKA]
What in the hell is going on?!
[gasps]
I don't remember giving you
girls permission to leave!
Mirei... Use me again.
Just do it. Iit's the only
way to save the others.
Here we go.
[MEIFENG gasps]
Where did that come from?
Uh-oh.
Is this...
They joined... The Perfect Form.
Liberator and Extar
together as one.
Reaction size, 100%.
I didn't know it
was actually real.
[MOMOKA] It's the Valkyrie...
the Valkyrie Drive?
I'll make you pay.
How dare you
disrespect me, Mirei!
[D5] Please A3...
Use me to destroy her.
Then here goes.
[yells]
This ends tonight... A3.
Shut up, Mirei!
[screaming]
[gasps]
All right! Now's our
chance to escape!
Let's go!
Give her back!
Mamo's mine!
She's my Arm and I can do
whatever I want with her!
[MIREI]
That's not happening.
I'm sick of you blocking me from
doing what needs to be done!
E9, c'mere!
[E9]
Yes, ma'am!
[E9 squeals]
[MOMOKA] Now this... is the
true power of a Soldier Arm!
--Oh, no.
--What?!
Now she's a giant robot?!
This way!
Move it, ladies!
Nimi! Faster!
Hold on. Mirei's going
to need our help!
[MOMOKA giggles]
I'll crush you like a paper cup.
[NIMI yells]
[MOMOKA groans]
Now's your chance, guys!
[KASUMI yells]
[MOMOKA]
What?!
[MIREI]
A3!
[MOMOKA groans]
You bitch...
I'll kill you.
You took my power...!
[MAMORI] We have to help
everyone... Even our enemies.
Right.
[MOMOKA yells]
[pants]
A3... Stop.
[MOMOKA gasps]
No more fighting...
...Momoka.
[MOMOKA gasps]
[growls]
[whimpers]
What the--?
Our Arms, they-- they vanished!
[KASUMI]
I don't understand it.
Must be another power
of the Soldier Arms.
[MOMOKA] You're sucking
in the Armed Virus,
without consuming me.
You're better than I ever
gave you credit for, Mirei.
I can't believe it.
The virus is gone.
[RITTER A]
What's that floating orb?
Guys, I feel weird.
Like our powers...
have vanished.
Oh, Mirei... and Mamori.
Gouverneur Charlotte,
the virus... is no more.
We can leave.
We're going... back home.
All the colors of the rainbow.
Beautiful.
That flash is the
ultimate Valkyrie Light.
[A]
Just as we long suspected.
The absorbed virus transformed
into a new lifeform altogether--
Evolution's miracle.
[A]
That is what happens when
the reaction from a Valkyrie
Effect goes over 100%.
Oh, Mirei...
Mamori...
I'm finally...
For the first time, I'm excited
to have these super powers.
I can use them to help
people everywhere.
And make the world better.
You're right.
[MAMORI]
So...
--...let's shine!
--[MIREI] Let's shine!
So, you're Island Five's
Watcher, Torino Kazami, right?
I'm going to need a
full report from you.
I understand.
One more thing-- Some names
on this list of exiles...
They're not among any
of the returnees.
Don't worry about them.
They're out there.
Finding a better use for what
they learned on the island.
Mamori, are you sure
you wanna do this?
Over going home?
Believe me, I do still
dream of going home,
of seeing my mom and dad
and old friends again.
But...
There are so many
people around the world
that I want to use our powers
to help before I go back.
We can remove the Armed Virus
from anyone who carries it
and give them their lives again.
If we can prevent just one girl
from having to go through
what we did, we owe it to her.
So, yeah. I'm sure
I wanna do this.
Whatever you want, it's fine.
But what I still don't get is
why Meifeng's coming with us.
I wanna see what
Super Mamori does next!
And to be blunt-- [giggles]
It sounds like there's
money to be made.
That'll be a lot of work--
Just you two, saving the world.
So we're here to help.
Helping because you
want to, right?
That's free will, baby!
Great!
We're all here!
Let's go.
[MAMORI] Our happy ending...
has just begun.