All right, ladies!
It's time to place your bets!
The dice are cast,
so put your money down.
With odds like these,
you're bound to get rich!
[HEXE A]
Odd!
[HEXE B]
Even!
[HEXE C]
Odd!
[chuckles]
Heh! Now--
They're coming!
[gasping]
How'd they find us?!
[FUTABA yelps]
All of you are
now under arrest!
[FUTABA] Everyone,
get out of here! Run for it!
There's a back way!
Take it, I'll follow!
The money! We can't leave it!
You gonna spend it in jail?!
Of course not, go!
[HEXES whimper]
[MEIFENG]
No! Not in the face!
[BOOKMAKER grunts]
[MEIFENG groaning]
Stop! Please!
I don't wanna die!
Don't do this! No!
Please not there,
anywhere but there!
Don't think
they're coming back.
I guess that's
mission accomplished.
Strange how it doesn't
even occur to them
that we might've set them up.
[laughing]
[FUTABA, HYOUKO, MEIFENG]
Cheers!
Whoo! Nothin' like some
non-alcoholic grape juice
after pullin' off a good scam.
I agree. It has a certain class.
The sweet and tart
are very balanced.
It tastes just sour enough
to be exciting.
Speaking of,
that acting of yours
was pretty intense, Futaba.
Why, thank you.
Yeah, and what
about you, Meifeng?
"Not there! Anywhere but there!"
Ha! You really went
for the Oscar, huh?
Shut up! Look, if you
don't like how I do it,
then next time,
you take the part,
and we'll hit you for real.
Simmer down, girls.
Everything worked out perfectly.
What is there to fight about
if we're filthy rich?
We do make a good team.
Agreed.
It helps that we have
our own personal Ritter.
Know what I mean, Hyouko?
And in castle management,
we have Futaba Kirii.
And to sell all
the goods we steal?
We have Meifeng.
[laughing]
[MEIFENG]
Yup! Gotta hand it to us--
We're an awesome trio.
[HYOUKO] Good work, Ritter.
You can go. I'll take over.
Heh!
[MEIFENG] So, did you get
the paper trail sorted out?
[FUTABA]
Of course.
I adjusted the on-file
inventory last night.
It should be as good as if
these supplies were never here.
I sack the castle.
I make sure she
doesn't get caught.
And I sell the goodies!
[chuckling]
[GIRLS murmuring]
[RESIDENT A]
Oh, look! Meifeng's here!
I wonder what
she brought this time?
[RESIDENT B]
Wow! That's so pretty!
How much do you think
she'll want for it?
[RESIDENT C]
What are these?
I've never seen
anything like them.
[murmuring continues
Ho, ho, ho! Behold,
your out-of-season,
genderbent Santa Claus'
triumphant return!
[GIRLS murmuring]
--[MAMORI gasps]
--[MEIFENG chuckles]
You're a blessing as always,
dear. Good to see you!
Everything's okay
though, right?
You know, those Warter people,
they aren't going to
follow you again, are they?
Yup, it's all good!
This time, I made sure
I could cover my tracks!
[TORINO] Thanks, Meifeng.
It puts me at ease to know that.
Hey! Wow, it's a Guru-Neko!
Huh? What's a Guru-Neko?
Have you never seen one before?
Everybody thought he was
the coolest thing ever
back when I was still little.
Hey!
Did you just ask yourself if my
growth wasn't stunted somehow?
[MIREI groans]
[MAMORI]
Guru-Neko was my favorite.
I had everything!
I even put erasers shaped like
his head on all my pencils!
[MEIFENG] Hm... So this was
your favorite toy, then.
Well, actually, there was one
Guru-Neko toy I never could get.
They had this
huge plushie for a raffle.
Mom grounded me
for wasting my allowance.
I miss that now... Ya know?
Back then, I kinda
took it for granted.
[sighs]
So what gives? Are you
gonna introduce your friend?
Oh. This guy?
He's a reminder that everyone's
tastes are different.
[FUTABA]
Hmm...?
[HYOUKO]
Well, anyway.
The Mermaid Festival's
coming up soon.
How're the books for the
beauty pageant coming along?
They're filling up even faster
than they did the last time.
It's the biggest contest
of the year;
who wouldn't wanna make a bet?
Are we looking at the
same favorites as before?
Yeah, you guessed it. Get ready
for the long-awaited rematch
between Charlotte and Lady J.
Oh, yeah. I still remember the
stupid look on Charlotte's face
when she realized
Lady J had beaten her.
Haven't had a laugh
like that in ages.
Like, honestly,
what'd she expect?
She spread the word all over
that anyone could join,
no questions asked. So of course
Lady Lady showed up!
She was so mad!
Yeah, I'll say.
I'd never seen her throw such
a fit. The mess was huge.
[MEIFENG sighs]
Kinda makes ya think, though.
If we could help
some other girl to win,
with the odds this tilted,
the three of us could make
a friggin' killing off of it.
No one would know her, so...
...we wouldn't have
to pay out a penny.
All we have to do is find some
hot chick no one knows about.
As if it'd be that easy.
We'd need a miracle
if we want--
[MEIFENG]
Hey... Futaba.
You are a member of the festival
committee this year, aren't ya?
Yes, I am. Why do you ask?
I was just wondering how
preparations were coming along.
Pick a prize for the pageant?
We have. Same as last year.
The victor goes home with
a dozen cans of peaches.
Gotcha. How hard
would it be for you
to change that
to something else?
Well... It kind of
depends on what to.
But, yes, I could probably
pull a few strings.
Heh!
The Mermaid Festival?
You're still pretty new
to this place,
so I doubt you've heard of it.
But, yeah, it's a pretty
big deal to the locals.
We do food stands, competitions,
all sorts of fun stuff.
It's like a giant party!
[gasps]
That's cool!
Is it okay for us
to come, though?
Why else would
I tell you about it?
Look, as long as
the festival's going on,
everyone puts that
political crap aside!
For that time only, people
from the town and the castle
can all hang out and unwind!
Anyway, we put on
this Beauty Pageant--
It's like the main event
of the whole party. Check it!
Wow! Is that what I think?
It sure is! I was just as
surprised as you are!
But yeah, I remember you sayin'
you like this cat thing,
so when I saw that it was our
prize, I had to show you!
[sighs]
[MAMORI]
So cute!
Thanks, but,
I don't have a chance
of winning a beauty pageant.
The only thing that stands out
about me is how small I am.
You shouldn't
underestimate yourself.
Aw, thanks, Mirei.
[groans] Well... Maybe you
don't have to win it yourself.
I don't know if you're friends
with any bombshells,
but if you are, then
maybe you could ask her
to win the pageant for you.
Okay, but what exactly does
a bombshell look like?
Oh, you know.
Someone with long legs,
luscious blonde hair.
And let's see,
a voluptuous body with curves
in all the right places.
Ohh, and if she acted
a little bit boyish,
at a competition with only
girls, it'd be perfect!
[MEIFENG] Oh yeah, if you
could find someone like that,
you'd have your
cat toy in the bag!
But if such a beautiful
person existed,
do you really think
she'd be willing to enter
the pageant for me?
Oh, well, who's to say? Depends
on how much they like ya.
[MAMORI giggles]
[MEIFENG] It's time for beauty
pageant training to commence!
Prepare to be beautified!
[MAMORI]
Woo-hoo!
All right, we'll start
with your posture!
This oughtta flatten out
that belly of yours!
[MIREI grunting]
[MEIFENG] Next, I want you
to raise those hips!
[MIREI grunting]
We're gonna train
those breasts to stand tall!
[MIREI grunts]
[groans]
[sighs]
[MIREI, MAMORI grunting]
Now that we've
got you trained up,
all we need's a
smokin' hot outfit!
What do you think
about this idea?
I cooked up a little
somethin' myself!
I was thinking something
more professional.
I say we go bolder!
Check this one out!
Hey! That just gave me
another idea!
Considering our model,
perhaps we should go
for something a little
more adult, like this!
I feel like that's
a little too bold.
[gasps]
Here's an idea!
What if we dressed her
up in something
like Mr. Hiiragi might wear?
[GROUP sighs]
Oh. Well, no worries
if you don't want to.
[yawns]
Guess we should probably
call it a night soon, huh?
[gasps] No, let's
try to keep going.
Mirei's been training really
hard to win this pageant,
so I need to work
just as hard to help her.
After all, she's only
doing this for me.
Ah. All right, just a
little bit longer, then.
[CHARLOTTE]
I assume that preparations
for the festival are
going well so far?
Yes, ma'am. We've no
issues to report.
[CHARLOTTE] No? Well,
isn't that good to hear?
Oh, by the way.
I think I may join
the beauty pageant again.
I was wondering how you
feel that might go for me.
Oh! You'd surely win!
I agree! The girls
of Mermaid Island
are eager to see
your beauty on stage!
I have no doubt that the contest
would be a rout in your favor!
[CHARLOTTE laughs]
If that's really true,
I suppose I have no choice
but to toss my hat in.
I trust that you won't allow
any incidents at this pageant.
We wouldn't want a repeat of
last year, now, would we?
No, I don't believe that
would bode well for anyone.
[BOTH]
Yes, ma'am.
[CHARLOTTE giggles]
[fireworks popping]
Amazing!
[NIMI]
Hey, Mamori!
[MAMORI]
Hmm?
Oh! Hi, Nimi!
Heh! Welcome to
the Mermaid Festival!
Let me show you around,
to repay you for
helping out me and Noe!
Speaking of, she and I have
started our own foodstand!
Can I offer you a free sample?
[NOE yells]
[MAMORI whimpers]
--[MAMORI sighs]
--[SAEJIMA chuckles]
[BOTH groan]
[screams]
[MIREI growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[MAMORI giggles]
So are you having a good time?
Sure am!
Everyone's been so nice.
I just wish that people from
the town and the castle
could always get
along like this.
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention.
The beauty pageant
will commence shortly.
[MAMORI gasps]
[CROWD cheering]
[KOUZUKI sighs]
[CROWD squealing]
Look! It's about
to be Mirei's turn!
No. I can't look,
I'm just too nervous!
Why would you be nervous? She's
the one who's goin' out there!
C'mon, we gotta support her!
Don't miss the big moment!
Yeah. Okay.
[ANNOUNCER]
Contestant number 13.
Mirei Shikishima.
[CROWD screaming]
Perfect posture!
Her belly's totally flat!
Have any of you seen her before?
[CROWD screaming]
She's beautiful!
[MEIFENG] Nailed it!
This thing's in the bag!
I'm about to make
so much frickin' money!
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies. The
time has come for everyone
to vote on their
favorite contestant.
[ANNOUNCER]
The votes are in.
The winner of the Mermaid
Festival Beauty Pageant is...
--[drumroll]
--Please be Mirei...
Hey, don't worry!
The atmosphere was totally in
Mirei's favor, I could feel it!
[ANNOUNCER]
Contestant number 12!
Miss Charlotte Scharsen!
--Wow! She really did it!
--What'd I tell ya?!
--Huh...?
--Uh?
[BOTH gasp]
[laughs]
[CROWD cheering]
[CHARLOTTE sighs]
[MEIFENG growls]
[MEIFENG]
Yup. Just as I suspected.
Meifeng?!
What on earth are
you doing in there?
[MEIFENG] I could tell
the pageant was rigged,
so I asked myself, if I wanted
to dispose of the truth,
where would I put it?
Oh, look! Practically
everyone voted for Mirei!
Huh.
Someone must have
swapped the boxes!
[growls]
[MEIFENG]
Talk! Why'd you do it?!
We've been taking
too many risks lately.
This is our chance to
build up some good will
with the powers that be.
The money's been
good, hasn't it?
It only makes sense that we'd
want a bit of security next.
We've come too far
to risk a shut down.
[MEIFENG] So not only
did you go behind my back,
you did it to go
kiss Charlotte's butt.
You know me, girls. I've got
nothin' against pullin' out
a dirty trick or two, so long
as it makes me some money.
But this is just sick.
We cheat to screw authority
over, not to help it!
Now you're just
as bad as they are!
As always, you've a
fascinating point of view.
But as you may have noticed,
there're two of us.
So I think our perspective
might matter more.
Oh, come on, Hyouko,
you know me better than that.
I would never go on
a foxhunt all alone.
[BOTH gasp]
[MEIFENG] Three against two!
How the tides have turned.
We heard everything you said!
Mirei put in a lot of work
on this pageant.
She deserved to win!
You ruined that for her,
and I'm not gonna let you
get away with it!
They're all yours. Make 'em pay.
Are you ready, then?
[MAMORI]
Mm. Yes.
[MAMORI gasps]
[moans]
[MAMORI moaning]
[yelps]
Do we really have to go so far?
They see me!
[gasps]
[MIREI]
It's much faster this way.
[MAMORI moans]
They're Driving so passionately.
[gasps] Futaba!
We need to do the same!
Very well. Do it!
[FUTABA sighs]
[moans]
Yes! Keep on going,
you're driving me wild!
[MAMORI gasps]
[MAMORI moans]
[FUTABA, HYOUKO moan]
--[MAMORI] ♪ Ahh... ♪
--[FUTABA moans]
Hah!
You won't escape.
[HYOUKO grunts]
Just a decoy?
[MEIFENG] Mirei should be
able to take them on easy.
It looks like
my work here is done.
[HYOUKO] You would
hand off the tough job.
Don't expect your
bodyguard to save you.
She'll be busy dancing with
my decoys for quite some time.
You're alone.
And without a dancing partner
for yourself, you can't do much.
[MEIFENG]
Heh.
[gasps]
You think you can pay us off,
after all you've done?!
That's a desperate move,
even for you!
Shut up! The only
thing I'm ever givin'
a two-faced, brown-nosing,
turncoat like you
is a beat down!
This is for me. I use it
to throw myself a party.
To set my soul on fire.
To get that sweet release.
What?!
[laughs]
[giggles]
What the--?! You can't
make an Arm out of money!
[MEIFENG]
Actually, I did the opposite!
I used that cash as a Liberator.
I'm an Extar who can turn
herself into an Arm!
Now get ready to see what
the power of money can do!
Heh! Come on!
[HYOUKO grunts]
[MEIFENG]
I didn't wanna fight you
'cause it costs a lotta maid!
It's too bad money is the only
thing that gets you off!
At least I don't have
to lick someone's tit!
[MEIFENG grunts]
Well, you can
color me impressed.
I never thought I'd need
my ace to deal with you.
[HYOUKO yells]
[gasps]
Come on, is that all
the fight you've got?!
[gasps]
Seriously?!
How desperate are you?
Yeah, well. You can't blame
a girl for tryin', right?
I suppose not.
Goodbye, Meifeng.
It was certainly fun
while it lasted.
Yeah, that it was.
[HYOUKO screams]
[MEIFENG]
Well, this sucks.
Between the fight and the
pageant, I'm deep in the red.
Meifeng!
Are you okay? What happened?
Ah! Oh my!
Yeah. Don't worry, I handled it.
Wasn't too hard.
[CROWD murmuring]
[HEXE D] "We two have been
found guilty of tampering with
the votes in the Mermaid
Island Beauty Pageant"?
[CHARLOTTE]
What do you mean,
you're revoking my
beauty pageant victory?
On what grounds?!
Foul play. I received
a report of it sometime
after the voting was concluded.
A completely baseless accus--
If you would prefer it, I could
launch a full investigation.
But that investigation
would be public,
and would likely expose all
who had a role in the planning.
[growls]
Is... that for me?!
It's the least I could do.
Consider it a thank you
for having my back earlier.
You're welcome.
Wait, does this mean that--
Are you saying I can
actually keep it?!
That's right, he's all yours!
Ah! Thank you so much, Meifeng!
You're the best!
[MEIFENG laughs]
There's just one thing.
I'm a bit short on cash.
You don't mind helpin' me
make some, right?
[MIREI]
"To Believe."