[FATHER]
What's wrong with her?!
[MAMORI gasps]
[MOTHER] They found it
during her last physical.
The doctors are calling it...
They say it's...
...an abnormality! [sobs]
[FATHER] Does she have
any of the symptoms yet?
[MOTHER sobs]
Why is this happening to her...?
My little girl...
My little Mamori...
[MOTHER sobs]
[MAMORI] They cried and
argued for hours that night,
but I was still
too young to understand
why my parents were so upset.
[MAMORI] Looking back, I should
have just run up and hugged her
and said, "Don't cry, Mommy!
Everything's gonna be okay!
I'm fine!"
[gasps]
[MAMORI]
But maybe I held back,
because even as a
little girl... I knew.
[MAMORI] Deep down, I knew.
In fact, I've always known.
[MAMORI]
The truth.
That I'm not a normal girl.
[groans]
Huh...?
[gasps, yelps]
A crab...?
[MAMORI]
Why am I at the beach?
How'd I get here?
And, wait--where is here?
Did those two guys kidnap me?
[whimpers]
Please be a dream...
[RITTER A] Unregistered
entity is on the move, ma'am.
I guess she finally woke up.
[KASUMI]
Then let's test her.
Intercept her with
the nearest Ritter.
[beeping]
[RITTER B]
Miyasato and Kouzuki are near.
What is with them?
Always slacking off.
[RITTER A] Attention,
Miss Miyasato and Miss Kouzuki.
Please check in.
Sorry, Miyasato's busy.
Kouzuki can't talk
either--she's training.
[KASUMI]
You know I can see you!
[KOUZUKI, MIYASATO gasp]
Kommandeur Kasumi?!
[BOTH chattering]
[KASUMI]
I have a job for you.
Go to Point 302. and test
the aptitude of the new student.
[sighs]
[MAMORI] I've never seen
a beach this empty... and hot.
[MAMORI]
What do I do now?
[MAMORI] Maybe I can
cut through the jungle?
No, I can't! There might be
giant bugs hiding there!
I'm just a teenage girl
raised in the big city!
I can't handle stress like this!
[MIYASATO]
Hey, kid, are you lost?
[gasps]
[MIYASATO]
Why, hello there.
Are you all alone?
[sighs]
I'm saved!
So, um, can one of you
tell me where we are?
Or even better, just let me
borrow your phone
so I can call someone
to pick me up.
[laughing]
[MAMORI]
Why're you laughing?
It's what's on your shirt, kid!
It says "Virgin!"
[laughter continues]
[gasps]
Way to tell the whole world
what a loser you are!
I'm sure some perv out
there will find it hot.
No! That's not true!
It's just a
spelling coincidence.
You see, the Kanji for
my last name looks the same.
To-ko-no-me! That's what
it really spells!
So you're not a virgin?
I guess you really can't
judge a book by its cover.
Well, I didn't quite say that.
I've actually never
been with a boy...
So I am a virgin...
But the shirt just says
Tokonome--my last name!
Now that we're clear,
phone please?
So, Tokonome the Virgin,
which one are you?
Liberator?
Or are you... an Extar like me?
Lib... erator? Extar?
What're you talking about?
Are those good or bad things?
[BOTH giggle]
Let's show her. Ready?
[KOUZUKI moans]
[gasps]
[moaning continues]
[MAMORI whimpers]
--[MAMORI] They're perverts?
--[KOUZUKI] Oh, yeah! That's it!
Keep going! Yeah!
[MIYASATO giggles] She's
watching you get turned on.
She likes it.
I like being watched!
Keep rubbing!
We gotta give her the moneyshot!
[KOUZUKI moans]
Harder! Faster!
You've almost got it! Come on!
[KOUZUKI gasps]
[screams]
[MAMORI grunts]
[gasps]
You understand now?
I'm even more confused.
I just saw a girl on the beach
morph into a gun!
Well, well. So you haven't
been awakened yet?
[MAMORI]
Awakened?
That's right. So I'm gonna
be your alarm clock.
[gasps]
[ringing]
New transfer!
That's twice in one day!
What?!
What the...?
[grunts]
--[MAMORI yelps]
--[gasps]
[gasps]
What?! This can't be!
Are you already in Drive?
[MAMORI gasps]
Why're you protecting her?
Are you two friends?
No! We've never even met!
Okay?
Well, fine, then.
One new transfer or two,
it makes no difference to me.
C'mon! Lemme see
those powers, girls!
[MIYASATO]
Damn, she's fast!
[yells]
What the--?
[MAMORI gasps]
[MAMORI]
Why're you... grabbing me...
...on the boob?
[grunts]
[gasps]
I'm not gonna stand still
and watch you two get handsy!
[gasps]
Eat this!
[MAMORI]
So this is it...
I'm going to die...
[MAMORI]
It's weird, though...
It doesn't hurt.
[MAMORI]
You'd think getting blown up
would be the worst feeling ever.
Instead...
[MAMORI]
...I feel good.
[MAMORI gasps]
A new Liberator
has just awakened.
Extar as well.
And at the same time.
[RITTER A]
Drive spotted!
[KASUMI gasps]
They already match?
With no adjustment period?!
[MIYASATO gasps]
What in the hell...?
[KASUMI]
Retreat!
Kommandeur?
[KASUMI]
Move!
Oh, shit!
[MIYASATO, KOUZUKI scream]
[MAMORI] That first day
on Mermaid island...
...I had no idea
what had happened to me.
It was as scary
as it was pleasurable.
[MAMORI]
But in that confused haze
is how I met her--
Mirei Shikishima.
[MAMORI] Now I know there
was nothing random about it.
It was fate.
Gouverneur, sir.
This new report will
be of great interest to you.
The Information Division
detected two new transfers.
And both have
awakened, successfully.
Even better is that one's
a Liberator and one's an Extar.
And you'll be even
more happy to learn that
immediately upon awakening,
they were able to Drive.
They put on quite a show.
Injuries?
[groans]
[CHARLOTTE]
They'll both recover fine.
C-class girls... Why would
Kasumi send those two bozos
to greet the new transfers?
[AKIRA] Miss Charlotte.
Where are the new transfers?
[giggles]
Well, we are on
an island, aren't we?
We'll find them soon enough.
There's only one place
for them to go.
[birds squawking]
[MAMORI groans]
[gasps]
We're alive!
Where are those girls
who tried to kill us?
You rescued me. And we...
we're total strangers.
Well... Thanks for that.
I owe you big time.
[MAMORI] So, since you seem
to know what you're doing,
do you know where we are?
Oh, okay...
[gasps]
I can still walk, you know.
I didn't really get hurt
during the battle.
You can put me down whenever.
[hissing]
[MAMORI]
Huh...? Ah?
[squeals]
Wait! Wait! Wait! [squeals]
On second thought, carry me
until we're outta the jungle!
I can feel their
hot, flicking tongues
getting closer with every hiss!
[screams]
Go! Go, go, go!
[KASUMI]
You want to use Saejima?
Yes. Unlike those two
beach bimbos, she's an A-class.
The perfect rank for assessing
our two new transfers.
[KASUMI] To be blunt, she has
some personality issues--
[CHARLOTTE]
Kasumi, enough.
Personality issues
can be overlooked.
Besides, finding new talent's
all that matters.
No second-guessing,
no hesitating.
[KASUMI] So you're
ordering me to use Saejima.
You got it.
Huh. That little spy's
faster than I thought.
Listen up, you guys!
We got two new transfers coming!
For real?
It's been weeks
since we had some.
And here's the coolest part:
Wärter wants to test them
against Saejima!
[GIRL STUDENTS chattering]
All right then, time to
open up the bettin'!
Two-to-one odds for Saejima.
Nine to one for them.
This should be good, so the
minimum bet is one Maid!
I'll put two on Saejima.
[FEMALE HEXE F]
Make that four for me!
Ladies, please,
please, slow down!
So, um, are we just walking, or
do you know where we're going?
[gasps]
Sorry! You can just ignore me...
Yeah...
[whimpers]
[gasps]
That's... a castle?
[sighs, giggles]
Well, come on, let's go!
There has to be someone there!
[sighs]
Um...
Hello?
Is there anyone home
in this castle?
[MAMORI grunts]
[GIRLS cheering]
[MAMORI gasps]
[cheering continues]
From your innocent looks, I
assume you're the new transfers.
[gasps]
[growls]
You're cute, so I'm
gonna start right away.
It'll be fun having
some new girls
to help me release my stress!
[SLAVE GIRL grunts, whimpers]
[gasps]
[SAEJIMA]
Heh.
[SLAVE GIRL moans]
[gasps] Why're you
hurting her like that?!
Please, just let her go!
[SAEJIMA] Oh, honey,
you're so innocent.
I know this might
look bad, but trust me--
It's exactly what she wants.
Roughing her up
like this is the only way
she can get excited down there.
She's a hard-core masochist!
[SLAVE GIRL moaning]
[SAEJIMA laughs]
It's like...
...the same thing that
happened on the beach.
Slave Girl makes a
pretty good Liberate Arm--
for a slut who lets anyone
take her for a spin.
So then...
Let's get started!
[MAMORI]
No!
Hey, stop--and
show me--your Arm!
[MAMORI gasps]
I don't get it.
Why won't they Drive this time?
Maybe the beach was
just a... one time thing.
[KASUMI] Or maybe they're
making a conscious choice
not to fight again.
[MEIFENG]
They're just runnin'!
They should at least
try to please the crowd!
Otherwise, I'm the one
who's gonna take the blame!
[RAIN]
Meifeng.
[gasps]
I'll bet one Maid on
the two new transfers.
Uh... Sure thing.
One Maid, right.
[MEIFENG]
Lady Lady.
[SAEJIMA yells]
[gasps]
[MAMORI grunts]
[MAMORI whimpers]
[SAEJIMA] It sucks that
you're not putting up a fight.
But--
[MAMORI whimpers]
The sadist in me can't resist
a good old-fashioned curb-stomp!
Just... tell them we surrender.
Maybe if we apologize
for intruding on their castle,
they'll leave us alone.
[SAEJIMA chuckles]
Never.
[gasps]
We have no future...
by showing weakness.
Now just relax.
[gasps]
[MAMORI]
What-- What is this feeling?
It's like something's
bubbling up deep inside me.
[MAMORI whimpers]
[MAMORI moans]
[moaning continues]
[MAMORI]
Oh, god! She's molesting me!
But... it feels so good!
Her hand... Her fingers!
I think-- I think I'm...
...being deflowered!
Fusion Transform.
Liberator Arm!
--They're Driving!
--It's about time.
All right, you finally
came to the party.
[yells]
[SAEJIMA growls]
[SAEJIMA gasps]
My arm! What's happening to me?!
[gasping]
What...? They beat her...
The rookies won.
They took down Saejima.
I wasn't expecting that.
Could it really be...
that these girls
are even stronger
than those of A Class?
[AKIRA]
Are they soldiers?
With that power... perhaps.
[RAIN giggles]
Well, this is starting
to get interesting.
But at least...
...now I won't be bored.
[gasps]
[yelps]
What... you did...
with your hands...
[MAMORI] Why do you think
I'd be okay with that?
Do you know... you're my first?
[FEMALE HEXE G laughs]
Oh my god, look at her chest!
It says "virgin" on it!
[laughs]
[gasps]
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Well, not anymore!
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
I can't believe she left
the house in that.
No! That's not it!
Listen to me, it's my last name!
Tokonome! They look the same!
It doesn't say "virgin." Why
would I wear a shirt like that?!
How many times
do I have to tell you?!
[MAMORI]
"The Wedding Aisle."