--[whip cracking]
--[screaming]
You let a turncoat
get the jump on you...
...which allowed our prisoner
to literally walk out of here.
Stupid bimbos...
You have lost the right to ever
again call yourselves
Ritters of Warter.
No! Please forgive us,
Miss Charlotte!
We're sorry!
Will you let us down now?
Not today, ladies.
[KOUSUKI screams]
[MIYASATO screams]
--[ANGE giggles]
--[GIRLS screaming]
[rappid whip cracking
[giggles]
[AKIRA] Though the virus
may grant us powers,
we still retain Man's ability to
build and run a civil society.
It is essential that outsiders
watching this island
see such restraint.
That is why I first
established the Warter
and personally lead it
in all its actions.
In turn, I ask each and
every one of you
for your support
in maintaining order.
If we can show them that,
we can soon leave this
island and return home!
[GIRLS cheering]
[RAIN] Akira Hiiragi... the only
man on this entire island.
The Gouverneur of Warter.
And...
...one of the biggest
hypocrites in the world.
[MAMORI sighs]
[stomach growls]
One omelette, please...
And, Mom, can you
re-fill my bowl of rice?
And beef... Thank you...
That's nice...
[gasps]
I forgot.
We ran away... and we've
been camping for the last day.
[screams]
[MAMORI]
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa-oh!
I know we're on the beach,
but isn't that kinda skimpy?!
Your breakfast, Miss.
[gasps]
Thanks, I really needed that.
I'll add cooking
to your skill chart.
I just wish we had some fresh
lemonade or something
to wash it down.
I should have
known better, Miss.
[MAMORI] What?!
No, it's fine! I'm not mad!
Um... Why, uh...
Why are you suddenly
speaking so formal to me?
Because you're my elder.
C'mon. None of that
stuff matters out here.
Besides, I'm such a petite girl,
when we stand side-by-side,
you look way older
than me, anyway.
You're a runt, that's true.
[groans] I said "petite," that's
your hint to not be so blunt!
Whenever I think about
being small it depresses me.
I'm sorry.
We should find
a way off this place
before the castle girls find us.
Over there.
[MAMORI]
Mm?
What is that?
One of the footings
for the clear dome
that seals off
this entire island.
Is there any way
around it or under it?
She was right.
[KASUMI] You, me--all of us--
have been brought here
because we're infected
with the Armed Virus.
[NUKUI] But, you're
never going back home
to your old life again.
[MAMORI] So... we're
stuck here with a bunch of
crazy, violent girls
for the rest of our lives?
That's... so depressing.
[MAMORI whimpers]
--[engine rumbles]
--[gravel crunches]
[MEIFENG]
Well, there ya are! Hey!
[MEIFENG giggles]
[MAMORI]
Huh...?
[gulping]
Ah! I really needed that!
Thanks for picking us up,
Miss-- Ah! What was your name?
Meifeng. Meifeng Sakura.
I'm like a
jack-of-all-trades around here.
I can get things for ya,
and get things done.
Just let me know what you want!
O... kay.
[MEIFENG] I heard you guys
ran away yesterday.
I just never expected to find
you two spending the night
on a jungle beach
with no supplies.
Most girls would start crying
once the sun went down.
You're tougher
than you look, kid.
Thanks. If I was alone,
I probably would cry
just like them. But I
had you there by my side!
Y'know, you haven't
introduced yourself, big girl.
Mirei Shikishima.
[MEIFENG]
Age?
Fifteen.
What?! You're younger than me?!
But you're so developed!
Ow!
Why're you helping us?
Because someone asked me to.
And who is that?
A freelance businesswoman
never names her clients.
Well... how 'bout...
I'll tell you my name!
I know it! You're
Mamori the Virgin, aren't you?
Ah? Tokonome!
It's Mamori Tokonome!
I know! I'm messing with ya!
But to be honest,
I actually do think
it's a really pretty last name.
Bet people tease ya
about the kanji, though.
I think I've re-opened
this wound enough times
since I got to this island.
[MEIFENG laughs]
I'm not surprised!
It's almost the same spelling.
If you catch it outta the
corner of your eye,
it really does
look like "Virgin!"
Hey. I'm teasing.
'S'not worth crying over.
[MIREI growls]
Now you're gonna make me cry!
We're almost there, ladies.
Huh...? Almost where?
[MEIFENG]
At the home of my client.
So, now can you tell us who?
[receiver beeps]
[gasps]
Go ahead.
[RITTER B]
Kommandeur, please come
to Warehouse F-2, immediately.
[MEIFENG grunts]
[MEIFENG] Books, clothes,
underwear, make-up.
Take your pick, girls!
[GIRLS gasping]
--It's beautiful!
--Can't believe it!
--I want one of everything!
--Soft, fresh panties!
All right, remember: No pushing
and everyone shares.
And who are all these girls?
Same as us. Virus carriers who
were deported to the island.
But they don't like
living in the Veste,
so they escaped out here.
Wait, the Veste?
Are they the same ones
who kidnapped us
and then tried to marry me off?
Veste's the castle.
Warter are the soldiers
who control it
and put you two through hell.
They make up and enforce
every rule there.
Do it all under the
pretenses of "protecting"
the lower ranked girls.
Of course, whenever one of them
breaks a rule,
the Warter
imprison her. Or worse.
But we weren't even there
a day and they were
already coming after us.
What did we do...?
It's what you might do.
The Warter play hard
ball with all new transfers
to test their
strength potential.
If they seem strong enough,
they'll be invited to join
the Warter themselves.
But most of the girls'
power potential is pretty weak,
so they're told to just
fall in line and do
what the Warter say
for their own protection.
And no one complains
about that fate?
All of Mermaid Island's
lifelines are
under Warter control.
Like the factories in
The Veste responsible
for producing food
and medical supplies.
[MEIFENG]
As long as you obey Warter,
they'll make sure you
have the food, shelter,
and clothes you need
for a safe life.
And no girl's gonna complain
about getting free stuff.
[MIREI] I take it you stole
these goods from the Warter?
[MEIFENG]
Bingo!
[gasps]
Why would you do that
and then tell us how
scary-powerful they are?
Aren't you worried
they'll come after you?
Don't worry about me,
I'll be fine.
I didn't take enough for them to
notice, let alone trace to me.
[VOICE]
Oh, Meifeng!
I need to give you a
big ol' hug for once again
making our day with another
awesome supply delivery!
You're the best friend
we could ever ask for!
[MEIFENG (muffled)]
Torino! Can't breathe!
I take it you two are
friends with Meifeng?
I'm the manager of
this little free society.
Name's Torino Kazami, but most
people 'round here
call me "Big Sis."
Um, 'kay.
Welcome to Torino Town, ladies.
[RITTER 1B]
My Apologies, Kommandeur.
We didn't really lose
too much, but it still stings.
I appreciate your apology.
I'll handle it from here.
Don't tell anyone else
what happened. Understood?
Um. Yeah, I Understand, ma'am.
[KASUMI] Meifeng has to
start being more discreet.
[CHARLOTTE]
Oh, Kasumi.
Something happen down here
you want to tell me about?
Oh, it's nothing.
[TORINO]
All right, girls, listen up!
Let's give a toast to
Meifeng and her new friends,
who brought us
these great gifts!
Banzai!
[GIRLS giggling, chatting]
So, uh, do you know what
we're supposed to do now?
[MIREI]
I have no idea.
[MAMORI giggles]
I guess...
It is pretty nice here.
[sighs]
Mm... it doesn't
get better than this.
I can't remember how long it's
been since I had a nice bath.
--[MAMORI sighs]
--[rustling]
[MAMORI]
Unbelievable...
[MAMORI] I refuse to believe
she's younger than me.
There's no way! It's not fair!
What's wrong?
No! Nothing! Everything's fine.
Oh. Mamori, dear.
I've got fresh clothes for you.
[MAMORI]
Oh, thank you so much!
[TORINO]
And that's that.
Adorable!
Doesn't she look
adorable in that outfit?
Cute, right?!
Uh, yeah. She is.
Consider that outfit
my gift to you, Mamori.
[MAMORI]
You sure?
[TORINO]
Of course!
As pretty as that
wedding dress was,
you can't wear it all
the time on the island!
[MAMORI]
Well, thank you Miss Torino.
I just love it.
For the record, I'm the one
who brought the clothes
she's giving to you.
Right, how could I forget?
Thank you for the
new clothes, Miss Meifeng.
[MEIFENG]
We're the same age.
Just call me Meifeng.
Right! Thank you
very much, Meifeng.
Heh... Since I found you on
the beach this morning,
I'm guessing you guys
don't have a place to stay.
So feel free to make yourself
at home in here tonight, 'kay?
[MAMORI]
Really?!
[MEIFENG] You don't mind,
do you, Miss Torino?
No! You're both welcome to
stay for as long as you'd like!
Ah! You really mean it?
[TORINO]
Of course!
[gasps]
Big Sis, thanks for
your hospitality.
Sure! Always happy
to help new girls!
[sighs]
[CHARLOTTE] These recent
incidents of theft...
Why was I not
informed immediately,
the first time it transpired?
[KASUMI]
It wasn't an incident big enough
to warrant your attention.
Because the amount
stolen was so small,
I thought that making a fuss
over it might cause us
to take our minds off far more
pressing concerns,
and in turn, cause
even more of a mess.
[CHARLOTTE] You made
a dumb assumption, then.
The smallest, most
insignificant-seeming problems
can bring down even
the biggest organizations.
[KASUMI grunts]
We must capture this thief.
And then hold her
accountable for her actions
in front of everyone.
[KASUMI]
We shouldn't be too harsh.
On the contrary, we must show
those outsiders watching us
that we're capable of
maintaining law and order.
After all, that is why
we Warter exist.
Don't you dream of one day
leaving this wretched island?
Of course, ma'am.
[giggles]
Miss Kasumi. I can't keep
this secret any longer.
All of the supply thefts?
I've had my own investigators
looking into them
for quite some time.
Huh?
Yes, indeed. That's
why I had trackers
placed in all
the at-risk supplies.
Kasumi Shigure...
...I have a vital new
mission for you,
in your role as
commander of the Warter.
Tomorrow, you'll roll out
all available forces
to this location and
apprehend our thief.
And if she resists, you have
permission to use your powers.
[MAMORI] It's great having
a nice place to stay
with nice people around.
[MIREI]
Yes.
[MAMORI]
Uh... So, uh, Mirei?
I haven't really had the chance
to tell you this yet, but...
If you didn't save me, I would
be a married girl right now!
I know.
One thing--and it's
kind of a big one.
Why are you always so
quick to risk your life?
To save me?
We just met, like,
barely two days ago!
I have no answer.
It just feels
like the right thing.
I'm glad we're friends now.
We're even roommates to boot.
But try not to be so rash
in your actions.
Otherwise, you'll be...
fighting all the time.
[gasps]
[MAMORI]
She fell asleep...
[MAMORI whimpers]
[MAMORI]
I wanna go home...
Daddy... Mommy...
I wanna see you again...
[MAMORI]
I just wanna... go home...
[sobbing quietly]
[RAIN giggles]
Now... I think it's time
we do another scan.
Looks like... it'll be
harder to find than I thought.
The black box of Mermaid...
[LADY J moans]
[RAIN giggles]
Could that be...?
[MAMORI groans]
You ladies sleep well?
Oh, good morning, Meifang!
We slept very well, thank you.
Great. Like they say:
A good night's sleep
always does the body right.
So, Meifeng, I take it
you gotta leave us?
Yeah. I'm heading back to Veste.
I have to keep up appearances
that I live there. Later!
You stay safe, Meifang!
[MIREI]
Don't go yet.
[MAMORI, MEIFANG gasp]
I sense big trouble coming.
Big trouble? Hold on,
I better take a look.
Right.
Hmm?! Warter armored cars!
Waugh! They're
attacking the town!
I think they know you've
been stealing from them.
Aw, crap.
Well, if they find me here,
it'll only make things worse.
So, I'm gonna take off now.
Be safe and have fun, you two.
Save the others if you can!
Wait, Meifeng?
[TORINO]
Warter...
Hey, I know her!
[KASUMI]
We are the Warter from Veste!
[We've received intelligence
this town is currently
sheltering a thief who's been
stealing from our warehouse.
Please give her up at once,
or we'll have no choice
but to remove her by force.
Anyone who gets in our way
will be dealt with, harshly.
Drama. I wonder who
the nasty thief is.
[KASUMI]
This is our last warning.
If we don't get the thief,
we're using force.
Wait, Mirei?
Don't do it! Get back in here!
--[gasps]
--Huh?
She's the thief.
Your name is?
Mirei Shikishima. Hello.
I should have known.
Mirei... No.
[KASUMI gulps]
Confess, Mirei Shikishima.
Did you do it?
Have you been stealing
from our warehouses
and then selling the goods here?
All right, then as an
officer of the Warter,
I hereby place you
under arrest for grand theft.
You're coming with me.
[CHARLOTTE giggles]
Don't, Mirei!
You can't turn yourself in!
You know they'll come up with
the cruelest punishment
possible for this!
Was that little girl
your accomplice?
[MAMORI gasps]
Mirei!
--[gasps]
--[MIREI grunts]
Let her go!
[CHARLOTTE chuckles]
[CHARLOTTE] I have to admit, new
girl, I am surprised it's you!
Charlotte, please!
Let me handle this!
[CHARLOTTE]
Absolutely not.
This girl has embarrassed
me twice, publicly,
in under a week.
[CHARLOTTE growls]
[CHARLOTTE] I'll make you
squeal for bringing shame
to me and the Warter!
[gasping]
Mirei!
--Run!
--Never!
Get outta here!
Why would you do
something this drastic
without even telling
me about it first?!
[gasps]
I warned you just last night
to stop being so rash!
Stupid young love.
[MAMORI] Oh, Mirei.
I don't know what to do.
You leave me no choice...
I have to...
...kiss you...
[MIREI gasps]
[MIREI grunts]
[MAMORI moans]
[MIREI gasps]
[MAMORI gasps]
[MAMORI moans]
[MAMORI gasping, moaning]
[moans]
[gasps]
They're Driving...
I've been waiting for
another shot at you!
[yells]
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
My Arm!
It's supposed to
cut through anything!
That's not fair!
Miss Charlotte!
[KASUMI yells]
[MIREI grunts]
[grunts, groans]
[CHARLOTTE giggles]
Your fighting skills never
fail to impress me, Kommandeur.
Once again, you live up to
your nickname... the Zero Arm.
Both of you girls...
are under arrest.
[MIREI gasps]
--[gasps]
--What's that?
That looks like--
[CHARLOTTE yelps]
[MAMORI whimpers]
Wait... Hold on!
What're you doing here?
[KASUMI]
Lady? Lady...?
[MAMORI]
"Gouverneur."