Until I entered high school two months ago, I thought I...
that I didn't know anything.
The dampness of my uniform's hem...
wet from someone leaning an umbrella up against me.
The smell of mothballs clinging to someone's suit...
like a ghost.
Bodies... warm... pushing up against my back.
The chill breeze of the air conditioner against my face...
When I was little, the sky was closer... so much closer.
That's why I like the rain. It's
like I can smell the sky coming.
On most rainy mornings, I don't take
the transfer. I exit out the station gates.
Chocolate and... beer?
She looks familiar though.
Here.
Oh, Thank you.
Have...
I'm sorry, but have we met before?
No.
Right. Yeah, of course. My mistake.
It's OK.
How about this?
A faint clap of thunder... clouded skies.
Perhaps rain come, and if so.
Will you stay with me?
Rain conditions continue tonight
with storms covering most of Kyushu
Nagasaki, Saga, Kumamoto, can expect to get
wet all through tonight and well into tomorrow.
I'm home.
Oh hey.
I bought croquettes.
Cool. Dinner's almost ready?
Thank you.
Where's Ma?
Ran out.
More for us. Did she say anything?
Just the same note. "Don't come looking for me".
But maybe we should...
I'm sure she'll be back after fighting with her boyfriend.
Oh, I've found a place. I'll be moving in next month.
With her?
She's ready.  I'm ready.
That's why Mom left. You told
her you were moving in together.
Didn't you?
You know,
I wish you would realize we're not kids anymore.
That's the only reason she dates guys our age.
It's disgusting !
OK, fine.
Why don't I just go live with Hiro? How's that?
She's looks young for her age.  So what?
That's because she's never
worked an honest day in her life.
But you?
You're the one who looks like
a 100 miles of shitty highway.
OK...
since I look so beat up, you do the dishes.
Won't you be glad to have more space?
Suppose so.
Help me move, OK?
Sure.
Hey, have you heard of this?
What is this, a haiku?
It's a tanka.
OK.
Ask Ma when she gets back.
On sunny mornings, I transfer to the
subway and head here, like I'm supposed to.
Like I'm supposed to... "What a joke!"
It's raining...
Oh, good morning!
Good morning.
Hmm...
Today a school holiday?
What about you, early retirement?
I'm skipping work again.
And knocking back a couple of
beers in the park apparently.
I have to say it's not exactly
my idea of a power breakfast.
Maybe you should eat something.
You seem to know a lot about the subject.
Oh no, it's not me, I don't drink. My mom's the drinker.
So, you wanted me to eat something?
Will these do?
I can see it in yours eyes. You think I'm nuts !
No, I...
It's OK. I promise, I'm saner than most.
Just another human being, with
all the quirks, little foibles.
Maybe...
Definitely.
Okay, it's about time for me to go.
Off to school?
Rain's letting up, and that's the deal I
made. I can only cut classes on rainy days.
Well, then maybe we'll see each other again?
I mean, it's going to rain again...
...someday.
And then... just like that.
It was the first day of Kanto's rainy season.
A shoemaker?
I heard you. You were going to say it, a "cobbler."
But I don't know, I like it...
the design, I'm creating something...
truly making... something.
I suck at it bad, but...
It's what I want to do.
I know that now... or, well, I can admit that now.
I've never told anyone this before.
Do you have any idea how late you are?
You know why I've called you
here. Don't even act like you don't.
Oh, Come on!
Evenings, before I went to sleep...
Mornings, in the moment I woke up...
I was praying...
for rain.
Because on sunny days, it was there...
a place filled with children.
And I was filled with impatience.
She lives in a world where people work.
They do what they're meant to do.
And that place is a world away from where I am.
And she...
she represents every secret that world holds.
Right now, I only know two things.
One: She looks at me like I'm
just another 15 year-old kid.
And two: This is what I'm meant to do.
It's the only thing that's going
to get me out of this place...
and into that world...
...full of secrets.
"Please stay behind the yellow line for your safety."
"Please be careful of the closing doors."
Well, hey, good morning!
I kind of thought you might not come today.
I mean, it's a miracle you haven't been fired yet.
Wow! That's beautiful!
Hey!
I can't see?
No, not yet. Maybe never.
Really?
Yes, really!
Come on, sit down over there.
I brought breakfast.  I have enough for two.
That's alright. I got my own.
I'm not big on talking.
I can cook, you know.
Oh?
Wow! You can. Hey my mom used to make those.
Wait, I'm not really that good a...
a cook, you know.
Otherwise...
It's your own fault though.
That's a side of you I didn't expect.
What?
Sorry. But it's tasty in its own way.
It's got bite.
You're just saying that.
I'm not!
Can I have another?
Hurry up!
Wait, bro!
Takao, be careful.
Happy birthday, Mom!
Thank you.
Oh, my baby always buys me great presents.
Hey...
What do you think?
Do you think it's too late for me?
The thing was... I could actually taste it. It had flavor.
Sounds like you're better.
I wouldn't go that far.
It's just nice to be able to taste
something other than liquor and chocolate.
I think the loss? Is flavorless.
My tongue is numb as the rest of me.
I think you deciding to just quit was really for the best.
Maybe so.
I hate you when you talk like this...
Gently like you're touching
something you think you could break.
Because back then...
when I found it hard to even breathe
much less talk... you didn't believe me!
You only heard the rumors... all the little whispers.
Why did you believe them so quickly?
We'll start the resignation paperwork after the holiday.
And I'll notify the higher-ups.
Hey...
Thanks for doing it. I mean it's
not like we're together anymore.
I'm glad, really...
Huh?
About that old woman you met...
You know, the one you keep talking
about who brings her lunch box to the park.
It seems like you've really struck a chord.
I think it's great you have someone to talk to.
Get some rest, OK?
Ever since then,
I've been nothing...
Nothing but lies.
Huh?
It's raining.
Here, this is for you.
For me?
I've always ended up eating your food...
And you said you wanted it, right?
This book isn't cheap!
My Gosh!  Thank you so much.
It's my pleasure.
It's the fact that...
Wow, I'm making a pair right now, I so need this.
Really?  For yourself?
I haven't decided whose shoes yet...
They're women's shoes.
But I haven't been able to get them right, and...
It just happened...
I wasn't, like, walking anymore, and then I cried.
I'm sorry, are you talking about your job?
A lot of things...
I don't know anything about her.
What her job even is, her age...
why she's here... drinking so much...
Why is she so... pained.
Yeah.  So much pain.
I don't even know her name.
I can't stop thinking about her.
"The rainy season is officially over ten
days later than normal in the Kanto region."
"The current temperature in the city is 26 degrees."
Like someone just flicked a switch,
the sunny days came one after another.
Oh sure, now I think to myself "I'm
glad that he's not skipping class anymore."
But in reality...
I wish the rainy season never ended.
This park sure is big.
I can't believe we're in Shinjuku.
Oh, pardon us.
Go ahead.
This is the Japanese gardens?
Where should we go next?
Isn't there a greenhouse? Let's check it out.
It's like a totally different place on sunny days.
Thanks for the help.
And, how about as a date that
you stay and have dinner with us?
Sorry, but I've got my part-time job today.
This late?
And I don't want to impose.
Not at all!
I'm going to be living with him from
now on. I mean I'll be sick of him first.
Hey, I can hear you.
Well then, see you later.
Oh, I think he's a really cute kid.
Yeah, if don't look below his ankles.
A handmade mocassins.
They're awesome!
Oh, really?  C'mon they look stupid.
What do you know?  He might have talent.
Hey, I wonder if he'd make a pair of them for me?
Oh, baby, come on, Takao? A designer?
Let's just be honest about this, OK?
My brother moved out, and the rainless days continued.
I had no excuse to head to that place.
August And then, it was summer vacation.
I worked part-time almost every day over the summer.
The pork ramen is really hot today if you like spicy.
I like spicy.
I'll take that too.
Good, I'll have it right out.
Vocational school wasn't going to be cheap.
I needed to work my ass off.
Tuition, tools, leather.
I wasn't going to get some grant.
Sure, I missed her...
but if I cling to those feelings
I'll never get out of here.
I'll be stuck... and she'll be stuck.
So I'll keep working.
I'm going to make a pair of shoes that
will make her want to get up and walk...
and find her way.
What will the weather be like tomorrow?
I'm not a bit smarter at the age
of 27, than I was at the age of 15.
I've always been here, stuck... stuck in the same place.
I can't believe it was him.
English class is no big deal.
That's cause Kiso's a pushover.
Akizuki!
Oh, wow, look at you.
Beach look.
I know, pretty bad. Right?
Speak for yourself. I look
good. Why didn't we see you, dude?
Worked the whole time.
The whole time?
School, part-time job, house work, that's no life man.
I skip school sometimes!
Now that you mention it, you are late a lot...
a whole lot.
Yep, if it's raining he never makes 1st period.
I've got a condition where I can't
ride the subway on rainy mornings.
Whatever, weirdo.
Ms. Yukino?
Ms. Yukino!
Satou...
I'm so sorry.
Alright girls and Satou, save it for later.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I'll be here until after 6th
period so let's just wait until then.
I can't believe it.
She is actually here.
You didn't hear about Yuki quittin'?
Didn't know her or hear that.
Then you got more class than I thought.
The third-year girls started it.
Oh, man, those bitches were
just merciless to that poor woman.
It was tragic.
They were awful, and you can think what
you want. She didn't do anything wrong.
Someone's boyfriend thought she was hot
so they were mean to her because of it.
Those rumors got all the way to her parents.
Her parents heard them.
I can't imagine.
Then she just stopped showing up.
I think she should have called the damn cops.
But you know if she would the
principle would have put the ee on that.
And he wouldn't have done anything about it.
He didn't want anymore bad
publicity for his stupid school.
It makes me sick! He's worse than they are!
Hey, what's the matter?
Those upperclassmen...
Do you... know them?
Ms. Yukino, wait!
Because he sucks at it and he's a loser.
Ah, you're such a bitch.
But man, you sure go through 'em.
What do you want, fish?
Are you Aizawa?
Another fan.
Hardly.
Who the hell are you?
Ms. Yukino... You heard she's quitting, right?
Huh?
Oh, please, you think I care about some slutty hag?
What the fuck is your problem?
I'm gonna like this.
Ah, holy shit.
You love her!
What a creep!
Does he even know how old she is?
I wonder how far he'd die.
He looks inexperienced.
He could do her now and not get school policy.
It's not legal either.
Fuck this.
You should be thanking us.
I'm waiting for the rain.
A faint clap of thunder
even if rain comes not.
I will stay here
together with you.
Yes, that's the correct answer.
That's the right response to the
tanka I told you when we first met.
If it rains, I wonder if you will be staying here?
In response to that verse, I answer...
Even if it doesn't rain, I will be here.
I know it... classic Japanese literature.
And if Yukino, I...
I'm sorry...
I thought you would realize
it. I mean it seemed so obvious.
Everyone in town seems to know
about the classic lit teacher.
But then again you're always off
in your own little world, aren't you?
Wait a minute. What happened to your face?
I was acting like you and drank too much beer.
Then I tripped and fell on the
Yamanote [train line] platform.
Oh, my God!
I'm kidding.
I got in a little fight.
I don't even know why we're running, we're soaking wet.
I think this might...
this might be...
...the happiest...
time of my life.
I love you.
What?
Yukino, I can't help it. I
think I've fallen in love with you.
Not Yukino.
Ms. Yukino.
I'm going to be moving next week.
Back to my hometown in Shikoku.
I made the decision a while back.
I was practicing how to walk
on my own, there in that place.
Even if I'm barefoot...
So then...
So I want to thank you for everything, Akizuki.
Thank you for your hospitality and for the clothes.
I can get changed now.
But wait, your shirt...
I've got my things...
so I'm good.
I'm going to go now. It was nice meeting you.
I've brought breakfast. I have enough for two.
I haven't decided whose shoes yet.
They're women's shoes.
I was acting like you and drank too much beer.
Then I tripped and fell on the Yamanote platform.
A faint clap of thunder.
Even if rain comes not.
I will stay here.
Together with you.
Yukino...
I want you to forget what I told you earlier.
I couldn't love someone like you.
I hate you.
I thought it the second I saw you in the park.
It was poison.
Drinking beer in the morning,
quoting some stupid tanka to me...
You listening to other people's talking all day...
just so you'd never have to
reveal a thing about yourself...
You knew who I was, I was just a kid.
What were you thinking? What's wrong with you?
If I'd known you were a teacher, I would never
have told you anything about me or my dreams.
You don't think I can do it. You don't
really think I'll ever amount to anything!
What? Is that why you didn't say anything to me?
You thought maybe that you were with a little kid?
Indulge his fantasies for a
little while. Just string him along?
Go on, say it. I'll never measure up to my dreams.
You knew from the beginning.
You could have just admitted it.
But you played along.
So tell me god damn it.
Tell me that little kids should run along to school!
Tell me that you hate me! Say it!
Come on Listener, say something for a change.
Loser!
It's because you act like that.
You never say what's important,
You pretend it's none of your business.
You've been living your whole life alone.
Every morning!
Every morning I put on my suit to go to school...
But I was... I was scared...
I couldn't go, I couldn't go...
But then you... you came and...
you, you, you saved me.
Oh my God, Oh my God, you saved me...
Summer ended.  Summer uniforms became winter ones.
Finals:  Barely squeezed by there.
I wasted who knows how many pieces of expensive leather.
Winter break:  Part-time job again.
And every time I added a layer I-I find...
I thought of her.
I  realize now, I was learning to walk as well.
I haven't mastered the steps.
But I'm on my path.
My path.
One day that path will take me to her.