[bell rings]
[STUDENT A] What are your
plans for summer vacation?
[STUDENT B] My father bought
a yacht, so going on a cruise!
[STUDENT A groans]
Nice! The ocean sounds like fun.
Our summer house is way
up in the highlands.
[KAZUYA]
Summer vacation, huh?
[KAZUYA] I won't be able
to go back to Japan
for another two
months, at least!
They're all so lucky.
[AVRIL]
Oh, there you are! Kujo!
[gasps]
Do you wanna go with me?
To... the Mediterranean?
You mean on the water?
I stay in my grandmother's
summer home when I visit.
She said I could bring a
friend with me if I wanted.
But she insisted that
they have good manners.
So, anyway... would you like to?
--Sure. Love to!
--[bell rings]
[gasps]
Just... give me a minute?
[AVRIL]
Uh... Okay.
[KAZUYA groans]
That heat is oppressive.
[KAZUYA]
There you are, Victorique!
You haven't prepared a case yet.
No. I haven't had
a chance to pack.
Anyway.
--I need to talk to you.
--Did you bring candy?
No.
Not this time.
I just wanted to...
So you've interrupted my reading
and brought nothing
to satiate my boredom.
You've certainly started to
think highly of
yourself, haven't you?
[KAZUYA gasps]
[VICTORIQUE] Go bring me
sweets from the lower world!
And until you find one
that truly satisfies me,
you can keep doing it over
and over until the day you die.
Fine, have it your way!
I'll bring you something from
the Mediterranean after summer!
[VICTORIQUE]
That fool.
They're all fools.
Moving to and fro in this heat
when they could be
expanding their horizons.
[VICTORIQUE] And Kujo wins the
grand prize for foolishness
with that little
stunt he pulled.
He's such a transparent boy.
Coming without a case for me.
Looking so happy and carefree.
I don't even need my wellspring
of wisdom to see into his mind.
[VICTORIQUE]
He's an utter fool!
Burning his skin in
the toxic sunlight.
Exposing himself for all to see.
He should...
...be here.
He'd be so much
better off with me.
[train hisses, whistles]
[AVRIL]
Hurry! Hurry!
[KAZUYA]
Wait up, Avril!
[LITTLE GIRL]
Mama!
[LITTLE GIRL sighs, giggles]
Come on! Why the wait?
[KAZUYA]
Sorry! I can't go after all.
[gasps]
But why not?
Victorique will be stuck
at school all summer.
I know I'd be lonely if I
were stuck in those shoes.
That's why.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Sorry.
It's... fine.
Well, what can you do?
I hope you realize
just how kind you are.
Your friend is lucky.
Will you be okay?
You bet! I'll even
bring you a souvenir.
And one for Victorique, too.
Maybe I'll bring a couple
matching linen shirts
for you both.
Shirts?
I don't know...
That's a little simple
for someone who loves
complicated dresses
covered in frills.
Huh? This friend of yours has
a pretty bizarre sense
of fashion for a boy.
Oh. No, Victorique's a girl.
Huh?!
A-- A girl?!
[whines]
[VICTORIQUE groaning]
Stupid sunlight.
It's so distracting, I
can't focus on the words.
[sighs]
I'm making a discovery here.
Even a boring book like
this must have some merit.
And I swear... I'll find it.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
What are you doing
out here, Victorique?
K-K-Kujo!
You-- Why-- Didn't--?!
I thought you were
leaving today!
Here. Take it.
I bought it just for you.
[VICTORIQUE]
I don't need it.
I was just about to discover a
revolutionary way of reading.
[KAZUYA]
There was a package from Japan
waiting for me at
the post office.
And these... are yours.
[VICTORIQUE]
My word...
Precious gems?
Better! It's artisanal candy!
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[laughs]
And this one's
addressed to you.
I think it's a reply
from my second brother.
[KAZUYA] I wasn't sure
if you remembered or not.
So, wait for the
opponent to strike.
Then, turn their own
power against them
using this technique.
Hiya!
After that, get
into their space.
What is that you're reading?
Huh?
Oh, it's a magazine
my brother sent me.
It's called the
"Monthly Toughs."
[VICTORIQUE]
Sounds like dangerous study.
[KAZUYA] I'm still the third
son of an imperial soldier.
I can't neglect my training
just because I'm half-way
across the world.
[sighs] Anyway...
[VICTORIQUE]
This one.
Is this a science book?
[KAZUYA] Yeah. My oldest
brother's a tough guy,
but my second brother is smart.
I can't beat them
on either front.
[VICTORIQUE]
Here.
What is this one about?
[VICTORIQUE]
Tell your "smart" brother
to solve this riddle
in five minutes.
No longer.
[KAZUYA]
What is it?
[VICTORIQUE]
It's a puzzle.
Rearrange the donkey so that
it makes the image
of a horse as well.
[gasps]
Turn that ugly thing
into a horse?
[VICTORIQUE] If he's as
smart as you say he is,
something like this
should be child's play.
I guess he finally
replied to you.
[VICTORIQUE] Hm. It clearly took
him longer than five minutes.
Well, yeah, you sent it by boat.
What the--?
[gasps] The negative
space makes a horse!
I get it now!
[KAZUYA]
Wow! You really have to think
from a different
angle for this.
[KAZUYA laughs]
That's so neat!
Oh, hey.
He wrote a letter, too.
Let's see.
"This was super easy.
I solved it in three minutes.
Tell the little girl
to send something
challenging next time."
That's all.
Hey, wait a minute.
My sister and second brother
seem to think you're a child,
but I never said you were that
young in any of my letters,
so I wonder what gave
them that impression.
Well, you certainly
act childish,
so they're
not far off.
[groans] That hurt!
Sheesh!
Huh? Hey, there's something
written on the corner here.
It's my sister's handwriting.
[RURI] Our brother was
stewing over your puzzle.
He spent every night groaning
with nightmares about horses.
Eventually, he had his math
teacher solve it for him.
[KAZUYA chuckles]
Well... It seems I claim
victory this time around.
You know, these colors don't
exactly spark my appetite.
In that case, I can exchange
them for other ones.
I didn't say that I
wouldn't accept it!
Just try to bring better sweets
for me next time, okay?
All right. Fine.
[KAZUYA]
Hey...
Shouldn't you head back?
[KAZUYA groans]
[KAZUYA grunting]
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[gasps, coughs]
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
Victorique really is amazing.
This tiny girl makes even
my scary older brothers
seem harmless.
[VICTORIQUE humming]
[KAZUYA]
The summers here are just as hot
as they are back home.
Yet... I feel like
something's different.
[cicadas chirping]
[KAZUYA]
Oh, yeah...
Saubure Summers lack
the chorus of cicadas.
[FATHER]
The only reason Kazuya is weak
is because you failed
to raise him properly!
[MOTHER]
Forgive me, husband.
[FATHER]
Stop covering for him!
He'll never learn that way!
[MOTHER]
Forgive me, husband.
[FATHER growls]
[RURI]
Don't let it bother you.
I don't want you to become
like father or our brothers.
Covered in hair and always
stuffing their faces like pigs.
Not to mention
smelling like one.
Just thinking about you turning
out like them makes me furious.
So, don't bother!
[MOTHER]
Ruri, please.
[RURI] I wish Kazuya had been
born a girl, sometimes.
We could play otedama and
wear pretty clothes together.
Right?
[MOTHER]
I suppose so.
But Kazuya's always been
a compassionate child.
It takes a lot of courage
to be kind, you know?
I think he'll make an
upstanding young man.
[KAZUYA]
That summer...
Mother was always there to
keep me safe and happy.
[horn blows]
[KAZUYA]
And yet...
I ended up leaving for
Saubure all the same.
[MEN]
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
[CROWD MAN]
Do your best, okay?
[CROWD GIRL]
Take care!
[KAZUYA] It felt like I was
running away from it all.
Maybe I was.
[KAZUYA gasps]
I fell asleep.
[KAZUYA]
What is it?
You could have woken me up
if you needed something.
You seemed preoccupied
with the matter.
No doubt reorganizing
some trivial chaos
with your trivial mind.
[KAZUYA]
Uh-- Hold on!
Victorique! Your books! Hey!
[footsteps]
[grunting]
[pants]
[VICTORIQUE]
Hmph.
[KAZUYA yawns]
[SOPHIE]
Oh! Good morning, Kujo!
Good morning to you, too.
[SOPHIE chuckles] I'm not sure
that hat goes with your outfit.
What's that smell?
Something special I whipped up.
Why don't you take
it off my hands?
[KAZUYA]
Hey! Where'd you go?
Victorique?
Our dorm mother made
an orange cake for us!
I've got some here for
you, if you want it.
Come on out!
Here, kitty-kitty-kitty!
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Oh, I get it.
You're stuck in the tree.
And you need me to get
you down, is that right?
Silly...
Want me to climb up?
If I did that, we
could eat it together!
[VICTORIQUE] Leave it there
and get out of my sight.
What about my half?
I said, leave it there!
All right, sheesh.
Bye.
[footsteps]
[groans]
--[CÉCILE humming]
--[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[CÉCILE] Ooh! What a
delicious looking cake!
But whose is it?
Yoo-hoo! Cake Owner,
are you here?
Come on out!
No one's around, so...
[sniffs]
Oh, it smells fantastic.
It'd sure be a shame to
let it go to waste, right?
Tasty!
Having to stay at the
school over summer break...
[CÉCILE]
I was hating it at first.
But I guess it has its perks!
My goodness.
You'd think it was autumn
with these leaves falling.
[CÉCILE]
These orange slices are so good!
If only I had some tea,
it would be perfect.
That was delicious!
What a treat!
I'll wash the plate
and return it.
[thunder claps]
[KAZUYA] Uh-- How am I supposed
to read all these magazines?
There's another letter in here.
Huh. It's for Victorique.
"I challenge you to a duel."
He's so immature sometimes.
I sure hope Victorique
made it back to her room.
[KAZUYA whimpering]
Something's wrong.
[CÉCILE humming]
I knew it!
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
Darn. You really can't get
down from there, can you?
Stop being so stubborn!
[gasps]
Here. Jump down. I'll catch you.
[VICTORIQUE]
I... I can't.
You'll be okay, I promise.
[KAZUYA groans]
Ow! Why did you jump
down feet first?!
I'm bleeding internally!
[VICTORIQUE]
Who cares.
[gasps] Hey, wait!
Victorique!
Your parasol!
[yelps]
[KAZUYA]
Ugh, I'm soaked.
You okay in there?
I can call Miss Cécile
if you need help changing.
--[VICTORIQUE] Shut up!
--[KAZUYA yelps]
[KAZUYA]
Fine, fine.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA] I guess she
liked them, after all.
--[door opens]
--[gasps]
--[VICTORIQUE grunting]
--[dishes clattering]
[KAZUYA]
Victorique?
What are you doing?
That looks heavy!
Hold on, is that... tea?
I didn't think you
knew how to make it.
Please. Don't talk to me.
It's distracting!
I don't believe it.
I mean, you can barely
tie your own shoelaces.
And you made tea?
[VICTORIQUE yelps, screams]
[crash]
[KAZUYA]
Oh boy...
Don't move.
I'll clean it up.
It's like the simplest things
are impossible for you.
Why were you making tea?
[gasps]
Wait a minute, did you...
...make that for me?
Kujo!
Drop the rag!
It's too good for
the likes of you!
Wait, what?
Get down on all fours and
slurp it like the dog you are.
[KAZUYA]
Huh...?!
No way!
Wow...
Lots of lightning.
When I was still a kid,
storms would terrify me.
My brothers thought
it was hilarious.
And my dad would get angry.
Did you manage to conquer
your fear of storms?
Yeah. My dad's anger was
a good catalyst for that.
He'd even yell at my
mom if I got scared.
[VICTORIQUE]
Your mother...
[KAZUYA]
Hm?
Nothing.
Oh, that's right!
My second oldest brother
sent you a challenge!
Let's see.
"If you can't solve this
riddle in three seconds,
you're a smelly brat."
[laughs]
Oh? What a reckless man.
I accept his challenge.
Okay!
"Taro- kaja , Jiro- kaja ,
and Saburo- kaja
--went to a mountain together."
--[VICTORIQUE] Wait, wait, wait.
I can't follow along
with those names.
I hear you.
I'll change it to something
you're more familiar with.
How about...
Jean, Phil, and Pierre
went to a mountain together.
The three of them were
supposed to carry
three logs home at once,
as ordered by the tono --
I-I mean, the baron
of their town.
But the logs were too
long for one man to carry.
[VICTORIQUE]
Such weaklings.
Hey, you're one to talk.
Anyway... The three
men were stumped--
no pun intended-- until
Pierre remembered that
the baron had ordered each of
them to carry two logs at once.
[VICTORIQUE]
Hm...
[KAZUYA]
They did as they were told
and got all of the logs
safely down the mountain.
So, the question is
how did the three men
manage to carry all of
the logs at once? [gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
I solved it in one second!
Tell your brother
he's the smelly brat!
There is nothing my wellspring
of wisdom cannot solve!
[KAZUYA]
Wait... I don't think I follow.
What's with the triangle?
[VICTORIQUE]
That's how they did it.
Jean, Phil, and Pierre made
a triangle out of the logs.
Then, each of them stood
at one of the three corners
with a log in each hand.
This allowed them to easily
distribute the weight
and carry them
down the mountain.
In effect, each of them
was carrying two logs,
just like the baron had ordered.
Amazing!
It's so simple!
[VICTORIQUE] I can solve a
riddle from your older brother
in the time it takes to blink.
Yeah. You have a great
mind, I'll give you that.
But...
...though it hurts to admit...
You're much better at climbing
trees than I'll ever be.
Huh?
This school is
filled with children
from wealthy families,
just like mine.
I doubt any of them could
climb trees better than you do.
[KAZUYA] Well, my big
brothers are pretty good.
Yes, I know full well
that your siblings
are good at all sorts of things.
But you're the only
Kujo at this academy.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
Remember when we first met?
You were always reminding me
that you are the third son
of an imperial soldier.
Yeah.
I remember.
[VICTORIQUE] I found that
phrasing deeply unpleasant.
But you've said it less
and less as of late.
I'm proud.
[gasps] Victorique!
Kujo. The rain has let up.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Was that...
...Victorique's unique
way of encouraging me?
[KAZUYA] I'll go into town and
buy her more sweets tomorrow.
Maybe some of the macarons
she likes so much.
And then...
I'll enjoy the summer.
[KAZUYA] This Saubure
summer, free of cicadas.
And I'll spend it...
...with her.
[KAZUYA] I promised Avril
I'd go see a movie with her.
[VICTORIQUE]
Oh? Isn't that nice?
I hope you have a
great time, Kujo.
[KAZUYA gasps, whimpers]