[STUDENTS chattering]
[AVRIL] I guess Kujo's
gone to the library again.
[sighs]
What type of girl is she,
this "Victorique"?
[VICTORIQUE, CÉCILE grunting]
[VICTORIQUE] Get your stupid
hands off of me, Cécile!
Victorique!
Don't be like this!
One of us is going to get hurt!
[VICTORIQUE grunts]
[KAZUYA]
Hey, you two. What is this?
Kujo! Quick, get her off of me!
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
I saw her on my way to
the classroom and thought,
"If she's out of the library,
she can come in and say hello."
But she's just so stubborn!
[VICTORIQUE] ...never going,
so you might as well give up!
What? Why not?
I don't want to! That's
the only reason I need!
Now, let go of me this instant!
[CÉCILE] Well now,
it's about time you met!
This is your fellow classmate.
Say hello to Victorique!
[STUDENT A]
The Victorique? Really?
[STUDENT C]
From the library?
[STUDENT B]
The Gray Wolf!
So this is...
the girl he mentioned?
[AVRIL]
Her skin is fair and smooth.
Her cheeks are
the color of roses.
That long,
flowing golden hair.
Those tiny hands and feet.
She's like a doll made by
the hand of God himself!
[CÉCILE]
Avril and everyone behind her,
could you please
move back one seat?
[gasps]
Victorique, you can take
the seat next to Kujo,
as I think it'll
help you adjust.
Come on now. Don't be shy.
[AVRIL growls]
Something wrong, Avril?
Just saying "good morning."
Oh, thank you. Same to you.
[CÉCILE]
Everyone, sorry I was late,
but a rather disturbing incident
took place this morning.
As a result, class will be
off for the rest of the day.
[AVRIL]
What's going on with her?
She seems so tense.
Hey there. Are you okay?
You feeling sick or something?
Hey.
What, can you not answer
when someone talks to you?
Or maybe Gray Wolves don't
understand human language
like all the legends say.
Hey.
Little Gray Wolf.
Or maybe you prefer
"demon girl"?
Hey, Demon Girl!
[gasps]
[VICTORIQUE growls]
Impudent fool!
Keep your hands off of me!
Put the desk down, Victorique!
[screams]
[STUDENTS scream]
[KAZUYA gasps]
I'm glad your injury
wasn't that serious.
[AVRIL]
Yeah, me too.
[KAZUYA]
Hey.
Apologize.
I will do no such
thing; thank you.
Wait, Kujo.
It's okay.
You could have seriously hurt
her with that little stunt.
Say it!
Kujo!
Listen. It's not like that--
[VICTORIQUE]
This woman is a farting newt!
I don't talk to newts!
[KAZUYA]
That's it. Come here!
Apologize to her!
Hold on!
It's fine! Let go!
I'm just trying to teach
farting Victorique
that she can't treat
people this way!
I'm not letting go until you
apologize, understand me?
Darn it.
You half-baked, no talent...
mediocre excuse for a man!
[AVRIL]
Please, stop!
It's not like that!
My goodness!
[AVRIL]
A murder in the clock tower?
So another strange thing
happened yesterday.
Do you think it's the ghost
of Leviathan, after all?
[VICTORIQUE] Of course
the farting newt thinks
this is the work of spirits.
Knock it off!
Wait, I get it now.
That's the reason
you were so angry
when you chased me and Kujo
out of the clock tower, right?
It seemed so out of
character for you.
This isn't the first
time that someone's died.
The tower has a history
of violent death.
That's why.
How many times has it happened?
This last one makes it five.
They all happened in that room.
Each one had a purple bruise
on their right index finger.
Autopsies always reveal
that the cause death
was poison injected
into that finger.
Could you tell me when the first
incident occurred, Miss Cécile?
I believe it was the
turn of the century.
[AVRIL] That would
put it around the time
Leviathan left the
tower, wouldn't it?
Were there any similarities
between the victims?
[CÉCILE]
Uhh...
I think they were all outsiders.
New teachers, for example,
or trespassing travelers,
friends of students, visitors...
You get the idea.
[KAZUYA]
Where are you going?
The riddle of Leviathan
can only be brought to light
in the clock tower,
so it should be obvious
my investigation would
have to continue there.
My wellspring will carry me
through like it always has.
Wait, you're not
going without me.
[AVRIL gasps]
Kujo! I'll go, too!
[ALL gasp]
This is rather unexpected.
You're out of the library again.
What could it mean, I wonder?
[VICTORIQUE]
I received a challenge
from the alchemist, Leviathan.
I intend to accept and win.
[BLOIS]
Leviathan?
Sir? You've... got bugs.
Ugh, I was in a hurry and
hardened it with sugar water.
This is the end result.
So, where are you going?
The tower is the other way.
Investigation's over.
I'm going back to the station.
Already? Did you find anything?
Come, Squirrel.
I'd like to speak with you.
[BLOIS] Are you aware that this
school only began to accept
transfer students like
yourself a few years ago?
For hundreds of years before,
foreigners were forbidden
to even enter the grounds.
[KAZUYA]
Huh. Why was that?
[BLOIS] There was a time when
this educational institution
was actually a front
for a secret royal armory.
Everything was kept
out of the public eye.
It's been a hiding place for
the darker parts of our history.
We'd rather not have the people,
or the research they did,
brought into the light.
Leviathan being one
of the more notorious.
And that's why you're not
investigating the case.
It's all for the Kingdom
of Saubure's security.
Not to mention...
[BLOIS]
Kujo...
If my little sister attempts
to interfere in this incident,
I want you to stop her.
Understand?
We don't know what dangers
might be lurking about.
[KAZUYA]
Danger?
What are you saying?
I mean, powerless little
squirrels would be better off
waiting with the Gray Wolf
until this is over.
Now, excuse me.
Danger?
Dark history?
Hey, don't just stand there!
Let's get to the village and
bust this case wide open!
[KAZUYA]
Sure, okay.
[AVRIL gasps]
You should come too, Victorique.
I think I'll pass.
[AVRIL gasps]
You can go anywhere you
want with the farting newt.
It doesn't matter to me.
[KAZUYA hisses]
Okay, Victorique.
Apologize to Avril.
We've been through this.
Victorique!
Seriously, Kujo, it's okay!
I'm the one who--
Please, stay out of this, Avril.
Now, Victorique, what is
going on with you today?
I thought you were
nicer than this.
I wish you'd talk to me.
You're my closest friend.
[AVRIL]
His closest friend? Her?
Come on. Please? Let me help.
Fine. I'm done with you then.
Let me know when you
decide to grow up.
[AVRIL]
Uh...
Sure you don't want to come?
You're welcome to.
Then how about we make
a game out of it?
Whoever solves the alchemists'
riddle first is the winner!
'Kay?
Okay...
I guess we'll see you later.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[VICTORIQUE cries]
Kujo... You idiot.
You didn't have to get so angry.
Big dumb jerk.
[crying continues]
[gasps]
[sobs]
[VICTORIQUE]
That's right.
I don't have time for tears.
Leviathan waits.
[AVRIL]
His closest friend, huh?
Great.
Maybe I was too harsh
on her back there.
[gasps] Hey! There are a bunch
of names written on this one!
[KAZUYA]
Mm?
[AVRIL] Does that mean they
were all buried together?
[OLD MAN]
Yes, five hundred years ago.
[screams]
This tombstone marks
a Protestant grave.
A grim reminder of the wars
between the Protestants
and Catholics of old.
Everyone listed here was
killed in this village.
--[AVRIL] Hm.
--[KAZUYA] Huh.
Some older buildings
still contain secret rooms
that were used to hide
those being oppressed
by the Holy Roman Empire
during the Thirty Years' war.
Now, is there something
I can help you find today?
Actually...
[OLD MAN] Ah, the outsiders
that were killed in the tower.
There're no graves for them.
Only the people of the
village are buried here.
Oh, I see.
Thanks.
Bye, now.
I was only a child
when it happened,
but I remember
those days clearly.
We should get going.
It's scary at night.
One time... when I
was still a boy,
I saw an invisible spirit.
The soul of the dead!
[screams]
So, how did you see it
if it was invisible?
I'll tell you.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[OLD MAN] I definitely
heard the footsteps.
But the only sign that
anyone had been there
where the prints on the ground--
The last marks it would
leave on the world.
[squeals]
[OLD MAN] Judging from
the size of the footprints,
the spirit must have
belonged to a child.
[KAZUYA]
And... I've lost Avril.
[SOPHIE]
♪ Doo-da-doo! Da-doo! Doo! ♪
[KAZUYA, AVRIL gasp]
[SOPHIE] ♪ Gold that shines
bright in the sunlight! ♪
♪ Dee doo-da-doo! Da-doo! Doo! ♪
Oh hi, Kujo!
What are you doing here?
[KAZUYA]
Hi, Miss Sophie.
Visiting someone?
Why else would I
be in a graveyard?
What about you?
On a date?
--[yelps] No, not at all!
--[AVRIL giggles]
By the way, what was that song?
[SOPHIE]
Hm?
[thud]
[footsteps]
And you are?
[ROSCOE] Just a traveler,
searching for something.
[VICTORIQUE] You couldn't have
lost anything in this place.
And yet, the beautiful
monster escaped me.
[VICTORIQUE]
Monster?
I get it now.
You're the companion of the
Oriental man who died here;
the red hair proves it.
[ROSCOE]
Very good.
Wong Kai the Illusionist.
Have you heard of him?
Never.
[ROSCOE]
Wong was intrigued by the film,
"The Illusion in
the Black Tower."
He snuck in here
to get a glimpse
of what the film was based on.
I take it you're an
illusionist as well?
[ROSCOE]
Yes.
How'd you know?
Because I'm the
monster in question.
[ROSCOE] I see.
So you know who I am then?
Obviously.
I also know what you're after.
And who it is you travel with.
That's very impressive work.
There's nothing in this
world I cannot solve.
And yet you're little more
than someone else's tool.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[ROSCOE] What could a helpless
tool raised without love
possibly understand
about the real world?
There is nothing I do not know!
[door opens]
I don't think you
two should be here.
[ROSCOE]
Who might you be?
[CARPENTER] What's it look
like, son? I'm a carpenter.
One of the higher-ups asked me
to check to see if this
place needs tearing down.
Old buildings like
this can be dangerous.
That's why they tell people
like you to stay out.
[ROSCOE]
I see.
We'll be careful.
[gasps]
I'd like you to check
something else.
[CARPENTER]
Hm?
We really learned a
lot from the old man.
Yeah.
[gasps]
Uh, Kujo?
Where are you going?
[footsteps]
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
How are you doing?
Hello? Hey...! Victorique?
You hear me, right?
I bought you a souvenir.
I see.
Is it another strange hat
or perhaps some candy?
Nope! It's a raspberry sandwich!
[snorts]
[gasps]
[panting]
Oh, boy. Kujo sure can...
--...run real fast.
--[KAZUYA] Apparently
the older buildings
have hidden rooms
that Protestants had
used to hide out.
I also ran into Miss Sophie
who was singing that folk song
I heard the kids singing before.
I guess it's popular
with the locals.
They say it's about
a group of Africans
--that lived in the village
--[BOYS singing]
--a long time ago.
[KAZUYA]
Neither Sophie or the old man
could tell us where it came
from or what it means.
But they were all over the
place, then just died out.
Yes, that was around
the tail end of 1873.
I remember it well.
At the beginning
of the next year,
the King of Saubure just up
and died without any warning.
It was a sad time indeed.
[KAZUYA, BOYS]
♪ Dee doo-da-doo! Da-doo! Doo! ♪
♪ March together all for
one and one, one for all! ♪
♪ Pretty sisters all around,
their skin as black as night. ♪
♪ Dee doo-da-doo! Da-doo! Doo! ♪
♪ Gold that shines bright
in the sunlight. ♪
♪ Dee doo-da-doo! Da-doo! Doo! ♪
♪ On and on,
they rowed their oars. ♪
♪ Trying to land
on better shores. ♪
The gold could
refer to Leviathan!
Doesn't it make you wonder?
--Stop, Kujo!
--[gasps]
Why? What did I do?
I said it's a contest!
Why are you telling
our adversary
everything we found out?
I just thought everything
would be easier
if we pooled our
information together.
Isn't that a good thing?
I thought you would have
given up by now, Newt.
Say that again, you nasty frill!
Did you call me a nasty frill?
What does that even mean?
I don't know!
It's what you are!
Leave me alone!
[KAZUYA sighs]
All right, then.
Let's compare our conclusions
and get this over with.
I think Leviathan's spirit is
wandering the clock tower
in a never-ending
state of torment.
And he doesn't want
outsiders getting in.
[KAZUYA]
Hold on.
Didn't Leviathan disappear after
he was shot by poison arrows?
There was never a body.
I think he's still alive and
killing people for some reason.
[VICTORIQUE]
Idiots. You're both wrong.
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps] What did you say?!
However, your belief in spirits
is particularly stupid, Newt.
Why not come back to reality?
So what then, you think
he's alive like Kujo,
or is it something else?
Leviathan has been dead
for a very long time now.
He simply did a phenomenal
job of hiding that fact.
He wasn't invincible
like some believe.
His alchemy was nothing
but parlor tricks.
How can you say that?!
He was an alchemist through
and through. Definitely!
--It was all real!
--Hey, calm down.
It's fine.
Leviathan did manage to
turn a white rose blue;
I'll give you that much.
Yes, he did!
And he had an audience!
The King, the Queen,
their entire court saw him!
Yet it was still nothing
more than a trick,
and I'll prove it to you.
But when I do, try not
to die of embarrassment.
I'd hate for Kujo
to have to carry
your flatulence-ridden
body out of the school.
[gasps]
Now, now...
Hmph! You'll never pull it off.
[gasps]
No way!
How'd you do it? Tell me!
[KAZUYA]
Cotton?
If you soak some in ink and
press it against a cut stem.
you could dye a white rose
any color that you wanted.
It's a simple trick, really.
--[BOTH gasp]
--I don't believe it.
[KAZUYA]
So Leviathan really is dead?
That's disappointing.
I've already figured out
how he managed to pull
off most of his illusions.
[BOTH gasp]
[VICTORIQUE]
But some of it still eludes me.
I'm waiting for the last
fragment to reveal itself,
so I can reconstruct the truth
and solve this riddle.
Any thoughts on where to look?
I think...
Yes, it's a man
named Brian Roscoe.
She said that ten years ago,
Brian Roscoe came back here.
It would make sense that my baby
picture was placed here then.
Sorry, I just remembered
something I have to do!
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Wait, Kujo!
[AVRIL]
Victorique?
[gasps]
I'm sorry. I've been
pretty mean to you.
You really are an
incredible person.
The way you solve these things,
it makes... me feel like
I really am stupid.
I don't know.
What do you think?
You're stupid.
Without a doubt.
But still... you're
free to do as you please.
After being around you,
I realized if Kujo keeps
spending so much time
with a girl this brilliant,
he'll start thinking I'm stupid
and want nothing to do with me.
I guess what I'm
trying to say...
...is that I'm afraid
of losing Kujo.
So please don't take him
away from me, Victorique!
[wails] Sorry, this
is so embarrassing!
Just forget I said anything!
Huh?
[gasps]
Oh, thank goodness.
[sighs]
[CÉCILE] Hm...
Ah, the wonders of youth.
[LEVIATHAN] Thou who hast
found this book in the future:
Art thou a man?
A woman?
An adult?
A child?
[foosteps]
[BLOIS] I mean powerless little
squirrels would be better off
waiting with the Gray Wolf
until this is over.
[ROSCOE]
Can I help you... little boy?
[KAZUYA gasps]
[LEVIATHAN]
Heed me.
Thou must follow my
tale to completion.
[LEVIATHAN]
If thou dost...
...thou will know my sin...
...and my deepest regret.
[VICTORIQUE]
What are you waiting for?
Take it.
This is my answer
to your challenge.
[KAZUYA]
Okay, give it to me!
[VICTORIQUE]
Not you, Kujo!