[LEVIATHAN] The most glorious
moment of my life...
...was the night I created a
blue rose for my beloved queen.
Two years later though,
everything changed.
[ROSE]
Leviathan...
After all we've done together,
you still won't
show me your face?
[LEVIATHAN]
Please accept that the true me
is the one standing
before you now.
I would never deceive you...
...my beloved Coco Rose.
[ROSE chuckles]
--[door rattles]
--[ROSE gasps]
Baron Musgrave!
[LEVIATHAN]
May I help you?
[LEVIATHAN] A hearing was
held several days later.
I call the next witness.
Jupiter Roger from
the Academy of Sciences.
[LEVIATHAN] The "validity
of alchemy" was on trial.
When a scholar from the Ministry
of the Occult testified,
another scientific expert
would try to cut me down.
It was a trap.
They were trying to make
me slip up in public.
[LEVIATHAN]
What a farce.
[MUSGRAVE] I'll give you one
more chance to prove yourself.
Create gold for your country
right here and now.
No excuses. This is a
direct order from your king,
His Majesty Rupert de Giret.
[LEVIATHAN]
I see what is happening.
You wish to chase me
out of this land,
so you may produce
gold yourself.
[MUSGRAVE gasps]
How dare you!
[LEVIATHAN]
Dost thou agree, Majesty?
[RUPERT gasps]
Show your face.
I need to see what
you really look like.
[LEVIATHAN gasps]
[RUPERT]
The gold means nothing to me.
I'm afraid of what you might be!
Are you a demon?
Or are you a mere human?
Reveal yourself.
Show me what sort of creature
with which I have made the
mistake of forming a contract.
[LEVIATHAN gasps]
Stay back!
[RUPERT]
Please...
Take it off.
Show us all...
what is underneath.
[LEVIATHAN]
Stop it!
--Don't touch me!
--[RUPERT groans]
[CROWD gasps]
[ROSE gasps]
[RUPERT gasps]
[IAN]
The verdict is in.
My father's court concluded that
alchemy doesn't really exist.
How can they be so foolish?
[LEVIATHAN]
Ian...
Thou needs not worry about it.
But all you have to do is teach
me how to become an alchemist.
And then I can use
your techniques
to convince my
father he's wrong!
[IAN gasps]
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[LEVIATHAN] I forced the
boy to drink molten gold.
[GUARD A]
You monster!
[GUARD B]
Arrest him!
[LEVIATHAN]
Can you show me
where the gold in
this room is hidden?
Here's a question for Musgrave.
If real alchemists
truly do not exist,
then from where did this gold
that killed his son
magically appear?
[LEVIATHAN]
No one here can punish me.
Understand?
I am invincible.
[cackles]
[footsteps]
[LEVIATHAN]
Forgive me... Ian.
You allowed your
anger and despair
to get the better of you.
What a pathetic fool you are.
--[gasps]
--[footsteps]
[LEVIATHAN]
Ian?
[ALBERT] It's about time I get
to meet the great Leviathan.
The honor is truly all mine.
I am Albert. And I've
come to protect you.
[LEVIATHAN] You said that
you're here to keep me safe.
Who's after me?
[ALBERT]
The King, of course.
Now, the Ministry of the Occult
would never betray His Majesty
by helping you out
of this predicament.
However, I have my
own personal reasons
for wanting to keep
you alive and well.
But naturally, my help
doesn't come free.
[LEVIATHAN] Hmph. Thou wishes
for me to make thou gold?
Nothing so tacky.
I desire something else.
[LEVIATHAN gasps]
A storm's coming.
And I need your talents
to prepare for it.
[LEVIATHAN]
What storm?
[VICTORIQUE]
That's the first one.
[ALBERT] The King is not
aware of its approach.
But it will be a tempest
of unprecedented size.
[LEVIATHAN]
What are you referring to?
[BOTH]
A great war.
The human race has never
experienced a conflict
of this magnitude in
its entire history.
We will all be torn apart
from fighting each other.
Every single town.
The oceans.
And even the skies will
become a battlefield!
[ALBERT] Blood from every
citizen will fill the streets.
Many countries
will be destroyed!
[ALBERT]
When the storm has blown over,
the world will be changed.
A new age will arise, governed
by a more modern set of rules.
They can't be allowed
to destroy us!
I will protect our history!
And our knowledge!
The power of the ancient ones!
[LEVIATHAN]
What role do you expect me
to play in all of this?
He wants to use you
for his own gain.
Give me the strength and power
needed to fight for us.
Let me defend not only Saubure,
but all of old Europe from the
upcoming regime's new laws.
[LEVIATHAN]
What dost thou want from me?
Make me an army of men
that cannot be defeated.
Immortal soldiers.
Homunculi!
[LEVIATHAN gasps]
[VICTORIQUE] An unstoppable
force to face the storm.
And a lonely monster
trapped in a clock tower.
The alchemist still wanders
around in that prison of his.
All alone.
[VICTORIQUE]
Just like me.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
You don't scare me.
I know who you are.
Brian Roscoe.
I heard all about your donations
to the village of
the Gray Wolves.
What are you doing here?
And how do you know
Victorique and her mother?
A-Are you related?
What is your relationship
to that cub?
I'm just-- Well, you see--
The two of us are
really good friends!
You two are friends?
[laughs]
What's so funny?!
[ROSCOE] Gray Wolves
simply aren't capable
of having human friends.
It's not possible for them to
give their hearts to people.
That's not true at all!
Don't be foolish.
Humans were born to
fear the Gray Wolves.
From my experience,
men only get close to them
to use their powers.
[panting]
[CORDELIA]
Victorique...
[ROSCOE grunts]
[ROSCOE]
During the first storm,
that beautiful little
monster of yours was born.
She's only alive so that she may
be used during the second one.
For a storm?
[SERGIUS] I'm told that
many years from now,
a great wind will blow.
The strength of it will cause
our entire world to shake.
[ROSCOE] It's true that
your "friend" and I
come from the same people.
But she's also the child of
an influential nobleman.
She's nothing more
than a tool to him.
[grunts] You came to take
Victorique away, didn't you?
[ROSCOE]
And what if I did?
Then I'll protect her!
Let's see you try.
[KAZUYA grunts]
[KAZUYA grunting]
[groans]
That cub is lucky
to have such a knight.
[KAZUYA] Victorique is
not a tool to be used!
And she's not a monster.
Or a Gray Wolf.
She's my closest friend!
The wheels have already
been put in motion.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Wait, stop! What does that mean?
Just be careful.
The Marquis de Blois
is a very fickle man.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
He disappeared.
Victorique's father...
What does he have
to do with all this?
Something's going to
happen to her soon.
They'll try to take her away.
No, Victorique!
What's wrong?
[KAZUYA]
Uh...
Oh! I didn't see you there.
I was just working... on my...
...um, daily vocal exercises.
--No! Vic! Tor!
--You just keep getting
--Eek! No!
--weirder and weirder.
[KAZUYA laughs nervously]
What are you doing at
the clock tower anyway?
[VICTORIQUE] Obviously,
I came to solve the riddle.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA] You already unraveled
Leviathan's mystery?
Yes, I've gathered all
the fragments of chaos.
Would you like me to
explain it to you?
[KAZUYA]
Of course!
Meet me up top.
And don't forget to
bring the farting newt
and Investigator
Spike-Head with you.
[KAZUYA]
Okay.
[VICTORIQUE chuckles]
[VICTORIQUE]
There are two reasons why
the clock tower ghost story
was so popular among locals.
One, is that there really
was a mysterious alchemist
who lived in this creepy
building over twenty years ago.
And the other reason is...
...the sensation that you're
all feeling right now.
Look at this.
[KAZUYA]
What is it?
[VICTORIQUE]
I asked the carpenter
who's surveying the tower
for a copy of the floor plan.
The blue lines are the
tower's original design,
while the black lines show
the actual construction.
The source of our strange
sensation is at the bottom.
The building was intentionally
built to be slightly warped.
[ALL gasp]
[VICTORIQUE]
For example...
All the stairways are
tilted ever so slightly.
They look straight
to the naked eye,
but they are in fact curved.
And every single stair sits
at a moderately different
height than the others.
That explains it!
I was wondering why I fell.
[KAZUYA] But... why would
they build it like that?
[VICTORIQUE] You know about
the secret rooms that were used
in this part of the country
to hide Protestants, right?
Yeah?
The same basic idea was
used to hide rooms in here,
but their purpose was
completely different.
And according to these
original blueprints of mine...
[ALL gasp]
[VICTORIQUE] This school's
campus was initially built
to serve as a secret
Sauburean armory.
Some of these facilities
were constructed in order
to hide confidential
things from the public.
The presence of concealed rooms
shouldn't come as a surprise.
That means... the answer to
the riddle is hidden, then!
[BLOIS]
Be careful.
Victorique.
Kujo, you need to sing for us.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Sing what?
[VICTORIQUE] That old
song about the Africans.
Uh-- No! Why would I sing that--
[groans, yelps]
[whimpers] Fine, I'll do
it. Just stop kicking me.
[VICTORIQUE]
Excellent.
[sighs]
[inhales]
♪ Dee doo-da-doo! Da-doo! Doo! ♪
♪ Gold that glows bright
in the sunlight. ♪
♪ Dee doo-da-doo! Da-doo! Doo! ♪
♪ On and on,
they rowed their oars. ♪
♪ Trying to land
on better shores. ♪
♪ Dee doo-da-doo! Da-doo! Doo! ♪
♪ Finally, they land
shouting loud ♪
♪ as the burning sand
swallows... the... crowd. ♪
♪ One by one they
disappeared till all... ♪
♪ ...were... ♪
♪ ...gone. ♪
[sighs]
There! I hope you enjoyed that!
And just so you know,
it's mean to make a man sing and
dance in front of other people.
Be quiet. Just stand there
with your mouth shut
and try not to be embarrassed
about your poor singing voice.
[KAZUYA groans]
Those song lyrics
brought a great deal of
chaos to the surface. Gold.
And what happens to them after
they arrive? Shouting loudly.
Then they disappeared.
Didn't you tell me that all
the Africans in this village
mysteriously died out in 1873?
[AVRIL gasps]
Yeah?
[VICTORIQUE]
Interesting.
I doubt it's a coincidence
that there was a gold rush
in both the New World and
Africa that very year.
[BOTH gasp]
[VICTORIQUE]
The Kingdom of Saubure
had set up colonies there, too.
So the King at that time
put the Africans to work,
making them secretly smuggle
gold into our country.
And then...
He made sure they stayed quiet.
[VICTORIQUE] The year
after he stole the gold,
the King unexpectedly died.
In the chaos that followed,
everyone who knew
about the secret stash
passed away as well.
Except for him, of course.
Who else knew?
[VICTORIQUE]
He fled this area
and went into hiding
for a long time after,
before returning to Saubure
twenty years later...
...as a mysterious masked man
with a knack for alchemy.
--Leviathan?
--[BLOIS gasps]
Hold on.
I thought you said he was a
fraud and not a real alchemist.
Kujo.
Please tell me you were
actually paying attention
when I was telling you about
the Philosopher's Stone.
You said it was an
important gemstone.
And that every alchemist
used to carry one around.
What color is it?
I think... that it's
a deep red, right?
Like a pomegranate.
Look around this room
and tell me if you see
that shade of red.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[VICTORIQUE] Surely, anyone
who had knowledge of alchemy
would automatically be drawn
to that flower, wouldn't they?
[VICTORIQUE]
All of the people who died here
were from out of town.
More than likely,
they came looking for the
secret of Leviathan's alchemy.
[VICTORIQUE]
Stop it!
Don't touch that, Avril!
[AVRIL]
Why not?
Because it's poisoned, idiot.
[ALL gasp]
Leviathan set that trap himself.
To conceal the truth about
his alchemy and background.
[KAZUYA]
But why?
[ALL gasp]
Here we go.
--[KAZUYA gasps]
--It's so bright.
[VICTORIQUE] Looks like
I found you, Leviathan.
Doth that frustrate thee?
It should.
Because I also figured out...
...the identity you were
trying to hide... under this!
Admit... that... I beat you.
Admit... it now.
[growls]
[gasps]
[KAZUYA chuckles]
[VICTORIQUE growls]
[clears throat]
I know who you really are.
[BOTH gasp]
Wait, he was from Africa?
Fifty years ago...
An invisible spirit was
felt at the graveyard.
But it wasn't a ghost.
[footsteps]
[VICTORIQUE]
It was Leviathan.
An African boy running naked
in the middle of the night
would be hard to see.
I know what happened.
You were the only
person alive who knew
where the gold was hidden.
So you used that gold in your
plan to get close to the King
by pretending to
be an alchemist.
The only reason to do that...
..would be to protect
your beloved homeland.
Manipulating the King
was the only way
you could stop Africa from
becoming a foreign colony.
[VICTORIQUE]
But you failed.
And died before
completing your mission.
[VICTORIQUE] This all
happened a long time ago.
Your story is fading.
[VICTORIQUE]
Like a dream.
Or illusion.
--[BLOIS gasps]
--Look out!
[KAZUYA gasps]
Victorique!
[footsteps]
[AVRIL]
Are you okay?
[KAZUYA]
Yeah.
Rest in peace...
...my fellow monster.
[LEVIATHAN groaning]
Is this how I die?
[ALBERT]
Leviathan!
Where are you? Answer me!
Have you forgotten
about the deal we made?
You promised!
I need my army!
[LEVIATHAN panting]
Thou honestly thought I could
make unstoppable soldiers?
You're a fool, Albert.
If it's power thou desires,
then thou needs to sire a child
with a woman who
possesses such powers.
That is the only way,
Albert de Blois.
Leviathan!
[footsteps]
[BLOIS] They've decided
to tear the old tower down.
[VICTORIQUE]
I see.
[BLOIS]
Do you know the whole story?
[VICTORIQUE] My wellspring
of wisdom knows many things.
[BLOIS] Our father
tried to use Leviathan
to create an army
of homunculi for him.
[VICTORIQUE]
But they were never made.
So he decided to
have me instead.
A Wolf child of his very own.
It's not hard to see that
Leviathan and I are the same.
Both tools for
the upcoming storm.
I realized why I've been
locked up in this school
for all these years.
I'm another weapon
in the secret armory.
I've often wondered if our
father intends to leave you here
for the rest of your life.
What's his real plan?
[KAZUYA gasps]
There you are!
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
About time!
I've been looking for you!
It drives me crazy when you
disappear on me like that!
I'd honestly like to know
how many hours I've wasted
just trying to track you down.
Now, don't go blaming me
when you get lost for
real one of these days.
[VICTORIQUE]
Are you being serious, Kujo?
[KAZUYA gasps]
Do you think a day will come
when you won't be
able to find me?
[gasps]
Let's see you try.
The two of you will be
blown apart by the winds.
Never to be put
back together again.
[gasps]
[SERGIUS]
However...
Your two hearts are connected.
And always will be.
Don't worry about that...
because nothing in this world
will ever be able to stop
me from finding you.
[KAZUYA]
Now... Let's go.
[LEVIATHAN]
To the person who someday
finds this book of mine...
[LEVIATHAN]
Thou art the twin of my soul.
I beg of thee to please find me.
Release me from this prison.
From this loneliness.
Only thou can save me.
[KAZUYA]
Hey! Victorique!
Where are you?
Don't tell me that you
ran off somewhere again.
A-Are you really not here?
Victorique!
Where did you go this time?