[gunshot]
[KAZUYA whimpering]
[gasps]
[KAZUYA gasps]
What... just happened?
[KAZUYA]
Julie!
This was hidden inside
the wall lamp.
There must be more
just like he said.
[NED]
Now, you toss yours.
We're already jumping
at shadows as it is.
Toss it.
Or do you have a
reason to carry it?
[JULIE]
Tch.
[KAZUYA]
Sorry.
[gasps]
Thanks a lot.
Well, shall we be going?
Uh, right.
[VICTORIQUE] Kujo. You were
saying something about being
the third son of an
imperial soldier back there.
Does birth order mean
something significant
in your home country?
You could say that.
But despite their advantage,
I made far better grades
than my siblings.
Oh, that's interesting.
So do those good grades
give you an authority
over your two brothers?
Of course it doesn't! [growls]
Look, I'm just being stubborn.
My brothers get all the
preferential treatment.
So I had to study like crazy
just to compete with them.
Stubborn... Huh.
Kujo. I hope you know
that your honesty...
...is a virtue.
--[NED screams]
--[KAZUYA gasps]
[JULIE]
Ned!
[ALL gasp]
[KAZUYA]
Ned...?
No pulse.
We were too late.
It's all... the same...
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo, come here.
Give me a moment.
Knowing the cause of death
might help us out later.
Get away from there
this instant.
Hey, this isn't the
time to be selfish.
We need information
if we're gonna--
[VICTORIQUE]
I'm  scared, okay?
I can't help it.
Now, please come here.
I'm begging you.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
I thought so.
She's been afraid
this whole time.
At this rate, we'll be killed.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[JULIE]
What's wrong?
There's no time to explain.
Just run!
[KAZUYA yelps]
[JULIE gasps]
[VICTORIQUE] Come on, we'll
hide in one of the rooms.
Hopefully, it will have
a hidden weapon or two.
[rattling]
[KAZUYA gasps]
--[JULIE] He's coming.
--[KAZUYA gasps]
Who?! We're the only
--ones left!
--[thump]
Do you know why I'm
doing this, little girl?
You're hares.
And I'm a hunting dog!
[JULIE gasps]
Victorique!
[NED groans]
[VICTORIQUE groans]
Run away!
I can't... My locket!
[NED grunts]
[KAZUYA yells]
[NED groans]
We should move.
[JULIE]
That's the telegraph room.
Here, this is yours.
Thank you, Julie.
I'm guessing it's
pretty important to you.
Kujo?
I'll get it.
Hey, Victorique.
I have to ask you.
How'd you know Ned
was still alive?
That's right.
He definitely didn't
have a pulse back then.
Back then?
Sorry. I meant "back there."
He used the tennis ball.
The one he was playing with
while we were below deck.
[VICTORIQUE] If he pressed
it against his armpit,
he would have temporarily
stopped his pulse.
[KAZUYA]
Oh.
I get it now.
You knew that
from the beginning.
That's why you called Kujo over.
The "scared" bit
was cute, though.
I didn't mean a
single word of it!
It was the only way I could get
this "third son of a solider"
to move his stubborn
behind to safety.
[sighs]
I wish you'd stop
calling me that.
It's really annoying.
[VICTORIQUE]
Well, it's what you are.
[KAZUYA]
True, but...
[JULIE screams]
[KAZUYA gasps]
--[JULIE whimpering]
--[NED chuckles]
[KAZUYA]
Victorique, get in! Quickly!
Send out a distress signal!
[VICTORIQUE]
But--
What about you?
I'm the one who got you
into this stupid mess.
It's my job to
get you out of it!
You're wrong!
You wouldn't be here if it
weren't for me, remember?
I'm the one who
found the invitation
and made you come here!
But if I can't protect you.
My honor as an
imperial soldier's son--
No, that's not it.
My honor's not the issue.
If I'm being honest...
I just want to save you!
Kujo...
[yelps]
--[thumping]
--[VICTORIQUE] Don't do this!
Please, stay with me!
We'll go home together!
Don't leave me!
Kujo!
[yells]
[NED groans]
[KAZUYA groans]
[BOTH grunting]
[KAZUYA]
It's just like that day.
I'm on the ground.
I can't do anything.
But... there is a difference.
[KAZUYA]
If I stay down...
It's all over.
Not just my life...
But Victorique's, too!
[NED groans]
[KAZUYA groans]
--[thud]
--[NED groans]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[sighs]
How are you feeling, young man?
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
--[door rattles]
--[gasps]
[KAZUYA chuckles]
Kujo...
Aside from your bruises,
you seem to be more
or less unharmed.
Yup.
You seem lost in thought.
[VICTORIQUE]
Just admiring the view.
It's beautiful.
[gasps]
My lady.
Your hand.
[JULIE]
Who are you?
Inspector Blois.
[JULIE gasps]
[gasps]
How did you know...
...that I was behind it all?
You aren't a very good liar.
You aren't a coal heiress.
That much was quite obvious.
But how could you
tell that was a lie?
She has a noticeable habit.
[VICTORIQUE] She only walks
a few steps before she turns.
Right?
I'm not sure I follow.
That isn't the habit of someone
who was raised
in a large estate.
If they spent
most of their lives
in a place where you
couldn't take five steps
without hitting
a wall, however...
A solitary confinement cell.
A room in a hospital.
The attic of a mansion.
[clears throat]
These are common conditions.
I meant nothing by them.
So, what's it mean?
I'll get to that.
First, there was another
important clue.
The weapon you used
to shoot Maurice.
You had it with you
the entire time.
What?
[VICTORIQUE] Kujo, do you
remember when she hit you
with her handbag in
the lounge earlier?
[KAZUYA]
Yeah. It really hurt... A lot.
[VICTORIQUE]
But...
When I picked it up later,
it was light as a feather.
You wouldn't have felt
anything being hit by that.
[sighs]
We were all orphans....
...when they took us.
Ten years ago, we were
placed in black carriages
with bars on the windows.
We lost consciousness,
and awoke on that accursed ship.
We were from
different countries,
so communicating
was pretty difficult.
But our common circumstances
made us sympathetic
to each other.
However...
[ITALIAN BOY]
Murder... Someone killed him!
[GERMAN BOY]
But... who?
[FRENCH GIRL] We're the
only ones on this ship...
So one of us must
be the murderer!
[JULIE]
His death was the start of it.
We grew suspicious and paranoid.
Then...
We killed each other.
[JULIE]
And yet...
You're bleeding badly.
Hold still, 'kay?
Wait, you're giving that to me?
But it's important
to you, isn't it?
[JULIE] In the middle of
the chaos, I made a friend.
I won't leave you.
We're escaping.
No one can stop us.
[JULIE] We kept each
other from giving up.
And finally made it to the deck.
[ITALIAN BOY]
Yes!
There's the telegraph room!
We'll be safe soon, okay?
[CHILDREN gasp]
It seems the brave little hares
have finally reached
the finish line!
Now which ones survived?
Speak up, children!
Tell us, what are
your nationalities?
[HUEY]
France, Italy, America...
...and the Kingdom of Saubure.
[ALEX]
You!
Yes. He's our hunting dog.
Quite a useful little Brit.
We wouldn't have been able to
do this without his assistance.
His job was to confuse the hares
and drive them
the way we wanted.
[ROXANE] A young man's life
will soon end in betrayal.
His death will be
the start of it all.
The world will turn to brittle
stone, and down it shall fall.
[GUEST A]
Madame Roxane...
[ROXANE] And thus, the running
of the hares is ended!
[ROXANE]
Now, let us sink this box.
And follow the path that
has been laid out for us!
These hares...
...will all prosper!
So it is foretold!
Why "the running of the hares"?
I believe she was
conducting a form
of large-scale fortune telling.
How so?
Roxane kept many
hares on her estate
to use in divination rituals.
She would let them
loose in her garden,
along with a hunting dog,
and predict the future based
on which hares survived.
So, she was using
us as stand-ins?
There are many fragments of
chaos present in this case.
First, there are
the eleven orphans
that were brought together
from different countries.
Then, Roxane's
morbid proclamation.
And last...
The fact that all
of this happened
during the spring of 1914.
[KAZUYA gasps]
That would put it around the
time of the Sarajevo incident,
the one that started
the Great War.
What a coincidence!
Yes. Too much of one, actually.
[VICTORIQUE]
At the end of June 1914,
the Crown Prince of Austria
was assassinated in Sarajevo.
[VICTORIQUE] When the Great
War broke out as a result,
politicians turned
to fortune-tellers
and other forms of mystics to
try and predict the outcome.
And to that end...
They prepared a proper stage,
known as the Queen Berry ,
and used human
hares to represent
the nations of the world.
But that's--!
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo.
You're an earnest enough
student, I suppose.
Can you tell us how
the Great War ended?
Thanks, I guess.
Well...
The Allied forces won when
Germany signed the armistice.
And who were the Allies?
Let's see.
They were France and Italy...
England, America...
...and Saubure.
[gasps]
Thus, Roxane's
prediction came true.
They used us to make
political decisions?
I always thought it was
just a twisted game.
[sighs]
[ALEX]
It was traumatic.
I never recovered from it.
I spent years in a sanatorium...
...in a small room...
...just like you said.
I could only take
five steps in a row.
However, the other
survivors and I
were given generous
sums of money.
So we could prosper,
as she foretold.
When I was released,
I used that money to
build a new Queen Berry .
A new stage.
Now, tell me, little detective.
When did you first realize that
I may have been behind this?
[VICTORIQUE]
My suspicions started when
we all woke up in the lounge.
[ALEX gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
You made a lot of noise
about the door being locked,
but that was a lie.
And you were the one
who pointed out
the threat written on the wall,
to make it clear to everyone
what kind of ritual
was taking place.
Very observant...
Now I understand why you held
onto Kujo's hand so suddenly.
You knew I was a threat.
But he treated me like
an old acquaintance.
Am I right?
Aw, thanks, Victorique!
I've heard enough.
Let's go.
[BLOIS]
Hm? Is that...?
[COP A] Yes. They managed
to apprehend Roxane's killer.
[ALEX gasps]
It's... Lee!
So... She got her revenge, too.
Both of us can finally move on.
--[ALEX] Lee!
--[LEE gasps]
[LEE gasps]
[bell rings]
--[footsteps]
--[KAZUYA] Victorique!
[VICTORIQUE yawns]
I don't see why
you have to shout.
That scoundrel did it again!
"Another great achievement
for Inspector Blois!
A brilliant end to the
Queen Berry affair!"
He only caught her
because you reported it!
And as if that wasn't enough,
he shamelessly plagiarized
your explanation!
[yawns]
My big brother has
always been a snob.
I bet.
How do you put up with it?
Uh-- Hold on.
Could you please
repeat that for me?
My big brother is
a snob, always was.
[KAZUYA]
Oh, I see.
What?!
Well, we both have
the same father.
However, we have
different mothers.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
Grévil is the eldest son
of the Marquis de Blois.
My mother was one
of his mistresses.
She was a dangerous person,
under government watch.
I was raised alone,
in a small room deep
within the Blois mansion.
My freedom was limited.
And even though I was
eventually allowed
to come to this school,
I have to get permission
from the Marquis de Blois
if I want to leave.
I guess you could say
I'm a princess in a tower.
But that... doesn't suit me.
[yawns]
Anyway, the princess is
getting bored again.
Wow...
[gasps]
Kujo, I want you to
go to the lower world
and find me a mystery.
[KAZUYA] Uh-- How do you
expect me to do that?!
Oh, I don't care
how; just do it!
Otherwise, I'm going
to die of boredom!
Besides, you have so
few friends already.
Do you really want
to risk losing one?
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Friends?
Hey, Victorique?
[stammers]
Don't tell me you
just died on me!
Say something.
Or just shake your head.
Come on!
[KAZUYA gasps]
[VICTORIQUE snoring]
She's... asleep?
[sighs]
[KAZUYA]
The captive Princess.
The mysterious Victorique.
There's so much I
don't know about her.
But one thing is certain...
[KAZUYA]
This strange girl is...
...for whatever reason...
...my friend.
Tell you what, Victorique.
We'll go outside again
soon, just the two of us.
And then...
We'll look at the beautiful
light reflected on the ocean.
That's a promise.
[yelps]
[VICTORIQUE sighs]
[KAZUYA] Avril, the new transfer
student, is really nice!
She's so mature.
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo...
If you're going to
get hot and bothered,
could you do it somewhere else?
[KAZUYA stammers]
Hot and bothered?