[CORDELIA screaming]
[CORDELIA gasping, screaming]
[MARQUIS] The gray Wolf pup
will be born on the same night
that the savior
Jesus Christ was born.
How very ironic indeed.
[CORDELIA gasping]
[MARQUIS]
Such an unfortunate child...
To be brought forth
from a wellspring
of tainted blood and sin.
I offer a grievous blessing.
[CORDELIA gasps]
[KAZUYA panting]
This is the first snow
I've seen in Saubure.
And in a few weeks...
...I'll have my first
Christmas here.
[KAZUYA] Victorique,
you have to come with me
to the Christmas party.
It's supposed to be lots of fun.
And there's also a gift
exchange we can take part in.
It doesn't make any sense
for a person to celebrate
their own birthday by giving
someone else a present.
Well, I do have to
agree with you on that.
But giving out gifts is a
really fun holiday tradition
that I happen to like a lot--
Did you mean because it's
Jesus Christ's birthday?
[VICTORIQUE]
It's not only his.
[KAZUYA]
Huh?!
Since I'm shopping for a
birthday and Christmas present,
it needs to be special!
[enging revving]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[tires screeching]
How's it going, Kujo?
Uh-- Hey Miss Sophie!
[SOPHIE]
Where are you headed?
[KAZUYA] Oh. I'm just going
Christmas shopping in Saubreme.
[SOPHIE]
What a coincidence!
Hop on! I'll give you a lift.
[KAZUYA]
Thanks!
Are you shopping, too?
No, the Phantom Theater is
putting on a Christmas play
called "The Blue
Rose of Saubreme."
That rings a bell.
It must be about--
--[gasps]
--Here!
You see? It's based
on the real life story
of our most tragic
queen, Coco Rose!
I've been a fan of hers
since I was a little girl.
I wouldn't miss this
play for the world.
Hurry up and get on,
we can talk more later.
I appreciate the ride.
I had no idea you
even knew how to
--drive a motorcycle.
--[engine revs]
--I'm very impressed.
[SOPHIE]
Hm?
This is my first time on one.
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[screaming]
[VICTORIQUE]
Where is he?
[AVRIL panting]
Hey, Victorique!
[VICTORIQUE]
It's the farting newt.
[AVRIL]
Do you know where Kujo's at?
I was hoping he'd help me
get some stuff ready
for the school's
Christmas party.
I know!
[screams]
How about I tell you a
really spooky ghost story
while we wait for him?
It'll be more fun
than a dumb book.
[VICTORIQUE growls]
[VICTORIQUE panting]
[AVRIL]
Um... Are you okay?
Here's the deal.
You are not allowed
to take one step
over this wall of knowledge.
Do you understand me?
[AVRIL]
Huh?
All right.
Now tell me this story of yours.
It's about Coco Rose!
I'm sure you remember that
she's the beloved queen
Leviathan made
the blue rose for.
[VICTORIQUE]
Of course.
[AVRIL] Well, Queen Coco was
not able to have a baby.
And King Rupert de Giret
reproached her for that.
So he sent her away to live in
a country house with a maid.
[VICTORIQUE] When is this
going to get interesting?
[AVRIL] Be patient!
I'm setting up the story!
Anyway, Leviathan had
given her a magical rock.
And whenever she
held that stone,
it gave her the ability
to turn invisible.
Thanks to that powerful gift,
Queen Coco was able to
slip past the guards
and sneak out of her prison
to actually have some fun.
[VICTORIQUE]
Hm...
A young queen locked
away in a country house.
And a magical rock that
helped her escape captivity.
[VICTORIQUE]
Well, I guess his head is
as dense as a rock, at least.
[AVRIL]
Huh?
[ROSCOE]
"The Blue Rose of Saubreme."
I shouldn't be surprised
that Marquis de Blois
is the one putting
on this damn play.
And, of course,
it's on Christmas.
The sacred night he tainted
with your humiliation.
But I doubt he did all this
simply as some twisted joke.
There has to be a reason
he picked this specific play
to be performed on
this specific night.
Ugh! That man is such a coward.
Doesn't he have better things
to do than try to hurt you?
[CORDELIA humming]
[ROSCOE]
Such a rosy life.
But if the rose is blue...
...that changes everything.
[DANCER A] Oh, just hurry
up and pack it in there.
[DANCER B] Hey! Has
anyone seen my eyelashes?
[GINGER]
Cordelia.
The red-haired boy is
in the audience again.
[CORDELIA]
Yeah.
I promised to meet him
after tonight's performance.
[GINGER laughs]
Well, look at you!
Be careful though.
The quiet types are known
to have wandering hands!
Oh, he would never try
something like that,
and besides he's just a child.
[GINGER]
Hm...
How old is that
necklace of yours?
You should get the redhead
to buy you a new one.
No way.
This is proof that I've
taken ownership of my past.
[whistling]
--[CORDELIA gasps]
--Our cue!
Better hurry!
La vie en rose!
[GINGER]
[applause]
Cordelia!
[whistles]
[PERFORMERS] ♪ I have no tarts
or macarons I can spare ♪
♪ There's just crunchy,
crusty bread to go around ♪
♪ No fair ♪
[PERFORMERS] ♪ There isn't
a Prince Charming ♪
♪ No brave knight
to come save me ♪
♪ But I honestly don't care ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ I'm free ♪
♪ 'Cause I do ♪
♪ Have my love from you ♪
[PERFORMERS]
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ You've got me ♪
♪ I know it sounds naïve ♪
♪ We'll be okay ♪
♪ Don't you cry ♪
♪ We'll give 'em a show ♪
♪ Grab my hand and away we go! ♪
♪ It's a rosy life ♪
♪ Rosy life ♪
♪ La vie en rose!
La vie en rose! ♪
[CORDELIA gasps]
[MARQUIS] Looks like I've
caught myself a Gray Wolf.
[CORDELIA gasps]
Hey, Cordelia!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[ROSCOE gasps]
--[clap]
--[CORDELIA gasps]
[ROSCOE groans]
[CORDELIA gasps, screams]
[DOCTOR]
Marquis de Blois,
the baby's crowning.
[MARQUIS]
My little Gray Wolf.
You've been a guest of
mine for a year now.
The time has come for you to
actually be of some use to me.
Our blood is mixed together.
Wolf and human are now one.
A child of destiny...
...will finally be born.
Arriving to purify
the corruption
and cut through the storm.
Now do your part
and give me power.
[gasping
[screams]
[ROSCOE]
Cordelia...
Cordelia!
[gasps]
I think it would be wise
for us to head to Saubreme
sooner rather than later.
Brian...
Let's go see the Wolf pup.
Though I despise her,
it doesn't matter.
You love her.
Besides, we need to know
just what Victorique can do.
I've never questioned
my daughter's strength.
Her intelligence and kindness
are without parallel.
There's nothing I believe
in more than her power.
My whole life has
been full of nothing
but humiliation and resentment.
[CORDELIA] She's the only
thing I can count on.
So the "interesting" ghost story
turned out to be another fart
from the brainless newt.
Why am I not surprised?
[AVRIL gasps]
I haven't finished yet!
Mm...
[fluttering]
[BOTH gasp]
Ew! A dove! I hate those
filthy birds with a passion.
They're always trying to
walk on people's heads,
all pitter-patter like.
[gasps]
[AVRIL] And just listen to that
creepy noise they make.
Proo-proo. Proo-proo.
[AVRIL gasps]
Victorique? Hey!
What happened?
Did that dove try
to touch your hair?
Why are you running away?
[MARQUIS]
The stage has been set.
The performance of "The Blue
Rose of Saubreme" at the Phantom
will undoubtedly root them
out of whatever hole
they've been hiding in.
Then I'll have "it"
reveal the murderer
from that day in front
of them and the country.
For with her
"wellspring of wisdom,"
the small Gray Wolf
with my blood
shall solve the
murder in no time.
[JULIE]
Stop it! Please!
--No!
--[NURSE A] Please. Calm down!
Hunting dogs?
[ALL grunting]
I promise that neither
one of us are animals.
We just need to get you
undressed for a bath, dear.
[CORDELIA]
It's the pendant.
[ALL gasp]
She's upset because
you tried to take it off.
[JULIE grunts]
[CORDELIA]
That seems to be why.
[JULIE cries]
[CORDELIA]
It's important to you, isn't it?
[JULIE]
Huh?
I know how you feel.
[NURSE B] Cordelia, you
shouldn't be in here.
Your next bath is not
for three more days.
[CORDELIA]
Before I knew it,
he had me locked up in
a mental institution.
In a rare act of kindness,
one of the man's sympathetic
servants gave me a picture
of my infant daughter as
he tore me away from her.
[CORDELIA]
The child I never wanted
had been forced on me
by that hateful man.
[CORDELIA]
And yet...
That night...
[CORDELIA] It felt as if
the very mind and soul
that I had been born
with and loved,
that which made up
who I was as a person,
had been torn out of my body.
And had taken on its own form.
Right in front of my eyes.
[howling]
You're a hard girl
to find, Cordelia.
[CORDELIA]
I was eventually rescued
by my red-headed friend,
Brian Roscoe.
[VOLUNTEER grunts]
Hey!
[laughing]
[ROSCOE]
Good job, Cordelia.
Looks like you're starting to
get the hang of it in there.
I've always loved
being on stage.
I know.
So, I was thinking we should
celebrate tonight's success?
What are you in the mood for?
[CORDELIA]
I'd like...
...to see her.
My daughter.
[CORDELIA]
Several years had passed
since I had been
taken away from her.
I was finally going to
hold my daughter again.
But... what I found there...
[CORDELIA gasps]
[CORDELIA]
...was my story repeating.
[CORDELIA] She was now the one
locked up in that cold tower.
Her freedom stolen.
[VICTORIQUE whimpering]
[CORDELIA]
With her cries unanswered.
And her screams forbidden.
[whimpering]
Don't worry, my love.
No words are needed.
Take this.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[CORDELIA]
As long as you have it with you,
I'll always be able to find you.
No matter where you are,
I'll come running
as fast as I can.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[gasps]
My sweet little girl...
You are... my entire soul.
[STUDENT A] Watch out!
It's the Golden Fairy!
[STUDENT B]
Huh?
[STUDENT E screams]
--[VICTORIQUE yelps]
--[STUDENT F] It fell down!
[STUDENT C]
Is its nose broken?
Oh no, it stood up again.
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo.
You've always been
able to find me.
No matter where I was.
[VICTORIQUE]
But now... I need to find you.
[VICTORIQUE] I'll search every
inch of this place if I have to.
[BLOIS]
What are you doing?!
Let go of me, you
four-eyed lunatic!
I'm not going to let you
take Victorique away again,
you spikey-haired degenerate!
S-Say what?! You're crazy-- Ah!
I won't be defeated.
Your dumb drill
doesn't scare me!
In case you haven't noticed,
my hair has tiny drills, too!
[VICTORIQUE]
Miss Cécile.
Run away, I've got him!
Where have you been?
[VICTORIQUE] I've been
trying to track down Kujo.
[gasps]
You've come here
to take me away.
Isn't that right?
So tell me...
What is it our father
wants this time?
[BLOIS]
Your assignment...
...is to unravel the most
famous unsolved murder
in all of Saubure's history!
[VICTORIQUE]
What case is that?
You can't mean...
Yes.
The one that took
place in the palace.
The murder of Queen Coco Rose!
[SOPHIE]
No way!
Tonight's show
can't be sold out!
[KAZUYA sighs]
We actually made it here alive.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
What's with the soldiers?
[SOPHIE]
It's so not fair.
Those servicemen
abused their power
and scooped up all the tickets--
Watch where you're walking!
[RUPERT]
That's enough.
Please forgive us.
Are you all right, mademoiselle?
[SOPHIE]
Oh! Yes.
That's good.
[ROGER gasps]
I'm sorry.
Let me make it up to you, miss.
We have an extra
ticket to the show.
Please take it.
[SOPHIE gasps]
Seriously?
Glad I almost ran into you!
How rude! This man is your Ki--
Hold your tongue.
Need I remind you again
that we're here on a
private matter, Roger?
Well, that was bizarre.
Ah, they must be my
guardian angels.
Sent down by God to
give this ticket to me.
[CROWD gasps]
Allow me to introduce to you...
...the two beautiful women
who will be playing Coco Rose
in tonight's show.
We have palace Coco.
And country house Coco!
The audience will get to watch
both actresses' portrayals.
[SOPHIE whines]
I can't see anything!
I'm sorry to leave
you like this.
[SOPHIE growls]
But I really need to
go shopping right now.
[SOPHIE]
I see them!
Hey! Look over here,
pretty ladies!
I'm heading off to the shops!
[KAZUYA]
Christmas seems amazing!
It's so different from the
Obon or New Year's festivals
that I'm used to.
[KAZUYA] I wonder what
I should get Victorique?
Perhaps a new pipe?
With candy hidden inside?
Or maybe...
[KAZUYA gasps]
What's this?
That? It's a locket I created
using one of the gold coins
from the king's coronation.
[KAZUYA] It reminds me
of the precious pendant
Cordelia gave
Victorique as a child.
[KAZUYA]
She sacrificed that necklace
in order to keep me from
falling to my death.
As long as she had the pendant,
Victorique's mother
would be able to save her
from any danger,
no matter what.
[KAZUYA]
It's time I replaced it.
With one from me.
[KAZUYA] She'll be safe as long
as she wears this locket.
But it won't be her mother
that comes to the rescue.
I'll be the one that saves her.
[KAZUYA groans]
[CROWD murmuring]
[SERGIUS]
A great wind will blow.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[SERGIUS] I'm told that
many years from now,
a great wind will blow.
The strength of it will cause
our entire world to shake.
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo...
Please forgive me for
not being able to find you.
I tried so hard.
[SERGIUS] Your bodies will
be weightless in its grasp.
[KAZUYA groans]
[KAZUYA gasps]
Excuse me.
[SERGIUS] The two of you will
be blown apart by the winds.
Never to be put
back together again.
[SERGIUS]
However...
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo?
I hope the prophecy
isn't coming true.
That we still have
time together...
...before we're
blown apart forever.
[SERGIUS]
Your two hearts are connected.
And always will be.
[AVRIL panting]
[sighs]
Where in the world did
that girl run off to now?
[gasps]
[AVRIL]
"The second storm is coming"?
[CORDELIA] Any day now, the
second storm will be upon us.
[CORDELIA] The time has
come to show me your power.
My sweet daughter...
My soul...
My everything...
[CÉCILE]
You can call me the trunk fairy!
I'm here to protect
you, Victorique!
Trunk, trunk, trunk!
[VICTORIQUE]
Now I feel even more nervous.