[VICTORIQUE] I was brought
here by the Marquis de Blois
for the sole purpose of
luring my mother, Cordelia,
out into the open.
The assumption was that if I
howled for her to rescue me,
then she'd have no choice
but to come to my aid.
She couldn't resist.
At least, that's what
Blois was hoping for.
[gasps]
But I defied him
and remained silent.
I wasn't about to give
him the satisfaction.
And besides, it's possible she
wouldn't have come anyway,
even if I had called her.
[KAZUYA gasps]
No, you can't believe that.
She's your mother, so
if you had, she'd be here.
But I've met her
only once in my life.
And I was so little that
it's hard to remember her.
[VICTORIQUE crying]
[CORDELIA]
Take this.
As long as you have it with you,
I'll always be able to find you.
No matter where you are,
I'll come running
as fast as I can.
[VICTORIQUE] That pendant
was the only proof I had
of my mother's existence
and of the bond between us.
But then, I lost it and
everything's changed.
[KAZUYA]
That's right.
Because of me...
That night...
[VICTORIQUE] Kujo, you're
the one who came for me
when I desperately
needed somebody.
Just like you always seem to do.
It's thanks to you
that I can even...
--[stomach rumbles]
--[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[groans]
[KAZUYA chuckles]
[KAZUYA]
Hey, slow down for a second.
You've got cream on your cheek.
[chuckles, gasps]
Oh, yeah!
I thought you might
be missing this, too.
Very good thinking, Kujo!
I do what I can.
And I'm glad to see you getting
back to your usual bossy self.
[RECEPTIONIST] Sir, the
Oriental boy has appeared.
He's very likely to take the
Gray Wolf with him when he goes.
[DIRECTOR]
No matter.
We were told to leave
them be, anyway.
The prey we were hunting
has already willingly
entered the net.
Welcome to the
Phantasmagoria night.
We are honored, Mr. Roscoe.
[ROSCOE] My apologies
for appearing unannounced
and without an invitation.
Not at all.
On the contrary, it's a
distinct privilege to have
a man of your prominence
and prestige in our midst.
However, I hope you know
that what you'll witness
at the feast isn't
mere sleight of hand.
They're true miracles, not
just an entertaining spectacle.
Right, that's what I hear.
Please don't worry.
I'll be as reverent as can be.
[DIRECTOR]
Very well.
[ROSCOE] Believe me,
I'm looking forward to this.
Keep a close eye on him.
There's no doubt in my mind
that the reason he's here
has to do with Cordelia Gallo.
Right.
And, sir?
[DIRECTOR]
Huh?
[DIRECTOR grunts]
So, he's Roger's rat.
[VICTORIQUE]
Hm.
[KAZUYA]
Hm?
What is that?
Some kind of machine?
Yes, it's a magic lantern.
[VICTORIQUE]
It's a device that's used
for projecting images.
It magnifies photographs
and pictures several
times their original size.
[KAZUYA]
Wow!
Now I see.
Its presence here might
actually explain a few things.
[KAZUYA gasps]
What's it explain?
It sounds like you've
figured something out--
[gasps]
Isn't that...
Wait, Kujo!
Hold on!
[KAZUYA]
Mr. Hunt!
[HUNT grunts]
Hey, Mr. Hunt,
what're you doing here?
--[footsteps]
--Oh! Nothing much, really.
--[thud]
--[VICTORIQUE yelps]
[groans]
[KAZUYA]
Uh-oh.
Are you okay?
[HUNT]
You aren't hurt, are you?
I'd hate to see you scratched
up, you frilly little thing!
Who do you think you are?
Hands off me, you big moron.
Hold on a minute, Victorique.
This is my friend Mr. Hunt.
He's a clockmaker.
Yes, Kujo and I came in
on the train this evening.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My, what a bore.
By the way, is that
machine oil I see?
It looks like you've
got a bunch of dirt
up under your fingernails.
Time to go, Kujo.
Oh. Sure.
[laughs nervously]
[yelps]
Calm down. They're just--
They're balloons painted
with phosphorus, that's all.
[KAZUYA]
Don't you have a pocket watch
to go fix or something?
The train doesn't leave
till first light.
And I'm intrigued
by the prospect
of hanging around with you.
It seems like it could
be quite educational.
[VICTORIQUE]
Hmph.
She has some sort of device
to support her weight
hidden on her back.
Of course.
And it's rigged with a
spring-action pulley.
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
Is that true?
[yelps]
[HUNT]
Easy one.
The bullet in the gun...
[VICTORIQUE]
...is obviously a fake.
[KAZUYA gasps]
It's comprised of tin and water,
so when it's fired, it simply
dissolves into a fine powder.
He shot that at the girl.
[HUNT]
And she had the real bullet
in her mouth from the start.
It's a very simple trick.
[KAZUYA gasps]
They're both so
ridiculously smart.
[OLD MAN]
What are you playing stupid for?
I was under the impression
magic's your
particular specialty.
Hello. I didn't expect
to bump into you again.
That reminds me.
Were you ever able to find
--your daughter?
--[OLD MAN] She isn't here.
I want to know where
you've hidden her, Reaper!
[KAZUYA gasps]
Fine, if you intend
to take her away,
I won't try to stop you.
You can go.
But know this, if you
help her escape,
you'll have to bear the guilt
of a crime even greater!
Excuse me, I need
to find my friend.
[DIRECTOR] Everyone, may I
have your attention, please!
I'm the elder sister, Carmilla.
And I am the younger, Morella.
For many years now, these
women have been well-known
in the local villages as
being the final descendants
of an ancient family who
possessed magical abilities.
This could be our last and
final glimpse of the old power!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I hereby present to you,
the Fell Sisters' Cabinet.
Go ahead and watch
if you so dare.
And don't close your
eyes for a single second.
[AUDIENCE A]
What will they do?
[AUDIENCE B]
This makes me nervous.
[AUDIENCE C]
I'm so excited!
I wonder what'll happen.
[AUDIENCE gasping, murmuring]
[KAZUYA gasps]
They switched places!
[DIRECTOR]
It's a miracle!
Once, on this very continent,
the lands of Europe
were overflowing
with the old power
and magic was all around us.
And we accepted it as a natural,
everyday occurrence
in our lives.
But now look at us.
We burn coal to
power steam engines.
We fly airships through the sky.
We use electric signals to
communicate across distances.
Progress is, indeed,
a good thing.
But at what cost?
We are losing our
essential powers
to the demands of
modern convenience.
So then, as for instance,
you there, sir.
What is our most
important power?
I would say, science.
[KAZUYA]
Mr. Hunt?
Fascinating.
Even after witnessing a miracle,
that's your answer
to this question?
I think you lack
faith, my friend.
[HUNT]
It's a trick!
What's "miraculous"
about what we saw?
[MORELLA, CARMILLA]
If that's what you believe.
Then why not put it to the test?
Step into the box.
Then, you will see.
You will see.
You will surely learn.
The undeniable majesty
of the old power
which science has never
been able to explain.
You're an arrogant, boastful
pup born of the new age.
You'll be judged.
You'll be judged and
you will pay dearly.
Very interesting.
In that case, I readily
accept your challenge.
Then everyone will see
this was all just a trick.
[DIRECTOR]
If I lay the knife here,
it should be ample proof that
the ropes on their wrists
were not untied.
However, if the knife were
to fall to the floor...
Sure. Guess that's fair enough.
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo...
Kujo!
Something's not right.
You must stop this.
[DIRECTOR]
Magic of the ancients...
Give us a miracle once more!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[screams]
[MORELLA screams]
[AUDIENCE D]
What?
[gasps]
Morella!
[AUDIENCE screaming]
Oh my god, that man is dead!
[AUDIENCE E]
It's the dagger from before!
[AUDIENCE F] But... their
hands are still tied!
[AUDIENCE G]
Then who...?
[KAZUYA gasps]
[AUDIENCE gagging, groaning]
[AUDIENCE H]
Out of the tent!
[AUDIENCE I]
What's going on?
[VICTORIQUE]
Cover your mouth!
Don't breathe it in!
This smoke must contain a
hallucinogenic substance!
They use it to trick the
audience into thinking
the magic they see on
stage is the real thing.
Let's go!
[KAZUYA]
Right, okay!
[DIRECTOR]
What's happening?
The fog is too thick!
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Is that...?
[VICTORIQUE]
Where're you going?
[KAZUYA]
Wait here! I'll be back soon!
No, stop-- [gasps]
[VICTORIQUE coughs]
Don't go, Kujo...
It's... dangerous... [coughs]
[KAZUYA]
Brian, what are you doing here?
I won't let you do anything
to hurt Victorique!
Where'd he go?
[door creaks]
Hey, it's you again.
Yes, we meet again...
...Mr. Kazuya Kujo.
[KAZUYA]
Cordelia...
Are you here to see...
The memento box.
The Academy is quite impressive.
It would appear that we were
a bit too late getting
here, after all.
The box we were searching
for is already lost to us.
Huh?
If you would, please
give her this for me.
[CORDELIA]
Tell her, "Solve the mystery.
Show me that you have
the power to live."
And one more thing...
[KAZUYA gasps, yelps]
[CORDELIA]
I'm counting on you.
Wait! Come back!
Please don't leave here
without seeing Victorique!
You can't imagine how
much she wants to see you!
It's so bad, she can
barely keep from crying!
We were finally able
to stop the fog.
You were right.
There were signs someone
tampered with it.
And where's Brian?
When last seen, he was with
the Wolf cub, Director.
[DIRECTOR grunts]
[ROSCOE] Sorry, but I'd like
you to stay here a bit longer.
It's necessary to draw their
attention to myself for a while.
[VICTORIQUE]
You're nothing but a swindler.
Utilizing deception just like
you did with the German army
ten years ago at the
start of the Great War.
[ROSCOE chuckles]
Mary Who Caused the Fall.
That story is well-known.
It was you.
You were behind it!
The incident at
Beelzebub's Skull.
You, Brian...
...with a little help from
the magic lantern.
[VICTORIQUE]
I don't know why you helped
the Academy back then.
And I don't care.
What I really want to know...
...is why ten years later,
you and my mother came
back here together.
Your mother and I, as well as
the Ministry of the Occult,
are all looking for
the same thing.
I ask you, Wolf cub, have
you ever considered this?
What lies ahead of us is
a budding age of science,
represented by
the new continent.
And the ones who will hold
the power in that New World...
It won't be we of
the old tribes,
nor the ancient
Ministry of the Occult.
The Academy...
The memento box is needed
to erode their influence.
To diminish their power.
[chuckles]
During the war, you see,
I took it upon myself
to hide that box away
in the magic lantern room.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Oh my. Looks like I might've
spilled a little too much.
See you later,
misbegotten Wolf cub.
[VICTORIQUE]
No, wait!
One more thing.
Please, just let me ask you
one more thing about her.
Mama... Did she say...?
Brian Roscoe...
Where the hell did you go?
[gasps]
[OLD MAN] It's said that long
ago, during the Middle Ages,
a king barricaded
himself in here,
fearing the spread
of the Black Death.
But a messenger of death
came nonetheless
to take him away
to the afterlife.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[OLD MAN]
So Black Reaper from the East...
[MARQUIS]
Tell me, whose soul is it
you plan to spirit away
from this land tonight?
Who are you, really?
[MARQUIS] I must confess,
I did assume my wife, Cordelia,
would've ridden in on that
train, yet she didn't appear.
But you haven't been a bad
consolation prize, Reaper.
Cordelia's your wife?
You alleviated my boredom
and helped kill some time.
It was fascinating meeting you
when we spoke on the train.
You're even more
sinister looking
than I imagined,
Mr. Kazuya Kujo.
Wait, I get it now.
You're Victorique's
father, aren't you?
You're Marquis Albert de Blois!
[gasps]
[MARQUIS]
You see, Reaper,
I really want to thank you.
You've brought about deaths
and cases for my Wolf cub.
Thanks to you, its intellect
has been well-honed,
and it is now on the cusp
of attaining true perfection.
It was born solely for my
benefit, you understand.
It is my most useful tool in all
of Europe, and I will use it.
All I ask is that you
keep refining it for me
until the time is right.
[rumbling]
[ALL gasp]
We have a problem!
It's the floodgate.
She's just a useful tool?
Is that really all you have to
say about your own daughter?!
Yes, you whelp,
it is my daughter.
And I will bloody well
do with it as I see fit,
for the good of the country.
It belongs to me, and me alone.
But you're her father first,
and that means you have a duty
to love and protect Victorique.
Above everything else!
Appealing to the heart?
You're so young, my boy.
[BOTH]
We should leave, My Lord!
I'm taking Victorique
with me, Blois.
I will never leave her at the
mercy of a monster like you.
How entertaining.
Very well, then.
But remember,
that school of yours
is as firmly under my power
and in my grasp as this place.
And it doesn't matter
where you may try to go
because I promise you,
no one will be able to
escape the coming storm.
Come on, hurry!
The seawater's breaking
through the floodgate!
We won't make it home
alive at this rate!
Where's the train?
[KAZUYA]
There you are!
Hey, are you okay?
Did you inhale some of
that smoke earlier?
--[VICTORIQUE groans]
--[gasps]
Just hang on to me.
And... ups-a-daisy.
[train whistles]
Look, it's the Masquerade!
Oh, thank goodness!
It's a true miracle!
[KAZUYA]
We have to go!
[VICTORIQUE]
Just leave me here, it's fine.
No. You know I won't!
You're wasting your breath.
I came here to get
you, Victorique!
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo...
There's just no point.
I don't even know
why I was born,
so why should I bother
trying to preserve my life?
[VICTORIQUE]
Stop it.
If you do this, then you won't--
You know, I met your
father earlier tonight.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Adults are selfish and
always do whatever they want.
But we're not like them
because we care for each other,
and I'm not leaving you.
[KAZUYA]
You can feel free to ponder
the meaning of life later.
I want us to go back
to school together.
That's the whole reason
I came to get you.
[VICTORIQUE]
I see it now, Kujo.
You've made my life better.
It's thanks to you
that I can even...
[VICTORIQUE]
I don't have to be alone.
I can know love.
I can be a girl who opens up,
rather than pushes away.
Kujo... Protect me.
[train whistles]
Promise you'll always
be there for me...
...from now on.
[KAZUYA]
I will.
[train whistles]
Little further! You can do it!
[KAZUYA yelps]
[yelps]
Guess that's it for
Beelzebub's Skull.
[VICTORIQUE] Also known
as the cursed fortress,
the Lord of the Flies.
But...
We survived passing
through its walls.
And it's all thanks
to you that we did.
Oh, right. I forgot.
For you.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
But this is...
Is this Mama's?
And she wanted me to
give you a message, too.
"Solve the mystery."
She said, "Show me that you
have the power to live."
And she also told me...
This mother still loves
and will forever love
her little daughter.
Even if you choose
not to cry out to me,
I will always come
running for you.
[VICTORIQUE cries]
[VICTORIQUE] "Show me that you
have the power to live."
Mama... I swear that I will.
[KAZUYA]
Victorique! Keep going! Fight!
[VICTORIQUE]
Could you please just be quiet?