[clock chimes]
[AVRIL]
A skeleton!
[KAZUYA gagging]
[WALLA: CROWD]
[AVRIL giggles]
Oh Kujo.
You were such a
'fraidy cat in there!
[KAZUYA]
Speak for yourself!
I was fine 'til you started
throttling me out of nowhere!
Silly girl.
[AVRIL]
True, true.
But I love a good mystery.
It was tops, wasn't it?
Honestly, I slept
through most of it.
Come to think of it, that story
seems really familiar to me.
A masked monster hiding away
in a tall, black fortress.
And I feel like I've seen
that clock tower before, too.
[BOYS] ♪ Until the hens
start to crow. ♪
♪ Until the fire
turns to snow. ♪
♪ They'll always
march together! ♪
♪ Even if it takes forever! ♪
♪ On and on
they went their way! ♪
♪ Trying to find
a place to stay! ♪
♪ Dee doo-da-doo! Da-doo! ♪
--♪ Doo! ♪
--[BOTH giggle]
[BOYS] ♪ March together all for
one and one, one for all! ♪
[laugh]
[KAZUYA humming]
Strange that it's the
last day of summer.
Uh-- That reminds me, Avril.
You ended your summer
vacation pretty early.
Was the Mediterranean
not what you were hoping
it would be after all?
[AVRIL gasps]
I thought you were
staying at your grandma's
till the last day.
Uh-- The plans weren't set.
How could I stay away?
You were here alone with
Victorique the whole time.
I couldn't stand it!
What was that?
[AVRIL]
I-It's nothing!
Don't mind me.
Okay.
Well then, thanks
for the movie,
but I should probably
get going now.
To where? The library?
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[gasps] Just...
forget about it.
--[KAZUYA yelps]
--Of course, that's it!
What is it?
I remember now!
Come on, let's go!
[KAZUYA]
Wait, where are we going?
[BOTH panting]
Avril, wait for me!
What's this about, anyway?
There, look at that!
Oh, wow!
[AVRIL]
See?
It's just like the movie, right?
[KAZUYA]
Yeah!
It's uncanny, really.
[AVRIL]
Maybe there's a curse here, too!
[KAZUYA]
No. that part can't be real.
[KAZUYA chuckles]
Darn, it's locked!
Looks that way.
Well, see ya.
No, wait!
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
Uh...
I mean...
Look! It's open now!
[KAZUYA]
Are you sure we should be here?
[AVRIL]
Really, Kujo.
I finally came back,
and now all you want to
do is go to that library.
Is Victorique
really that pretty?
I mean, I'm not too bad...
[KAZUYA]
Hm? You say something?
[AVRIL]
Mm-hm! I love adventure!
[KAZUYA sighs, groans]
[AVRIL] Maybe I don't
see myself clearly.
What if I'm wrong and
I'm not pretty at all?
Kujo might think
I'm the ugliest girl
in the world, for all I know.
Oh, that's so depressing!
[gasps]
--[screams]
--[KAZUYA gasps]
You okay?
Pardon me!
Maybe we should head
back, you think?
No, not yet!
[KAZUYA gasps]
[AVRIL gasps]
Because-- Well--
If it really is
like the movie,
then it just might have that
alchemist's room in it, too!
Let's go find it!
Avril, there's no way!
[gasps]
Or not!
[KAZUYA]
This can't be.
[AVRIL gasps]
I remember now!
It's the alchemist, Leviathan!
Of course! It's just like
the ghost story at school!
I haven't heard that story.
How does that one go?
Well, the way I know it is
there was a masked alchemist
that lived in these parts around
twenty or thirty years ago.
He was said to have built
his workshop in this tower.
He became a favorite
of the Queen's.
He even had some influence
in the political realm.
But the king didn't trust him.
He feared his power.
[AVRIL] Even when Leviathan
was shot with poison arrows,
he didn't die.
Instead, he simply disappeared.
He'd become immortal.
[AVRIL] If the rumors are true,
he wore a robe and mask
in order to hide the fact
that he never aged.
And ever since then,
they say a monster has
lived in this clock tower,
forever roaming these same
grounds night after night.
[screams]
Interesting. I guess somebody
must have heard that story
and thought it would make
a good motion picture.
[AVRIL]
Huh? That theory's boring!
What can I say? Sometimes
the truth isn't thrilling.
We did find the room
you were after, though.
Our work's done.
[AVRIL]
Wait a minute!
Why, is there more?
[footsteps]
Listen, what is that?
[footsteps continue]
[BOTH gasp]
[growling]
[BOTH scream]
[wailing]
I'm blinder than a
bat in this place,
so let's get out
of here right now!
[KAZUYA]
What's she doing here?
I've never seen Ms.
Cécile like that before.
You should know this area
is off limits to students!
If you get too close...
[roars]
Catch my drift?
[AVRIL]
She was really worked up!
So weird. Makes me think there
is something in that tower.
What do you think?
Kujo?
Where'd you go?
Kujo!
[AVRIL]
I guess he went to the library.
[groans]
Jerk! This was
supposed to be a date!
I asked him out to a movie!
What'd he think it was?
I picked my cutest dress, too.
And I let myself get
all excited about it.
Then he spent the
whole time sleeping!
Why are boys so stupid?!
[VICTORIQUE]
Oh, the monotony.
He's late again today.
That dolt.
He's well aware I'm in here
wasting away with boredom.
What on earth is
he doing out there?
That useless-- [whimpers]
[yelps]
[yelps, groans]
That hurt...
[gasps]
[VICTORIQUE] "To whomsoever
findest this treasured book
--someday."
--[LEVIATHAN] "...someday."
[BOTH] "These are the
writings of Leviathan, 1899."
Leviathan? As in the
legendary alchemist?
This is his book, then?
What kind of an idiot
writes a pop-up memoir?
[LEVIATHAN]
I am an alchemist.
I have mastered
the mystical forces
that can create
something from nothing.
[LEVIATHAN] Thou that hast
found this book in the future.
Art thou amazed?
[VICTORIQUE]
My, what an unpleasant man.
[LEVIATHAN]
To thee in the future:
Art thou a man?
A woman?
An adult?
A child?
It mattereth not.
For thou shalt never
solve my riddle.
Doth that frustrate thee?
What? You're an insolent wretch!
There's no problem in
the world I can't solve!
[LEVIATHAN]
I am the Fool.
Thou must become the Fool's
spokesman and expose my secret.
Don't order me around!
The impudence!
[VICTORIQUE]
Hmph.
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
Good, there you are!
I just heard the most
interesting story.
You'll love it!
I assume that you
heard this story
when someone took
you to the movies?
Uh-- But how'd you know that?
I can clearly see the ticket
stub in your jacket pocket.
The title suggests you didn't
choose the film yourself.
Right, again!
Avril invited me to go with her.
I see.
And you went.
Anyway, listen!
So, there's this alchemist
called Levia... than...
Are you... okay?
[KAZUYA]
Then, I started feeling dizzy
and I got really disoriented.
There are apparently rumors that
Leviathan is still alive, too.
Think it could be true?
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
First, alchemists are those
who claim to have perfected
the art of turning one
substance into another.
Most pursue gold,
eternal life,
or homunculi--
artificial life.
They use an object most
commonly referred to
as the Philosopher's Stone.
That's how they achieve this.
They use a stone?
That's right, and all truly
skilled alchemists possess one.
It's said to be red.
A deep, beautiful red,
like a pomegranate aril
or the ripest cherry.
[KAZUYA]
Wow...
[VICTORIQUE]
But when it comes down to it,
alchemy is nothing but a fraud.
A racket.
And the people who
make a lot of noise
about believing it
wholeheartedly...
...are idiots!
End of story!
[KAZUYA]
I guess... that's that.
[SOPHIE]
It's a new semester!
This'll start it
on the right foot!
Right. Thanks!
By the way...
Who's the handsome fella
you were with yesterday?
A good friend of mine
saw you in town together.
She said she saw an Oriental
man with dark eyes and hair,
walking alongside a
redheaded gentleman.
An Oriental man and a redhead?
Come on now, who is he?
I have to know!
Sorry. But it couldn't
have been me.
[SOPHIE gasps]
I was with another classmate
all day yesterday.
You were?
Phooey!
And here I thought you might
actually be able to introduce me
to a promising new suitor.
I would if I could.
[KAZUYA] I thought I was
the only Asian here...
[gasps]
Wait. That looks like--
The very man!
[gasps]
[groaning]
[KAZUYA]
What happened?
It's-- It's the alchemist.
Leviathan... He... [groans]
[footsteps]
Who is that?
Oh, Kujo. Good morning to you.
Uh-- Good morning to you, too.
Uh... Beg your pardon, sir,
but how to do you know me?
[gasps, sighs]
For the love of...
Do you know me now?
[BOTH gasp]
[KAZUYA]
Oh, Inspector!
Sorry, I should've
known by your suit!
Your, uh, hair...
It's so different!
It looks so ordinary now.
I had to leave the house
too quickly to style
it this morning.
It... is a process.
Hmph.
It's just so silky...
[BLOIS]
Lay off, would you?
Where's the crime scene?
[gasps] The machinery room,
off the second floor.
Come, show me the way.
[sighs] As fragrant
as spring flowers!
[BLOIS]
Enough about my hair!
Last night...
It was rumored that two
outsiders came to the village.
One was from the Far East.
And the other one had red hair.
This is obviously the
one from the Orient.
The redheaded man is at the inn.
One of my lieutenants is
bringing him here as we speak.
[KAZUYA panting]
Victorique!
[gasps]
[VICTORIQUE grunting]
[KAZUYA]
Ow! That... hurt!
You're late again.
Well, I'm sorry.
What do you need, now?
Uh-- Right!
Here's what happening.
[VICTORIQUE]
A clock tower.
A finger with a purple bruise.
And an alchemist.
Where's the inspector?
I'm surprised he
isn't here already.
[VICTORIQUE]
That stupid man.
Who's stupid? Your brother?
Not me, I hope.
Then, who?
I mean Leviathan!
You see...
I received a direct
challenge from that fraud.
I will solve Leviathan's riddle.
And I will put an end
to these murders.
Wait. What are you saying?
Do you honestly think
today's murder was
the work of an alchemist
who, by all accounts,
died over twenty years ago?
[VICTORIQUE] The riddle is,
indeed, difficult.
But I have my wellspring of
wisdom, which never fails.
I will reconstruct the fragments
of the chaos he left behind.
I will become the official
spokesman for the Fool!
In other words, you'll
solve the case, right?
Hey, where are you going?
[VICTORIQUE]
The lower world.
[KAZUYA]
No way.
You're going outside?
Wait for me.
I'll come with you!
[VICTORIQUE] You can use
the stairs, like always.
[KAZUYA] I can't even use the
lift if we're on it together?
[VICTORIQUE]
Don't you know?
Seeing you gasp for breath...
Watching your thighs
turn to noodles...
Being forced to drag yourself up
and down those stairs every day,
just so you can visit
dear little old me...
[gulps]
It's my favorite thing!
[KAZUYA]
You've gotta be kidding me!
[groans]
Crazy girl...
I wonder, is this
what she was reading?
[gasps] What the?!
"For thou shalt never
solve my riddle.
Doth that frustrate thee?"
Oh, boy. I bet that's
what got her mad.
[KAZUYA]
"It is the winter of 1899."
[KAZUYA, LEVIATHAN]
"At this moment,
which marks the end
of the century.
I, Leviathan, confess."
[LEVIATHAN] Long ago,
I was nothing more
than a nameless vagabond.
During my travels, I happened to
acquire a certain precious item:
The Philosopher's Stone.
Its power bestowed upon me
the gift of eternal life.
A timeless existence.
[LEVIATHAN]
In the winter of 1897,
on nothing more than a whim,
I abandoned my roving lifestyle.
[LEVIATHAN] What did I create
with the Philosopher's Stone?
Gold, of course.
An abundance of it.
My name became widely known
throughout the country.
And then...
The beautiful queen
of Saubure, Coco Rose,
honored me with an invitation
to the royal palace.
But someone else had plans.
The man's name
was Baron Musgrave.
He was a servant of the
King, Rupert de Giret.
I think you're a fraud.
[LEVIATHAN]
No more than thou art.
[MUSGRAVE growls]
[IAN laughs]
[IAN]
My father and the King
both think you're a
liar and an impostor.
Hurry up, men! Find it, now!
The Queen is ignorant
to the ways of the world,
so they fear she's
being deceived by you.
[LEVIATHAN]
Dost thou think so, as well?
[LEVIATHAN] Musgrave's son, Ian,
had the kind of faith in me,
and in alchemy,
that can only belong
to the wide-eyed
innocents of this world.
The baron searched every
corner of my laboratory,
and he confirmed that
there was no gold.
Then he turned to me, and said:
You won't leave this place
until you produce gold.
No matter how many
years it takes!
[LEVIATHAN]
Three days will be enough.
[MUSGRAVE, GUARDS gasp]
[LEVIATHAN]
And three days later...
Impossible! How can this be?
There are no other ways
out of this room!
The building was surrounded.
You charlatan!
Tell me! How did you do it?
[LEVIATHAN]
I wish to see the Queen.
[MUSGRAVE gasps]
[LEVIATHAN]
I want only to prove my troth.
Your Majesties...
As evidence of my
unending loyalty to you,
and to prove that
I am what I claim,
I shall take this
colorless white rose
and transform it to blue,
as a blessing on your union.
There's no such thing
as a blue rose!
His claim is a preposterous lie!
[LEVIATHAN] There is nothing
that alchemy cannot do.
--It can't be!
--[CROWD gasps]
[RUPERT gasps]
[ROSE] I'm in such awe,
Dear Alchemist!
[LEVIATHAN]
For the sake of the country,
I continued to produce gold.
[LEVIATHAN] I promised the Queen
eternal youth and beauty.
[LEVIATHAN] The King
began to seek my opinion
on matters of state.
And I gave them.
[LEVIATHAN]
Then...
[RUPERT]
Who are you, really?
What are you after?
What exactly is it
that you're hiding?
Show me what's under your mask!
[LEVIATHAN] If the mask comes
off, it is the end of me.
[LEVIATHAN]
Winter, 1899.
I can no longer bear
the weight of my sin.
That great sin was not
my deception of the King.
[LEVIATHAN]
Nor was it my conscious
manipulation of the Queen.
It was unimaginably worse.
That innocent soul...
Ian...
[LEVIATHAN]
I killed him.
To thee in the future:
Art thou a man?
A woman?
An adult?
A child?
It mattereth not.
Save me.
I cannot bear the
weight of my sin.
If the time of my
death doth come,
my soul shall linger
at the clock tower
where Ian died for eternity.
And I shall continue to kill.
I will forever wander
this earthly realm...
...as a vile murderer.
[gasps]
[BLOIS]
Where were you this morning?
[ROSCOE]
I was at the inn all day.
I'm sure the innkeeper
will vouch for me.
For what did you
come to this village?
[ROSCOE] Wong, the man
who brought me here,
did seem to have
some ulterior motive,
but I don't know what it was.
And your motive, sir?
[ROSCOE chuckles]
I'm here looking for a monster.
The Monstre Charmant.
[VICTORIQUE]
He's so stupid.
Taking the side of
that farting newt...
[VICTORIQUE]
You... You farting reaper!
[KAZUYA]
Um... Farting?