--[buzzing]
--[gasps]
[screaming]
There are wounded here! Stop!
[NUN A groans]
[gasps]
[NUN A]
Curse you...
Curse you.
Curse you! Curse you!
Curse you all!
[NUNS]
Curse you. Curse you. Curse you!
[NUNS gasp]
[PILOT A gasps]
[GUNNER gasps]
[PILOT B screams]
[NUNS chuckling]
[giggles]
[KAZUYA]
"Dear Kazuya.
As I write this,
it's been six months
since you left for Saubure.
We just received a report
card from your school.
Well done.
According to it,
your grades have been
excellent in every subject."
Sounds like they're
proud of you!
"But never forget, our
future is on your shoulders.
Always push yourself
to greater heights
and do not grow conceited."
Whoa... Your father
sounds really strict.
[KAZUYA]
Yeah...
[AVRIL] What do you think
you'd do if you went back home?
Become a soldier like your
father and big brother?
[KAZUYA]
I guess.
I mean, it's what
I've been told to do
ever since I was a little kid.
[KAZUYA]
But...
Uh-- So, what about you?
I think you mentioned
adventuring before?
Yup, like my grandfather did!
I want to travel the world
and become famous for it!
That's wonderful.
[AVRIL giggles]
I spy some sweets!
[chuckles]
[KAZUYA]
Hmm...
Maybe I should go
with the pear tarts?
Don't look so serious.
They're just pastries.
Well, Victorique's been
whining about sweets lately.
If I disappoint her, I'll
get full punishment again.
What does that mean?
Hi, Victorique!
I brought some presents.
Where are you?
[KAZUYA]
Hey!
Victorique!
Are you here?
[gasps]
It's her pipe.
[footsteps]
[KAZUYA panting]
[KAZUYA]
She's not here, either.
Or here.
[footsteps]
Couldn't be...
[CÉCILE]
Hm? Hi, Kujo.
I can't find
Victorique anywhere!
I know.
Inspector Blois came
here last night
with some of his
father's men in tow.
[gasps] The Marquis did this?
She's moving... to some
distant convent, I think.
[KAZUYA]
But... why so suddenly?
[CÉCILE]
I wish I knew.
Sorry, but before
they took her away,
Victorique wrote this for you.
[KAZUYA gasps]
She was so brave.
She wouldn't leave until she
had the chance to write it.
[CÉCILE]
But despite her courage,
I could still see tears
welling up in her eyes.
Once she had finished, she left
of her own accord with no fuss.
[cries]
[blows nose]
Victorique...
[BLOIS]
I did as you asked, Father.
But... the move still
feels premature.
[MARQUIS]
Do you feel sympathy for it?
The faint of heart cannot
arrive at the truth,
as I have told you
many times over.
[BLOIS stammers]
No, sir. I was only trying to--
[MARQUIS]
Despite the risk it represents,
we need it if we're to
accomplish our goals.
[VICTORIQUE coughs]
[TEACHER] Now, can anyone
solve this problem?
[KAZUYA]
Yes.
Very good. You may
return to your seat.
The next problem's
a little trickier. Uh...
[STUDENT A]
Is he okay?
Hey!
What, are you deaf?
I said go back to your seat!
He's not even listening.
[AVRIL]
I see.
Victorique's gone.
[KAZUYA] Yeah. I went
by the police station,
but Inspector Blois
wasn't there.
I'm sure it will all work out.
I mean, can you imagine
Victorique in a convent?
No way that's going to last.
She'll escape and
come right back
to eating sweets
and solving crimes.
Besides, she's with her father,
so I doubt she'll be in danger.
Actually, that's a big
part of why I'm worried.
[gasps]
I'm sorry...
No...
I'm the one that's sorry.
Thanks, Avril.
I'll see you later.
Sure, we'll talk tomorrow.
Poor Kujo...
[scoffs] At a time like this,
she still manages
to get a jab in.
If she was on the
verge of tears,
she could've asked for help.
But, that's her...
Where have you gone, Victorique?
[VICTORIQUE]
Do you think a day will come
when you won't be
able to find me?
[KAZUYA gasps]
How do I find you?
Idiot.
[footsteps]
[KAZUYA grumbling]
This.
[KAZUYA]
That should do it.
[BLOIS]
Wrong.
That pannier only goes with
the frilly dress, there.
[KAZUYA]
Inspector!
Are you really going to
search for the Wolf cub
without a single lead?
I thought you were a
smarter squirrel than that.
Then tell me where
she's been taken!
The little Gray Wolf's life
has begun to wane as of late.
Since the move, it won't eat
anything, won't read anything,
and hasn't let
loose a single howl.
[gasps]
[BLOIS] I realized it may
be an abnormal creature
that can only survive
in certain conditions.
I thought if I picked up
some of its belongings,
its health might take
a turn for the better.
Fortunately,
the full moon is coming.
With this, even you
could get in there.
In where?
Beelzebub's Skull, of course.
The little Gray Wolf is being
held deep within its walls.
[gasps]
[CÉCILE]
Uh... Ahem!
Apparently, Mr. Kujo
will be taking time off
for personal reasons.
He probably caused
another murder.
Yeah. I, for one,
hope he stays gone.
Uh, please, listen.
I'll bet my lunch
he was kidnapped.
[BLOIS]
On the coast of Lithuania,
there's a convent,
far from any civilization
that's been around
since the Middle Ages.
That is known as
Beelzebub's Skull.
Lithuania has been an ally of
Saubure for quite a while now.
It was the perfect place
for my father, the Marquis,
to keep the Gray Wolf
quiet and out of sight.
[KAZUYA]
Why go so far?
To draw out a certain
person for a certain reason.
That's all I can
say on the matter.
The Gray Wolf was our only bait,
so we used her, simple as that.
It's still not right.
Look, Kujo.
Having it run freely wherever
it pleases is a problem for us.
But letting it die would
cause even more trouble.
Either way, Father
doesn't seem to care.
But if things keep following
this course, then--
[KAZUYA]
I understand.
I'll go to see her, myself.
But not for you or for
the Marquis de Blois.
Because Victorique is my...
...closest friend.
[train whistles]
[bell ringing]
[CONDUCTOR] Those boarding the
Old Masquerade, please hurry!
We'll be leaving
the station shortly!
I'll be joining you,
if you don't mind.
My, you don't see
Orientals that often.
Could it be you're going to
Beelzebub's Skull as well?
Yes, sir.
You must be a smooth operator,
securing an invitation to the
Phantasmagoria at your age.
[KAZUYA]
I'm sorry?
You don't know?
It's this.
Once a month,
during the full moon,
the convent holds a
secret party for VIPs.
It's called...
The "Phantasmagoria"?
[HUNT]
Smart lad!
We'll call it a type of "show."
Ghosts flying all around you.
Men vanishing into
mysterious boxes.
Practitioners of old magic
gather from all over Europe.
It's extremely
antiquated entertainment
for the 20th century,
but the rumors suggest
that the ones running the show
are all women of great beauty.
Isn't that right, good sir?
You would know.
[OLD MAN]
Imbecile! Hold your tongue.
[HUNT gasps]
I'm only here... to pay
a visit to my daughter.
Oh, I see!
Then, she must be
one of the nuns
if you're willing
to travel so far.
[OLD MAN]
Black hair.
Black eyes.
You're the spitting
image of the Reaper
from the legends, young man.
[KAZUYA]
Uh...
[HUNT]
Yes, indeed.
The convent was built during
the spread of the Black Death
back in the Middle Ages.
The people of the time likened
the disease to a Black Reaper.
Please, don't compare
me with that legend.
I have enough people calling
me the "Black Reaper"
back at the Academy.
It's... trying.
--[OLD MAN] Hmph.
--[laughs]
What's your name, my boy?
[KAZUYA]
Kazuya Kujo.
I'm Simon Hunt.
I work for one of the foremost
clockmakers back in Saubreme.
If you ever need a quality
time piece, call me.
I'll give you a discount.
Uh-huh... I'll do that.
Come on.
Why can't I get any sleep?
[door clicks]
[gasps] That's Brian Roscoe!
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
That's weird.
I could have sworn
he came in here.
[KAZUYA]
The chess automaton.
No doubt about it, Brian's
on this train for sure.
What a bizarre face.
[yelps, gasps]
What the hell?
Cogs.
[KAZUYA]
Here, too.
So, what made it move
out of nowhere like that?
Whatever the reason may be,
if Brian's on this train...
[KAZUYA]
Then I'm positive...
We're heading for
you, Victorique.
Just hold on a little longer.
[KAZUYA] I looked all over, but
Brian vanished into thin air.
[HUNT] "The Mystery of Mary
Who Caused the Fall"?
It was about a decade ago,
just before the end of the
Great War, as a matter of fact.
The convent at Beelzebub's
Skull was attacked
by a squadron of
German fighters.
So I've heard.
Apparently, a giant
statue of Saint Mary
appeared in the sky
and destroyed them all.
But there are more
than a few rumors that
Saubure's Academy of Sciences
was engaging in some
construction there.
Isn't that a strange
coincidence?
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
The Academy?
They're the ones working against
the Marquis de Blois's
Ministry of the Occult.
That's nonsense.
Science could only dream
of explaining such a thing.
If you say so, my dear lady.
[chuckles]
Well. Hmph.
[train whistles]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
I don't care.
I've come this far.
No matter what I find out
there, I will save you.
I promise.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Is that Beelzebub's Skull?
[HUNT]
Indeed.
Well, Mr. Kujo?
Do you see why it's named
after the Lord of the Flies?
[KAZUYA] Yeah. It looks
just like a fly's head.
[CONDUCTOR]
Safe and happy travels to all!
This is the train's last
stop of the evening.
We'll be back tomorrow
morning at first light,
so unless you're planning
to join the convent,
do not be late.
See the massive flood
gate over there?
It's the only thing protecting
Beelzebub's Skull
from becoming a part
of the ocean floor.
If it were to open during
high tide tonight...
At last...
I... will finally
see my daughter again.
[CROWD murmuring]
Oh! Sorry!
By the way, I'm here to pick
up a close friend of mine.
Her name is Victorique,
and she's the daughter of
Marquis Albert de Blois.
Would you know where she may be?
Welcome to a night of magic!
Grab a glass and
enjoy the banquet!
[KAZUYA]
Uh...
[CROWD cheering]
[squeals]
[BEAUTY A]
What a cutie.
--What is this?
--[BEAUTY B] Drink with us!
[scoffs]
It's all changed so much.
[ROSCOE] The last time
I came here was 1914,
in the middle of the Great War.
[ROGER]
So you're Brian Roscoe?
Yes.
Welcome, sir.
I'm Jupiter Roger,
the Chairman of the Saubure
Academy of Sciences.
It's a pleasure.
[ROGER] As far as our
organization is concerned,
we're not just fighting
against enemy countries,
but the Ministry of
the Occult, as well.
For the sake of our
country's advancement,
we're aggressively trying
to replace the old ways
with the superior
power of science.
But the Ministry
has other plans.
Let me guess, they're opposing
this new age you're after
using superstitions
and political power.
Yes, as a Gray Wolf, you
should know all about that.
So, what's the Ministry to you?
They're my enemy. Same as you.
Albert de Blois must answer
for the sins he's committed.
[ROGER]
Mm.
And that's why I want
you to work with me.
We'd like to incorporate
sleight of hand into
the projects we
have going on here.
[ROSCOE]
Excellent.
Fortunately, I have a tool that
will suit your needs perfectly.
I, Brian Roscoe, am
about to wage war.
If anything, it'll be
a hell of a show.
[ROSCOE] But, of course, Roger
wanted far more than that.
The thing his academy
was truly after...
...was the box.
The secret memento box I brought
out of the nameless village.
Its recovery is paramount.
We can't afford to falter
even if it would put the
frail Wolf cub in danger.
What a pain.
I can barely see anything.
The crowd is too big.
[GUEST A]
It's starting!
Let the Phantasmagoria begin!
The Phantasmagoria!
Yes, how exciting.
[hiccups]
[laughs nervously]
[gasps]
--[DRUNK MAN groans]
--[KAZUYA] Victorique!
[panting]
[KAZUYA gasps]
Wait, Victorique!
I've come to get you!
Why are you running?
Why isn't she stopping?
[panting]
[KAZUYA]
It's not an illusion.
It has to be her!
[KAZUYA panting]
Dead end.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[coughs]
I'm coming in.
Victorique?
That's you, isn't it?
[KAZUYA]
Hey, it's me.
[VICTORIQUE coughs]
You're all right now.
I came to get you.
C'mon, let's get out of here.
[VICTORIQUE sneezes]
Oh no, did you catch a cold?
Well, we can take care of that.
Here, I brought your luggage.
[VICTORIQUE]
You're late.
[KAZUYA]
I know. I'm sorry.
--I tried--
--[VICTORIQUE] Idiot! Die!
Seriously? Do you know how far
I had to travel to save--
No excuses!
[VICTORIQUE sobs]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Hey...
I still found you, didn't I?
[VICTORIQUE sneezes]
[VICTORIQUE] Kujo, hand me
the gooseberry-colored dress.
Uh...
This one?
[VICTORIQUE]
No! That's raspberry.
How'd you manage to find me
if you can't even
tell colors apart?
[KAZUYA]
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
[VICTORIQUE]
Really, men are so helpless.
Not only are you stupid,
you're also deficient in taste.
[laughs] I guess you're already
back to your old self, huh?
But why did you run away
from me a moment ago?
[VICTORIQUE]
What?
Uh, you're kidding, right?
I saw you in the garden.
I followed you all the way here.
You're being serious,
aren't you?
I've been in here
the whole time.
Whoever you saw down
there, it wasn't me.
[KAZUYA]
Then... Who?
It must have been Cordelia.
You saw my mother.
[gasps]
Good. All the players
are present.
Now to see if the full moon
drives them all to lunacy.
The night of magic...
...is about to begin.
[KAZUYA]
I finally found you, Victorique.
[VICTORIQUE]
Yes. I've been longing for you.
At last, we're together again...
...my delicious, flakey,
cream-filled pastries.
[KAZUYA]
Sweets?!