This place is...
[BLOIS]
That's right.
Now I see.
That's why you
brought me here...
...to the Phantom.
[footsteps]
[KAZUYA panting]
Is Sophie in there?
It's so big!
--[thumping]
--[PORTER A] What the hell?!
[PORTER B]
What is it?
[PORTER A] This... trunk
has a mind of its own!
[PORTERS scream]
[sighs] I'm alive!
[KAZUYA]
Miss Cécile!
[CÉCILE gasps]
Mr. Kujo!
Why were you in that trunk?
What's going on?
--Do you need any help?
--[CÉCILE] She's in trouble!
As a teacher,
I can't just stand by
while a student's in jeopardy!
This was my drastic
infiltration plan!
Please, calm down.
What student are
you talking about?
Who do you think?!
Victorique, you big dummy!
[CÉCILE]
Her father called her out again.
She's inside!
[CÉCILE grunting]
[VICTORIQUE] You should
stay out here, Cécile.
Don't get any closer
to this, understand?
[CÉCILE]
She sounded so different.
I know she's in danger;
I can feel it.
But... I was stuck in here,
so I couldn't do
anything to help--
[gasps]
Wait! Kujo, come back!
Thank you, Madam.
Enjoy the performance.
[KAZUYA]
Excuse me!
Huh?
Get out of my way!
[TICKET COLLECTORS gasp]
What's his problem?
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
Where are you?
[KAZUYA]
Victorique...
Don't you worry.
[KAZUYA]
No matter where you are...
[KAZUYA] No matter what
storm might come...
...I will find you!
[GINGER gasps]
[KAZUYA]
I promise!
[footsteps]
[doors rattle]
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
I found you!
[BLOIS]
Kujo! What?!
Why are you here?
You really did.
You found me.
You really did!
[KAZUYA]
I told you!
I always will.
Don't you forget it!
Stop there.
Come no further.
[gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
[TICKET COLLECTOR A]
There he is!
Don't, Victorique!
Wait! Please!
[TICKET COLLECTOR B]
Quick! Grab him!
Let go of me!
You don't understand!
Wait! Victorique!
[TICKET COLLECTOR B]
Stop struggling!
[KAZUYA]
Victorique! What are you doing?
[gasps]
Victorique!
[doors shut]
[TICKET COLLECTOR B]
Come on!
[KAZUYA]
Get off of me!
Please! I beg you!
[TICKET COLLECTOR B]
Shut up!
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo...
[footsteps]
[VICTORIQUE]
Take me to him already.
Let's go.
Marquis Albert de Blois
isn't going to wait forever.
[MARQUIS]
At last, welcome, my daughter.
After all of these years,
it's time for your power
to be of use to me.
I've used it a lot lately.
But something still puzzles me.
Why is the Ministry of
the Occult only now trying
to solve Coco Rose's murder?
have a feeling you already
know who the culprit is.
But you haven't been able
to track down solid proof.
That's your current goal.
Find it and exploit the culprit.
Doing so will allow you
to achieve an even greater
position and authority.
[VICTORIQUE] Which means
whoever in this country
has that much influence
and power...
...is the murderer.
They're the ones who
killed Coco Rose.
[MARQUIS]
Interesting.
As expected of my
beloved Gray Wolf,
your intuition is
as sharp as a knife.
[BLOIS]
The Coco Rose Murder.
It was Spring of 1914.
Just before the start
of the Great War.
A messenger came from France for
an audience with Queen Coco.
At the time, she was living
in the country house,
but the King invited her to
the palace that evening.
[BLOIS]
And then...
[BLOIS] The queen was
found dead in her room.
Her head severed and missing.
[BLOIS] No one had gone
in or out of her room
since her arrival.
Except for one person--
Her husband, the King.
But, of course, he didn't have
anything suspicious with him.
He couldn't have
been the culprit...
...because something happened
at the country house
at that same time.
[NOBLES gasp]
[BLOIS] And someone from
the Academy of Sciences
was among the witnesses.
[BLOIS] After that,
the case just stopped.
[KAZUYA] Why do they need
Victorique to solve the case?
[BLOIS]
I'm honestly not sure.
But...
[KAZUYA]
What is it?
[BLOIS]
If it can't solve the case,
it will never go back
to the Academy with you.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Why in the hell not?!
That's what my
father has decreed.
[KAZUYA]
No way!
[BLOIS]
Calm down.
There hasn't been a case that
the Wolf cub couldn't solve.
I wouldn't worry so
much if I were you.
[KAZUYA]
The fragments.
Does she have all the
fragments of chaos?
[BLOIS] Huh? She's been
provided newspaper articles,
and the case file from the time.
She should have
everything she needs.
You're wrong!
It won't be enough.
[BLOIS gasps]
[KAZUYA] Victorique probably
knows everything you could learn
from normal documentation.
Then what do you suggest we do?
[KAZUYA]
I'll go gather them.
You'll what?
[KAZUYA]
I'm the only one who can.
I'll bring Victorique
the fragments she needs.
I swear it.
From now on,
I'm fighting, too.
I won't stand by while
Victorique is taking
this on alone.
[KAZUYA]
Be patient.
I'm coming!
[KAZUYA gasps]
Is that Victorique?
[GINGER] Cordelia was
beautiful, wasn't she?
Who was what now?
That's Cordelia Gallo.
[KAZUYA] Then the woman
in this picture...
...is Victorique's mother.
Hard to believe it's
been sixteen years
since I last saw her.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[GINGER]
She was one of our best dancers.
Then, she simply
vanished without a trace.
[KAZUYA]
I see.
This is where her mom worked.
[KAZUYA] And poor Victorique
is stuck here now.
Actually... you're
not the first person
to notice this picture today.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[GINGER]
There was a girl earlier.
She looked a great deal
like Cordelia, in fact.
But it couldn't have
been her, right?
[KAZUYA]
Excuse me.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Hold on.
What's a picture of Queen
Coco Rose doing here?
[GINGER]
It's not her.
That's Nicole Lulu, a dancer.
But she was a dead
ringer for the Queen.
So much so that the regulars
starting calling her
"the Blue Rose of
Downtown" and all.
The Blue Rose, huh.
She must have been popular.
[GINGER] Oh, they
practically worshiped her.
And she never lost
her cheery demeanor.
But, like Cordelia,
she suddenly vanished.
[CORDELIA humming]
[humming continues]
[MAN A] Quit wasting time and
solve the mystery, Wolf cub!
[VICTORIQUE]
I can't.
I don't have enough
fragments, you dolt.
[MAN A] You have all
the information you need!
[MAN B]
I thought Gray Wolves
were supposed to
know everything.
[VICTORIQUE] Only if I
have all the fragments.
I don't. Therefore, you're
the ones wasting time.
What are you doing?!
[LANDLORD]
A private secretary?
[KAZUYA]
Yes, sir. Was one hired in 1900?
I know that would have been
over twenty years ago, but--
[LANDLORD]
Yes, strange one, that.
I remember it quite clearly.
[KAZUYA, CÉCILE gasp]
[LANDLORD] The only requirements
were blonde hair and blue eyes.
Those that qualified were
measured from head to toe.
And after the interviews were
over, they all moved out.
Something wasn't quite right
about the men
conducting the thing.
[CÉCILE]
So, let me get this straight.
The dancer, Nicole Lulu, goes to
that bizarre secretary interview
and then promptly
disappears without a trace?
[KAZUYA] Yeah, it's
definitely suspicious.
We're on the right trail, we
just need to keep searching.
Yes! For Victorique's sake,
we both must soldier on!
So, uh, you really think
she's connected to this?
Miss Downtown Blue
Rose or whatever?
Uh--
Uh... No... I'm just following
a hunch is all, a gut feeling.
Anyway, we should
get going, huh?
Now that you mention it.
I saw her in a horse-drawn
carriage this one time.
Huh?
Uh...
[GENTLEMAN] I guess it
was about ten years ago.
She had just left the
stage for a new life.
I heard she'd become the
mistress of some rich fellow,
like a noble, and moved
out to the country.
Yes, I heard the same thing.
[OLD WOMAN B]
What? Well...
Thinking back on it, I'd say
it was around ten years
after Nicole disappeared.
She answered the secretary ad,
then became a noble's mistress?
[CÉCILE]
Sorry, Kujo!
Thanks for waiting!
[KAZUYA]
You went shopping?!
Well, I did come all
the way down here!
Besides, if I didn't get
a souvenir for Sophie,
she'd wring my neck.
For... Sophie?
You mean from school?
Yes, we come shopping
together all the time!
She'll probably be angry
when she finds out
I came here by myself,
but what can you do?
So you don't know?
Sophie's actually in
Saubreme right now.
[CÉCILE]
Huh?
Yeah. She brought me here
on her bike earlier today.
She said she was going to
see the big Coco Rose play.
Huh?! Why didn't
she invite me, huh?
Why would she abandon her
best friend of ten years
to go with you? Tell me!
You've been friend
for ten years?
That's great!
How'd you two meet?
Not telling you!
[KAZUYA gasps]
I hate you, Kujo!
Don't talk to me again!
Oh, come on.
--Don't be like that.
--And I hate Sophie even more!
That traitor!
[SOPHIE sneezes, groans]
I better not be catching a cold.
Aah... Oh, well.
As long as I get to see
Coco, it's worth it!
[BAKER]
Nicole Lulu?
I heard you were a fan and
thought you could help us.
I was. And my heart's
still broken,
even after all of these years.
I can't believe she's dead.
[BOTH gasp]
[BAKER gasps]
Wow, you two really
are clueless.
Nicole's long dead.
[KAZUYA]
He's right.
[CÉCILE]
It says she passed away in 1900!
[KAZUYA]
Can't be.
That's the year she was
supposed to have gone missing.
Right after they recruited
for a private secretary.
You're right!
And those women said they
saw her ten years after that!
[bell ringing]
[VICTORIQUE groaning]
[BLOIS]
Put an end to this, Father.
Nothing good is coming of it.
[MARQUIS]
Oh, ye of little faith.
Watch your sister
carefully, Grévil.
Her true power will
leave you in awe.
[phone clicks]
[BLOIS]
Wait, Father! Listen to me!
[VICTORIQUE chuckles]
[BLOIS gasps]
[VICTORIQUE] They've employed
a blend of specific herbs
that hone the senses.
The monotonous ringing and
the flicker of the candle light
do little more than enhance
the effects of the smoke.
There's nothing
occult about this.
In the end... even our
father must rely on science.
[CÉCILE]
The tickets are sold out,
and there are guards everywhere.
How are we supposed
to get inside, Kujo?
Inspector Blois should be
coming any minute now.
[MAN A]
Who's the culprit?
[MAN B]
Solve the mystery, Gray Wolf!
[MAN D] No one is allowed
to leave this room
until the ritual is complete.
[BLOIS grunts, growls]
Think you've been had.
[gasps]
Come on, Miss Cécile! This way!
[CÉCILE gasps]
Kujo, wait! Where are you going?
[yelps]
[VICTORIQUE groaning]
[MAN A]
Cooperate! Solve the mystery!
[MAN B]
Hurry!
[MAN C]
Who is the murderer?
[MAN D]
How did they kill Coco Rose?
We know you have the power!
[MAN A]
Stop wasting our time!
[MAN B]
Use your talents, Gray Wolf.
[MAN C]
Solve it! Solve it and it ends!
[BLOIS grunts]
[KAZUYA grunts]
[ROSCOE]
What's wrong?
What happened to all
that self-confidence
you showed me before...
...little boy?
Why are you here--
[MAN B]
Stop being stubborn!
[MAN C]
Solve the mystery!
[BLOIS]
Leave her alone--
[MAN B]
What's going on?
[MAN A]
Get the lights! Hurry!
[gasps]
Brian Roscoe...
[GUARD groans]
[ROSCOE]
Hurry up.
The cub is through
the door back there.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Thanks!
Victorique! Victorique!
Victorique!
[BLOIS gasps]
Kujo!
That man...
How can you be in here?!
[KAZUYA gasps]
Victorique!
Are you okay?
Answer me!
Victorique!
[VICTORIQUE groans]
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo?
I'm so glad.
You're okay...
You're okay.
Thank goodness.
You don't understand!
This case is too--
[KAZUYA]
I know!
Believe me, I know.
You didn't want me
to get involved.
That's why...
You...
...left me.
You had to.
[KAZUYA]
But I did get involved.
And that's okay.
I'm your friend and
a busybody, remember?
So you'll always have...
You'll always have someone
who will get involved for you.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Kujo...
[MAN A] The sacred
ritual's been disturbed!
[MAN B]
Throw that boy out of here!
[BLOIS]
Stop right there!
Kujo.
Huh?
[VICTORIQUE] We can continue
to struggle against this.
But nothing we do will free
me from my father's curse.
Hold on.
Solve the mystery.
[gasps]
Solve the mystery...
...in order to survive.
[CODELIA, VICTORIQUE]
I'll show them my power.
[grunting]
[VICTORIQUE]
I'll solve it!
That's what you want, right?
The mystery of Coco Rose's
murder won't stay that way.
[MARQUIS] To the beautiful
Wolf mother and her cub...
...I give this blessing.
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo...
What made you, of all people,
think to investigate
Nicole Lulu's case?
[KAZUYA gasps]
Not sure, really.
Probably...
...because I thought the
story would make you happy.
I'll admit, for a dull honor
student, that was good thinking.
Well done.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[footsteps]
[BLOIS] I received my
father's permission.
Now then... Where are we going?
[VICTORIQUE]
The graveyard.
The what?
You heard what I said.
We're digging up
Nicole Lulu's grave.
[KAZUYA]
The curtain will finally go up
on Coco Rose's last performance.
[VICTORIQUE]
Coco, I'll lay a special bouquet
upon the story of your life...
...made with the flowers
of falsehood and truth...
...that can only
bloom within chaos.