[KAZUYA]
A murdered fortune teller.
An invitation meant for Roxane.
[KAZUYA]
A box garden evening...
I jumped at the chance to come
without a second thought.
I'm afraid that may
have been a mistake.
[KAZUYA]
Who's the host of this dinner?
Our guide got off the
ship before we left port.
Hey, what about me, Victorique?
Do you need something?
It's not fair that you're
eating all the food
while I'm standing
over here starving.
What did you expect?
The invitation was addressed to
Roxane, not Roxane and guest.
One invitation means
one plate of food.
[sighs]
Fine then. I guess I'll
try to find something else
to eat around here.
Hey, wait. Didn't you bring
some candy or something?
[KAZUYA gasps]
I had packed certain tools that
would be useful, quite a few.
Candy was indeed
one of those things.
Emergency rations as well.
[KAZUYA]
Uh--
Unfortunately, someone
went through my luggage
and took them all out.
If you hadn't been such a busy
body, you wouldn't be hungry.
That's what one
gets for being nosy.
[KAZUYA growls]
Me, a busy body? That's
not true at all! I--!
Hopefully, this bread will put
an end to your complaining.
[gasps]
It's delicious.
[foosteps]
[VICTORIQUE snoring]
[KAZUYA snoring]
[YASUHIRO]
Kazuya!
Young man!
You need to get up!
Right now!
[KAZUYA groans]
[YASUHIRO] Being a son of Japan
comes with the burden of duty.
Makes you responsible
for protecting the weak.
Now are you the third-born son
of an imperial soldier, or not?
Prove it! And get up!
[KAZUYA groans]
[VICTORIQUE]
Hello? Can you hear me,
Mister Complains-A-Lot
exchange student?
It's time to wake up.
[KAZUYA groans]
I'm up, so you can
stop kicking me!
Hold on...
How'd we get in this room?
[GUESTS groaning]
[VICTORIQUE] I have a feeling
everyone's food was drugged.
Someone must have moved
us to this location
after we all passed out.
--Wait, what?!
--[MAURICE groans]
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
What's this? How did
I get into this room?
--[JULIE] It's locked!
--[GUESTS gasp]
[JULIE grunting]
Damn it! We're trapped in here.
[KAZUYA yelps, whimpers]
That was rude.
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo, something's very wrong.
You don't say.
[VICTORIQUE]
I counted nine other people
eating in the dining
room with us earlier.
That makes eleven total
when including you and me.
But now, there are
twelve of us in this room.
[gasps]
Which means a new person
has joined the party.
[KAZUYA]
You're right.
There are twelve of us.
[VICTORIQUE]
I know.
After we all fell asleep,
the extra must have come
into the dining room,
and moved our unconscious
bodies into this room
for some unknown reason.
How can you be so certain?
[GUEST D]
It's the box garden.
[GUEST A]
I believe you're right.
The hares must be...
...those children over there.
[KAZUYA]
Hmm...
[gasps] Hm...
[KAZUYA]
That ship... The Queen Berry .
There's something oddly familiar
about this thing's name.
[MAURICE]
No, don't touch it!
[KAZUYA gasps]
[GUESTS gasp, murmur]
--[JULIE gasps]
--[GUEST C] So it's true.
This ship is...
There's no doubt.
It's the real thing.
[VICTORIQUE]
Are you okay, Kujo?
--[KAZUYA] The Queen Berry ...
--[VICTORIQUE gasps]
I've read about this boat.
It's haunted.
[KAZUYA]
Ten years ago, the ship sank.
According to the story,
the dead passengers
didn't go to heaven.
Instead, they reappear on stormy
nights to capture living souls
and drag them down
into the depths.
[laughs mockingly]
What? Why would you laugh
at something like that?
Laughing after someone says a
joke is an appropriate reaction.
It's no joke. I was
being serious--
--[gasps]
--[GUESTS gasp, chatter]
--The power!
--[GUESTS chattering]
Hello, Victorique?
Are you still with me?
Say something!
Victorique!
[VICTORIQUE] Yes, what? Why
are you yelling for no reason?
[KAZUYA gasps]
[laughs nervously]
It was nothing. Forget about it.
[JULIE screams]
[GUESTS gasp]
So it's true.
No. That writing...
It wasn't there
before the blackout.
"It's been exactly ten years.
How time flies.
And now it's your turn to
participate in the game.
The box has been prepared.
Ready?" [gulps]
"Get set...
Run, Hares!"
[GUEST A screams]
It's the "box garden evening,"
and we're the hares!
[GUEST A]
I only agreed to dinner,
not the running of
the rabbits as well.
We're about to be hunted down.
They're going to kill us all!
It's those children.
--Their spirits have come
--[JULIE] You can't leave!
--for our souls!
--The door's locked, remember?
[KAZUYA gasps]
[JULIE screams]
At least there isn't
a trap there anymore.
This is our chance to
get the hell out of here!
Get moving!
[GUEST D]
To the lifeboats!
[GUEST B]
Follow me!
[GUEST C] Hurry! Before
the ship kills us, too!
[NED]
Come on, you two.
We need to get off this boat!
[gasps] Right!
Wait. You don't have to
look at him, Victorique.
Just stay behind me.
You're not scared, are you?
[KAZUYA] She walked
right past a dead man.
And it didn't seem to
bother her at all.
Hey! Wait up!
[footsteps, panting]
[NED]
You shouldn't use those!
[KAZUYA] A dinghy will
capsize in this storm!
It's too dangerous!
[NED]
Listen, old man!
Unhand me, you fool!
If we stay aboard this vessel,
we'll become the prey!
I'm reeling it down!
No! Not yet!
Don't leave without me!
I need to get on that
lifeboat right now!
[KAZUYA]
They're not thinking straight.
[gasps]
[GUESTS grunting, groaning]
[whimpering]
[GUEST B screams]
[NED]
Fools...
You damn fools!
I tried to warn them,
but they wouldn't listen.
[VICTORIQUE]
What a shame.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA] Those people died
right in front of us.
But she's totally calm.
[KAZUYA]
The same as the day we met.
She's been like this many times.
As peaceful as a doll.
So peculiar.
And mysterious.
[KAZUYA]
Victorique...
Who are you?
[FRENCH GIRL]
Huey!
[ALEX]
He's gone...
We've lost him.
[CHILDREN crying]
[screams]
[JULIE screams]
How can this be?
--[GUESTS gasp]
--Impossible!
We were only on the
deck for a few minutes.
[NED]
Look.
The body is missing.
Where did it go?!
[MAURICE]
The ghosts took it.
It can only be the hares.
They've come back for
their revenge--! [groans]
Sir! Are you okay?
[KAZUYA]
Here you go.
[MAURICE]
Thank you.
I'm sorry I lost my head.
You children can
call me Maurice.
I'm employed at Saubure's
Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
Now what about you all?
My name's Julie Guile.
I'm an heiress.
No job.
The coal business has been
quite kind to my father.
--[NED] Ned Baxter.
--[JULIE gasps]
I hail from England.
I make a living there
as a stage actor.
In fact, I'm staring in
a play next month...
...portraying a murderer.
[JULIE gasps]
Are you confessing then?
I'm no killer!
Hey. It's my turn.
My name's Kazuya Kujo.
I'm originally from Japan.
And this girl...
...is Victorique.
She's my friend and classmate.
You look familiar.
Young girl, excuse me but do
I know you from somewhere?
I doubt it.
Maurice, you need to be honest
with us and start explaining.
What exactly is going on
with this box garden evening.
Huh? But what makes you
think I know anything?
That model, there.
[MAURICE]
Huh?
[VICTORIQUE] When Kujo
touched it a few minutes ago,
you tried to stop him.
You knew that there was a
trap attached to the model,
which means you've been
on this ship before.
[MAURICE gasps]
[MAURICE]
You're right.
I have been on this ship before.
Ten years ago, in
1914, this ship sank.
I watched it go down
with my own eyes.
Straight to the bottom
of the Mediterranean.
But this boat is none other
than the Queen Berry herself!
[MAURICE]
We put children on this ship.
They were referred to as the
"hares" for our experiment.
They were all different, from
their hair color to their eyes,
even the languages they spoke.
There was a total of
eleven boys and girls
from all over the world.
Certain adults picked
out the children
to participate in a scheme.
It involved the orphans
spending the night here
on the Queen Berry.
[MAURICE]
The next morning...
My supervisors gave me orders.
I was to investigate the ship.
And what I saw...
What happened to them?
[MAURICE]
They were all dead!
They had murdered each other.
It was terrible.
[NED growls]
So, what was this scheme
of yours about, huh?!
Why did you use children?!
My boss didn't give me any
details on the operation.
I just retrieved
their dead bodies!
But why would all of those
children attack each other?
I can't even imagine why.
And the ship sank before I
had time to investigate...
...taking all the
evidence down with it.
This is where that ghost story
you mentioned earlier
comes from, Kujo.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Huh?
The spooky tale of
the lost Queen Berry ,
whose dead souls raise the ship
from the bottom of the ocean
to claim more lives.
[KAZUYA groans]
[MAURICE]
It's the ten-year anniversary.
And the hares have finally
brought the people responsible
for their deaths together to pay
for their unspeakable crimes.
[laughs bitterly]
This is the end of the road.
We are all going to die in here!
[laughs mockingly]
[KAZUYA groans]
Not with that laugh again.
Stop it!
What's so damn funny?!
[VICTORIQUE] Once again,
I was just laughing at a joke.
It's no joke!
--They're going to kill us!
--[VICTORIQUE] I see.
So you must think...
...the ghosts wrote all of
these invitations as well.
[KAZUYA]
She's right.
Then explain to me how this
ship resurrected itself
from the bottom of the sea?
[VICTORIQUE]
Do me a favor.
And try using your
noses for once.
[ALL gasp, sniff]
What is that smell?
It reminds me of...
A fresh coat of paint.
[VICTORIQUE] Now let's
take a look at this wine.
According to the label,
it's a vintage 1890.
Which would make one think that
this is a thirty-year-old
bottle of Saubure wine.
However, this wine
has a dazzling hue
and an undeveloped bouquet.
[KAZUYA]
What are you getting at?
I happen to know that
this wine is a fraud.
Its vinery burned down
back in the summer of 1914,
during the fires
of the Great War,
meaning the original wine...
is impossible to purchase now.
You're saying the
label is a fake?
[VICTORIQUE]
Correct.
Probably swapped.
But why would anyone go
through that much trouble?
[VICTORIQUE]
It's obvious.
They wanted this ship
to be a perfect replica
of the real vessel.
But how do you explain
the bloody writing
scrawled on the wall?
Or the sudden flood
damage in this lounge?
And where the hell did
the corpse run off to?
[VICTORIQUE sighs]
Instead of explaining
the scheme,
I will now reconstruct
the chaos for you all.
Then, you will see how the
events unfolded for yourselves.
[VICTORIQUE] After we ran back
down here from the deck area,
all of us naturally
chose to enter this room.
But why did we do that?
Because it was the only
open door in the hall?
As you can see,
the others are closed.
You're correct.
Now Kujo...
Do me a favor and try to
open that door please.
[KAZUYA gasps]
What's the matter?
Well, uh... I could be wrong,
but I think this is the
lounge we were in before.
[VICTORIQUE]
Indeed.
This is the room that we
originally woke up in.
It was a very simple
trick to pull off.
The same goes for the
writing on the wall.
[VICTORIQUE] My reconstruction
of tonight's chaotic events
leads me straight to the answer,
which I'm now holding.
Wallpaper? Of course.
Clever.
[whistles]
[VICTORIQUE]
The letters where there before
we were moved into this room.
The culprit stripped off
the wallpaper covering them,
and the blackout provided
more than enough time
for them to be revealed.
Your explanation makes
this ruse seem so obvious.
Amazing! You're really
a genius, Victorique!
Ssh!
I hear water.
[gasps]
We're flooding!
To the telegraph room!
We'll call for help!
[MAURICE]
What are you all waiting for?!
Unless you want to drown,
we need to hurry!
[MAURICE] If the layout's the
same as the Queen Berry ,
we'll need to go down
to cross the ship.
It's the only way to
reach the telegraph room.
[JULIE] Ugh! What's with
this ship's crazy design?!
[KAZUYA]
Here's the elevator!
[NED]
No, don't!
Let's find the staircase.
[footsteps]
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
--Come on!
--[VICTORIQUE gasps]
What do you want me
to do with your hand?
Well... I thought...
...that I could protect you.
You can hold it.
How dare you presume
I need help!
In case you haven't noticed,
I can take care of
myself just fine!
[KAZUYA] Uh-- Excuse me
for worrying about you!
Why do you have to be so
stubborn?! I'm just trying
to be a good friend,
you little control freak!
What did you call me?!
[BOTH gasp]
[KAZUYA] There are traps
everywhere on this ship.
[footsteps]
[NED]
Hey, everyone!
Keep moving, I've
found the staircase.
[JULIE]
You're a very caring young man.
I've noticed that you're always
looking after your girlfriend.
It's very sweet of you.
Uh-- It's not a big deal.
[giggles]
What a typical male response.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA] So now she
wants to hold my hand?
Let's go, boyfriend.
[KAZUYA]
Ugh, uh--
[MAURICE]
We're too late...
It's already flooded.
Right.
We had better be quick then.
There may still be a
chance if we hustle.
Hurry up!
--[water splashes]
--[GROUP gasps]
--[KAZUYA] Hop on!
--Huh?
Let's go. We don't
have much time.
The water's rising.
That's too tight.
Loosen it up a bit; I'm choking.
[VICTORIQUE]
That's your problem.
So you're strangling
me on purpose?
[VICTORIQUE] You brought
this burden on yourself.
[KAZUYA]
Burden?
What is she talking about?
She's easier to carry
than my suitcase.
[KAZUYA]
It makes me wonder.
Are all girls this light?
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
It can't be.
Is Victorique...
...actually afraid?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
[KAZUYA]
I forget...
...that no matter
how smart she is...
...or how eccentric
she may be...
...she's still
just a young girl.
[KAZUYA]
So small...
And childlike...
I'm the reason
she's on this trip,
the reason she's in danger.
[YASUHIRO] Being a son of Japan
comes with the burden of duty.
Makes you responsible
for protecting the weak!
[KAZUYA hisses]
Look! If we go this way,
it should take us out
onto the ship's prow.
[MAURICE groans]
Why bother?
At this rate, we're all
going to become hares soon.
Pull yourself together.
We still have time to send
out a distress signal.
But that doesn't
guarantee help will come!
If we're destined to die,
you'll go first!
What was that all about?!
Hang on just a minute!
[NED]
Hold up!
Maurice, you need
to keep it together.
--[ALL gasp]
--Hey. Wait.
Guess you didn't realize that
there are hundreds of weapons
hidden on this ship, in
the drawers, inside vases,
even under carpets!
They're stashed everywhere.
[JULIE]
Why are there weapons?!
To help the children kill
each other, of course.
The hunting dog
stirred up the hares,
made them distrustful
and scared.
Then once the kids
found the weapons,
they started using them
against each other.
[JULIE]
That's awful.
[MAURICE] Yes... Now which
one of you is a hare?
I thought you said all
of the hares were dead.
[MAURICE]
Shut up!
A few of them survived.
In fact, there were
about as many survivors
as there are people
standing in front of me.
But I can't make heads
or tails of this anymore!
That's why I have no choice
but to kill all of you.
It's my only chance of
getting off this ship alive!
Don't do this!
You know that
Victorique is innocent.
I don't care!
I can't trust any of you!
What a fool.
[KAZUYA]
Sir... You've gone mad.
And you won't be hurting anyone.
Because I'm not
going to let you!
Kujo...
Excuse me, but what do
you think you're doing?
[KAZUYA]
I brought you on board...
That means it's my
responsibility to protect you.
As the third son of a
Japanese imperial soldier,
it's my duty to keep you alive.
[gasps]
[MAURICE laughs manically]
I understand now.
You were the hare all along!
In that case... die!
[gunshot]
[KAZUYA]
All this talk about hares?
And hunting dogs, too?
I don't understand what's
going on aboard this ship!
[VICTORIQUE]
And I don't understand you.
Kazuya Kujo...
So willing to die for
someone you just met.