Anyway, I was told
that a gray wolf lives
in the conservatory at
the top of the library!
[KAZUYA]
Huh? A gray wolf?
I heard it was a golden fairy.
You were told one of
the older stories.
They say this wolf is smart.
It can even speak
human languages.
It also has an obsession with
shiny things, apparently.
Well, wolf or fairy,
the one that I know
prefers sweets to trinkets.
Our mission is clear!
We must find something sparkly
to temp the wolf out of hiding!
[sighs]
[KAZUYA]
Avril fits right in with
the people at school
and in this country.
It hasn't been long,
but she's learned more
of the school's secrets
than I knew existed.
[KAZUYA] And she's had far more
luck making friends than me.
Oh well.
At least I'm the only one
who knows about Victorique.
Hold on. What's all
the ruckus for?
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
There!
[BOY gasping]
[ROSCOE humming]
[ROSCOE grunts]
[CROWD laughs, gasps]
[coos]
[ROSCOE gasps]
How boring. Oh well...
Moving on.
Where are we going now?
[gasps]
Hey! My textbooks!
Huh?!
[KAZUYA]
That was--
[ROSCOE chuckles]
Amazing!
But... my textbooks are gone.
[AVRIL]
Get moving!
[gasps] Okay!
Hold on a second!
That's a new look for you.
Forget about it.
So, uh, can I borrow your books?
I need to copy them.
Huh?
[MILDRED]
Hey, you two!
See anything you like?
[MILDRED]
Feel free to browse.
[KAZUYA]
She smells like liquor.
[AVRIL gasps]
What a beautiful plate!
You have a discerning eye.
This Dresdan plate was donated
by one of our disciples
and has quite the history.
[KAZUYA gasps]
It must be worth a fortune.
I think you'll
like this as well.
A music box!
[MILDRED chuckles]
[AVRIL, KAZUYA gasp]
Whoa! What's with all the doves?
[MILDRED screams]
[BOTH gasp]
--[footsteps]
--[KAZUYA panting]
Victorique!
Are you here?
[gasps, groans]
Man, would you
look at this mess.
[VICTORIQUE]
Hm?
Okay, this is
getting out of hand.
[KAZUYA] You could try
not being such a slob.
Is that thing a hat?
What an unusual shape.
I thought you might like it,
so I brought it from the--
Boring.
Try giving it a chance.
You can't be bored with it when
you haven't even put it on.
You're so hard to
please sometimes.
Oh wait, I know.
A mysterious theft occurred
in the flea market
where I got this.
A priceless plate vanished
in the middle of a crowd.
You have my interest.
[KAZUYA]
All right, so, this music box
burst into smoke and
doves flew out of it!
It's been a pretty
dovey day, actually.
Anyway, the plate!
In all the confusion,
someone made off with it.
No one saw the culprit!
[yawns]
Those fragments
are so simplistic.
They hardly qualify
as chaos at all.
For real?
[VICTORIQUE]
I'll put it to you this way.
My boredom is dying of boredom.
Maybe if you tried the
hat, it wouldn't be.
[elevator rattles]
[BLOIS]
Hello there, Little Squirrel.
Been keeping your fur glossy?
Hmm?
[gasps]
[BLOIS gasping]
You're Cordelia... Gallo.
What on Earth are you here for?!
Who's Cordelia?
You twit.
It's just me.
[BLOIS gasps]
You... deceived me!
And I'm no twit.
Hey, who's Cordelia Gallo?
[VICTORIQUE]
You must be here because
of the theft in the market.
All right, listen.
The nun is the only one
who could have stolen the
plate during the confusion.
Of course, I'm going solely
on Kujo's fragments here.
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
I believe she rigged
the music box to break
the moment someone
started to wind it.
Then, to provide
further misdirection,
she released the doves from
a cage underneath her skirt.
And you know this how?
[VICTORIQUE] Nuns are
typically modest and reserved.
Why would this one be sitting
with her legs spread like a man?
Likely, because she was
hiding the doves between them.
[VICTORIQUE]
After setting them free,
she used the cover
of the commotion
to quickly hide the
plate under her skirt.
Then, she stood up and
screamed that it was gone.
I give up.
--[KAZUYA] Huh?
--Oh, nothing.
What's that? I think I
hear a kookaburra laughing.
I'll take my leave.
He's always so confusing.
Oh, right!
So, uh, Victorique?
Who is... that Cordelia
person he mentioned?
[sighs]
[KAZUYA] "The renowned Inspector
Blois throws in the towel"?
"Stolen Dresdan plate
considered lost for good"?
[KAZUYA]
What a surprise.
I expected him to solve the case
and steal credit from
Victorique as usual.
I almost feel sorry for him.
[KAZUYA]
What's this one about?
"From the village
of the Gray Wolves.
The solstice draws near.
We welcome you, our progeny."
[KAZUYA] It said "the village
of the Gray Wolves"!
They're from a town
called Horovitz.
See, the article
even has a simple map.
[KAZUYA] It all sounds so
mysterious, doesn't it?
I figured it would at least
give you something to mull over.
It may even relieve
your boredom a bit.
[gasps]
[VICTORIQUE yelps]
[gasps] I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
[VICTORIQUE]
It hurts...
Yeah, I bet.
It made one heck of
a noise for sure.
[VICTORIQUE]
I said it hurts! It's not funny!
Okay, I'm sorry.
[gasps]
Ah! Darn, these snacks
are getting everywhere.
[VICTORIQUE]
Take responsibility and eat it.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Uh-- Uh...
I'm waiting!
[KAZUYA gasps]
All right.
[VICTORIQUE] Once you're done I
want you to fetch a book for me.
Eighth floor, seventh
shelf, third row,
thirty-first book
from the right.
Make it snappy.
[KAZUYA]
Fine, I'm on it.
[VICTORIQUE] Out of all the
ghost stories in Saubure,
there is one that
gets more well-known
the deeper you go
into the mountains.
[VICTORIQUE]
The Legend of the Gray Wolves.
Many of the stories surrounding
them are clearly fabricated.
However, the diary of a 16th
century traveler from England
gives a clear account
of their presence.
[KAZUYA]
She's still rubbing it.
I thought she was
overreacting at first,
but could Victorique really
be that sensitive to pain?
However, the evidence suggests
that he doesn't mean
it's a wolf literally.
[KAZUYA]
Victorique?
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[laughs]
What, did I scare... you?
You really do
overreact to things.
I mean, come on,
it was just a flick.
--[VICTORIQUE whimpers]
--[KAZUYA gasps]
[VICTORIQUE sobs]
Are you... really crying?
[VICTORIQUE]
You jerk.
I didn't know you were
that kind of man, Kujo.
Hey, I'm sorry.
It couldn't have hurt that much.
Here, let me--
What's wrong?
As of this moment,
you and I are... over!
What, are you serious?
Come on, Victorique.
You really want to
end our friendship
over one little flick?
Fine, I get it.
You like books more
than you like me.
--Great.
--[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Then, I'll leave. Permanently.
[yells]
I mean it, I'm never coming
back to this stupid library!
You're just so--!
[KAZUYA]
You need thicker skin!
I'm sure it will all be fine.
If I bring her another
bag of sweets tomorrow,
she'll probably forget
this even happened.
[sighs, yawns]
It shouldn't take this long
to copy one little textbook.
Hah! I'd know that
trunk anywhere.
[VICTORIQUE grunting]
[KAZUYA] What are you
doing out this late?
I thought you said you
couldn't leave the school
without getting permission.
Besides, the front
gate is locked.
How are you going
to get past it?
Didn't think of that, huh?
[KAZUYA]
Ah! A cavity.
[VICTORIQUE grunts]
That's what happens when
you eat lots of sweets.
Just look at your cheek! Puffy!
[gasps] This one, too!
It's getting worse!
You don't need to pack your
case just to see a dentist.
That's a lot of stuff!
A change of clothes,
a washbasin,
a set of tea cups and dishes,
a stuffed toy, a vase.
And, uh... a cot?!
What do you need
this thing for?!
Stay here a minute.
I'll go get my wallet.
There's a way we can
get past the gate.
Avril showed me.
It's crude, but it
will get the job done.
We'll go to the
dentist together.
[VICTORIQUE groans]
[KAZUYA] So... How did
I end up on a train?
I'm confused.
Lovely night, isn't it?
--[VICTORIQUE] Hmph.
--[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA] I assumed she was
going to the dentist.
Instead, she took
me to the station.
And then...
[VICTORIQUE]
To Horovitz.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
The town from the article.
What would possess
her to go there
in the middle of the night?
Maybe...
Hey, Victorique, are
you planning to--
[MILDRED]
Mind if I join you?
Sure, come in. [gasps]
It's... you!
[MILDRED]
Well, well!
You're going to Horovitz, too?
What in the hell for?
Oh. Nothing special.
And... you?
Please, call me Mildred.
Horovitz... Well, it's...
the town I grew up in.
Nothing more.
So, uh, what happened
after I saw you last?
With the plate, I mean.
[MILDRED]
Tch, who can say?
They still haven't found it.
The Bishop chewed
me out, so I quit.
Hey, whaddya know?
We're already there.
[train whistles]
[INNKEEPER]
Gonna be a windy night.
Best to stay indoors.
The Wolves will be out tonight.
We heard about that.
Gray Wolves live
up the mountain.
Nights like this they come down
and hunt for anything
foolish enough to get caught.
I suggest you settle in, unless
you fancy being slaughtered
in the bushes like cattle.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Around here, we hang dead
birds from the doors.
It keeps the Wolves out well
enough, but you never know.
You here for the sights
or because of the ad in the
paper like the rest of them?
There are others here?
[INNKEEPER]
Yeah, they were excited about
driving up the mountain
in that fancy car of theirs,
but the paths are too steep;
thing didn't stand a chance.
They best behave, lest they
earn the wrath of the Wolves.
That's the path
to ruin, my friend.
Are they the only animals that
attack people around here?
[INNKEEPER]
Animals?
They're all human, lad.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[INNKEEPER]
These aren't fur covered mutts.
They're golden-haired,
rosy-cheeked, pint-sized
little doll people.
They even have the same face,
like someone stamped them on.
[gasps]
Just... like her.
She's the spittin'
image of them.
And her eyes, they
have the same stare,
silent as death!
[gasps] You've gotta
be kidding me.
[MILDRED] Innkeep, could
I get another blanket?
It's freezing.
Uh... Yes, of course.
It can get rather
chilly here after dark.
[MILDRED]
I noticed.
Hey... Is there a
phone I can use?
Sure.
[KAZUYA] I thought she
said she was from here.
She should have known
it would be cold.
[clatter]
[KAZUYA]
Let me carry that for you.
--[KAZUYA gasps]
--[VICTORIQUE grunting]
[groans]
[KAZUYA groans]
[howling]
[gasps]
That's no human.
[door shuts]
[door opens, creaks]
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
Did the wolf's howl
wake you up, too?
A squirrel...
It came out of my closet and
won't stop running around.
Do you want me to
chase it out for you?
[VICTORIQUE] It will probably
leave if you ask it to.
Just speak squirrel.
You're still dreaming.
I'm glad you're talking
to me, at least.
I was starting to
feel kind of lonely.
[KAZUYA chuckles]
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Hold on a second!
[gasps]
Calm down!
I get that you're upset with me.
But I need to know
why we came out here.
If I don't know,
I can't help you.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
You aren't supposed to
leave the school grounds.
Not without your
father's approval.
You've always obeyed
that rule until now.
So something big
must be happening.
Are you still ignoring me?
Do you honestly hate
my guts that much?
You said that we
were friends, once.
I don't have very many.
So I'll be damned if I
abandon the ones I do.
[KAZUYA] You'll get soaked if
you leave the window open.
[KAZUYA]
I'm coming in.
I'll just close
the window, okay?
[VICTORIQUE]
I came here...
...to prove someone's
innocence, once and for all.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[gasps] Victorique?
--What are you--
--Stay back.
Hey! Come on.
--Knock it off!
--[VICTORIQUE] Stay! Sit! Heel!
Stop treating me like a puppy!
[gasps]
That's... um...
...you, right?
Cordelia Gallo.
A Gray Wolf... and my mother.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
Cordelia was a renowned dancer.
She had exotic make-up,
clothes, and clients.
But it was her heritage
that caught the attention
of the Marquis de Blois.
My father wanted to incorporate
the legendary power of the
Gray Wolves into his bloodline.
[VICTORIQUE] And so, he made
Cordelia his mistress.
I was born soon after.
[VICTORIQUE]
All was well.
But then, the Marquis de Blois
learned my mother's secret.
And that was?
That the Gray Wolves had
branded her a sinner.
[gasps] A sinner?
[VICTORIQUE]
That's right.
Aside from dancing,
she worked as a maid in
the Gray Wolf village.
They say she committed a
terrible crime one night.
And was banished forever.
The Marquis de Blois was enraged
when he learned of this,
and cursed the moment he
added her tainted blood
into his "noble family line."
Mother ran away.
And threw herself
into the flames
of the Great War as it spread.
[VICTORIQUE]
I was locked away in a tower.
And that's where I grew up.
[KAZUYA gasps]
All the suffering in
my life and my mother's
can be traced back to the night
she committed that crime.
If not for that, things would
have turned out for the better.
She would still
be in her village,
and I would never
have been born.
[gasps] But I
wouldn't want that!
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
It... slipped out. Sorry.
It's just...
--[VICTORIQUE laughs]
--Why are you laughing?
[VICTORIQUE] Sometimes you
say the dumbest things, Kujo.
[KAZUYA]
Well, excuse me.
Present your forehead, please.
[KAZUYA yelps, groans]
[VICTORIQUE]
I came...
...because I don't believe
Cordelia really
committed that crime.
There's a battle
being fought here.
It's between the village
of the Gray Wolves...
...and her.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Until my mother is
absolved of her sin...
...I stay.
[ALAN]
Hi, there. I'm Alan.
These here are my
friends, Raul and Derek.
It's nice to meet you.
[RAUL] Hey, are you
sure this mountain road
will take us to the village?
[DEREK]
What, afraid you'll fall?
[GROUP laughs]
[GROUP gasps]
Now that is one
hell of a village.
I'll pick you back up
tomorrow evening at this spot.
Don't make me wait.
[KAZUYA]
Hey! Hold on!
[GROUP gasps]
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
They look angry.
Well, this is some welcome,
I feel at home already.
[VILLAGER A]
Is that Cordelia's daughter?
Look at her face.
It's exactly the same!
That's a bad omen.
[SERGIUS]
Stand down!
[VILLAGER A]
Headman!
This progeny has received
the call of her people.
Move aside.
We will not drive her out.
Welcome.
You're just in time
for the festivities.
We will allow you to celebrate
with us, our daughter,
even if your mother
--was a murderer.
--[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
My mother is innocent.
No matter what it takes,
I will prove that to
everyone in this village.
[KAZUYA]
This case...
It's so easy to get swept up in.