[train whistles]
Okay, we're ready.
Now, move your hands exactly
as I instructed you.
[gasps]
This was the trick behind
Simon Hunt's gruesome murder.
It's known as a slipknot.
And it's a favorite among escape
artists and other magicians.
[VICTORIQUE]
All Morella, the nun, had to do
was pull the end of the knot.
Then she was free to murder
the helpless Mr. Hunt.
My goodness! How vile.
But it's so simple that it
barely qualifies as chaos.
If I'm ever going to reconstruct
the truth, I'll need a...
A...
A...?
[VICTORIQUE grunts]
[sneezes]
[groans]
Are you okay?
[VICTORIQUE growls]
By the way, thanks
for saving us earlier.
Didn't I see you on the
train coming here, as well?
[knocking]
[door opens]
There's room here.
[GIDEON]
No, it's all right.
I couldn't possibly.
[KNIGHT]
Don't worry.
[GIDEON laughs nervously]
Sorry to be a bother, but
could we join you good folks?
[KNIGHT]
You're our saviors!
Every other car
was packed tight.
[chuckles]
[KAZUYA]
So, uh...
Are you two acquaintances?
No, he found me looking
for a place to sit down.
When he saw that you had room,
he called me out
into the hallway.
Well, let's introduce ourselves!
Fate has clearly brought us
all together this morning.
Young lady... What were
you doing at the convent?
[sighs] I'm an orphan.
Huh?
I don't even know
when my birthday is.
And that means, whenever
I reach the afterlife,
I'll be wandering
it for all time.
I joined Phantasmagoria
hoping a magician would
reveal my birthday.
So? What's your story?
Well... I'm just a
simple scarecrow.
I typically stand in fields
around the country
and scare all the
nasty birds away.
[KAZUYA]
Hold on.
Are we playing some
kind of game?
[KNIGHT laughs]
I like it!
Then, for now, you can
call me the Knight!
I ride the countryside
on my noble steed,
finding evil
wherever it may hide,
and smiting it!
And you?
Just a lumberjack.
Cutting down evil is best left
to those of a noble heart.
Smiting trees is about all
I can manage, I'm afraid.
A cowardly rich kid, huh?
How about you two?
We're, uh...
A proud Gray Wolf that has
lived for thousands of years.
And her dimwitted retainer.
Hey, wait a minute!
I'm not dimwitted!
Take it... back?
[yelps]
[train whistles]
[ROSCOE] The Masquerade
is quite a fitting name.
That's truly what's
about to unfold.
[ROSCOE]
You really have that much faith?
I'm not sure the cub will
be able to steal it back.
[CORDELIA]
She has to.
That box is the Gray
Wolf's trump card.
I'm sure it will help protect
her from the coming storm.
[ROSCOE] That's why you
want to entrust it to her?
What happens to us, then?
I'd hate to think that we came
all this way for nothing.
Don't you worry.
I've got another plan
in mind, my friend.
Dear daughter,
solve this mystery.
I beseech you.
Show me that you have
the power to live.
[KAZUYA]
"Miss Lesglant still missing.
The police continue to search."
Huh. That happened in Saubure?
Oh! By the way...
What were you going to say you
needed for your reconstruction?
Tell me, do you know
what a memento box is?
It's fine if you don't.
[KAZUYA]
No.
[VICTORIQUE] It's a custom
that's been passed down
throughout many parts of
Europe over the years.
A person places items that
represent turning points
in their life into a small box.
When the owner dies,
the box is placed into the
coffin and buried with them.
So, in other words, it's
like a symbol of their life?
A simple definition,
but it's a fitting one.
The box at Beelzebub's Skull
most likely contains a
person's life, as well.
And for some reason,
Mama is trying to retrieve it.
My job's clear.
I have to figure out
what's inside that box.
[ALL gasp]
[KAZUYA]
That scared the hell out of me!
[VICTORIQUE]
K-K-K-K... Kujo!
[KAZUYA gasps]
Get off!
[KAZUYA yelps]
Sorry!
You jerk!
I'll remember this later!
[sneezes]
[laughs nervously]
[SCARECROW sighs]
Poor thing...
You'll catch your death if
you stay in those wet clothes.
I'll see if a crewman
has something dry
you two can borrow.
Oh! Wait, I'll come with you!
[ORPHAN]
It's gone!
[BOTH gasp]
--[KAZUYA] Something wrong?
--[gasps]
Hey, Mr. Knight.
This air is giving me chills.
Would you mind asking Scarecrow
if she could grab
something for me as well?
[KNIGHT]
On it.
[GIDEON]
I can go.
You stay here, kiddo.
[KNIGHT] The only one who can
fulfill a princess's request...
...is a knight.
That's it.
[footsteps]
[SCARECROW gasps]
You meeting a lover?
One hell of a spot.
[SCARECROW groans]
[KNIGHT]
You went against your archetype.
What kind of scarecrow steals
someone else's harvest?
Did you think my comrade
wouldn't notice it was missing?
[groans, coughs]
Have it your way.
It's been forever.
What happened to them?
[KAZUYA]
I-I'm sorry.
You didn't have to tell us
that if you didn't want to.
It's fine.
[KAZUYA] I hope...
you find your birthday.
[ORPHAN gasps]
[VICTORIQUE growls]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
We need a crewman.
Someone fell off the train!
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Not yet.
[door opens]
Sorry for the wait.
Fresh clothes here, all yours.
Hey, shouldn't the
Scarecrow be with you?
[KNIGHT] She ran into
an old friend of hers
and moved to their compartment.
Sends her regards, and all that.
I see.
[VICTORIQUE]
We should get changed, Kujo.
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[VICTORIQUE]
Don't doubt yourself.
That definitely wasn't
an illusion earlier.
I don't know if
they're dead or alive,
but someone has left
the stage prematurely.
You think that--
Do you think it
was the Scarecrow?
[VICTORIQUE]
Yes.
The Orphan is in on it, as well.
Everyone in that compartment
this evening is working for
the Ministry of the Occult
or the Academy of Sciences.
[gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
Good grief.
We've been mixed up in quite
the masquerade, it would seem.
But, in a way, this
could be fortunate.
[VICTORIQUE]
I'm just not certain
what we should expect
from this dance.
[VICTORIQUE]
That wouldn't be an issue
if I had more fragments
of chaos to pull from.
There a problem?
No... It just looks
so perfect on you.
[KAZUYA yelps]
What does that mean?!
Are you saying I
should wait tables?
Someone's grown high and mighty.
[KAZUYA] That's not what
I was saying at all!
[GIRL]
Brother, please...
Help me...
[GIDEON]
I will!
Just wait for me.
[GIRL]
Hurry!
[KAZUYA]
A radio?
[KAZUYA] Mr. Lumberjack!
Who were you talking to?
No one.
[footsteps]
[KNIGHT]
Oh, good.
You're all together.
You took so long
that we got worried.
I'd hate for anyone
else to fall out.
Agreed? Lumberjack?
How does the buffet sound?
Drinking until dawn beats
a stuffy compartment.
Sounds good to me.
As long as you're
paying, of course?
Sure thing. My pleasure.
[KNIGHT chuckles]
I'm assuming we're invited
as well, Mr. Lumberjack?
[gasps] Certainly.
Sir? Vodka please?
[yelps]
[VICTORIQUE]
It's a raisin-picking game.
You take one and eat it
as quickly as you can,
despite the pain.
If you don't spit it out,
you speak your wish.
You're pretty knowledgeable.
[ORPHAN]
So, who wants to start us off?
Well, if you don't mind,
I'd like to give it a try.
[groans]
Or not.
[GIDEON]
Guess I'll go, then.
[GIDEON groans, sighs]
I'd like to make it home in
time for spring next year.
The irises are more
beautiful than any other.
[KAZUYA]
I wasn't expecting that.
That's some wish.
But if you want it to come true,
you'll have to leave your
fellow lumberjacks behind.
--[KNIGHT chuckles]
--Okay, I'll go next.
There's no fear
of food poisoning
from these things, correct?
[GIDEON]
Of course not.
Are you okay?
You should have some water.
I don't need your advice.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[ORPHAN sighs]
Let's see...
What should I wish for?
Let me think.
[KAZUYA]
What's wrong?
[VICTORIQUE]
Nothing.
I don't want
anything for myself,
but I do hope you
make it home safely.
[GIDEON]
What do you mean?
[ORPHAN]
Well, you never know.
Stop! Don't drink that water!
[ORPHAN gasps]
[groans]
What's wrong with her?
Oh no!
Let's drop the act.
You're the one who poisoned her!
Hey! Stay with me!
[coughing]
Is anyone here a
doctor or a nurse?
What are you saying?!
I couldn't have poisoned her!
I ate the raisins
from the same bowl.
And I drank the water, too!
[VICTORIQUE] The poison settled
at the bottom of the glass
slightly frozen from
the water temperature.
When the two of you
drank for the first time,
the poison hadn't had a chance
to mix into the water yet.
But eventually,
the ice began to melt.
By the time she drank
again, she had no chance.
--[KNIGHT] Bastard!
--[GIDEON gasps]
[PASSENGERS scream]
[ORPHAN gasps]
Enough.
Holding a gun doesn't suit
a man like you. Mr. Lesglant.
[GIDEON gasps]
How do you know who I am?
Tell me something.
What's behind this foolish
masquerade party?
Are you with the
Ministry or the Academy?
[gasps]
Damn Ministry dog!
[GIDEON groans]
[gasps]
[panting]
The box is mine!
I will not give it up!
[PASSENGERS scream]
[ORPHAN panting]
[KAZUYA gasps]
The box...
It's just as I thought!
[ORPHAN pants]
[KAZUYA]
Don't be crazy!
If you keep moving,
you'll die for sure!
Don't move!
It's too late; everyone on this
damn train is as good as dead.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KNIGHT] Our allies broke
their usual contact with us.
They're probably arranging for
the train to have an accident.
[BOTH gasp]
[KNIGHT] Better to bury that box
in a pile of iron and bodies
than let the Ministry of
the Occult get ahold of it.
Don't follow us! Understand me?
Get to the engine, go!
Stop this train!
But how?
[KAZUYA]
I guess...
You stay here!
I'll be right back-- [gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
No way. I'm going, too!
[KAZUYA]
But Victorique...
All right.
[KAZUYA grunting]
--[gunshot]
--[BOTH gasp]
Let's hurry.
Hold on tight!
[KNIGHT]
Stop where you are!
Better get moving!
--[screeching]
--[KAZUYA grunts]
Kujo!
[KNIGHT gasps]
It would seem, in the end, the
knight was thrown off his steed.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Hang in there!
[ORPHAN groans]
Get away... from me.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[ORPHAN] I won't let...
anyone... have it.
[KAZUYA]
Who cares about that?!
Your life is more
important than some box!
[ORPHAN gasps]
[ORPHAN]
Iron bridge...
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Ex... plo... sives...
--[ORPHAN gasping]
--[KAZUYA] Hey...
Hey!
I'm scared. Everything
is so dark now...
[ORPHAN]
Mother...
--[gunshot]
--[KAZUYA gasps]
It's still not possible
at this range.
[KAZUYA]
What?
[VICTORIQUE]
Look over there.
[KAZUYA]
That's...
I have a feeling
it's a detonator.
When it blows, the train
will derail and kill us all.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Wait!
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
We've only got one bullet left.
[VICTORIQUE]
Give it to me.
The next one will hit.
No, it's too dangerous.
I'll do it.
Mama challenged me!
I need to prove that I
have the strength to live.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[VICTORIQUE] I will do
this with my own hands.
All right then.
But only if I help.
[VICTORIQUE] Yes, your
assistance will be necessary.
A lady and her vassal
are one, after all.
[KAZUYA]
You are something else.
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo...
Do you believe in me?
In my Gray Wolf blood?
Yes.
Normally, I don't buy
into such things.
It's beyond crude.
But in this case, I'll take
all the help I can get.
I've never used one of these
before, but I get the basics.
Don't be scared.
I know you can pull this off.
We'll overcome this storm, too.
And make it back, like always.
To our home, Saint
Marguerite Academy!
[BOTH]
Together!
[gunshot]
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[BOTH sigh]
[VICTORIQUE]
What do you know?
I really could do it!
Yes, you could.
Never doubted it.
So, uh... How do we
get off this thing?
Just let it run.
There isn't any coal
for it to burn off.
It'll stop on its
own, soon enough.
[VICTORIQUE] You're the brother
of Mademoiselle Lesglant.
[VICTORIQUE] I'm guessing
you know why she's missing.
[GIDEON growls]
[VICTORIQUE] I think the
Ministry of the Occult
kidnapped your sister
and held her hostage.
That way, they could use
you as an impromptu spy.
It's pretty obvious what
they were desperate to get.
[GIDEON grunts]
A simple memento box.
Inside it are the fragments
of a certain man's life,
and his most guarded secret.
First, he was born.
[KAZUYA]
Hm?
This piece is all that's left
of his umbilical cord. So tiny.
[KAZUYA groans]
Nasty...
[VICTORIQUE]
He grew up.
And failed at attempting art.
He fell in love.
This perfume
belonged to the girl.
And finally...
...he failed.
"Never look back." Huh.
[KAZUYA]
You got that from one sentence?
This is all the box contains.
So then, we can be
certain it's incomplete.
[KAZUYA gasps]
In other words, the
owner is still alive.
If he'd died, there'd be
something to show it.
Furthermore...
This box wasn't
buried in a grave,
it was hidden beneath the
floor of a certain house.
In that nameless village.
The place where we found
my mother's picture.
Hold on.
That would mean the box's owner
is actually a Gray Wolf!
[VICTORIQUE]
And his name was...
[KAZUYA]
"Jupiter Roger.
Seven years old.
From Saillune!"
You're right!
[VICTORIQUE]
Indeed.
Jupiter Roger, chairman of
the Academy of Sciences,
was a Gray Wolf from
the nameless village.
A place of tradition, where
science could never thrive.
This is an important truth
that would shake
the balance of power,
if not demolish it.
That's why the
Ministry wants it.
They could be rid of
their biggest threat.
No wonder they
were on the train.
Both sides risked
everything for that box.
[VICTORIQUE] At least I have
all the fragments now.
Take it.
[GIDEON gasps]
I don't care what the Ministry
does with the thing.
But to you, it's life or death.
Take it back to them
and save your sister.
[KAZUYA]
Hey, Victorique!
Hold on a second!
[GIDEON]
Thank you.
[KAZUYA]
Are you sure about this?
If the Marquis de Blois
gets his hands on that box...
[VICTORIQUE]
I'm not worried.
I've solved the case
that my mama gave me.
[VICTORIQUE]
And besides...
The biggest trump card...
...is still in my hands.
[VICTORIQUE] ♪ I have no tarts
or macarons I can spare. ♪
[KAZUYA]
What?
We have plenty of tarts
and macarons.
Here, have some.
[VICTORIQUE]
No, that was a song.
Ugh. Forget about it.