[ROXANE] A young man's life
will soon end in betrayal.
His death shall be the
start of great turmoil.
The world will turn to stone.
And down it shall fall!
[WORSHIPERS murmuring]
[MAN A]
Is there any hope?
[MAN B]
Please, tell us, Madame Roxane!
You must prepare
for me a great box,
and set it afloat
upon the mighty sea.
And then...
Set eleven hares and
a hound loose within!
[VICTORIQUE yawns]
[KAZUYA] Nestled between the
nations of France, Switzerland,
and Italy is the
Kingdom of Saubure.
And at the base of
the majestic Alps,
sits Saint Marguerite Academy.
[KAZUYA]
It's an educational institute
for the children
of noble families,
and it's renowned
across the globe.
[KAZUYA]
I'm a student here.
My name is...
[STUDENT A gasps]
It's The Black Reaper!
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[KAZUYA]
Yeah... The Black Reaper.
[KAZUYA sighs]
[STUDENT C]
Look at his pitch black eyes.
Even light can't escape them!
[STUDENT D] I bet his
insides are equally as dark!
[KAZUYA]
Well, at least I won't be late.
[YASUHIRO] Dear Kazuya,
how is your life abroad?
[YASUHIRO] Not much has
changed since you left.
It's been quiet since
the end of the Great war--
even quieter without you here.
I'm still in awe that your
grades were good enough
to get you accepted
to Saint Marguerite.
For that, Father and
the rest of the family
are deeply proud of you.
[CÉCILE gasps]
[YASUHIRO] Kazyua, I hope
you grow into a proper man
and return to us
as soon as possible.
Be successful, and you will have
served your country honorably.
Your Eldest Brother.
[sighs]
[yelps]
I think you should read some
ghost stories, Mr. Kujo!
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[KAZUYA]
Uh-- Huh?
[CÉCILE]
This school--
No, this country is
overflowing with them!
[CÉCILE]
Our government even went so far
as to establish a
Department of the Occult!
Because everyone
loves a good scare!
So does that mean my
"Black Reaper" nickname
came from one of those stories?
Yes!
Though it's The Reaper
Who Comes in Spring .
But I have a feeling
they added the "Black"
out of respect
for you, Mr. Kujo.
[KAZUYA]
Respect, huh?
[KAZUYA gasps]
You should learn
more ghost stories
and use them to make friends
with the other students!
Then, once you've made
over a hundred friends,
you can go to the Alps.
And conquer them together!
[KAZUYA]
Right.
Learn more ghost stories, huh.
This... might take a while.
[KAZUYA]
" The Queen Berry .
A ghost ship that appears
during stormy nights...
...and steals souls.
Or, Leviathan, the alchemist
who takes the guts of
the dead to make gold"?
These all sound pretty gruesome.
[KAZUYA]
"The genius Gray Wolf.
Capable of learning and
speaking human language"?
Well, it doesn't have any gore.
Which makes it the perfect story
to try and make friends with.
Gold string?
It couldn't be...
[pants]
A... doll?
[VICTORIQUE]
You finally came.
It took you long
enough... Mr. Reaper.
[gasps]
Wait, how do you know me?
Have we met before?
[VICTORIQUE] A future that
rises from a silver vase
is reflected in a magic mirror.
My prediction tells me
you will come here again.
[VICTORIQUE] Tomorrow, in fact,
when the bell rings noon.
[KAZUYA] How could you
possibly know that?
Because you're a
chosen fragment.
You're destined to relieve
me of my constant boredom.
I hope you will serve me well.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[screams]
[KAZUYA]
What the hell?
That living doll just
predicted my future!
[howling]
[KAZUYA]
It was like a dream.
A conservatory on
top of a library.
A strange girl...
...who spoke even
stranger words.
[CÉCILE]
Oh!
You met Miss Victorique
then, didn't you?
[KAZUYA]
Uh.
Wow! You've already
managed to make a friend.
And with a classmate to
boot. How impressive!
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
The empty seat in the back
of the class belongs to her.
Oh, this is perfect!
You can take these
print-outs to her for me!
Thank you!
I'll see ya later!
No, wait, Miss Cécile!
[bell rings]
[KAZUYA]
When the bell rings noon.
It couldn't be...
--[footsteps]
--[KAZUYA panting]
[gasps]
[VICTORIQUE groaning]
[KAZUYA]
Huh?
[VICTORIQUE]
What took you so long?
Uh... What are you doing?
You got here much later
than I had been expecting.
My boredom started to take hold.
Are you some kind
of fortune-teller?
Why?
You predicted that I would
come here at noon today.
For that, you can thank
my wellspring of wisdom.
Wellspring of what?
A foreign student with black
hair suddenly transfers here
in the middle of spring.
If you take his sinister
appearance into account,
then it's easy to understand
why the student body
would peg him as "The Reaper
Who Comes in Spring."
My sinister appearance?!
Tell me. What's your name?
Kujo. Kazuya Kujo.
Well... Kujo. A student as
bright and bullheaded as you
would surely come to investigate
the origins of the Reaper story.
And there's only one place
on campus you could do that.
Okay, I get the idea.
But I was expecting
something more.
[KAZUYA]
Weird.
She seems different
than yesterday...
[KAZUYA]
Whatever...
Hey, stand still for a second.
You were rolling around so much
your necklace is backwards.
--[VICTORIQUE] Don't touch it!
--[KAZUYA gasps]
This is...
...important to me.
Very... very important.
--[elevator rattles]
--[KAZUYA] Huh?
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
That hair!
Talk about making a statement!
Hello, Grévil.
You know this guy?
[BLOIS] Aah.... What glorious
weather we're having!
I see I have a little black
squirrel here with me.
I guess it can stay.
Though, I doubt
it will comprehend
the complexity of my story.
Last night, in a local mansion,
Roxane, an old fortune-teller,
was brutally murdered.
Wait. What is going on here?
Only a manservant and
a maid lived with her.
The man in question is Indian,
and the woman Arabian.
However, they did have
a visitor last night--
Roxane's granddaughter.
Is there a reason why
she only had servants
from foreign countries?
Apparently, Roxane had a
soft spot for exotic servants,
and she spoke enough
Hindu and Arabic
to get by without a translator.
Oh! I should mention
the maid is only fluent
in her native language.
All... right.
So, is this man a
detective or something?
[VICTORIQUE]
Inspector Grévil de Blois.
He's well known in Saubure,
and not just for his
curious hairstyle.
[BLOIS grumbling]
The fortune-teller was
relaxing in her room
moments before the
murder took place.
The manservant was
outside her window,
returning the rabbits
in the garden
to their respective hutches.
Rabbits?
The fortune-teller kept
quite a number of them,
although not as pets.
Apparently, she would
have hunting dogs
kill them from time to time.
[gasps] Please, Little Squirrel,
I'm trying to tell a story here!
Hold on...
Am I crazy, or are you
using me to talk to her?
And then, out of
nowhere... Gunfire!
Everyone gathered in the
hallway to check on her.
[BLOIS] But none of them
had a key to the door.
The maid called out,
but no response came.
The manservant wanted
to break down the door.
But the granddaughter
wouldn't have it.
She would inherit the mansion
upon her grandmother's death,
and wanted it intact.
What a blasphemous reason.
But the maid couldn't understand
the grandaughter's
selfish pleas.
So, she got a pistol
from the next room.
Then...
[BLOIS]
The door opened.
And beyond it lay...
[BLOIS] The fortune-teller,
her left eye shot out.
The door was locked
from the inside,
and no murder weapon
could be found.
Now, Little Squirrel.
Do you have an answer
for this conundrum?
I do have a real name, you know.
[VICTORIQUE yawns]
So that's the best
you could bring me?
Huh?
It's a simple enough puzzle
when you have all of the parts.
I guess I'll reconstruct
them for you.
[BLOIS]
Hm...
What truly wonderful
weather we're having!
[KAZUYA]
I am so lost right now.
I have taken fragments from
the chaos of this world.
Using the wellspring of
wisdom that lies within me,
I will reconstruct
them into the truth.
Are you saying that you're
gonna solve the case for him?
[BLOIS]
Hmph!
Please, I don't need the help
of a squirrel to do my job.
Obviously, the manservant
is the culprit.
The maid is the
murderer. No doubt.
[BLOIS gasps, growls]
Are you daft?! Why would
you even think that?
Why are you asking me?!
Because only the fortune-teller
could understand what
the maid was saying.
[BOTH gasp]
You said the maid knocked on the
door and cried out in Arabic.
Then, when there
was no response,
she retrieved a pistol
from the next room
and shot off the
door's lock, correct?
[BOTH]
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
But what did the maid
actually say to Roxane?
I'll tell you.
"Did you hear the
gunshot, Mistress?
I'm afraid that your
life may be in danger.
Please, move away
from the window!"
[BOTH gasp]
In other words.,
the maid knew that
the fortune-teller
was alive and well
before shooting the lock.
She tricked Roxane into
a false sense of danger.
And, once the old woman
had moved to the door,
she shot the lock...
And the fortune-teller with it.
I have a feeling her
left eye was shot out
because she tried to
look through the keyhole
at the worst possible moment.
[gunshot]
[BLOIS]
Wait a minute!
If that's the case,
then where did the first shot
come from, Little Squirrel?
Kazuya! Not squirrel, okay?
I'm Kazuya Kujo!
[VICTORIQUE] The first shot was
likely fired in the next room.
To frighten the fortune-teller,
and gather everyone in
the mansion at one spot.
Investigate it, if you like.
I have a feeling you'll
find another bullet hole.
I see. Hm...
Well, I should get
back to the office.
I've enjoyed the fresh air.
There's one more thing, Grévil.
[BLOIS gasps]
The maid's motive will be hidden
in whatever she hit when
she fired the first shot.
What does that mean?!
[gasps, screams]
[KAZUYA]
That was strange.
[yawns]
It was over far too quickly.
Now I'm bored again.
[groans]
So, who are you, exactly?
The Inspector was relying
pretty heavily on your input.
...I think.
At the very least, he
seemed concerned about you.
Do you really want to
know more about me?
I wouldn't mind it.
Then dance.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Is that supposed to be a joke?
Guess not.
[KAZUYA]
Okay.
[KAZUYA humming]
Hmm, I'm not familiar
with that type of dance.
Oh, it's called a "bon."
[KAZUYA] I've danced for
her three times already.
But she still won't
open up to me.
Victorique is so mean.
[SOPHIE]
Hi, Kujo!
How's the food?
[KAZUYA gulps, gasps]
[SOPHIE gasps] Gee!
You could have asked for it.
[KAZUYA] "Another great
achievement for Inspector Blois.
Brilliantly solves the
murder of Roxane,
the famous fortune-teller"?
[KAZUYA]
What's going on here?!
[BLOIS]
Who are you?
[KAZUYA] The granddaughter
was so grateful
she gave you a kiss and a yacht?
Oh, that. Can't be helped.
She planted it on me
without any warning.
It's not like I asked for it.
Not the kiss!
It's the luxury yacht and
the family's gratitude!
You didn't earn any
of it, you glory hog!
Without Victorique--
I get it!
I'll talk, just be quiet, okay?
Your passion wins this
round, my Little Squirrel.
[sighs]
I planned to take the
yacht out this weekend.
You're both welcome
to come along.
We certainly will!
[BLOIS] You say that
like it will be easy.
It won't.
Victorique will never be
allowed to leave the library
without a considerable
amount of work on my part.
She isn't allowed outside?
[BLOIS gasps]
Please, don't worry about it.
See you this weekend.
[VICTORIQUE] Grévil will
get me out for the weekend?
Yes!
He owes you at
least that much.
Stealing your credit
was beyond selfish!
I could never allow
such injustice!
Kujo... Weekends
are precious things.
And now, you will be
spending yours with Grévil.
Do you... really want that?
No, of course I don't.
Simply being around a guy
with hair as ridiculous as his
will be embarrassing.
[gasps]
How did I let things
end up like this?
Yes, your pursuit of justice has
committed us both to suffering.
And yet, I think...
[VICTORIQUE]
...going outside would be nice.
If only for a bit.
[VICTORIQUE]
I'll prepare for the journey.
What do you mean
"you'll prepare"?
You realize the
weekend doesn't start
for another few days, right?
There's no point.
[KAZUYA]
Hold on!
Hey, we're not
allowed to use that!
[VICTORIQUE]
This elevator is reserved
for staff, faculty, and myself.
You, on the other hand,
can enjoy the feeling of your
thighs turning to noodles
while you suffer your way down
the endless flight of stairs.
Now, good day!
[KAZUYA gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Victorique!
Okay...
Could you explain to me
why you would need
all of this for
a one-night stay?
It's simple.
After utilizing all of my
significant intelligence,
I concluded this would be
the bare minimum of my needs.
[KAZUYA] But, can you
even carry all of this?
No, that's obviously your job.
[gasps]
How dare you root through
--a lady's things!
--A compass?
There will be one
on board the yacht.
Now...
You won't need a life jacket.
Or this many clothes.
[gasps]
What is this dinner set for?
Or this basket?
Really? Are you a refugee?
I told you I need them,
so put them back now!
[KAZUYA] How long are
you gonna keep pouting?
It had to be done, okay?
[VICTORIQUE chuckles]
[KAZUYA]
She's acting as if she's never
been on a train before.
[KAZUYA]
Seeing her this way...
She really is like a doll.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
What are you doing?
[KAZUYA gasps]
Uh, well, uh...
It's something we
do for fun in Japan.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[chuckles]
What's that over there?
--[CHILD] Faster! Faster!
--[KAZUYA] An ice-cream stand?
And there?
[KAZUYA]
A... newspaper stand.
Come on, we have to hurry
or we're going to be late.
--[whistles]
--[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Hop on in.
[VICTORIQUE] It's like magic the
way you summoned your servant!
[DRIVER  gasps]
[KAZUYA] You don't get out very
often, do you, Victorique?
[VICTORIQUE]
Hmph.
Ahoy! Maties.
[KAZUYA]
Uh... That outfit is--
[BLOIS]
Great, right?
I am a true man of the sea.
Oh, and about the case...
The first shot in the room
next door was fired into...
...a hand mirror.
Such a waste.
That's weird.
Interesting.
But why the Magic Mirror?
Also, your culprit,
the Arabian maid, was...
...gorgeous.
Ahem!
The explanation of her motive
was truly puzzling, indeed.
She said it was revenge
for the... box.
Revenge for the box?
[KAZUYA]
Huh.
[COP]
Inspector!
I just received word
from the home office!
The Arabian maid has escaped!
[GROUP gasps]
No! How could she?
Hey! Kujo!
Watch the boat for me!
I'll be back!
You can get on it,
but do not take it out!
Aw... But that's no fun at all!
Too bad!
Later!
That jerk.
We came all the way here.
What now, should we get on--
Hm?
Victorique?
[KAZUYA]
Hey!
Where'd you go?
Oh! There you are!
[VICTORIQUE]
Question.
This yacht belonged
to the fortune-teller,
Roxane, correct?
[KAZUYA]
Yeah.
I found this invitation.
It's addressed to her.
Read it for me.
All right then.
Let's see.
"Please join us for
dinner this weekend
on the luxury liner
moored on the coast.
A box garden evening..."
[gasps]
"And the main dish
will be hare"?
[VICTORIQUE]
The fortune-teller kept hares.
And the term "box garden
evening" is too similar
to the maid's "revenge for
the box" to be coincidence.
[KAZUYA] I'd have to
agree with you there.
So, what should we do?
[VICTORIQUE]
What do you want to do?
[KAZUYA]
Let's check it out.
[VICTORIQUE]
Words worthy of a reaper.
[KAZUYA] We end up on the
luxury liner without a hitch.
But... Huh?!
I don't get any dinner?!
[VICTORIQUE squeals]
♪ High-quality meat is
the best meat there is! ♪