[VICTORIQUE]
The white knight diligently
protects his king again,
as they move slowly
towards a victory.
But... I can see that the
black rook is covered in ash.
This will bring unexpected
changes to the chessboard.
[RUPERT]
We have received word that
the Germans have begun
their invasion Poland.
As for us, we won't
be following them.
Thanks to the efforts of
the Academy of Sciences
chairman, Jupiter Roger.
We have decided to keep the
citizens of Saubure here at home
where we know they will be safe.
There's no reason
for our country
to involve itself in this war.
May the light of peace shine
in from all our windows.
[applause]
No one would deny how truly
splendid Roger's work
has been for our kingdom.
That's what makes
it such a pity.
[RUPERT]
Hm?
I hate to tell you this, but
he hasn't really been working
to shelter our country
from this new storm.
The truth is that he's been
pushing his own personal agenda.
[RUPERT]
Now Blois, what do--
[MARQUIS]
I'm sure you know about
the fabled Kingdom of
Saillune, don't you?
--[ROGER gasps]
--Get to the point.
[OFFICIAL A]
Did he say Saillune?
[OFFICIAL B] I hate those
wretched Gray Wolves
with a passion.
[VICTORIQUE]
This is where white,
which had the overwhelming
advantage, stumbles.
Before they have a chance to
react, the bishop strikes.
[MARQUIS]
The Kingdom of Saillune is home
to those terrible Gray Wolves
who use their
intelligence against us.
Saubure has been hunting
them down for centuries.
That's why the remaining Wolves
still hold a grudge
against our country.
Bring it to me.
Their people have a custom
where each one of them
keeps a memento box.
Inside this box are the owner's
most precious keepsakes.
It belongs to a man born in the
village of the Gray Wolves,
which makes him a
descendant of Saillune.
Isn't that right?
If I'm not mistaken,
this belongs to you...
...Jupiter Roger.
--[RUPERT] Roger?
--[OFFICIAL C] He can't be.
--Is... this true?
--[CROWD murmuring]
[MARQUIS]
He deceived the former king
by hiding the truth
about his past.
This allowed him full
access to the palace,
where he ingratiated
himself to the court,
and was eventually
promoted to President
of the arrogant
Academy of Sciences.
But it was all just a
part of a greater plan
to take control of Saubure
in order to revive the
Kingdom of Saillune.
Here's the proof: A contract
outlining the Wolves' intentions
to overthrow our government...
...signed by Jupiter Roger.
[chuckles]
--[CROWD murmuring]
--[ROGER gasps]
[MARQUIS]
You said it's "peace" you want.
But this war will influence
which countries control
the majority of the world.
If we don't get involved in
this war, Saubure will lose
all of its power and will be
wiped completely off the map.
That's what our friend Roger
is hoping will happen.
--[ROGER gasps]
--[RUPERT] Please tell me
this isn't true!
Answer me, Roger!
Majesty... I can explain.
[CROWD gasps, murmur]
[glass shatters]
[OFFICIAL E]
The traitor has escaped!
So he really is a Gray Wolf!
[MAN C]
We'll send out a search party.
No need. A Wolf who's
had his fangs ripped out
will die of hunger soon enough.
[chuckles]
[VICTORIQUE]
The chessboard has spoken.
[clack]
The scuffle in the box
garden is now over.
[clack]
[VICTORIQUE] The stage for
the next game will be...
[clack]
--[planes whirring]
--[CITIZENS murmuring]
Hey, where do you think
those planes are coming from?
The army's here!
--[honking]
--[tires screeching]
[MALE CITIZEN C]
Get out of the road!
[MALE CITIZEN D]
Do you want to die?
My son! Honey?
[gasps]
[MALE CITIZEN E]
What's their deal?
[MALE CITIZEN F]
They must have an urgent order.
--[CHILD crying]
--[WOMAN] Baby!
Don't you ever let go
of that hand again.
[WOMAN]
Huh...?
[CORDELIA]
Never let go of your child.
[CORDELIA] If you lost him,
you would lose your own soul.
Sweet Cordelia,
I hope you know that I--
I will always protect
you, I promise.
[CORDELIA] And I must be
there to protect Victorique.
[ROSCOE A] Your Wolf pup
is being held prisoner
in the palace's dungeon.
[ROSCOE A]
There's no way we can reach her.
[CORDELIA] I can't just stand
back and let her be killed.
My daughter is my everything.
[CORDELIA]
We'll find a way in.
[CÉCILE]
This stinks.
Are you going to be heading
back home to England as well?
[AVRIL]
I am.
All right!
This is our last class.
Let's make it the best one ever!
Now, who can answer
this problem?
Raise your hand if you can!
Really? No one?
I'll have to call
on someone then!
You! Get up here, Avril!
[AVRIL gasps]
[chuckles]
[RIOTER]
Monstre Charmant!
[RIOTERS] Monstre Charmant!
They want the
Monstre Charmant?
I heard the Ministry
of the Occult
has her locked away
inside a dungeon.
[MALE CITIZEN H] That's what
has them all riled up?
It's just an old fairy tale.
Excuse me.
Please come over here
where it's safe.
[MALE CITIZEN G] Those people
are a bunch of lunatics!
Kujo, Victorique...
I hope you two are safe.
[BLOIS] I'm here on behalf of
the Ministry of the Occult,
to ask for the police
department's assistance,
Superintendent
General Signore.
So you're the Ministry of
the Occult's lapdog now.
Disappointing.
--[door opens]
--[footsteps]
[JACQUELINE]
Grévil!
Hello, Jacqueline.
You lied to me and sent that
boy back to his country!
How could you trick
him like that?
I know you're not
that kind of person.
Why did you do it?
[BLOIS]
As the Marquis' oldest son,
it is my duty to carry
out my father's plan.
[BLOIS]
But still...
[knocking]
[RUPERT]
Who's there?
[door opens]
[RUPERT]
Oh. It's you.
I just informed
the German messenger
that we've accepted their terms
and will fight alongside
them as allies.
Soon the whole world
will have no choice
but to recognize Saubure
as a powerful nation.
What's the use?
[scoffs]
[RUPERT] My subjects are
crying in the streets.
Building our kingdom up at a
time like this feels wrong.
But here I am, forcing
innocent people to fight
and die in a war
I don't even support.
Causing families
to be torn apart.
What kind of king does that?
[MARQUIS]
I know you've done worse.
[RUPERT gasps]
Let's not forget...
..the night you couldn't
control your pride and jealousy,
the night you to murdered
the woman you loved.
[RUPERT gasps]
[RUPERT panting]
[MARQUIS] We're both aware
of what kind of king you are.
No matter how hard you try,
the blood on your hands
can never be washed off.
So why not stain them
with a little more?
But this time you won't be
murdering someone in cold blood
to fulfill your own
black desires.
These deaths are necessary for
the survival of our kingdom.
[RUPERT]
You're right.
I won't deny it.
I did kill for love.
[MARQUIS] And now you'll
kill for your country.
[MORELLA] As we speak,
armies from various countries
are assembling in Saubreme
and preparing for battle.
[CARMILLA] Research shows that
over 80% of noble families
support our cause.
[MARQUIS]
Who are they?
[MORELLA]
Volunteer soldiers.
[CARMILLA] The return of the
Monstre Charmant has hundreds
devoting themselves to her
and racing to be the first
one into the palace.
[CARMILLA]
They're each hoping to become
the young lady's new heart.
[MARQUIS] Why in the world
would they want to do that?
Capturing the beautiful
monster alive
is the only way to
obtain her power.
[RIOTERS] Monstre Charmant!
Monstre Charmant!
[MARQUIS] The people are
certain of Saubure's victory.
That's why more of them are
leaning in favor of war.
Unbeknownst to them,
the entire country now serves
the Ministry of the Occult.
The Monstre Charmant has
one more part to play
before she's of no use to me.
[VICTORIQUE] The white queen
makes her way to the east.
But the black knight
anticipated this move.
[door opens]
[MARQUIS]
Monstre Charmant.
The treaty with Germany
has been finalized.
Who do they plan
on invading next?
Saubure? The entire world?
The strategy is laid out
on that chessboard of yours.
Now, tell me their next move!
[VICTORIQUE]
You can't even be bothered
to offer a proper hello.
Such a boor.
[MARQUIS]
I took the time to collect
all of the books you
requested, didn't I?
This place has become no
different from the library tower
of which you were so fond.
[VICTORIQUE]
You're right.
Every book that I asked for
was brought down to
this new prison of mine.
And a wise man from your
past has told me everything.
[VICTORIQUE] He even told
me about your schemes.
[MARQUIS]
Who did?
[VICTORIQUE] Leviathan's
memoir went into detail
about a certain dream of yours.
The one where you create
an army of homunculi
to fight your battles for you.
And now it looks like you've
finally made that happen...
...Marquis.
As a young man, you
believed wholeheartedly
in the alchemist
Leviathan's powers.
In fact, your deepest desire
was to harness his strength.
But Leviathan's so-called
alchemy turned out to be
nothing more than a trick.
[VICTORIQUE] You were the
only one to discover the truth
about his treachery.
And it shook everything
you believed in.
[VICTORIQUE]
It made you question
whether the occult held
any real power at all.
[VICTORIQUE] But you decided
not to give up on them yet.
The country kept dancing
to Leviathan's lies.
And they continued to
expend a great deal of gold
and military power
because of him.
That's when you realized
the occult's true power.
It has the ability to
move people's hearts.
Shut up, you!
I won't hear any more
of your slander--
[gasps]
Your new goal was
to create puppets
that would dance just for you.
The same way you used to
dance as a naïve scholar...
...when Leviathan
pulled the strings.
That's how you
finally got homunculi.
And now, they've gathered
as your own little army.
Like pawns in your hands,
anxiously awaiting
their next move.
It's no surprise that you
now believe in the power
of the occult more than anyone.
[VICTORIQUE]
For it indeed has the power
to enchant people's hearts...
...with deception.
Impressive logic.
My plan for this country
has been put in motion.
I'm now the one in charge.
The Academy of Sciences
has been driven out
and King Rupert has
become my pawn as well.
His kingdom is overflowing
with my homunculi.
And don't forget
that you are also
under my control, Gray Wolf.
[VICTORIQUE whimpering]
Your blood tastes
exactly the same as mine.
You're my creation.
Just another homunculus
I made to do my bidding.
Your entire life belongs to me.
Your blood...
Your flesh...
And of course, your
wellspring of wisdom.
[yelps]
[MARQUIS] You exist only to be
a tool that I alone can use.
[VICTORIQUE]
Just like at the library tower,
there are thousands of
books here for me to read,
and so much knowledge
to be consumed.
But... you're not here...
...my knight.
[door closes]
[SOPHIE]
You done yet?
[CÉCILE]
Uh?
Sophie... L-Look what I found!
Those look pretty sweet.
[CÉCILE]
They really aren't.
I don't have a job anymore.
[SOPHIE] You can stay
with me for a while.
I've got plenty of room.
[CÉCILE]
Thanks.
When this stupid war is over.
I have to find those kids
and make sure they're okay!
I have to.
[SOPHIE]
You're one heck of a teacher.
I'll help you any way I can!
[CÉCILE]
Deal.
I'm so worried.
I hope they're safe,
wherever they are.
[SUPERIOR]
Are you daydreaming again?!
--[thud]
--[KAZUYA groans]
[SUPERIOR]
Listen up.
I don't care if you're
the son of an officer.
Here, you're just a soldier
like everyone else!
All of you need
to remember that!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[SUPERIOR]
Dismissed!
[BOY]
Need help?
[KAZUYA]
Thank you.
[BOY] That guy's kind
of a pompous jerk.
[KAZUYA]
It's okay.
I'm used to unreasonable people
being mad at me all of the time.
[KAZUYA]
Dear Victorique...
[SUPERIOR]
Fire!
[KAZUYA] I'm up north
completing my basic training.
Even though we're
far apart right now,
I'll never forget you.
Because...
...I always keep it close to me.
[SUPERIOR]
What's that around your neck?
[KAZUYA gasps]
--Stop! Give it back!
--Consider this confiscated.
What a ridiculous piece of junk.
Damn you!
I won't let you take this!
[SUPERIOR]
What did you say to me?!
--[KAZUYA groans]
--[blows hit]
[hitting continue]
[SUPERIOR panting]
I'm sorry, sir.
I can't... give this... to you.
It's important... to me.
[SUPERIOR growls]
[thud]
[footsteps]
[door creaks, slams]
[KAZUYA]
I managed to hold on to the ring
you gave me before I left.
[KAZUYA]
It gives me power.
The strength to carry on.
[VICTORIQUE]
This pendant gives me power.
The strength to carry on.
[VICTORIQUE]
No matter how far apart we are.
Even when you're not by my side.
[VICTORIQUE]
I feel you near.
[door opens]
[footsteps]
Look at this.
He sent his son this time.
Everything about you
now resembles Father,
from your footsteps
to the way you smell.
Tomorrow is the inauguration.
The Ministry of the Occult
is making Albert de Blois
the Prime Minister of Saubure.
That's when you'll make your
first public appearance.
Now put this on.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[door creaks, slams]
[VICTORIQUE]
The Monstre Charmant outfit
I wore at Christmas was dazzling
in a pretty shade of purple.
But this new dress...
It's black.
A bad omen.
[VICTORIQUE] But hopefully
this... will protect me.
[KAZUYA] As long as
you have this pendant,
I'll always come to save you.
[knocking]
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[KAZUYA]
I'm always by your side.
[MARQUIS]
Another storm is upon us,
with a much larger reach
than the previous war.
Right now, the citizens of this
nation have to band together,
or Europe and all its history
will be completely destroyed.
Many countries will falter.
But Saubure is different;
we have the power to survive.
Today, I stand before
you in celebration of
our country's promised future.
And there's no doubt
that we do have one.
The upcoming battle
will be glorious.
For even if we
sustain heavy losses,
we know for a fact that
victory will not be far behind.
What our enemies don't know
is that we have the all-powerful
Monstre Charmant on our side!
[CROWD cheers]
[LISTENER A]
Monstre Charmant!
[LISTENER B]
[LISTENERS] Monstre Charmant!
Monstre Charmant!
[chanting continues]
Listen to me.
I've made no such
promise of victory.
[microphone screeches]
[VICTORIQUE]
A promise is a sacred thing.
It can only exist between
hearts and souls
that truly respect
and cherish each other.
It means nothing without that.
Despite what this man says,
your country has no
promise of a future.
What it has instead...
...is Albert, who lied to you
and signed a contract
guaranteeing destruction!
How dare you!
It's been quite a while...
...Albert de Blois.
[MARQUIS gasps]
Mama, don't!
You have to take me back!
She's risking her life
because of me!
[ROSCOE B]
That's right!
She had to save you.
And now Cordelia might...
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
What are you doing
here, Gray Wolf?!
[CORDELIA] I didn't know if
you'd remember me, Albert.
But I haven't
forgotten you either.
Or the floor of
that tower of yours.
The floor in there was so cold
that it froze me
through to my heart!
[MARQUIS growls]
[CORDELIA]
My body has never recovered
and remains frozen still.
I need to be warmed up.
Get my blood flowing again.
And prepare my
child's first bath.
For that, I must have flame!
[LISTENER C]
Fire!
[screaming]
[MARQUIS]
Curse you!
I should have finished you off
a long time ago, evil Gray Wolf!
[CORDELIA]
I won't let you
play games with my daughter
anymore, you monster!
[yells]
[MARQUIS chuckles]
[CORDELIA growls]
[ROSCOE B]
Your mother...
...knew the only way protect you
was to take your
place on that stage.
[ROSCOE B]
In order to help Cordelia,
my other half went to
the palace as well.
He chose to fight for her.
Neither of us give
a damn about you.
But Cordelia said she'd rather
kill herself than ever lose you.
He couldn't bear to see her cry.
And she would cry!
Without shedding a single tear.
Or letting herself
sob in front of us.
--But...
--[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[yelps]
[ROSCOE B]
...I'm not like my brother.
I'll cut off the source
of Cordelia's tears.
Right here and now...
...I'll kill you!
[thud]
Cor-- Cor--
[ROSCOE A]
Cordelia!
[MARQUIS screams]
[pants]
[CORDELIA gasps]
[CORDELIA]
The flames... keep burning.
They burn...
...and clearly illuminate...
...my daughter's future.
[VICTORIQUE] On the morning's
calm water, I saw us together.
[KAZUYA]
Your flowing hair...
...glowing with
an eternal light...
[VICTORIQUE] I have someone
I can always count on.
[KAZUYA]
I write your name...
...on something certain.
--[VICTORIQUE] Kujo.
--[KAZUYA] Victorique.