[AVRIL]
Once upon a time,
in the heart of Saubure's
capital city, Saubreme.
[GIRL sighs] Wow, I wish I
could have a dress like that.
[MANNEQUIN]
Why don't you come inside then?
--I can help you.
--[GIRL] Huh?
[MANNEQUIN chuckles]
[AVRIL]
Little did she know
that the moment she entered
the department store...
--[AVRIL screams]
--[KAZUYA screams]
[laughs]
--Oh, I got you so good!
--[sighs]
Little 'Fraidy Cat Kujo!
Well, of course I'll react
if you shout like that!
--Come on, sheesh.
--[AVRIL] Huh?
Looks like you're
about to go shopping!
Yeah. My sister back home
asked if I could send
her a few things.
Let's see.
She lists three white,
cotton blouses.
Then, a separate plaid collar,
warm shoes and socks,
a glass pen and
lastly, a blue rose.
I've never even
heard of a blue rose.
[AVRIL]
You've got to be kidding.
May I present, the blue rose.
Ta-da!
It's a blue diamond.
The national treasure
of the royal family.
But it was stolen
during the last war,
so nobody knows
where it ended up.
[KAZUYA]
Huh.
Your sister probably meant
that she wants a replica of it.
There's a department
store called Jeantan
that sells glass,
blue rose paperweights.
Thanks for the tip.
Aww... But I'm a little jealous.
I wish I could go
shopping in Saubreme.
But, as long as you're going,
you should borrow this
book of ghost stories!
[KAZUYA]
Uh... Great, thank you.
[AVRIL]
By the way, you never told me
what your sister sent you!
[KAZUYA gasps]
That's right!
I better go-- I need
to visit Victorique.
Avril, thanks for all of your
help with my sister's letter.
See you later!
Wait a minute, who in
the world is Victorique?
[VICTORIQUE groans]
I'm bored, I'm bored, I'm bored,
I'm bored, I'm bored, so bored!
If something doesn't
happen soon, I'll--
[KAZUYA panting]
Hey. Sorry I'm so late.
Did you hear the news?
I'm going to Saubreme tomorrow
to pick up some souvenirs for--
[VICTORIQUE]
You'll do no such thing.
By tomorrow, you must be
embroiled in a mysterious,
bizarre incident with which
you'll desperately
need assistance.
[KAZUYA]
A-Are you kidding?
--No way!
--No need to worry.
You know I'll solve
it immediately,
once I put my mind to it.
But at least I won't be bored.
[KAZUYA growls]
Oh! That's right.
[KAZUYA]
Here. A present.
That'll distract you for a bit.
A present?
It had better not be another
one of those baffling--
[gasps]
It's so pretty!
They're clothes from my country.
I told my sister all
about you in a letter,
so she wanted to
send them as a gift.
If nothing else,
I thought they might
make some good pajamas for you.
Want 'em?
I do!
[KAZUYA chuckles]
I'm glad you like them.
You had me worried for a second.
I should probably show you
how to tie the obi though.
It can be a little--
I don't need your
help figuring it out.
You should know that nothing is
beyond my wellspring of wisdom.
You must be joking.
Let me show you, okay?
Look at that, I appear
to be reading a book.
If you don't have
any cases for me,
then leave that here
and get out of my sight.
You're no use to me.
All right... I guess.
If that's what you want,
I do have a few things to
take care of before my trip.
So, good luck with these.
Sorry to bother you.
[VICTORIQUE growls]
[sighs] Pretty!
And it's all mine!
[VICTORIQUE]
♪ New clothes, new clothes! ♪
♪ I... love...
new... clothes... ♪
[hums]
♪ Clothes from Kujo. ♪
[humming continues]
Didn't he say that
these were pajamas?
He's really such an idiot.
Is this a belt?
No, there's no buckle.
A ribbon?
But it's way too long.
Utter chaos.
[KAZUYA]
"The Devil-Worshipping Vagrants.
They kidnap children for
their sacrifices, and--"
What the?! "Hang them up
inside of their clothing"?
What kind of ending is that?
[laughs] These stories
are preposterous.
[VICTORIQUE snoring]
[groans]
[yawns]
Good morning, Miss Cécile!
[CÉCILE]
Morning, Kujo!
You have perfect timing.
I was looking-- [yelps]
[whimpers]
Are you all right?
Can't find my glasses...
Help me.
Here you go.
You sure you're okay?
[CÉCILE] I'll be fine!
You're such a gentleman.
Thank you, Kujo.
Oh! But there's
no time for that!
I need you to listen and
try not to be alarmed.
Something's wrong
with Victorique!
[gasps]
[sneezes]
[door opens]
[CÉCILE]
Here.
It's a message from Kujo.
[KAZUYA] Victorique, I'm sorry
to hear you caught a cold.
You must feel pretty stupid.
This is how you tie
an obi , by the way.
--[VICTORIQUE growls]
--[CÉCILE] He sent this, too.
I bet you could use it to
keep your boredom at bay.
Kujo went all the way to the
dorm just to get it for you.
[VICTORIQUE sneezes]
[CÉCILE laughs]
Huh. I didn't know she
had a house out here.
[door opens]
[KAZUYA]
How is she?
[CÉCILE]
Well, her face is bright red.
And she's sneezing a lot.
"Idiot"?!
Oh, my!
That ungrateful...
You're the idiot,
do you hear me?
Mean girls like you
shouldn't even get presents!
I'm leaving! Bye!
Get presents?
[door opens, closes]
[VICTORIQUE]
Hi, Cécile. Is Kujo leaving?
[CÉCILE]
Yeah...
He says he's going to Saubreme.
He has some things he
needs to buy, I think.
[VICTORIQUE]
He's really going now?
I guess he couldn't be bothered
to wait for me to go with him.
That selfish brat.
[sneezes]
--[door opens]
--[BLOIS] Excuse me.
Are these seats taken--? Uh!
Oh. It's you.
Little Squirrel.
What a surprise.
The police headquarters
in Saubreme has asked me
to lend my assistance
with a particular case.
It's rumored that several
priceless works of art,
which were stolen
during the war,
have been showing up on the
black market there lately.
And so, of course,
the higher-ups...
[KAZUYA] I really hope that
Victorique is feeling better
and resting well, now.
[KAZUYA]
She's such a tiny little thing.
She's bossy...
And hot tempered,
and a bit of a devil.
But for some reason, I can't
help caring about her.
[KAZUYA]
And...
I know she cares for me, too.
Your two hearts are connected.
And always will be.
[KAZUYA] She risked her
life to save me that night.
She seemed so afraid.
And as if that wasn't enough,
I've also been informed there's
been a series of disappearances.
Young women and children
keep vanishing.
They go out shopping,
and then all of a sudden,
--they're gone.
--[KAZUYA] Why?
Why, of all people, did it have
to be you here with me today?
Well, my sentiments,
exactly! Hmph!
Careful out there, Squirrel.
Don't let yourself
get swallowed up
by the dark, scary metropolis.
I'll be fine.
--[DRIVER grunts]
--[horse neighs]
[LUIGI]
Sauburean.
Italian.
Sauburean. Swiss.
[LUIGI]
Chinese?
[KAZUYA]
So, this is Jeantan...
[gulps]
Well, here I am.
Where are the blue roses?
[CLERK]
Hello, sir.
If I may ask, where're
you visiting from?
[KAZUYA]
Oh! Sure.
I'm from the East.
Blue Roses can be
found on the top floor.
Shall I show you the way now?
No thanks. I'm pretty
sure I've got it.
--[elevator dings]
--[doors rattle]
[KAZUYA]
I think...
This is where he said to go.
[KAZUYA]
Excuse me?
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
There it is!
[GARNIER]
Who's there?!
[gasps]
[GARNIER]
Hey! Kid! Who're you?
[KAZUYA]
Just a patron!
[GARNIER]
What are you doing in here?
I heard this was where
I could buy a Blue Rose.
[GARNIER gasps]
[GARNIER grunts]
Paperweights are in Stationary
on the second level.
On your way, then, young man.
Yes, sir, but--
I'm sorry to disturb you.
[GARNIER] Even if he does match
the description we were given,
no one would send a child
as their messenger.
Tell our men on the lower floor.
Yes, of course. Right away, sir.
And make the
arrangements at once.
[sighs]
Shame on me.
The third son of
an imperial soldier
shouldn't engage in shenanigans
like eavesdropping.
However...
[KAZUYA] That beautiful
woman intrigued me.
Her expression...
It was so cold.
She reminded me of a mannequin.
[KAZUYA]
Oh, no!
This must be the
service elevator.
I need to go back up--
--[thud]
--[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Hello? Is someone down here?
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Mannequins?
[gulps]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[KAZUYA]
Okay, she's one of them, too.
Wait a minute,
something's isn't--
Why is she the only
mannequin with closed eyes?
--[ANASTASIA gasps]
--[KAZUYA screams]
[gasping]
A devil! There's a devil!
So many...
They're coming for us!
We're going to die!
Miss, please, you
have to calm down!
You shouldn't be in
a place like this.
I'll call someone from
the store right away!
[ANASTASIA]
No! The police!
--You have to call the police!
--[KAZUYA yelps]
[groans]
Okay, that hurt-- [gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Hello? Miss?
[BLOIS] Well? Is that
all you have to say?
Yes. Please send some
officers to Jean--
[BLOIS] I've had quite
enough of this nonsense.
As you might've guessed,
we're extremely busy.
Inspector! There's a girl
there who's in trouble!
She told me to call
the police to get help!
This is a solid case!
--You have to believe me!
--[yawns]
--Superintendent General!
--[BLOIS gasps]
Welcome.
Grévil!
It's been quite a while.
You haven't been by the house
to see us in such a long time.
Jacqueline can't help
worrying, you know.
Yes, well, it's just that
I've been so busy that I--
[SIGNORE]
I've heard of your fine work.
I have high hopes
that your unique gifts
will be a tremendous asset to us
in breaking this
art smuggling case.
--Look alive there, boy!
--[gasps]
Come on!
[KAZUYA]
Yes... sir!
[BLOIS]
Pardon us, this is urgent.
Right. Of course.
[KAZUYA]
I'm grateful for the help,
but why did you suddenly
change your mind?
You said it yourself,
didn't you?
It sounds like there's something
mysterious going on at Jeantan.
And it's important for me
to meet the expectations
being placed on me.
Especially now.
--[BLOIS] So?
--[KAZUYA] Okay.
The first thing I did was ask
that gentleman over there
where they sell the
Blue Rose paperweights.
I'm sorry to say, I've never
seen this young man before.
[KAZUYA gasps]
But it was just a little while
ago, don't you remember?
You asked where I was from--
[BLOIS]
What are you playing at, Kujo?
[GARNIER]
Is there a problem, gentlemen?
I'm Garnier, the owner,
and I'm glad to help.
How can I be of
assistance today?
Sir. We met earlier upstairs.
I had gotten lost, and--
[GARNIER]
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Well, in the room
on the top floor,
behind the big, oak door,
there were these...
glass cases, and they had--
[GARNIER]
Can you explain to me
what this Oriental
boy is talking about?
Well, uh...
The door was oak.
And the paper was brown.
And there were black and
white tiles on the floor
in a checkerboard pattern.
Take me to that room, please.
It's important that I
prove to the inspector
that I'm telling the truth.
Fine.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Boy...
No way. It can't be.
Satisfied now, young man?
[KAZUYA]
This is it.
There was a girl in here.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
A mannequin?
But I know she
was in this crate.
[BLOIS] What is the
meaning of this, Kujo?
[GARNIER laughs]
You mean, this poor
kid actually mistook
a mannequin for a person?
I've seen it all.
Waste of my time.
No, you're wrong!
You have to believe me!
There really was a girl here!
She even spoke to me!
--[BLOIS] I'm too busy for this.
--Find her. She can't have
--gotten very far.
--Right.
[gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
Bored.
[thunder claps]
I'm so bored.
It'll be the death
of me at this rate.
Could someone... bring
me a book or something?
Please, save me...
[gasps]
What'd you say?
Do you need something?
[CÉCILE]
Oh dear, your fever's worse.
I'm afraid you'll need a shot.
[VICTORIQUE]
No!
You can't make me!
I'm never coming out of here!
My goodness.
It'll be over quickly
if you don't fight!
[VICTORIQUE]
I hate this!
Why can't you be like Kujo?
He always does what
I sa-ah--! [sneezes]
Kujo, you big fool.
Why aren't you back yet?
Surely, there's no way
he could've actually
gotten himself involved
in a case, is there?
[sneezes]
[groans]
[BLOIS]
Give me a break, Squirrel!
None of the clerks
saw you there!
The room you claim you
went to doesn't exist!
Neither does the girl,
for that matter.
[KAZUYA] Inspector!
I swear, I wouldn't lie!
I don't want to
hear another word.
Go finish up your shopping
and head back home.
I don't get what's
going on in this city.
--[OLD WOMAN grunts]
--[KAZUYA yelps]
My daughter...
My daughter, she was eaten up!
[KAZUYA]
She what?!
She was eaten...
by that place, there!
My daughter, she was
eaten by that place!
She's there, inside!
Please help me! Please!
[KAZUYA]
The way she's dressed...
It's like the
picture in the book.
The devil-worshipping kidnapper.
--[OLD WOMAN grunts]
--[KAZUYA screams]
[LUIGI]
Nine hundred and fifty-seven.
[OLD WOMAN gasps]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[LUIGI]
Come on! Leave him alone.
You know they're
gonna come back.
Who are you?
I'll be taking one of
these, okay, Chinese?
[chuckles] Hey, let's cooperate.
I was thinking I could
tell you something useful.
Yeah?
At about 11:50 today...
A group of men went in
the back door of Jeantan.
And they had an awful
lot of cargo with 'em.
--[KAZUYA] Like what?
--Well...
Tin cans of paint
and some carpeting.
And big rolls of some kind
of fancy golden paper.
[gasps] Interior decorators!
That means while I was
off talking to the police,
they were busy changing
that room's décor!
[LUIGI]
Yep!
So, I can have one
of these now, right?
[KAZUYA]
What's going on?
It's obvious something weird
is happening at Jeantan.
But what could it be?
You know I'll solve
it immediately,
once I put my mind to it.
But at least I won't be bored.
Hey. I need to ask
you one more thing.
[LUIGI]
Hm?
Are there any public
phones around here?
I said I don't like pain, okay?
But the pain is why
it works, my dear.
[VICTORIQUE]
You're a liar! [sneezes]
Now. Hold out your arm, please.
There's a telephone
call for you, Victorique.
That's unexpected.
Who would call me?
[CÉCILE]
Go ahead.
[KAZUYA]
Hello? Hello?
Oh, Kujo!
[KAZUYA sighs]
You finally answered!
Victorique, there's
an emergency!
I need you to focus
and listen to me.
The truth is, I really
need your help.
[VICTORIQUE yelps]
[KAZUYA]
"Gyick"? Who's Gyick?
Victorique, stop
playing around--
[screams]
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Hey, Kujo?
He hung up.
What on earth's
going on around here?
[VICTORIQUE] ♪ I do not
like get-ting shots! ♪
♪ No, I don't,
don't like shots! ♪
[KAZUYA] Sure sounds
like she's having fun.
[VICTORIQUE]
♪ No, I don't ♪