[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[VICTORIQUE] I've seen so many
people die in my lifetime.
None of those deaths
ever moved me.
I felt no sadness,
or remorse, or anger.
Because I wasn't
I afraid of death.
[VICTORIQUE]
But... Now I...
[gasps]
[ROSCOE B]
It's over.
Spare me.
Please, I beg you.
[ROSCOE B]
Hmph.
[VICTORIQUE]
I'll do anything.
Take any humiliation.
Just let me live.
How pathetic.
I thought a Gray Wolf backed
into a corner would put up more
--of a struggle.
--[VICTORIQUE] I want...
...to live!
Mama saved me.
And then I met Kujo.
After all that...
...I've learned what fear is.
[ROSCOE B gasps]
I may be pathetic.
But I've found something
more important than pride.
So please!
I'll protect my
daughter at all costs.
That's the only thing
I have left to live for.
[ROSCOE B]
Stop it!
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[ROSCOE B]
Cordelia! Stop obsessing
over this wretched cub!
[thud]
[ROSCOE B]
Why, Cordelia?
I will. I will protect you!
[ROSCOE B] I'll live on,
so I can be there for you.
[ROSCOE B gasps]
Cordelia!
[ROSCOE B]
Doesn't that mean something?
You should love me for it!
For everything!
[gasps]
No! Let go of that!
[ROSCOE B gasps]
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
Brian...?
[MAN A]
What's that?
[WOMAN A]
My god! He's covered in blood.
[OFFICIAL gasps]
Sir! How'd you get that wound?
I have two tickets here.
'Scuse me.
[OFFICIAL gasps]
H-Hey!
I told you I have tickets!
Let us go!
--[groans]
--[VICTORIQUE] Brian!
Fine, just line up over there.
I'll check your tickets
and papers in a moment.
Understand?
[VICTORIQUE]
Let's go, Brian.
[ROSCOE B]
Why did you save me?
[VICTORIQUE]
I've lost a lot.
I don't want to add to
that if I can help it.
[gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
Grévil...
[ROSCOE B]
Run!
I can barely walk,
but I'll hold them off.
[VICTORIQUE]
I can't do that.
You may despise me,
but you still saved me.
So I'll pay you back.
I swear it.
This time, I'll protect you!
[BLOIS]
You there, half-dead man.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
By any chance, have you seen
a Gray Wolf around here?
[ROSCOE B groans]
[BLOIS] That stubby little cub
is just nowhere to be found.
I've searched every
corner of the city
from the brothels to
the docks and nothing.
Hm... Well, no matter.
If you do happen to
see her, tell her this.
If she wants to run away,
she should get as far
from Saubure as she can.
Of course, with
that mind of hers,
that shouldn't be too difficult.
Farewell.
[VICTORIQUE]
Thank you.
[BLOIS]
Now we're even, Sister.
[SUBORDINATE A]
I'm afraid I have bad news.
[BLOIS]
What is it?
[SUBORDINATE A]
We've just received word.
In Saubreme, the Marquis is...
[BLOIS gasps]
[RUPERT]
Blois's... gone?
[clattering]
[RUPERT grunts, whimpers]
[SUBORDINATE B]
Your Majesty!
Don't leave me.
Please, I beg you.
[sobbing]
Don't leave me
all alone in here!
[MAN B] Move it! The fire's
spreading this way!
[MAN C]
Here, too!
[MAN D]
Run!
[ROSCOE A]
This flame is all consuming.
The place we met...
Saubure...
It's nothing but ash now.
[ROSCOE A]
No...
It's Saillune.
The place we were born.
The place that abandoned us.
[ROSCOE A]
That which still binds us.
Such a tragic kingdom.
[CORDELIA] Live on, my sweet
Victorique, my soul.
As long as you
remain in this world,
I... will never disappear.
[ROSCOE B groans]
Still hurting?
Just hold tight;
I'll bring medicine.
[MAN E] Marquis de Blois of
the Ministry of the Occult
was killed tonight.
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[MAN E]
Apparently, some woman dressed
as the Monstre Charmant did it.
[MAN E]
What a night. It's crazy.
--[rustling]
--Huh?
[VICTORIQUE]
What about her?
Uh...
[VICTORIQUE]
Tell me!
Is Mama-- I-I mean, the woman.
Is she alive?
That's all I know.
Now get off me, will ya?
[ROSCOE B groaning]
[gasps]
What a beautiful color.
In fact...
It's almost as golden and
pure as Victorique's hair.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[planes whirring]
[KAZUYA gasping]
[WOMAN B]
My! How frightening!
[MAN F] It said she's
a young blonde girl
that's actually a
dangerous fugitive.
I hope she didn't
stow away on our boat.
[ROSCOE B groaning]
[VICTORIQUE] It seems
they have wanted posters up.
We're trapped.
It's only a matter of time.
[ROSCOE B groans]
Forget about that for
a moment, Wolf cub.
I need you to listen.
[groans] I don't have long.
The two of us...
My brother and I were not
born of pure Gray Wolf blood.
[ROSCOE B]
Because of that...
...the villagers persecuted us.
We were driven out.
[ROSCOE B] Our own mother
wouldn't protect us.
Too afraid to leave Saillune,
we hated everyone
and everything.
Saillune.
This world.
[ROSCOE B]
But... Cordelia...
Despite the stain of Saillune,
she forged ahead with a smile.
Yes. Just like you
are now, Wolf cub.
[gasps]
[ROSCOE B] Even though
you were forced on her,
she tried desperately
to protect you.
In a way...
It became her reason for living.
To my brother and I, she was
the mother we never had.
We loved her dearly.
I've wanted to kill
you for so long.
If you were gone...
...then Cordelia would
only have the two of us.
She could live for us instead.
We could be a family.
[groans] Yes...
[groans]
Stop it. Save your strength.
[ROSCOE B]
You must live!
[gasps]
Understand?
That was Cordelia's last wish.
[grunts]
Brian...?
[gasps, sobs]
[FEMALE PASSENGER] What a
dreadful time for a funeral.
[MALE PASSENGER]
That poor girl is all alone now.
[DECK HAND A] Apparently the
fugitive has blonde hair,
is fifteen, but looks
to be about ten.
[DECK HAND B]
Excuse me.
Silver?
[gasps]
Huh?
[VICTORIQUE gasps]
[VICTORIQUE]
Is that... me?
And the farting newt.
Miss Cécile.
The tall one with an
ice-cream cone on his head
has to be Grévil.
[VICTORIQUE chuckles]
[VICTORIQUE]
Kujo...
[laughs]
I should have known you'd have
no artistic talent at all.
[DECK HAND C]
We'll be moving out shortly.
Hurry up!
[ROGER]
Excuse me.
[gasps] It's you!
Did you come all this
way to catch me?
[gasps]
[KAZUYA]
For the longest time,
I rebelled against my father and
brothers' militaristic ideals.
[KAZUYA] But after being
drawn into the powerful flow
of history this way,
I started thinking about
what it is I'm fighting for.
[SUPERIOR]
Advance!
[KAZUYA] Of course, I could
just be lying to myself.
But I think I must be
fighting for the people
that are most important to me.
I've realized...
[KAZUYA] The reason I can
feel that way, Victorique,
is because of you.
[KAZUYA] I want to survive
this so I can see you again.
And... when I do make it back,
I want to tell you something
I should have long ago,
but didn't have the courage to.
This place...
...isn't where I end.
I will come back to you.
[VICTORIQUE]
Please, Kujo.
Of them all, you're the
one who mustn't die.
I am my mama's soul.
And you, Kujo...
You're forever my heart.
[groans]
[VICTORIQUE]
If my heart were to perish,
I would perish
right along with it.
[yells]
[KAZUYA]
Tell you what, Victorique.
We'll go outside again
soon, just the two of us.
And then...
...we'll look at the beautiful
light reflected on the ocean.
[VICTORIQUE]
My dear Kujo.
You managed to keep your
promise, didn't you?
You're here with me,
looking at the ocean just
like you said we would.
[KAZUYA]
So heavy...
My body's... so heavy.
[KAZUYA]
What is this?
Where am I?
[KAZUYA]
That's right.
I need...
...to find Victorique.
She's waiting for me.
[KAZUYA]
But...
My legs won't move.
[gasping]
[screams]
[grunting]
Victorique!
[KAZUYA groans]
Victorique...
Where are you?
If I keep going, will I
really find you out here?
Help me.
[KAZUYA]
Your light inspires me.
Guides me.
[LIBRARIAN]
Could you put this book up there
while you're at it?
[AMBROSE]
Sure.
[LIBRARIAN]
You've been working so hard
you've barely had time to rest.
[AMBROSE]
It's okay.
I'm learning so much here,
I don't mind being tired.
Uh-huh...
[LIBRARIAN]
Monstre Charmant?
Burn this one.
I don't want to look at it.
That legend and the
Ministry of the Occult
are to blame for this war.
[JACQUELINE]
Are you okay?
Do you think Grévil
will be angry?
[LUIGI]
I seriously doubt it.
Signore got him his job
with the police again.
Drill-boy's probably overjoyed.
[JACQUELINE]
Still...
I had the wrong idea
about him, you know?
I felt so betrayed, but he
helped Victorique in the end.
You sure he didn't let
her go by accident?
Luigi!
[LUIGI chuckles]
Grévil really hadn't changed
from the man I once knew.
He was still in there, waiting.
[JACQUELINE]
In fact...
That man kind of reminds me of--
Am I dreaming?
[LUIGI gasps]
No, I see it, too!
I think that's really him!
[gasps]
Ciao!
Uh-- Mm...
[chuckles]
[AVRIL]
Kujo... Victorique...
[AVRIL] If a miracle occurs,
and these letters find you,
I hope that you're both happy.
Huh?
[AVRIL gasps]
Oh, come on! Darn it!
[yells]
[knocking]
[RUPERT]
Come in.
[door opens, closes]
[footsteps]
[gasps]
Roger!
How-- Why are you here?!
I merely came to tell you
something important, old friend.
Gray Wolf! After all this,
you presume to call me friend?
How dare you!
[ROGER]
You should know.
You did not kill Queen
Coco all those years ago.
[RUPERT gasps]
Majesty...
That day, on your order,
I made arrangements to
have Queen Coco killed.
I thought it would
earn me your favor.
But when I got there, I saw it.
You chose to kill
the Queen yourself,
in some misguided attempt
to make your love eternal.
It's twisted, really.
[RUPERT] But-- B-But you said
I didn't kill her, right?
[ROGER] The maid hid the Queen
and her child to protect them.
You were so blind
with mad passion,
you didn't notice who she was.
[ROGER]
Such pure love.
[RUPERT growls]
[ROGER]
The exact opposite of yours.
But despite their differences,
they were still love.
[RUPERT gasps]
[RUPERT]
Please, don't go.
[RUPERT] You can rebuild
Saillune, if that's your wish.
But in exchange, I want you
to return to the palace
and work at my side
again for Saubure.
[ROGER gasps]
The age of the Academy
of Science is nearing.
[ROGER] Forgive me,
but you're wrong, Majesty.
It's something else entirely.
[AMBROSE]
The world is changing.
Carriages are
becoming automobiles.
Gas lamps are electric.
Tanks are now bombers.
[gasps]
[AMBROSE]
The war... is finally over.
There he is.
--It's really him!
--Welcome home.
[JAPANESE MAN A crying]
I missed you so much.
Ah! There, there.
[RURI]
Hey, don't start worrying.
He said he'd definitely
be home today.
I'll go ask those soldiers
if they've seen him.
Wait right here.
[gasps]
Sorry, were you bored?
Well, I have a lot of fun
stories to make up for it.
Your hair, it's--
You're late, Reaper
Who Comes in Spring.
Please don't be angry.
I got back to you
as fast as I could.
I'm guessing, you got
my letters after all?
Yeah.
Smart move sending me your
family's address, Kujo.
Once I had it, I used
my wellspring of wisdom
to make my way here.
[KAZUYA]
Victorique...
[VICTORIQUE]
It's okay.
It was enough of a challenge
that I wasn't bored, at least.
I suppose you deserve praise.
Thanks.
[chuckles]
[gasps] Kazuya!
[RURI]
What is she saying?
The English and French
I learned in school
was about as useful as
speaking gibberish to her.
The only things I could tell
were that she was in a bad mood,
and she has an unending
hunger for sweets.
--[CHILD] Pretty!
--[MAN G] That girl...
[WOMAN C]
Wow! What a beautiful foreigner.
[KAZUYA] Your hair really
is pretty that way.
Like snow.
[VICTORIQUE]
I've been through quite a lot.
[KAZUYA]
Yeah. Me too.
But, you know...
I was never afraid.
[VICTORIQUE]
Neither was I.
[KAZUYA]
Because Victorique was always...
[VICTORIQUE]
...Kujo was always beside me...
...and always will be.
[BOTH]
No matter how the world changes,
it will never be enough...
...to tear us apart.