[IZUKU] Beneath our flashy
superhero society
lurks a dark underworld.
Every time we've driven
the villains back,
they've retreated to the
safety of the shadows,
regaining their strength.
Waiting for the perfect
time to strike.
[SHIGARAKI]
The Master is good.
I tried so hard to find out
where those idiots were going,
and he figured it out
in an instant.
Guess he really showed me up.
[KUROGIRI] It was worth
having a team on standby,
then, wasn't it?
Tomura Shigaraki.
[SHIGARAKI]
Hmph. I guess.
[door bell chimes]
[GIRAN] I heard back
from the union today.
You can expect
a delivery tomorrow.
It was thrown together quickly,
so it might not look like much.
But quality is guaranteed.
[KUROGIRI]
I must apologize for making
such an unreasonable request.
Tell me, Shigaraki.
Do you know why
the union accepted
this outlandish order of yours?
'Cause everyone's got
high expectations of you.
If the League of Villains
steps into the light,
then the scum hiding on the
sidelines will follow suit.
And if that happens, it means
brokers like me win big.
We'll be rolling
in new customers.
Crime pays.
[SHIGARAKI]
Oh, yes.
You're gonna be so busy,
you won't be able to keep up.
[GIRAN chuckles]
I'm looking forward to that.
Anyway, thanks.
[SHIGARAKI]
The board is set with my pawns
and their prey.
Finally. Time for the
real game to begin.
[IZUKU]
Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out
some of the world's
greatest heroes.
I'm running toward
my dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[AIZAWA]
Now that you've finished up
your first semester at UA High,
it's time for summer vacation
to officially begin.
However...
Don't think these
will be months of rest
for you heroes-in-the-making.
At this camp,
we'll push you to
go beyond your limits.
You're aiming to
become "Plus Ultra!"
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
I'm so psyched!
I've been looking forward to
this camp all semester, Deku!
Oh, yeah! It's
definitely close, huh?
[IZUKU]
So close!
[OCHACO]
Hey, what's the matter?
I'm just a little hot!
Huh?
[gasps]
[AOYAMA]
Is it because you like him?
Uh. Let's hear it for camp!
[OCHACO, KAMINARI, ASHIDO]
Yeah! Camp! Camp! Camp! Camp!
[IZUKU] Wow. Uraraka and
the others sure are excited.
I heard some of Class A
is taking extra courses.
Does that mean they actually
failed the final exams?
That must be so embarrassing.
Especially since you're
supposed to be
so much better than my class.
All of you must be
wallowing in shame!
Don't mind him!
[IZUKU]
Uh... Heh...
Monoma's scary.
Oh. The rest of Class B!
It's nice to see you outside
of the sports festival.
I guess now we're not
technically rivals.
Time to get on the bus.
[TSUNOTORI, YANAGI]
Okay!
[GIRLS giggling]
[MINETA] The girls of
Class A and Class B.
It's like a buffet
of bombshells!
Dude, get yourself together.
For real.
[TENYA] Attention, Class A,
our bus is here.
Everyone line up
in seating order!
[AIZAWA]
Here's the deal.
We'll be on this bus about
an hour before our first stop.
Make sure you stay focused.
Why aren't we
blastin' some music?
[TENYA]
No one should be standing!
That is a safety hazard!
Please stay seated!
[STUDENTS chattering]
Why do I bother?
Well, I guess this
is the only time
they'll have to fool around.
[TENYA]
Do not open that window!
[KAMINARI]
Finally. I needed off that bus.
[MINETA]
Let me get through, I gotta pee!
[KIRISHIMA] Huh. This isn't
much of a rest area.
[JIRO]
No. And where's Class B?
You don't really think
we stopped here
just so you could stretch
your legs, do you?
[JIRO, OCHACO gasp]
Please, sir, the toilet.
[MANDALAY]
Heya, Eraser!
[AIZAWA]
Long time no see.
Your feline fantasies are here.
Say, "meow."
Purrfectly cute
and catlike girls!
[PIXIE-BOB, MANDALAY]
You can call us
the Wild, Wild Pussycats!
[AIZAWA] These are the
pro heroes you'll be
working with at the
summer training camp.
[IZUKU]
They're a four-person hero team
who specialize in
mountain rescues!
The Pussycats were founded
when we were kids,
--like forever ago!
--[PIXIE-BOB, MANDALAY gasp]
This marks their
12th year working as a--
I'm pretty sure your
math must be off.
I'm 18 at heart.
[IZUKU]
Understood!
[KIRISHIMA, KAMINARI]
That's so sad.
[AIZAWA]
Everyone, say hello.
[STUDENTS]
Hello! Nice to meet you!
[MANDALAY] We own this whole
stretch of land out here.
Everything you can see.
The summer camp
you're staying at
is there at the base
of the mountain.
[STUDENTS]
That's far!
Uh.
Then why did we stop
all the way up here instead?
I'm afraid we both know
the answer to that.
That can't be right.
[SERO laughs nervously]
Um. Back on the bus.
Quick. Let's go.
Good idea. Load up.
The current time is
9:30 in the morning.
If you're fast about it,
you might make it there by noon.
No way. Guys!
Holy crap!
Save yourselves!
Kitties who don't
make it there by 12:30
won't get any lunch.
[AIZAWA] You should
have guessed, students.
The training camp...
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--...has already begun.
[STUDENTS yelping]
[OCHACO]
What the heck?
[IZUKU] She must be
controlling the ground!
[STUDENTS screaming]
[MANDALAY]
Good news!
Since this is private land,
you can use your Quirks
as much as you want to.
You've got three full hours.
You should be able to make it
to the facility in that time.
That is, if you can get
through The Beast's Forest.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[IZUKU]
The Beast's Forest?!
[KAMINARI]
That sounds like a name
right out of a fantasy game.
Why do we keep falling
for Aizawa's little tricks?
I guess there's
no use complaining.
Might as well get going.
[MINETA] I held it.
Didn't spring a single leak.
Now to find a secluded spot.
[BEAST A growling]
[BOTH scream]
We're all gonna die!
[BEAST A roars]
Please calm yourself
my giant friend!
You don't wanna hurt them!
[IZUKU] Koda's power
lets him control animals,
but is this one immune?
[IZUKU gasps]
A dirt clod. I get it.
It's Pixie-Bob's Quirk.
[PIXIE-BOB humming]
[MANDALAY]
Don't you think you've got them
on a pretty crazy
schedule, Eraser?
Yeah.
We're hoping we get an
entire second semester's
worth of knowledge in them here.
That's going to take an
intense amount of work.
But the rewards'll be worth it.
They'll get permits
to use their Quirks
if there's ever an emergency.
And provisional licenses
that will allow them
to work as heroes.
Most importantly, with all
the villainous activity
--we've been tracking...
--[PIXIE-BOB gasps]
...they need to be able
to defend themselves.
[IZUKU]
One For All Full Cowling!
[BEAST A growls]
Recipro burst!
[TENYA grunts]
I'll kill you!
[BEAST A roars]
[IZUKU]
Smash!
[IZUKU grunts]
[AIZAWA] I trust that I can
count on you, Pixie-Bob.
[PIXIE-BOB]
Leave it to me!
Oh, wow, my fur's
standing on end!
You guys took that beast
down in seconds!
It was awesome.
They're relieved.
And I relieved all over myself.
You showed that
thing who's boss.
We're not done.
[BEAST B growling]
[KAMINARI]
Hey, come on.
Don't you think this
is a little unfair?
What now? Do we run?
Not good.
If we don't make it to
the camp fast enough,
then we won't get
anything to eat.
He's right.
We have no choice but to
cut through these woods
using the shortest
possible route.
Ribbit.
All right.
Let's go, Class A!
[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
[SHOJI]
I spot three up ahead.
And two flanking each side.
So seven total. They're coming!
[SERO]
All right. I've got this one!
Sato! Kirishima!
[yells]
[KIRISHIMA yells]
[SATO grunts]
[TOKOYAMI]
Dark Shadow!
[DARK SHADOW]
Got it!
[BEAST D groans]
Aoyama. You're up!
Bonjour!
[BEAST D groans]
Damn it!
If it weren't for
you monsters, my pants
wouldn't be wet right now!
[KAMINARI]
Mineta, get outta here.
One point three million volts!
[BEAST E groans]
[giggling]
Lovely birds of the forest!
Remove this evil beast and
restore peace to this wood!
[ASHIDO]
Take that!
[HAGAKURE]
Oh, no! I'm completely helpless!
It's gonna eat me!
[YAOYOROZU] Good, Hagakure.
Perfect distraction.
[ASHIDO]
And you!
[BEAST G groans]
[YAOYOROZU]
Everyone, quick. Take cover now!
[ASHIDO]
That was amazing, Momo!
[OCHACO]
Tsu. He's all yours!
[TSUYU]
Leave it to me.
--[TSUYU] Ribbit!
--And now, Release!
I've spotted more
of them closing in.
[roars]
[KATSUKI yells]
You're in my way there, icy hot!
Then pick another route.
[BEAST J growling]
--[BEAST K growling]
--[BEAST L screeches]
Midoriya. Now!
Right!
[PIXIE-BOB]
Hi-ya!
So you're gangin' up on me now?
Well I can fight dirty, too!
[MANDALAY]
Kota. We're leaving.
[PIXIE-BOB]
Scratch! Ha, ha!
Idiots.
[KOTA] How pointless.
To wanna be a hero.
Ha! The litter is almost here.
That took a lot
longer than expected.
[STUDENTS panting]
[panting]
[grunting]
[STUDENTS sigh]
[SERO] You said it would
only be, like, three hours!
[MANDALAY]
I guess we timed it based on
how long it'd take us. Sorry!
Now you're braggin' about
how much better you are?
That's so mean!
I'm starving. This is hell.
[PIXIE-BOB] Meow, meow, meow,
meow, meow, meow, meow!
I thought it would take
you kids even longer.
But, you did much better
against my dirt monsters
than I thought you would.
You guys were seriously great.
Especially the four of you!
It seems like you've had
quite a bit of experience.
I call dibs on these kittens.
I'll groom them myself!
[AIZAWA] Mandalay. Has she
always been like this?
It's gotten worse lately.
She's at the age to take a mate.
Uh. Speaking of people's ages--
Choose your words
carefully, boy.
[IZUKU] I've just been wondering
since we got here earlier.
Who is that kid?
What's he doing here?
Oh, this little guy?
He's my cousin's son.
He lives with us now.
Don't be shy, Kota.
Say hi to everyone.
You're gonna be around
them for the next week.
Hey there. My name's Midoriya.
I'm from the UA High
School hero course.
It's nice to meet you!
[yelps]
What a low blow!
You fiend of a child!
A punch to the scrotum
is unforgiveable!
The last thing I want is to hang
with some wannabe heroes.
[TENYA] "Wannabe"?!
How old are you, kid?
That brat's got spunk.
He's like a mini version of you.
What are you talking about?
You need to shut your mouth
before I blast you
all the way to hell.
Yeah, sure.
[AIZAWA]
Enough playing around.
Get your stuff off the bus.
Once your bags
are in your rooms,
we'll have dinner
in the cafeteria.
After that, you can
bathe and sleep.
Tomorrow your training
starts in earnest.
You'd better get a move on.
It looks so good!
[SERO]
So,
you girls got stuck in a tiny
little bunk room, didn't ya?
Why? Is the guys'
room really big?
[ASHIDO]
Oh, yeah?
So, like, can I come
check it out later or what?
[SERO]
Sure! Whenever you want.
[KIRISHIMA] It's so good.
I can't get enough!
[KAMINARI] My stomach
is so happy right now.
It's as good as
Lunch Rush's food!
I think I might eat
until I burst.
[KAMINARI gasps]
I smell beef.
Hey, wait, you got
meat over there?
[PIXIE-BOB]
Yeah.
Jeez, it's like you guys haven't
eaten in a week or something.
Anyway, today's the only time
we'll be doing this for you.
So make sure you kids enjoy it.
[KAMINARI, KIRISHIMA]
Thank you!
[MANDALAY]
Hey, Kota!
Can you bring me
those vegetables?
[MINETA] The food and stuff
is fine, but to be honest,
I'm hungry for somethin' else.
Just one little wall.
A few pieces of wood.
And heaven's waiting
on the other side.
A bath full of boobs and babes
ready to be seen by yours truly.
[KAMINARI sighs]
Are you over there talking
to yourself again, Mineta?
[ASHIDO]
This feels amazing!
[JIRO] I'm so glad they've
got a hot springs here!
Bathe, my angels.
How stupid of them not
to stagger the times
that we'd be naked
next to each other.
I hope they never learn
from their mistakes.
It's too much for him.
You're to stop this
at once, Mineta.
What you're doing is demeaning.
For both the girls and yourself.
It's shameful behavior!
Now I know why
I have this Quirk.
[MINETA] It's because walls
are meant to be climbed.
I'm coming for you,
ladies, Plus Ultra!
All that Quirk training.
All the times I almost died.
It was to prepare for
this shining momen--!
[KOTA]
Before you become a hero,
you should learn
how to be a good human.
I'll get you for this!
[MINETA, TENYA yell]
--[splash]
--[KOTA] Hmph.
[TSUYU] Mineta really is
the worst, isn't he?
[ASHIDO]
Thanks so much, Kota, babe!
We owe you one!
[yelps]
[ALL gasp]
[yelps, screams]
[IZUKU]
Look out!
[MANDALAY]
The rush from the fall
likely caused him
to faint. Thank you.
Eraser warned me one of you
boys was a little girl crazy,
so I stationed Kota
up there to keep watch.
I suppose that's the danger
of teaching kids your age.
Well, anyway. I'm just
glad he's all right.
You must've moved
pretty fast to catch him.
[KOTA]
The last thing I want is to hang
with some wannabe heroes.
[IZUKU] Um. He doesn't like
heroes very much, does he?
I admit, that's weird to me.
Most everyone I know
wants to be one.
It's... my dream.
So, it's just wild to
think that a kid his age
is against heroes.
Hates them, even.
How observant. Of course,
he isn't alone.
There are many in our society
who don't approve of us.
If he'd had a normal childhood,
maybe he would've admired heroes
like you did growing up.
[gasps] What happened?
[PIXIE-BOB]
It was Mandalay's cousins.
Kota's parents, that is.
They were heroes, too.
But they were murdered.
[gasps]
It was a villain.
Two years back.
Kota was still so small.
They were killed while
protecting citizens.
Perhaps the most respectable
way for any hero to die.
But...
[KOTA]
Papa. Mama.
[MANDALAY] How do you even
begin to explain to a child
that his parents died
honorable deaths?
They were his entire
world. Everything.
But to him, his parents
had left him behind.
And all the while,
they were being praised.
Because... their sacrefice
was such a noble one.
Honestly, he doesn't
seem to like us
that much either. We're
heroes, like they were.
I'm sure he feels like
he's stuck here
because he has
nowhere else to go.
Heroes just don't make
any sense to Kota.
After all, if his parents
hadn't been heroes,
they would still be here.
[SHIGARAKI]
He's why these morons
are able to smile thoughtlessly!
Because that garbage pro
is smiling thoughtlessly, too!
[IZUKU] I'd heard so many
different people talking about
heroes over the last few months.
Had listened to so many
different viewpoints.
It would be irresponsible
to shrug them off.
And yet, in that moment,
I had no reply.
[yawning]
[AIZAWA]
Good morning, class.
Today, we begin a training camp
that will increase
your strength.
Our goal is to increase
your skills exponentially,
so that each of you earns
a provisional license.
This will allow you
to face the dangers
that continue to fester
in the darkness.
Proceed carefully.
Look alive, Bakugo.
Try throwing that for me.
Yeah, sure. Like in
the fitness test.
[AIZAWA]
That's right.
When you first started school,
your record was 705.2 meters.
Let's see if you've improved.
[ASHIDO] Oh, I get it!
We're checking our progress.
[SERO] A lot's happened to
us the last three months.
Maybe he can throw it
a whole mile now!
[KIRISHIMA]
C'mon, get it, Bakugo!
I've got this. No one blink.
Go to hell!
[IZUKU]
"Go to hell"?
[AIZAWA]
That was 709.6 meters.
[KATSUKI grunts]
[SERO]
That's it? Kinda disappointing.
[AIZAWA] You've had
a single semester at UA,
and due to your
various experiences,
all of you have
definitely improved.
But those improvements
have mostly been
limited to mental prowess
and technical skill.
With a slight increase in
stamina thrown in along the way.
Your Quirks really haven't
grown that much stronger.
Not on a fundamental level.
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] That's why we're
now going to focus
on improving your powers.
[AIZAWA] This'll be so hard,
you'll feel like you're dying.
Let's hope you all survive.
[TOGA] Hey, hey! Special
delivery from Tomura!
He wants us to bring
these along when we go,
so I'm guessing there's
enough for everyone.
[MUSCULAR]
C'mon. I'm ready.
Let's hurry up and do this.
[MUSTARD]
It's still too early.
Besides, don't forget,
he said we shouldn't
do anything flashy.
[DABI]
Yeah.
He acted like a spoiled
little brat when we first met.
But suddenly, he's begun
to take charge.
This is gonna be nothing
more than a warning shot.
We'll pull those
false heroes down
from their shining pedestals.
And in doing so, we'll create
a bright new future
for this world.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
It turns out that developing
our individual Quirks
is this summer training
camp's main focus.
To do that, we've got to
push ourselves to the limit.
It's the only way we can
hope to become pros!
But Kota still scoffs at us.
Even though he's part
of Mandalay's family,
he doesn't like heroes.
I wonder what happened in his
past to make him feel that way.
Next time: "Kota."
I can't wait to find out what
the Pussycats' test of courage
has in store for us!
[IZUKU]
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!