[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward my
dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome obstacles
and save people with
a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[ALL MIGHT] Will you allow me
to devote myself to Young Izuku?
Together, we will go beyond.
I will lift him up.
And I will protect your son,
even if it costs me my life.
[sighs]
[gasps] Are you okay?!
[IZUKU'S MOM]
I can't. I mean...
[IZUKU'S MOM] You're
Izuku's reason for living.
All Might.
Don't give up your life.
He needs you.
To protect him. Raise him.
If you can promise me
you'll do that,
then he can return to UA.
Oh, Mom!
[ALL MIGHT]
I promise.
[IZUKU'S MOM]
Izuku.
If you're going to go
back to this school,
you have to be so careful.
Of course. I won't
make you worry.
[IZUKU'S MOM]
That look on your face.
You're so grown.
While I wasn't looking,
the hero you admire so much
actually began to admire you.
I'm proud of you,
too, Izuku. My baby.
I hope that knowing
how whole-heartedly
he respects you
makes you happy, son.
[ALL MIGHT] She entrusted
you to my care, Young Midoriya.
She wants me to be a mentor.
To act like a natural-born hero
instead of the Symbol of Peace.
[ALL MIGHT]
You have a really good mother.
I do.
You know,
she reminds me
of my predecessor.
[IZUKU]
She does? Wait, how so?
It's the hairstyle.
[IZUKU]
O-Oh, sure.
And she's got the
mighty heart of a hero!
[WOMAN 51A] Ew. Look at
that walking skeleton!
[ALL MIGHT gasps]
Crap.
Now everyone recognizes
me in this form, too.
I forgot.
[ALL MIGHT]
Well, see you at school.
Right. Cool!
[IZUKU] After my mother
gave me permission,
I left home and
started a new life.
[IZUKU]
On the edge of UA's campus,
about a five-minute walk
from the main school,
they built a student dorm.
Heights Alliance, constructed
in just three days.
This was my--no-- our new home.
[NEZU] The new dorm
system we put into place
isn't just to ensure the
safety of our students.
It's also how we're addressing
one of the threats
we've yet to take
care of. The leak.
A feeling of unease has
settled upon our school.
To help alleviate that,
we'll be holding a private,
behind-the-scenes investigation.
It pains me to suspect
not just the teachers,
but the students as well.
Unfortunately, right now,
I have no other choice.
We've lost the Symbol of Peace.
And I have no doubt
that this will have
big ramifications on
us as time passes.
What UA needs right now
is positive energy
and revitalization.
We must remind the children
that there's a bright
future ahead of them
despite what they've endured.
[AIZAWA] Given everything
that has happened,
I'm glad we were able to
bring Class A back together.
So, we all got the go ahead
to move on-campus.
[HAGAKURE sighs] It took a lot
of convincing for my parents.
I was pretty concerned
about mine.
It makes sense.
You got the worst
of the gas attack.
We're glad to see the teachers
got to come back, too.
I was afraid you
wouldn't be allowed.
The people at the
press conference seemed
pretty upset with you guys.
Yeah.
[AIZAWA]
I was surprised, as well.
But circumstances have changed.
[AIZAWA] I suspect it was
easier for administration
to let the teachers
return instead of
revamping the entire faculty.
Now, then.
I'll explain how your dorm
assignments will work shortly.
First, however...
We haven't forgotten about the
provisional hero licenses
you were supposed to get
during the training camp.
[SATO] Oh, yeah! That's
what we were there for.
[ASHIDO] So much has happened,
it totally slipped my mind.
[AIZAWA]
This is important. Listen well.
Kirishima. Yaoyorozu. Todoroki.
Midoriya. Iida.
You five are the ones
who broke the rules
and went to rescue
Bakugo that night.
Ribbit.
Based on your reactions,
I assume the rest of you were
at least aware of their plan.
[AIZAWA] I'm going to set
aside a number of issues
and just say this.
If it weren't for All Might's
retirement from the Hero scene,
I would expel everyone here
except Bakugo, Jiro,
and Hagakure.
[AIZAWA] The five of you
who went, of course.
But also the remaining 12
who didn't stop them.
You betrayed our trust.
Even if it was to
keep your friends
from getting into trouble.
In order to regain
our confidence,
you'll need to obey
every rule to the letter,
and live as model students.
That's all.
Now. Look alive.
Enjoy your new home.
[SERO, KAMINARI]
Uh.
We're supposed to be
excited after that speech?
[KATSUKI]
Tch.
Come here.
[KAMINARI]
Uh-- Huh? Wait. For what?
[KAMINARI yells]
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay.
Dude. What'd Bakugo do to you?
Kirishima!
[KIRISHIMA] Whoa, did you
shake him down for cash?!
[KATSUKI]
No! This is my money, you idiot.
To replace what you spent.
Uh. How'd you know I bought
night vision goggles?
[KATSUKI] Don't say I
never gave you anything.
Now I'm not in your debt.
Kaminari, show 'em
your dumb side.
[JIRO] Oh, man. What a moron.
You're so hopeless.
[KAMINARI yelling]
--[STUDENTS laughing]
--[SERO] It isn't funny, guys!
[KIRISHIMA]
Thanks, man.
[AIZAWA]
Sometimes blowing off steam
is the best thing
to do, I guess.
[KIRISHIMA]
Sorry, everyone!
I know this won't
make up for it,
but let's all go out
to eat tonight on me!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[KAMINARI]
Yay!
[AIZAWA] Each student
dormitory holds one class.
Girls are on the right
and boys are on the left.
The entire first floor
is a common area.
That's where you'll
find your kitchen,
baths, and laundry rooms.
[HAGAKURE]
Ah!
There's even a courtyard.
So spacious and new! [laughs]
I'm living in a mansion.
Uraraka!
[MINETA]
Doth mine ears deceive me?
Our baths... are located
in the common space?
[gulps] Is this heaven?
[AIZAWA]
They're separated by gender,
and you'll behave yourself.
Yes, sir.
[AIZAWA] Living quarters
start on the next floor.
A few boys and girls
on each level.
Everyone gets their own room.
You should be comfortable.
You've got your own AC,
toilets, fridges, and closets.
We have balconies?! Wow!
This room is about the same
size as my closet at home,
but I'll manage.
[OCHACO]
It's the size of my house!
Uraraka!
[AIZAWA]
These are your dorm assignments.
The belongings you sent ahead
have already been placed
in your new rooms,
so spend the day unpacking
and getting settled.
I'll tell you more about your
next few lessons tomorrow.
For now, get to work.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, Mr. Aizawa!
[KIRISHIMA]
Ah, I'm so beat.
[SERO] You and me both.
You done unpacking?
I think so.
Feels good, right?
I know we could've died.
But it's kind of exciting
to be living here.
[IZUKU]
Mm-hm!
A unified class.
It's the perfect way to increase
our cooperation and discipline.
How smart!
So you never relax, do you?
[ASHIDO] Hiya, boys.
All done with your rooms?
Yup, we're just unwinding now.
Well, the girls and I
have been talking and...
[HAGAKURE]
We have a great idea!
Let's go around and see
who has the coolest room!
[screams] No, wait,
you can't go in there!
Please, it's not fit for--
[GIRLS squeal]
[OCHACO]
It's All Might everywhere!
You're such a fanboy!
[IZUKU]
Well, I admire him...
This is embarrassing.
Does this mean...
...they're judging
our rooms, too?
Probably, could
end up a good time.
No way.
[ASHIDO, HAGAKURE]
So dark and scary!
[TOKOYAMI]
You fiends.
[KIRISHIMA] Oh, man,
I had a keychain like this
when I was in middle school.
So this is how boys
like to decorate.
[TOKOYAMI]
Please leave.
A sword?! So cool!
[TOKOYAMI]
Get out!
Aren't you dazzled?
[STUDENTS]
Shiny...
Non , non .
It's not shiny, it's...
Mag...
...ni...
...fique.
[HAGAKURE]
Exactly what I pictured.
Honestly, I expected more.
This is turning out
to be really fun!
The last person
on this floor is.
[MINETA panting]
Hey. Come on in, girls.
I've got so much to show you.
[OCHACO]
So, the third floor?
Where are you going? Come back!
[OCHACO]
Ooh... It's so bare in here!
[HAGAKURE]
Did you move anything in at all?
[ASHIDO] Please tell me you
just haven't unpacked yet.
Um, if we're done here,
then let's go.
[OCHACO] Whoa! It looks
like a library in here!
[ASHIDO]
That's the class rep for you.
You'll find nothing odd in here.
[OCHACO]
You have so many glasses.
[TENYA]
Of course I do!
I expect them all to be
destroyed during training!
[ASHIDO, HAGAKURE, OCHACO, JIRO]
Really?
[JIRO] This is the store
in the mall I'd avoid.
What? It's perfect!
[OCHACO, ASHIDO]
He has a rabbit! It's so cute!
[KAMINARI]
Hey, no fair, we don't get pets.
You're trying to buy
the judges' love!
[IZUKU] Everyone's really
getting into the competition.
[KAMINARI] Man, this sucks.
I feel so judged right now.
Hey, what a coincidence.
I don't feel great. At all.
Same here.
Et moi .
[MINETA] That's because
the boys are the only ones
who are getting picked on.
They said it was
a contest to see
who has the coolest dorm room.
Well, what about them?!
We have to see the girls' rooms
to tell which one's best.
Their interior designs
skills should be held
at the same standard as ours.
Maybe even higher.
Show us those dorms!
[IZUKU] This surprisingly
convincing argument
from Mineta hit home, and
stoked our competitive spirit.
I'm into it!
Huh?
[IZUKU] Even the most completely
uninterested got involved.
And that is how the very first
Class 1-A Best Room Contest
got its start!
[IZUKU gulps]
[IZUKU]
The girls' dorms?
I suppose. If we must!
[ASHIDO] Okay, so, like,
what're the rules?
Are we figuring out who has
the best taste in the class,
or just the overall coolest?
We're doing this?
This doesn't have
to be a contest.
[MINETA] If I was the only one
asking to see the other rooms,
then everyone would yell at me.
But, since all these guys with
bruised egos are on board,
I get to join in all
inconspicuous like.
The whole class is doing it,
so why shouldn't I, right?
[MINETA cackles]
[MINETA] I'm gonna be rummaging
through the girls' rooms.
Who knows what scintillating
secrets I'll find.
[TODOROKI]
I'm over it.
Let's see, who else
is on the fourth floor?
It's Bakugo, Kirishima,
and Shoji, isn't it?
Where is Bakugo?
Uh, he thought this was lame,
so he went back
to his room to sleep.
I could use some Zs, too.
[HAGAKURE]
Then we'll do your room next.
[ASHIDO] You can sleep
all you want after.
[KIRISHIMA]
Not that I care.
But you might not get
what I'm goin' for.
A den of manliness!
[HAGAKURE] If I found out
my boyfriend had a room
that looked like this,
I'd dump him.
So bold! Makes me
wanna work out!
You get it.
[ASHIDO]
Next up, Shoji.
You're not gonna find
anything interesting here.
[ASHIDO] Uh... More like
nothing at all, dude.
So, you're a minimalist, huh?
I've just never
understood why someone
would wanna fill
their room with junk.
[MINETA] Guys like this always
have a super pervy side.
[HAGAKURE] All done! Let's
head up to the fifth floor.
[ASHIDO]
We'll start with Sero.
Are we seriously doing everyone?
[GIRLS]
Wow!
Exotic!
[OCHACO]
It's lovely!
Sero, I didn't peg
you for someone
who'd like this stuff.
He, he, he. Yup, that's me,
always the wild card.
[HAGAKURE]
Let's keep moving!
[YAOYOROZU]
Next is Todoroki's room, right?
[YAOYOROZU] The most capable
student in our class.
[ASHIDO]
The most handsome boy in school.
[HAGAKURE] A chance to glance
into his quiet private life.
How exciting!
[TODOROKI] Let's get this
over with. It's late.
[BOTH yell]
So Japanese!
[KAMINARI]
It was even built differently!
We've got these kinds of
floor mats at my home.
They're much more
comfortable than hardwood.
This isn't your house!
How did you remodel
this entire room
in just one day?
With hard work.
[KAMINARI]
You are a beast.
[HAGAKURE]
He'll make such a good pro.
Pretty boys have tricks
up their sleeves.
Okay, next! The last
of the guys is...
Me...
[SATO] Anyway, it's
a pretty boring room.
[KIRISHIMA] All of them
are after Todoroki's.
[OJIRO] Something smells good,
though. What is it?
Oh, crap, I forgot about that!
I finished unpacking
really early.
So I started to bake
a chiffon cake.
I thought we could
all eat it together.
It hasn't been iced yet,
but, want some?
[ASHIDO, HAGAKURE, OCHACO]
Yeah!
The strong guy's
an expert baker?!
It's delicious! So fluffy.
[HAGAKURE]
I could eat it every day.
Forget Sero, this is unexpected.
[JIRO]
Mm-mm!
I think it's great that you have
such a fun hobby, Sato.
Would you like to bake something
to go with my tea one day?
Uh. I seriously did
not expect this reaction.
Mostly I bake as
part of the training
for my sugar Quirk.
Store-bought sweets
can get pricey.
[HAGAKURE]
That's it for the boys.
Now, it's our turn, ladies.
[JIRO]
Aw, man, that's so many rooms.
Shouldn't we turn in?
[ASHIDO]
Come on, Jiro, live a little.
[JIRO]
It's kind of embarrassing.
Whoa, you've got
so many instruments!
[HAGAKURE] It's because
Jiro's totally punk rock.
Can you play all these?
Yeah. At least a little.
Your room's girlier than this.
Because I've got style.
We're done here.
[HAGAKURE]
Next is me! Welcome in, guys!
What do ya think?
[OJIRO]
A-Ah...
[KAMINARI]
Now this is girly. So pink...
Plus Ultra!
[HAGAKURE] Get away from
there, Mineta, you perv!
We can do mine next!
Ta-dah! Isn't it super cute?
[STUDENTS]
Whoa...
Yeah, it's not very
interesting, I know.
[STUDENTS]
Wow...
[OJIRO]
Is this okay?
It feels dirty seeing so
many girls' rooms up close.
This is their private space.
[TOKOYAMI]
Forbidden gardens.
Next is Asui.
Wait, where is Tsu?
Haven't seen her.
[OCHACO]
Oh, she wasn't feeling too good.
So she's in her room.
Well, we shouldn't bother her.
She can show us later
when she's feeling better.
[SERO] Then the last
one up is Yaoyorozu.
The thing is...
I... maybe miscalculated
a few things.
My room's a little bit more
cramped than I intended.
And maybe not as creative
as some of yours.
That bed is huge!
You can't even walk in here!
It's my furniture from home,
so I thought it'd fit.
I had no idea how small
these dorm rooms
would end up being.
[OCHACO, IZUKU]
I forget how rich she is.
[ASHIDO]
All right, everybody.
Has everyone got
their votes in?
Remember, you can't
pick yourself, guys.
And now, without further ado,
here are the results of the
first Best Room competition,
minus Bakugo and Tsu.
Drumroll, please!
[drumroll]
[ASHIDO] With a total of five
votes, the overwhelming
winner of this totally
awesome contest is...
Rikido Sato!
Uh?
[ASHIDO] By the way,
all the girls voted for you.
Because...
That cake was delicious.
I want some more.
[SATO]
That's why?!
[KAMINARI, MINETA]
You villain!
Aspiring heroes shouldn't
resort to bribery!
[SATO]
It wasn't on purpose!
But what the heck!
Is it over? Can I sleep now?
Yes, and since you had cake,
don't forget to
brush your teeth!
Thanks for sticking it out.
Hey! Todoroki, wait a minute.
Deku and Iida, you, too.
Yaoyorozu, Kirishima,
you have a sec?
It's really important.
[KIRISHIMA]
So, uh. Where are we going?
[OCHACO]
Right here.
Tsu said she had something
she wanted to tell everyone.
[TSUYU] You guys know
I'm pretty straightforward,
and always speak
what's on my mind.
But sometimes...
I don't know. I'm at a loss.
Remember what I said
back at the hospital?
When you were talking
about the rescue...
Going after Bakugo
would break the rules.
That means you'd be
acting like villains,
not heroes.
Yeah. Every word.
My heart was hurting.
And the things I said
must've upset you.
It's okay, Tsu.
Despite my warning,
you still went and saved Bakugo.
I didn't know that
until this morning.
I thought I'd stopped you.
But it turns out
I was worthless.
A complete failure.
And suddenly I had
no idea what to say.
I didn't think I deserved
to joke around and have fun
with everyone like usual.
But...
It made me... so sad
to be without you.
[TSUYU] That's why I
wanted to talk to you.
Even if I'm still not sure
how I'm supposed to be feeling.
I wanted you to know
so we can hang out and talk
and have a good time again.
It's not just you
who thinks that.
Everyone... felt
pretty bad and...
...wanted things back the
way they used to be before.
That's why we did
the room contest.
To bring us closer together
and make us feel
like a class again.
It's all we could come up with,
so please don't think
we were trying to
trick you or anything.
Look, what I'm saying is,
let's all work hard
at our training
and be good friends again, okay?
[KIRISHIMA]
Tsu!
I'm sorry!
Thanks for telling
us how you feel!
It's okay.
I apologize.
[TODOROKI]
You shouldn't feel bad.
[IZUKU]
Asu-- Tsu!
Listen. I won't
make you sad again!
[YAOYOROZU]
Me either.
We promise!
[IZUKU]
That's right.
Everyone wants things
to go back to normal.
[IZUKU] We need our
lives to feel stable.
Even though so much has changed
and will keep changing.
It's our duty to make
each other better, stronger,
so we can become
heroes together.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
Settling into dorm life
will be an adjustment, sure,
but that's not all we're facing.
There's a long road ahead of us
if we're going to develop
our Quirks further
and get comfortable with
our fighting styles.
Plus, to prep for the exam,
we need to come up
with ultimate moves.
The problem is, I can't
overuse One For All
or I'll hurt my body.
How am I supposed to come
up with a new attack
when my arms are so messed up?
Next time: "Create Those
Ultimate Moves"!
Changing the way you think
can be the key to victory!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!