[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward my
dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[ALL MIGHT]
Smash!
[TSUKAUCHI] Remind the world
what you can do, Heroes!
You'll tell us where
he is right now.
Shigaraki!
[SHIGARAKI]
This is your fault! I hate you!
[NOMUS growling]
[KAMUI WOODS]
Nomus? How'd they get here?
What is this?
[GRAN TORINO]
They keep on coming.
[KATSUKI]
The crap?
Bakugo!
No!
[KAMUI WOODS]
Endeavor! Help us!
How?
[growling]
Toshinori. What now?
They shouldn't have been
able to warp Nomus here.
And this backup came too fast!
[ALL MIGHT]
I fear that he has made a move.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Don't worry. I am here for you.
[SHIGARAKI]
Master.
[gags]
[KAMUI WOODS gasps]
Stop them! Before
they all disappear!
Damn it! You won't
escape, Shigaraki!
Take me with you!
[KAMUI WOODS]
No. No!
I'm so sorry!
[EDGESHOT]
This wasn't your fault.
None of us were
able to do anything.
Kurogiri's Quirk
opens up warp gates
that allow anyone
to pass through.
But this was targeting
specific people.
All Might!
[ALL MIGHT]
Oklahoma Smash!
[RIOT SQUAD 48A] Hope that
wasn't a load-bearing wall.
[RIOT SQUAD 48B]
Focus on the enemies out here!
On your left!
[RIOT SQUAD 48C]
They're monsters!
More of them?
I thought we were supposed
to have a handle on these!
Jeanist isn't
answering me anymore.
It's possible they failed
at the Nomu factory.
This is putting a lot
of stress on my power.
[ALL MIGHT]
Endeavor!
[ALL MIGHT coughing]
Are you keeping up?
Does it look like
I'm having any trouble?
Worry about your own
responsibilities, you fool.
If you're gonna go
after them, now's the time.
[ALL MIGHT]
Right. I'll leave you to it.
[clapping]
[ALL FOR ONE] I see why
you're the number four hero,
Best Jeanist.
That blast should
have annihilated
the lot of you.
[BEST JEANIST grunts]
[ALL FOR ONE]
But you were able to manipulate
everyone's clothing and
pull them out of the way
just in time.
Quick thinking.
Consider me impressed.
[BEST JEANIST]
It's him.
[SPECIAL AGENT 48A] We believe
there must be an architect
behind the League of Villains.
It's likely that his strength
is comparable to All Might's.
He will be crafty and cautious.
If he doesn't feel like
his safety is guaranteed,
he will not reveal himself.
So you must capture Shigaraki
and the others quickly.
Then move on to their leader.
[BEST JEANIST] It wasn't
supposed to go like this.
[BEST JEANIST]
But that doesn't matter.
A true hero doesn't
believe in excuses.
[BEST JEANIST grunts]
[ALL FOR ONE]
Now, I see.
Your strength
comes from practice
and practical experience,
not raw power.
I don't need your Quirk.
It wouldn't pair well
with Tomura's disposition.
[TODOROKI] Who is this guy?
What just happened?
[KIRISHIMA] He took out
three pros in an instant!
[YAOYOROZU] We have to run.
I know that, but...
[TENYA]
I'm so scared, that my legs...
[IZUKU]
My body... won't move!
What... in the world...
...was that?
[splash]
[KATSUKI coughing]
[KATSUKI]
Damn it.
The hell?
[KATSUKI coughing]
--[IZUKU] Kacchan!
--[KIRISHIMA, TODOROKI] Bakugo!
[ALL FOR ONE]
My apologies, Bakugo.
[pants] Huh?
[splash]
[SPINNER gags]
[TOGA]
That was so gross.
[TWICE] This black
stuff reeks! I love it.
[SHIGARAKI]
Master.
[ALL FOR ONE] So. You've
failed once more, Tomura.
But you must not be discouraged.
You'll try again.
That's why I brought your
associates back with you.
Even this child,
because you judged
that he was an important
piece on your game board.
[ALL FOR ONE] Start over
as many times as it takes.
I am here to provide
you with help.
All of this is for you.
[KATSUKI growls]
[IZUKU]
I can't freak out now.
I have to remember why I'm here.
Because my body
couldn't move back then,
and I let the villains take him.
Being scared is no excuse.
He's right there in front of me!
[IZUKU]
Their leader doesn't seem
to have noticed we're around.
Otherwise, he wouldn't talk
so freely in front of us.
There are six or seven meters
separating me from Kacchan.
With Full Cowl, I can get
there in less than a second.
But could I get away?
Where would we run to next?
Plus, I'd be putting
the others in danger.
That won't work. I need a plan.
[IZUKU] I need to find a way
to reach out to him.
[TENYA gasps]
[IZUKU] If I can't do that,
then this was all for nothing.
[TENYA]
I will...
[YAOYOROZU]
I have to...
[TENYA]
...protect you!
[YAOYOROZU]
...focus!
[TENYA]
I have to think!
[TENYA, YAOYOROZU]
We have to get away. But how?
[ALL FOR ONE]
Ah. There you are.
[TENYA gasps]
I'll have you return
my student, All For One!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Have you come to kill me
a second time, All Might?
I'll have you return
my student, All For One!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Have you come to kill me
a second time, All Might?
[KATSUKI, SHIGARAKI grunt]
[TOGA, TWICE,
MR. COMPRESS scream]
[GROUP grunting]
No. There's too many of them!
[ALL FOR ONE] It took you
long enough to find us.
It's only five kilometers
from the bar to here,
and yet it was
at least 30 seconds
after I sent the Nomus
that you arrived.
You've gotten weaker, All Might.
You're one to talk,
it's kind of difficult
to ignore that fancy
life-support mask you've got on.
Aren't you
overexerting yourself?
[KATSUKI] He held All Might
back with his bare hands!
This guy must be
the boss villain!
I won't repeat the mistake
I made five years ago.
You hear me?
I will take Young Bakugo back.
And I will make certain
you're locked up
for the rest of your sad life.
Right along with your despicable
League of Villains.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Sounds like you've got your work
cut out for you. This will
be hard for us both.
[ALL FOR ONE] Hm. Air Cannon
plus Spring-like Limbs.
Kinetic Booster times four.
Strength Enhancer times three.
What a delightful combination.
Maybe a few more
enhancers next time.
[gasps] All Might!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Don't you worry.
It'll take more than
that to kill him.
Get off the battlefield, Tomura.
And take that child with you.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Kurogiri. Warp them away.
[MAGNE]
Be careful!
One of the heroes messed with
him and he's unconscious.
I'm not sure what's going on,
but if you can teleport,
why don't you get
us out of here?
[ALL FOR ONE] My warp power
is still new, Magne.
There is much I need
to learn about it.
Its distance is limited,
and while he can
teleport to
specific coordinates,
I only transport people
to and from my own location.
Or, with focus,
to or from someone
I am very familiar with.
That is all.
It's easier to have
Kurogiri do it.
[ALL FOR ONE] Forcible Quirk
Activation. Leave this place.
[SHIGARAKI]
What about you?
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[ALL FOR ONE]
You're not thinking, Tomura.
There remains much room
for you to grow.
You're mine!
[SHIGARAKI]
Master.
[MR. COMPRESS]
Let's go, Shigaraki.
While our masked lead is
keeping All Might entertained.
Claim your prize.
Huh. This is gonna be fun.
Young Bakugo, don't!
[IZUKU]
All Might!
All For One is in the way,
so he can't get to Kacchan!
If something doesn't change,
the League will escape
with my friend. Again.
They've got him surrounded,
so he can't escape by himself!
[KATSUKI]
These guys know I'm screwed.
It's six against one,
and they're willing to drag me
out of here by force this time.
[KATSUKI] I can't let that
magician lay a finger on me.
I'm coming for you.
[ALL FOR ONE] I don't
think so. Because I am here.
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[IZUKU] All Might and Kacchan
are both completely stuck.
What now?
[TSURAGAMAE]
That's why it's against the law
for uncertified people to use
their Quirks to cause injury.
None of you had the authority
to harm the villain.
[SHOJI]
I'm upset, too.
But... We can't let our
emotions get the best of us.
If you know that you're
breaking the rules,
then you're acting like
villains, not heroes.
Why did it have to be
you two of all people?
Why are you trying
to make the same
stupid mistakes I made?
[IZUKU]
It's no use.
As heroes-in-training,
we're not allowed to fight.
[IZUKU]
But maybe...
If there's an opening...
An instant...
We might have a
chance to swoop in
and grab Kacchan.
And if we can save him,
All Might can use the
full extent of his power.
[IZUKU]
But how?
Nothing seems like it'll work.
[IZUKU]
Come on. Think.
Somehow, we can help
him out of this!
[IZUKU gasps]
Yes.
Iida. Listen!
You can't fight.
I won't let you.
No, I think there's another way!
A way that won't
involve any combat.
That'll let us escape. With him.
Come on, we can still
get Kacchan back!
Tell us your plan.
The thing is, it's all
going to depend on him.
[KATSUKI]
Stay back, Deku!
I just don't know, you guys.
Think about what
Bakugo would want.
We'd just make everything
worse I'm afraid.
[IZUKU]
If I did the plan myself,
I don't think it would
work. So, Kirishima.
You're the key to this
being a success!
[gasps]
We need details Midoriya. C'mon.
Right. Here's what I'm thinking.
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
[yells]
[ALL FOR ONE]
Are you holding back against me?
Trying to keep the boy
from being blown away?
You've put yourself
in quite the predicament.
So how will the "hero" prevail?
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Bakugo!
[KATSUKI grunts]
[KATSUKI] It'll be hard for
All Might to kick his ass
as long as I'm here. Damn it!
--[TODOROKI gasps]
--Are you out of your mind?
[IZUKU] Kacchan will have
realized the situation
that All Might's in.
I agree.
He's staying on the
defensive with his enemies,
keeping his distance.
That's good for us.
We have to move when
he's got some space
between him and the villains.
Iida...
It is a gamble.
But all things considered,
there's not much risk to us.
And more importantly, it could
change the tide of this fight.
[TENYA]
I'm in.
[IZUKU]
This is what we do.
First, we'll propel
ourselves using my Quirk,
combined with Iida's Recipro.
[IZUKU] Then, using
Kirishima's hardening...
[IZUKU]
...we'll break through the wall.
The second we've cleared it,
Todoroki will make a huge
slab of ice for us.
[IZUKU]
As high as he possibly can.
The villains haven't
noticed us yet.
Up until now, they've been
able to outmaneuver us.
But we're finally
in the position
to get the jump on them.
[IZUKU] And we'll cross the
battlefield at a height
that they'll never
hope to reach.
[IZUKU] Right now, the guy
in charge of the villains
is holding All Might back.
But that means the
reverse is true, too.
[IZUKU] The last part's
up to you, Kirishima.
It's no good if I do it.
Or Todoroki,
or Iida, or Yaoyorozu.
Ever since school started,
you've built a solid
relationship with
Kacchan as equals!
If his friend calls to him...
Come on!
[IZUKU]
...he'll listen.
[KATSUKI yells]
You idiots.
[SPINNER]
What?
Bakugo. On my mark,
you give us a giant--!
Don't tell me what
to do, damn you!
It's not the time
to fight, you guys!
Just as we thought.
All eyes on them.
This is our chance.
Let's go!
[SHIGARAKI] Why do you keep
showing up everywhere?
Seriously? You kids.
[MR. COMPRESS]
Don't let them get away!
Who can do distance?
Kurogiri and Dabi.
But, they're down!
[MAGNE]
You two, come here!
[PRESENT MIC]
Magne's Quirk: Magnetism.
Its wielder can apply
a magnetic force
to anyone within
a 4.5 meter radius!
And focus on a whole
body or just a part.
Men become south poles and
women become north poles.
Magnetism doesn't work
on Magne, though.
Ready!
[MR. COMPRESS]
Repulsion Breakup.
Night Flight Cannon!
[MT. LADY]
Titan Cliff!
Whoa, Mt. Lady!
The rescue's priority.
Go home, you dumb kids.
[MAGNE] We can still
catch them! C'mon, you two.
[IZUKU gasps]
Gran Torino!
You're too slow.
You're just too fast, hot shot.
So, you saw the kid, right?
He's turning out to be more
and more like you every day.
Not a compliment.
[ALL MIGHT] Tch. After his
experience in Hosu...
I didn't think he'd come
to the battlefield.
Damn teenagers!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Shimura's friend, huh?
[ALL MIGHT coughs] It's shameful
that I needed their help.
But now,
I don't have to pull
any punches against you.
You're finished.
[GRAN TORINO] Two left
over here. I'll handle them.
Tomura, I do not wanna
die in this place.
[ALL FOR ONE]
They got us.
Turned the tables of this
fight with a single move.
[ALL FOR ONE] Forcible Quick
Activation. Magnetism!
[SHIGARAKI]
You are dust!
[GRAN TORINO grunts]
Huh?
Hey! Watch out, you guys!
You'r coming at me too fast!
[SHIGARAKI]
Wait. Don't. Master!
Not so fast.
[SHIGARAKI]
Your body is too damaged!
[ALL FOR ONE] No one's come
to save you, have they?
You've had a hard life,
Tenko Shimura.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Don't worry. I am here for you.
No, I... won't go!
[ALL FOR ONE] Tomura.
You must continue to fight.
[ALL FOR ONE] "Warping."
Plus "Shock Inversion"!
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
I'm sorry!
[ALL FOR ONE]
I only came to save Tomura.
But if you say you're
going to fight,
then I'll face you as you wish.
In the past, your fist crushed
one after another
of my comrades.
Many were forced into
the shadows, underground.
While you were extolled
as the Symbol of Peace.
What a grand view you must have
had from atop our sacrifices.
A hero standing on the
mountain of our defeats.
Detroit... Smash!
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
[ALL FOR ONE]
He stopped the attack himself.
You still won't fight me
with your full power, huh?
Because doing so would
endanger all those people
you've sworn to protect.
You shut up.
[ALL FOR ONE gasps]
[ALL MIGHT]
Always toying with people,
probing their weaknesses.
You steal. Break them.
Manipulate and discard them.
You scoff at innocent people
who are just trying
to lead happy lives!
[ALL MIGHT]
It cannot continue.
[ALL FOR ONE]
It's over.
I won't let it!
[GRAN TORINO groans]
[gasps] Toshinori.
[ALL MIGHT panting]
[GRAN TORINO]
You've reached your limit.
[ALL FOR ONE]
What's wrong?
[gasps]
[ALL FOR ONE]
You seem to be worked up
about something, All Might.
I've heard that same exact
line before, you know.
[ALL FOR ONE cackles]
[ALL MIGHT gasps]
[ALL FOR ONE] From the person
who had One for All before you.
Nana Shimura.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
The Symbol of Peace, All Might,
and the Symbol of Evil,
All For One go head-to-head
in an epic battle.
We saved Kacchan
and left the scene,
so the only thing we can do
now is watch the fight play out
along with the
rest of the world.
Even after the secret he's
been hiding is exposed,
All Might continues to stand up
against the villain
in front of him.
Next time: "One For All."
This could be the final shining
moment for the number-one hero!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!