[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward my
dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[IZUKU] The provisional
licensing exam is upon us.
[MERA]
Oh, right.
For the 100 of you who
passed the first test,
please turn your
attention to the screen.
It's the test arena.
What's happens next?
[STUDENTS]
Why?
Wait. Does that mean...?
[MERA] There's only one
more round to the exam.
Your goal is simple:
undertake rescue exercises
and save the bystanders
who are trapped
in these disaster sites.
[BOTH]
Save the what now?
[HAGAKURE]
Bystanders.
We learned about them
in class, remember?
They're people at
a disaster scene.
It can also simply refer
to innocent citizens
on the street.
[MERA] Use this time to show
us how you will carry out
successful rescue
procedures once you receive
your provisional licenses.
Treat this as though
it were the real thing.
[sighs] Rescuing.
On the screen.
[gasps] Little kids
and old people?
[MINETA] That's so dangerous--
why're they here?
[MERA] These specialists have
been trained as professional
"persons in need of rescue."
They're very popular.
Introducing the
"Help Us Company,"
also known as HUC for short.
So, they're basically
actors, I guess?
It's the kind of job
you never think about.
But a necessary one
in our world,
since they support
our hero training.
[MERA] The HUC bystanders
have dressed up
like injured victims
and will be located
throughout the disaster site.
We'll be judging how well
you keep them safe
as you go about your mission.
Oh, by the way.
We'll be scoring you
on a point system.
If you have more points
than the benchmark
at the time the exercise
comes to an end,
then you pass the exam.
We'll start in ten minutes.
Take care of any necessary
preparations now.
This looks familiar.
It's like Kamino Ward.
I wonder if they
based it off that.
[TENYA] It's true that
the situations are similar.
But our only goal then
was to rescue Bakugo
from the villains.
We let the pros handle
search and recovery.
And you'll recall,
there were many casualties.
Not this time.
[SERO] Guys. You gotta
listen to this story.
It's pretty juicy.
What's the rating?
Triple X.
Go on.
[SERO] That fox in the
bodysuit from Shiketsu.
--The one over there.
--[KAMINARI] Yeah?
If you're just gonna say
she's hot, that's obvious.
I've had my eyes on her since
the moment we crossed paths.
Well, get this.
I saw her hiding in the
rocks with Midoriya,
buck naked.
[BOTH]
Midoriya!
What were you doing
while the rest of us
were just trying to
stay alive, you bastard?!
Was this entire test
nothing but a joke for you?
Guys, cool it! What's going on?
Don't play stupid with us!
What devious things were you
doing with that uber hottie?
[giggles]
[MINETA shrieks] The casual
greeting exchanged between
a man and woman whose
sexual relationship
has advanced several bases!
Just how Plus Ultra did you
end up going with her?
Uh-- Now I get it. Sero talked.
Listen, guys. Whatever
he told you is wrong.
It was a side effect
of her Quirk.
Actually, I had no idea
what was happening
and almost failed the test.
[KAMINARI]
But you did see her naked?
Well, sorta.
[MINETA]
Don't you lie to us!
[KAMINARI]
Why is she still waving at you?
[MINETA] Give us details,
Midoriya, I beg you.
[IZUKU] I told you,
nothing weird went down!
Oh, hey, it's Shiketsu.
[MORA]
Bakugo.
[KATSUKI]
What?
[MORA] I think you met
Shishikura in the test.
My classmate with the
flesh-molding power?
[KIRISHIMA]
So much hair.
Yeah. I took him out.
[MORA]
I thought so.
[gasps]
[MORA] I'm guessing he
may have acted rudely,
or perhaps offended you.
He has a tendency
to try and push
his own values onto others.
He probably couldn't
help it in your case,
since you're pretty famous.
I apologize for him.
I'd like to build
a good relationship
between our schools.
I-I guess he wants
to be friends?
So he says.
But the way they were fighting,
it didn't seem that way.
[TODOROKI]
"A good relationship."
But then there's that guy.
[MORA]
Anyway. That's it.
Hey. You with the collar.
Did I offend you somehow?
Huh?
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
Did I hurt your feelings?
Well, the thing is,
son of Endeavor...
[gasps]
I just can't help
but hate both of you.
You've changed a little bit
since the first time
our paths crossed.
But you definitely still
have your father's eyes.
[TODOROKI gasps]
[MORA]
Something wrong, Yoarashi?
Nope, not a thing, sir!
[TODOROKI]
My father's eyes?
Todoroki...
See you out there.
Ah! Yeah! Sure!
"See you out there"?
What is that supposed to mean.
You're an insatiable deviant!
[IZUKU] I told you,
it's not what you think.
That girl is actually
super scary.
Please. You're
acting disgracefully.
This test isn't over.
You need to focus.
[MINETA]
Just look at her!
[YAOYOROZU] Have you even
begun to strategize?
[OCHACO] I don't like this.
Why do I feel so flustered?
I was fine when I was
fighting earlier.
[OCHACO]
But now...
--Dek--
--[bell rings]
[MERA] Villains have
performed a large-scale
terrorist attack spanning
all of Insert City Name Here.
Since most buildings collapsed,
there are many injured.
Guess that's the
background story.
[gasps] So, then...
We're starting.
[MERA] Due to heavily damaged
roads, the first responders
have unfortunately been
delayed for the time being.
[KAMINARI]
What is with these rooms?
[MERA] Until emergency
services arrive,
the heroes in the area will
lead the rescue efforts.
Your task is to save as
many people as you can
and help the injured.
And with that...
Begin!
[TENYA] Saving lives
is the greatest ambition
a hero can have!
[IZUKU]
We have to do this properly.
And succeed!
[SHINDO] He mentioned points,
but he didn't say anything
about how we'd
actually be scored.
[TODOROKI]
Since we're in the dark,
all we can do is
follow our training.
Come on, come on,
come on, let's do this!
[TENYA] Let's start by heading
to the closest urban area.
We'll work as a team
as much as possible.
[STUDENTS]
Right!
[ASHIDO]
You're going on your own again?
[KATSUKI growls] Why are you
damn extras always following me?
[BOTH]
We just wanna!
[MERA]
Right, so, uh...
Try to get this over
quickly for me, yeah?
Rescue exercises.
[TSUYU] Even though this is just
a test, it feels pretty real.
Stay alert!
Be careful of falling
debris and explosions.
[gasps]
[HUC CHILD 57A crying]
[TENYA]
What's wrong, Midoriya?
[IZUKU]
I hear someone.
[HUC CHILD 57A crying]
Help me, please!
[IZUKU]
Look! There he is.
[HUC CHILD 57A]
My grandpa! He's been crushed.
I think he's hurt.
Oh, no. This looks bad.
Where is he?
"This looks bad"?
That's points off your score!
[IZUKU yelps]
[HUC CHILD 57A]
The first thing you should do
is see how bad my injuries
are and if I can walk.
I'm breathing kinda
weird, too, aren't I?
And didn't you even notice
that I'm bleeding from the head?
People with hero licenses
should be able to judge
a victim's condition
in an instant!
[IZUKU]
Are the members of HUC the ones
who are gonna be scoring us?
Your gross lack of training
is all too apparent right now.
You better shape up and
pay attention, newbies!
[EXAMINEE 57A]
All right.
Let's rope this area off
as a hazard zone.
No. That's not enough.
Think about it. This
whole area's unstable.
[MORA] I'll clear a path and
make a helicopter landing spot.
Watch out.
[PRESENT MIC]
Shiketsu High, second year.
Nagamasa Mora!
His Quirk: Extend-o-Hair!
He can grow all
the hair on his body
and manipulate it at will.
The only bad thing is how
easily it gets tangled.
[YOARASHI]
That was awesome, Mora!
You're amazing.
Here's the first-aid station.
There's a lot of space.
We can make part of this
an evacuation zone.
Good.
I'll be in charge of triage.
Leave the setup to me.
[AIZAWA] When it comes
to saving innocent lives,
experience really does
make a difference.
[HUC CHILD 57A] You're not
just here to provide aid.
Until the police and
firefighters show up,
you need to exercise
authority and make sure
this goes off smoothly.
Think of the victims here.
They must be terrified.
There are many aspects
of being a hero.
But take note.
There is one thing to keep
in mind above all else.
Anyone who needs
rescuing is having
the worst day of their lives.
And the first thing you said was
"This looks bad"? Seriously?
[IZUKU gasps]
[ALL MIGHT]
Fear not, citizens.
Hope has arrived.
Because I am here.
[growls]
[IZUKU]
I've got to get it together.
I need to do my best.
Passing this test
and getting my license
aren't just things I have
to do to succeed at school.
They're essential if I'm going
to become a real hero.
The kind I want to be.
Steps toward achieving my dream!
Hey! It's fine!
[sobs] Over there! My grandpa!
Don't you worry.
We'll definitely save him.
I can carry this boy to the
first aid station myself.
You guys, go on without me!
[TENYA]
All right!
Let's do this.
[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
[IZUKU] It'll be all right!
It'll be all right.
[HUC CHILD 57A]
Is that your only line?
You're terrible at this.
[IZUKU]
I'll save you! I promise I will!
[HUC CHILD 57A]
Shut up!
[OCHACO] This buzz in
my chest. What am I doing?
[AOYAMA]
Is it... because you like him?
It's love!
[OCHACO] I've gotta push
these feelings down.
Deku is giving his all
to reach his goal.
No room for anything else.
I don't wanna change that.
You've got a crush
on someone, right?
So do I. And I bet
you also wanna be
exactly like that
special person, huh?
[OCHACO]
I'll put these feelings away.
I'll focus on working
just as hard as he does.
[OCHACO]
And reach my dream.
[MERA] It's been ten minutes
since we started.
Everyone's doing well
for the most part.
But there's still a ways to go.
What's a test without
a few surprises.
[MERA]
I hope they didn't think things
would be straightforward.
Inasa Yoarashi,
a Shiketsu first year.
My Hero name is Gale Force!
Rescue exercises
get me pumped up.
You're gonna be safe with me!
[MORA]
Inasa!
[HUC BABY 57A chuckles]
Wind, eh?
[HUC BABY 57A] Seems like
a sloppy approach at first.
But in reality he's manipulating
countless airstreams
to adapt to all the people
and debris he's moving.
Hah. His subtle control
is unbelievable.
But it's still reckless!
Minus Points.
Ah--
[MORA] You shouldn't move
anyone or anything unless
you've checked on the
condition of the injured.
You could make things worse.
Of course. I apologize!
[SHIKETSU STUDENT 57A]
Hey. Camie ran off again.
What's her deal lately?
Are you all right?!
Reckless!
Ah--
[SHISHIKURA]
The quality of one's training
is most apparent in their
initial response to a situation.
Take Inasa.
He petitioned to take
the test even though
it's normally reserved
for second-year students,
and was strong enough
to be accepted.
He even passed the first round.
However, he's acting
far too impatient.
His lack of experience
is obvious.
You realize you're
sitting in the stands
because you're the one who
failed. Right, Shishikura?
Yes, I am aware.
Just checking.
You should use this as a chance
to analyze what went wrong.
Reflect on your bad influences.
[SHISHIKURA]
What do you mean?
[SHIKETSU TEACHER 57A]
Seems to me you've taken
Stain's words to heart.
[SHISHIKURA] Me? Influenced
by a villain? Absurd.
[SHIKETSU TEACHER 57A]
No, it's not.
Listen, what he taught
wasn't necessarily all bad.
Between Stain's
fundamentalist ideas
and All Might's retirement,
there are many who wish
to reform the role
that heroes play in society.
That's just fine.
But if negativity
and hate take over,
like they did for you during
the first round of the exam,
they can impair your judgment
and keep you from
your potential.
[EXAMINEE 57D]
There's someone in here.
But they're not
responding when I yell.
It's way too dark for me to see.
[EXAMINEE 57AA] I can at least
check their pulse and breathing.
I'll make some
room for treatment.
[SERO]
They're so good at this.
[YAOYOROZU] Everyone! We should
be moving quickly as well.
This old man's conscious.
He needs help.
[HUC ELDERLY MAN 57A] It hurts!
What are you waiting for?
He's trapped by debris.
I'll float it away.
[HUC ELDERLY MAN 57A]
Poor girl.
She's gonna lose
points that way.
Please wait a moment.
Look at the way the walls
have collapsed around him.
Right now, the structure
is balanced precariously,
like an intricate puzzle.
Everything will topple
if we're careless
with our movements.
We have to do
this strategically.
Now I see. You're right.
[YAOYOROZU]
First, let's use a support beam
to prop up this wall.
It'll take some time to get
everything into place though.
[SERO] No worries.
You can leave that to us!
How's that for a brace?
[SERO]
I've reinforced the wall, too.
Now, then. Your turn!
Move the debris
that doesn't affect
the structure and
make a path! On it!
[HUC ELDERLY MAN 57A]
It's not perfect,
but it's not a
horrible plan, either.
[HUC ELDERLY MAN 57A] When
there's a large-scale disaster,
there are never enough rescuers
to help those in need of saving.
That means the work
should be as fast
and efficient as possible.
If someone tries to do
everything themselves,
they'll lose time
in the long run.
What's important is
being realistic about
what your own Quirk
can and can't do,
and then figuring out how
you can divide the labor
with the other heroes.
Focusing on your role
during a test where you're
trying to stand out
takes courage.
It's something you can only do
if you really understand
the situation.
But there is still a lot
of wasted effort here.
If they keep going like this,
we won't be able to
grant them licenses.
This isn't good.
We're just standing
around and watching.
[SHOJI] Several people already
went off on their own.
Unlike in the first round,
we may need to split up
for this one.
We could move in smaller groups.
In that case, I'll be
of much more help
if I head to the river.
I'll join you.
[HAGAKURE]
Me, too!
Guys, work together?
--[ASHIDO] Cool beans!
--[TOKOYAMI] Sure.
Yo, Koda.
Can you use animals
to look for people
who need rescuing?
[SHOJI]
I'll keep my eyes open.
Mineta. Will you help me?
Sure thing!
[TENYA] Good. Depending
on the situation,
we should also work together
with other schools.
That's how we'll save lives.
[STUDENTS]
Right!
[AOYAMA] Did you say
it was too dark in there?
Allow my twinkling
to save the day!
[EXAMINEE 57D]
Perfect. Thanks!
That's a shocker.
I didn't think you'd
be the first to help.
But, then, you do
love that pose.
[TENYA]
Yaoyorozu.
We'll disperse across
the field and get to work.
Roger that!
I think his right leg is broken.
Sero! Tape him up!
[SERO]
I got him.
All right, Jiro.
Look for the next person
in need of rescue.
I'm on it. Gimme a sec.
[HUC MAN 57A]
Help. Someone!
My arm hurts pretty bad.
Mine, too. Save us.
Shut up! Save yourselves,
you whiners.
[BOTH yelp]
Man, you've gotta work
on your rescue style.
They might be really hurt--
we can't just leave 'em here.
Wait.
We are supposed to be
low-priority victims
with only minor injuries.
So you think...
that he figured it out.
And that's why he told us
to go off on our own?
You're kidding me.
They took it in a way
that made it sound okay?
[KIRISHIMA] We'll get
you two somewhere safe.
[KAMINARI]
Yeah!
His tone was
wildly inappropriate.
Minus points.
[KATSUKI]
What the hell did you say?!
[BOTH yelp]
[SHOJI] I hear a voice.
Coming from over there!
[TENYA]
Excellent.
I'll go first to check
on the conditions
of those who need to be rescued.
[MINETA]
Sounds good.
[TENYA]
Even if this weren't a test,
I would still reach out to
save those looking for help.
Because I'm sure
that's what my brother,
Tensei, would've done.
[OJIRO]
Let's head to the mountain zone.
There should be
animals over there!
[ASHIDO] Smart! Then Koda
can use his Quirk!
[HAGAKURE]
Todoroki! Tsuyu! Over there!
[HUC BOY 57A]
Help! I can't swim.
[TSUYU]
I'll be right there.
We might need to
warm the boy up.
Let's gather firewood.
[HAGAKURE]
Leave it to me!
We're almost to a safe
space, don't you worry.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
There are so many.
You, there. Let me see that boy!
Yeah, of course.
His head got hurt somehow.
He's bleeding quite a bit,
but his wounds don't
look very deep.
He responds to
questions clearly.
[EXAMINEE 57BB]
Hm. He should be fine.
Take him to the space
over there on the right.
Yes, ma'am!
[HUC CHILD 57A]
Good.
[GANG ORCA] In the short
time until emergency
responders arrive,
heroes must act alone.
Helping the victims
and performing first aid.
Once the professionals show up,
the transition
should be seamless.
How goes it?
[MERA]
Let's see.
During their initial response,
there was some poor judgement.
But the points taken off
by HUC members
are still pretty minimal.
The students are doing
better than expected.
Less incompetence than
usual, I would say.
[GANG ORCA]
Wonderful.
But in order to protect
citizens in need,
heroes must multitask.
They can't just rescue.
They must adapt.
[gasps] What happened?
[KIRISHIMA yelps]
--[KIRISHIMA] Whoa!
--[KAMINARI] We're gonna die!
Explosions?
[HAGAKURE]
What?
[OCHACO]
Wait. Could this be...
[MERA] A villain has completed
another large-scale attack.
Everyone! This is
part of the exam.
You think so?
That means...
[EXAMINEE 57E]
Hey, look!
[IZUKU gasps]
[GANG ORCA]
Tell me, wannabe heroes.
Can you rescue people
and fight at the same time?
That's Gang Orca!
[MERA] During the
search-and-destroy mission
against the League of Villains,
Gang Orca fought alongside
Endeavor and Best Jeanist.
[MERA] He's a strong pro,
currently ranked number ten.
Impressive. He's also ranked
third in the list of heroes
who look as though
they should be villains.
[MERA]
The terrorists have appeared
and are beginning
to sweep the area.
Hero candidates at the
scene should continue
their rescue efforts
while also suppressing
the newly-arrived villains.
[TENYA] We're gonna have
to save people and battle?
Are they serious?!
Jeez! Come on!
Aren't they expecting
too much from us?
Even for a pro,
this would be difficult.
They're going a
little far I'd say.
[GANG ORCA]
Now. How will you react?
Will you fight or protect?
Help or run away?
What would a hero do?
[ALL MIGHT]
I am here for the preview!
Next week will be a special,
completely original episode!
Why? For fun!
Next time on My Hero Academia :
"Save the World with Love!"
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!