[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward my
dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
The first 100 students
to fulfill the requirements
will pass today.
The examinee will put
three of these targets
on his or her body.
They can go anywhere you want
as long as it's an exposed area.
So no soles of the
feet or armpits.
Each of you will also
have six of these balls.
The targets are
programmed to light up
whenever they've been
touched by the balls.
If all three targets
light up, you're out.
Oh, and the person who
lights up your third target
will get credit for your defeat.
You get through this round
by taking down two people.
I'm sure each of you
have different terrains
that you like or want to avoid.
Use your Quirks well
and do your best.
Or not. Whatever.
[MERA]
Let's see.
The 62nd person has
passed the exam.
[sighs] Another 38,
and it'll finally be over.
All right, guys. Let's
think about our situation.
At the beginning of the test,
we focused on attacking UA,
splitting them up and putting
them in check right off the bat.
Now our school's going
after them in two groups.
But a bunch of other classes
took advantage of our work.
And we're at the final
stage of the test.
So everyone's fighting
at max levels,
and the arena's full
of chaos. It's a warzone!
Your attack kinda backfired.
We didn't take out
any of those kids.
I mean, I know I was rushing,
but if you really
think about it,
this is a pretty good
place to be in.
As long as we don't freak out,
we can take advantage
of the current state of the exam
and the desperate
players involved.
Right now, all anyone
can think about
is the number of slots left,
so they're panicking
and no doubt being careless.
Burning through stamina.
They've got tunnel vision,
and are focusing on UA,
since they have
the most intel on them, which
means that we can lie in wait
until the perfect
moment to strike.
We've basically already
passed the test.
It's about time you stopped
pretending to be so nice.
Honestly. You're too sneaky, yo.
[SHINDO] I'd prefer
to be called "tactful."
Besides, if we swoop in
at the eleventh hour
and make it a good
show, it'll prove
we have an indomitable spirit.
Everyone taking this
exam is struggling
to live up to their own ideals.
I respect that.
But unfortunately,
I can't go easy on 'em.
[SHISHIKURA] UA High.
I have respect for your school.
I take pride in the fact
that our institutions
are treated as equals.
But your class is shameful.
You act in ways
that disgrace heroes.
He's attacking again!
I don't wanna be gross!
Shut up!
"Obligation"? "Dignity"?
You just like to
hear yourself talk.
I don't see any proof.
Show us with your actions,
not your cheap words.
If you can.
Beast. You're worst
of all, Bakugo!
AP Shot. Auto-Cannon!
[SHISHIKURA grunts]
I had to make a weak version
so I didn't kill anyone.
You know what,
this is why everyone's
terrified of you--
you're way too hardcore!
Dammit.
[SHISHIKURA]
I can't believe I fell for that.
But I won't again.
So those nasty finger things
just float back to 'im?
[SHISHIKURA] He's the type
who reacts impulsively
to a simple provocation.
This sort of
mentality comes from
an inflated sense of pride.
I see now.
I'll teach you a lesson
by breaking you.
This will show you what
it means to be dignified
and behave like a hero!
What is up with
this disgusting dude?
He thinks he's better than us.
But I bet he'll
shut up when I...
[KAMINARI]
Hey, wait, don't forget
that we're in the
middle of a test!
That's exactly why
I'll kill the guy!
Absurd!
Ugh. Let's just get
this fight over with.
Maybe this'll speed
things along.
You should work on your aim.
Ah-- Aw, crap!
And your look.
Maybe I can make you
something more appealing.
[KATSUKI]
Enough talk. Die!
You've left yourself open.
What the--?
[SHISHIKURA]
You weren't paying attention.
I had a piece of flesh
sneak beneath us.
You saw. Earlier with Kirishima.
Once I touch you,
you're my plaything.
Bakugo!
[KATSUKI]
Hey! Idiot! Fix this!
[SHISHIKURA] Pathetic. You must
be remade from scratch.
[PRESENT MIC] Shiketsu
High School. Second year.
Seiji Shishikura.
His Quirk: Meatball!
He can reshape flesh
by massaging it.
For someone else's body,
he can only knead it
and make it a ball.
But, his own flesh
is more versatile!
For example, he can cut it off,
manipulate it, or make
controllable objects.
It's as handy
as it is horrifying!
No way!
[SHISHIKURA]
This is a demonstration.
The test has an unusually
low passing rate.
At first this
seemed counterintuitive
given our current world.
With All Might retired,
wouldn't it make more sense
to flood the streets
with heroes?
And so,
I must assume that their goal
is to weed out the riffraff.
We can surmise that they're
starting to be more selective
in order to bring the profession
of hero to a higher level.
And I agree with
this way of thinking.
So I decided to thin
the herd myself.
You're ignoring the test
because you think
you're superior?
What are you, a crazy person?
[SHISHIKURA] I'm simply
separating the mediocre
and extraordinary. By the way,
your comrades here still
feel pain in this form.
Your untamed electricity
will torture
your friends if you use it.
Ugh. You've been doing nothing
but hurling insults
at us this entire time.
I'm kinda starting to take
it personally, ya know.
Then perhaps you are more
self-aware than I thought.
I'd take time to reflect
on your failure.
[KAMINARI]
How 'bout you reflect on this!
[SHISHIKURA grunts]
[SHISHIKURA] An explosion?
But I stopped Bakugo.
His equipment?
Those ugly-ass
gauntlets of his aren't
just some kind of
fashion statement.
He can use that gear
along with his nitro sweat
to create simple grenades.
That's it! He tossed it to you.
[KAMINARI]
By the way, big shot.
You've stumbled into
a really killer spot.
[yells]
[POWER LOADER]
Sharpshooting?
[KAMINARI] I can't really
manipulate electricity,
so it gets hard to fight
with other people around.
Do you think you could
help me with that?
[POWER LOADER]
I've got a solution
to your problem, I think.
We're calling it a
pointer and shooter.
It's a genius baby the two
of us collaborated on!
Fire with the pointer
set to "Shooter,"
and the projectile
will stick on impact.
As long as you're within
ten meters of the spot
you've tagged, your
electricity will be gathered
in a single line.
If you have multiple targets,
then you can use the
dial to select them.
The attached scope
will help you lock on
to their exact locations.
Uh... You mean it requires
a lot of thinking?
But if I fight with this,
then I won't run the risk
of zapping my teammates, will I?
[KAMINARI]
I understand, Bakugo.
You stopped our
opponent's attacks using
your smaller-ranged new move
instead of a big explosion.
Not because you were
testing it out,
but so you wouldn't
hit me or Kirishima.
You actually had
us on your mind.
Listen up.
Bakugo might seem like
a total jerk on the surface,
but he's actually trying
really hard to be a pro hero.
He threw that grenade
to me while being attacked.
That was the result of
calm judgment and planning.
And Kirishima is
such a good dude
that he rushed into enemy
territory for his friends,
even though it was a
totally stupid thing to do.
[SHISHIKURA] Blast. I lost
my hold on them for a second.
[KAMINARI] You only know bits
and pieces of information
about these guys. Don't insult
what you don't know!
[SHISHIKURA] I'll teach you
to be more aware of your place.
You degenerate!
[SHISHIKURA groans]
[KIRISHIMA]
The more damage he takes,
the more people get released.
[KATSUKI]
No wonder he was only using
long-distance attacks.
Thanks for the save, Kaminari.
You idiot. What took so long?
Why are you so mean?
No one's ever gonna like
you if you act that way!
Whoa, look behind you!
Those other fleshballs
are all waking up.
We've got targets.
[EXAMINEES chattering]
[MERA]
Currently 70 people have passed.
Thirty more and we'll be done.
[TODOROKI]
Where are my classmates?
Maybe the information everyone
had on us did them in.
Good, I'm glad to see
you passed, Todoroki.
I didn't doubt you.
[JIRO]
Have you seen the others?
[TODOROKI] No. So far
we're the only ones here.
I just arrived.
[SHOJI]
We can't count them out.
I thought Midoriya had
everyone working together.
[YAOYOROZU]
That was the plan, but someone
from Ketsubutsu Academy
split us up with his Quirk.
[JIRO]
Just 30 spots left.
[TSUYU] I hope everyone
in our class passes.
Faster, Sero!
[SERO]
Midoriya! Carry me and jump!
Uh?
[SERO]
Just do it!
You're up, Uraraka!
Release!
[EXAMINEES yelp]
Tape? Seriously?
They stuck boulders on
the ends and trapped us!
Not me!
Wh-What?
[SERO]
I gave some tape to Uraraka
and had her set
some snares for us.
Oh, whoa.
I said to get as many as
possible, but this is nuts.
In order to make sure
that no one was in a spot
where they'd get
crushed by the debris.
I hid and figured out
the perfect timing.
[MERA] Looks like 76 people
have passed at this point.
We'll be at capacity soon.
[SERO]
We don't have much time,
and I'm sure others
will come for us soon.
Let's take 'em out.
You guys are first years, right?
C'mon, can't you
give us a break?
We have to earn our
provisional hero licenses
this time around.
I'm sorry, but so do I.
[MERA]
That's 79 people.
Everyone's moving at
an exhaustive pace now.
[SERO]
Wow, that was fast.
[TARGET] Students who
have passed the exam
should congregate in
the anteroom. Chop, chop.
[IZUKU]
Are the others already there?
[MERA sighs]
Hope these kids don't take
their youthful
energy for granted.
The battle royale format
is nothing new for the exam,
but this time, the patterns
are a bit unusual.
UA is always heavily
targeted from the get go,
but so far, all of those
students are still on the board.
[TENYA gasps]
That's...
[AOYAMA gasps]
[TENYA]
Aoyama!
Bonjour. Are you out here alone?
What a coincidence. So am I.
[TENYA]
I've been trying to find as many
of our classmates as I can.
There's a handful
of us gathered nearby,
but I came to look
for stragglers.
[gasps] So you left the group
just to come help the others?
[TENYA grunts]
[AOYAMA laughs]
You're so funny.
How do you even think
you'll find people out here?
And what are you gonna do
if everyone left behind
passes without you?
[TENYA] First of all,
I found you, didn't I?
And if everyone else
passes the test,
that's a wonderful thing.
I'm our class representative.
It's my duty to lead the others.
I want to serve our peers
to the best of my abilities.
That's what my brother would do.
It's through my actions that
I'll realize my ultimate dream.
[AOYAMA]
Your ultimate dream?
[TENYA] Obviously, I do wanna
get my provisional license.
And the test will be
coming to an end soon.
So I'll continue my search
while trying to pass.
Please, work with me!
[MERA] Oh. Three more
one after the other.
Our total's at 82...
[KIRISHIMA] Whoa, this entire
arena's going insane.
Hey, look, some of
our classmates.
Aw, yeah! Class-A represent!
Oh, you know it!
Our class is amazing! We did it!
[SERO, KAMINARI, OCHACO,
KIRISHIMA] Class 1-A. Class 1-A.
Class 1-A. Class 1-A. Class 1-A.
Class 1-A. Class 1-A!
So you passed, too.
How'd you manage that, Deku?
Kacchan. Hey!
[IZUKU] Oh, boy, here it comes.
It's been a while though!
Ever since Kamino, he hasn't
been near as mean to me.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised
with that Quirk you got.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
Wait. Hold on. What did he say?
It looks like you've made
that borrowed power your own.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
You'll see.
I'll work until
I have full control
of this borrowed Quirk.
And I'll finally beat you
with my own power!
Kacchan...
Oh, hey! What a relief.
I was starting
to get so worried!
No need to worry
about us, Yao-momo.
What's up? When did
you guys pass?
You been here long?
[SHOJI] We just finished
as well. Todoroki beat us.
[JIRO] I was kinda shocked
Bakugo wasn't here already.
But I get it now. It's
because you were with him.
Oh, come on!
Why is everyone
dragging me today?
Ochaco?
The key to take off your
targets is in the back.
They asked us to return
them to the shelf
now that we're done.
Oh, cool. Thank you, Tsu.
I'll do that.
Looks like only 11 from
our class have passed.
So nine more to go.
And the announcement said
only 18 spots left.
[IZUKU]
Come on, guys.
That target's mine!
Oui!
[TENYA]
Aoyama!
There are two of us, Iida.
This has turned into a war.
Iit's going to be très hard
for both of us to survive it!
Just leave me here.
[TENYA]
What are you talking about?
Keep fighting! Class 1-A
does not give up.
Non, that's not what I'm doing.
[TENYA]
We're finished if we stay put.
Ah, balls, almost out of time!
So how are we gonna
get our points?
[MERA] Wow. Eight people just
passed at the same time.
That leaves only ten open spots.
Ha! Those eight were
all from my class!
See 'em? They're headed
into the anteroom.
Great job there, kiddos!
[AIZAWA]
Ten people left.
Looks like our class...
...still has nine people
who haven't passed.
I hate to say it, but it's
not sounding good for us.
[TENYA]
I want to serve our peers
to the best of my abilities.
That's what my brother would do.
It's through my actions that
I'll realize my ultimate dream.
[AOYAMA]
Your ultimate dream...
Papa! Maman!
Why am I so different
from everybody else?
[TENYA gasps]
Um. What is that?
[TENYA]
Are you out of your mind?
Seriously. What are you doing?
I'm standing out.
[TENYA]
Yes. Yes, you are.
That's exactly the problem.
If you try to protect me,
you'll fail the test.
I've already got two
of my triggers hit,
and they'll be swarming me soon.
You'll have a much better
chance without me.
Please. Let me do this for you.
[TENYA gasps]
[AOYAMA] While I've got the
spotlight, you can sneak up
on the people who come after me.
With your speed, you should
be able to hit their targets.
[TENYA]
Where is this even coming from?
Something you said
earlier inspired me.
Your ultimate dream.
I always wanted to be an equal
to the amazing people
at our school.
Our enemies'll be
here soon. Get ready!
[TENYA]
You can't!
[EXAMINEES yelling]
[AOYAMA]
Now! You have to run!
[EXAMINEE 56H]
Wait. What are those!
[EXAMINEES yelp]
Damn birds!
Where'd they come from?
[TENYA]
This is...
[KODA]
Thank you, birds.
Please continue
to swarm this area!
Black Abyss!
Covert Black-Ops Arms!
Crap! I'm stuck!
What are these things?
[yells]
[EXAMINEES grunting]
Damn it!
[MINETA]
Go, go, go, go, go!
Get some out while
they're distracted!
Iida, what're you doing?
Don't just stand there!
[TENYA]
You came for us!
[EXAMINEE 56Q]
It's UA!
[HAGAKURE]
Warp Refraction: Say Cheese!
[EXAMINEE 56Q]
My eyes! I can't see!
[EXAMINEES yelling]
[HAGAKURE]
I've got two people out.
Same here!
[MERA] That's two more in.
Eight spots left.
Wait. Why would they...?
[ASHIDO] Everyone was going
nuts and getting desperate
in the final minutes.
I couldn't see anything!
I couldn't tell who
was friend or foe!
But then we spotted
your bellybutton laser,
and we knew we'd
be able to meet up
with our classmates again!
C'mon. Let's do this!
[yelps]
[MERA]
Seven spaces remain!
Sorry.
[MERA]
Six left!
[MERA] Make that five!
The pressure's on, now!
In the final minutes,
UA came together and pulled off
some absolutely insane combos!
[AIZAWA] There were that many
of you left on the field?
--[MERA] Four spots!
--[KODA] I did it!
--[MERA] Now three!
--[SATO] I'm in!
[MERA] Ooh! That's one in
from Shiketsu High!
So only two spots remain.
[TENYA] Aoyama. I don't
know who you want
to be equal with,
because I don't know
what you're measuring
yourself against.
[EXAMINEES yelp]
[TENYA] But this was
your doing! Thank you!
Well, I guess this
means my twinkling
won't have to stop after all.
[TENYA]
No. Keep twinkling.
Whatever that means.
--[alarm blares]
--The last students passed!
Every spot is now filled!
One hundred students
will advance!
The end is finally
here! Wah-hoo!
[KAMINARI, KIRISHIMA]
Yeah!
Our entire class passed
the test, I'm so excited!
Aw, man! I am so proud of us!
Ribbit, ribbit!
[sighs] We really pulled
it off, you guys.
[SHOJI]
Yeah.
[MERA] Unfortunately,
those of you who failed
will now have to withdraw
from the licensing exam.
Please leave the
test area immediately.
They just had to keep me
on the edge of my seat, huh?
We're training so hard
when we get back.
Oh, come on, you're
happy, aren't you?
Furious.
[MS JOKE] Then what's
that sparkle in your eye?
--[AIZAWA] Annoyance.
--[MS JOKE laughing]
[YOARASHI] Huh?! What do
you mean Shishikura
didn't pass the test?
[MORA]
Tone it down.
It's because he went ahead
of us and fought alone,
like he didn't need help.
Just like you two.
Yoarashi at least has the
excuse that he's a first year.
But not you, Camie!
Yeah, yeah.
[MERA]
Oh, right.
For the 100 of you who
passed the first test,
please turn your
attention to the screen.
Huh. It's the test arena.
What's gonna happen next?
[STUDENTS]
Why?
Wait. Does that mean...?
[MERA] There's only one
more round to the exam.
Your goal is simple:
undertake rescue exercises
and save the bystanders
who are trapped
in these disaster sites.
A rescue mission.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
The final test is to save people
who're trapped around the arena.
The hero license and this exam.
They're both steps
toward my dream!
Next time: "Rescue Exercises"!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!