[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward my
dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome obstacles
and save people with
a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Midoriya. Listen.
I'm officially retired as a pro.
It's clear now that my body
won't allow me to
fight another battle.
[ALL MIGHT] The last sparks
of One For All have left me.
And my muscle form won't last
for any significant
amount of time.
I can't protect you
when you put yourself
in danger now.
And you're always rushing
in to try and help,
no matter what I tell you.
Destroying your body,
over and over.
Yet, back there,
you managed to...
[ALL MIGHT] ...rescue your
friend without being injured
or getting into a fight.
I'm so proud of you.
[gasps]
[ALL MIGHT]
From here on out,
I will devote myself
to training you.
You're stuck with me.
So let's keep working
hard together.
Thank you.
Nothing would make me
happier, All Might.
I'll do my best!
Wait. This isn't...
Oh, right. I'm in the dorm now.
[IZUKU]
Good morning.
[IZUKU] After being attacked
by the League of Villains
twice in one school year,
UA brought its students
to live on campus
in order to keep us safe.
[IZUKU] Our dorm, Heights
Alliance, was a five-minute walk
from the main school building.
Things were a little strange
at first, but once we finally
settled into our
new home, we returned
to normal coursework and our
goal of becoming heroes.
[IZUKU] I will definitely
be a pro one day.
Because of what I
inherited from All Might.
Not just One For All,
but his spirit, too!
[AIZAWA] I believe I
mentioned this already,
but your main focus this summer
is obtaining provisional
hero licenses.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
Do not take this lightly.
A hero license means that you're
responsible for human lives.
You can imagine that the exam to
receive one is very difficult.
Only 50 percent of
students pass the tests
required for these
permits each year.
It's that hard to get
a provisional license?
[AIZAWA] In order to prepare,
today you'll concentrate
on creating something new.
[AIZAWA]
Two ultimate moves.
[KAMINARI, KIRISHIMA]
Ultimate moves?
[BOTH] An exam is a
normal school thing.
[KIRISHIMA, SERO]
But this is total hero work!
[ECTOPLASM] When we say
"ultimate," we mean a move
that will ensure you win
against your opponent.
[CEMENTOSS] An action
so unique to your identity
that no other person
can hope to copy it.
Simply put,
you must learn to lean
into your strengths.
[MIDNIGHT] Your moves
represent who you are.
These days, most pro heroes
have an ultimate move.
Those who don't are fools.
This may sound abstract,
but we'll explain more
as the day goes on.
For now, change
into your costumes
and meet in Gym Gamma.
[AIZAWA] Gym Gamma,
also known at the Academy
as the "Training
Dining Land," or TDL.
[OCHACO, ASHIDO, IZUKU]
Huh?
[IZUKU]
First the USJ, and now this?
This facility was my idea.
We can prepare unique
terrains and obstacles
for each student here.
Here you will learn
to serve up justice,
hence the name.
That's pretty cool.
[TENYA]
Please allow me a question.
What is the advantage
of having ultimate moves
for our provisional exam?
May we know your reasoning?
That's two questions. Calm down.
The job of a hero
is to save people
from all sorts of dangers.
Crime, accidents, and natural
or man-made disasters.
Of course, the
licensing exam analyzes
how well you're able
to deal with such things.
It won't just be fighting.
Your ability to
gather information
and make quick decisions
will be judged.
In addition to how well
you communicate, cooperate,
and lead others.
Every year a new test is used
to evaluate these qualities.
One thing is
especially important.
If you want to be a pro hero,
you must be able to
prevail in battle.
If you're prepared,
you won't have to worry.
And those of you with
an ultimate move
will have stronger results.
Your circumstances
should not dictate
the results of your
future battles.
Learn to be consistent and
you will be a great asset
on the front lines.
[ECTOPLASM] Your ultimate
move doesn't necessarily
have to be an attack.
Take Iida's Reciproburst,
for example.
[TENYA gasps]
[ECTOPLASM] This sort of
temporary boost in speed
is valuable enough that
it falls into the category
of excellence we're looking for.
[TENYA gasps]
You mean I've been doing
an ultimate move all along?
So, it's basically
our secret weapon.
Something that gives us
the edge so we can win
no matter who or
what we're facing.
There's a smart boy.
For example, how
Kamui Woods is able
to use his Lacquered
Chain Prison
to capture opponents
in an instant.
That's exactly what
we want to see.
The training camp
was interrupted.
But the practice you did get
in to develop your Quirks
was part of the process
needed to create
these defining abilities.
Now that you're caught up--
you'll be working hard
to develop powerful moves
of your own for the
next ten days or so.
This is how you will
spend the remainder
of your summer vacation.
Prepare for intensive training.
In addition, you
should think about
how you can improve your
costumes, especially now
that you have a better
understanding of your Quirks.
I expect each of you
to go Plus Ultra.
Do you have it in you?
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
I am so charged up for this.
[IZUKU]
What's my move?
[ECTOPLASM]
It's obvious you're relying
too much on your tail.
Let's re-examine the
basics of how you fight.
Yes, sir!
[OJIRO]
But my tail is my power.
Ultimate move.
Shooting acid from
my hands. Super geyser!
Whaddaya think?
[ECTOPLASM] If you're
going to go that route,
make a nozzle with your fingers
to increase aim and reach.
Yes, like that. Go.
Oh, crap! I'm totally awesome!
[ECTOPLASM]
Now let's focus on increasing
the potency of your acid.
Two Creations at the same time.
You may start with
something simple.
Yes, sir!
[IZUKU]
Everyone's making headway.
[IZUKU grunts]
[ECTOPLASM] Why are you
staring off into space?
[IZUKU]
Oh, um.
About the moves we're
coming up with. See...
If I put too much
power into my arms,
then I won't be able
to use them anymore.
I'll break them.
So I don't know what
a special attack of mine
would even look like.
[ECTOPLASM] Hm. It's true that
your Quirk is interesting.
Not exactly one that
we'd call consistent.
If you don't have a
fixed attack style yet,
then let's focus on
developing your power.
Yes, sir.
[ALL MIGHT]
Everyone's workin' hard, huh?
[AIZAWA]
All Might.
Yeah, I am here.
Because I have the day
off and I don't have
anything else to do. Ha!
[AIZAWA] Will you please
focus on recuperating
and lesson planning?
Hey, why the cold reception?
They're workin' their
big moves now, right?
There's no way I could
miss being here for this.
I'm still a UA
teacher, you know.
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Midoriya.
Looks like you're
having trouble.
[crash]
Now you explode!
It's been a while since I was
able to really let loose.
Ectoplasm! I killed 'em!
Gimme another one.
That boy is incredible.
Yes. And he'll get even
stronger in the future.
Ooh. Look at that!
Bakugo's going hardcore.
I bet he's got a ton of ideas
for his special moves already.
[HAGAKURE]
He's been planning this stuff
since the entrance exam!
[yelps] Whoops!
[ECTOPLASM]
Focus!
[OCHACO]
Yes, sir!
[MINETA] Just in case
anyone was wondering,
I've been working on
Grape Rush since I was a kid.
I mean, we've all thought
about it before, right?
I used to imagine wielding
a lightning sword!
I'm getting hyped up
just thinking about
doing something that
cool in real life.
[IZUKU] How can I fight
with these damaged arms?
[ALL MIGHT]
Hey.
What are you doing here?
[ALL MIGHT]
I've come with advice.
Think for yourself.
You're still trying
to imitate me.
Oh. I guess I didn't...
Yo, Young Kirishima.
Hey, All Might.
[ALL MIGHT] I've got some
wisdom to lay down on ya.
[ALL MIGHT] So, instead of
going for small tricks
with your Hardening,
try being a bulldozer.
Yes, sir!
[ALL MIGHT]
I wouldn't be a good teacher
if I just gave you the answers.
Use that clever head
on your shoulders.
There's no right or wrong here.
What's important
is that you realize
your full potential on your own.
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Jiro. Listen up.
I have a few things
that might help you.
[AIZAWA]
He's suddenly good at this?
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] Regarding your
costume improvements.
Once you've figured out if
anything needs to change,
head to the
development studio here.
Get the experts to help you
out and give suggestions.
They'll know what to do.
Think for yourself.
You're still trying
to imitate me.
[IZUKU] I don't really get
why that's a bad thing.
But I know I have to do
something about this.
They have to have
some kind of brace
to reinforce my arms here.
I've gotta train my body
so I can wield One For All
at maximum power.
[IZUKU] And I need to figure
out a way to use my Quirk
in my ultimate move.
Otherwise, I'll fall
behind everyone else.
That's not going to happen.
I have to make it to the
top and achieve my dream.
[TENYA]
Ah, I see.
You're focusing on making
your own body float.
[OCHACO] Mm-hm. If I
increase my mobility,
I can use the martial arts
I learned from my
internship even more.
What are you doing?
It's quite simple.
I want to reduce
Recipro's drawbacks.
I plan on asking the development
studio to improve my radiator.
[OCHACO]
Oh! Hey there, Deku!
I was just wondering
where you were!
Don't run in the halls!
You here for costume
improvements, too?
Oh, Uraraka.
[BOTH gasp]
[HATSUME] Ow, ow, ow, ow,
owie, owie, ow.
[POWER LOADER coughs] Ya know,
you shouldn't try to mix
everything you can find in
the lab together like that.
[HATSUME chuckles] Failure is
the mother of invention,
Mr. Power Loader.
Thomas Edison said
something like that once.
[HATSUME coughs]
[HATSUME] Even if something
I make doesn't work
like I've envisioned it,
that doesn't mean
it's a waste of time.
You almost blew up
the entire design studio!
Will you please open your ears
and listen to me
for once? Hatsume!
Hey. When did you get here?
[OCHACO]
Boobs!
[HATSUME] Oh, sorry about
the sudden explosion.
It's been a while, huh?
Class 1A, right? Uh...
Yeah, I forgot all
your names already.
Uh, Izuku Midoriya. H--
I'm Tenya Iida!
The man you tricked into
being a walking advertisement
during the sports festival.
Never heard a' you.
Well, I'm busy developing
new babies, so, bye!
Wait a second, please!
I wanted to ask
Mr. Power Loader about
improving some elements
of my costume.
Wha... Wha... What?
You can count me in!
[POWER LOADER]
Hatsume!
It's fine for you to be in
and out of the studio all day
since you're in the dorms.
But if you stop
following my instructions
and keep running wild in here...
...you're banned.
Um. Hello.
[POWER LOADER]
I heard from Eraser Head.
You're here to upgrade
those costumes
for your new moves,
yes? Come in.
[IZUKU] Ooh! This looks
like a top-secret lab!
Now. Hand over your
instructions, please.
They should've been
with the case
your costume was delivered in.
I have a license
to make costumes,
so I'm allowed to do
some mild tinkering
with those that were
made out-of-house.
For small changes and repairs,
I can simply report what I
altered to the design company.
They'll do the paperwork for me.
But, for major changes,
we'll have to fill out
an application and ask
the design professionals to
make the adjustments for us.
After that's completed,
the government
will make sure the new costume
meets certain standards.
When approved,
it'll be sent back here.
And we work with the best
design agencies available.
So there's usually just
a three-day turnaround.
Uh, well.
I was wondering if there
was a way I could reduce
the strain on the
ligaments in my arms.
Is that hard? Or possible?
[POWER LOADER]
Hmm, let's see, Midoriya.
You mainly fight with your
fists and your fingers.
In that case,
I should be able to do
something for you pretty fast.
Deku, that's awesome!
Yeah!
Yes, yes, I see the problem.
H-Hatsume. What are
you doing to him?
[HATSUME]
I'm feeling out his muscles.
Oh, my, your body's much more
muscle-y than it looks.
[shrieks]
[HATSUME]
Don't you worry.
I've got just what you need.
My very special baby.
The power suit!
Okay.
This high-tech darling can read
muscle contractions and
support your movements.
Meet my baby number 49!
Um. But I really just need
support for my arms.
[HATSUME]
Program Start!
Holy whoa. This
thing is amazing!
Wait. No. I take it back.
My spine! It's
twisting me in half!
--Oh, god, I'm gonna die.
--[OCHACO] Are you okay?
End program.
Looks like I made
a mistake or two
in the limit calculations.
That's my bad.
Oh, my gosh, are you hurt?
[IZUKU] I came in asking
for some kind of arm brace,
and instead my body
almost got pretzeled.
Now that I think about it,
I could use this suit
as a capture item.
Sir. I was wondering
if you could improve
the cooling devices in my legs.
If that's what you're
in the market for.
Try this baby on!
How--?
It's an electric
booster for radiators
that can coolify anything
that gives off heat!
Sweet baby number 36.
Hatsume, there's nothing
wrong with my boosters.
--And why my arms?
--[HATSUME] Booster. Go.
Hey!
[IZUKU, OCHACO]
Iida!
[TENYA] My Quirk is in
my legs, you madwoman.
[HATSUME] Yeah, I know.
But you don't understand.
Come on, it's so brilliant.
If you're wanting to
cool down your legs,
then why don't you just run
with your arms instead!
[gasps]
[POWER LOADER]
Stop messing around!
[TENYA] What in the world
are you talking about?!
[HATSUME]
Violent!
[ALL MIGHT] You're still
trying to imitate me.
[IZUKU gasps]
Hold on. Maybe...
Sorry, guys.
I'm trying to get her to
look past her own devices.
I'm not sure
that'll ever happen.
Same.
But y'know.
If you all are
aspiring to be heroes,
then you should treasure
your relationship with her.
You'll need her once
you've been made pros.
Look in the corner.
[POWER LOADER]
That pile of junk?
Those are all the support
items Hatsume's made
since starting school here.
She's always inventing,
even when school's
not in session.
I've seen many support
course students in my career,
but I tell you, this girl
is something special.
She made all of this
in such a short time?
That's nuts.
[HATSUME giggles]
[POWER LOADER]
"Common sense is a collection
of prejudices
acquired by age 18."
That's something Einstein said.
That girl is
unafraid of failure.
Constantly thinking of new
ideas and trying them out.
Innovators are people
who don't feel chained down
by existing concepts.
[gasps]
Think for yourself.
You're still trying
to imitate me.
[IZUKU]
Wait!
[GRAN TORINO] But your
admiration for All Might...
[IZUKU]
I think I get it.
It's so simple.
[IZUKU gasps]
[IZUKU]
I understand!
Iida!
Please, there's so much
I want you to teach me!
Uh, wait, what are
you talking about?
You want my help
with your training?
We haven't made any progress
on our costumes yet.
Oh! That's right!
[OCHACO] Whoa! Your face
totally lit up just now!
I was just realizing something.
Oh, I never asked, are you
changing part of your costume?
A little. I don't wanna
feel sick anymore.
[HATSUME]
Oh, you don't say.
In that case, you've
gotta try this out!
[OCHACO] Why do I feel like
it's about to explode?
[HATSUME] Just handle this
baby with care, or...
What is that? Smoke?
[BOTH]
You'll kill us!
[laughs] Work in progress.
[IZUKU] As the days passed,
our training to create
our ultimate moves continued.
[ALL MIGHT] Aizawa.
How are things progressing?
[AIZAWA] You're back again?
We're getting there.
[MINETA] Hey, Midoriya!
Did ya switch your costume up?
Yeah.
I got braces added that reduce
the strain on my arms.
You missed a solid chance
to change your entire design.
It's so boring.
I like it.
Congratulations!
I'm so proud you got into UA!
I don't wanna change the base.
At least not much.
Now. Onto me, Dark Shadow.
[DARK SHADOW]
Right!
[TOKOYAMI] By covering
myself with Dark Shadow.
My strength is enhanced.
I'm better at close combat.
I call it Abyssal Black Body!
[MIDNIGHT]
Is that hard to say?
It's important that
it's easy to call out.
[DARK SHADOW]
Got it!
Some of them have
finally solidified
their fighting styles.
And there are those
already putting together
multiple special moves.
[KATSUKI]
Not from my entire hand.
But a blast from a single,
concentrated point.
AP Shot!
Ha, ha! I did it!
[ALL MIGHT] No surprise that
Young Bakugo is doing well.
As usual.
[AIZAWA]
Uh-huh.
Hey! Watch out!
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
Smash!
All Might's signature moves
usually involve his fists.
Since I inherited
One For All from him,
I tried to do the same thing.
Copying his every technique.
That's where I went wrong.
It's so obvious that
I didn't even realize it!
[IZUKU] If I'm worried about
my arms, then I'll use my legs.
One For All: Full
Cowling. Shoot Style!
You did it, kid.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
Using my legs instead of my arms
is the key to my new
way of fighting.
One For All, Full Cowling:
Shoot Style!
Together with Costume Gamma
that Hatsume made for me,
I'm finally ready for the
Provisional Hero Licensing Exam!
If I can just pass this test,
then I can participate
in hero work,
taking me one step closer to
my dream of becoming a pro.
Next time, "The Test."
Shiketsu High School,
Ketsubutsu Academy;
we've got some fearsome rivals.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!