Boo! I am here.
In a flashy yellow shirt
that matches Young Midoriya's!
Ta-dah!
All Might, this isn't
where I'm supposed to be!
Me and the rest of Class 1-A
are in the middle of our
provisional hero licensing exam!
It's important!
[ALL MIGHT]
I know!
And I can't wait to find
out what happens next.
But, kid...
Just ignore that for now!
Why?
Here's a Q.
Do you know the best
way to save people?
With love!
I don't understand.
You gotta learn to let loose.
You're working hard, but you
should have fun when you can!
So let's go beyond your
existing story arc!
[BOTH]
Plus Ultra!
Hope you enjoy this super
special side episode.
I take a daring new turn in
"Save the World with Love!"
Now, cue those
opening credits! Go!
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
Morning.
Perfect timing.
You're on TV right now.
Some kind of retrospective.
About me?
[TV NARRATOR 58A]
So, just how did All Might,
the Symbol of Peace,
become the number-one
hero in the world?
Let's take a look
back on his time
studying abroad in America.
You're safe because I am here.
[ALL MIGHT]
That takes me back.
[MIDNIGHT]
How many decades?
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
[MIDNIGHT] Real subtle way
of sidestepping the question.
I know that costume.
It's from your Young Age!
Heh. Yep.
Well spotted.
Oh, well, thanks.
I've been a fan of All Might's
since I was just a little kid.
Well, aren't you an inspiration.
No, not at all!
[MIDNIGHT]
Could he look more smug?
[TV NARRATOR 58A]
All Might wasn't acting
alone while abroad. The
sidekick who supported him
was none other than
a young David Shield.
[MIDNIGHT] Wait, does he
mean that David Shield?
[CEMENTOSS] Birds of
a feather, and all that.
It's no surprise such
elites found each other.
[ALL MIGHT] Dave. It's been
far too long, my friend.
[COMPUTER] An email is here!
An email is here!
[AIZAWA] It's about time
to begin the special class.
I have a few notes
about my costume.
Not to worry.
Everything is ready.
[ALL MIGHT]
Let's teach those wannabe pros
a thing or two about hero-ing.
[IZUKU] UA High holds special
classes for those wanting
to train during summer vacation.
Today's the first
one this break,
and we have no idea
what's in store.
We'll be running this
course multiple times
with small groups
from your class.
Today it will be the six of you.
Just so you know,
this will be harder
than a regular class.
Prepare yourselves.
[TSUYU] I wonder what
they'll have us do.
[IZUKU] Is this gonna be one
of those times he threatens
to expel us if we fail?
[AIZAWA] In this master
class, you'll be tasked
with saving innocent bystanders.
And capturing a villain.
Huh?
[BOTH] We're not just studying--
we're playing heroes!
[AIZAWA]
This should be obvious.
But villains commit many
different types of crime.
You six will be
dispatched to a scene
and will need to determine
what happened there.
Whether or not a villain
was actually at fault.
Whether or not you should fight.
We will be judging your ability
to assess the situation
as well as how well
you diffuse it.
Welcome your instructors.
I am here, sneaking in
through the back door!
All Might's teaching us?
ou're looking extra
muscly today! Yowza!
[laughs]
He's not the only one today.
Cementoss, Midnight, and
Present Mic will be assisting.
They'll be acting
as special trainers.
[AIZAWA]
Let's get started.
Head to Ground Beta
and we'll begin.
I see cardboard police cutouts.
This must be where the
crime is taking place.
[AIZAWA]
I'll brief you on the situation.
There's been an attack
in this jewelry store.
The employees and
customers have been
taken hostage and are
barricaded inside.
The number of villains
and bystanders is unknown.
As pro heroes,
you have been asked
by the police to intervene
and resolve this incident
to the best of your abilities.
Excuse me, Mr. Aizawa!
Our teachers--are they
playing the roles
of hostages or villains--
I won't be answering questions.
Verify the situation yourself
and act accordingly.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
[AIZAWA] With that, let the
capture training begin.
[buzzer blares]
[TENYA]
Okay. What's our first move?
That's easy.
First we need to figure
out how many villains
and hostages there are inside.
[KATSUKI]
Uraraka. You go.
Me by myself?
[KATSUKI] If we all run in,
the villains'll notice us.
But you can float up
to the top window
and not get caught.
Yeah. You're right! I'm on it.
Isn't that dangerous?
[TODOROKI] It is. But we
can distract the villains.
[beeping]
[phone ringing]
[ALL MIGHT]
Who is this? The fuzz?
All Might's pretending
to be the criminal.
[TODOROKI]
I'm a pro hero. And you are?
[ALL MIGHT]
Pro shmo. I'm not impressed.
[IZUKU] Tell us how many
villains on your right hand,
and how many hostages
on your left.
Yeah. 'Kay.
[TODOROKI]
Release the innocents,
and we'll consider your demands.
[ALL MIGHT]
I only have one demand.
I want the cops and the heroes
to get the hell out of here.
If you don't leave, I guarantee
I'll slice up these hostages.
[TODOROKI]
Very well.
But first, I need information
on who you've got inside.
Is anyone hurt?
[ALL MIGHT] Someone will
be if you don't stop
taking your sweet time.
Hurry up and get lost, dammit!
[IZUKU]
One villain. Three hostages.
Nice, Urakaka!
Stay there. Wait for us!
[gasps] Quick, hide!
[TSUYU]
Ribbit!
[IZUKU] It's All Mi--
I mean, the bad guy.
[TODOROKI]
He's checking to make sure
that everyone's gone.
[TSUYU] In that case,
we need to stay hidden.
We can't put those
hostages in danger.
How do we help them?
Think there could
be a back way inside?
[AIZAWA] Here's the first
big decision they must make.
Should they contact
the villain again
and attempt to persuade him?
Or...
[KATSUKI yells]
[KATSUKI]
This is stupid.
Kacchan?!
[TENYA]
Bakugo. Calm down!
[TODOROKI] You're planning
to charge straight in?
Obviously.
I'll fire off a
bunch of explosions
and take down that villain.
You guys can save the hostages
or whatever, I don't care.
You're being way
too irresponsible.
What are you talking about?
He's right there in the window.
This is our chance!
Of course. I knew
it'd go like this.
We have to move now, too!
[IZUKU]
Yeah. Let's go!
[AIZAWA]
Unfortunately for you,
this isn't a problem you
can fight your way out of.
[gasps] The villain's
disappeared inside.
[KATSUKI] Damn it, I won't
let you have those hostages!
[TENYA]
Oh, no! Hurry!
Wait. Is that...?
[AIZAWA]
Now you get it.
[AIZAWA] This is the moment when
the special class really begins.
[AIZAWA] Today's training is
not what you expected it to be.
I'm interested to see how you
deal with this development.
[IZUKU]
The villain was... killed?
[chuckles, coughs]
Okay, All Might's still alive.
He's playing. But we're
supposed to think he's dead.
Is it because of Bakugo's blast?
No way--it wasn't
even that strong.
Weren't you watching?
You were supposed
to be our eyes.
Yeah, but, I couldn't
see anything
because of all the smoke.
[growls]
[TODOROKI] The murder weapon
is a knife covered in blood.
[TENYA] The building was
surrounded by police,
so we know no one
went in or out.
That means whoever
killed the villain
must still be inside!
Hold on. Maybe...
But it's too soon
to know that for sure.
We should listen to what
they have to say first.
[TSUYU]
He's right.
We need to know
how events unfolded.
[CEMENTOSS] I'm but a humble
employee of this store.
A villain suddenly appeared
and threatened me.
I handed over the jewels,
and then he tied me up.
[MIDNIGHT] I dropped by to
pick up a few new pieces,
and the villain
was already here.
He caught me while I was
too surprised to resist him.
Yo, yo, my pros. What it do?
I came to find a bomb-ass
piece of frosting
for my hottie GF. Then that
villain laid me out flat.
It was so not dope!
When the villain first arrived,
was this man already
in the store?
Yes, he was browsing.
That beast knocked
him unconscious,
and he was asleep for
quite a long time.
And when you first came
into the shop, ma'am.
Did you see both of these men?
I didn't get a good
look when I walked in.
But when he was tying me up...
...I noticed these
two men had been
in different parts of the store.
[TODOROKI] Hm. So far their
stories all seem to fit.
[IZUKU]
Excuse me.
We need to take a quick look
through your wallets and bags.
See anything of
interest in there?
She's got a bunch of
credit cards and cash.
Present Mic's is the same way.
They both had enough money
on them to buy jewelry.
[OCHACO]
Yeah.
One of you killed
this stupid villain.
Just come out and
tell us, or else.
What's the motive?
What?! The stolen
jewelry, you moron!
Plus, they're just bad guys.
Even if that were the case,
isn't it a little too
reckless to kill the villain
when you're locked in a store?
You'd definitely be a suspect.
Besides, the criminal
dropped the jewelry.
Yet no one took the bag.
If the theft wasn't
the motive, then maybe...
[OCHACO]
Another conflict?
Yeah, if there were
two villains in here,
and during the attack,
they argued about
how to split up the loot,
that could be the motive.
If that's the case,
then the hostages
would have heard
their conversations.
Nah, girl, I didn't
hear anything like that.
Nor did I.
[MIDNIGHT]
Me neither.
Then you think the
villain was working alone?
Yes.
[TENYA] I've inspected
every corner of the store.
There's no back exit,
and all the windows are sealed.
It's impossible that
anyone escaped.
Then, the person at fault
has to be one of these three.
I didn't do it.
I'm innocent!
[PRESENT MIC]
I'm not goin' down for this.
It wasn't me, yo!
[AIZAWA] They haven't been
able to find definitive
evidence of who
the killer is yet.
It's time for their
second big choice.
Wouldn't it be best
to call the police?
The investigators can get
to the bottom of this case.
Perhaps that would be wise, yes.
[OCHACO]
This is so frustrating.
We know the culprit has
to be one of these people!
[KATSUKI]
Simple.
[PRESENT MIC yelps]
We'll just force them
to start talking!
Bakugo!
Be a hero.
If you torture them,
then the police
will arrest you along
with the perpetrator.
I didn't say anything
about torture!
Hey, you damn nerd.
You've got a new idea,
haven't you?
Uh--! Well. Something's
bothering me here.
[TODOROKI]
What is it?
Why did the villain barricade
himself inside the store?
You know?
'Cause, if he wanted to,
he could have just
escaped with the goods earlier.
So then, why did he stay?
[CEMENTOSS]
Timing wise,
the authorities arrived
just as I was putting
the jewelry in a bag for him.
He had no opportunity to flee.
[OCHACO]
Did you call the police?
I never had the chance.
Someone outside the
store must've seen
what was happening.
They're the ones who
called the police.
If that's the case,
then it has to mean...
Midnight, it was you.
[gasps] What? Me?
[IZUKU] You were the
only one who came into
the jewelry store after
the villain was already here.
Don't be hasty, Midoriya.
Don't you make us look
like a buncha idiots.
Why would somebody
who called the police
come inside to face the
villain and allow themselves
to be taken as a hostage?
Hear me out.
I think she's the
reason the villain
barricaded himself
in here to begin with.
[IZUKU] Midnight. You knew
the man on the floor
before this incident,
didn't you?
[IZUKU] And not just
as an acquaintance--
you knew he committed crimes.
You saw him and knew he was
going to rob the jewelry store,
so you called the
police the moment
he went inside so
they would stop him.
And then, before
they could arrive...
[IZUKU]
You decided to go in yourself.
[IZUKU] He must've been
shaken to see you.
But he also understood
your true intentions.
Why you were there.
[IZUKU] Even so, the villain
continued the robbery
and tied you up like the others.
[IZUKU] While he was doing
that, the police arrived,
and he was forced to barricade
himself in the store.
[MIDNIGHT]
No!
Why would I willingly put
myself in danger like that?
Because you wanted him
to change his life.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
Didn't you?
[IZUKU] No matter how any times
you tried to convince him
to step away from
crime, he wouldn't.
So you made sure
that, this time,
he'd be forced to
change his ways.
[gasps] Wait, Deku.
Even if things happened the
way you just said they did...
Why would she kill the villain?
[TODOROKI] All she wanted
to do was get him arrested.
[TENYA]
Yeah, that's right.
She has no motive to kill him.
True. There's no motive.
[IZUKU]
That's why the murderer...
...isn't one of these three.
What are you talking about?
Seriously, Deku, hold on!
Could it have been...
Suicide. Right?
Probably.
Once he figured out what
Midnight's intentions must be,
it's likely he still expected
to escape as planned.
But then we pro heroes
showed up on the scene.
He refused to be taken alive.
[IZUKU]
Not quite.
I think he was worried
about something else.
If he was caught by the police,
his relationship with Midnight
might have been exposed,
putting her in all
sorts of trouble.
If that had happened,
a dark shadow would've fallen
over the rest of her life.
[IZUKU]
That's why this villain
silenced himself
with his own weapon.
[IZUKU] Midnight didn't say
anything because she realized
what he was thinking when
he took his own life,
the sacrifice he was making
so that she could live.
[IZUKU] Out of respect,
she couldn't say anything.
You think Midnight and the
villain were that in love?
[IZUKU]
Mm-hm.
That's so sad.
Midnight was only trying
to help the criminal
because she cared
so much about him.
And the robber was
trying to save Midnight,
because deep in his villainous
heart, he loved her, as well.
They were both just
trying to look out
for each other.
That's ironic, isn't it?
[IZUKU] I believe that
this is the truth behind
the attack in the jewelry store.
[TSUYU sadly]
Ribbit.
[KATSUKI] This was actually
some kinda love story?!
[AIZAWA]
Okay, that's enough.
Ooh! This was so fun!
[OCHACO, IZUKU, TENYA, TSUYU]
What a 180!
Thanks, you three.
You're all done here.
Save your strength
for the next group?
[PRESENT MIC]
What'd you think of my acting?
[CEMENTOSS]
I'd reel it in a bit.
Midoriya.
Sir!
[AIZAWA]
Your deductions were exactly
what we had scripted
for this scenario.
The villain did stab
himself with his own knife.
It was smart work getting
to that conclusion
by asking a logical
series of questions.
Wow! Praise from Mr. Aizawa!
Extremely well done, Midoriya!
[IZUKU chuckles]
[AIZAWA]
But you weren't perfect.
You six overlooked
one major thing.
Therefore, you earned...
...zero points.
[GROUP yelps]
You've gottta be kidding!
[AIZAWA]
Observe.
[OCHACO]
What?
[IZUKU]
The villain's body is gone!
[cackling]
[IZUKU, OCHACO, TENYA]
He's alive!
[ALL MIGHT]
I am fleeing the scene
and running toward freedom!
[ALL MIGHT cackling]
[AIZAWA] You were all
under the assumption
that the villain was a corpse,
so you didn't tie him up.
And that's why you all fail.
[KATSUKI]
Is that even allowed?
Didn't you realize that
All Might gave you a hint
about the truth?
He tried to help you.
When Asui tickled his nose.
Ribbit!
[chuckles]
[AIZAWA]
He reacted, didn't he?
You thought it was a mistake.
But he was alive.
That's it for your special
class. You're dismissed.
Aw, man.
[KATSUKI]
That's a dirty trick!
Uh-- Wait a second. If the
villain is alive, then...
He pretended to kill himself,
but looked for a chance
to escape the whole time!
He didn't stay
there for Midnight!
Midnight misunderstood
and thought he did
everything because
he wanted to protect
her name and honor.
But their love story!
It was...!
...never real.
I hate this test.
And this love stuff!
[OCHACO]
The window!
[STUDENTS scream]
[coughs] Staying in
my muscle form
for so long is excruciating.
[ALL MIGHT] Oh, that's right.
I had an email.
It's from Melissa?
[ALL MIGHT]
"Dear Uncle Might."
[MELISSA]
It's been such a long time!
Melissia Shield here.
I bet you're surprised
to get a message from me.
I'm writing you because I-Expo
will be held on I-Island soon.
Where Papa and I live!
Schools in Japan are on summer
vacation right now, right?
You should come see Papa!
I'll send you a formal
invitation to the Expo later.
A Japanese hero who
fought villains while
studying abroad reunites
with his American friend
after so many years.
[MELISSA giggles] Don't you
think it sounds dramatic?
P.S. This is a surprise.
He'll be so shocked if you
show up out of the blue!
Can you imagine
the look on his face
when he sees you again?
[DAVID]
The Symbol of Peace?
[ALL MIGHT] I wanna see
a society where everyone
can smile without worry.
I will become a
Symbol of Peace--
a beacon of hope in this world.
[ALL MIGHT]
Dave.
I am here!
Waiting to ambush Young Midoriya
on his walk home from UA!
Hi!
Huh? What are you doing here?
[ALL MIGHT coughs]
Young Midoriya.
There's a place called I-island.
You ever hear of it?
Oh, yeah, for sure.
I-island is amazing!
Every company in the
world that's involved
in the hero business
invested money to create
a technological paradise
for the research
and development of Quirks
and support items!
The result was an artificial,
mobile island where
almost 10,000
scientists now live.
It's incredible!
It's security system...
Do you wanna go there with me?
[gasps] Really? You want
us to go together?
I don't mean we'll
just be goofin' off.
Now that you've officially
become my successor,
there are lots of
tricks of the trade
you need to learn about.
You're doing it for me?
Are you sure about this?
Let's go!
Then you'd better
run up to your room
and pack your bags
right away so we can jet.
Can't keep the plane waiting.
We're going now?!
[ALL MIGHT]
Yes! Hurry up! Go!
[IZUKU]
Ah, yeah, yeah, I'm going!
Don't leave without me!
Young Midoriya!
Did you enjoy my star
turn as a criminal?
You almost caught me!
Man, I'm such a sucker
for love stories.
[IZUKU] Well, it wasn't
actually a love story.
But!
More importantly, we're going
to I-Island really
soon, aren't we?
What's it like over
there, All Might?
You'll see! But only
if you watch the movie!
Oh, I get it, nice plug.
People can watch
My Hero Academia: Two Heroes
in theaters soon!
Spoken like a true
hero of marketing!
[laughs]
Next time we'll continue where
the last episode left off!
Can Young Midoriya and the rest
of his intrepid classmates
defeat Gang Orca,
who barged into the middle
of the second round?
Will they be able to get
their provisional hero
licenses or not?
They might fail miserably!
[IZUKU]
Come on, why would you say that?
Anyway.
Thank you so much
for watching the show.
[BOTH]
You are the real heroes!
You ready, kid?
[BOTH]
Let's say it together!
Go Beyond! Plus Ultra!
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
In the final round
of our licensing exam,
a villain has sprung
onto the scene.
Do we fight or run?
We're going to have
to work together
to get out of this situation.
Next time: "What's
the Big Idea?"
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!