[IZUKU]
Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out
some of the world's
greatest heroes.
I'm running toward
my dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[yawns]
[grunts]
We're focusing on our Quirks?
[VLAD]
Class A's already training.
You all need to catch up.
Last semester, Class A
was in the spotlight.
Next semester,
it's Class B's turn.
From now on, you're
shooting for the top.
Don't let me down!
[TETSUTETSU] We're such
disappointing students!
I get you want everyone
to improve our Quirks.
But we have 20 unique
powers in our class.
What kind of training will
help all of us get better?
[KAMAKIRI]
Yeah, can you be more specific?
[VLAD] When your muscle
fibers are overused,
they break and
grow back tougher.
Thicker. Quirks are
the same way.
They improve the harder
you push them.
Stronger after every workout.
In other words, there's
only one thing to do!
You'll have to break yourselves!
[ALL whimper]
[yells]
[PRESENT MIC]
Katsuki Bakugo.
He's plunging his hands
into boiling water to expand
his sweat glands, then
creating chain explosions
to increase the scale
of his bangin' attacks.
Shoto Todoroki.
Alternating between
ice and fire,
he's regulating the
temperature of the water.
His body gets
accustomed to the cold
and he works on
controlling his flames.
Some day he might be able
to use both at once!
[PRESENT MIC]
Hanta Sero.
Having him produce tape
continuously will increase
his capacity and improve
the tape's tensile strength
and shooting speed.
Eijiro Kirishima
and Mashirao Ojiro.
Every time Ojiro hits
Kirishima's Hardened skin
with his Tail, both of their
Quirks are steadily improved.
[whimpering]
[PRESENT MIC]
Denki Kaminari.
By running his currents
through a high-capacity battery,
he's learning to handle
larger amounts of electricity.
[yelling]
[PRESENT MIC] Koji Koda.
In order to increase the reach
of his Anivoice, he's
doing vocal exercises
to help him build up his range.
It's also good for helping
him to become less shy.
[AOYAMA]
Ooh!
[PRESENT MIC]
Yuga Aoyama.
He's building up his body
by blasting Navel Laser.
This increases
the attack's range
and lets him use it
even with tummy issues.
[PRESENT MIC]
Fumikage Tokoyami.
His goal is to keep
control of Dark Shadow
even when it goes wild.
[TOKOYAMI]
Dark Shadow!
[PRESENT MIC]
Ochaco Uraraka.
She's getting her inner ear
canals used to zero gravity
in an effort to reduce nausea.
All while increasing how
much weight she can lift.
[PRESENT MIC]
Tenya Iida.
Hardcore long-distance
running improves
his leg strength and stamina.
Tsuyu Asui.
She's working out all
the muscles in her body
including her tongue.
Rikido Sato.
He's lifting weights, while
at the same, time scarfing down
the sugar that allows him
to power up his sweet Quirk.
Momo Yaoyorozu.
Also stuffing her face,
she hopes to amp up
her creation Quirk and
shorten the amount of time
needed for her to use it.
Kyoka Jiro.
Amplifying the quality
of her audio by honing
her headphone jacks.
Mina Ashido.
By constantly creating acid,
she can increase her
skin's durability.
Minoru Mineta.
Increasing the strength of
his scalp will keep his head
from bleeding even when he
keeps poppin' off balls.
Toru Hagakure and Mezo Shoji.
They're improving their
Quirks by having Shoji
quickly create
multiple Dupli-Arms
and hunt down Hagakure,
who is working on her stealth.
--[MINETA] Ow...
--Oh, man.
This is pretty intense.
Operative types will
be raising your limits,
maxing out your power.
And the rest--you'll mostly
focus on strengthening
body parts related
to your Quirks.
Now normally,
these changes happen
gradually as you grow.
[AIZAWA]
But we don't have time for that.
Your class has a lot
of work to do.
Once we team up with Class A,
there'll be 40 students here.
That's a whole lot of Quirks
for our homeroom teachers
to manage on their own.
Which is why we called them.
[RAGDOLL] That's correct!
Four kittens in one litter!
[MANDALAY]
Your feline fantasies are here.
Say "meow."
[RAGDOLL]
Allow us to lend a helping paw!
We're champions
serving up justice.
With our tails.
Purrfectly cute
and catlike heroes!
[WILD, WILD PUSSYCATS]
We're the Wild, Wild Pussycats!
Full version!
Damn it!
I'm Ragdoll, and my
Quirk is Search.
I can look at up to 100 people
and know everything about them.
Like their location
and weakness.
With my Earthflow,
I can create the ideal training
ground for every student.
And my Quirk is
called Telepath.
I can give advice to
multiple people at once.
[TIGER]
The name's Tiger.
And I'm here to beat
you guys to a pulp.
[RIN]
I have questions about him.
Damn it!
[TIGER] All you kids
with strength Quirks,
time for Tiger's bootcamp.
Class A's already sweating,
so catch up quick!
C'mon, show me what you got.
[IZUKU]
Five percent Detroit Smash!
[grunts]
[TIGER]
If you don't push yourself,
you won't shred
your muscle fibers,
and then you won't get stronger!
[IZUKU]
Right, sir.
I can't hear you!
[IZUKU]
Right, sir!
[KAIBARA]
He's scary.
You wanna be
Plus Ultra, don't you?
Then show me what that means!
[IZUKU]
Yes, sir!
[SHISHIDA] That guy is way
more intense than I expected.
[VLAD]
There's a lot going on at UA,
so it's hard for us
to spare much staff
for the hero course first years.
[AIZAWA] Based on their
experience and range of powers,
these four were the
most logical choice
to help you enhance your Quirks
in such a short amount of time.
[VLAD]
Don't fall behind Class A.
Do me proud!
[CLASS B STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
[panting]
[IZUKU] The Quirk
All Might passed on to me
was more than I deserved.
And then Gran Torino
taught me how to use it
in a way that wouldn't
destroy my body.
[ALL MIGHT] You're overflowing
with energy at the moment.
With training, your body
will hold it better.
[IZUKU] I've come a long way
in such a short time.
It's up to me to move forward
and make this power my own!
--[IZUKU yells]
--That's right!
Tear that weak Quirk apart
and make it stronger!
[IZUKU]
Yes, sir!
[IZUKU panting, grunting]
[PIXIE-BOB]
Now. Remember what I said?
We're not serving
your food anymore!
If you guys wanna eat,
you'll have to make
your own meals!
Starting with curry!
[STUDENTS]
Yes, ma'am.
[RAGDOLL laughs] Oh, man,
do you guys look exhausted.
But that doesn't mean
you can coast by
making sloppy cat food.
Oh! I see.
An important part of
saving someone recovering
from a disaster is providing
for their physical needs
as well as spiritual.
Ah! This is a great opportunity!
Let's make the most
delicious curry
in the world, everyone!
[STUDENTS]
Yeah, okay.
[AIZAWA]
Thank you, Iida.
[ASHIDO]
Hey, Todoroki!
Can we get some fire
over here, too?
Bakugo. Use an
explosion to light that.
This is so beneath me!
[TOKOYAMI]
Too much.
[YAOYOROZU] Rely on others
and you'll never learn
to start a fire yourself.
We should focus on
acquiring new skills.
Ugh.
[TODOROKI]
Here. Let me.
[OCHACO]
Wow! Thank you so much!
[ASHIDO]
Burn, baby, burn!
But not too hot, okay?
[STUDENTS]
We did it!
[KIRISHIMA]
If I got this at a restaurant,
I'd send this crap back.
But after today,
I'll eat every bite.
[SERO]
Don't say that!
Whoa, you're scarfing, Momo!
Yes.
My Quirk transforms lipids
into brand new atoms
to create inorganic materials.
That means, the more I eat,
the more I can make.
Like how poop works.
--Apologize!
--[SERO] Okay, I'm sorry!
[KOTA]
Tch.
[MANDALAY]
Kota. It's time for dinner!
Where are you?
[IZUKU]
Hm.
[stomach growls]
[IZUKU]
I heard that.
You must be hungry.
Here. I brought you some curry.
No way! How'd you
find this place?
[IZUKU] Oh, sorry.
I followed your footsteps.
I thought you might want some
dinner before it gets cold.
Whatever. I'm just fine.
Get lost. I don't wanna
hang out with you.
So forget about
my secret hideout.
This is a secret hideout?
[KOTA]
Hmph. Spending your entire life
trying to improve your
Quirk. It's dumb.
All you want to do is show off.
Get lost!
Hey, about your parents.
I was wondering.
Were they the Water Hose heroes?
With the water Quirks?
Did Mandalay tell you?
No. It's, um...
Well... Sorry!
But...
I heard a little about
what happened to them.
And based on that
information, I figured...
I remember reading about
that horrible incident
a few years ago.
Go away.
Everyone here's so crazy.
Calling people stupid names
like "hero" and "villain,"
and then killing each
other because of it.
Always focusing on their Quirks.
If they hadn't been showing off,
they'd still be here. Idiots.
[IZUKU] It's not just heroes.
Kota hates Quirks.
And this entire
superhuman society.
[KOTA]
We're done here.
Go back to camp
with the other losers.
[IZUKU]
Um. Hey. My, uh, my friend.
This guy I know really well.
He didn't inherit any
abilities from his parents.
[KOTA]
Huh?
It's a hereditary thing.
And these days it's
really uncommon.
He admired heroes so much,
and wanted to be one.
Thing is, you can't
usually become a hero
unless you've got
some kinda Quirk.
But still.
My friend refused to accept
that, and hoped for a miracle.
He tried to use telekinesis.
And to breathe fire.
But it was no good.
There are lots
of different ways
to think about how Quirks work.
So, we might not
be on the same page.
But I think that if you
reject them completely,
it's just going
to make life harder.
In so many ways.
Will you just leave
me alone already?
Go away!
I'm sorry.
I guess I have a habit
of rambling sometimes.
Here, I'll leave the curry.
Shut up. All of you.
Just stop it.
[TOGA grunts]
[TOGA] I do not like this.
It's so not cute!
[MUSTARD] They were engineered
for the black market,
from what I hear.
You should be worried
that they work,
not that they look pretty.
[TOGA] Ugh, I'm just
saying they could be
a little more stylish.
Is that too much to ask?
[MAGNE] Hi, darlings!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Get to work.
[DABI]
That makes seven of us.
[MUSCULAR]
I don't care. Just let me loose.
I'm too pumped up to stand by.
Shut your mouth,
you crazy bastard.
We wait.
We're still expecting
three more people
to join our little party.
The League of Villains
made a mistake
going after them with a bunch
of random thugs at the USJ.
Better to use a small
group of elites.
[DABI]
The first thing we have to do
is take away their
sense of peace
and show them that their
lives rest in our hands.
[KODA screams]
[AIZAWA]
Hey, remedial group. Keep at it.
Yes, sir!
Sorry. But I need
more beauty rest.
[KAMINARI] Who knew
yesterday's extra lessons...
[SERO] ...would go on until
two in the morning...
[SATO]
...and start back up at seven.
[AIZAWA] I told you
it'd be tough. Remember.
You're not just
improving your Quirks.
You're also working to
overcome the many weaknesses
I saw in the finals.
[STUDENTS yelp]
[AIZAWA] Think carefully
about why you're more tired
than the others before
you start whining.
You have much to improve here.
[STUDENTS]
Right. Yes, sir.
[AIZAWA]
Uraraka! Aoyama!
The same goes for you.
Your team didn't fail,
but you were very close.
I'd say you passed the
proverbial finish line
by only a hair.
[OCHACO yelps]
That bad?
Mon dieu .
[AIZAWA]
Don't lose focus.
Each of you can move faster!
And no matter what you're doing,
just remember where
you started from.
Don't forget who
you were before UA.
Always keep in mind
why you're sweating,
and why your limits
keep getting tested.
That's what it means to improve.
[KATSUKI]
Where I started.
[TODOROKI]
Who I am.
[IZUKU]
How I got here.
[IZUKU] Hey, that
reminds me, Mr. Aizawa.
It's already the
third day of camp.
[AIZAWA] Weren't you
listening? Stay focused.
[IZUKU] I was just
wondering if All Might--
I mean, the other teachers
from UA will be joining us.
Like I said before
we came out here.
To keep the camp a secret
from the villains,
hardly anyone knows
where we are.
That's why you get to work out
with us four pussycats!
And think about it.
We believe All Might is one
of the League's targets,
so we can't have him here.
It's for your own safety.
For better or for worse,
that's what he gets for
standing out so much.
Hah.
[IZUKU] Seems like it's mostly
"for worse" these days.
[IZUKU]
So that's it.
All Might won't be
here to help me.
Meow, meow, meow, meow!
More importantly,
tonight's gonna be fun!
We're pitting classes against
each other in a test of courage.
I know you've been
training hard today.
And later, you'll
get to play hard!
How's that for a reward?
[KENDO] It just sounds
like more training.
And training in
the dark, no less.
Revelry in the dark.
[RIN]
How much can we do in one day?
[laughs] 'Least we get to
beat Class A, am I right?
Don't slack now!
Make sure you keep on pushing
yourself as you work!
[STUDENTS]
Yes, ma'am.
Remember... where I came from.
[TIGER]
Hey. You're not Plus Ultra yet.
[IZUKU yelps]
Right!
Whoa, Bakugo,
you're really good
with that knife!
It's weird.
What do you mean "it's weird"?
How can you people be so
damn bad at everything?
[KAMINARI] Look at that.
He's not blowing stuff up.
I'm too tired for this.
[TODOROKI]
Did you need All Might
for a particular reason?
You asked Mr. Aizawa about him.
Yeah. Um. I did.
Because of Kota.
Kota? Who's that?
[IZUKU]
Huh? The boy that's over there.
He's Mandalay's cousin's...
Hold on. Where did he go?
[IZUKU]
Probably to his hideout.
He really doesn't like
being around everyone.
[IZUKU] Anyway, Kota
doesn't like heroes.
Actually, he hates the whole
concept of superhumans,
Quirks and everything.
I tried to talk to him, but I
think I just made things worse.
I was just wondering what
All Might would have done
to help him if he'd been here.
I mean, what would you
say to him, Todoroki?
It depends.
Of course! Sorry I asked!
To have a complete stranger
try to change your
mindset sounds like
a pretty irritating
conversation.
What matters are actions.
You have to show him what
you're trying to prove. Right?
If you're going to
rely on words alone,
then they'd better
be incredibly powerful.
What you say doesn't
matter near as much
as what you actually do.
[ALL MIGHT]
So when I saw this timid,
Quirkless boy try
to save a life,
it inspired me to act, too.
Young man. You, too,
can become a hero.
You're right. I went
about this the wrong way.
How can I, a stranger,
say anything to him?
I don't know what your goal is
when it comes to this child.
But it sounds to me
like you shouldn't be
sticking your nose in
a delicate situation.
You tend to cut to the heart
of people's feelings.
It can be annoying.
[IZUKU]
Right. Sorry about that.
[TENYA] You guys!
Your hands aren't moving!
We'll never make the best
stew if you stop now.
[PIXIE-BOB]
Perfect.
We've filled our bellies
and cleaned the dishes.
It's time for...
A totally awesome
test of courage!
[KIRISHIMA, SERO, KAMINARI]
We're gonna win!
[AIZAWA]
Not so fast.
It pains me to say it,
but the remedial class
will be having lessons
with me tonight instead.
You've gotta be kidding me!
[AIZAWA]
Sorry.
Your training during the
day didn't impress me,
so I'll be using this time, too.
[KAMINARI, SERO]
Oh, give me a break!
[SATO, KIRISHIMA]
I just wanna prove my courage!
Okay. So.
Class B is going to start
out as our "scarers."
When they're in place,
Class A will leave in pairs
every three minutes.
There are tags with
your names on them
at the far end of the route.
Your goal is to collect those.
Revelry in the dark.
[OCHACO]
Why's he keep saying that?
[PIXIE-BOB] Now, those who
are scarers aren't allowed
to make physical contact.
Use your Quirks to
terrify the others.
Got it?
The winners are
the creative students
who make the most people
piss their pants.
Did we need that visual?
I see!
They're encouraging us
stoke our imaginations
as we compete with each other,
all while showing us
more uses for our Quirks
in the process.
As expected of UA!
All right!
Everyone draw to see
who your partner will be.
[IZUKU] Hm? If we're
in teams of two...
Wait.
There are 20 of us,
but five in extra lessons.
[IZUKU] One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight?
Okay let's try this again,
I must be missing something.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight?
[IZUKU yelps]
I'm all alone.
We were randomly assigned.
It's not that nobody
chose you or anything.
Listen up, Tail.
--Trade with me.
--[MINETA] Aoyama.
[MINETA] Please switch me
partners, I should be with her!
Wait, what did you call me?
Revelry in the dark.
[JIRO, HAGAKURE scream]
[PIXIE-BOB]
Next team!
That's you two kittens.
Ribbity and Miss Floater.
[JIRO, HAGAKURE screaming]
[OCHACO]
I'm getting scared, Tsu.
And those screams
aren't helping.
[TSUYU]
That's Kyoka and Toru, I think.
Here, take my hand.
Don't be afraid.
We'll look out for each other.
One step at a time.
[OCHACO]
Mm-hm.
[HONENUKI laughs]
Nice going, Kodai,
you managed to scare
everybody so far,
ya big creeper!
[KENDO] Yeah, you're
the star of the night!
[KODAI]
Huh?
I can't get over how funny
Bakugo and Todoroki were.
[KATSUKI, TODOROKI]
Oh.
I thought they were tough.
[KENDO]
Hey. Smell that?
I think there's
something burning nearby.
[HONENUKI]
Huh? Now that you mention it,
it's kinda smoky out here.
Maybe Bakugo and Todoroki
got so scared, they fire--
Honenuki?
[gasps]
[KENDO]
Yui! Don't breathe in!
This smoke. It's poisonous!
[PIXIE-BOB] What's this
foul smell in the air?
[IZUKU]
You see that?
[MANDALAY]
Black smoke.
[TENYA]
Has something been set ablaze?
[OJIRO]
Maybe a fire on the mountain?
[DABI]
Now, it begins.
[PIXIE-BOB]
Hey, what's happening?
[MANDALAY]
Pixie-Bob!
[DABI]
Take them down.
Those who believe they
deserve the title "hero."
[TOGA cackles]
[DABI]
We, the Vanguard Action Squad
of the League of Villains, will
tear them off their pedestals.
[MAGNE] First, let's get
rid of these feral cats.
[MINETA]
What? No way!
I thought they made sure
no one could find us.
So why the heck
are there villains
attacking this place?
Pixie-Bob!
This is bad.
[gasps] Where's Kota?
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
The League of Villains
suddenly attack
during our test of courage,
and not even Kota can escape
their evil clutches.
To make matters worse,
I'm the only one
who knows where he is.
That means it's up
to me to save him.
But I have to hurry!
I need to remember
why I want to be a hero
if I'm going to succeed,
and how far I've come
since I first met All Might.
Next time: "My Hero."
With One For All at full power,
hopefully, I can protect
Kota from harm!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!