[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward my
dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[IZUKU] The provisional
licensing exam is upon us
and my classmates and I
are doing all we can
to make it through
the first round.
[AIZAWA]
If you can pass this test
and get your
provisional licenses,
then you novice eggs
will hatch into chicks.
You'll be semi-pros.
I expect your best.
[IZUKU] This first test
is a free for all.
Each of us has put three
targets on our bodies.
They can go anywhere,
as long as they're visible.
We've also each been
given six special balls
that can trigger the spots.
If all three of your targets
get hit, you're done.
And only the first 100
people to get at least
two people out pass and
move on to the next round.
[MS JOKE] If you like
your class this year,
then you should have warned
your students about all this.
We've seen it time and
time again in this exam.
UA is immediately crushed.
[IZUKU]
One for All. Full Cowling.
Shoot style!
[TOKOYAMI]
Dark shadow!
[AIZAWA]
So you think we'll be taken out?
I don't really see a reason
why I should've warned them.
I doubt anything would've
changed if I had.
They're still going to have
to overcome this either way.
Real heroes could turn
this situation around.
Besides, if they become pros,
they'll face villains
who already know their Quirks.
Perhaps at UA, we look
a little further ahead
than other schools.
[MS JOKE]
Hey, Eraser.
I'm guessing a lot
of our kids will think
it's important to finish fast.
Like the first ones to pass
will be ranked as the top.
So they'll want to
attack. Immediately.
Yes. But teamwork is the key.
The wise ones will cooperate
and gather information together.
But if they're seduced
by the urge to win
and rush to get points, they'll
end up exposing themselves.
And then it's all over.
None of our attacks are landing.
I guess we shouldn't
be surprised
UA won't go down
without a fight.
[MAKABE]
Maybe not. But we have a plan.
[PRESENT MIC]
Ketsubutsu Academy.
Second year. Shikkui Makabe!
His Quirk: Stiffening!
He can make whatever he touches
with his hands super hard!
But this Quirk doesn't
work on living things!
All done.
I'll take it from here.
Just try not to be
jealous when I end up
finishing ahead of
the rest of our class.
But I'm sure you won't
mind since I'll be
reducing enemy numbers
with this elegant attack.
Target. Lock-On.
[TOTEKI] Boomerang.
Crescent Moon Trajectory.
My aim is always true.
And since these projectiles are
coming at them from underground,
no one will have time to dodge.
[PRESENT MIC]
Ketsubutsu Academy.
Second year. Itejiro Toteki!
His Quirk: Boomerang!
He can throw objects
at any trajectory
with stupidly precise aim.
Even underground!
Where are they gonna pop out?
Get back, I'll handle this.
[JIRO] Sound Amplification.
Amplifier Jack!
Heartbeat Distortion!
[gasps]
She's breaking the ground apart.
It won't help.
[MINETA]
They're coming straight for me!
[ASHIDO]
Maximum strength and viscosity!
Protect this perv, Acid Veil!
Wow, thanks! That's
such a great move!
It's my defensive special
that creates a melty wall.
So, they've been working on
ultimate moves already.
Yes, of course they have.
Black Abyss!
Cooler name. And easier to say.
[TOKOYAMI] Now, Dark Shadow.
Piercing Twilight Claws.
[NAKAGAME]
No, no, no, no!
Whew. That was close.
[PRESENT MIC]
Ketsubutsu Academy.
Second year. Tatami Nakagame!
Her Quirk: Telescopic.
She can pull her body
into itself like a turtle.
It's actually pretty creepy
when you see it in action.
Interesting.
This isn't the Class A
from the Sports Festival.
It's obvious their training
is making them better fighters.
[MERA]
Mm. Looks like all the students
are still in a stalemate.
Not a single one's passed yet.
Oh. And don't worry, students,
I'll keep you updated
with an announcement
every time a few students
move on to the next round.
[IZUKU]
What's our strategy?
Everyone will be focused on
protecting their targets,
their weak points.
It's going to be
basically impossible
to hit them by chance.
We'll have to aim well and
break through their defenses,
even if we don't
know their powers.
[MAKABE]
Maybe not. But we have a plan.
[IZUKU] Everyone's
holding back right now.
Watching for their
opponents' blind spots
and how they use their Quirks.
But, at any moment,
the real fight will begin.
All right!
"At UA, you look further
ahead than other schools."
That's a pretty condescending
thing to say, Eraser.
Do you have any idea
how many kids in this world
want to be heroes?
Strength of will is far
more important than going
to a famous school
or having renown.
When you think you're the stars
and look down on others,
you reveal your weaknesses.
That's how you fail.
Outta the way.
Their defenses are
too strong right now.
I'll fix that.
[gasps]
Maximum force!
[SHINDO]
Tremoring Earth!
[IZUKU yelps]
[TENYA]
Not good. Everybody run!
What the heck is this?
[MINETA]
His power is insane!
Deku!
We've got Ultimate Moves, too.
You didn't think you were
the only ones, did ya?
[PRESENT MIC]
Ketsubutsu Academy.
Second year. Yo Shindo!
His Quirk: Vibrate!
He can make anything
he touches shake.
However, the aftershocks
affect his body,
temporarily making
him immobile.
Tremors. An Earthquake?
No. Probably someone's Quirk.
[EXAMINEE 54AA]
Who has that kinda power?
And which school are they from?
Don't lose focus.
There are enemies everywhere.
[yawns] Come on.
There should be at least one
or two who've passed by now.
Stop biding your time
and get this over with.
[gasps] This breeze...?
Hey! No fair!
[EXAMINEE 54B] Why're just
the balls getting sucked up?
I believe it's very important
for heroes to have passion.
And all of you are
fighting with it.
Thank you!
That's one of my favorite
things on Earth to see.
[EXAMINEE 54C]
It's one guy from Shiketsu High?
[EXAMINEE 54D] What'd he say?
It's hard to hear.
[EXAMINEE 54E]
Wait, what's he gonna do now
that he's got our balls?
Please let me join your fight
and show my own passion.
I'm so looking forward to it!
[EXAMINEES screaming]
Huh?
It's about time somebody
perked up and passed.
[yells]
[MERA] What?! There were
120 people taken down?
A single person managed to
do that in just one attack?
[sighs]
That's the stuff. I won!
[MERA] That actually surprised
me so much that I'm awake!
I assume we'll see a lot of
people passing from now on.
Everyone, let's get this out of
the way so I can take a break.
Good? Good.
[IZUKU]
What a Quirk.
Although it seems like it would
be hard to use in a city.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
Oh, no. We've been split up.
Is this what Ketsubutsu was
planning the entire time?
I've gotta find everyone,
or at least somebody soon!
If I'm alone, I'm done for.
The other schools have
had so much more time
to work together and learn
to make decisions in battle.
We're behind by a whole
year's worth of training,
even with everything
we experienced.
[AIZAWA]
Inasa Yoarashi.
He's the same year
as you all and received
the top scores for
students admitted
through recommendations.
But for some unknown reason,
he turned down his acceptance
to UA and went to Shiketsu.
[IZUKU] If he had the top score
for those with recommendations,
then he must be even
better than Todoroki!
Today, I'm gonna do my
best to learn from you.
I really hope you don't mind.
Maximum force!
[SHINDO]
Tremoring Earth!
[IZUKU]
These are strong students
from all over the country.
I don't know why,
but I'm actually getting
pretty excited about this.
[IZUKU] What? This girl
came outta nowhere!
[CAMIE]
Tag, you're it.
Not smart. Staring
off into space.
But... What's really weird
is that you're in trouble
and still smiling.
[IZUKU] I've seen her.
She's from Shiketsu High School.
[laughs] You couldn't be cooler.
[OCHACO]
Wow, that was super intense.
Someone could have even
died in that attack.
If I call out to the others,
I'll just become a target
for the rest of the schools.
My classmates shouldn't
be too far away, though.
I need to find them.
Otherwise, I'll have
to fight by myself.
In moments like this, you
have to be calm and careful.
It's time for Sneak Uravity.
[CAMIE] In fights where
a lot of one-on-one combat
is expected, most people
tend to go after
opponents they've already
got a lot of intel on,
since it's safest.
That's why I tracked you down,
because there's the good
possibility that UA's students
will be ganged up on.
See, I didn't wanna miss
the chance to interact
with such a prestigious school,
and I've taken quite
an interest in you.
Huh. You sure like to talk.
[IZUKU]
Ketsubutsu Academy will show up
to fight any second now.
This is no time for
a leisurely chat.
But I'm sure she
understands that.
Does she have teammates
coming to help her?
Or is she just
that overconfident?
[IZUKU]
Doesn't matter.
I've gotta make sure
I don't get taken out.
[gasps]
[IZUKU] Where'd she go?
She couldn't have--
All I have to do is
tap you with a ball
and that makes two.
[IZUKU]
No way. Gotta counterattack!
Or not. She's gone.
Oh. You think my Quirk
lets me disappear?
No--!
[CAMIE] That's not it.
I was just hiding.
It wasn't your power at work?
Nope. That's just a technique.
I make my opponent's
eyes and ears blind
and deaf to my presence.
To do that,
I hold my breath, clear
my mind, and disappear.
It's simple.
The hardest part is not
thinking, to be honest.
[IZUKU]
Wait.
You learned a technique that
impressive at Shiketsu?
[CAMIE] The trick is to
not view your training
as some kind of chore.
[CAMIE chuckles] I'm glad we're
learning about each other.
Now, my question.
Why exactly do you
wanna become a hero?
For honor? Pride?
Or is it someone else's sake?
I wanna know your deepest
desires, and what scares you.
[TOTEKI] Man. Shiketsu's trying
to take him down, too?
Not good.
[IZUKU]
I'm trapped.
I couldn't find anyone,
and now I'm the target.
The worst-case-scenario
I thought of earlier
is now a reality!
This is it. Here they come.
Dodge!
[IZUKU]
Dodge! Dodge!
Just keep avoiding them!
[OCHACO]
Are you okay?
[gasps] Uraraka!
Over here. Hurry!
[IZUKU]
What? Does she have a plan?
[SHIKETSU BOY 54B]
Don't let them escape!
Hey, watch where
you're shooting.
[SHIKETSU BOY 54B]
I'll take her down fast.
[SHIKETSU BOY 54C]
No, wait!
[IZUKU] Back then, I chose
to fight and save someone,
which destroyed my arms.
If I could've used them,
then I might have been
able to save Kacchan.
And if Kacchan was never taken,
then All Might would
never have had to fight
against All For One
at the warehouse.
If I had only been faster...
I should have been able to get
Kota to Mr. Aizawa sooner.
And then I could have gone
after the villains myself.
[IZUKU] That's why I have
to train my legs now.
So that I never fail to
save anyone ever again.
An opening!
[IZUKU] Because to help others,
you have to be able
to take care of yourself.
[SHIKETSU BOY 54C]
Dammit! The whole mountain's
coming down!
[SHIKETSU STUDENTS scream]
[ALL MIGHT]
I dunno. Based on that kick,
I'd say you're further
along than you think.
So, you should be
ready for this test.
[IZUKU]
It's just like All Might said!
Until my body is able
to catch up to my Quirk,
I won't use One For All
at 100 percent.
Instead, I'll work on my legs.
Thankfully, these new iron soles
create a powerful impact.
And the toes spring back, so
it's basically two hits in one.
This support item compensates
for my lack of power.
[IZUKU] I'll make myself
stronger. I'll keep fighting!
And become the ideal
hero I want to be.
[yawns] Well, we've finally
had a 30th person pass.
Still a pretty long
way to go, though.
Can't you kids speed
this along? For me?
[SHIKETSU BOY 54A] Where'd
those UA brats run off to?
[SHIKETSU BOY 54B]
Are they gone? Or just hiding.
[SHIKETSU BOY 54C]
They gotta be close.
Anyway, this isn't working.
There must be a better
way to tag them.
[IZUKU]
Anyone chasing us?
No. Maybe they gave up.
Thanks, sorry.
I really messed up
back there, huh?
[IZUKU]
No. That's not true.
You were outnumbered.
[IZUKU] Let me guess.
You're someone from Shiketsu?
I'm what?
[IZUKU] Uraraka has been
working on her Quirk.
Training hard.
She can even ignore its
side effects for a short
period of time and use it
to make herself float
without getting sick.
But you. You haven't
tried to use it at all,
even though you were in danger.
And even more suspicious.
You exposed yourself to
the enemy without a plan.
That's not like the Uraraka
I know. So who are you?
[OCHACO chuckles]
If you saved me even though
you knew I was a fake...
...does that mean you were
trying to use me somehow?
[gasps] No. I didn't have time
to think that far ahead.
I'd do it again, though.
In a heartbeat.
Because if you're not Uraraka,
you couldn't have
floated away back there.
Falling from that height,
you definitely would've
injured yourself.
Oh? I see now.
So you're just that
good of a guy, huh?
Please, tell me more
about yourself. Everything.
[IZUKU] Can't we talk
about this after the exam?
[CAMIE] Does that mean
you'll save anybody?
Is there no boundary?
Where do you draw the line?
[IZUKU] Holy whoa, what
happened to your clothes?
You're basically naked!
I'll get dressed when
my mission's complete.
[IZUKU]
She scratched me?
What's the matter
with this girl?
[CAMIE]
What?
[IZUKU]
Tape?
[SERO] Midoriya! What's this
enviable situation you're in?
[IZUKU]
Sero!
Uraraka!
Release!
[OCHACO]
Those reflexes!
And here things were
just getting good.
Too bad.
I really, really ...
wanted to talk to you some more.
But not with so many people
around. What a bummer.
Ochaco Uraraka.
He really trusts you
a lot, you know.
Huh?
[SERO]
Come back, naked girl!
Don't follow her!
[SERO]
Aw, man, why not?
[IZUKU]
It might've just been her Quirk,
but it looked like
she wasn't wearing
her clothes or her targets.
There's still a chance
she might come after us.
But think about it, we
don't have much time left,
and it would be hard
to get a point off of her.
Also... You two are
actually you, right?
Huh?
[SERO]
What are you talkin' about?
Well, earlier, that girl
transformed into
Uraraka's clone.
[BOTH yelp]
[SERO] Was she naked
then, too, Midoriya?
That's what you're
concerned about?
Of course not,
she had a costume on!
[SERO]
So that hottie's Quirk
is to transform into
other people. Weird.
[IZUKU]
I think so.
[SERO] We can't underestimate
how much those other schools
have learned about us.
They even know you and Uraraka
are really good friends.
[IZUKU] Probably because
we were on the same
cavalry battle team
at the sports festival.
[OCHACO]
Yeah, that must be why.
Anyway. How'd you guys find me?
It was perfect timing.
[SERO] I just saw a fight
and rushed over to help.
We ran into each other
along the way.
[OCHACO]
I'm glad we got to help.
Yeah, me, too.
So we're a trio
for now. What next?
[SERO] I wish we could meet up
with the rest of our class.
We're way safer in numbers.
That's true.
But 30 people have already
passed this the test so far.
We have to hurry.
If we're gonna pass,
we've gotta earn some points.
[TODOROKI] The other schools
are sticking together,
moving around in groups
of ten or more.
I could attack one of them,
but there could be
people with Quirks
I'm weak against.
Ideally, the various teams
would fight each other,
bringing the numbers
of each group down
to something more manageable
for me to pick off.
[MERA]
Let's see, where are we at now?
Things've been moving
a lot more quickly.
Looks like 52--make
that 53 have passed.
And, looking on the
other side of things.
It seems 230 examinees
have failed.
Less than half
the spots are open.
Now's the time to move.
Don't dally, kids.
[TODOROKI] I don't have the
luxury of waiting around.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
That was pretty good!
Just what I'd expect
from the runner up
of the UA Sports Festival.
The name's Todoroki, right?
I can't believe you're out here
wandering around
all by yourself.
You must be really confident.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54B]
But even if he is from UA High,
acting alone is just
asking for trouble.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54AA]
A ten-on-one fight.
He doesn't stand a chance.
This is great.
Now I don't have
to find opponents.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A chuckles]
Aren't you cool.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54B gasps]
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54C]
Damn it! I can't move.
You're surprised?
I thought you said you
watched the sports festival.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
Don't be cocky, we're prepared!
[TODOROKI] Looks like a Quirk
that makes things bigger.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A] That's
not all I brought with me!
[TODOROKI]
Should I use a big attack?
No, not yet. I'll wait
to see if there are more.
[TODOROKI]
Even if I couldn't melt it,
I should have at
least made a mark!
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
Your fire won't work
against any of my tools.
Tungsten has a
super-high melting point!
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A] I'm afraid
I told you so, Todoroki.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
Even if you're a top UA student,
if you think can pass
this exam alone...
Well, then,
your pride will
be your downfall.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
The exam continues,
and me and my classmates
aren't doing so well.
Todoroki's targeted
by Seijin High School.
And even Yaoyorozu's in a bind.
Next time: "Class 1-A."
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!