[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward my
dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[IZUKU]
All Might told me there'd always
be people beyond our reach.
That we can't protect
even though we want to.
Which is why we have to save
the people we can reach.
I was so close to
being able to save him.
I needed to save him. Had to.
That's the entire reason
I have my Quirk.
My body wouldn't move.
I couldn't save someone
who was right in front of me.
And since I failed, he's gone.
All right, then
let's go get him.
We have to leave this
to the professionals!
It's not the right time for
us to get involved. Idiots.
Maybe, but all I know
is that at camp,
I couldn't do anything.
I heard my friend was targeted,
and I just stood by. Helpless.
So if I stand by
and do nothing now,
how am I supposed to call
myself a hero or a man?
C'mon. He's still
within your reach!
We can save Bakugo!
[ASHIDO]
So, let me get this straight.
You're going to get Momo
to make you another receiver,
track a bad guy, and then
try to save Bakugo
all by yourselves?
Yeah.
The villains who
attacked the camp
planned to kill some of us.
But they took Bakugo alive.
What we don't know
is how long they'll
let him live.
That's why we're
going after him.
[inahles] Have the two
of you lost your minds?
[SHOJI]
Hey. Calm down.
I get how frustrated
Kirishima is.
And how Todoroki feels since
he couldn't grab Bakugo.
I'm upset, too.
But...
We can't let our emotions
get the best of us.
Right?
[AOYAMA] Um. We should just
leave this to All Might.
Mr. Aizawa only gave
us permission to fight
and use Quirks at
the training camp.
Aoyama is correct.
Though, I'm part of
the reason we failed.
So, I can't talk.
You guys!
[TSUYU]
Listen.
We're all shocked that
Bakugo was taken from us.
But we have to be rational.
It doesn't matter how
noble your intentions.
If you go out there trying
to find the bad guys,
knowing you're
breaking the rules,
then you're acting like
villains, not heroes.
[knocking]
[AOYAMA gasps]
Sorry for interrupting you guys.
But I need a moment
alone with Midoriya.
Sure. Let's bolt.
I wanna see how Jiro
and Hagakure are doin'.
Good idea.
Yeah, okay. Feel better, Deku.
Thank you for visiting me.
[KIRISHIMA] We talked
to Yaoyorozu yesterday.
If we're doing this,
it's tonight.
Look, I know you've got
some pretty hardcore injuries.
So, I don't know if you can go.
But I wanted to invite you,
since you probably
feel the worst.
[KIRISHIMA] We'll meet in front
of the hospital after dark.
[DOCTOR 46A]
Recovery Girl performed some
pretty strong healing
on your arms
while you were unconscious,
so you should be able
to move them around fairly well.
But they were
seriously messed up.
You've done absurd
damage to your body
in the last few months.
And, frankly, this is a whole
new league of trauma.
[IZUKU] You mean... I was
hurt a lot worse this time?
I took a close look
at your charts.
Your past injuries were bad.
Splintered bones and ripped
muscles that were painful, sure,
but could eventually
be repaired.
This time, the damage
was devastating.
Usually, a person's body
has limiters that keep it
from using more than
80 percent of its power
at any given point.
But in a crisis situation,
it's possible for those
limiters to fall away,
allowing someone
to use 100 percent.
We call it
"hysterical strength."
The reason we
have those limiters
in the first place
is because our bodies
can't handle that
type of strain.
You had this
"hysterical strength."
And because of that,
your power ended up overcharged
for an extended period.
It's bad for your bones and
muscles to get battered,
of course, but it's worse
for your ligaments.
Ligaments protect the joints,
and yours have
seriously degraded.
In other words, if you
sustain this type of injury,
even just two or
three more times,
I don't think you're
going to be able
to move your arms anymore.
For now, focus
on rehabilitation.
Use them a lot,
even if it hurts,
and we'll leave the rest to UA.
I'll discharge you today,
so you can go home
and take it easy.
Take this seriously.
Right. Thanks for
your help, Doctor.
I'm sorry for any
trouble I caused.
Recovery Girl is
fed up with you.
But, hey. I get the
impression that's nothin' new.
Also, don't forget
you did save someone.
Healing begins in the mind.
Try not to worry. Stay positive.
[KOTA]
"Dear Mr. Midoriya,
I'm sorry I punched
you in the balls.
Thank you for saving me,
even though you'd just met me.
Please get better soon so I can
thank you in person, okay?
Kota."
[IZUKU]
Kota.
[phone rings]
[IZUKU]
Hi, Mom.
Yeah, I was discharged,
but there's something
I have to do, so I won't
be home until tomorrow or so.
Yeah.
I can move now, at least.
My body feels kind of
run down and sluggish, though,
even with all the healing
they performed on me.
I heard it's because
UA wants a close eye
on the students. Well, that,
and they want to keep the
media out as long as they can.
[IZUKU'S MOM]
Izuku.
Do you really have
to go back to UA?
[WOMAN 46A] There's a call
for you, Endeavor, sir.
[ENDEAVOR]
Who is it?
[WOMAN 46A] A Mr. Tsukauchi
from the police department.
I'm listening.
[TSUKAUCHI] We would like to
request your assistance, sir.
[BEST JEANIST] I've received
an emergency summons,
and must leave this
place in your hands.
Be strong as heavyweight
denim without me,
smart as tailor-made suits.
Keep the fabric of society safe.
[SIDEKICKS]
You got it, Best Jeanist!
[YAOYOROZU] You want me
to make a new receiver?
[KIRISHIMA]
Yes. Please!
[TODOROKI] You must know
what we're planning.
I do. Let me think about it.
[KIRISHIMA]
I wonder what Yaoyorozu decided.
[TODOROKI] No matter how much
we wanna go after him,
It's her choice.
She's here!
[BOTH gasp]
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya.
So, how 'bout it? You decide?
I think that--
Hold on!
[GROUP gasps]
[KIRISHIMA]
Iida...
Why are you here?
[TENYA] You. Why did it have
to be you two of all people?
The ones who stopped me
when I acted recklessly.
Who received amnesty
with me after Hosu.
Why are you trying
to make the same
stupid mistakes I made?
Didn't you learn?
What are you talking about?
[TENYA]
We are still just students.
And UA's in a bad
position as it is.
Anything we do will
reflect on our school!
Don't you get that?
Iida. We have to.
I know you don't like us
breaking rules, but--
[TENYA] I'm frustrated, too!
And concerned. Obviously!
I'm the class rep, dammit.
I'm worried about all my
classmates. Not just Bakugo.
When I saw your injuries,
all I could think of
was my brother in the hospital.
What if your bodies
end up irreparable,
just like his, because
I didn't step in.
Have you not stopped
to think about
where I'm coming from?
[TENYA] Or are you saying
that you don't care how I feel?
Of course I do.
[TODOROKI]
Iida.
You've got it wrong.
We don't expect to face
them head-on and win.
We'll get him back
without fighting.
Yeah, we'll be stealthy.
I'm talkin' covert ops here.
We can rescue him without
breaking the rules.
[YAOYOROZU] I trust in
Todoroki's judgment, but...
Still. Things could
always go wrong.
So I'll join you as backup.
I'll stand behind my classmates.
You can't be serious!
You're the best.
[IZUKU]
I know I'm hurt.
But if I can still move at all,
then I can't just sit still.
I have to reach out
and do something.
'Cause all I can think
about is saving him.
[ALL MIGHT] There are
stories about every hero.
How they became great.
Most have one thing in common.
Their bodies moved before
they had a chance to think.
Almost on their own.
We'll never agree.
So I'm going to come with you.
[GROUP gasps]
[IZUKU]
After the USJ and Hosu attacks,
we thought we'd seen true evil.
That the worst was over.
We've gathered some of our
finest heroes here today.
Now. Let's talk strategy.
[SHIGARAKI] I'll ask you one
more time, Katsuki Bakugo.
Aspiring hero. Will you join
the League of Villains?
Go throw yourself into traffic.
[IZUKU] But something far
worse was about to begin.
[TENYA]
Midoriya.
I shouldn't have
hit you back there.
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
I have some concerns, Iida.
What exactly is
your justification
for changing your mind
and joining us?
Hey, it's fine, you don't
need to apologize.
[TENYA]
To be clear,
I'm coming because I don't
condone your behavior.
It's a simple as that.
If there's even a hint
that physical combat
might break out, I'll make
you retreat immediately.
So in other words...
I'm your watchman!
Exactly what we needed.
The same goes for me.
Rescuing Bakugo is a
job for the pros.
Objectively speaking,
there's no reason for
any of us to go after him.
However,
I understand how each of you
feels, so I'm compromising.
Don't forget that.
Right.
Understood.
[YAOYOROZU]
A rescue without us fighting...
It's not plausible.
The others are so
driven by frustration
that they're blinded. But...
Once they see the situation
first-hand and realize
how difficult it will be,
they should understand
their plan is
completely unrealistic.
[YAOYOROZU] The coordinates
indicate Camino Ward,
Yokohama City in
Kanagawa Prefecture.
Our travel time will be about
two hours from here.
We should arrive around
ten o'clock tonight.
So, um.
Did you tell the rest
of the class about this?
Do they know what
we're doing tonight?
[TODOROKI]
Yes.
And they tried their best
to talk us out of it.
Yeah, even Uraraka
ganged up on us
and tried to get us
to change our minds.
I just don't know, you guys.
Think about what
Bakugo would want.
We'd just make everything
worse I'm afraid.
[KIRISHIMA]
Anyway...
[IZUKU]
Kacchan!
[KATSUKI]
Stay back, Deku!
Just to make sure.
You know we're going
against everyone's wishes,
and being completely
selfish by doing this.
We can call this off
if we want to.
Does it look like
I wanna turn back?
Bakugo wouldn't
think twice about
going after the villains
if he were here.
What about you, Midoriya?
He's my friend.
[ALL MIGHT] Meddling where you
don't technically have to
is the essence of being a hero.
[IZUKU] Mom. All Might
gave me everything.
He trusted that I'd make
the most of his Quirk.
I refuse to turn back.
I see. All right, then.
[IZUKU]
So this is Camino Ward.
[TODOROKI]
It's so crowded.
[KIRISHIMA] Those Villains are
hiding somewhere in this city.
Just tell me where to go!
Wait a second!
From now on,
we going to need to be
extremely careful.
These criminals already know
what we look like, remember?
We have to consider that
we could be attacked
at any moment.
Yeah, you're right!
Stealth mode.
You're standing out
even more, Midoriya.
We won't be able to
scout effectively
if we're recognizable.
'Kay, so what should we do?
I have an idea.
Though it is a bit old school.
Yo, fool. What chu lookin' at?
This is me, incognito.
Now we'll blend in perfectly.
I feel so ridiculous.
I dunno, I kinda dig it.
Watch it, you punks. Get lost.
That's all wrong--
you gotta stick
your chin out more.
You talkin' ta me?
[KIRISHIMA]
That's it!
We're just a few scoundrels
cruising for hot girls.
[KIRISHIMA]
Close enough!
Great disguises.
We'd stand out in this
district dressed like kids.
Yaoyorozu?
Couldn't you have used your
Quirk for this to save money?
Well, technically, but
that's against the rules.
If I started making everything,
think of the impact
on the economy.
We must ensure the
flow of commerce!
That's right! It's our
civic duty. As citizens!
[TODOROKI]
Sure.
[KIRISHIMA] So the rich girl
just wants to go shopping, huh?
Everyone. Our
destination is this way.
[MAN 46A]
Whoa, it's UA High!
Huh?!
[IZUKU gasps]
[NEWSCASTER 46A]
Let's return to a short clip
from the UA High School
press conference
that just wrapped up.
Mr. Aizawa.
And Vlad King and the principal!
We are here to apologize.
A recent incident allowed harm
to come to 27 first year heroes.
And we staff were ill prepared.
We take responsibility
for any trauma caused
by our negligence.
It's our duty to train heroes,
but also to protect
heroes in training.
This is crazy.
He hates being on TV.
[REPORTER 46A]
I'll take the first question.
Since the beginning of the year,
UA students have had four
encounters with villains.
This time, there were students
who were gravely injured.
How did you explain this
to their families?
And what are some of the
specific steps you're taking
to ensure their safety
in the future?
[IZUKU] The media should know
what UA's basic position is
since they didn't cancel
the sports festival.
They just want him to look bad.
They're treating
them like... villains.
[NEZU] We will increase patrols
around the school grounds,
and review security measures
within the school.
The safety of UA's students
is our main priority,
make no mistake about it.
Ugh. What are these
dudes thinkin'?
They're gonna get
those kids killed.
[MAN IN CROWD 46C]
They should be ashamed.
[MAN IN CROWD 46D] Increased
patrols? Gimme a break.
[MAN IN CROWD 46E]
What about the rest of us?
[IZUKU]
The mood was changing.
You could feel it in the air.
People were turning
against heroes.
And if we didn't do something,
it was just going to get worse.
[SHIGARAKI]
Isn't that strange?
The heroes are
becoming the bad guys.
Seems like they're not dealing
with this very well at all.
So much criticism.
But everyone makes
a mistake or two, right?
It's not like they're
supposed to be perfect.
Modern-day heroes
sure have it rough.
Don't you think, Bakugo?
[SPINNER] Once a hero receives
payment to protect people,
they aren't a real hero anymore.
That's what Stain's
actions taught us.
[SHIGARAKI] A hero in this
current system only cares
about money and glory.
And since society buys in
to those idiotic rules,
anyone deemed a loser
is shoved aside.
So, we want to
pose some questions.
What is a hero? What is justice?
Is this society truly fair?
Soon, everyone will be asking.
That's when we'll
know we've won.
And you like winning. Don't you?
[growls]
[SHIGARAKI]
Dabi. Let him go.
[DABI]
You know he'll just fight.
[SHIGARAKI]
It's fine.
We're recruiting him, so we
should treat him as an equal.
Besides, he's smart
enough to know
he can't take us all, right?
After all, UA students
are so clever.
Hey, Twice. You do it.
[TWICE]
Sure thing! No way.
Do it.
[TWICE]
Oh, man.
[MR. COMPRESS] I do apologize
for such forceful methods.
But please understand that
we aren't some kind of
unruly mob committing crimes
without a third act in mind.
We didn't kidnap
you by accident.
[SHIGARAKI] Even though our
backgrounds are different,
everyone here has suffered.
Because of people. Rules.
And heroes who try
to hold us back.
I'm sure you're the same.
[TWICE grunts]
[yells]
[TWICE]
Shigaraki!
[KATSUKI] I'm done listening
to your endless talking.
Can you not get to the point,
or do you just like
your own voice?
Basically, what you're saying
is you wanna cause some trouble
and you want me to join you.
Well, screw you.
[KATSUKI]
Did you see what he just did?
Man, it doesn't get any
cooler than All Might!
That's why he's the greatest.
No matter how much
trouble he's in,
he's always the winner.
[KATSUKI] I like to win. I wanna
win just like All Might.
No matter what you
have to offer me,
that will never change,
do you understand?
[SHIGARAKI]
Father.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
While the UA teachers
hold a press conference
to appologize for allowing
a student to be kinapped,
five of us head to the
League of Villains' hideout
to try to save Kacchan.
Yaoyorozu's tracking
deviced leads us to...
...a Nomu factory?!
But, why isn't anyone here?
Where in the world are
they hiding Kacchan?
Next time: "All For One"!
The true villain, the source
of this evil arrives,
and the full story
is finally revealed!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!