[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward
my dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[COMMISSIONER 59A]
Targets and balls?
Sounds more like a game
than an examination.
Is it too easy?
You're not seeing
the bigger picture.
The real test is how they
handle the ensuing chaos.
Will they panic?
Or maintain the level head
of a pro who utilizes
their Quirk to make
wise decisions.
It's crisis response.
[COMMISSIONER 59A] And the
second round is the same way?
We normally focused
on individuals,
not how well they work together.
This proposal came from
the National Police Agency.
They've revised
the exam criteria
and the way we grant licenses.
We have to abide
by their orders.
We're to assume that,
at this level,
all examinees will
have knowledge of basic
emergency procedures
and first aid.
Therefore, we'll be
paying closer attention
to how they cooperate
with each other.
[COMMISSIONER 59A]
Heh. Teamwork, huh?
All right.
It's necessary for our future.
People loved All Might
not just for his strength,
but for his personality.
We must accept the fact
that the number-two hero
is no replacement.
It will be difficult to find
someone so charismatic.
Rather than waiting
for the next All Might,
we should fill the hole he has
left with an army of heroes
boasting a strong sense
of unity and comradery.
And the exam now
reflects that goal.
[MERA] Well, the second round
of the test is underway.
Rescuing people injured in a
large-scale terrorist incident.
And dealing with the
villain behind the attack.
[IZUKU]
What happened?
[GANG ORCA]
Tell me, wannabe heroes.
Can you rescue people and
fight at the same time?
That's Gang Orca!
[MERA] During the
search-and-destroy mission
against the League of Villains,
Gang Orca fought alongside
Endeavor and Best Jeanist.
He's a strong pro.
[MERA] The terrorists have
appeared and are beginning
to sweep the area. Hero
candidates at the scene should
continue their rescue efforts
while also suppressing
the newly-arrived villains.
[TENYA] We're going to have
to save people and battle?
Are they serious?!
Jeez! Come on!
Aren't they expecting
too much from us?
Even for a pro,
this would be difficult.
They're going a
little far, I'd say.
[GANG ORCA]
Now. How will you react?
Will you fight or protect?
Help, or run away?
What would a hero do?
[OJIRO]
Another attack?
Look! By the first aid station!
[OJIRO]
Not good.
[ASHIDO] Right by all those
hurt kids and old people?!
That's so mean!
We still have a lot
of bystanders to rescue.
But we can't just
ignore the villains.
I know.
[MERA] For this second test,
everyone starts out
with a certain number of points.
They'll be judged on
how many they lose.
HUC evaluates whether
or not someone's
acting properly during
their rescue.
For example: if the examinee
has put themselves
in the position
to best use their Quirk.
Additionally, there are
one hundred employees
of the Public Safety
Commission who are grading
each person individually,
based on the scoring manual
and the examinee's background.
Students automatically
fail the moment
their total score
falls below 50 points.
I hope everyone down
there has the patience
to make smart decisions.
[SHINDO]
Get everyone to safety!
Shindo, wait!
[SHINDO]
Do it!
Get them as far away from
the villains as possible!
Right!
I'll start hammering
away at the henchmen
at one second intervals.
[ORCA TERRORISTS yell]
Weren't expecting that.
[GANG ORCA]
Nice try.
Whoa, dang, look at that.
He's going all out.
[AIZAWA]
I wonder.
[IZUKU]
Shindo!
[GANG ORCA] A single rear
guard to hold us back?
You've underestimated me.
[PRESENT MIC]
Gang Orca! Quirk, Orcinus!
He can do whatever an
orca can, even on land.
That includes using
an ultrasonic wave
to paralyze his prey!
[GANG ORCA grunts]
[IZUKU]
Todoroki!
[OJIRO]
Midoriya, are you evacuating?
We'll help!
--[ASHIDO] Todoroki's fast.
--[IZUKU] Hey.
Where have you guys been?
We found hurt people
over by the river.
Everybody else ran
to the city first,
so we were searching
on the outskirts.
Yaoyorozu and Asui stayed behind
to search for survivors.
But we couldn't stand by and
watch these villains do this.
[GANG ORCA]
Your power is nothing.
Guess I know why
he's number ten.
This wind.
[YOARASHI] I'm gonna blow
you evildoers away!
A second villain attack.
Man, they really pulled out all
the stops for us, didn't they?
[gasps]
[IZUKU] Hey, it's him.
The one who turned down UA.
[OJIRO]
Good timing.
We can keep evacuating
while the strong attackers
hold them back.
[ASHIDO]
Yeah!
[COMMISSIONER 59C]
Good.
They're prioritizing the safety
of the first-aid station,
which is the cornerstone
of the entire rescue effort.
That's smart of them.
And they put the two students
best suited for holding Gang
Orca back on the front line.
Nice work!
[YOARASHI]
Of course you're here, too.
I just can't help
but hate both of you.
[TODOROKI]
That's my line.
Everything you say
is a distraction.
Why don't you go help
with the first aid
station instead?
Your Quirk would
be good for that.
I'll take care of him.
[GANG ORCA]
Here they come.
[ORCA TERRORIST 59A]
Huh? Where are they aiming?
Why'd you use your flames?
The heat makes the air rise up!
Because he didn't fall
to my ice earlier.
You ruined my shot
on purpose, didn't you?
Using your wind to
blow away my fire.
[gasps]
[YOARASHI] You blocked me
so you'd get all the glory!
[TODOROKI] What? Why would
I do something like that?
[YOARASHI] Why wouldn't you?
Hatred's in your blood.
You are Endeavor's son.
What the hell has been up
with you this whole time?
My old man's got
nothing to do--
[ORCA TERRORIST 59B]
Like my Cement Gun?
Good luck tryin' to move
when that hardens up.
[GANG ORCA]
This is outrageous.
I can't believe you're arguing.
[YOARASHI]
This has everything to do...
...with your
cold-blooded father.
To me, heroes should
be full of passion.
They bring hope and
inspiration to people
with the fire burning
in their hearts.
They care!
[ENDEAVOR]
Move it. You're in my way.
[YOARASHI] It was a shock
to meet your father.
Because the only thing
I could see in his eyes
was an insatiable anger
aimed at the entire world.
[YOARASHI] And then, at the
entrance exam, I saw you,
and I knew who you
were immediately.
Because when I said hello...
[TODOROKI]
You're in the way.
[YOARASHI]
Your eyes were the same as his.
You think we're the same?
Don't be ridiculous.
You're a fool.
I'm nothing like him.
[TODOROKI]
I have to stop listening.
He's just someone
who hates my father.
He doesn't really know me.
I have to focus on the test.
I have to keep my cool.
I have no feelings about
my old man anymore.
[TODOROKI] No. There is
still some hate inside me.
Dammit. This is no good.
[GANG ORCA]
Hmph.
A villain in front of you
and you've done nothing.
Jeez.
You and your father
are the only heroes
I can't accept.
You don't deserve
the title. Understand?
Now move!
[TODOROKI]
Focus.
Again? Are you kidding me?
[TODOROKI]
No! He'll be incinerated!
Dammit. What are you two doing?!
[YOARASHI] I've never
been afraid of anything.
Even when I was a kid,
I was fearless.
[YOARASHI]
Ah! It's so fast and cool!
[CLASSMATES scream]
I dig these little bugs.
[YOARASHI] I could find reasons
to like just about anything.
That's why, the minute I
understood what a hero was,
I knew what I was going
to be when I grew up.
Tackling crises,
rescuing people,
risking their lives for
the sake of the world.
That took real passion!
[YOARASHI] Which is why I
couldn't understand him.
Endeavor.
Who had eyes that seemed
to hate everything they saw.
He was the only thing
I couldn't stand.
[PRESENT MIC]
Rock on!
The written part of the
recommendation test is over.
The practical's next. And then,
finally, the interview.
You'll go six at a time
for the practical.
Get steppin' when
your number's called.
The exam will be
a three-kilometer race.
But, it's an obstacle course,
so you can't just run
straight through it.
Use your Quirks to
reach the finish!
[YOARASHI] This is it.
The best hero school in Japan.
[buzzer blares]
[YOARASHI] The most passionate
training I could hope for
is waiting for me.
[YOARASHI] Making an ice path
to move. That's smart.
I really didn't like
the look in his eyes.
But his abilities are on fire!
He'll probably be
accepted after this.
Then maybe I can become
friends with him,
and his eyes won't
bother me anymore!
[PRESENT MIC] Wowzah! Number 41
finishes first by a hair!
[PRESENT MIC]
And it's three minutes faster
than the average time.
All right! I won!
But who knows what'll
happen next time.
You were amazing!
I'm guessing you must be
Endeavor's kid, am I right?
That's so awesome.
Shut up.
I just came here to pass
a stupid test, that's all.
I don't care if I beat you
or not, so give it a rest.
[YOARASHI]
Those eyes.
You're in my way.
[YOARASHI] It's like he hates
something that isn't even here.
Dammit. What are you two doing?!
[gasps]
[YOARASHI gasps]
Hard to believe they're
from top schools.
Probably end up failing.
Not that I'd blame the judges.
[typing]
[TODOROKI]
A Quirk that uses wind.
That's right. He was in my way.
He beat me at the
recommendation exam.
Why didn't I remember him?
He's so loud and obnoxious.
[TODOROKI] I guess I wasn't
really seeing him back then.
I just needed to
reject that bastard.
I wasn't thinking
about anything else.
I forgot all about you.
[gasps]
[TODOROKI] Whether that's
a good thing or not...
Well, I guess I'll find out.
[TODOROKI] I did everything
I could to ignore who I am.
Is that catching up to me?
[TODOROKI]
My past, and my blood...
[TODOROKI] I can't just bury
them or forget about them.
[GANG ORCA]
No more games.
First I'll stop the wind.
[YOARASHI]
No!
[yells]
[ORCA TERRORIST 59A]
Got 'im!
[ORCA TERRORIST 59B] That's our
boss! A total powerhouse.
[ORCA TERRORIST 59C] Now it's
time to trap these do-gooders
in cement.
[YOARASHI]
No good. I can't control it.
[TODOROKI]
Hey!
[GANG ORCA]
You reap what you sow.
[GANG ORCA] He was too
far away. He's not done yet.
[ORCA TERRORIST 59A]
While the boss is at it,
let's go destroy the
evacuation shelter.
He'll love that!
[ORCA TERRORIST 59B]
Hell yeah!
[TODOROKI]
Shit!
[YOARASHI]
Not like this.
[IZUKU]
Dammit. What are you two doing?!
[TODOROKI, YOARASHI]
Seriously!
[YOARASHI] How did I become
everything I hated?
[TODOROKI] I'm in this mess
because of my own actions.
[YOARASHI, TODOROKI]
I have to fix this.
Oh, no. They're gonna
catch us! Faster, guys!
[IZUKU] They're too close.
I have to be the front line.
I'll take care of this.
[ORCA TERRORISTS yelping]
Whoa, Shindo!
I thought you couldn't move
because of his blast.
Well, my extremities
are still pretty numb,
but I'll bounce back.
Soundwaves aren't that bad.
Not much different
from my vibrations.
So I've built up a pretty
good tolerance to them.
Might be the first time I've
been thankful for that recoil.
Anyway.
I was trying to get a surprise
attack in on that whale!
And then those two
first-years ruined it.
[IZUKU]
So intense.
I've tripped the henchmen.
Now you make sure
they're out of the game.
We'll split up and get
the remaining injured
to the shelter.
[IZUKU]
Right!
[GANG ORCA]
Now, then.
I'll take down the wind-user
and continue with the attack.
[TODOROKI] We competed with
each other for no reason.
Our Quirks aren't compatible,
and we have zero teamwork.
There's no way we
can beat a top hero
when we're at odds like this.
Hopefully, he understands, too,
and feels the same way I do.
[YOARASHI]
The heat makes the air rise up!
[TODOROKI]
Come on. Work with me.
[YOARASHI] I'm so numb
that I can't put much
into my Quirk, but...
I have to do this!
[TODOROKI]
With fire...
[YOARASHI]
...and wind...
[TODOROKI, YOARASHI]
...we'll trap you!
[GANG ORCA]
He didn't even move his body.
His strength and
accuracy have decreased,
but his incapacity
wasn't complete.
He's able to control his Quirk.
Barely. And this one.
Todoroki can't move either.
But he's adding his raw power
to Yoarashi's attack.
This won't make up for
their foolishness earlier,
but it's not a bad start.
[GANG ORCA]
They realized their mistake.
And as such, they're trying
to make up for it.
I have to admire
their persistence.
[ORCA TERRORIST 59A]
Hey, behind us!
[ORCA TERRORIST 59B]
The boss is trapped by
some kinda fire tornado!
[ORCA TERRORIST 59C]
Isn't that bad?
He's an orca, so he's super
weak when he gets dried out!
Forget the wind. Stop the flame!
[ORCA TERRORIST 59A]
What?
[ORCA TERRORIST 59C]
Todoroki! He used both sides!
[TODOROKI] If I could only use
both sides at the same time.
Switching slows me down.
I need to practice more.
[TODOROKI]
When I can't move,
my speed doesn't
make a difference.
[ORCA TERRORIST 59D]
Should we go back and help?
[ORCA TERRORIST 59E]
Hey! Look out!
[IZUKU]
Smash!
We can stop them.
[ORCA TERRORIST 59F]
Keep shooting!
[OJIRO]
I'll take this.
--Nice moves.
--[OJIRO] 'Kay.
The injured have
all been evacuated,
and reinforcements should
be here any minute now.
[MERA] Looks like almost
all of HUC has been rescued.
They only have three
people to get to safety
before they're done.
Then, the test will
be over for the year.
They just have to do their best
to hold Gang Orca
off until then.
I'll be able to sleep soon.
Hey, guys! You miss me?
We're here to help.
[ORCA TERRORIST 59G]
Mow them down! Don't let up!
[TSUYU]
Ribbit!
Asui--er, Tsu! When did
you sneak over here?
[TSUYU] I've been training
my frog skills,
and I've finally reached
a new level of control.
Camouflage. That's my
new special move.
[OJIRO]
Wow, Asui.
Are you done with the search
and rescue already?
For the most part.
Ribbit! Look out!
[ORCA TERRORISTS yelp]
[OJIRO]
Shiketsu High!
[MORA]
I sent Inasa here to help.
But he has disgraced
on our school's name.
There should be no enemies left.
So strong!
Yeah.
We're not done yet.
[TSUYU]
Ribbit.
[GANG ORCA] A cyclone
prison of wind and fire.
Not bad. An ordinary
villain would give up.
Would weep and beg your mercy.
But what would you do,
if your desperate
trap was not enough.
You must always be
planning your next move.
So... What now?
[TODOROKI]
I have nothing.
[IZUKU]
No! Get away from those two!
[GANG ORCA]
Midoriya!
[TODOROKI]
How does he always do this?
--[buzzer blares]
--[IZUKU] Huh?
[MERA] Um, yeah, so, at this
time, all of the HUC members
who were deployed have been
rescued from the disaster zone.
[KAMINARI]
Huh?Really?
We were the last ones?
[MERA] It may seem
anticlimactic, but with this,
the provisional licensing exam
has officially been completed.
It's over?
[MERA]
After we tally the scores,
we'll announce the results
here in the arena.
Anyone injured should
go to the infirmary.
The rest of you are
free to change clothes
and wait wherever you like.
[ORCA TERRORIST 59A]
Sorry, Boss.
I guess we didn't do our
job all that well, huh?
And your restraining gear
must've made it
pretty hard to move.
[GANG ORCA] No. The gear
wasn't the problem.
That tower of flame
was an inspired attack.
And with Midoriya's
surprise counter
once I had been weakened...
We might have had a hard
time if the test went on.
Even lost. Hmph.
[MERA]
Okay. Everyone.
Thanks for your hard
work in today's exam.
Now, before I
announce the results.
I should probably explain
the way we evaluated you.
Between HUC, and those of us
at the Heroes Public
Safety Commission,
we had a two-fold demerit
system that we used
to determine your total scores.
In other words, we were
evaluating you based on
how few mistakes you made
in a crisis situation.
Anyway, the names
of those who passed
are listed here in
alphabetical order.
Keep my words in mind
as you search the screen
for your name.
[IZUKU]
Midoriya... Midoriya...
[IZUKU gasps]
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
After the exam,
Kacchan confronts me,
but I can't tell
what he's thinking.
Will we end up fighting?
This might not be good.
[IZUKU] Next time:
"A Talk About Your Quirk."
Go Beyond! Plus Ultra!