[BUBAIGAWARA] Having a good
sense of who you are
is one of the most
important things in life.
Look at all those happy people
on their way to work.
Makes me sick.
[TWICE]
Nah. They're freakin' great.
[BUBAIGAWARA] They think they're
such good, decent citizens.
[BUBAIGAWARA]
And what about me?
I'm doin' the same
thing I do every day.
[TWICE]
You're doing something special!
[BUBAIGAWARA] I'm starin' out
my window and people watching
while having my
morning cigarette.
[TWICE]
Then the fun begins.
[BUBAIGAWARA]
Two weeks since All Might fought
All For One in Kamino Ward,
and then retired.
It's the only thing
anyone's talking about.
Media's tryin' to scare people
by stirring up unease.
However, despite
All Might's retirement,
we haven't seen many big
changes in everyday life.
We should be looking
ahead of all this.
This is a time to investigate.
How will villains act and
what are our countermeasures.
[BUBAIGAWARA] You're different,
though, Mr. Miyagi.
I approve of you.
[TWICE]
Gross. I don't.
[MIYAGI] The fact of the
matter is that All Might
simply got too big.
He was such an
all-encompassing symbol
that his existence
was an impossibility.
[BUBAIGAWARA] The biggest
change for regular folks
is the new number one.
Endeavor.
Not quite the same as All Might.
So the public is focusing
their fear on him.
Waiting to see how he'll
act. Not surprising.
He's not the type
that everyone loves.
[BUSINESSMAN 62A] It's not
that I don't like Endeavor,
I just can't help but
compare him to All Might.
And, you know,
that's kind of a lot
for any hero to
live up to, right?
[BUBAIGAWARA] Yeah, he's
not really a cuddly person.
More like an average guy
pretending to play the hero.
[TWICE]
He is a superhero!
[BUBAIGAWARA]
Through circumstances
beyond his control,
he's inherited a role that
he's totally unsuited for.
Poor bastard.
Now he's a symbol of
the weakening heroes.
[MIYAGI]
Although Endeavor has resolved
a number of large cases,
he's got a temper and has
gone overboard many times.
Also, we polled males between
the ages of 20 and 40.
They do not like him.
He's just no replacement.
This is a prime example
of why those of us
in the media should stop
reporting negatively
about pro heroes and actively
raise excitement for them.
Instead of focusing on
the problems we're facing,
we should see how we can
highlight the positives.
[BUBAIGAWARA] The man knows
what he's talkin' about.
Physical power isn't the
only thing that weakens.
The heart does as well.
[TWICE]
Nah, it's all about power.
Shut up! Leave me alone.
[BUBAIGAWARA]
"I am here."
That's what he said when
he saved people's lives.
For any regular Joe,
that was reassuring.
But for people like me, it was
nothing short of a curse.
[YELLOW laughs]
Holy crap. That was too easy!
And ain't nobody
gonna stop me now.
[BUBAIGAWARA] Villains.
Only faithful to themselves.
This is the future
now that he's gone
[STORE MANAGER 62A]
Oh, come on.
Give me a break for once.
Hey, help me! Somebody stop him!
[BUBAIGAWARA]
I get it.
Crime is tempting for
those who don't know
what else to do
with their Quirks.
That part will
play out as usual.
Ya'r through, villain.
Your life of crime ends here!
[BUBAIGAWARA] But this part
is gonna be slightly different.
[VILLAIN 62B]
Yellow, hurry up!
[VILLAIN 62C cackles]
Look at this idiot.
He brought the whole counter!
[VILLAIN 62B]
Too bad for you, hero.
[VILLAIN 62C]
He's not some two-bit robber.
We're a team.
[VILLAIN 62B]
Yeah!
[VILLAINS] You're facing
the Reservoir Dogs!
Don't you forget the name.
[BUBAIGAWARA] Not as scary
to cross on a red light
if everyone else
is doin' it, too.
Those who're teamin'
up and getting
coordinated are starting
to get some traction.
The thing is,
we're looking for people
who are a little more...
[phone rings]
What's up, Giran?
How you been doin' lately?
Long time no talk.
I trust that you've
been all right.
[BUBAIGAWARA]
Hard to say.
I don't know how to tell
if I'm doin' good or not.
I see, that is a tough break.
[BUBAIGAWARA]
You didn't answer my question.
Are you okay? Tell me.
Yeah, sure I am.
I've been so busy I'm
crying with delight.
These past few weeks,
there's been
a monumental surge
in the black market.
Everyone's looking for
suits or support items.
Demand couldn't be
any better, my friend.
And, of course,
the League of Villains
are the darlings of the hour.
Well, that's nice to hear.
[TWICE]
No, it's not.
Shut up! Dammit.
So? Why are you calling me?
I'm a busy man, you know.
[TWICE]
I've got nothin' to do.
I couldn't get ahold of Dabi.
Any idea where he is?
Shigaraki wants everyone
to have a quick meetup.
I'm sure he'll be
contacting you soon.
[TWICE]
I know where he is.
No, I don't.
You can't keep
pullin' this crap.
Right. Okay, then.
Caught you at a bad time.
Take care of yourself, huh?
[BUBAIGAWARA]
Damn it. I'm me. I'm in control.
[BUBAIGAWARA] The league
of villains is currently
scattered across
different locations.
To get the police off our backs.
Hide our trails.
And recruit new comrades.
The goal is to make the
organization even bigger.
[HOODLUM VILLAIN 62A]
What the hell are you?
Your face makes me wanna puke.
[HOODLUM VILLAIN 62B]
Keep lookin' at me like that
and I'll kill ya.
[DABI]
Pity. You're not what we need.
[HOODLUM VILLAINS scream]
Stay down. You make good fuel.
Allow my flames to consume you.
[BUBAIGAWARA]
This is no good.
I need to bind myself together.
I'm gonna tear apart.
[BUBAIGAWARA groans, pants]
Split in two.
[TWICE]
Once I'm wrapped up, I'm whole.
[rumbling]
[TWICE]
Here's a story.
I used to be one of those guys
who liked to cause trouble.
My Quirk is called Twice.
It's a simple power that
turns one thing into two.
I can make a clone of myself.
And then make clones
from that clone.
An entire gang of just me.
I made my clones do everything.
I was a king ruling over them.
But, the other mes weren't
satisfied with that.
And they put together
a little coup.
[TWICE]
I was almost killed by myself.
The things I make
don't disappear
until they've taken
some serious damage.
Before long, all of us were
arguing with each other.
Each one of us thinking
we were actually the real me.
This absurd
self-mutilation continued
for nine days.
Can you imagine that?
In the end, they
killed each other.
And disappeared. All gone.
Ever since then,
I haven't been sure
that I'm the real me.
How could I be after
all the madness?
And there's no
place in the world
where crazy people can belong.
Heroes only care about
saving good citizens.
But the league
accepted me as I am,
problems and all.
And I'd like to think I'm
okay with who I am, too.
Now, I'm scouting people.
Trying to find the ones
with the same kind of crazy.
[TWICE] We're all wackos
lookin' for a place we belong.
[CHISAKI] A bunch of capable
adults got together
and all they stole was a
convenience store register?
Heh.
This big a gang, they should
have shot for a loftier goal.
[CHISAKI]
You guys aren't well.
What you need is a cure.
[KURONO]
We got the money.
We should skedaddle before
any heroes get here, yeah?
Overhaul.
[CHISAKI] They're all sick.
Every last one of them.
[TWICE] But the biggest wackos
have stopped searching
for a place to belong
and created their own.
Both the hero side and
our side have started
changing in unexpected ways.
Still. What's important is
knowing who you truly are.
What you wanna become.
What you wanna do.
Yes. That's very important.
So. What should I do?
[IZUKU] There's hardly any
pain or weird sensations.
[DOCTOR 46A]
In other words, if you sustain
this type of injury, even
just two or three more times,
I don't think you're
going to be able
to move your arms anymore.
I was really careful
to hold back
when I threw a punch
against Kacchan yesterday.
But when I'm not fully under
control of my emotions,
I should be extra careful
to not use my arms.
Instead, I'll concentrate
on my Shoot Style.
Listen up, everyone.
Stay in line and move
promptly into position.
I want to see order!
Uh. You're the only one
who's not in line.
[TENYA]
The dilemma of a class rep!
I heard a little rumor
about Class 1-A.
Two people!
You had two people fail the
licensing exam, you losers!
Monoma from Class B.
He's just as uhinged as usual.
Bet you were the only one
in your class to fail.
Just like in the final, huh?
[laughs]
That wasn't an answer!
Ha! Actually...
Every one of us passed.
We've pulled ahead
of you big shots.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
They're the ones who're
turning it into a competition.
It's no big deal.
Accordin' ta teacher Vlad,
we'll have classes
together this semester--doesn't
that sound like it'll be fun?
I'm lookin' forward to it.
[KIRISHIMA] I can't wait
to test out my skills!
Oh hey, isn't she
the exchange student?
Touch me and I'll
pummel you till
yo mama doesn't know ya.
[laughs]
Stop filling her
mind with crazy!
[SHINSO] Hey. We're tryin'
to get through back here.
Our apologies.
Come on, everyone.
Save your chit chat for later.
We're clogging up the hallways.
I honestly can't believe
how uncool you are.
Shinso.
Oh right, the guy
who fought Midoriya
at the sports festival.
You sure that's the same guy?
Looks like he's bulked up
a bit since then.
Hi there! It's the
adorable small mammal
you all know and love,
the principal.
You may notice the
fur I'm so proud of
has deteriorated in quality.
I haven't been
taking care of it.
This is something that can
happen to humans, too.
Even if you eat a balanced diet
full of vitamins and minerals,
you won't have a mane
of luscious locks
unless you're getting lots
of sleep. That's the secret!
Disturbances in your
normal resting patterns
are terrible for your hair.
So, if you want to
improve your fur's...
[OJIRO] Is this really
important right now?
[KAMINARI]
Please tell me he's almost done.
My own sleep cycle has been
upset by the incidents
that took place over
summer vacation,
which I'm sure everyone
here knows about already.
We lost a pillar of hope.
The ramifications of which
have appeared faster
than I could have ever imagined.
And there will likely
be even more chaos
throughout our world
in the near future.
In particular,
this will be most
apparent to those of you
studying in the hero course.
You must approach
extracurricular activities,
like the hero work
studies available
to second and third years,
with a greater
sense of caution...
Hero work studies?
Maybe they're the next level
after the internships
we already did?
[NEZU]
The air always feels heavy
when we talk about
gloomy subjects.
But, rest assured, your
teachers are working hard
to remove this weight
from yours shoulders.
I'd like all of you to learn
from their diligence,
and remember that hard work
will help you develop
into capable heroes.
Whether hero core,
support, business,
or general studies.
I don't want any
of you to forget
that you're the one's who
will inherit our society.
[VLAD KING] Well spoken.
Thank you, Principal Nezu.
[NEZU] If you're looking
for a successor,
there's no place
overflowing with more
raw talent than UA High School.
Think about coming
to teach for us.
Given your current state,
I'd recommend cutting back
on the heroing, anyway.
And trust me, I'm not
saying this without
a few students in mind.
I have no doubt that someone
worthy of your power
walks the halls
of our fine school.
[VLAD KING] Now, we'll hear
from the extra-curricular
guidance teacher.
Please give Mr. Hound Dog
your attention.
[HOUND DOG]
Yesterday...
[HOUND DOG growls]
Two students--
[snarls]
[howls]
[VLAD KING]
All right.
As you just heard, there were
students fighting last night.
I know you're not used
to life in the dorms,
but let's all be a little more
respectful moving forward.
[KIRISHIMA, KAMINARI]
What was Mr. Hound Dog
even here for?
Does he forget human speech
when he gets angry?
There's still so much weird
stuff at UA I don't know about.
Midoriya and Bakugo
were doing well,
but now they're being treated
as problem children.
[VLAD KING] That's it.
Back to the classrooms
starting with the third years.
[HADO] Hey, hey,
listen to what I heard!
It was a couple of first-years
who were fighting.
Two boys from Class 1-A.
Isn't that a scoop?
Hey, do you know them?
They must get excited easily.
Really?
[AIZAWA]
Okay.
Starting today we'll
resume our regular classes
and training schedule.
I know a lot has happened
recently, however,
you need to switch gears and
focus on your school duties.
We're lecturing today,
but this semester
you'll have even harsher
training than before.
[ASHIDO]
He can't mean that, right?
Like to share, Ashido?
His icy stare is back!
[TSUYU] Excuse me, sir.
May I ask a question?
What were those
things the principal
was talking about during
the opening ceremonies?
I've never heard the term
hero work studies before.
I know right?
That had me pretty
confused, too.
I also have concerns.
He said they're something
the upperclassmen
participate in, correct?
[AIZAWA] I was planning
to talk more about those
at a later date, but I guess
telling you now is more logical.
To put it simply, it's
work outside of class.
Like the internships you did
at pro hero agencies before.
Only closer to the real thing.
[OCHACO]
Huh. I never heard about these.
Wait, then why did
we work so hard
at the sports fest?!
She has a point.
If we have work studies,
those who weren't scouted
at the sports festival
still have career paths.
You gotta calm down.
You're acting kinda nutso.
This doesn't make sense!
You'll be using your connections
from the festival to
secure a work study.
It's basic networking.
This isn't part of your
normal classwork.
It's discretionary
for each student.
That means those
who weren't scouted
at the sports festival
will have a hard time
lining one up I'm afraid.
Originally, individual agencies
recruited on their own.
But there was lots of
competition as people
tried to recruit UA students.
So this is how things ended up.
Good enough, Ochaco?
I'm sorry I jumped
to conclusions, sir.
[AIZAWA] Now that you have
your provisional licenses,
you can assist in real ways,
for longer periods of time.
Until now, there haven't
been many first years
who've received their licenses.
With the increased
activity of villains,
we're currently exploring
the idea that you can
participate in work
studies as well.
We'll explain more about
the work study positions
and what that program entails
at a later date, but for now...
We've got other things
to worry about.
That's all. Sorry to
keep you waiting, Mic.
[PRESENT MIC]
First period is English!
In other words, it's jam time!
Been an age since
I stood on this stage.
Ya miss me?
We've got a lot to cover today!
Let's get rollin'
with it. Ya dig?
Excuse me, but what is
with this dust, Bakugo?
[KATSUKI] Deku was s'posed
to do that! Shut up!
Hey, can't you even clean
something right, you idiot?
Right! Sorry!
Man. I'm so beat.
[IZUKU] Hey, guys. If you put
your trash in the halls,
I'll take everything
down in a second.
[SATO]
So. Present Mic's class today.
You as lost as I was?
Were we supposed to
know all the grammar
he was going over?
[ASHIDO]
Oh, yeah, that! Right?
I was, like, is
this even English?
[KIRISHIMA] I think I
studied the wrong chapters!
[SATO] I got stuck at
the beginning and then
I couldn't figure out
anything after that.
[JIRO]
About those work studies.
I wasn't scouted, so I wonder if
I'll get to participate in one.
[HAGAKURE]
Maybe we can go to the places
we did our internships.
I'd be totally down
with doing that.
[OJIRO]
I hope I get to do one.
[TENYA high-pitched]
In just one day,
I've been completely
left behind!
That's what you're thinking,
right, House Arrest?
Hey, don't call
me that, it's mean!
Um, Iida. What's a work study?
Something I can't
tell you about.
The teachers have forbidden
us from giving you
any details about our classes.
Sorry, but you'll just have
to experience the same shock
and surprise we went through.
Did you catch that? Bakugo?
Shut your mouth!
I heard you, four eyes.
[IZUKU]
Aw, man. What is a work study?
I'm clearly being left behind.
I know it's just the
start of the semester,
but these three days
of house arrest
are gonna hit me really hard.
There's hero basic
training tomorrow!
Everyone's gonna be
learning new stuff
while I'm stuck hanging
out in my room.
I hate this. I'm falling behind.
I can't slow down now.
Ha! Trash, amiright?
[yelps]
What are you doing?
You know you can just
throw away the food trays
with the burnables, don't you?
Uh. Yeah.
[IZUKU] Am I going insane?
What was that?
[IZUKU screams]
So, you must be that excitable
first-year, aren't you?
Ha, ha! I bet that was a
freaky surprise for ya.
Kinda sorry about that!
Gotta admit, I did pop up
here 'cause I thought
you'd be shocked, though.
What in the world are you?
[laughs] Not a bad question
there, my friend!
I admit, sometimes I
even weird myself out!
You know, once in a blue moon.
But don't worry,
you're gonna find out
who I am soon enough.
I'm just glad it looks like
you've got a fighting spirit.
You see, the truth is that
people are talking about you,
so I came to see what
the fuss was about.
[IZUKU]
Okay. What just happened?
I feel like I've seen
him somewhere before.
[IZUKU] Despite it seeming
like time was crawling by,
three days eventually passed,
and I turned in
my written apology.
My house arrest ended
the day before Kacchan's.
I was back!
Guys! I'm sorry for all
the trouble I caused!
No sweat, Deku. Thanks
for your hard work.
All he did was vacuum.
And what's with
those steam nostrils?
Class Rep! Iida! I'm sorry
I disappointed you!
Right.
Well, I'm glad you learned
from your mistakes.
Follow the rules from now on.
I'll catch up with
everything I fell behind on
these past three days!
[KIRISHIMA] That's fightin'
the spirit! Do it, man!
Time to take your
seats, everyone.
[IZUKU yelps]
[chairs scraping]
[AIZAWA] Morning. Now
that Midoriya is back,
we'll go into more detail about
what the work studies entail.
Go ahead and come in.
[AIZAWA] I'll have people
who've experienced them
firsthand explain.
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] I suggest you listen
carefully as they point out
how work studies differ
from internships.
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] These three
are third years at UA.
They rank at the very
top of our student body.
You may know them
as the Big Three.
The Big Three. And it's him.
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
In work studies, we'll be able
to act like real heroes.
The students teaching
us about the program
are those who rank above
all other students at UA.
The trio known as the Big Three.
One of them is Mirio Togata,
who suddenly offers to fight
everyone in my class!
How will I fair against the
best students at school?
Do any of us stand a chance?
Next time: "Unrivaled"!
Wow, with that ability,
he could totally become
the number-one hero!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!