[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward my
dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome obstacles
and save people with
a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[REPORTER 47A] You spoke about
keeping the students safe,
Eraser Head.
But according to our
information, you encouraged them
to fight during the attack
on the training camp,
putting them in grave danger.
What was your
reasoning for this?
I concluded that because we
didn't know the full situation.
Allowing them to use
their Quirks would help
avoid the worst
possible outcome.
And what would that outcome be?
Do you think 26 victims
and one kidnapped child
is a win for UA High?
I assure you that
things could have gone
much more poorly.
I feared every student
would be tortured and
killed in the end.
Most of the victims were
harmed by the gas attack.
We've determined it to be the
result of a poisonous Quirk
used by one of the villains.
It's thanks to the quick
actions of Ms. Kendo
and Mr. Tetsutetsu that injuries
were kept to a bare minimum.
Additionally, we're providing
mental health counseling
to every student,
though at the moment,
we do not see any signs of
serious psychological trauma.
So you've found a bright
spot in this tragedy?
We're relieved that
an entire class
of burgeoning heroes
still has a future.
Can you say the same thing
for the abducted,
Katsuki Bakugo?
He enrolled at your school
with excellent marks,
and went on to win
the sports festival.
Before that, he
survived the attack
of a powerful sludge
villain who eventually
had to be taken down
by All Might.
The boy is obviously
strong and heroic.
On the other hand, the violence
he displayed in the finals
and his attitude at
the awards ceremony
both showed that he
cannot control his temper.
What if this is the real reason
the villains kidnapped him?
What if they're brainwashing
Bakugo right now,
pulling him toward
the path of evil?
How can you sit
there and tell us
he still has a future?
[VLAD KING] This reporter knows
exactly what he's doing.
He's trying to antagonize us
so we say something damning.
You can't fall for it, Eraser.
He probably knows how much
you hate the media.
Don't let him trick you.
[AIZAWA]
As Katsuki Bakugo's teacher,
I take full responsibility for
not taming his violent behavior.
However, his actions
at the sports festival
were born of his
deep-seated convictions.
He's trying harder than
anyone in his pursuit
to become the top hero.
If the villains think they
have a chance with him,
then they are grossly mistaken.
I can guarantee you that much.
That doesn't amount to
real evidence, though.
I didn't ask you how you feel,
I asked you if you had
concrete information.
We're doing our best
with the intel
we currently have available.
I have no doubt the police
will break this case very soon.
We won't rest until
our missing student
is returned to UA.
Hah! Did ya hear the teachers?
They get me more than I thought.
I'll never join your
league of bastards!
[KATSUKI] They went through
the trouble of mounting
a huge attack, all just
to bring me back here.
The idiots even told me
what they wanted.
For me to join their
pathetic group.
Which means I know
they won't kill me.
What a bunch of amateurs.
Now's my chance.
I gotta take a couple
of 'em down quick,
and get the hell outta here.
We may not be at camp,
but I'm still allowed to fight!
He must've figured out
he's important to us.
What a clever boy.
No. He's a fool.
Let me stab him.
[MR. COMPRESS] A clever
performer would've acted
like we were winning him over.
Now that he's broken
character, he's finished.
I only do whatever I want to,
and I won't even
pretend otherwise.
And I'm tired of
being surrounded
by a bunch of lame-ass wannabes.
[SHIGARAKI]
Father.
[KUROGIRI]
No, Tomura Shigaraki. Be calm.
Don't lay a finger
on him. Any of you.
This "hero"...
[SHIGARAKI]
...is still a valuable piece.
[SHIGARAKI] I wish you would've
listened to what I had to say.
I thought you and I could
come to an understanding.
[BEST JEANIST]
Heroes and villains
are cut from the same cloth.
What, you think we're the same?
Not a chance.
[SHIGARAKI]
Then I have no choice.
The heroes said they'd
continue their investigation
of our group, so we don't have
time to stand here and talk.
Master.
Lend me your power.
That is a wise decision,
Tomura Shigaraki.
Okay, this is the spot the
tracker is broadcasting from.
So that's their hideout?
Not a bad one, I guess.
[YAOYOROZU]
Maybe it is and maybe it isn't.
According to the
tracking history,
the villain hasn't left this
location for the past day.
But that's all we know.
One villain is hiding here,
but that could be it.
They might have Bakugo
somewhere else.
We're going into this
operation completely blind
for the most part. Please
try to proceed logically.
I don't like this.
None of us are good
at sneaking around.
We need Hagakure or Jiro here.
If I think things are gonna
be the least bit dangerous,
we're done.
I won't hesitate to
call the police, either.
To make sure my
friends are safe.
[IZUKU]
Thank you, Iida.
So, what can we do with
what's in front of us?
Let me see here.
[mumbling] The prerequisite is
that we don't use our Quirks
to fight the villains,
and on top of that,
we need to figure out...
[KIRISHIMA] It's been a while
since I've seen him this weird.
[YAOYOROZU] Yeah, this is
truly peak Midoriya.
[TENYA]
That's right.
Once you set your
heart on something,
there's no swaying you.
You won't stop.
It's what I respect
about you as a friend.
And a rival.
But there must be boundaries.
And someone has to make
sure you don't cross them.
This time, I'll protect you.
[ENDEAVOR]
Why should I clean up UA's mess?
I'm a very busy man,
as you know.
[BEST JEANIST]
Get off your high horse.
You are a UA alum.
We can't call any heroes
away from the school.
There is a bigger
picture, Endeavor.
[ENDEAVOR]
Tch.
[TSUKAUCHI]
It's possible this incident
is the beginning of the
end for Hero society.
We'll stop at nothing
to resolve this successfully.
[BEST JEANIST]
During the internships,
I invited Bakugo to my agency
to try and reform him.
I've met very few
as stubborn as he is.
I imagine he's fighting back.
We need to hurry.
[GANG ORCA] Not even you were
able to change his behavior.
[BEST JEANIST]
Yes. He was inflexible,
pride sewn into his very core.
My comrade, Ragdoll,
was also taken.
This is my chance
to get her back.
[TSUKAUCHI] Thanks to
the tracking devices set
by one of the students,
we now believe there are
two separate hideout locations.
We know from our investigations
where the kidnapped
victim is located.
We'll send the bulk
of our forces there.
Retrieving Bakugo
is our priority.
At the same time,
we'll gain control
of the other hideout.
This will cut off
their paths of retreat.
We'll arrest them all at once.
[GRAN TORINO]
Toshinori.
If they're recruiting
old men like me, then...
What are you suggesting?
You're still Gran Torino.
And with such staggering
stakes at hand.
We can be sure that
he is involved.
All For One.
We have the element of surprise!
These villains will not succeed!
At the press
conference earlier,
we had Principal Nezu
act clueless
to deceive the villains.
He feigned ignorance on camera,
as if we didn't have leads.
After hearing his words,
the villains won't expect us
to rush in on the very same day.
We'll retaliate! It's time
for our counterattack!
Remind the world what
you can do, Heroes!
We've gotten pretty close,
but I haven't seen
anything move inside.
And not a single light is on.
It doesn't look
like anyone's home.
They're hiding this
lair in plain sight.
It looks like any other
abandoned warehouse.
[IZUKU]
The weeds under the front door
are thick and undisturbed.
There must be another
way to get in.
Maybe someone's
Quirk is hiding it.
We can't just enter carelessly.
It could be a trap.
If we could just
see inside somehow...
[DRUNK MAN 47A] Hey. You lookin'
for a real man, darlin'?
I'm good.
Ditch these losers
and come drink with us.
Come on, don't go
pickin' fights.
[IZUKU]
Hey! You talkin' ta us?
Let's get out of here.
It's not crowded, but
there are people around.
We can't draw
attention to ourselves.
So what's our next move?
[IZUKU]
Let's go around the back.
It might be the best
chance we have to get
some solid intel on this place.
This is so narrow.
I might get stuck.
Just keep moving.
We have to figure out
what's happening inside.
No one will see us
from back here.
[gasps] There!
We should be able to get
a look through that window.
We'll be blind in the darkness.
One second, I'll make
a night vision scope.
Wait. No need.
I actually brought one
along with me for this.
[IZUKU]
Whoa, really?
When I thought about
what we'd have to do,
I figured we might need it.
Sure, but aren't those
models super expensive?
I did some research on
them when I was thinking
about my costume, but,
they cost, like,
50,000 or something, right?
[KIRISHIMA]
Whatever, man. Just drop it.
Right. Then Kirishima
will serve as our scout.
Back him up, Midoriya.
[IZUKU]
Hold steady.
[TENYA]
Don't lean forward too much.
We may have to run
at a moment's notice.
[KIRISHIMA] Iida, can you
move back a little?
[TENYA]
Tell us what you see inside.
Quickly. And be quiet!
Got it. The place
is pretty trashed.
Doesn't look like... Uh...
[yelps]
Hey, you okay?
What's wrong? You weren't
spotted, were you?
The back left.
The corner, Midoriya. Look!
[IZUKU]
No way. Are those all...
...Nomu?
[SHIGARAKI]
Master. Lend me your power.
A master?
I thought you were
the boss around here.
But you're a sidekick.
[SHIGARAKI]
Kurogiri. Compress.
It's time to put him
back to sleep.
[MR. COMPRESS sighs]
I can't believe he's such a bad
audience member.
It's almost impressive.
If you want me to listen,
then get on your knees and beg!
[KATSUKI]
I wanna blow them away
with maximum firepower, but
that warp guy is way too fast.
Think.
I need to make an opening
somehow and get to the backdoor!
[knocking]
[VOICE] Hello? I gotta
pizza delivery here.
[ALL MIGHT]
Smash!
[SPINNER]
What the--?
[SHIGARAKI]
Kurogiri! Gate!
[KAMUI WOODS]
Pre-emptive Binding...
...Lacquered Chain Prison!
Heh. That's it?
Don't do anything foolish.
It's in your best interest
to cooperate with us.
[ALL MIGHT] Just what I'd expect
from a competent new hero.
And a veteran pro who moves
faster than the eye can see!
You can't run anymore,
League of Villains.
Understand?
Because we are here now!
[MR. COMPRESS] Right after
the press conference?
They had this ruse
planned the whole time!
[TWICE] Tree man!
You're hugging me too tight!
Harder!
[EDGESHOT]
One tends to neglect defense
when they're on the offense.
But we didn't come alone.
Take a look.
[EDGESHOT]
You're surrounded by the police.
Not to mention powerful
heroes like Endeavor.
Tsukauchi!
Why does Edgeshot get
to rush into the fight
while I'm stuck here with you?
Because if someone slips out,
we'll need you to
capture them immediately.
Ugh!
Ah, you must've been scared.
But you stayed strong.
I'm sorry. You're
safe now, young man.
What?! I wasn't scared!
Not even close!
[ALL MIGHT]
Heh!
[SHIGARAKI] After I went
through all the trouble
of preparing this,
the final boss
goes and shows up
on my doorstep.
Everyone's been restrained.
There's no easy way to escape.
It can't be helped.
So, they've got backup,
huh? Well, we do, too.
[SHIGARAKI] Kurogiri!
Warp over as many as you can!
The Nomu, right?
[thud]
[KIRISHIMA]
Hey!
[IZUKU gasps]
Is that...?
[STUDENTS yelping]
[SHIGARAKI] What are you
waiting for, dammit?
[KUROGIRI]
I'm sorry, Tomura Shigaraki.
The Nomus were supposed to be
in a fixed location
but... they're gone!
[SHIGARAKI]
Huh?
[ALL MIGHT] It seems you have
a lot to learn, Shigaraki.
You're still green.
[SHIGARAKI growls]
Your little League
underestimated all of us.
The soul of this young man.
The police's diligent
investigations.
And... our righteous fury!
[BEST JEANIST] We have control.
The Nomu are neutralized.
Enough is enough.
Your game has come to
an end, Tomura Shigaraki!
[yelps] All Might, please!
You're the only hero
Stain respected!
You are worthy!
You think it's over?
Don't be stupid.
I've only just begun to play.
Justice. Peace.
You created a garbage
society by lifting up
such ridiculous ideals.
That's why I targeted
you, All Might.
It's why I started gathering
people to my cause.
You think this is the end?
Then you've lost.
Kurogiri!
[MAGNE yelps]
What just happened?
I couldn't see anything.
Did they kill him?
[EDGESHOT]
I played around with his insides
and made him fall unconscious.
Ninpo: Thousand Sheet Pierce!
He was such a nuisance.
He had to sleep.
Weren't you listening earlier?
You'll all be better off
if you take us seriously.
Kenji Hikiishi.
[gasps]
[GRAN TORINO]
Atsuhiro Sako.
Shuichi Iguchi.
Himiko Toga.
Jin Bubaigawara.
[GRAN TORINO] Though they had
little time and information,
the police worked
through the night
to discover your
true identities.
Do you understand?
There's nowhere left
for any of you to run.
So, Shigaraki. One question.
Where is your boss hiding?
[ALL FOR ONE] No one's come
to save you, have they?
You've had a hard life,
Tenko Shimura.
"He'll be fine.
Eventually, the
heroes will help."
I'm sure that's what
everyone thought
as they looked away
and ignored you.
The world shouldn't
be so unforgiving.
You didn't do anything wrong.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Don't worry. I am here for you.
[SHIGARAKI]
No. This is not over.
Just you wait.
The game is still mine.
You'll tell us where
he is right now.
[SHIGARAKI]
Go away. Disappear!
[ALL MIGHT growls]
Shigaraki!
[SHIGARAKI]
This is your fault. I hate you!
--[SHIGARAKI gasps]
--[NOMUS growling]
[KAMUI WOODS]
Nomu! How'd they get here?
What is this?
Dammit, Edgeshot. Stop Kurogiri!
[EDGESHOT] He's still out.
This isn't his doing.
[GRAN TORINO]
They keep on coming.
Don't release them under
any circumstances, got it?
[KAMUI WOODS]
Right!
[KATSUKI]
The crap?
Bakugo!
No!
[KAMUI WOODS]
Endeavor! Help us!
No!
[growling]
Tsukauchi. Evacuate the area!
They're from the other hideout.
That location should
be locked down.
Come in, Jeanist. What the
hell is going on over there?
Jeanist?!
Toshinori. What now?
They shouldn't have been
able to warp Nomu here.
And this backup came too fast!
[ALL MIGHT]
I fear that he has made a move.
[SHIGARAKI]
Master.
What? Did the building
just come down?
[gasps] Gang Orca and Mt. Lady?
Whoa, even Best Jeanist is here.
[YAOYOROZU]
And Mr. Tiger, too.
Ugh. Are these gross
dudes really alive?
I thought we'd be in for a
fight, but this was super easy.
Maybe we should've
left this to the police
and gone with All Might.
[BEST JEANIST]
Difficulty and importance
are two very different
things, rookie.
Riot squad, get the
transports ready.
There could be more of them.
Be on your guard.
[RIOT SQUAD 47A]
Yes, sir!
C'mon, Ragdoll. Wake up for me.
[GANG ORCA]
Is that your teammate?
She's breathing. That's good.
Yes, but... Look at her.
What have they done
to you, my friend?
Everything's fine.
The heroes were on top of
this way before we were.
This is great!
Now then, let's get back home.
At least we won't have
to explain ourselves.
It sounded like All Might
is somewhere else.
Does that mean he's
rescued Kacchan?
If All Might's on the scene,
there's no reason
for us to worry.
Let's go. Quick.
Right.
[ALL FOR ONE]
I'm sorry, Tiger.
But Ragdoll's Quirk
was so useful.
I just had to take it.
How could I not?
Are you with the League?
Somebody get us a light.
[ALL FOR ONE] Since my body
was mostly destroyed,
I haven't been able
to stock up on Quirks.
[GANG ORCA]
Stop there! Don't move!
Hey! You can't attack like that!
What if he's just a bystander!
[BEST JEANIST]
Think about the situation.
A moment of hesitation
could decide the fight.
We can't let these
villains try anything!
[BEST JEANIST grunts]
[ALL FOR ONE] Tomura has finally
started thinking rationally
and making decisions by himself.
I do wish that you hadn't
gotten in his way.
[IZUKU]
There was no time to stop him.
No time to even move.
It happened in an instant.
A microsecond.
And in that moment,
this man made us feel death.
We could see it in
front of us clearly.
[ALL MIGHT]
Since you now bear One For All,
you may one day have to fight
against this great
evil yourself.
Because I failed.
[IZUKU]
"Tomura." He meant Shigaraki!
What is this? It's not
true, is it, All Might?
Don't tell me that this...
...this is... All For One.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Now then. Shall we begin?
[IZUKU]
Now, the preview!
In one horrible instant,
the pro heroes
who raided the Nomu factory were
defeated by a massive blast.
The one to blame for the attack
is the villain
All Might spoke of,
the Symbol of Evil, All For One.
In the face of his
terrifying presence,
fear has us unable to move,
even though Kacchan is
right in front of us!
Next time: "Symbol of Peace"!
Everything's okay now. Why?
Because he is here!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!