I've been giving it
a lot of thought.
You got your Quirk from
All Might, didn't you?
He gave you his power.
You're not trying
to deny anything.
Which means I must
be right. So say it.
Okay. What if it's true?
When you and I were kids,
we both wanted to be
like All Might.
But I had the potential.
Then somehow, a little
nobody like you
was singled out by the
person I admired most,
and I didn't even realize it.
That's why we're here.
We are settling this.
Right here. Right now.
Wait, what?
How is that the best way
for us to work things out?
No. This is bad.
We're not even supposed to be
at Ground Beta by ourselves.
Why don't we talk about this
during one of our free periods?
We could reserve a training
room or something.
There's no reason
it has to be right now.
If we fight for real at
school, we'll be stopped.
[gasps]
I wanna know what made All Might
give his power
to a loser like you.
Let me see for myself.
Is it because you looked up
to him more than I did?
And if that's the case,
does it mean everything I've
done to be like him is wrong?
No, Kacchan.
[KATSUKI] Hey! Did you
see what he just did?
Man, it doesn't get any
cooler than All Might!
[IZUKU]
He's always smiling.
No matter how bad things get.
[KATSUKI] No matter how
much trouble he's in,
he's always the winner.
[IZUKU] He's the coolest
in the universe!
[IZUKU] Do you think
I can be a hero, too?
[IZUKU]
Y-You really wanna do this?
If you don't wanna
get hurt, punch back.
Oh, yeah, you switched
to using kicks
more these days, didn't you?
Come on, stop!
This isn't smart.
Kacchan!
[IZUKU]
A right hook?
No. I got him like that before.
He'll remember.
That's a feint.
[grunts]
[KATSUKI]
You know your problem?
You're always
over-thinking things.
Just fight me!
You're serious? You wanna spar?
[SECURITY ROBOT 61A]
Two students from Class 1-A
identified breaking curfew.
Contacting their
homeroom teacher now.
Hey. Eraser Head!
Your students are loitering
at Ground Beta!
You're responsible for
rounding them up.
Are you kidding me?
[AIZAWA] Who would be stupid
enough to sneak out?
[IZUKU]
You have to stop this.
Why hurt each other when we
could just talk things out?
You were right to look up
to All Might like you did.
I know just how much
he meant to you
when we were growing--
I told you to wait!
--[KATSUKI growls]
--[IZUKU] Wait for me! Please!
Kacchan!
[KATSUKI] You were always
behind me. Our whole lives.
Are you all right?
[KATSUKI] You were stuck to me.
I couldn't get rid of you.
No matter how much I tried,
you kept coming back.
Listen to me!
Stop running!
Stand up and fight!
[KATSUKI]
We both admired him. So why?
[ALL MIGHT]
In small doses,
pride can be useful
attribute to have.
I'd say you certainly have the
ability to become a pro hero.
I know why you're so
angry, Young Bakugo.
Because of Young Midoriya's
sudden improvement, right?
But you have to remember
each of your rankings
when the year first began.
It's much easier to level up
when you're a novice.
[KATSUKI]
Why?
[grunts]
Tell me!
[IZUKU pants]
Hey.
Are you all right?
[KATSUKI]
Don't you dare worry about me!
Attack me!
Why won't you fight back?
Why did I end up
having to chase after
someone who was always
so far behind me?
Why did a damn small fry like
you get strong and become
the number-one hero's
sidekick? His favorite?
You got so much better,
and I destroyed All Might.
I admired him so much.
But it's because of me that
he ended up losing his power!
If I had been stronger...
If I hadn't been
kidnapped by villains...
Then it never
would have happened.
All Might knows it was my fault,
but hasn't said anything.
Everyone has to know, though!
I can't get it out of my head.
It's like it's constantly
playing on loop.
So, what the hell
am I supposed to do?!
[IZUKU]
No.
He's been carrying this guilt
with him the whole time?
Even more than me.
[IZUKU]
He's been blaming himself.
Obsessing over it.
[IZUKU]
It turned out our fight wasn't
what I thought it would be.
It didn't really matter
who won or lost.
That wasn't the point.
Even so.
I felt like I had to
go through with it.
Because, in that moment,
I was the only
person in the world
who understood how Kacchan felt.
[KATSUKI growls]
[IZUKU]
This is actually good.
I can see whether or not my
Shoot Style works against him.
[IZUKU] If I'm gonna do this.
I'm going all out.
I refuse to be your
punching bag, Kacchan.
Let's go!
[IZUKU] He just needed
to vent his emotions,
and fighting was the
only way he knew how.
I couldn't ignore
him or run off.
Not after everything
we'd been through.
Our relationship to one another
was totally screwed up.
Kindergarten, elementary,
middle school, high school.
We'd known each other
for so long,
but until that point...
...we'd never talked
about how we really felt.
[KATSUKI grunts]
[IZUKU]
Above!
That was close.
[KATSUKI]
Can't let him think.
[IZUKU] He'll be on me
before I land. This is bad.
[IZUKU]
Watch out for his hand.
[KATSUKI yells]
[IZUKU gasps]
[IZUKU grunts]
[KATSUKI grunts]
[IZUKU]
No time to catch my breath.
[KATSUKI yells]
[IZUKU grunts]
[IZUKU]
It's no good.
He's not giving me any time
to try and predict his moves.
His reaction times
have gotten faster.
Much better than the
last time we fought.
I guess I shouldn't be
surprised that we've both
been getting stronger.
What're you smiling about, huh?!
[KATSUKI] I thought you weren't
gonna be my punching bag!
[IZUKU]
I'm not!
I bet you've got some kinda
plan up your sleeve.
That's one of the things
I hate most about you!
[KATSUKI] I can never tell
what you're thinking.
No matter how much
I beat you up,
you keep coming back!
It's obvious you've
always looked down on me.
Even when we were kids.
[gasps]
[KATSUKI]
You think you're better than me.
But if you seriously
believe you're gonna
surpass me as a hero,
even with your new power,
you better think again, Deku!
Wait. Is that what
you actually believed?
All this time?
Think about it, Kacchan.
If I looked down on you,
I wouldn't want anything
to do with you anymore.
But I'm still here.
I noticed things you
couldn't all these years
because I had nothing at first.
There were things
I hated about you, sure.
But I could clearly see
how amazing you were.
You had so much going for
you that I didn't have.
All Might was my hero,
but you were the one
actually in my life.
[KATSUKI]
He's faster than before.
[IZUKU]
Because I was so emotional,
I lost a bit of control.
I'd been focusing on
keeping my Full Cowling
at five percent power
the entire time.
But I didn't realize how
much stronger my body
had gotten thanks to all
the training and testing.
[KATSUKI]
I can't dodge. Gotta block!
[IZUKU] My continuous
whole-body limit had been
raised to eight percent.
[IZUKU] I thought you
were incredible, Kacchan.
I wanted to see...
what you'd become!
[grunts]
That's the reason...
I kept chasing after you.
[IZUKU] I wasn't prepared for
this new level of speed.
[KATSUKI grunts]
[IZUKU] Going from a continuous
five percent to eight percent
isn't a dramatic change
in the long run.
But with that slight difference,
just for an instant...
That's the reason...
I kept chasing after you.
[KATSUKI]
You passed me.
[KATSUKI, IZUKU yell]
[IZUKU yelps]
[KATSUKI grunts]
[KATSUKI]
My timing was off on that hit.
He kicked into a higher gear.
Is that all you've got?
[yells]
[IZUKU] I'd never admit
something like this
to your face.
But the truth is...
[IZUKU]
Can't you see?
That's why I wanna beat you!
Because you're amazing!
[IZUKU] When I get riled up
and my desire to win
surpasses my desire
to save someone,
without meaning to,
I start talking like you.
You're so mean sometimes.
And I hate it.
But my idea of victory is
so tied to the image of you
in my head that,
in those moments,
I can't help but imitate you.
[KATSUKI] I've got the
upper hand in the air.
[IZUKU]
I didn't jump without a plan.
Kacchan thinks he's
got a strong handle
on my new Shoot Style.
But I'm not nice enough
to let him pummel me
just to relieve a little stress.
[IZUKU] The only reason
I'm using my kicks
is so my arms don't
get too abused.
But I never said I couldn't
use them at five percent.
[gasps]
[IZUKU] You're the best.
That's why I want to defeat you!
[ALL MIGHT]
Now, it's your turn.
[IZUKU] I have to, in order
to meet the expectations
that All Might has for me.
[IZUKU] I'll work until
I have full control
of this borrowed Quirk.
And I'll finally beat you
with my own power!
[KATSUKI]
I won't lose to you!
[BOTH panting]
[IZUKU coughs]
[KATSUKI grunts]
That's it. We're done here--
I won this fight.
You have All Might's power,
but even using his strength,
even after making it your own,
somehow you still
managed to lose to me.
[panting]
Why?
[KATSUKI]
How could you lose?
[coughs]
[ALL MIGHT] Stop this
right now. Both of you.
I'm sorry. But I heard
what you've said.
All Might.
When'd you get here?
[ALL MIGHT] I didn't notice
before. I should have.
[KATSUKI]
It's too late now.
Why did you pick Deku?
It started when the sludge
villain came, didn't it?
So why him?
He was powerless.
But still more heroic
than anyone else.
I knew you were strong.
That much was obvious.
You were someone who
could already fight.
So, I decided that he
should have the chance
to stand in the ring.
But now you know
I'm weak, too.
I always wanted to be like you,
which meant being
as strong as possible.
But look what I did to you.
Because I'm not good enough.
[ALL MIGHT] This is not
your fault, Young Bakugo.
I was always going
to lose my power.
You couldn't do anything
to change that.
You are strong.
But I focused too much
on your physical strength
and overlooked what
was important.
This isn't your burden.
I apologize.
Sometimes I forget
that you're children.
After being a hero
for so many years,
you learn a few things.
Striving to be the best,
like you, Young Bakugo.
And caring deeply about people--
about rescuing those in trouble,
like you, Young Midoriya.
Both of those feelings
are necessary in a hero.
Otherwise, they'll never truly
be able to represent justice.
That's why you admire
his strength so much,
Young Midoriya.
And I know that's why you've
always feared his heart
and spirit, Young Bakugo.
Now that you've laid your
feelings out on the table,
maybe you can
understand each other.
If you have mutual
respect and focus on
making one another stronger,
I've no doubt you'll become
the ultimate heroes,
winning and saving people
at the same time.
[KATSUKI] Dammit. That's
not what I wanted to hear.
[KATSUKI]
You.
You had the strongest
guy in the world
lay the groundwork for you.
Don't you dare lose again.
I'll work harder
so that I can beat you.
[sighs]
Okay, so talk. Who
knows about you two?
Recovery Girl and
Principal Nezu do.
As far as students
go... Only you.
And you don't want
this to get out.
'Cause that would be bad.
Don't worry. Your
secret's safe with me.
I won't tell anyone
what's going on.
Unlike Deku, I can
keep my mouth shut.
This will stay between us.
Thanks, Kacchan.
I don't deserve this.
I should be down on my hands
and knees begging for you
to keep this secret for me.
Yet here you are,
being considerate
and helping me out. Thank you.
I'm not doing this for you.
It would just be a real pain
if this got out and
messed stuff up.
[ALL MIGHT]
Now that it's come to this,
I can explain what
happened between
me and Young Midoriya.
That's only fair.
[IZUKU] And so, All Might told
Kacchan the whole backstory.
About the power passed
down through generations
in order to be used
against great evil.
About how he used
that power to become
the Symbol of Peace.
How he was gravely injured,
which limited his strength.
And finally... how he
chose his successor.
[KATSUKI] If this got out
people'd be confused,
and they'd start wondering
where the power is.
You idiot. What
were you thinking
when you first told me about it?
[ALL MIGHT]
It was my own choice
to use up the last
of my abilities.
I said this earlier, but...
That was in no way your fault.
[KATSUKI]
Yeah. Sure.
[KATSUKI] It doesn't change
what I have to do.
I'm gonna end up being
the number-one hero
no matter what!
True. You're right about that.
Things aren't gonna be
the same, though, Deku.
You got that?
You've been watching me
and everyone around you,
absorbing what you see
to get stronger.
Well, I can do
the exact same thing
and keep getting better myself.
I'll go higher than
even you, Chosen One.
Right, then I guess
I'll just have
to be better than that.
You what?
I have to go higher than you.
[KATSUKI grunts]
Dammit, nerd.
I just said I was gonna
be the one to surpass you.
[IZUKU]
I know!
And now I'm saying that I'm
gonna go beyond that level.
[KATSUKI]
What?!
[ALL MIGHT] They've become
proper rivals now.
In a way that they
weren't before.
[IZUKU] The secret between
me and All Might
became a secret the
three of us shared.
[IZUKU]
And then...
[AIZAWA] You fought the
night you finished
the preliminary
hero licensing exam?
I'm glad to see that you
two have so much energy.
Aizawa, wait, hold up
with those restraints.
It's my fault that they
sparred in the first place.
Huh?
[AIZAWA]
Midoriya and Bakugo.
Why am I not surprised
to hear that.
I understand they're
at the practice field.
Yes. I wanted to catch
you before you went.
I've known these two since
before they came to UA.
And I've given the pair
quite a bit of thought.
Will you leave them
to me for now?
I'll bring them back.
Your fault? And how is that?
[IZUKU, KATSUKI yelp]
[ALL MIGHT] It seems Young
Bakugo has been feeling
like he was responsible
for my retirement.
He had to face
the licensing exam
with those pent-up emotions and
then his inferiority complex
exploded and this happened.
It's all because I didn't
realize I was being negligent.
This whole fight
was brought about
because of the failure
of his teacher.
[AIZAWA grunts]
[AIZAWA]
I understand that they felt
they had to break the rules.
But this isn't something
I can just ignore.
There must be a
suitable punishment.
Who threw the first punch?
I did.
I also went pretty hard.
It wasn't just him.
You're both on house arrest.
Four days for Bakugo,
and three for Midoriya.
During that time, you'll
clean all the common areas
in the dorm, morning and night.
Plus, I want a written apology.
If your injuries need
to be checked out,
head to the infirmary.
But don't rely on the
old lady's Quirk this time.
Figure out a way
to heal yourselves.
[sighs]
[AIZAWA]
That's all! Go.
[STUDENTS]
What?
You guys threw down?
[HAGAKURE] And now you're
under house arrest?
[KAMINARI]
Hilarious.
[AOYAMA]
Tres tragique .
[SERO]
You're both morons.
[TOKOYAMI]
The pinnacle of stupidity.
[KATSUKI growls]
So, did you guys
make up after or...?
[IZUKU] Well, it wasn't
that we made up, exactly.
Hm... It's kinda hard
to put into words.
You're lucky you two got
away with house arrest.
Though this does mean you'll
miss the opening ceremony
we're going to right now.
Bakugo. What about
our extra classes?
Shut up, Icy Hot! This has
nothing to do with you.
[KAMINARI] 'Kay, well,
thanks for cleaning up!
[KATSUKI growls]
[IZUKU]
So... about my Shoot Style.
What did you think of it?
[KATSUKI]
Your movements are too obvious.
Even when you got faster,
I was able to dodge them.
You're not gonna win
any fight that way.
Oh. Right.
[KATSUKI]
And when you added in punches,
it really pissed me off.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
Got it.
Here's the preview!
UA High's second
semester has begun.
After the Hosu Incident,
the training camp,
and the provisional
licensing exam,
we've all grown quite a bit.
Now it's time to show
off what we can do
in our work studies!
Unfortunately, with
All Might's retirement,
a lot of the villains who've
been hiding in the shadows
are starting to become
much more active.
Next time: "A Season
for Encounters"!
This is the story of how
I met the Big Three
who rank at the top of UA.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!