[IZUKU] Welcome to UA High,
the prestigious school
that's turned out some of
the world's greatest heroes.
I'm running toward my
dream in these halls.
Learning to overcome
obstacles and save people
with a smile on my face.
That's how I'll become the
greatest hero in the world!
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
Don't be cocky! We're prepared!
[TODOROKI] Looks like a Quirk
that makes things bigger.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A] That's
not all I brought with me!
[TODOROKI]
Even if I couldn't melt it,
I should have at
least made a mark!
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
Your fire won't work against
any of my tools.
Tungsten has a super
high melting point!
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A] I'm afraid
I told you so, Todoroki.
Even if you're a top UA student,
if you think can pass
this exam alone...
Well, then...
Your pride will
be your downfall.
You fools.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
Do it!
[SEIJIN STUDENTS]
Right!
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
Keep attacking. Don't let up!
[SEIJIN STUDENT 55A]
Got it!
[TODOROKI] Water for my flames
and physical attacks for my ice.
They've worked out a way
to counter everything I have.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54AA]
It's useless to resist!
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
Where'd he go?
[TODOROKI] The Heroes
Public Safety Commission
must have constructed
this factory
to be as realistic as possible.
No wonder they told us
to choose a terrain
that would suit our style.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
There he is. Surround him!
[TODOROKI] In that case,
I'm guessing that this tank
is full of the real thing.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A gasps]
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
He got us.
[SEIJIN STUDENTS scream]
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
To pull such a move. He's crazy!
[TODOROKI] Well, it looks
like the commission
kept the force of the explosion
from being too damaging.
[SEIJIN STUDENT 54A]
You bastard.
Apologies. But I simply
cannot afford to fail.
[TODOROKI] If I could only use
both sides at the same time.
Switching slows me down.
I need to practice more.
[beeping]
[TARGET] Students who have
passed the exam should
congregate in the
anteroom. Chop, chop.
[PRESENT MIC] These high-tech
targets keep track
of who passes and fails.
With so many examinees,
it's the only way
that makes sense.
The targets can also determine
who is responsible each
time one of them is hit,
based on a student's
location, movements,
and various other
factors being recorded!
Oh, and, once mounted,
they can only
be removed with a
special magnetic key.
It's all very fancy!
[SEIAI STUDENT 55AA] Miss Sai?
We'll soon have company.
I've confirmed four UA students
have entered the building.
[INTELLI]
Let's have a look at the video.
Certainly.
[INTELLI] Arm duplication.
A sound-wave manipulator.
The frog. And a Quirk that
allows you to make things.
It seems that our prey
has been decided.
Please gather the other ladies.
Yes, Miss Sai.
[INTELLI] The formula for
my success is flawless.
What an excellent
day for an exam.
[INTELLI laughs]
[TODOROKI]
So they've all passed?
[YOARASHI] Seriously?
I'm a huge fan of Stampman!
I love a hero who's
super passionate!
[STUDENT 55A]
Who is this guy?
[TODOROKI] If he applied
through recommendations,
I should've seen him
at the entrance exam.
I wanna be like...
Wait, what were
we talkin' about?
[STUDENT 55A]
I dunno...
You just came up
and started talking!
[MERA]
So far, 56 people have passed.
Don't panic, but do consider
that your time is almost up.
Good luck.
[TSUYU]
Having any luck, Shoji?
[SHOJI] It's no use. I can't
see anyone from our class.
[TSUYU]
Maybe they're in another area.
[SHOJI]
Most likely.
Yaoyorozu. You heard that right?
Less than half of
the spots remain.
We should probably give up
on finding everyone.
We need to fight for ourselves
and make sure we pass.
Yes. That would be wisest.
[JIRO]
Shh!
I hear four people
climbing the stairs.
Ten floors below.
They're headed up here.
[SHOJI]
Are they planning to attack us?
[YAOYOROZU] I don't understand
why there are only
four of them coming
if that's the case.
All the other schools
we've observed have moved
in much larger groups than that.
Maybe their companions
were defeated
and they're running
away to hide in here.
[JIRO] No. That's not
what this sounds like.
They're not stopping
on the other floors.
Are there more of them
hiding somewhere?
[YAOYOROZU] Is this a
distraction? Or worse.
[guitar strums]
[screams]
--[YAOYOROZU] Jiro!
--[TSUYU] Are you okay?
[SHOJI] There's music playing!
It's not too bad for me.
But hearing it suddenly must've
been a huge shock for Jiro.
So they must know Kyoka's Quirk
and were targeting
her on purpose.
[SHOJI]
It's a coordinated attack.
[YAOYOROZU]
This isn't good.
Now we can't tell
where anyone is.
Phase one's officially complete.
Let's begin phase two. Shouldn't
keep our guests waiting.
Everyone hide!
Attacks from the outside?
What's their plan?
[SHOJI] They're trying to keep
me from using my eyes.
[YAOYOROZU] The first thing
they did was counteract Jiro
and Shoji's Quirks,
which are perfectly suited
for detecting enemy locations.
Our opponents know
exactly who we are.
And more importantly,
what we can do.
[SHOJI] Yaoyorozu. What
could their next move be?
[YAOYOROZU]
I'm not positive.
But it seems likely that
they're trying to trap us here.
And then they'll surround us
and move in to
attack as a group.
[YAOYOROZU] Yes. We should
assume they're already
close by, waiting for the
right moment to strike.
In that case, we have to fight!
Wait, don't be reckless!
Heartbeat Dist--!
Phase two is complete, ma'am.
[SHOJI]
Jiro!
Are you injured?
[JIRO] They got my amp.
And my left ear!
[YAOYOROZU]
They knew what she'd do?
If they were able
to predict our actions
so accurately after
seeing only one attack
in the beginning of the exam,
then their plan is
well thought out.
There must be someone
extremely intelligent
among our opponents. A student
with an eye for strategy.
[SHOJI]
Does it feel colder to you?
Actually, now that
you mention it, yes.
[gasps] It's coming
from the vents!
[SEIAI STUDENT 55CC]
Phase three is underway.
[SHOJI]
They've shut us in?
The temperature is
steadily decreasing.
This place is turning
into a freezer!
Ri... Ribbit...
[SHOJI]
Asui! What's wrong?
--[YAOYOROZU gasps]
--[JIRO] Oh, crap.
Since the temperature
dropped all of a sudden,
her body's going
into hibernation!
Ribbit...
[SHOJI] We need fire!
Make a lighter or matches!
No, I can't. We'll set
the sprinklers off.
That's only going to
make her even colder.
An electric heater or something?
Our opponents have control
over the air conditioner.
They've probably turned off
the electricity as well.
Here's a blanket for now.
[SHOJI]
All right.
What're they doing to the door?
[YAOYOROZU] Welding it shut.
Trapping us further.
[SHOJI] Are they trying
to freeze us solid?
[JIRO] Those doors over there're
the only ones we have left.
[SHOJI]
We could break through.
[YAOYOROZU]
Our opponents are definitely
waiting on the other side.
It's dangerous.
[SHOJI] How did they manage
to outthink us so quickly?
What are we supposed to do?
[SHOJI] If we stay
holed up in this room,
we'll have to do
something about the cold.
Otherwise we'll be done for.
Yao-momo. What if
you made a bomb?
We could blow the door
to the emergency exit.
We'd run the risk of causing
a phreatic explosion.
And they likely knew
we'd think about that.
Which is why the sealed
the observation room
and lowered the temperature.
Then what?
[YAOYOROZU]
Think, Momo. You have to.
Figure out a solution
to this situation.
With one ear injured,
Jiro can't use
her sound attacks to
their fullest capacity.
So what? Should we smash
the wall to escape?
No. That's a simple move,
and our enemies
will have expected
something so obvious.
For now,
we need to do something
about the air conditioning.
I could make some clay
to seal off the vents.
It looks like there are
eight of them in the room.
That will end up using
a lot of my Quirk,
but right now...
it's all I can do.
[SEIAI STUDENT 55DD]
Miss Sai.
Phase three has been completed.
Lovely. Now we just
give them time.
[SEIAI STUDENT 55AA]
Yes, ma'am.
[INTELLI] The biggest problem
facing these UA students
is the frigid air being
pumped into the room.
In order to fix that,
the one named Yaoyorozu
must utilize her power.
Her Quirk uses the
lipids inside her body
to create solid matter.
In other words,
there's a finite limit
to how much she can create.
We'll make her
exhaust her abilities.
Then all four of their Quirks
will be rendered quite useless.
This is my strategic design.
My equation for success.
[PRESENT MIC] Seiai Academy.
Saiko Intelli, Second Year.
Her Quirk: IQ.
After she drinks tea
and closes her eyes,
her IQ multiplies.
It's already 150 to begin with,
so after a few sips,
she becomes a real genius!
By the way, different
brands of tea
have different effects
on her Quirk!
[INTELLI laughs]
[SEIAI STUDENTS]
Ah!
Now. Use your Quirk, Yaoyorozu.
It will be the
beginning of the end
for you and your friends.
[INTELLI giggles]
[INTELLI]
Now. Use your Quirk, Yaoyorozu.
It will be the beginning of the
end for you and your friends.
Hey, why aren't you
making anything?
[SHOJI]
Is there something wrong?
No matter how many different
ways I look at this situation,
I get the same answer.
The enemies want me
to use my Quirk.
[SHOJI] Until you can't
create anything else.
[YAOYOROZU] Right. My Quirk
has many applications.
They can't account for all
the things that I might make.
Which is why they're doing this.
At first, I thought
the manipulation
of the air conditioning was
to take Asui off the board.
But I believe their true
intention was to force my hand
and exhaust me.
[SHOJI]
Very clever.
And once you're powerless,
they'll march in.
No doubt they could
easily hit our targets.
Yes. So I can't use it.
We'd just be playing
right into their hands.
We wait for the need to arise,
when there's no other option.
[JIRO] But if we stay hiding
in here, there's no possible
way we'll pass
the licensing exam!
We should just charge out that
door and attack them head on.
[SHOJI] I'm sure that such
a smart enemy has predicted
that we might do that.
Okay, fine, then what do we do?
[YAOYOROZU]
Come on, think!
How would Todoroki act
in a time like this?
Or Iida. Or Midoriya?
[IZUKU]
I know I'm hurt.
But if I can still move at all,
then I can't just sit still.
I have to reach out
and do something.
'Cause all I can think
about is saving him.
[YAOYOROZU gasps]
[YAOYOROZU] That's right.
I have to save them.
Shoji, Jiro, and Asui!
Forget about my
provisional exam.
Focus on these three.
That's what really matters.
[YAOYOROZU]
In order to do that...
In order to get my
friends out of here...
[YAOYOROZU] Everyone, please,
endure these conditions
for a few more minutes.
[SHOJI gasps]
Hey, are you crazy?
[YAOYOROZU]
Just bear with me!
[JIRO]
Huh? Why headphones?
[YAOYOROZU]
Please, put them on.
[YAOYOROZU] It's the first time
I've made this device,
but its structure isn't
all the complicated.
I'll just save enough lipids
so I can still move.
And make it as big as possible.
Almost there.
Wait is that...?
[INTELLI]
It's been almost ten minutes
since they were
trapped in the room.
It's probably about time.
Prepare to take them, ladies.
[SEIAI STUDENTS]
Yes, ma'am!
[INTELLI]
Oh! How utterly delightful.
I wonder what we'll find inside.
[high-pitched rumbling]
[INTELLI]
No!
Is this... a sonic attack?
The headphones help, but the
force is rattling my body.
Ribbit.
[SHOJI]
Asui, are you all right?
Please, everyone.
Seven more seconds
and it'll be over.
Six... Five...
Four... Three...
Two... One.
[JIRO]
All right! We rocked this!
[panting]
Now, hit their targets.
[SHOJI]
You got it. Can you move?
Yeah. Ribbit. I'll be okay.
Oh, thank goodness.
[YAOYOROZU yelps]
[JIRO]
No!
[INTELLI] You used your Quirk
to attack not defend.
It was a high-risk move.
I can't believe a UA student
would choose such a method.
But because of that, you
can't fight now, can you?
I may not pass,
but I'll make sure
you don't either.
[YAOYOROZU]
I can't give up now.
Think of all the intensive
training we've done
at camp and school.
It's time to show off
those results.
[INTELLI growls]
You're struggling in vain!
[TSUYU]
Ribbit!
[INTELLI gasps]
You guys!
But, why did you come back?
Surely you assumed
that I'd already hit
all three of her triggers?
We're in the middle
of the licensing exam.
You should be thinking
of yourselves,
not your other classmates.
That might be how
you roll, but not us.
We're obviously different.
She's our friend.
Which means we'd never
leave her behind.
[SHOJI]
And we don't give up.
[IZUKU] I don't want to
choose one or the other.
I'm going to save both of them!
[SHOJI]
It's just like Midoriya said.
[YAOYOROZU]
It's how Class 1-A is.
We look out for each other.
You've defeated me completely.
UA doesn't disappoint.
[KIRISHIMA] Hey, Kaminari.
Why'd you follow us?
[KAMINARI] I dunno. 'Cause
you guys started running.
I didn't wanna end up alone.
Where're we going?
Shut up!
Why you always gotta
sound so mad?
I told you to chill out, Bakugo.
Looks like there's a lot
of people up there,
so the three of us
should work together.
[KATSUKI]
Go die.
[KIRISHIMA]
Come on, man.
Look out!
Kirishima!
[KIRISHIMA]
Damn it!
What's going on?
[KAMINARI] What the crap?
Did that really just happen?
[KATSUKI]
All I know is
that bastard looks
like he's to blame.
So I'll kill him.
[MERA]
More examinees have passed.
We're at 60 people now.
That means there
are 40 spots left.
[SERO]
We're running out of time.
This is bad. What do we do?
[IZUKU] Yeah. I knew we'd be
in trouble if we got split.
But at least we can probably
do something about the group
that's near us, and maybe
even make a few points.
[SERO]
Really? What are you thinkin'?
[IZUKU] Earlier, someone tried
to outpace his classmates.
[SHIKETSU BOY 54B]
I'll take her down fast.
[SHIKETSU BOY 54C]
No, wait!
He was panicking that he
wouldn't get enough points in.
Since his class
attacked as a group,
they'd definitely end up
fighting over their targets.
Oh, so, as people
get worried,
they'll break away from
their classmates,
and then they'll be
at a big disadvantage.
[SERO]
Wait. Then why were you saying
we should all stick together?
We'd be in the same boat.
Well, to begin with, we were
told to hit weak points
with balls, so it's
easy to think of this
as target practice.
And without knowing
our opponents' Quirks,
we're basically going in blind.
But it's not easy or efficient
to go after moving targets,
'cause, after all,
they'll be protected.
Think about it.
I wanted to first make
sure that we trapped
enough people for everyone
in our class to pass.
Then we'd use our
balls only after
they couldn't move anymore.
Our class has a lot
of people who excel
in restraining groups.
So I kinda thought it
wouldn't be any trouble.
[SERO]
I see.
It's true that if we were
just doing target practice,
they'd only be able
to tell whether or not
we were good shots.
There's more to this test
than I originally realized.
Shh! Listen, you guys.
Does it sound like
they're getting closer?
[SERO]
What should we do?
I'll go after them.
[SERO]
Huh?!
I'll be a decoy
so you can move.
Be on the lookout for
openings that'll let you
immobilize people
to get some points.
Your Quirks are better
at that than mine.
I'm more of a fighter.
[SERO] A decoy.
There's three of us, so,
we'd need six people.
Roger.
[SERO gasps]
Sero. Let's do it.
[SERO groans]
Okay, fine!
[OCHACO]
I trust Deku.
He's pulled through enough
times that I believe in him.
Now. Move.
[SHISHIKURA]
I'm from Shiketsu.
Please notice, my school
keeps our hats on
when we're working.
Why's that? Because...
Each and every one
of our movements
is crowned by the legacy
and honor of our school.
This is a demonstration.
Proof of the difference
in level between
my peers and your vulgar class.
We value obligation
and dignity--
things that appear to be
sorely lacking among you.
I really hate your type.
He's hard to follow.
Makes me feel kind of dumb.
[KATSUKI] He said his beady
eyes are full of tears,
so he can't see how
strong his opponents are.
[SHISHIKURA] My eyes are dry
and handsome, thank you!
Hey. Maybe don't
provoke this guy?
Look what he did to Kirishima!
[KATSUKI]
Tch.
[SHISHIKURA] UA High. I have
respect for your school.
I take pride in the fact
that our institutions
are treated as equals.
But your class is shameful.
You act in ways
that disgrace heroes.
He's attacking again!
I don't wanna be gross!
Shut up!
"Obligation"? "Dignity"?
You just like to
hear yourself talk.
I don't see any proof.
Show us with your actions,
not your cheap words.
If you can.
Beast. You're worst
of all, Bakugo!
[IZUKU] Draw the opponents
in as close as possible.
Make them gather in one place.
[IZUKU gasps]
Want some gum?
It's really a
finger trap, isn't it?
I hate this.
It's frustrating that we can't
tell who passes and fails
in real time.
And our Shindo
only made it worse
by splitting the ground open.
Now it's hard to see anything.
Wait. Eraser! Are you
actually worried?
There's something I've realized
after watching my students.
In school and in the field.
They might not have
realized it themselves,
but in Class 1-A,
there are two people
whose spirits have a big impact.
[AIZAWA] They're not leaders,
or the most popular.
And the two of them
don't get along at all.
Sometimes they seem
like polar opposites.
However, before I knew it,
their passion had spread
to the rest of their peers.
[AIZAWA]
It's strange.
But every time there's
some kind of major event,
one of them is at
the center of it.
[AIZAWA]
I'm not worried, Joke.
It's the opposite, actually.
I can't wait to see
what they'll do.
Even if those two aren't
physically with the others,
their presence raises the
standard for the entire class.
[MS JOKE] You've fallen for
them hard. It's kinda gross.
I'm honored to have
them as students.
My Class 1-A!
[IZUKU]
Here's the preview!
It's the final few minutes
of the licensing exam's
first round, and the rest
of my classmates and I
are fighting desperately.
I refuse to let us fail!
Next time: "RUSH!"
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!