Kota's parents died
two years back.
He was so small
when it happened.
It was a villain.
Huh?
[MANDALAY] They were killed
while protecting citizens.
Perhaps the most respectable
way for any hero to die.
But...
[KOTA]
Papa. Mama.
[MANDALAY] How do you even
begin to explain to a child
that his parents died
honorable deaths?
To him, they had
left him behind.
And all the while,
they were being praised.
Everybody kept telling him
that his parents' sacrifice
was noble.
Heroes just don't make
any sense to Kota.
After all, if his they
hadn't been heroes,
they would still be here.
[MANDALAY]
Trust me, Kota. It will happen.
You'll meet someone,
and you'll finally understand
why we do what we do.
Someone who'll risk their life,
put others first.
Someone who will be...
No one like that really exists.
[gasps]
[MINETA]
No way!
Why are there villains
attacking the camp?
Pixie-Bob!
This is bad.
[gasps]
Oh, no. Where's Kota?
[ASHIDO] Aw... We wanted
the chance to face off
with all the others.
I thought Pixie-Bob said
we'd be getting a reward.
This is more like torture.
We want our treat, Mr. Aizawa!
Do you want me to
tighten your bindings?
[AIZAWA] For tonight's lesson,
we'll be talking about
how to behave in an emergency.
If you don't become more aware
that you're falling
behind your classmates,
then the gap will
keep on growing.
In a broad sense, this
knowledge is your reward.
How's that for a treat?
I knew I shouldn't have
gotten my hopes up.
Oh, strange. Now,
who do we have here?
Five members of Class A
bombed the exams?
And look, there's only
one guy from Class B!
[KAMINARI]
You failed, too, idiot!
He tried to get under our skin
the same way yesterday.
At this point, I'm kinda
worried about him.
So, Vlad.
Why don't we start
with practice maneuvers?
I was thinking the same thing.
Perhaps we should pair them up.
[MANDALAY]
Everyone!
[KIRISHIMA]
It's Mandalay's Telepath.
So weird, right?
It's giving me chills.
It is sort of annoying
that it only works
in one direction, though.
Stop talking.
[MANDALAY]
Two villains attacked us.
It's possible there
are more coming.
Everyone, return to
camp immediately.
We're regrouping.
Do not engage any enemies.
[AIZAWA] I'll look after
the other students.
Protect them.
[MONOMA]
Wasn't this a secret?
[AIZAWA]
If it's a full-scale attack...
We're in big trouble.
Looks like your concern
has you distracted, Eraser.
[AIZAWA]
Vlad!
You pros oughta lay off.
We haven't come here
for any of you,
so just stay out of our way.
[SPINNER] How are you this
evening, UA High School?
We are part of the
Vanguard Action Squad
of the League of Villains.
[OJIRO]
The League of Villains?
What are those guys doing here?
[MAGNE] I could crush this
kitty's head so easily.
How about it, dears, should I?
You get away from her!
Now, now. Hold on, Big Sis Mag.
You, too, Tiger, calm down.
When deciding if someone
should live or die,
we must be careful that we're
abiding by Stain's principles.
Stain?
So, you're the ones
he ended up inspiring.
At your service. That's us.
And you, four eyes.
I believe I recognize you.
You're one of the
self-righteous brats
who attacked Stain in Hosu City.
Lemme introduce myself.
Call me, Spinner.
I'm here to make Stain's
dreams a reality.
[gasps]
[TIGER] I don't care who
you are. You're criminals!
The woman lying there
is named Pixie-Bob.
She's a pro hero who's
saved countless lives.
She's giving her all
for these young heroes,
pushing them to reach
their full potential.
She's looking for a mate,
but otherwise she's content.
What gives you the right to
cut such a happy life short?
Didn't anyone ever tell you
it's not a hero's
job to be happy?!
Tiger! I've talked to everyone.
Trust the safety of the
other students to Ragdoll.
You and I will stay here.
We'll hold them back!
You return to camp!
Class Rep, you're in charge
on the way there!
Don't engage anyone!
Leave it to me. Let's go!
Midoriya!
Go on ahead without me.
--Mandalay!
--[TENYA] What are you saying?
Kota. I know where he is.
[coughing]
[TETSUTETSU]
Kendo!
[KENDO]
Tetsutetsu! Ibara!
Where'd you get those masks?
[TETSUTETSU]
Yaoyorozu from Class A.
She made them for us.
Awase's taking her to
the rest of our class
so she can help them, too.
Take some. We brought a bunch.
Great. Thanks!
[KENDO] We need to get
back to camp fast.
Who knows how many villains
could be roaming
through the woods.
[TETSUTETSU]
No. I'm goin' to fight.
You make sure these two
get back to camp.
[KENDO] What? Mandalay
told us to retreat!
[TETSUTETSU]
You're always getting on Monoma
when he talks about the
differences in our classes,
but you feel it, don't you?
We're not the same.
[KENDO gasps]
[TETSUTETSU] We all got into
UA with the same exam.
We study the same curriculum.
So why are they better?
Isn't it obvious?
Class A has been through
crisis after crisis,
and turned each one
into an opportunity.
They've had so many
chances to prove themselves.
And come on, Kendo.
A real hero doesn't turn his
back and run from a bad guy.
Fighting villains is what we do!
[KENDO]
Yeah, but...
[TETSUTETSU]
Don't try to stop me.
We're in the hero course.
If we don't stand up now,
then when will we?
I'm goin' to find these villains
and show them what
we're made of.
[MANDALAY]
Kota. Kota!
I hope you can hear my voice.
Hurry up and come back to camp!
I'm sorry, I can't come to you!
I don't know where you're
always running off to.
Forgive me. Just get
back home, fast!
[MUSCULAR] I came up here
scouting for a nice
vantage point,
and here I find someone
who's not on our list.
By the way, nice hat,
kid. I like it.
Why don't you trade me
for this lame mask, huh?
They made me wear it
'cause I'm new.
Said they couldn't
get a shipment
of the good ones in time.
--[KOTA yelps]
--Ah, well.
[gasps, screams]
[MUSCULAR]
I think you and me should
have some fun up
here, kid. Ready?
[gasps]
[NEWSCASTER 14A]
Water Hose.
Two heroes sharing one name.
But this couple's bright
future was cut short.
Ended by one criminal's
heinous actions.
A truly tragic story.
The villain in question
is still at large,
though police and heroes
are on his trail,
hoping to apprehend him soon.
[KOTA]
It's you.
[NEWSCASTER 14A] The suspect
is extremely dangerous
and has a power-up Quirk.
If you see this face,
contact the police immediately.
Do not approach him.
Additionally, the
suspect sustained
a major injury to his left eye
during his fight
with Water Hose...
Papa! Mama!
[IZUKU coughs]
What are you doing?
Huh. Now you, I recognize.
You were on the list.
[IZUKU] I came up here to
make sure Kota got back safe.
I didn't think I'd actually
run into any villains!
Damn it. That landing
broke my phone.
I didn't tell anyone
where I was going.
Which means, I can't hope for
reinforcements to show up.
It's just me. All alone.
I have to stop
this guy by myself.
But... can I really do that
while protecting Kota
at the same time?
No, I don't have time to think.
I just have to do it. Right now.
With the power I have!
Hey. I promise
everything will be okay.
I'm going to save you, Kota.
[KATSUKI grunts]
Damn it.
There must be some sort of
gas villain out here.
I'm worried about the others
who're still in the forest.
But I don't see that there's
much we can do now.
Hopefully, Ragdoll can
take care of everyone else.
[KATSUKI] Don't tell me
what to do icy--
[KATSUKI gasps]
[KATSUKI]
Crap.
Who's that?
Hey. Which group was
in front of us again?
Tokoyami, I think, and Shoji.
[MOONFISH]
So pretty.
No, have to work. Can't.
But's it's so delicious,
beautiful flesh.
Don't tempt me.
I have a job to do.
No fighting, is that the rule?
You fake heroes only
care about yourselves
and your glory. We'll purge
you from this world.
[MANDALAY] Spinner, even
though you're a villain,
you're still pretty cool.
Totally my type.
Uh--
Are you really
blushing? How cute.
That was a dirty trick to pull.
Don't toy with me, cat.
[gasps]
[yelps]
Over here, my little kitten.
I won't let you use
the same trick twice!
Kenji Hikiishi.
Villain name, Magne.
Wanted for nine counts
of aggravated robbery,
three murders, and
29 attempted murders.
[MAGNE]
Ooh, does that mean I'm famous?
What the hell did you
come here for, criminal?
Tiger. Something's wrong.
I still haven't
heard from Ragdoll.
It isn't like her not to report!
Uh-oh, I wonder
what happened to her.
[MUSCULAR] You really think
you can save this little brat?
That does sound like something
a wannabe hero would say.
Your kind sure likes to
mouth off about justice.
[MUSCULAR] The name's
Midoriya, right? Perfect.
We were told we could take
some initiative and kill you.
But first, a little torment.
Show me your blood.
[IZUKU grunts]
[MUSCULAR]
Whoopsie.
[yells]
Oh, yeah. Hey.
Maybe you can help me out
a little bit first.
Do you know where
a kid named Bakugo
might be around here?
[IZUKU]
Kacchan?
I still have a job
to do, after all.
[IZUKU] Wait, they're
after Kacchan? Why?
I'll take your silence to
mean that you don't know.
Is that right?
Oh, good, then. Play time!
[MUSCULAR laughs]
Yes!
Blood is exactly what
I wanted from you.
What'd you promise?
That everything would be okay?
How's that workin'
out for ya, huh?
Don't just lay there, stupid.
[IZUKU] That muscle Quirk
of his is too powerful.
I need a plan.
If I worry about Kacchan
right now, I'm dead.
I have to focus on the
enemy in front of me!
Smash!
[MUSCULAR]
What? Is that all you've got?
You're fast, but you're not
strong enough to hurt me.
[IZUKU grunts]
[MUSCULAR] My Quirk increases
my speed and strength
so exponentially that
my muscle fibers
can't even be
contained by my skin.
I know I'm bragging a bit.
But I mean, c'mon.
I guess what I'm
trying to say is...
You're just an
inferior version of me!
[MUSCULAR] I can't help
but laugh at you, kid.
You'll really think
you're a hero, don't you?
[MUSCULAR]
How are you gonna save him, huh?
Don't make promises
you can't keep.
Live up to your words or
they don't mean anything.
You're no hero--
you're just a fraud,
and you'll die that way!
Remember Water Hose?
My mom and my dad.
Did you torment
the two of them, too?
Before you killed them?
Huh? Seriously? Those
losers were your parents?
Well then, this must be fate.
The Water Hose heroes--
they're the reason
I have an artificial eye
in my left socket right now.
This is all your fault.
Nothing in the world
is right anymore
and it's because of
crazy people like you!
[MUSCULAR]
Little kids are always so quick
to say it's someone
else's fault.
[gasps]
Don't get the wrong idea.
It's not like I took them out
'cause I was mad
about the eye thing.
I wanted to kill people--
it's as simple as that.
And those two tried to stop me.
What happened was the result
of all of us doing our best.
The real travesty is promising
to do something you
aren't able to do.
That's why your dear old
mommy and daddy died.
Nice try, with the sneak
attack, but I'm ready!
You ruined his life,
and you won't take the blame?
Got you now. Doesn't matter
how quick you are.
But what's your next move?
You gonna punch me with that
puny Quirk of yours again?
It's not a matter of
whether or not I can do it.
[gasps]
[IZUKU] A hero's job
is to risk his life,
to turn his promises
into a reality!
[MUSCULAR]
What?
[IZUKU]
One For All, 100 percent!
[MUSCULAR] Wait. There's
something different about him.
[IZUKU]
Smash!
[screams]
[IZUKU]
Gotcha! Sorry about that!
Thank you for--
[panting]
[KOTA]
Why?
[IZUKU] Let's get back
to camp. It's not far.
[IZUKU]
No way. It can't be.
I was at 100 percent!
The same as All Might's power!
[groans]
Heh. A bit too obvious.
But, hey. Not too bad, Midoriya.
No. Stay away!
[MUSCULAR]
Naw, attacking sounds more fun.
[IZUKU] It's no good.
What am I supposed to do now?
I just need some time to think.
Tell me. Why have you come here?
What does the League
want from us?
Doesn't matter to me,
I'm just glad they finally
let me off the leash.
Long as I get to use my Quirk
all I want, I really don't care.
Remember what
I told you earlier.
We've just been playing around.
Having fun. Until now.
Now, I'm serious!
Recess is over.
I'm coming at you for real.
'Cause truth be told,
you're pretty strong.
I see that now.
Quick. Grab on! Hurry!
[IZUKU] It's like his Quirk
has been supercharged.
It's completely insane.
He really was just
playing around,
toying with me
before he killed me.
Aw, damn. I got too excited.
[KOTA, IZUKU grunt]
[IZUKU]
If we can just get back to camp,
Mr. Aizawa should be there.
Then he can erase
this guy's Quirk.
Yeah, that's it!
I need to get him to
chase after me and Kota.
But...
I'm so tired from the
training today. It won't work!
If I turn my back on
this guy, I'm done for.
I have no choice but to
fight him right here.
Right now!
I have to remember where
I started, how far I've come.
I'll stand my ground.
And I'll make sure Kota is safe!
[IZUKU] Stay back, Kota.
And then, when it's time,
run as fast as you
can back to camp.
You're attacking him again?
You can't do that!
Let's just go! Come on!
Your punch didn't hurt
him earlier, remember?
Besides, both your
arms are busted up.
[IZUKU]
It's going to be fine.
[MUSCULAR cackles]
[IZUKU]
One For All, 100 percent!
I'm coming for you!
[IZUKU]
Detroit...
...Smash!
[MUSCULAR]
Aw. What's wrong?
That was even
weaker than before!
Okay. It'll all be okay.
I will not let him get
past me! Kota, Run!
[grunts]
Go now!
Still looking
after him. Oh, man.
You're somethin' else,
aren't you?
[IZUKU]
Shut up, dammit!
But, why?
[MUSCULAR]
Show me... your blood!
[ALL MIGHT]
A real hero...
...will always find a way
for justice to be served!
[IZUKU]
Please, forgive me, Mom.
I tried my best.
I'm sorry...
...All Might.
I'm gonna crush you.
What the--? Is that water?
[KOTA]
Stop. Let him go!
[IZUKU]
Ko... ta?
Hold on, there, 'kay?
I'll kill you after
I'm done with--
[MUSCULAR]
Crap. I was distracted.
[IZUKU]
I won't let you hurt Kota.
Damn it. How are
you getting stronger?
You won't lay a hand on him!
[IZUKU]
One for All, 1,000,000 percent!
Delaware... Detroit Smash!
[IZUKU yells]
[KOTA]
Why?
[MANDALAY]
Kota.
Your mom and dad,
the Water Hose heroes.
It's true that they ended up
leaving you behind
in this world.
But, they saved so many lives
through their sacrifice,
you'll see that someday.
Why did you risk your life?
[MANDALAY]
You'll meet someone,
and then you'll understand
why we do this.
Even though... you don't
know me at all.
Why did you try to save me?
Someone who will
risk their life.
Someone who'll be...
[KOTA]
...a hero.
My hero.
[IZUKU]
Now, the preview!
Somehow, I survived a fierce
battle against Muscular
and kept Kota safe.
But the League of Villains
is still attacking us,
and it turns out,
they're targeting Kacchan!
What do they want with him?
Whatever the case, I have
to find him before they do!
Next time:
"Drive it Home, Iron Fist!!!"
Criminals, beware! Tetsutetsu is
going to use his awesome power
to strike in the
name of justice!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!