[ALL MIGHT]
I must remember where I started.
[ALL MIGHT] I wanna make a
world where everyone smiles
and lives together happily.
For that to happen,
people need a symbol.
[NANA]
A symbol?
[ALL MIGHT]
A Symbol of Peace.
The reason crime is
on the rise everywhere
is because citizens have
no one to believe in.
They need to rely on someone.
That's why I wanna
be the pillar
that gives people hope.
Huh. So that's what drives
you to become a hero
even though you're Quirkless.
[ALL MIGHT]
Yes.
[NANA chuckles]
Toshinori Yagi. S'that right?
Those are some pretty
funny ideas ya got.
You're kinda crazy.
[sirens blaring]
[TODOROKI]
Midoriya. Are you four safe?
[IZUKU]
Yeah. How about you guys?
No one saw you?
I don't think so.
We're on the street,
blending in with the crowd now.
Some pros are here
helping people evacuate.
[IZUKU] Good. We're stopped
in front of the station.
Luckily, we missed
that last shockwave.
Our rescue totally worked.
A rescue?! That's not
what happened back there.
You idiots just happened
to be my best escape route.
You're welcome!
I had to get out
of there so All Might
could destroy that guy.
[IZUKU] He's right.
We would've been in the way.
The smart thing to do
was leave him to it.
Gran Torino can help him out.
[IZUKU] We made the
right decision. Didn't we?
This is what you
would've wanted.
Right, All Might?
[ALL FOR ONE]
You have so much in common
with Nana Shimura,
the utter waste of
a human who passed
One For All on to you.
[NANA]
Be proud, Toshinori.
You went down a long, hard
road to obtain this power.
Of course it's gonna take
a lot of work to master it.
My master was a true hero.
Keep her name out
of your filthy mouth.
[ALL FOR ONE]
A woman with no skill,
and grand ideas she
couldn't live up to.
How embarrassing for me,
the creator of One For All,
to see her inherit the power.
And the way she died
was so pathetic.
Shall I tell you all about it?
Enough!
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL MIGHT]
Gran Torino!
[ALL FOR ONE coughing]
[ALL FOR ONE]
You're in the way.
It's the same as the last time.
Toshinori. Calm down!
Six years ago,
you got distracted,
and that's how he escaped.
And put a hole in your stomach.
That's always been
your weakness.
Don't let him get
under your skin!
Yes, sir.
[GRAN TORINO]
His Quirks and fighting style
are completely different
than they were.
You won't be able
to stop him head on.
Use your wits!
Can you still fight?
It's do-or-die. You must
go past your limit!
I will.
The scene below's straight
out of a nightmare.
Half of Camino Ward
was demolished
in a single, horrifying instant.
All Might is currently
fighting the villain
who appears to have
caused the blast.
I can't believe it.
How is one person so powerful?
He's destroyed the city and
is more than holding his own
against the Symbol of Peace.
[NEZU]
Our plan has been thwarted!
It's up to you now, All Might!
[WOMAN 49A]
You see this? Jeez.
Oh, crap, that looks terrible!
[CITIZEN 49A]
All Might looks kind of beat up.
[CITIZEN 49B] Whoa. I've never
seen him like this!
[TEENAGER 49A]
Where's Camino Ward again?
[CITIZEN 49H] Daddy may not
have work tomorrow, hon.
[CHILD 49A]
Really?
[CITIZEN 49C] Why aren't
the other heroes helping?
[CITIZEN 49D] Man, these villain
attacks are getting insane.
[CITIZEN 49E] That, or the
heroes are just slackin' off.
[CITIZEN 49F]
They're gettin' soft!
I mean, I hate to say it,
but it's true.
[CITIZEN 49G] It looks bad,
sure, but All Might's the best.
He'll win in the end, right?
[ALL MIGHT coughing]
[ALL FOR ONE]
I find myself conflicted.
Tomura has been
the one to chip away
at society's trust in heroes,
so is it fair that I should
land the final blow?
You know, All Might,
as much as you hate me,
I think I probably
loathe you more.
I killed your master, sure.
But you took away
so much from me,
everything I tried to build.
That's why I want you to suffer
until your last breath,
and die broken and disgraced,
for all the world to see.
Big one's coming!
Dodge and counter!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Not everyone's so fast.
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
[GRAN TORINO]
Watch out!
[ALL FOR ONE] I will obliterate
everything you've protected.
[GRAN TORINO grunts, yelps]
[ALL FOR ONE] First to go
will be your self-respect,
and ridiculous public image.
Show the world how
pitiful you really are,
"Symbol of Peace."
[CITIZENS murmuring]
[CROWD MAN 49B]
He looks like a skeleton.
[REPORTER 49A]
Uh. What's wrong?
Is-Is everyone else seeing this?
It looks like All Might's
been shrunk somehow!
[ALL MIGHT] Most of the world
has never heard of this fight.
I did everything I could to
keep the injury under wraps.
I'm supposed to be the guy
who's always smiling, right?
I'm the Symbol of Peace.
People everywhere have to
think that I'm never afraid.
[IZUKU]
All Might... Your secret!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Hollow cheeks and sunken eyes.
To think that you're
their greatest hero.
Now the adoring public
knows your true form.
Try not to be ashamed.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Your move.
[ALL MIGHT] Even as my body
rots and grows frail.
Even as you expose
my weakened state.
In my heart, I remain
the Symbol of Peace.
And there's nothing you
can do to take that from me.
[ALL FOR ONE]
Is that so? Ah, well.
I'd forgotten how
stubborn you are.
I guess I'll just give up.
Oh!
But there is one thing you
might be interested to know.
Tomura Shigaraki? My apprentice?
He's Nana Shimura's grandson.
[ALL FOR ONE] I kept wondering
what would annihilate
your golden heart.
And so I found Tomura.
Groomed him to hate you,
and watched you smile so proudly
as you beat your
master's descendant.
That's a lie.
[ALL FOR ONE] Oh, come now.
You know it's the truth.
That is clearly
something I would do.
Huh! Well, well.
That's strange, All Might.
Where is your smile now?
[ALL FOR ONE cackles]
[NANA]
If you have to you save someone,
that means they've
probably gone through
something terrifying.
They'll be frightened.
Remember that real heroes
don't just save lives.
They save a person's heart, too.
You know what I think?
No matter how scared you are,
you should smile to show
that things'll be okay.
In this world,
the ones always smiling are the
ones who are the strongest!
You bastard.
[ALL FOR ONE laughs]
How very entertaining.
I think I've taken
a piece of you after all.
[ALL MIGHT]
He's my master's grandchild...
My god, what would she say
if she knew how we turned out?
[ALL MIGHT screams]
[WOMAN 49AA]
Don't lose.
Keep going, All Might!
We need you!
He's frozen!
This is bad.
Beat this guy.
No way.
What next?
Is he gonna lose?
[CROWD MAN 49D] He's always
be able to win before,
so he can do it again, right?
[CROWD WOMAN 49C] Yeah, even if
he looks totally different,
he's still the same All Might.
[CROWD MAN 49E] Come on,
All Might, you can do it!
[CROWD shouting]
[CROWD MAN 49F]
Beat this sucker!
[CROWD MAN 49G]
Show 'im what you can do!
Win this!
Beat him!
[BOTH]
Come on, All Might!
[ALL MIGHT]
Fear not, miss.
I'm not done yet.
You were right.
A hero has so much
to protect in this world.
Which is why I will defeat you!
[NANA]
Toshinori, when you think
you can't go on anymore,
look inside.
[ALL MIGHT]
I must remember...
[NANA] Remember why it is
you clench your fist.
[ALL MIGHT]
...where I started.
Your past. Remember
where you came from.
Keeping your origin
in mind will help
push you past your limit.
My origin. Of course.
I wanna make a world
where everyone smiles
and lives together happily.
[GRAN TORINO]
How many times is he gonna
have to counter such
a large-scale attack?
He shoulda been outta
power a long time ago.
Muscles are only forming
on his right arm.
This distorted form
can't be good.
[gasps]
[ALL FOR ONE]
There it is.
That's the last of your
strength, isn't it, All Might?
A wounded hero is a most
frightening animal.
Do you know that even
now I sometimes dream
of you charging at me
with your entrails
strewn across the ground.
[GRAN TORINO]
Oh, no.
[ALL FOR ONE] You have, what,
two or three punches left?
[ENDEAVOR]
Are you serious?
What the hell's going on
with that weak little body?
[EDGESHOT]
Looks like we made it in time.
[TSUKAUCHI] We've got
the Nomu under control.
You have to help All Might.
[EDGESHOT]
Tsukauchi must've expected this.
He feared for his friend's life.
[ALL FOR ONE] Hm. Those Nomu
weren't particularly strong,
but I'm still impressed you
handled them so quickly.
As expected from the man
who clawed his way
to the number-two spot.
Dammit, All Might.
[ENDEAVOR] I did everything
I could to get ahead of you.
But the harder I worked,
the more obvious it became
just how much of a widening
gap separated the two of us.
The stronger you got,
the angrier I became.
[ENDEAVOR] Stand up and show
them why you're better!
[ALL MIGHT]
Endeavor.
[ALL FOR ONE]
If the only reason you're here
is to cheer him on, I'd
prefer you to remain silent.
[EDGESHOT]
Think again, madman.
We're here to assist.
[KAMUI WOODS]
That's our job as heroes!
You did your best, Mt. Lady.
All of you came.
[TIGER]
Of course we did.
We can't do much, but if we
can just help a little...
...then we have
fulfilled our duty.
Thank you.
[TIGER]
You have to stop him, All Might.
This personification of evil.
Pros and citizens everywhere
are praying for your victory.
No matter what you look like,
you're still everyone's
number-one hero!
[GRAN TORINO]
Toshinori Yagi?
[NANA] He's an interesting
guy. A little crazy.
For instance, he thinks
that crime hasn't gone down
because the citizens don't
have anyone to rely on.
That the world
needs some kind of
"pillar of support." And he says
that's what he's going
to become one day.
[GRAN TORINO]
Toshinori. You are a pillar.
One that must not be broken.
You are the number-one hero.
[GRAN TORINO]
You can hear them, can't you?
Even after everything
he's done so far.
The entire world continues
to cheer you on.
Their united voices
cry out for your victory!
That includes your students,
whose admiration
knows no bounds.
Who aspire with their whole
hearts to be like you.
[CITIZENS]
All Might!
[ALL FOR ONE]
Hmph. How pointless.
[EDGESHOT yelps]
[ALL MIGHT grunting]
[ALL FOR ONE]
Let's stop dwelling on heroism
and start focusing on reality.
Springlike Limbs.
Kinetic Booster times four.
Strength Enhancer times three.
Multiplier. Hypertrophy.
Rivets. Air Walk.
Spearlike Bones.
The shockwaves until now
were simply to wear you out.
I knew it would take much
more than that to kill you.
In order to put
you down for good,
I'll punch you with the
ultimate combination of Quirks
I have stored up
within me right now.
This will end you.
[ALL FOR ONE]
I wasn't certain until
we exchanged blows
tonight, All Might.
But now I am.
One For All no longer
dwells within you.
What you're attacking me with
is just a lingering ghost.
The embers that remain from
what you've already passed on.
And that fire gets weaker
every time you use it.
Even now, it's a feeble spark
about to put itself out.
Izuku Midoriya!
[ALL MIGHT gasps]
[ALL FOR ONE] He's the child
you passed One For All on to,
isn't he? I bet he came
here without your asking.
You have no control
over him, do you?
It sounds as though you'll die
full of regrets, All Might.
As a hero and as a teacher!
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[ALL FOR ONE]
Impact Recoil!
[ALL MIGHT]
You're right. As his teacher,
I should have reprimanded
him for coming here.
I failed.
Which is why I have
to make it up to him.
[ALL FOR ONE]
I see.
The weak embers inside
you are resisting.
Trying to rekindle some
of your former strength.
A desperate attempt to rage
against the inevitable,
and fulfill your duty.
But it's not enough.
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[gasps]
[NANA] When you think you
can't go on anymore, remember.
[ALL MIGHT] I'll beat you,
not because I'm a symbol,
but because I will do
as my master did for me.
Until I finish training
Young Midoriya...
[ALL MIGHT]
Until he's ready...
[ALL FOR ONE] It's embarrassing
how much you're resisting.
[ALL MIGHT]
...I won't...
[ALL FOR ONE]
Perhaps I was wrong.
[ALL MIGHT]
I refuse to die!
[GRAN TORINO] You won't be
able to stop him head on.
Use your wits!
[GRAN TORINO]
At the last moment,
he transferred the power
in his right arm to his left.
He used his right arm as bait!
But...
[ALL FOR ONE] A clever trick.
That's so unlike you.
Still weak, though.
[ALL FOR ONE gasps]
[ALL MIGHT]
That's because I didn't
put my back into it that time!
[NANA] This power has been
passed on from hero to hero.
Each praying that it will bring
joy and peace to humanity.
That One For All will
give the world hope.
And now it is your turn.
Do your best, Toshinori.
[growls]
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[ALL MIGHT]
Goodbye, All For One.
United States of Smash!
[ALL MIGHT]
Goodbye, One For All.
[gasps]
[sobs]
--[REPORTER 49A] All Might wins!
--[CITIZENS cheer]
[REPORTER 49A]
The villain's not moving!
He's knocked out!
All Might stands victorious!
He's saved us yet again!
[EDGESHOT]
He shouldn't push himself.
Let him be. He's still working.
This is his last job.
[GRAN TORINO] A final act as
the Symbol of Justice and Peace,
and the number-one hero.
[CITIZENS chanting] All Might!
All Might! All Might! All Might!
Two people. Below the rubble.
And more there!
The heroes began rescue
operations during
All Might's fight, but the scope
of the damage is staggering.
Authorities are estimating
a large number of casualties.
The villain who
caused this is-- Oh!
There!
He's being led into
the maiden right now!
Meanwhile, All Might and other
heroes remain on high alert!
[CROWD MAN 49H] Sorry, the
trains aren't running right now!
[TENYA]
We can't go anywhere.
I wish we could find
Todoroki and Yaoyorozu.
Let's just head that way.
We should let the heroes
know we got Bakugo
in case they're lookin' for him.
Good idea.
[ALL MIGHT]
Now.
[IZUKU gasps]
[ALL MIGHT]
Now. It's your turn.
[CITIZENS gasp, murmur]
That's our hero!
He couldn't be more amazing!
Yeah!
[CITIZENS cheer]
[IZUKU] All Might's message
was only a few words long.
As far as most people
were concerned,
it was meant for
other criminals.
A warning that the
Symbol of Peace endured.
But, to me, it meant
the opposite.
[IZUKU]
He'd used up everything.
And now it was left to me.
[IZUKU]
Now, the preview!
All Might finally
defeated All For One,
his greatest nemesis.
But he's not able
to fight anymore.
The number-one hero
and Symbol of Peace
has retired.
I'll be the one to
take over One for All
and the mantle he's
leaving behind!
Next time:
"End of the Beginning,
Beginning of the End."
Mom, no matter how
worried you are,
I'll still become a hero!
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!