[music playing]
[DISTANT GRUNTS, SHOUTS, AND
CLASHING WEAPONS]
‐Are you all right?
‐What are they, immortal?
[music playing]
‐Not good.
Hurry, everyone fall back.
‐Giant sand barrier.
‐About time, Gaara.
‐So, who are we dealing with?
‐We’re not sure.
They all just came
up out of the sea
when we set up
camp for the night.
‐They’re not getting away!
‐Hang on!
Don’t go out there.
[snapping and shouts]
‐We’re at a complete
disadvantage at sea,
and it’s pitch black out there.
‐Fire off a few flares.
‐Right.
‐Huh?
What on earth is that?
I’ve never seen a boat
like it in my life.
[creaking]
‐No!
[music playing]
‐[giggling]
‐Oh.
‐Oh yeah, we got him!
‐Hey, this is important.
Be quiet.
[clattering]
[squeaking]
[music playing]
‐We did it! [laughing gleefully]
‐Well now, you’re
friendly, aren’t you, boy?
‐His hind legs have
got black fur on them.
Yep.
It looks like we
bagged our animal.
You gonna cage him?
‐[laughing] I can’t believe this
fur ball fell for such a lame
trap.
‐[growling]
‐What is it?
‐Naruto, stop antagonizing him.
‐What do you mean?
What did I do?
Ah!
SHIKAMARU: You knucklehead.
Don’t let him get away.
‐If you lose him,
I’ll beat [inaudible].
‐Ah!
‐[sigh]
‐Idiot!
‐[dazed laughter]
NARUTO: Man, I can’t
believe someone
would pay us to find
this rabid little run.
He’s like the meanest cat ever.
‐Quit you complaining, will you?
A mission’s a mission.
Besides, the hard part’s over.
Now we just have to
deliver him to his owner.
‐And he’s not a cat, Naruto.
Haven’t you ever
seen a ferret before?
Just look at him.
He’s totally adorable.
‐Whatever.
Let’s just dump him, and
get back to the leaf village
already.
‐So if we cross this bridge‐‐
‐All right!
‐Naruto, slow down!
‐Come on, guys.
Let’s get this mission
over with‐‐ whoa!
[whimpering]
‐What are you doing, you idiot?
It says right over there that
this bridge is dangerous!
And I don’t care about you.
What do we do if something
happens to the ferret?
NARUTO: Oh, man, Sakura.
That’s cold.
SAKURA: Shikamaru?
Is something wrong?
SHIKAMARU: Maybe.
The village that hired us,
it’s just beyond that field.
I don’t know.
Something feels kind
of strange here.
‐Why?
What do you mean?
SHIKAMARU: It’s the
middle of the day,
and there’s not a
single person in sight.
SAKURA: Now that
you mention it‐‐
‐Well, what do you know?
Ah!
‐OK, let’s start
running recon tactics.
I’ll take the woods to the west.
You two head over the
opposite end, all right?
NARUTO AND SAKURA: Got it.
‐I hope this doesn’t
turn out to be a drag.
‐Just beyond those trees.
‐[squeaking]
‐Hey, keep a lid on it, will ya?
‐I wonder what’s got
him all riled up.
‐Huh?
What the?
Guys,
SAKURA: [screaming]
‐Hey, what’s going on?
‐Who the heck are you guys?
Huh?
[screaming]
‐Naruto!
‐We’ve got company over here.
SHIKAMARU: On my way.
‐What are they?
You want to play?
Oh yeah!
[music playing]
‐[grunting]
Uzumaki Barrage!
Heh!
Huh?
So you’re the leader then, huh?
Hiya!
Why you!
Ah!
[grunting]
[panting]
SAKURA: [screaming]
‐Sakura!
‐Naruto!
You jerk, put me down right now!
‐You coward.
Let her go, pal,
just you and me.
‐Hmm.
‐I mean it.
I won’t ask again!
‐Shadow Possession Jutsu.
Hah.
Naruto, leave that one to me.
‐Right.
I don’t care who you guys are.
I’m taking you all out at once.
Multi Shadow Clone!
Let’s go!
[music playing]
‐Rasengan!
‐Rising Thunder!
‐Oh!
[music playing]
‐Whoa!
‐Ah!
‐Naruto!
‐This is bad.
‐Naruto.
[distant explosions]
‐Sakura, this way!
[music playing]
‐[gasp]
‐What the heck is that?
[distant voices]
‐Wha?
Ah!
Hmm?
‐Now that you’re finally up,
try not to move around too much.
I didn’t think you’d wake
up for another two or three
days at least.
‐So who are you, gramps?
‐I’m the elder of this caravan.
The name’s Kahiko.
‐Caravan?
‐That’s right, young one.
The villages refer to
us as the nomadic tribe.
We travel near and far,
as the seasons dictate.
Have for centuries.
h yeah?
‐Fortune was smiling
on you, my boy.
If we hadn’t been passing
by the moment we did,
the river would’ve watched
the two of you away.
‐Hey!
It’s you!
[growling]
‐Hey, he’s regained
consciousness as well.
You, you jerk!
What the hell was that
all about back there?
What did I ever do to you?
‐[whimpering]
‐Well now, it’s good to see
you’ve got your energy back,
son.
‐[screaming]
‐Let’s not have any
fighting, shall we?
When traveling together, our
differences are put aside.
‐Yeah, but gramps,
this guy‐‐ huh?
Huh?
You again?
Why I oughtta‐‐
[music playing]
‐‐[chuckling] My
recovery time is crazy.
Most of my injuries
heal in a day.
‐Must be very convenient.
Your new friend over there
is pretty impressive as well.
Well, he’s healing almost
as quickly as you are.
‐Huh?
No kidding.
Hmm.
‐Ah, goodness.
I certainly envy your
youth, gentlemen.
‐Careful, old man.
That critter’s about as
vicious as they come.
‐‐[laughing] I know
Nerugui is a shy one.
But I’ve never known
him to bite anybody.
‐Wait, are you saying
you know this cat?
‐Indeedy I do.
It’s the first
time he’s ever been
separated from the caravan.
Isn’t that right, Nerugui?
I’m sure you’re glad to be back
safe and sound with us again,
eh?
‐Heh.
‐We all cherish him.
He’s our little treasure.
The truth, is I’m
actually the one
who hired the village hidden
in the leaves to find him.
‐No fooling.
So it was you, huh?
‐We move around all year.
We’re never in one place.
So we asked that he
be delivered to one
of the villages on the border.
How did you all wind up here.
‐Our team got ambushed by him.
KAHIKO: Hey, Nerugui.
‐Look at that.
Not so shy now, is he, gramps.
‐Well, how do you like that?
SAKURA: This area is
crawling with those guys.
SHIKAMARU: Yeah.
‐Who are they?
You got any ideas?
‐Beats me.
OK, Sakura.
You keep looking around,
and see if can find Naruto.
If he turns up, radio in.
‐I’m on it.
What about you?
‐I need to check something out.
[music playing]
MASTER HAIDO: Come, my boy.
[crickets chirping]
‐Master Haido.
NARUTO: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold up a second.
You’re saying this
caravan has always
been traveling like this?
‐That’s right.
The land we all hail
from was destroyed.
And we’ve been
traveling ever since.
‐Your whole country
was destroyed?
‐It’s an ancient story,
passed down through our clan.
According to the legend, we
had a beautiful homeland.
But it was completely wiped out.
‐Whoa.
What happened.
‐Supposedly, there was a great
catastrophe of some sort.
Our home was lost.
And the people of our clan
were scattered to the wind.
From then on, we became a
tribe of wandering nomads.
KAHIKO: There were even some
of us who crossed the ocean.
‐The ocean?
‐Actually, Nerugui is
evidence of all this.
He lived among our ancestors
in the days of yore.
This little ferret
is living proof
that we had a country long ago.
‐[laughing] Ah, go on, gramps.
If that were true, he’d have
been alive a pretty long time
now, huh?
‐Oh, it’s true, though.
He’s no spring chicken.
‐Uh huh.
‐Nerugui is even older than
grandpa, if you can believe it.
‐Come on, give me
a break, will ya?
‐Hard to wrap your
brain around, isn’t it?
Our people have been looking
after him for generations now.
‐Hmm.
‐That’s why Nerugui doesn’t take
to anyone outside the caravan.
He stays amongst his own.
‐[squeak]
‐Oh!
‐Uh.
‐At least I thought he did.
‐That’s the second
time he’s done that.
‐Nerugui, aww.
Are you OK?
What’s the matter?
‐Hey, are you ready
to talk yet, or what?
How come you attacked us out
of nowhere like that, huh?
Hey, I’m talking to you.
‐Uh, that power you
were using, what is it?
‐Huh?
What power?
You mean my chakra?
‐Chakra?
TEMUJIN (VOICEOVER): It’s true.
I don’t sense any
gelel from him.
‐Come on.
Let’s go.
I want answers here.
Just who the heck are you, pal?
‐I’m here to build a utopia.
‐Uh, utopia?
‐That’s a very interesting
power you have.
You should come with me.
‐Eh?
Look, I don’t understand what
you’re talking about here.
‐Just think about it.
‐Argh.
When pigs fly, I will.
Why would I go
anywhere with you?
I’m asking you why
you attacked me.
Do I have to tie you up,
and force you to‐‐ whoa!
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?
Help!
[giggling]
‐Uh, mm.
Oh!
‐[gasp]
[crash]
[scream]
‐Anya, what happened?
[interposing voices]
FEMALE SPEAKER: Are you hurt?
MALE SPEAKER: Hey, hey, you OK?
‐What were you thinking?
Oh, I can’t thank you enough.
‐Hmm?
‐I’m through here.
My debt to these
people has been repaid.
‐Oh?
‐Aw, come on.
There’s no end to them in sight.
They’re everywhere.
[dramatic music playing]
SHIKAMARU: It doesn’t look
like they’re conscious.
‐I don’t know how much longer
I can watch these brats,
you know?
‐Easy now.
Watch your temper, dear.
Lay off, will you?
‐Once the Stone of Gelel
is in our possession,
we’ll have no
further use for them.
Just have a little
bit of patience.
FEMALE SPEAKER: Well, we
could sure use its power now.
‐[gasp]
‐Huh?
NARUTO: [screaming] he
cut and ran, that jerk.
If you think I’m going
to let you get away,
you’re out of your
bleeding‐‐ huh?
‐How on earth could
this have happened?
‐What’s up?
Is there a problem here, gramps?
‐I can’t find Nerugui.
He vanished.
‐Does that mean he’s run
of with what’s his face?
‐Yes.
What was the point of
spending all that money
on the unparalleled shinobi
of the Leaf Village?
‐Hold on a sec.
We delivered him,
just as you requested.
‐Quiet!
I told you to deliver
him to the next village.
Besides, I just finished
telling you Nerugui is gone.
‐Look, be reasonable.
‐‐[sigh] If I knew this
was going to happen,
I would have hired those
legendary sand ninja from
the get go.
‐Argh.
OK.
I get it already!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
Someone’s been here.
Could it be‐‐
‐So I finally
caught up with you.
All right.
Just give me back the cat.
‐[hissing]
‐Why you‐‐ huh?
What is all this?
Who are you, anyway?
‐My name is Temujin.
Come.
I’ll introduce you
to Master Haido.
‐Uh, hey, hold on.
Wait up, will ya?
So who’s this Master Haido guy?
‐He’s my lord, and a
man of great strength.
You’ll see when you meet him.
‐Huh?
So what’s the deal with all
these big goons everywhere?
You friends with them?
‐They’re just soldiers who
are dedicated to the cause.
All of my comrades are‐‐
[ding]
‐I have returned, my lord.
‐Ah, Temujin.
Good to have you back.
You’re the one, aren’t you?
Temujin let me know
he was bringing you.
He tells me you possess
quite an interesting power.
‐That’s correct.
Allow me to show you.
‐What is this?
‐Stand and fight!
‐No, Temujin!
Stop this unnecessary fighting.
‐My lord.
‐Resorting to violence is
never the answer, my son.
Naruto, we have
traveled far and wide,
trying to create a utopia.
NARUTO: Wh‐‐ what’s a utopia?
HAIDO: Well, to put
it simply, a world
where there are no longer
any wars, and the weak
are never oppressed.
NARUTO: A world without any war?
‐Yes.
The land we’ve
traveled here from
is a far off continent,
ravaged by conflict.
War is an ugly thing,
a source of boundless
sorrow, bestowing naught
but misfortune on man.
Temujin knows this all too well.
He lost his homeland to strife.
‐So does that mean
you’re all alone, then?
‐No.
I have Master Haido.
‐When he was a boy,
Temujin was left
to survive in the ruins
of his shattered village.
I made a decision
when I found him.
I wanted to protect the
weak in any way I could,
to create a world where fighting
was no longer necessary.
That is our utopia.
It is my only dream.
For the sake of that dream,
I’ve traveled the world,
gathering believers.
It has taken time for us to
make it as far as we have.
And it grieves me to
admit, many noble people
have been sacrificed
along the way.
Tell me, Naruto, would
you like to join us?
We could use someone like you.
Together, we can make
the world a better place.
‐Hmm.
It’s not like it isn’t tempting.
But I’m going to
be Hokage someday.
So‐‐
‐Hokage?
‐Yeah.
That’s what we call the
top ninja in my village.
‐I see.
‐Tell you what, though.
I can’t go with you.
But I’ll do my best to keep
everyone happy back home.
How’s that sound?
‐Well, I’m sure we’ll
both do the best we can.
‐Uh.
‐Goodness me.
Who is your little friend here?
‐My apologies.
I spent some time
with a caravan.
And he took a bit
of a shine to me.
‐A caravan, you say?
My, isn’t that interesting.
[hissing and growling]
‐A caravan.
FEMALE SPEAKER (ON
INTERCOM): Master Haido, we
have a problem.
‐Tell me, what’s wrong?
FEMALE SPEAKER (ON
INTERCOM): The fleet
we sent to the land of
wind was annihilated.
‐The land of wind?
‐I’m on my way.
‐Hey.
Hold up.
What’s going on?
[ding]
‐We’ve no other choice.
Fugai.
FEMALE SPEAKER (ON
INTERCOM): Yes, my lord.
‐There’s somewhere I need
you to go for me, my child.
‐What the heck happened here?
Huh?
‐Hold up.
What is this all about?
Well?
[gasp]
KANKURO: Naruto, what
are you doing here?
‐Huh?
Kankuro?
‐You got it.
Thought you could
sneak up on us, huh?
You shouldn’t underestimate
the shinobi of the hidden sand.
‐I don’t get it.
What happened out here.
‐Oh man.
You didn’t know about this?
These people invaded the land
of wind from out of nowhere.
‐Are you serious?
We’ve had quite a few casualties
trying to stop their rampage.
Whole villages were
wiped out in the battle.
‐Tell me, is that the truth?
‐Noble sacrifices
for the greater good.
‐Oh, please.
What you say and do are
two different things.
‐Look, sorry for butting in.
But I’m going to
take him out now.
‐Stay out of this!
He’s my opponent.
You got that?
KANKURO: What?
‐Those who stand in our
way will be eliminated.
‐Yeah, whatever.
Huh?
‐Temujin, you know you’re not
supposed to be here, you idiot.
Your primary duty is scouting.
‐This one is just
acting as a lookout.
There’s another
unit waiting nearby.
‐Yes, but‐‐
‐What’s get you so worked up?
‐We’re splitting, before
things get ugly around here.
‐Not so fast.
‐Nice of you to finally show up.
‐Oh, all right.
I guess we can play.
‐You fellas should
learn when to walk away.
‐This is crazy.
What on earth are you thinking?
‐I already told you, didn’t I?
If one hopes to
achieve a higher goal,
certain sacrifices must be made.
‐What?
Look around you.
Aren’t these your
friends lying here?
TEMUJIN: They are.
And like me, they were
willing to give everything
to bring about our
dream of utopia.
‐Spare me, will you?
If they are your friends,
you sure don’t act like it.
‐Heh.
You’re pretty good at dodging.
All you got is darkness, huh?
I am not impressed.
[wailing]
FEMALE SPEAKER
(VOICEOVER): Hear the cries
of those who stood
against us, doomed
to wander the land of death.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): She
uses [inaudible] Jutsu.
FEMALE SPEAKER (VOICEOVER):
Prepare yourself
for an eternity of anguish.
‐I hope you know what
you’re getting into.
‐Oh, I can handle it.
Come.
‐Sure.
Tornado Lightning!
‐Sand Shower!
‐What’s the matter?
Don’t you want to play?
‐[grunting]
‐[cackling]
I’ll see you on the other side.
‐[inaudible].
‐Thunder Saber!
Huh.
That was easy.
Huh?
[gasp]
‐Sand Burial.
‐There’s no use in struggling.
FEMALE SPEAKER: [cackling]
So that’s your game, is it?
‐Have to admit,
this girl’s no joke.
‐‐[laughing] I’m not
through with you yet.
‐So you can increase
your strength
by altering the
structure of your body.
‐You got it.
Let’s finish this.
Useless.
That’s not going to work
against my plasma ball.
Take that!
Pathetic.
Well, that takes care of that.
[gasp]
GAARA: First time
facing a shinobi?
‐What?
You’re still alive?
‐Billowing Sand Tsunami.
[explosions]
‐‐[laughing] all of your
sand is worthless against
my electricity, kid.
‐Provided you still have it.
‐You’re no match for me!
‐Think so, huh?
Sand Lightning Rod!
gasp]
[wailing]
‐Giant Sand Barrier!
FEMALE SPEAKER: [screaming]
‐OH, I don’t believe it.
Huh?
KANKURO: Hah.
Found you.
‐[gasp]
‐You’re not leaving, are you?
‐You should have walked when
you had the chance, sweetie.
‐Heh.
‐What happened to her?
Nice trick.
‐[laughing]
‐Hey, we’re not through yet.
‐Ah!
Now what?
‐Temujin, withdraw.
‐Not a chance!
You’re not going anywhere.
‐Let go of me, you idiot.
‐Hah, forget it.
Huh?
What the?
‐Losing my grip.
‐Huh?
What the heck are you
even doing up here?
[screaming]
‐Where’s the stone?
‐What makes you think I
know anything about that?
‐Are you playing dumb with me?
‐[groaning and spluttering]
‐What?
‐Shadow possession complete.
‐[grunting]
‐Take it easy now.
Are you all right?
‐We saw your signal
flare pretty flashy.
‐Who are you?
‐By the way, don’t bother
calling for your goon squad.
I don’t think they can make it.
Useless bunch of
lugs, aren’t they?
‐[growling]
‐What in the?
‐[howling]
‐Huh?
What was that?
A wolf?
‐[coughing]
‐Catch your breath.
‐Thank you.
‐Hey, grandpa, what is
this Stone of Gelel?
‐Gelel?
‐Look, I know it’s got
nothing to do with us.
I’m just a little
curious, is all.
They were talking about it
back in their stronghold.
‐So you think they need it to
achieve their goal, somehow?
‐The stone could very
well be their goal.
Well, anyway, it’s
no skin off our backs
if you don’t want to tell us.
We’ve got a friend
around here to look for.
Come on, Sakura.
‐Yeah, but‐‐
‐Just a moment.
Is this friend you
speak of Naruto?
‐Wait a minute.
Are you telling us
that you’ve seen him?
‐Please help me.
I have no one else to turn to.
If we don’t hurry, something
terrible is going to happen.
‐What are you talking about?
‐[sigh]
‐If they were your friends‐‐
‐You don’t know
anything about me.
‐‐[whimpering] What
do we do, Temujin?
Everyone’s dead.
‐Don’t cry.
‐Yeah, but‐‐
‐A tragedy.
You two are the only
survivors of this village.
In a true utopian society,
this sort of misfortune
would never happen.
‐A utopia?
‐It’s a world free of war, a
dream I’ve devoted my life to.
Amazing, isn’t it?
If I can only gather enough
of the Stone of Gelel,
I’ll be able to
this world entirely
of war‐‐ ugly, sorrowful war.
MALE SPEAKER
(VOICEOVER): It’s amazing
how you’ve incorporated
the Stone of Gelel.
‐Think so?
‐Are you serious?
course it is.
I’m really, really proud of you.
‐I appreciate it.
‐I wish that I
could be like you.
I only have power
when I climb in there.
But our hearts are still one.
We’re friends.
Nothing can change that.
We mustn’t let other villages
suffer like ours did.
We give our all for utopia.
[beeps and static]
‐What’s wrong?
FEMALE SPEAKER (ON RADIO):
You blind little fool!
That caravan you were
traipsing around with
had info on the Stone of Gelel!
‐What?
‐So this lead, then,
has the trail gone cold?
‐I had Temujin head
out after them.
Well done my dear.
The day when he has failed
to meet my expectations
has not yet come.
All thanks to that power
he wields, fortunately.
‐What?
‐We’ve been waiting for ya.
What’s up?
NARUTO: You idiot!
Do you realize what you’ve
done to those people?
‐I have nothing
further to say to you.
‐Oh yeah?
‐Hold on, now Naruto.
You let me talk
to him for a bit.
‐It never occurred
to me that you’d
know anything about the Stones.
‐Never mind that.
Why are you after them?
‐They’re essential to our cause.
‐You don’t know the horror
those Stones carry with them.
They must never be returned to
this world, you understand me?
‐Save your lecture
for someone else.
‐[gasp]
‐It’s just as I thought.
hat is that light?
KAHIKO: This is a
crystal of Gelel,
the source of all life energy.
‐I know more about the
Stones than anybody.
‐That explains your
power of recovery.
How exactly did you come by it?
‐It was given to me,
by my Master Haido.
‐I see.
And is that the only Stone
you have in your possession?
‐Hmm?
‐That’s peculiar.
If you’re a descendant
of our clan’s ancestors
who traveled across the
sea, why wouldn’t you
know that, I wonder.
Was the Book of Gelel lost then?
‐What in the world
are you talking about?
‐In the days of old, it was
only the royal family members
that let our clan who were able
to fuse the Stones of Gelel
with the flesh of the body.
Naruto, I spoke to you
of this the other day,
how some of our
people took to the sea
after our country was lost.
‐Huh.
Now that you mention it.
‐According to legend, it
was the royal family itself
that left, taking
the book of Gelel,
and the last of the remaining
stone across the waves.
Temujin, wasn’t it?
You haven’t come
to a new land, boy.
You’re returning home.
You and I are of
the same people,
both descended
from a single clan.
We know little of
the Stones’ origin.
But it seems that
in very early times,
a mysterious vein of
mineral was discovered.
Our ancestors were
able to refine it
in a crystallized form.
And they name the mineral Gelel.
A vast empire was
built on this content,
with the precious stone
as its foundation.
Wells never ran dry.
Livestock multiplied overnight.
And trees continually
bore fruit.
It’s even said that
they looked for ways
to stop all life from aging.
‐First I ever heard of it.
‐This was a very long time ago.
But as is often the case,
great however brought with it
unimaginable catastrophe.
People fought and quarrelled
shamelessly over the Stones.
And in the end, their power
was used to wage a massive war.
Mountain and earth
were ripped asunder,
until eventually the back
obliterated the empire
altogether.
SAKURA: How awful.
KAHIKO: Only a handful
of the young survived.
Our ancestors sealed
away the coveted mineral,
deep underground,
and vowed never
to revive the Stone again.
‐If it was really
that dangerous,
why didn’t they try to
get rid of it for good?
‐Because the Stones
can only be destroyed
by those of royal blood.
But with the royal family
lost to us forever,
we can only watch over
them, guarding their secret
with every generation.
The legends have
slowly faded away.
And one day, the
story of our past
will just die out altogether.
‐Die out?
Fade away?
Hearing all that, my resolve
is stronger than ever before.
Nothing will stop me from
getting those Stones now.
‐Why you.
Weren’t you even listening?
‐Power is power, nothing more.
The only thing that matters
is who’s wielding it.
‐The Stone is too dangerous
to the world of men.
It must never be woken
from its slumber.
‐Whatever power it
may hold, Master Haido
will use it justly.
War breeds only suffering.
But without someone
guiding us from above,
there can be no
end to bloodshed.
This is what my master teaches.
The truth of his words
is etched into my heart.
In the fog of war, my village
fell prey to brigands.
Those of us who
survived were orphaned.
But Master Haido took us in.
I want to grant him his wish,
to free this world of war.
My comrades and I feel the same.
No sacrifice is too great.
That is my only dream.
And I need the Stone of
Gelel to bring it about!
‐Huh!
‐He was faking us out
from the beginning.
‐No way!
‐All right.
You’re going to tell me where
the mines of Gelel are hidden.
‐I will not.
ou leave me no choice.
‐Ah!
‐That dirty‐‐ come on!
We’ve got to go after him.
‐Emina, do you think
you could tell us
where the mines of
Gelel are located.
‐I would if I could But
only my grandfather knows.
‐We could sure use a
ninja hound right now.
Huh.
‐Hey, you think?
‐This is it.
I’m sorry for treating you
so roughly, little one.
Now go on.
[ping]
‐Well?
‐Everything’s ready.
‐Wonderful.
‐Let’s say we get
moving then, shall we?
‐Does he even know
where he’s going?
‐Doesn’t matter.
He’s the only shot we have.
‐Hey, an exit!
‐Whoa!
‐Naruto, do something.
‐Huh?
[grunting]
[squeak]
‐There he is!
‐You know this place.
Lead the way.
‐Follow me.
NARUTO: Hey!
You let gramps go!
‐Stay out of this!
‐What in the world is that?
‐Master Haido, the mines
of Gelel lie below.
‐Thank you, son.
I’m in your debt.
Because of all your
sacrifice, our utopia
is finally near at hand.
TEMUJIN: Yes, my lord.
‐Very well then, everyone.
Let’s get going.
SHIKAMARU: Hold on a second.
Sorry.
I hate to be rude, a and all.
But I had a couple of questions.
‐Master Haido.
‐Easy Kamira.
I’m fine.
A bit unsettling, though.
Good manners are such a rarity.
He’s not a friend of
yours, now is he, Naruto?
I’m a little puzzled, my boy.
We made a promise to
one another, did we not?
We swore that we do our best to
make this world a better place.
‐Whatever, pal.
You’re the only one who should
be explaining himself here.
‐What do you plan to do
once you get the stone?
What’s your end game?
‐What’ll I do?
Why I’m going to create a
utopia, a world without war,
where the weak will be free
from the weight of oppression.
‐It’s funny, though, you know.
Because it looks
like you’re doing
the exact opposite of that.
‐All that I do this in
the name of true justice.
‐And why attack an
innocent caravan?
Is that justice?
‐It couldn’t be avoided.
My children and I have
made great sacrifices,
you see‐‐ noble sacrifices,
necessary to finally create
a world free of war.
NARUTO: Hey, old man,
people gave their lives
for your dream.
Do you even care?
But in your book, they were
just a means to an end.
Is that all your fallen
comrades are to you now?
‐This is what it means
to accomplish something.
‐So you don’t mind that
these noble sacrifices
are your friends.
‐That’s right.
‐I’ve accepted it, as the
rest of my brethren have done.
‐It can’t be helped.
We share a common vision.
Each of us dreams
of a world where
peace is finally possible.
‐Then they’re not really
your friends, are they?
‐And why is that?
‐I don’t know how
to put it exactly,
but, but a friend, a friend
is someone that matters.
They should be the
most precious thing
in the whole world to you!
For the longest
time, I was alone.
But I made friends.
And that loneliness went away.
That’s why I dream
of becoming Hokage‐‐
so I can protect all the
people who are important to me.
This utopia you talk
about, who’s it even for?
Dreams that don’t
include your friends
are nothing but garbage.
That’s why I’m putting
an end to all this!
‐Huh?
‐Old man, what do you
think you’re doing?
‐It’s time this thing was
eliminated from the world one
and for all, even if
it means our doom!
‐Oh no, [inaudible].
‐Eliminate the Stone?
That cannot be possible.
Dah!
He must know something.
‐Ah!
‐Hurry.
I’ll catch up to you.
‐Master Haido, return
to the stronghold.
‐We’ll never make it in time.
Bring the stronghold with you.
‐Hey.
Huh?
‐Sorry, little boy.
But you’re going to
have to deal with me.
‐Hmm?
‐You’ve got some nerve.
‐Naruto, go!
‐Right!
Here I come!
‐Where are we?
‐According to the stories of
old, the chamber of sealing.
Everything is just
as the legend says.
I’ve never been here
in my life, and yet
it all feels familiar somehow.
The images you see were
left here by our ancestors
when they sealed
this place away.
They depict the terrible
power of the Stone of Gelel.
‐What’s this?
‐A portrait of despair, perhaps.
The empire was
reduced to nothing,
like the picture
you see before you.
‐How promising.
Our search hasn’t been in vain.
It’s all we hoped it would be.
‐And you’re telling me you’re
not horrified by all this?
That ghastly picture proves it.
This kind of power breeds only
destruction, and nothing more.
‐People will always fight,
with or without this power.
We, we shall be wielding
it for the greater good.
‐Is that so?
The Stone is further down.
But our journey ends right here!
‐Haha!
Stupid little girl.
Your meddling will
get you killed!
‐Ah!
‐Yah!
‐Oh, come on.
What’s the matter, boy.
Show me what you got.
What happened to that
shadow technique of yours?
‐Darn it.
She’s all over the place.
I can’t get a lock.
What do I do.
Think.
Huh?
‐How’d you like that?
Uh‐‐
‐Surprise!
‐Ah!
But I blinded her.
How can she be chasing me?
‐‐[cackling] I can
smell your blood.
That’s all I need.
[howling]
‐Huh?
‐[cackling] No use hiding.
[laughing] Where could you be?
Nice knowing ya.
[howling]
[echoes]
‐[moaning]
I’ll kill you!
[screaming]
‐Huh?
‐‐[laughing] You don’t think
this will hold me, do you?
‐You probably shouldn’t move
around too much, you know?
‐[sigh] Huh.
Oh, look.
An escape route.
Just kidding.
Your shadow’s waiting for me
down there, isn’t it, handsome?
[laughing] There’s more than
enough room for me up here.
And your shadow still
can’t reach me, can it?
Muah.
Bye bye.
Hey.
Let me out.
Let me out!
‐Secret Black Move
Iron Maiden Two.
Gotcha.
‐It was just as I
planned, more or less.
You saved my butt.
‐Forget it.
I had a score to settle
with her, anyway.
You know, all these
exploding tags of yours
are going to be a real
pain to get around.
‐Don’t worry.
Most of these are just
regular old pieces of paper.
‐Really?
‐How foolish.
Did you seriously think
you’d surprise me?
‐No, I suppose I didn’t.
But I’ve achieved my
goal all the same.
‐What?
‐Do you know what the
design on this floor is?
It’s an ancient form of
summoning Jutsu, used
to call forth an
immeasurable power.
TEMUJIN: What are
you getting at?
‐Here we breathe our last!
‐I’m not altogether sure
what he was planning there.
But I’m glad I came when I did.
TEMUJIN: Master Haido.
HAIDO: Temujin,
are you all right?
‐Master Haido‐‐ how did you?
‐Oh, I was using this.
‐[gasp]
‐[gasp] That’s a Stone of Gelel.
‐‐[chuckling] It’s
just like in the book.
Amazing, isn’t it?
I can blow things away
without touching them.
‐Are you referring
to the book of Gelel?
‐Sorry.
‐How did it come
into your possession?
‐Ah, it’s funny, actually.
I bought it from a peddler
on the side of the road.
‐That is utterly impossible.
I thought there was
something strange here.
You destroyed this boy’s village
to get the Stone of Gelel,
didn’t you?
‐‐[chuckling] Oh, what is
the cause of all this doubt?
My only goal in life is
to rid this world of war.
How could you even
say such things?
KAHIKO: One who truly
wanted peace would never
seek out the power of Gelel.
‐I desire the ability
to put an end to war.
There’s nothing more
to it than that.
Let’s see now.
Where might those mines be?
‐I can tell how black
your heart is, just
by looking in your eyes.
HAIDO: Hmm.
I don’t even know
where to begin.
Hmm?
Could this really be it?
it must be.
The key that grants access
to the mines of Gelel.
‐No!
Don’t touch it.
That isn’t meant for you!
Nerugui!
Oh, Nerugui.
HAIDO: Oh, there was a
small stone in its mouth.
The poor thing.
Yet another noble sacrifice.
Honestly, those who
stand at the top
have to make such
tough decisions.
‐I’ve had just
about enough of you.
‐Aw, it breaks my heart.
One more sacrifice for
the cause, it seems.
‐Ah!
HAIDO: I can’t control
my power very well yet.
Hmm.
Well, anyway.
What do you think
you’re doing, Temujin?
‐Forgive me, Master.
It’s just, the mines of Gelel
are in our possession now.
If we were to toss this
helpless old man aside‐‐
HAIDO: That’s not what I meant.
‐Huh?
‐Don’t stand in the
way of my target
‐Uh, Master Haido.
‐You heard me, lad.
You’re in the way.
Step aside.
‐What the heck is
going on around here?
‐Ah, this is
becoming so tiresome.
‐[gasp]
‐Temujin, what are you
just standing there for?
Are you going to
kill them or not?
‐What the‐‐
‐You call this a
noble sacrifice?
HAIDO: What’s wrong?
Take care of them
like you always do.
Hurry up!
‐No.
I’ve had enough.
I can’t.
HAIDO: Ah, Temujin, I’m
very disappointed in you.
You’re an inferior individual,
no different from your parents.
‐Huh?
‐You really are a
pathetic little brat.
‐But that’s impossible.
‐[cackling] That’s right.
It was me!
Such blindness, latching
on to the very man
who murdered your parents.
What an adorable
little pawn you are.
‐[gasp]
‐But now that I know where the
stones are, I hardly need you
anymore, do I?
‐Mas‐ter Haido.
‐Die, you good for
nothing mongrel.
NARUTO: No!
‐Ugh!
‐Temujin!
‐Now the entire world will
fall to it’s knees before me.
‐Temujin!
‐Naruto!
I beg of you, you have to
figure out a way to stop him.
‐Argh.
‐Worthless trash.
‐Where do you
think you’re going?
We’re not done.
‐Everywhere I look,
there’s garbage.
‐[grunting] Shadow Clone Jutsu!
TEMUJIN (VOICEOVER):
I‐‐ we were‐‐
‐[laughing]
‐What on earth have we done?
‐Vol‐‐
‐Too slow!
‐What?
Ah!
‐Why don’t you give
up already, boy?
‐Not a chance.
‐[laughing impetuously] Ha!
‐Augh!
[coughing] Come on.
Are you just going to,
going to just give up here?
Wasn’t it your dream to make
some sort of utopia of this
world?
Yah!
[distant punches]
NARUTO: [inaudible].
‐Heh.
I gotcha.
TEMUJIN (VOICEOVER):
His strength,
where does it come from?
‐Huh?
‐Well, that certainly
stings a bit.
‐What?
‐Huh?
‐This is‐‐
‐[laughing evilly] Wonderful!
‐It’s the mine of Gelel!
HAIDO: My wounds,
they are healing.
[laughing] So much power!
‐Temujin, come on.
Get up.
I can’t handle
this guy on my own.
‐You mean you still‐‐
‐Of course.
I don’t ever back down.
Now get on your feet, and help.
‐Hmm?
I’ve heard enough of
this pathetic blathering.
Let me deliver you
to your utopia.
‐Naruto!
‐Temujin!
‐Everyone.
What have I‐‐ what have I done?
‐Foolish children.
I told them not to interfere.
But I guess they’re at that age.
Well, no matter.
I’ll take care of
you myself, then.
‐Temujin!
‐[grunting] I, I’m going to‐‐
‐Let’s go, Temujin!
‐[panting] [roaring]
[music playing]
‐Let’s put an end to this.
Time for you to
join your ancestors.
‐Temujin.
‐It’s as you said, Naruto.
There’s no use for a dream
that sacrifices your friends.
‐‐[laughing] You’re
finished here.
‐Ah!
‐[inaudible] brat!
I doubt if you could
even touch me, boy.
Would you just die already?
‐Go to hell!
This is for Temujin!
‐Hah.
That’s not going to work on me.
What?
Oh no!
‐[groaning and gurgling]
[rumbling]
KAHIKO: Oh no.
That’s‐‐ that’s the
mine, the source of life.
‐Hey, uh, gramps, do you
think you could fill us in,
or something here?
‐When the key that unlocks the
mine was destroyed just now,
the seal was broken.
‐So what does that
actually mean?
‐It means the mines of Gelel
are spiraling out of control.
‐How are they?
‐They’re still
breathing, thankfully.
But they’re not
regaining consciousness.
‐I see.
[rumbling]
‐Ah!
‐What’s going on?
‐I don’t know.
But whatever it is, it
sure doesn’t sound good.
TEMUJIN: What happens when
it goes out of control?
‐I don’t know.
But considering the size of
the empire that was lost,
I wouldn’t be surprised if it
took out half of the continent.
‐Are you kidding me?
‐Just tell us how to stop it.
‐There’s nothing that we can do.
It’s too late to stop it now.
‐Then what were
you doing before?
You know of a way, don’t you?
What was that summoning circle?
‐There’s no bringing
it under control again.
Although there is a way in which
the mines can be destroyed.
‐So tell me!
KAHIKO: Place your
hand at the center.
This is an ancient
means of summoning,
bound by the royal
blood of our clan.
NARUTO: Yeah, but what
are you going to summon?
KAHIKO: A space time rift.
NARUTO: Wh‐what
the heck is that?
KAHIKO: A boundless gulf will
engulf everything around it.
But it will spawn from the
point the Jutsu is executed.
The person who performs the
ritual would be sacrificed,
never to return.
‐I understand.
‐Forget about it.
There’s no way I’d let anyo‐‐
‐Naruto!
TEMUJIN: This is how I’ll
atone for what I’ve done.
KAHIKO: You?
‐Take care of everyone.
[dramatic music playing]
‐Temujin!
‐How many are left?
‐Not a lot, just two
or three of them.
‐All right, then.
Naruto, you better get
out of there in one piece.
[music playing]
‐No way.
‐Come, my boy.
‐That’s enough.
‐Whatever you do,
just don’t let go.
‐Look, forget about me.
You’re going to die.
‐Will you shut up?
I don’t want to hear it.
Ah!
‐No.
That’s enough.
You’ll get pulled in.
‐Forget about it.
I’m not going to let you
die like this, you hear me?
I, I’ve lost too
many friends already.
And I don’t plan on losing you!
‐Naruto, where’s Naruto?
He’s still not in there, is he?
Oh!
‐Huh?
Sakura, wait!
Darn it!
‐Naruto!
Where are you?
Ah!
‐Uh?
‐Whoa!
‐What is this?
‐What the heck is
going on around here?
KAHIKO: It was even more
powerful than the legends tell!
‐Is sthat gramps?
It
‐Are you OK?
‐I was tossed like a rag
doll, and practically crushed.
I was sure my time had come.
‐So gramps, what happened?
‐The wastelands have
given birth to new life.
This happened because a
fraction of the stone’s power
was able to escape when
it was just destroyed.
That’s why I’m as fit
as a fiddle again.
[squeak]
‐Woo!
There’s my Nerugui!
‐What is this?
[gasp]
‐Temujin.
SHIKANOBU: Where‐ where am I?
I’m still alive?
I see these ruins.
Huh?
This is‐‐ It wasn’t a
picture of despair after all.
[music playing]
‐Temujin’s part of your clan.
He should have stayed here.
‐He’s heading toward
warring lands.
‐Well, what can you do?
That’s the path he’s chosen.
Besides, our destiny split
apart a long time ago.
His soul isn’t
tied to this land.
His home lies elsewhere.
‐It’s going to be tough.
‐At least he won’t be alone.
He said that this
time, for sure, he
wants to create a
world free of war
with the help of
his friends. [sigh]
‐Something wrong?
‐[moaning] So much for loyalty.
I’ve been dumped.
[music playing]
‐Oh yeah.
Where’s Naruto?
‐Well, I’ve been
looking for him.
But he’s nowhere around.
[music playing]