Thank you so much for everything, sir.
For all of this, how does thirty thousand sound?
I wanna close out the account.
Uh.
Everyone, take your seats.
Huh?
We have a new student that'll be joining our class today.
What do you want?
You're in luck, Shoya. I heard it's a girl.
So what?
Like I care.
Okay, class. This is Shoko.
Would you like to introduce yourself?
Hmm?
Uh.
Holy crap!
Hi, nice to meet you.
Yoo-hoo! Hey there, new girl.
Do you know how to speak Japanese?
Come on, Naoka.
That's not very nice.
Oh, uh, I...
Ah.
Do you have a nickname?
How do you like that?
Come on, take it!
Your nickname is Sho?
Huh?
Oh, just like Shoya.
Hey, we have another Sho now.
Two Shos is pretty cool.
What? No, it's not!
I'm gonna pants you!
Alright, make sure to write this down.
The exercises are on page 20-25 and on page 32.
All of this will be on your next quiz.
Give me your notebook, okay?
Look at the diagram.
At the center is the fulcrum.
Mm.
The fulcrum is both the point of
rest and the support for the lever.
It is the crux of any motion.
The placement of the fulcrum determines how
far the levered object will move, which forces...
Not yet, Shoko.
Huh?
You... you're coming in too early.
Watch me, okay?
Don't start singing till I start.
O-okay, from the top.
Guess we won't be winning the choir contest.
Hm?
You can say that again.
And this is for acting like a moron!
Okay, go easy on me!
Alright, I surrender!
I'm so sick of this.
He talks so fast. I can't write everything down.
Well, I can give you my notes if you want.
You're a lifesaver.
Hm?
Huh?
But I didn't do anything wrong,
and so I will never say I'm sorry.
Why are you reading so slow?
You sound like you're five.
Fine, enough of that. Who's next?
Four-eyes.
Shoko.
Mm.
Start reading from here.
There was an awkward silence.
His mother looked at him and waited.
She shook her head and said,
You need to stop being so stubborn all the time.
"'You have no intention of apologizing.'"
That's good. Shoya, you're next.
You gotta be kidding.
That isn't funny. Sit down, Shoya.
Okay.
Can you believe it?
Uh, no thanks.
Yeah, let's go.
Uh, we're leaving, Shoko.
You know something?
We're all sick of you and your notebook.
It's getting pretty old pretty fast.
What do you want?
Can we be friends?
Uh.
What?
You're such a freak!
Good morning, everyone. I'm Miss Kita, the DHH liason.
Do you all know what sign language is?
Okay.
It's kind of like
using your hands to talk instead of your voice.
Isn't that neat?
Alright then.
Sign, huh?
Since we wanna make it easier to communicate with Shoko,
every single morning, we're going to
spend three minutes of class learning to sign.
Miss Kita.
Yes?
Why can't we just write in her notebook?
It would be easier for Shoko if everyone
just learned a little sign language.
Yeah?
Well, it would be easier for me
if I could just write stuff down.
'Scuse me.
I'll do it. I can learn how to sign.
So, your name...
Mi-yo-ko.
Whoa, so it's...
Mi-yo-ko?
Goody-two-shoes loser.
He's so cool.
Oh, my gosh, mine too!
Hey, he'll be on the show next week.
Let's watch it together.
Gross, did she get dressed in the dark?
I can't believe you said that.
So based on the author's previous work...
By looking at the results of the experiment...
Keisuke, you draw over there.
Shoko is a...
What do you think you're doing?
You really shouldn't do that.
Almost done...
Don't you think you're going a bit too far?
Nope, but I can go even further.
You can be such a jerk.
Come on!
I'm not that bad.
Check out my masterpiece.
Hm?
Oh, my gosh! Who would write such a thing?
Some people!
Here, I'll just erase that for you
so you don't have to see it.
There, no need to thank me.
I said no need to thank me.
Let's go, guys.
During the Jomon period...
Huh?
Cut it out, Shoya.
Or would you rather have detention?
No, sir. Sorry.
Okay, where did I leave off?
Right.
The typical Jomon house was a pit dwelling with a...
That was startling, wasn't it?
Hey. Hey, Shoko.
What do we have here?
Does that mean you can actually hear?
Oh, you know what? I was wondering the same thing.
Can I see 'em for a sec?
Naoka!
What are those things? Toss 'em over!
Is that earwax?
That is so gross!
Huh?
Shoko, are you okay?
Oh, no she's bleeding!
What do we do?
You went too far, man.
Mr. Four-Eyes is such an asshole.
Oh, great. Now what?
You're in our way.
What is she even doing?
Get lost.
Sorry?
You're not sorry, you're just pathetic!
Hey, what are you doing? Stop touching me!
Check it out.
I think she wants to hold your hand.
You like it. You're blushing.
No, I'm not!
Come on, let's go.
Huh?
Oh, my god. Talk about crazy.
Ew, that water is gross!
Yeah.
We'll see you tomorrow, Shoya.
Later.
Listen up, everyone.
There's something very important
I'd like to talk to you about.
As you can see, Shoko Nishimiya is absent today.
Yesterday, the school received a
telephone call from Shoko's mother.
In the past five months, eight of Shoko's
hearing aids have been broken or gone missing.
Hearing aids are very expensive.
Her mother believes Shoko is being bullied.
If any of you have seen Shoko
being harassed or abused at school,
I need you to come forward and
tell us who has been doing it.
If no one comes forward,
I'd hate to have to bring your parents into this.
This is a very serious matter,
and the school does not take bullying lightly.
Shoya.
Stand up.
We all know that it's you.
I told you to stand up!
Yes, sir.
Now then, Naoka.
You sit right next to him. What have you seen?
Well, uh... It's kinda true.
He does tease her a little.
Like, he makes fun of her.
What?
And Kazuki?
Yeah, totally.
I kept telling him to knock it off,
but Shoya won't listen to anyone.
What? Wait!
Th-that's not fair!
Y-you were making fun of her too, Kazuki!
And it's not just the boys. The girls were doing it too.
I swear.
It's true,
especially Naoka and Miki!
That's mean.
I would never do anything like that.
How could you?
How could you say something like that?
No, I-I...
What the...?
Yes, I see.
I'm very sorry for any trouble he caused.
Yes, of course.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Shoya! Come back here, I'm talking to you.
Shoya!
I just got off the phone with the school.
W-wait a minute.
Why are you so wet?
Leave me alone.
I jumped in the river like always.
Freeze, mister!
Have you been causing trouble at school?
I wouldn't, Mom.
Then why did I get a call from
your teacher this afternoon?
Okay, fine, it's true!
Huh?
Get cleaned up.
We are going over to Shoko's right now.
Uh.
Hm.
Come on, Sho. Let's go home.
You're gonna try to be nicer from now on.
' Kay?
Huh?
All of these so-called great men
were going through their own struggles.
Huh?
Hey, what the heck is she doing?
Hey, what are you doing at my desk?
Don't you dare touch my stuff, you freak!
There's that look again.
Don't try to act all sweet and innocent!
What is it?
If you wanna say something, then spit it out!
All you do is just stand there
with that stupid look on your face.
Don't you ever get mad?
Well? Then do something!
What the hell is wrong with you?
I can't believe you bit me!
I'm mad at you!
I'm doing the best I can!
What are you even saying?
Get off!
I can't even understand you!
I hate her. She's so weird.
Shoko Nishimiya has transferred to another school.
Moving on.
Now, who was in charge of the class journal yesterday?
Well, whoever it was forgot to hand it in.
Will everyone just check their
bags to see if they have it?
Oh, look, it's Shoko. How are you doin'?
Shoko.
Uh, hello. Do you remember me?
We were in elementary school together.
I'm Shoya Ishida.
Oh.
Where are you going? Wait.
Please, come back!
Where'd she go?
Hey!
Hey.
So... I...
I came here to give you this.
I, uh...
You left this behind.
What's that? How do I know sign language?
From a class.
Here you go. It's yours.
I don't even know if you ever wanted to see this again.
I was wondering...
Can me and you, Shoko,
uh... can we be friends?
Is that an opt...
Whoa, what did I just say?
Huh, that's what you were trying to ask me back in school.
I finally understand you.
Don't cry.
Please don't cry, Shoko.
I wanted to ask if we could be friends.
Would that be okay?
Sho-Sho, Sho-Sho.
Sho-Sho, Sho-Sho!
Sho-Sho, wake up!
Time for breakfast!
Okay, Sho, up and at 'em.
Good morning, Maria.
Sho-Sho's awake!
I'm heading out.
Bye-bye, Mommy!
Have a good day, dear.
And breakfast is served.
Thank you for this meal. Mm.
Dig in, big guy.
What's got you so bright and cheery this morning?
Because...
I found this!
Oh.
You've been working so hard at your job,
and you even sold your comics,
your clothes, and your futon.
I am so lucky to have such a thoughtful son.
But tell me, Shoya,
why would you wanna kill yourself?
I just, uh...
I've been going through a lot of crazy stuff lately.
What can I say? I just...
I knew it.
I knew something was going on with you!
Do not even try to deny it!
Your room is clean for a change.
You cancelled your phone service
and everything after April's
been torn off from your calendar!
I can't believe it, it's so morbid.
Promise me you won't go through
with it or I'm torching this.
The 1.7 million yen you earned will go to waste!
Are you listening to a word I'm saying?
Uh, yeah.
Don't do anything crazy, Mom.
Crazy?
You were gonna off yourself!
No, wait!
I'm sorry, Mom. I'm really sorry.
I won't do it again. I swear I won't.
Please don't burn it.
What are you not gonna do?
Be specific!
I promise I'm not going to kill myself.
I swear I won't do it. Please believe me.
Do you mean it?
I swear to you.
Okay.
Then I won't burn this.
Mom, watch out!
Ooh, fire!
Ow, my fingers!
Ah, get me some water!
Oh, smokey!
Yesterday, I was planning to jump off
a really tall bridge and kill myself.
I only went to see Shoko
Nishimiya to wrap up any loose ends.
It was hands-down the greatest test of courage ever.
Well, it was supposed to be anyway.
Can we be friends?
I'm the world's biggest loser!
On the first day of junior high,
Kazuki made sure everyone knew.
You should probably stay away from Shoya Ishida.
He's a bully.
He's so bad, a girl had to switch schools.
Like they always say, what goes around comes around.
I knew I royally screwed up,
and that I needed to pay for being a jerk.
And so, I pushed everyone away.
Alright, everyone.
Make sure to have this translated by next week's class.
Hey, Shoya.
Uh, Miki.
Have you had a chance to hand in your math notebook yet?
Oh, sorry. I forgot.
That's okay.
Just try to hand it in soon, alright?
Sorry.
No problem.
Wanna go sit in the courtyard?
Shoya never hangs out with anyone.
What a loser.
Didn't you hear about him? Everyone knows.
No way, dude!
Hey, check it out. He's looking at us again.
Wonder if he gets lonely being by himself all the time.
What a total freak.
Why does he bother living?
Oh, hey. I got their new album.
You wanna check it out?
Yeah, since you like them, I don't anymore.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, right.
I've seen that head before.
Who is he?
Uh.
It doesn't matter.
Should I go and see Shoko again?
She said she feeds the koi bread.
But I can't just show up there.
Not after everything I've done.
Should I go and apologize for making her cry?
She did say she's there every Tuesday.
Or is it too creepy?
Huh?
Hey, Mom. I'm home.
Hi, Sho.
You scared the crap out of me. What's up?
Uh, I... I'm sorry.
For burning all your hard-earned money.
I didn't mean to.
Uh...
But then again, you only earned
that money so you could kill yourself.
So I don't want it anyway.
Sorry, Mom. I'll earn it back.
I know you will!
But I don't want you to worry too much about it.
In the meantime, how 'bout some dinner?
Who's hungry?
Ooh, ooh, I'm hungry!
Tuesday.
Hey, let me borrow your bike.
Who, me?
Huh? What do you need my bicycle for?
That kid I saw at lunch.
I forgot something at home so
I need your bike to get it.
What?
But I don't even know you.
Why can't you just use your own bike?
I'm asking you because I don't have one.
No, please don't.
Give it up, fatso.
Wait, stop.
I'm being robbed! Somebody help me!
Anybody out there!
Why won't anyone help me?
Shut up!
God, you're annoying.
Just let go of the damn bike already!
Hey, uh...
What?
Do you wanna borrow mine? It's over there.
Yeah? Thanks man.
You're a godsend.
Of course he stole it.
And today's Tuesday.
Of all days.
So is that a sign that I should just leave her alone?
It's not like I can't just walk there,
but it's like I'm being told not to go.
I need a good reason.
Huh?
Something real.
So it doesn't look like I'm trying too hard.
Half off fluffy new bread.
This is it!
Is Shoko Nishimiya here?
She's not here.
She's right there.
Not her.
There's nobody here named Shoko.
Who are you anyway?
I mean, are you actually a friend of hers?
Thought so.
Nothing to worry about.
There was a rat in the hallway.
A really gross one.
Don't worry. He won't be back.
Can we be friends?
Huh? What the...?
Oh, found him!
Hey, you! Over here!
Look, check it out. I found your bike.
This is yours, isn't it?
What perfect timing!
Oh, it's a good thing you had your address on it.
That's great.
But where did you find it?
That jerk dumped it in a rice field.
Man, it took me forever to find it.
Thank goodness I did.
And I found you, too.
Is something wrong?
What? Nothing.
Tell me. What's your name, anyway?
But, you don't already know?
Tomohiro Nagatsuka. I sit behind you.
Right, I knew that.
It's really good bread. You wanna split it with me?
Shoya!
Hey there, Shoya.
Good morning.
Uh, morning.
Hey, Shoya.
Do you wanna hang out with me after school today?
I mean, since we're friends now.
Shoya, over here!
I saved you a seat!
What's troubling you, Yasho?
Huh? It's nothing.
Who's Yasho?
It's your nickname.
Shows that we're close.
Oh, cool.
Well, so tell me what's troubling you?
You know you can tell me anything.
That's what best friends are for.
Hey, do you mind if I ask you something?
What does it mean to become someone's friend?
Like, is there some sort of
friendship process you go through?
Or like, do you need any specific qualifications?
'Ey, Yasho.
Give me ya hand, 'kay?
'Ey, 'ey.
Now you and I is friends.
It can be as simple as that, see.
Friendship don't gotta do with no rules or qualifications,
'cause it's about something deeper.
A bond. And ya just can't break that.
Capiche?
She's not here.
She's right there.
She's not.
Listen, I think maybe... Shoko's my girlfriend, okay?
Oh, well, that sucks.
Uh, not for me personally,
because I brought her all this bread.
But... I-I didn't know that Shoko was into younger guys.
I mean, nothing against you. I
just never would have guessed.
Can you at least give her the bread?
It's really good.
Listen.
If you're just here to make yourself
feel better, you might as well leave.
If you'll excuse me, goodbye.
Listen, boy!
What's your problem?
My friend here just wants to see Miss Shoko.
'Kay?
Where'd you come from?
So stop being so stubborn and go get her!
Seriously, what are you even doing here?
Ugh!
I followed you. Friends have each other's backs.
The shitty stalker has his own shitty stalker.
Makes you two a load of crap.
What? What was that?
What did you say?!
Okay, let's all chill out.
I called out your bullshit,
which makes you a piece of shit.
That doesn't sound good.
What's going on out there?
I'll teach you some respect!
Sounds like Yuzuru.
Wash your mouth out with soap!
Would you please calm down?
Oh, my.
Seriously, man. Don't worry about it.
Let's just get out of here.
Oh, hello.
Aren't you the nice boy from the other day?
It wasn't me.
It must have been someone else.
Sorry, buddy. You're on your own!
Hey, take that!
Hey, they're gone!
Great.
He got to see her after all.
Nice, smooth.
What are you doing? You spying on Shoko and Yasho?
Hand it over. I wanna see.
Man, Yasho sure does talk with his hands a lot.
It's called sign language, dumbass.
What?
Oh, wow.
I'm tellin' ya. My man's got real skills.
Do you understand sign?
Tell me what they're saying!
Who was that loser you were with?
I have never seen him before in my life.
He was disgusting!
Shut up, liar!
Alright, fine.
Hm.
Don't fall over, be careful.
The truth is,
I wasn't sure if it was okay to come see you.
For the past two weeks,
I've been wondering whether you
and I could be considered friends.
In order to see you,
I felt like I needed a good reason.
And finally, I found one.
Wow, what a great guy.
I'm glad you did.
I was thinking the exact same thing.
It's funny, isn't it?
Uh, so anyway, uh...
I brought you some bread to feed the fish.
Do you enjoy feeding the fish?
Duh, she can't hear me.
Huh?
Oh, uh, wait.
Uh, now that I think about it, you
really don't wanna read that stuff.
Ah!
Wait, what are you doing?
She fell in!
No way!
What happened? Is Yasho okay?
Hey, talk to me boy!
Ah! He went into the river!
Why?
What did you do that for?
What the...?
Over here, Shoko.
Shoko!
I'm really sorry that I dropped that.
Uh.
I don't believe it. What a dummy.
So long, stalker.
Have you seen this?
Seriously, is that really Shoya?
See ya later.
So it's okay.
Uh, hey, Shoya.
We've all been wondering.
Is that you?
Uh, where'd you get that?
Mr. Ishida, report to the faculty office immediately.
I jumped into the river from the Sui Mubushii Bridge,
even though I know it's prohibited.
And I posted a picture on the Internet...
Shoya!
Yeah?
Sorry to ask, but do you think
you could pick up Maria for me?
Well, I'm not supposed to leave
the house while I'm still suspended.
Oh, come on, it'll only take a second.
Uh...
You're a lifesaver. Thanks.
Wait! Ugh, really?
Okay, Maria. It's time to go home now.
Sho-Sho, there's somebody in there!
Uh, wait.
Hey, you.
Wake up. You okay?
Aren't you Shoko Nishimiya's boyfriend?
You're gonna catch a cold like this.
Oh, if it isn't the stalker.
What are you doing?
How'd you end up sleeping here?
Where are your shoes?
Aren't you mad at me?
Uh, 'bout what?
I'm the one who posted the photo of you online.
Oh, so that was you.
Thank goodness. What a relief, seriously.
For reals?
At least I have a pretty good idea of why you did it.
You're not angry?
Why should I be?
I mean, I kind of brought this on myself.
Sho-Sho, I'm hungry!
Okay.
Looks like I've gotta take off.
You should probably be heading home, too.
Crazy. Can't believe you've got a kid.
Ow! She's my sister's. Sheesh.
Whoa, whoa, hey!
Here you go, Yuzuru.
Eat as much as you want, 'kay?
Where'd sis go?
She said she'd be back late.
Well, Maria, do you like it?
I love it!
Oh, great!
What's wrong Yuzuru? Not hungry?
Oh, I know!
Ahh!
Open wide.
Crap.
Hm?
Huh?
What are you doing out here?
I woke up and you were gone.
Here, take it.
No.
Ow, stop it.
What are you doing? Just take it, okay?
Thank you.
Hang on, are you not...?
Wha... hey, ah!
Just as I thought.
Wanna wear these?
They actually used to be mine.
Don't fit anymore.
You can keep 'em.
So, uh... why'd you run away from home?
I got into a fight with Shoko.
Wha... wow.
Well, it's true what they say.
Relationships can get messy sometimes, right?
Yeah, it's 'cause I used Shoko's
shampoo without her permission.
And she told me that she doesn't need me anymore.
Wait, are the two of you living together?
Stop it. I'm just getting more wet.
What's the point of bringing an umbrella then?
Right, but I'm the idiot who
didn't think to bring two of them.
Besides, I'll feel bad for
Shoko if you come back with a cold.
Seriously? Just who do you think you are?
I see through your act.
Huh?
What are we, a couple of strays?
You doing this to feel better about yourself?
Must be extra amusing to you because she's deaf, right?
Yeah, you even went to the trouble to learn how to sign.
Big deal.
You think that suddenly makes you a hero or something?
I still can't stand you.
Uh...
I see.
I guess Shoko told you all about me, huh?
Well, you're right.
I am a horrible person.
The world would probably be better off if I wasn't around.
But still.
I just don't wanna cause Shoko any more pain.
Oh, but that doesn't mean
I'm gonna try and horn in on your turf.
You don't have to worry about that.
That said, it's true.
I guess I am being a bit selfish.
Huh?
This is far enough.
Okay.
By the way...
I'm sorry I didn't tell you this earlier, but uh,
I'm actually Shoko's...
Know what I mean?
Uh...
Younger sister?
Later.
Ah, Ah...
Uh.
Oh, I remember you.
You're Shoko's m...
Let's go.
Ow, Mom, that hurts!
I'm sorry for what I did.
I'm back.
Yuzuru!
Don't hug me.
You'll get all wet.
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
I want to apologize too.
Granny, there any shiso juice left?
I'd like some.
Yuzuru.
I don't want you hanging around that boy.
Tell your sister that, too.
I can decide who to hang out with on my own.
Same with Shoko.
Oh, the Prodigal Son returns.
How are you doing this fine day?
You come back for a rematch?
I'm just returning the umbrella I borrowed.
Oh, that's surprising.
So, our young lad has some manners after all.
Uh, Nagatsuka, that lad's actually a lass.
Huh?
That's Shoko's little sister.
Uh, I knew that the entire time.
I wanted to thank you for
looking out for my homeboy, Yasho.
This is my friend, Nagatsuka.
Hm.
Oh, oh yeah.
I got a new cellphone.
I'm guessing you have a cellphone too, don't you?
So, do you ever text?
Like with you friends? From your new school.
That's great! So, uh, anyone you want to meet?
I-I mean do you need anyone's phone number?
Oh, good! Maybe you'd like to have mine?
What's that?
Sa-ha-ra.
Miyoko? From elementary school?
Hey, Yasho.
Well? So how are you gonna track down this Miyoko chick?
Well, no, that's not exactly true.
But you get straight A's, don't you?
Oh, yeah. That's it.
Yasho?
But, Satoshi, I didn't even...
Uh, Miki?
Hm?
What's up?
Uh, there's something I wanted to ask you.
Do you know how to get in touch with Miyoko Sahara?
She went to the same elementary school as us.
Miyoko?
Sorry, I have no idea.
But I bet the school will have some kind of record.
I think Nao goes to the same school as her.
Taiyo Girls Academy.
Crap. I'm flat broke.
Yasho, my man. I've got your back, bro.
Wow, where'd that come from?
I don't really need that much.
Ah, come on. Let me spot you.
There are travel and meal expenses
and those love motels ain't cheap.
You'll be glad for the extra dough, trust me.
Guys, over here!
Looks like we just made it.
My sister was kind of annoyed that she was being
left out since she was the one who suggested it, so...
would you mind if she tagged along with you?
Huh?
Oh.
Uh... so.
If we start walking from here...
Sho?
Sho!
Huh?
Sorry about that.
Is that you?
It's me, Miyoko!
From school.
Hi! Hey, wait. Is that Shoya?
It's been a long time.
Hasn't it, huh?
And since the, I've been learning sign.
Or trying.
Was that right?
I know I just kinda disappeared on you back then.
Sorry about that.
But I never stopped thinking about you, ever.
Seeing you makes me happy.
I was so surprised.
Mm-hmm.
Really?
So where are you going to school now, Shoko?
Wow. Well your chest has gotten bigger.
Wonder what size you are.
Want me to check?
What's the matter?
Nothing, I just have to go to the bathroom.
Oh, okay then.
Special offer!
Here you go.
Naoka?
Here you are!
Please come and visit us.
Special offer!
Come on, just give it a try.
Meow-Meow Club.
Huh? Hm.
Oh, wow. I'd never have the guts to do that.
Guess they're having fun.
Oh.
Maybe I should reunite her with Naoka as well.
Yeah, that may be the worst idea you've ever had.
On second thought, I'll pass.
Here we are.
Shall we?
Meow-Meow Club, here we come.
Good afternoon.
Welcome.
And how long will you be staying with us?
An hour I guess?
Uh, I have a coupon.
Oh, good. Right this way.
Crap, he actually came.
This is not what I imagined.
They're cats. What were you expecting?
Well, have you ever been to a place like this?
What? No, I've never. I came here for you, man.
I wanted to help you reunite with your friend.
And, speaking of old friends,
where is she, anyway?
I wouldn't exactly call this girl a friend.
You wouldn't?
A lot of stuff happened when we were in sixth grade.
To be honest, this whole thing's kinda awkward.
She isn't here.
Wanna take off, then?
A bug!
Oh, what are you doing here?
I came over to play with Maria.
Hey, uh, do you think Shoko would like this?
Uh.
Kitty!
I brought you a present, Shoko!
What happened?
I'm just gonna leave this here.
Naoka?
W-What...?
Go, go!
Hey, what are you doing?
Long time, no see.
Uh, yeah. Long time, no see.
Hm?
Wait a minute. Isn't that the deaf girl?
Yeah.
Still all alone.
Poor thing.
Seriously, Shoya. It really has been way too long.
Let's hang out soon.
Uh, no, I don't think so.
Wow. You really hate me, don't you?
What? No.
I never said that.
You know what, Shoya?
I always thought I should have
made more of an effort to talk to you.
I'm sorry about everything
that happened when we were kids.
But it's not like it was that big of a deal.
Hey, Naoka.
Get off.
Huh? That's a purse from our café.
Where did that deaf freak get it from?
I gave it to her.
Oh, I see.
Later.
Yeah.
Naoka!
Hey there, Shoko. Long time, no see.
So how has life been treating you?
Stop!
That's weird, there's only one of them.
Naoka, what do you think you're doing?
Thought we'd have a game of catch.
Just like when we were kids.
I'm so sorry, Shoko.
No freakin' way.
You gotta be kidding me.
Hold on, wait a minute.
Don't tell me you guys are actually going out.
What? What are you talking about?
We're just friends.
Just friends? That's hilarious!
Are you telling me you are now
besties with the girl you used to bully?
I don't believe it. That's crazy!
Let me guess. Are you trying to make amends?
Not really.
Too funny. What's gotten into you?
Well, I'll leave you to your fake friendship thing.
Hm?
You wanna know what we were talking about?
Uh, nothing. Don't worry about it.
Look, I gotta take off.
See ya.
Yuzuru.
Uh, yeah?
Time to get up!
I'm up. You startled me awake.
Get out of bed. Breakfast is...
Wait!
Before you go. What's up?
Your hair. Today, it's in a ponytail.
Are you, uh...?
Uh, what's with that face?
Uh.
Shoya will love the new 'do.
Huh?
Oh, it's Shoko.
She's wearing a ponytail.
Where you goin', Shoya?
What was that? Where am I going?
To the bakery.
Yuzuru asked me to get some bread to feed the koi.
But she already has some bread!
I bet she only wants some more so she can eat it!
Whoa, slow down a sec.
Wait, just...
Can you sign it?
Is my voice weird?
Yeah.
Oh, I-I'm sorry, I didn't...
Your voice sounds totally okay.
I'm gonna go get some bread.
Be right back.
Whoa.
What are you doing?
A present for me? Wow, thanks.
Can I open it?
Like, right now?
What are these things?
Thank you so much.
I love you.
Huh, what's that? Something about these?
I love you!
Wh... huh?
Uh...
The moon?
Hm.
It is pretty, isn't it?
I-I...
Where are you going?
Oh.
Can I ask you something?
Do you think these look like the moon?
Mm, let's see.
Well, they don't look like the moon.
Hm...
Candy!
Nah.
I'm pretty sure these things aren't candy.
Shoko gave these to me as a present.
I have no idea what they are.
Hm?
Are you okay? What happened?
Ah, you what?!
Oh.
Wow, check out your hair! It's different!
What made you decide to change it?
Do you have a hot date?
Whatever it is, you should keep it like this.
Stop it, you guys. You're making me blush.
I just didn't have any time to do it, that's all.
Well, I think it looks good.
Hey, Miki, I've got a question.
Why did you suddenly change your hair?
Uh, what do you mean?
It's not like I need any particular reason.
Oh.
Girls just like to change things up sometimes, you know?
I see.
Huh? What is it?
The other day, Satoshi told me he thought
you'd be a pretty cool guy to hang out with.
Huh?
Who are you and tell us the nature of your business.
Nice to meet you. Miyoko Sahara.
Hi. Satoshi Mashiba.
Cut it out! Stop doing that over my head!
Miyoko, it feels like it's been a million years.
Hey, is Shoko coming today?
Nah, she has a stomach ache.
Oh, that's weird. I hope she's not avoiding me.
How come?
She was trying to tell me something the other day.
I just could not understand what she was saying.
What exactly did she say to you?
"The moon."
It's an easy enough word,
but her saying it didn't make any sense.
I bet she was so annoyed.
Well, if you really wanna know how she feels
about you, then I suggest you just ask her out.
If she says no, you'll have your answer.
I guess that you're right.
Come on! Let's all go on the big one first!
Now, everyone stick together so we don't get separated.
Why is she acting like our chaperone or something?
Who knows?
Shoya.
Hm?
Who's that over there?
Why is she acting so chummy with Shoko?
Naoka? Why is she here?
Is she like a friend or something?
Uh, yeah. From elementary school.
Hm.
Hey, uh, mind if I sit here?
Not at all, go right ahead.
It might be scary.
Okay, everybody. Are you ready?
Yeah!
Then hold on tight!
Miyoko, so are you, like, cool with Naoka now?
Hm? Oh, sure.
We're actually both in the design department at school.
Nao's got great taste. I've learned a lot from her.
You know, when we were in elementary school,
I was way too scared to ride this.
I was such a coward back then.
But the one day, I looked at it differently.
I was going to wait until after the
ride to decide if it's scary or not.
Can't help feeling a little scared, though.
Huh?
Here we go.
Oh! Oh, no!
Poor Shoko. Your legs are shaking.
Mm, you okay?
Mm.
Hey, that's pretty impressive.
I didn't know you could sign.
You must have worked really hard to learn sign language.
Uh... mm.
Hey! Get your dirty paws off my Yasho.
Who said you could touch him, huh?
Dude, I was just being friendly.
Well, go be friendly with someone else!
Oh, Nagatsuka, you really crack me up.
Yasho is my friend! I've got my eye on you.
You better watch it!
Hey is that your real hair?
Knock it off, will ya?
I'm not joking!
What's so funny?
What is this?
Faster, Satoshi!
They're catching up!
We can do this, Yasho!
Come on, pedal harder!
What is this?
Is it okay?
Am I allowed to have this much fun?
This feels so... familiar.
Ow, ooh.
Great catch, buddy.
Oh, yeah.
It almost feels like... like we're all friends.
Hey, Shoya.
Uh... huh?
I'm hungry. I feel like some takoyaki.
Come with me to get some.
Uh, I'm not... h-hey, wait!
Here you go. One takoyaki.
Huh, thank you.
And Naoka,
you need to learn how to mind your own business.
Kazuki?
Huh?
Shoya, where are you going?
I'll text you later, okay?
Hey, wait up!
Are you mad at me?
No, I'm not.
I'm fine. Yeah.
I just thought maybe you guys could be friends.
You know, like you used to be.
I guess I was hoping once you guys actually
saw each other, everything would be okay.
Don't do me any favors, okay?
Uh.
Wait.
I did the exact same thing.
You and I are more alike than you think, you know?
No, we're not.
Yes, we are.
We're nothing alike.
You know, if Shoko hadn't shown up,
we would all still be friends and be happy.
You don't know that.
Oh, come on, just admit it.
If it wasn't for her,
things wouldn't have gotten
all weird between Miyoko and me.
And then you wouldn't have stopped
being friends with Kazuki, either.
I just wanna go back to the way
things were before she showed up.
Kazuki and I... that was me.
I ruined that all on my own.
Shoya, tell me the truth.
Do you hate me?
Probably.
Fine. Time for a ride on the Ferris wheel!
I'll go see if Shoko wants to come with me.
Hey.
Huh?
Hey, Shoko, you gotta come ride the Ferris wheel with me.
Cut it out, Naoka.
If you guys are going, can you take my camera?
I wanna ride that roller coaster again.
Oh, hi, Yuzuru. Come on in.
Shoya's upstairs in his room.
Whoa.
Got a top-secret video for you.
A video from the Ferris wheel?
Yup.
How'd you get it?
Spying.
What?
I want you to listen to me carefully.
I hate you.
Uh, oh.
Put that thing away.
I'm going to speak slowly so you can understand,
and I'll listen to everything you have to say.
I'll admit that in elementary school,
I had no idea what things were like for you,
but it's not like you tried to
understand what I was going through either.
Know what I mean?
And instead of getting a clue like a normal person,
you just kept giving me that stupid notebook of yours.
You were always being so weird, and you
would apologize all the time for everything.
So I tried a different approach.
I ignored you and blew you off.
That was my way of telling you
that I didn't wanna hang out with you.
But nope, you just kept coming around
with your stupid book and your stupid signs.
You're so clueless.
Then you had to go run crying to the grown-ups.
You got Shoya in trouble.
And that's how he ended up losing
every single one of his friends.
You pretty much ruined everything for everyone.
You get that, right?
I'm sorry.
God, you still don't get it.
I'm not looking for another apology from you.
We were both going through a lot,
and I don't think either of us
could have done anything differently.
But still,
it's not like I wanna be your new best friend or anything.
I mean, I still hate you a lot,
and I'm pretty sure you hate me too, right?
So, why don't we stop pretending
we're something we're not, okay?
Let's shake on it.
From one hater to another.
But you're wrong.
I don't hate you.
I-I hate myself.
What did you say?
What did you say?!
Well? What are you gonna do?
You gonna say sorry again?
It's been five years and you haven't changed a bit.
You still have no intention of being real with me.
What do you think?
Oh, it's uh...
All I want...
is for Shoko to like herself.
Are you sure it was Naoka?
Yeah, it was her.
Is there really a lot of bad blood between her and Shoko?
Uh, why do you ask?
Miki said something serious went down at your old school.
Shoko's hearing is really bad.
I mean, she can barely hear anything, right?
Yeah.
It just occurred to me, maybe that's why she
kept getting bullied all the time, you know?
You'd have to be a major douche bag.
Who bullies a deaf kid?
What's wrong with people, right?
What are you saying?
Wait, you think I'm spreading rumors
about what happened in elementary school?
Shh, will you keep it down? The whole school can hear you.
I really wanted to believe that
you had actually changed, Shoya.
But you are still the same awful
person you were in elementary school!
You okay, Yasho?
Can you just please calm down a second?
Hey, guys, what's going on?
Remember when I told you Shoko was bullied?
Well, it was Shoya! He was the one who used to bully her!
How can you say that, Miki?
Yasho would never do that.
Why would I make up something like that?
But you used to make fun of her too, Miki.
I never, ever said anything horrible behind Shoko's back.
What? You picked on Shoko?
Yeah, it was him!
He was the one who made Shoko's life a living hell.
It was so awful.
I kept begging him to leave her alone,
but Shoya never listens to anyone.
I was so scared of him.
Yasho, what's wrong?
Sorry, gotta go.
Are you okay?
Hey, Yasho!
Yeah, I hate me too.
Hey, we're over here!
Hi!
Is something wrong?
Oh, no, not really.
It's nothing.
Oh.
There he is, my main man!
I brought your backpack for you.
Hey, guys.
Naoka?
I asked her to come.
I'm sorry about what happened.
But, well...
you were the one who started causing all that trouble.
The thing is,
Satoshi said I should go ahead and forgive you
since you've been trying to make things right with Shoko.
Are you kidding me? This is wrong on so many levels.
You can't blame everything that happened on Shoya.
We were all guilty.
We?
But, Nao, that isn't true.
What's not?
I never made fun of Shoko or did anything
to bully her the way the rest of you guys did.
Don't lump me in with you!
Naoka.
Oh...
Hm, you're right.
You and I are completely different.
You just sat back and laughed along with everyone else.
Did not!
Just ask Miyoko.
What, me?
Naoka used to talk about you
behind your back all the time, too!
I just said what everyone else was thinking.
Well, Miyoko, wanna weigh in?
Uh, to be completely honest,
back then, I was... I was scared of both of you.
What? Whose side are you on anyway?
I'm not on anyone's side.
Just stop.
It was my fault, okay?
It's all my fault.
I can't stand martyrs.
That's enough, Naoka.
Stop trying to drag everybody else down to your level.
That was harsh. You didn't have to p...
Oh, please, Miyoko.
We all know that you just run
away whenever things get tense.
Shoya.
What's gotten into you?
God, will you just stop talking?
You really love the sound of your own voice, don't you?
Listen, man. No matter what
anyone says, I've got your back.
I don't care.
Will you just back off?
You hardly know me.
I can't take this anymore.
I'm not staying here!
It's alright, you don't mean it.
But I'm gonna give you some space.
Hey, Shoko.
Later.
I'm sorry, Shoya.
I never should have agreed to come here to begin with.
That's not cool. You were way too harsh.
What do you know? You're not
even really part of our group.
I thought we were friends.
Almost forgot.
So, starting next week,
it's summer vacation.
Do you wanna go somewhere special?
You're going to ruin your eyes
reading in the dark like that.
Here.
You spend so much time worried about your big sister.
Now I'm starting to worry about you, sweetie.
You get so caught up in Shoko's life,
that you never leave any time for yourself.
I could say the same thing about you, Granny.
Instead of going to the senior center,
all you do is study sign language.
That's something I'm doing for
myself, so that doesn't really count.
What a coincidence, because I'm
doing all these things for myself, too.
Really?
You are such a good kid.
You think so?
Mom chews me out on a daily basis, and
I haven't gone to school in like weeks.
Yes, sweetie, but you've got a heart of gold.
Shoko's no slouch, either.
I've got some mighty fine grandchildren.
Have one of the mochi, too.
You've got it!
Granny.
Hey there, Shoko.
So today, I was able to score us some really great bread.
See?
It's awesome, like you're awesome.
Um.
Like really great bread is awesome.
This loaf here is just like you.
Well, that makes no sense.
Uh.
I wonder if she's coming today.
Guess not.
Is your stomach bothering you?
Is that too personal?
Hey!
Yuzu...!
Oh, I should go.
Shoya.
Huh?
Hey there.
What the heck are you wearing?
What's it look like? My uniform.
What do you think? Ya like?
Why are you wearing it?
For school, duh.
Uh, but we're on summer break right now.
So what's really going on?
Nothing is going on, I swear.
If anyone asks, tell 'em I'm cosplaying.
Uh.
That was from my sister so I better take off.
Where to? I'll walk you there.
What? No, it's fine.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah, everything's cool.
Then why were you crying just now?
Come on.
This actually doesn't have anything to do with you.
Sure it does.
At least, I think so.
Why?
I'm just worried about you, okay?
I don't believe it. You sound just like my grandma.
Alright, if you wanna come, then come.
This is it.
Thanks for walking me.
I appreciate it.
See ya.
Good luck, Yuzuru.
Shoya, wait.
Truth is, I'm scared.
Whoa, that's cool.
Come on, Shoko. Let's go check it out!
Uh.
Shoko?
Ah!
I'm fine, really.
Uh, why are you apologizing?
That's totally not true.
Hey, are you busy tomorrow? Let's hang out tomorrow, too.
Shoko said that I'll be miserable whenever I'm with her.
But I'm the one who made her unhappy.
It was me.
One thing to see
And to have someone love me
Even monsters feel
In their heart
There's no going back to the way things were.
Hey, Shoko! Cool. I see Yuzuru's gonna tag along with us.
Let's check out a movie.
This is hilarious!
Hey, greetings, classmates!
I gotta say,
this has been the best summer break ever!
Just ask Yuzuru.
Whatever.
Seriously, we're having an absolute blast!
What about tomorrow? We should go somewhere fun!
Any ideas where we should go?
Sorry, but we already have plans for tomorrow.
Hmm?
Huh? No way! Are you insane?
She wants to make what?
You sure it's okay?
I feel like I really shouldn't be here.
Your mission, should you choose to accept it, is
to assist us in baking our mother's birthday cake.
Are you absolutely sure?
I don't wanna get hit again.
She won't hit you.
She'll probably kill you this time.
For real?
Whoa, that looks amazing!
Hm?
Why is he here?
What is that boy doing in our kitchen?
I want an explanation right now.
Come on, Mom.
Get out.
Don't be like that.
It's a party, we're supposed to be celebrating!
Yuzuru.
You look great.
Mm.
You lucked out. Looks like Mom isn't gonna kill you.
Wow.
I declare a victory.
Speaking of winning...
I submitted some of your photography
to the local contest, Yuzuru.
Hm? You what?
It was actually your sister's idea.
Wha...? But I'm no good, I'm just messing around.
Oh, come on. That's not true.
Why would you do this to me?
Before I forget, next Tuesday you're coming
to see the fireworks with us still, right?
I-I don't have to.
You're totally coming.
Is here okay?
Yeah, this is good.
Well, perfect time to go buy snacks.
Wanna come, Mom?
Thank you.
Um, thanks for inviting me over the other day, too.
Your mom...
you really think she was happy?
I couldn't tell.
Speaking of which,
I don't know when your birthday is.
Your birthday was June 7th.
Oh, no! I missed it. That's too bad.
I can't believe you're already 18.
Next year, we'll celebrate together.
We'll throw a big party.
I made it sound like we're together.
I get it now. That makes perfect sense.
That's why you closed your eyes.
Huh? Where are you going?
What, why now?
The fireworks only just started.
To go study?
Okay.
Well, hey, wait up. I'll walk you home.
But why?
Oh, well, see you later.
Hey, what happened to Shoko?
Ugh, I forgot my camera!
Would you mind going back to our place to get it?
I'm comin' in.
Man, it's so dark.
Hey, Shoko, you here?
It's me, Shoya.
Good, there it is.
Mm, I should make sure it's fully charged.
Huh, you can see the fireworks from here.
Oh, so that's where she is. Hm?
What is she...? Hey.
W-wait a second.
What is she doing?
Hey, Shoko.
Uh, Shoko?
Don't do it!
Please no.
Shoko!
You have to grab on to the railing.
Please God, if you give me one more ounce of strength,
I won't run away from my problems anymore.
Just do this one thing for me, please.
Starting tomorrow, I'll look everyone in the eye.
Starting tomorrow,
I'll listen when people speak to me.
Starting tomorrow, I'll be better.
Shoko.
There it is.
The scar I gave her all those years ago.
Did I ever even apologize for that?
I'm sorry.
Sorry for everything, Shoko.
Are you still mad at me?
I'm so dumb.
I should have asked her what she really thinks of me.
And now I don't know if...
By the way, Shoko,
I think that I might...
Hey there, Sho.
Your sister whipped you up some of her famous pancakes.
I'm gonna watch the fireworks!
It's cold.
It's warm.
Mrs. Ishida!
Ah, what are you doing here?
I'm glad I caught you.
I tried calling the salon, but it was closed.
I just wanted to know about Shoya.
Well, he's doing a lot better.
They moved him out of the ICU.
I was going to his new room. Do you want to come with me?
Um, do you know if Shoya will...
Mrs. Ishida.
Uh, Mrs. Nishimiya.
I'm sorry for all the trouble Shoya has caused.
I know what he did in the past
is unforgivable but I want y...
Please forgive me.
What on earth are you doing?
Get up.
I'm sure Shoya must have done
something, otherwise, this wouldn't've...
Mrs. Ishida.
Shoya was trying to save my stupid sister.
If I had done better...
She wouldn't have...
I'm so sorry.
Please don't.
Come on, both of you. Please get up.
I'm just glad that Shoko is okay.
And you too, Yuzuru.
So please, get up.
Why is Shoya lying in a hospital bed instead of you?
Don't you dare try to play the victim!
Say something!
What, you finally felt bad for all
the problems you created for everyone
so you decided to kill yourself?
And now all you can say is "I'm sorry"?
Is that it?
Well, that's not going to cut it anymore!
Who do you think you are, huh?
You're a loser... a deaf loser.
You sit there in your own little world
and ignore everyone else around you.
You're the most selfish person I know!
Ah!
Hey, who the hell are you?
You must be the little loser's mother!
Stop.
If you can't keep your kid in line
then do us all a favor and stop breathing!
What are you two doing?
That's enough.
I said that's enough. Stop it!
What is wrong with the both of you?
Shoko, are you okay?
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
It's all my fault!
What are you doing?
I thought if she saw what death looked like,
she'd stop saying she wanted to kill herself.
I didn't know what else to do.
Mm.
Oh.
I can't open it. Someone is holding it shut.
Oh, I didn't notice you there, Shoko.
Are you, uh, thirsty?
How about I buy you a drink?
I heard about what happened with you and Yasho.
Does this have to do with that stuff on the bridge?
Yasho was kind and openhearted
enough to accept a guy like me.
For the first time,
I know what it feels like to have a true friend.
Yasho is my best friend in the whole world.
So I know he'll wake up.
He just has to.
Hm?
Uh.
You wanted to die because you were suffering?
What were you thinking?
Just calm down!
Everybody's staring.
I don't care who's listening!
I have to be loud in order for Shoko to hear me!
We were all so worried about you.
I know life can be hard sometimes,
but it's like that for everyone.
The thing is,
you have to accept the bad parts of
yourself with the good and just move forward.
I'm really glad you're okay.
I see.
So you went to see everyone then, huh?
That's awesome.
But I'm not as brave as you.
Even if Shoya does wake up from his coma,
I think I'd be too ashamed to face him
'Cause he's right. I haven't changed one bit.
You needed help and I still wasn't there for you.
I'm the same coward I've always been.
You can change. Start now.
It's not too late.
I'm really glad you came to see me, Sho.
Huh?
Hey!
Stop it.
Cut it out.
No, Shoko!
What is all this?
Mom? Hello?
What's going on?
Shoko!
Almost there.
She isn't here.
I'm so sorry.
Huh?
Yo.
Hm.
Hey, why are you crying?
I'm really glad
you're okay.
Don't worry, Shoko.
I am fine now, I promise.
Well, more or less.
So stop looking so gloomy, okay?
Oh, yeah.
I wanna tell you...
that I'm really sorry.
I never apologized
for all the stuff I did to you when we were kids.
Or any of the other stuff afterwards, either.
So I'm sorry.
But the thing is,
even though you were going
through a lot, I was being selfish
and focused on myself.
More than anything,
I wanted to have a conversation with you.
I wasn't trying to hurt you.
But I must have, because...
I made you feel so bad about yourself
that you decided to go and do the unthinkable.
No, you're wrong!
It's because I couldn't change!
And that's why you fell.
It's me.
Everything is always my fault!
So I thought I should just disappear.
I was so selfish.
I'm sorry!
Please, that's not true. Don't cry.
Shoko, look at me.
Did you know we were talking a little while ago?
I was dreaming.
And in this dream, I was ready
to just give up on everything.
I was wrong.
To be honest,
I've thought about ending things, just like you did.
But then I realized something.
Even though certain things can
make life difficult sometimes,
that doesn't mean that they're worth dying over.
I want to apologize and make sure I do it right.
Shoko?
I need some help from you.
I was hoping...
that maybe you could...
teach me how to live.
Please, Shoko.
Oh, God.
That's the creepiest thing I've ever said in my life.
I'm so sorry, just... never mind.
Forget everything I said, okay? I didn't mean it.
You have arrived at your destination.
Hey there, Maria.
You've become quite the gardener
since I've been gone, huh?
They're lookin' good.
Sho-Sho!
You died!
That's right, Maria.
Our Sho came back from the dead.
Don't listen to Grandma. I wasn't really dead.
Hey look. Isn't that Naoka?
You know, she was by your side
the entire time you were in a coma.
You really should thank her.
My mom said you came to the hospital.
Listen, I really suck at life sometimes.
Especially when it comes to stuff like this.
I just...
I just can't bring myself to like Shoko.
I'm probably gonna regret this.
Remember when you fell in the river?
It was Kazuki and the guys who pulled you out.
And then told me not to tell you but...
Anyway.
Welcome back.
Well, I'm gonna take off.
Thanks, Naoka.
I don't know.
Don't you think it's a little short?
No, no, it looks much cuter like this!
Oh, you're home, Shoya.
Oh, hi, Shoya.
Uh, Mrs. Nishimiya.
Wait a minute.
Yes?
I'm really sorry.
Uh, yeah. Me too.
No matter what, my son always bounces right back.
See ya later, Mom.
I'm heading out to pick up Maria now.
Okay!
Who's that?
That's my son-in-law. He's back from being deployed.
Oh, Shoya.
Yuzuru is waiting for you upstairs.
Give her the jelly that's in the fridge.
Yo.
Whoa.
New threads?
It looks good on you.
Check it out. I won.
Huh? Wow!
No kidding. Impressive.
Now feast your eyes on this.
Whoa.
Not so impressive.
Since you're alive again,
will you please help teach me how to study?
Of course, no prob.
So, uh, you're giving school another shot?
Yeah, I decided to take a cue from Shoko.
I figured the least I can do is try.
I don't wanna let anyone down.
Isn't your big school festival tomorrow?
Oh yeah, that's right.
Ah, good morning, everybody!
Up top, yeah!
Ha, ha, ha!
I said horrible things and I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm heading out.
Have a good day, sweetheart.
Oh, I see now. So that's what you're
supposed to do with those things.
What's that?
Oh, nothing. I'll see you later, 'kay?
Have a good day, Sho-Sho!
Ha! There you are.
Okay, let's go.
Isn't that Shoya?
Who is that?
Wait the one who was in the hospital, right?
The guy who jumped?
You probably didn't know this, but I...
don't really fit in at school.
It's cause I have trouble
looking people in the eye.
So it's easier for me to just
stare at the floor all the time.
You think it's okay to do that?
Uh, Shoko.
I can actually do it without you leading me.
But thank you.
This is my classroom here.
Has the water boiled yet?
Just a few more minutes.
Oh, wow. Shoya's back at school!
Are you okay now?
You know what?
I think my stomach's acting up a bit.
So, sorry.
Yasho! Huh?
Yasho?
Huh? Oh, hey. That you, Nagatsuka?
You feeling okay?
Yasho.
Good morning, Nagatsuka. Good to see you.
So how is everything?
About the...?
What's going on?
Why won't you look at me?
I don't know. I just feel weird.
I made myself a promise I would
look people in the eyes from now on.
Guess I'm too chicken.
Hey, Yasho.
Shoya!
You're okay. I'm glad.
'Cause if you... if you didn't wake up,
I didn't know what I would do!
You're everything to me.
I would have been all alone.
Listen, the stuff on the bridge,
don't worry about it, 'kay?
Friends say stuff they don't mean to
each other all the time. It doesn't matter.
I'm begging you, don't ever leave us again.
Promise me. I can't lose you.
It's gonna be okay.
Hey, look.
I'm sorry.
I mean...
Thank you.
For being a friend.
You've very welcome.
But, uh...
What's up with the facial hair?
That's my lucky 'stache.
I swore I wasn't shaving it till you woke up.
You did that for me?
Uh.
What's going on?
We heard Nagatsuka howling your name, so we followed it.
I-I see.
Miki, did you bring the stuff to give to Shoya?
I brought them, but I can't give it to him.
It's a total failure.
Don't be silly, hand 'em over.
Here.
Hm?
There was supposed to be a thousand of them,
but we couldn't finish it fast enough.
Everyone worked really hard and
did their best, but we just couldn't.
No, this is amazing!
It's more than enough.
No one's ever done anything like this for me.
It really means a lot, seriously.
Thank you, Miki.
Also, sorry.
And to you, too.
No worries. It's all good, bro.
Ugh, enough! All this sappy talk.
I'm gonna lose my lunch.
Why do you always have to be like that, Naoka?
What, you got a problem with me or something?
You pickin' a fight?
Okay, everybody just calm down.
Shoya.
Listen, I'm really sorry.
After all you'd been through, you really needed a friend.
But all I did was run away.
That's okay.
I did the same thing.
Stop acting so worried. They're just talking things out.
You apologizing?
Well, guess that's all you know how to do.
Moron.
Mm.
Whatever. I'm gonna go find something to eat.
Did she just run away?
I think she's embarrassed.
Hey, guys. I have a big favor to ask all of you.
That okay?
Do you wanna go together to the festival?
How's that sound?
OMG, this is so good!
Oh, hey, let's go to the gym next.
I can't believe he's back in school.
Oh, their store's amazing.