[energy crackling]
[GRUMMAN]
Are you watching, Mitsuki?
Your invention
is bridging the gap
between two different worlds.
Though we've been
separated for years,
our hopes will
finally become one.
They've gone completely insane.
Tokyo won't last at this rate.
Guys, we have to put
a stop to them.
-[crackling in distance]
-Huh?
Kark!
[KARK] At last,
the gates have been opened.
And while I'm eager to depart
for the land I've yearned for,
leaving unfinished business
in this world
would ruin the experience.
Bring it!
[CHIHIRO]
Wait, Kotetsu.
I'm the one he wants to fight.
You three head to
the Foundation's headquarters.
No way!
We are not leaving you
to fight him all by yourself!
Just go!
[KOUME]
We should listen to Chihiro.
If we don't stop
whatever's causing this,
Tokyo's gonna be consumed.
I'm going.
Otherwise, I won't be able
to face Inuki.
She's got a point.
Chihiro, please be careful.
I will. Same to you.
See you after we win.
We've got this
under control.
Apologies for the delay, Kark.
[KARK chuckles]
There's no need to worry.
It'd be in bad taste
if the god of death
was in the habit
of rushing final farewells.
I'm not planning on dying.
There's someone I have
to see before I go.
Regret is an anchor,
weighing down the soul.
The least I can do
is embellish it beautifully
with my requiem.
-[growling]
-Meet Jormungandr.
The Serpent god of death
that swallows the world.
Another beast?
Fine then!
The Lord of Vermilion demands
thousands of offerings.
[roaring]
[ghostly moaning]
[KARK] You're to blame
for everything,
Chihiro Kamina.
Listen to the grievances
of the people.
This is your chance
at redemption.
[grunting]
I told you once already,
I'm not asking for forgiveness.
Shouldering the burden
is my responsibility.
[chuckles]
Seeing as you're the closest
to becoming
the Lord of Vermilion,
your soul shall be mine.
Check it out.
[TSUBAKI]
That's AVAL's headquarters?
Looks nice from the outside,
but the location's
just terrible.
Grumman and Professor Mitsuki
once conducted
their research there.
You must act now.
They are attempting
to bring about the end.
[KOUME]
You're sure this is it?
-Kotetsu!
-Uh!
[DUX] If you want answers,
ask difficult questions.
[chuckles]
I leave the rest to you.
She's acting as if none
of this really affects her.
[TSUBAKI]
Densuke, go!
I'm second summer president.
The name's Tsubaki
"the Red" Manazuru!
Let's go!
-Oh!
-Wow, yes, ma'am.
[yelling]
[KARK]
You're wasting energy.
No blade can pierce
Jormungandr's scales.
[bellowing]
[yelling]
[shrieking]
[groans]
[KARK laughing]
[groaning]
[screams]
[KARK laughing]
Let there be celebration
and praise.
Death is kind and precious.
Its beauty, so arresting.
[laughs]
[CHIHIRO gasps]
[CHIHIRO]
Did I lose consciousness?
It's me?
[DUX]
Do you have to ask?
[CHIHIRO]
You mean...
[DUX giggles]
[DUX]
Don't worry. Not yet.
[CHIHIRO]
Good.
I can't leave this life
without completing my goal.
Still, my turn
is coming up regardless.
In what manner
would you like to die?
[CHIHIRO] You're the one who's
been giving me these dreams!
Was there a reason you filled
my head with illusions?
They were not illusions.
They're memories
from alternate timelines.
Reality is like a play.
Performed countless times,
over and over again.
Though the cast and ad-libbing
are different for each show.
And yet, the conclusion
never changes.
[CHIHIRO]
These are my memories?
[DUX] In other plays.
The dreams are a warning
to keep you from making
the same mistakes.
[CHIHIRO] Why me?
Why not help others!
Every time the curtain fell,
you raised another one
in its place.
I don't exactly know why,
but that is the reason.
[CHIHIRO]
In other words...
I've never been forgiven in any
of the plays I've appeared in.
I kept thinking
“maybe this next one.”
[chuckles]
How pathetic of me.
[DUX] Even the worst play
has its merits.
For example,
this is the first time
so many vessels
of Heroic Lineage have survived.
[CHIHIRO]
Can I change how this ends?
That is entirely up to you.
[TSUBAKI]
Densuke!
-You'll pay for that!
-We can't go rushing in!
[KOUME]
There's no end to them in sight.
[KOTETSU]
Koume, go on without us!
-[KOUME] What?
-[TSUBAKI] He's totally right.
He's totally wrong!
If we don't do this,
Tokyo will be destroyed.
Just remember.
We'll be counting on you!
I'm gonna be
so pissed if you die!
Well, we definitely drew
the short straw.
No way.
Any time I get to spend alone
with you always makes me happy.
What? That's really sweet,
but do you think
now's the right time?
Sorry. I've never been great
at reading the room,
but I don't want any regrets.
[TSUBAKI] [giggles]
I think I can forgive you.
What do you say
we put this on hold?
You can tell me more
after we thin the herd.
Deal. I promise
I'll protect you.
[KOUME]
Coming through!
Don't expect me to knock!
[GRUMMAN]
Kill them, Chiyu.
[CHIYU] If I'm not here
to manage the instruments,
odds are the device
will lose control.
That's fine.
If those pests close the gate
before I see Mitsuki,
all of this
will have been for nothing.
[distant explosion, rumbling]
It's time, my beloved daughter.
-[CHIYU] Sophistry.
-What was that?
Did you actually think
I was blind
to how you manipulate
the women in your life
by pretending you love them?
Me and Yuri
and Professor Mitsuki.
Whenever you talk about love,
it's only as a tool
to serve you and your vision.
And how could
a doll ever know?
Because... you mixed
the professor's DNA with yours
to create me
as a substitute
when you were no longer able
to have her by your side.
That's how I know.
I exist as both a version
of Professor Mitsuki
as well as you,
Aldo Grumman Shiraki.
The only person
you've ever loved is yourself.
You're wrong.
My heart belongs to Mitsuki.
One more thing.
While that may be true,
the Professor never loved you.
I don't think you need
to ask how I can tell.
[giggles]
Open the gate if you wish,
but she won't
be waiting for you.
You're not important to her.
She only wishes for one thing,
to return to her family.
Are you Mitsuki?
[grunts]
Stop, or else.
It's a fabrication.
You're lying.
[KOUME]
Huh?
I don't believe it.
I refuse to believe.
[giggles]
You're just trying
to deceive me!
[laughing maniacally]
I see you're still
alive, defect.
You haven't changed one bit.
You've been looking
down your nose at me
since we were
at the orphanage.
-Think so?
-Out of the way, Chiyu!
Or don't blame me
when you get hurt!
Argh! You bitch!
[CHIYU] This was brought on
by the obsessions
of a foolish man.
And while there's no reason
for me to fulfill my duty,
a foolish woman's curiosity
compels me to press on
and see how this ends.
[screaming]
We all have a reason
to fight, and that's mine.
[DUX] Moment by moment,
the wheel of fate turns.
[CHIHIRO] You're saying
we're all going to die?
It could end that way.
If so, I would simply go
and watch a new play.
[CHIHIRO] They entrusted me
with their dying wishes.
Inuki. Kurokami.
Kakihara. Shoko.
Even Jun fought against fate.
They weren't just following
the destiny
laid out before them.
They resisted!
So I won't give up either.
[DUX chuckles]
And what good will changing
the script do?
[CHIHIRO] I...
-[INUKI] Survive.
-Survive.
Survive.
Survive, Chihiro.
I'll keep on living!
[giggles]
The winds have
changed direction.
I won't stop fighting
until the very end.
I'm master of my own fate!
What?
[yelling]
[bellowing]
Impossible.
He's incinerating a god
that's supposed
to bring about the end.
[DRAYLE whistles]
Hey, that's not bad.
[KARK]
Lord of Vermilion.
No more distractions,
Kark. Fight me.
I've watched you burn gods
and destroy demons.
These are no longer
the deeds of a human being.
You've abandoned
your humanity.
You're mistaken, Kark.
It's the opposite.
I'm fighting
for those closest to me.
Their wishes
give me strength.
[KARK]
Your existence is an affront
to the gods of death.
You will never be forgiven!
Chihiro Kamina!
I will never forgive you!
Amadeus!
[screams]
My hands! What've you done?
Piano. Where's my piano?
Death comes to all of us.
Even you.
I was so close to his land.
Somebody,
play the piano for me.
Before I go, I want to hear
the ultimate requiem.
-Yah!
-Ah!
I don't think
there's much left in me.
Yeah, me neither. Is this it?
[growling]
[gasps]
I expected better. Disgraceful.
Are you or are you not a member
of the Guardian State?
Julia and Suruga? Why?
[JULIA]
Like I need to explain.
Our organization's purpose
is to protect the world
from evil spirits.
[SURUGA] We're simply performing
our sworn duties.
Thanks. You saved us.
Spare us your gratitude.
Destroy all demons!
Go, Gabriel! Exorcise them!
Go, Lia Fail! Crush them!
Don't underestimate me!
Come now. I've already
calculated your every movement.
Oh? Did you see this?
It's arrogant to assume
everything will go
exactly as you planned!
Because there are always
people in the world
who fight against
the impossible!
You're a defect.
Unworthy of challenging me.
There's no such thing
as a defective life!
Life's an obligation!
You have to struggle
against adversity,
no matter the cost!
That's why it's worth saving!
[grunts, breathing heavily]
If he were here,
that's what Inuki would say.
Now, stop the machine.
I can't.
[grunts]
That's enough.
I couldn't shut it down
even if I wanted to.
We've no other choice
but to accept our fate.
[GRUMMAN laughing]
That's what she gets
for mocking me.
No one can deceive me!
No one!
It won't be long now, Mitsuki!
I'm coming for you!
[DRAYLE laughing]
And much sooner
than you think!
Mitsuki!
[screaming]
Told you!
[laughing]
[KOTETSU]
Did they stop it?
[DUX]
No. The mission failed.
The gate's beyond control
and will continue to expand.
Eventually, it will consume
the world.
It's over?
Not yet!
I refuse to give up!
There's gotta be a way!
You know something, don't you?
Tell me!
There is a possibility.
Just one.
The Lord of Vermilion
has several powers,
including the ability
to create new worlds.
As the candidate closest
to taking on this role,
it's possible for you
to erase the gate.
However...
Uh...
Yuri.
You're in a hurry.
Where are you going?
It's not too late. Step aside.
[YURI]
You don't want to answer me?
Fine. I already know the answer.
You plan to enter the gate.
As the Lord of Vermilion,
you'd be able to erase the gate.
However, it would require
countering one power
with another.
It would cost you your life.
But how do you know that?
Because someone was
kind enough to inform me.
I'm not letting
you die, Chihiro.
The boy needs
to be stopped, Yuri,
and there's only one way
he can be saved.
By killing him!
It doesn't make sense!
Tell me why you're so insistent
on throwing your life away?
I found the reason!
Why I was told
to keep on living!
Because as long as I'm alive,
I can keep using my life!
[YURI]
What're you talking about?
I don't understand any of this!
[CHIHIRO]
I'm sorry.
I've no idea who you are.
The real Chihiro
would never leave
without saying anything to me!
Please, Yuri! I have to!
You're not going!
Besides, I'll never
be forgiven anyway.
I killed Cerdid
with my own two hands, remember?
It's not your fault!
I was there!
She forced you
to defend yourself!
That doesn't change
the fact I killed her!
So I must take up her role
as your protector!
I'm not letting you die!
[grunts]
Listen to me! Stop, Yuri!
[YURI] There's no
turning back for me now!
But at least I can save you!
It's wrong.
This should have never happened.
I was reunited with you.
We drank hot cocoa
in the sun together.
And both of us were
at peace again.
Why couldn't those days
last forever?
Chihiro!
Yuri!
Why didn't you?
You are the most
important person in my life.
I could never bring myself
to kill you.
So you haven't changed.
You're still the same
Chihiro I remember.
That means...
I can't believe what I've done!
I'm sorry.
Could you ever forgive me?
It's fine. Really.
[YURI]
Do you have to?
[CHIHIRO] I'm sorry,
but I can't stay.
[YURI]
Okay, I won't stop you...
if you let me come along.
[CHIHIRO]
What?
I don't have
much strength left
but I know
if you take me with you,
I can still help you out.
I have to do this
by myself, Yuri.
I think it would be better
-if you stayed here.
-Don't leave me!
-Uh!
-Please.
I can't go on living
without you.
Yuri.
Aren't you frightened at all?
[YURI]
Not when I'm with you.
Never let go of my hand.
I want you to stay
with me forever.
[CHIHIRO]
I will.
You and I will walk
together for all time,
in a beautiful blue sky
free of any conflict.
[chuckles]
Like Romeo and Juliet.
I thought you loved Shakespeare.
Of course I do,
but that play's a tragedy.
[YURI chuckles]
Our story will
turn out differently.
You're right.
Too bad.
I wish I'd come up
with a good line
to say goodbye with.
Huh, what do you mean?
Yuri...
give me the courage
to do this.
What? Chihiro!
You can't go! No!
[CHIHIRO]
I'm sorry, Yuri,
but where I'm going,
I can't take you with me.
[YURI]
Why? I don't understand!
[CHIHIRO]
Live, Yuri. Live for me.
You were the most
important part of my life.
You can't do this!
[CHIHIRO] Before I go,
you have to make a promise.
Please live.
Yes.
[inhales sharply]
I promise you.
Thank you.
Finally... I'll be able to.
[YURI]
Chihiro!
[grunts]
Huh?
[chuckles]