[splashing]
[JULIA]
You want to apologize?
In case you forgot,
we lost a valuable warrior.
Surely you understand
now, Tsubaki.
It's impossible to work
alongside these sinners.
I only wish we didn't have
to lose a teammate to prove it.
They're our enemies.
Nothing more.
You're wrong! We're your allies!
Allies, is it?
You were just betrayed
by a woman
you were convinced
was on your side.
Yuri didn't.
I have zero intentions
of being stabbed in the back.
Never contact us again.
Before you go, here.
[JULIA]
Keep your rock.
We don't need it.
Are you crazy?
-These are--
-[SURUGA] What, exactly?
Kurokami is dead because of you.
And you think giving us a stone
will earn you forgiveness?
[scoffs]
I don't have time
for this.
Tsubaki.
[RESEARCHER 1] Fog density
is stable at over 98 percent.
[DRAYLE] Hey, why not show
your face already?
You must be tired
of conserving your strength.
[GRUMMAN]
Begin the test.
[RESEARCHER 2]
Artificial keystone six,
final test.
[RESEARCHER 1] Resonance volume
at maximum strength.
[PEOPLE murmuring]
[groaning, screaming]
[growling]
It's beautiful.
[SHOKO] A shame
things didn't go as planned.
But what did you expect,
befriending an Agent of Chaos?
Fate is carved in stone.
There's no way to alter it.
Our relationship with the
Guardian State is beyond repair.
So what now?
I don't know.
You better think of something!
Kurokami died
because she trusted you!
And your answer
is "I don't know?"
How many will it take
before you're satisfied?
How many
do you have to kill?
I'm sorry, but... I don't--
[KAKIHARA] You're sorry?
Then fix this!
[grunts]
I was never willing to depend
on the Guardian State
to begin with.
As I've always said,
destroying Tokyo
is the only way
to save the world.
[KOUME] Kotetsu. Give me
Kurokami's blood crystal.
Huh? Oh. Okay.
And just where are you going?
To continue
with Inuki's research.
If you want to save the world,
then this is how
we're gonna do it.
We're leaving.
Come on.
I have my own method
of handling things.
-What? You can't.
-Kakihara, wait up.
[SHOKO] Don't you understand
your noble calling?
How can you turn
your back on it?
Destroying Tokyo's the only way!
Otherwise, we're all doomed!
Is that what you want?
[KAKIHARA]
She left us with our best lead.
Let's see if we can't uncover
what she's been working on.
[TSUBASA]
It's a list.
These are properties
owned by AVAL.
All the land the Foundation's
been forcibly acquiring
around the city.
Most likely, Kurokami
discovered something
at one of these locations
and was killed for it.
It's up to me
to avenge her death.
This is where we part ways.
You can do whatever you want.
After everything
we've been through?
You and I are a team,
and I'm not abandoning you.
What're you waiting for?
Let's go find out why AVAL
wanted those properties.
Right!
You have something to say,
well, here I am.
Or maybe you've
come here to kill me.
What? No! I...
I only wanted...
I'll bet you anything
you dreamed of my death.
Tell me that's not true.
[chuckles]
This is great news.
Now I finally get the chance
to cover one of the deaths
you're responsible
for firsthand.
How can you joke about this?
He has a point.
We ought to thank him
for bringing me the scoop.
We're usually the ones that have
to chase down the story leads.
You realize
I don't want you to die?
[chuckles]
You're going to make me weepy.
In all seriousness,
I see right through
your saint act.
You're doing this for yourself
and Yuri Shiraki.
You can't change fate unless
you can change your dreams.
And you can't change the fact
that it's your destiny
to kill one another.
You know what?
Maybe so.
You're a monster.
I'm delighted to hear that.
Now tell me about
how you killed your father.
I couldn't care less
if you hate me.
I don't have
to like you either.
It doesn't matter.
-I have to do something.
-Hmm?
[CHIHIRO]
Or nothing will be left.
We'll change our destiny.
We'll do it
for Inuki and Kurokami.
They trusted us
to carry on their mission!
-[KAKIHARA scoffs]
-Uh...
Kakihara!
If you don't want to die,
here's a suggestion.
Stay as far away
from me as possible.
Don't come near him again,
you hear me!
I didn't recognize his eyes.
They belonged to someone
trying to live.
Not the Chihiro Kamina
I've been pursuing.
[GRUMMAN] Our goal
is progressing smoothly,
but it's likely
we've been discovered.
I want you to tighten security.
Lay out a trap and put
the Church out of their misery.
[JUN] As long as
Chihiro Kamina is mine.
No, Jun. Your judgment
has been clouded by hate.
[scoffs]
[HARU]
Hey! Wait up!
[GRUMMAN] He's a fool.
Though he has a point.
Chihiro Kamina continues
to be a thorn in our side.
[chuckles]
Almost tempting your daughter
to leave us, for example.
[grunts]
[GRUMMAN]
That's not the issue.
The problem is an alliance
was nearly formed
between the Church
and the Guardian State.
And at the center of this plot
was Chihiro Kamina.
The boy managed
to temporarily unite
the Heroic Lineage.
He may have what it takes
to become the Lord of Vermilion.
I hope you're safe.
-[TSUBAKI] Kakihara's next?
-[KOTETSU] Guess so.
Chihiro said
that's what he dreamt.
[TSUBAKI] He'll fight
and try to stop it.
So what should we do?
That depends on
who you're asking right now.
A member of the Guardian State
or Tsubaki?
Huh?
I don't mind
helping out a friend.
We are friends, aren't we?
[KAKIHARA] What did you
stumble on, Kurokami?
The message
she left Tsubaki Manazuru
was her last communication.
Call history seems normal.
Uh! That's it!
Oh!
After all this craziness,
you're still beside me.
Tsubasa, you in there?
Hold on.
Coincidence?
No.
Shoko wanted us
to eliminate the barriers
in order to destroy Tokyo.
The barriers. Huh?
He doesn't know when to quit.
[CHIHIRO]
What did you want to tell me?
[KAKIHARA] Huh?
Is that some kind of a joke?
You're the one
who's following me, kid.
[CHIHIRO]
I just want to protect you.
The thought of dying
doesn't bother me at all.
Matter of fact,
it's been a long time coming.
Huh?
My parents saw a way
out of their money problems.
Suicide.
I was supposed to die with them.
In the end, they abandoned me.
I was a precocious brat.
I could tell my parents
were never really fond of me.
But to this day,
I still don't know
why they decided
to leave me behind.
Well, what about you?
Why'd you refuse to die
with your old man?
Your father wanted
to take you with him.
Why'd you reject his wishes?
[chains clinking]
You were so reluctant
to die yourself,
you took out your own father?
Time to finally admit it.
You murdered him
so that you could live!
I don't care about living!
You what?
[CHIHIRO] I have no memory
of what happened that day.
But ever since,
it's been endless suffering.
Not knowing if I was
responsible or not.
I wished I'd died.
Or that I could have
traded places with him.
But there has to be some
good reason I'm still alive!
That's it.
The reason I can't die yet.
There they are.
Those eyes.
They were darker
than a moonless night,
no matter how carefree
you tried to act.
Filled with regret
and despair.
Even though
you murdered your father,
you still sought redemption.
I could tell.
You craved it.
More than anything.
If you're going to despair,
you should've just died
beside him.
And if you do want to live,
stop looking so damn hopeless!
I don't care who forgives you.
But I promise,
it won't be me!
At least, that's what
I used to believe.
Now you have the eyes of a man
interested in living.
You were betrayed by a woman,
abandoned by your friends,
lost everything, and you
still want to keep going.
The truth.
Were you really the one
who killed your father?
[CHIHIRO]
What are we doing here?
[KAKIHARA]
These are the GPS coordinates
of Kurokami's final call
according to her history.
Did you call anyone?
[CHIHIRO]
Kotetsu.
Kakihara, why did you talk
to me last night?
Because I wanted
to find answers.
You are a journalist,
aren't you?
Then shouldn't you be open
to finding out the truth?
[KAKIHARA chuckles]
If I'm being honest,
I don't know why
I opened up like that.
Don't know why
I'm out here at night
walking around
or why I invited you.
But if I accept things
on the surface
without investigating,
I'm no journalist.
You're absolutely certain
there's a reason
you survived, right?
I am.
[pulsing]
[KAKIHARA] This device
most likely generates
artificial barriers.
Are there more?
Based on the data
Kurokami left behind,
there are seven on the map.
It appears
they're strategically placed
around the city.
[CHIHIRO]
What does it mean?
[KAKIHARA] My guess,
they're trying to erect
new barriers instead of relying
on what's already here.
Shoko's wasting a lot of time
trying to destroy the old ones
if they can be manufactured.
Is that the only thing
this machine is for?
It's excessive,
even for the Agents of Chaos.
They've got
something big in store.
A second Great Collapse.
[MAN] Clever boy.
But poor Icarus.
You've flown too close
to the sun,
and now your wings
are melting.
-[TSUBASA] Look out!
-[CHIHIRO grunts]
Stay back!
I'll protect you!
[KAKIHARA]
Kaburagi Kark?
[CHIHIRO]
You know him?
What, do you live in a cave?
He's a famous pianist.
Even I've got his albums.
The world has
branded me decadent,
but all I wish
is to share my music.
I offer this piece to you.
A beautiful requiem.
Listen and die.
No, you don't!
[screams]
Tsubasa!
How'd she hit her from there?
You're the one
that murdered Kurokami.
[chuckles]
The reaper doesn't remember
all those he's granted death.
You bastard.
[KARK]
Death comes for all.
It's inevitable.
[grunts]
Dad?
[screaming]
What's wrong?
No. It's-- It's not my fault.
Get a grip on yourself, Kamina!
I call this piece
“Binding Spell.”
Go on, break his spell!
What happened to all
that power you had?
My blood armaments!
I can't use them
for some reason!
What?
[KARK] My melodies capture
people's hearts.
But yours must be very guilty.
It refuses to give in
to my song and break free.
[KAKIHARA grunting]
Wait, you're helping me?
I'm just as surprised
as you are.
[KARK] How disrespectful,
interrupting the performance.
[KAKIHARA groans]
You have to get away
while you can!
I've still got some questions
that need answering
and until I get them,
no one's checking out.
[KARK]
Then you will die together.
[CHIHIRO]
Look out!
[TSUBASA sobbing softly]
No. Tsubasa!
[HALTING] I need to share
something with you.
[gasps]
[MARIE]
Keep living.
Survive.
Tsubasa!
[groans]
There's no need for grieving.
Death is but a moment's parting.
You'll see.
[KAKIHARA grunts]
What're you doing?
I hear the incessant wailing
of your soul.
Shut your mouth!
[groans]
You're just one more note
in my symphony.
Play it for me.
The Rhapsody of Death!
[KAKIHARA grunts]
[CHIHIRO]
Kakihara!
Cerdid!
Nobody lays a finger on Chihiro!
You... saved me.
Making you admit your guilt
was my life's purpose.
The thing that kept me going.
I didn't have the strength
to acknowledge
my own parents
had rejected me.
If you love somebody,
you should take them with you.
I couldn't bring myself
to forgive you
for refusing to die
beside your father.
Now I see that I was wrong
all this time.
I lost sight of the--
-[grunts]
-Kakihara!
Run, Chihiro! Go now!
Listen, you didn't kill
your father.
I reviewed the case
documents again.
[KAKIHARA] He must have
returned to his senses
after he was stabbed.
He feared what he'd become
and knew what he had to do
in order to save you.
So you wouldn't end up
being a murderer.
So you could continue to live.
Are you telling me
the truth right now?
You did not kill your father!
Kark!
-[grunts]
-Kakihara!
[KOTETSU]
Chihiro. Are you okay?
Kotetsu!
That's the same man
who killed Kurokami!
Then that bastard's
going to pay.
-We're not letting him escape!
-You got it.
That's all for today.
Where do you think
you're going?
Cerdid.
You mean that he's...
[KAKIHARA]
You should feel honored.
Looks like I gave my life
protecting you.
It's a bit out of character,
if you ask me.
Or maybe I was jealous
all along.
-What?
-Nothing.
It's in the past now.
It's ancient history.
Turns out in the end,
you and I were the same.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
[KAKIHARA]
Live.
Survive, Chihiro Kamina.
I have a message for you.
It's from Kurokami,
Inuki Akaya,
Tsubasa, and your father.
They wanted me to pass it on.
You have to keep living.
You hear me?
What about you?
There's a reason
you've made it this far, kid.
And hell, maybe I was
left alive this long
so I could have the chance
to get this off of my chest.
There's gonna come a time
you'll tell someone
what I told you.
[coughs]
Kakihara? Don't you die!
Tsubasa.
Father.
Mother.
You've got to hold on!
[CHIHIRO screams]
[DUX]
Another one lost.
Fate is truly unfaithful.
And yet somehow
Kotetsu was spared.
I chalked it up
as a rare blessing.
But then why tease us?
[SHOKO] Regardless,
at the rate we're going...
[DUX] Correct.
They'll be annihilated again.
Again?
Chaos's plan may still succeed,
regardless of whether
Tokyo is destroyed or not.
If the last one is connected,
there will be
a second Great Collapse.
And Chaos will reign.
I refuse to let that happen.
[DUX] The time has come
to settle this.
We cannot afford to retreat.
Soon, the Heroic Lineage
will be down to one.
Yes. I understand
Do it for
the splendid new world.