[footsteps]
[SHOKO]
You're late.
So why did we have
to meet out here, exactly?
[CHIHIRO] That's on me.
I asked you all to come.
[KOTETSU]
Who's there?
Hey. How you doin'?
Seriously?
Didn't expect us.
Did you?
The Guardian State's here?
I'd like to make a proposal.
Instead of fighting, our groups
should be working together.
Is that supposed to be
some kinda joke?
Well, personally,
I wouldn't mind if we teamed up.
You be quiet, Tsubaki.
And don't think for one second
that I'm not aware
of your involvement
with these people.
You're a member
of the Guardian State.
Your thoughtless actions
won't be quickly forgiven.
Don't forget
that they're responsible
for destroying the barriers
protecting Tokyo.
We're the ones trying
to save the world.
[MAN] I've had just about enough
of your fanaticism.
[SHOKO] That so?
You'll have to excuse me,
but I don't find your views
exceptionally persuasive.
Especially when they come
from an organization
that claims
it's protecting the country
while slaying anyone
who opposes them.
[WOMAN] No one gets away with
insulting the Guardian State!
Julia Ichijo, starting battle.
Gabriel! Come to me!
I, Suruga Jumonji,
call forth Lia Fail!
You wanna fight?
Wait! Calm down,
Julia and Suruga!
We haven't even heard
Chihiro out yet!
Chaos will continue
to stain the world.
Destroying Tokyo is
the only way to stop it!
There's a way to save the world
without sacrificing Tokyo!
That's... possible?
Uh...
[KOUME chuckles]
We're listening. Elaborate.
He's obviously lying.
[chuckles]
Of course he's making it up.
You know there's no other way.
That's why you've destroyed
your share of the city, right?
We can change our fate.
[KAKIHARA]
Yuri Shiraki.
She's an Agent of Chaos!
You're working with them now?
Just listen!
Yuri is on our side!
[chuckles]
You're kidding.
This must be
the Foundation's doing.
She saved Kotetsu.
We can trust her.
Are you serious?
He's telling the truth, Tsubaki.
She rescued me.
I owe my life to Yuri.
Since I woke up
after the Great Collapse,
I've been having
these awful nightmares.
Dreams about the ones
I love... dying.
First it was Kotetsu's dad,
then Inuki.
No matter how hard I fought,
I couldn't change the outcome.
Prophetic visions of death.
Those would happen to you.
And then I saw Kotetsu was next.
I thought that it was over.
That he couldn't escape
his fate.
But look. I'm alive, aren't I?
[CHIHIRO]
Because fate can change.
Yuri's the one
who taught me that.
I have all the proof I need.
Kotetsu's life shows
that we're in control
of how this ends.
I'm in charge
of my own destiny.
Oh, yeah?
I like the sound of that!
But your original objective
was to destroy this city.
Isn't it a bit late
to stop now?
AVAL's goal is to exterminate
the Heroic Lineage.
In order to do that,
they caused the Great Collapse
and are turning people
into gates.
The Maldeus Church wants
to destroy
the source of the gates.
Which just happens to be Tokyo.
That's how they plan on
protecting the Heroic Lineage.
[SHOKO] There is simply
no other choice.
There's a third option
available.
The Heroic Lineage survives
without leveling Tokyo
in the process.
As long as we're alive,
we can stop Chaos' plan.
And if we all work together,
we should be able to overcome
the Foundation's attacks.
[chuckles] I guess
that plan's not so bad.
We'd no longer have
to be enemies.
I will never trust these people.
But Shoko...
The Heroic Lineage is killed
or Tokyo is destroyed.
It can only be one
or the other.
Yuri thought her only choice
was to fight, yet she joined us.
And Kotetsu
was supposed to die.
If their fates can change,
then so can yours.
You've been so misled
by your love affair
that you dare
lecture us about fate?
You really have some nerve.
I just don't want
any more people to have to die!
I'm begging you.
Please help me!
Well, you already know
my answer.
I'm with you, man.
Since Kotetsu's down to play,
I guess there's no harm
jumping on board.
How about you?
If it means getting Haru back,
then count me in.
I'll be fighting
with you idiots as well,
so you'd better be grateful.
[SURUGA]
You can do whatever you want.
We will continue
to fulfill our duties
as members
of the Guardian State.
We don't require
the help of sinners.
Better be careful.
If you get involved, that kid
might be dreaming of you next.
Duly noted.
I'm helping anyway.
[KAKIHARA] Do you really
trust them that much?
[MARIE]
I have faith in them.
Can anyone tell me
where Yuri is?
Maybe she betrayed us.
Tell me, have you heard
anything at all, Jun?
Not a word.
It's true my daughter is a fool,
but she's still useful to us
for the time being.
Go and find her!
[KAKIHARA] I try to help
you out, and you ignore me?
Get involved and I die, right?
Not like you have that problem.
Seems like it'd take
a lot to kill you.
Resiliency is one
of my few good attributes.
If I had a real chance
to change the present,
I would take it,
even if it meant death.
There's no guarantee things
will improve, though.
What happens in the past
determines the future.
If his hands are already
covered in blood,
it stands to reason
any world he creates
will be equally blood soaked.
Nothing good will ever come
from trusting him.
He even killed his own father
to survive.
[MARIE]
Are you sure about that?
Meaning?
Come with me.
[YURI]
Were you waiting long?
[CHIHIRO]
No.
It smells good.
I'm pretty confident
I got it this time.
These reports are
from thirteen years ago.
When I learned Chihiro Kamina
was a vessel of Heroic Blood,
I acquired them immediately.
Autopsy report,
crime scene photos.
Info that was never made public.
You've been convinced you knew
the truth all this time.
Did you consider
you might be wrong?
So, you're saying
he didn't kill his father?
[KAKIHARA]
Thirteen years ago,
a family forced
into a double suicide
was discovered in
a Chichibusanchu neighborhood.
The seven-year-old son
was rescued in a weakened state,
but his father had been dead
for nearly two weeks.
It's assumed that the boy had
spent the entire span of time
next to his parent's corpse.
My dad. I think he's dead.
It was my fault.
I killed my dad.
Shortly after he was found,
the boy fell into a coma.
And when he woke up, he had
no memory of what had happened.
It's right there!
He confessed to the officers
that arrived at the scene!
The kid pled guilty!
It's likely
he was just confused.
Right. That's exactly what
you cops thought, wasn't it?
Then it was reported
as a forced double suicide.
[MARIE] There were bruises
on Chihiro Kamina's throat
that indicated he'd been choked.
It could be that his father
tried to strangle him
but changed his mind
and stabbed himself instead.
[KAKIHARA]
It was the kid who murdered him!
He used a broken piece
of glass to do it!
The cuts on his hands
are all the proof you need!
Kakihara. You are
a journalist, aren't you?
Shouldn't you be open
to finding out the truth?
As I said,
some of this wasn't made public.
What was thought to be
the father's dying message
was found at the scene.
Doesn't look like much to me.
If you want my personal
interpretation of it...
I'd say he was trying to tell
his son to keep living.
You think?
Actually. No way.
His son stabbed him,
why would he...
-Hey, Kakihara.
-Huh?
Just wanting somebody
to die can be simple
but telling them
to live isn't easy.
Especially for someone who's
about to lose their own life.
Wouldn't you agree?
He didn't kill him?
[cell phone beeping]
Yeah, what is it?
Right, got it. Tomorrow morning.
That was Kamina.
He wants us to meet up
with him at the Church.
I can't.
I refuse to accept this.
Kakihara.
This damn kid!
He freed himself
from the father
who was trying
to kill them both!
Instead of giving up,
he killed his own parent!
Here's what we know:
The Foundation is attempting
to bring about
a second Great Collapse.
-[ALL gasp]
-[KOTETSU] No way! A second one?
[TSUBAKI]
They can do that?
[YURI]
In preparation for it,
my father moved a number
of large machines
out of our research lab.
What kind of machines?
[YURI] I wish I knew.
And where were they sent to?
I'm sorry. I'm not sure.
It's fine.
Knowing the Foundation's plan
is a huge step.
You did good.
But if they cause
another Great Collapse,
doesn't that mean
we're gonna be turned
into those monsters?
Don't be deceived
by their falsehoods.
You're simply trying
to incite needless worry
so we fall into your trap.
-Aren't you?
-[YURI] No, I'm not!
I already told you.
Yuri is on our side now.
We can trust her.
Definitely. She did save
my life after all.
Let's investigate immediately.
You'll all regret this.
Just you wait.
[YURI]
Everyone sure is friendly.
Yeah, they are.
And now Kurokami and her friends
are going to be helping
us out as well.
It's all thanks to you.
Saving Kotetsu
made this possible.
You've done so much for us.
Mm.
I just wanted to help.
And if I can continue
to be of use, I will.
Yuri.
[wind blowing]
[CHIHIRO]
So, did you bring it?
[YURI]
Yes, but...
[CHIHIRO]
I want to remember. Please.
[YURI] There's no need to rush.
You can take your time.
[CHIHIRO]
The only memories I have left
are built on despair.
And if I want a new future,
then I'll need something
that gives me more support.
You said my mother
caused all this.
And, you know what?
Maybe you're right.
But still, if she set
everything into motion,
maybe that's why
we were reunited.
It was because of her.
You really think so?
And I'm glad.
You gave me the strength
to face things head on.
I have hope and courage
because of you.
Chihiro.
Finally, there's a chance
to regain what was lost.
I can see my fate
beginning to change.
I know it.
The Tempest, huh?
[YURI] Your mother was
the one who gave this to me.
It was the first thing
that came to mind
while looking for keepsakes.
It happens to be
my favorite play.
Just when everything
seems hopeless,
they all find a way
to be happy in the end.
[inhales deeply]
"As you from crimes
would pardoned be,
let your indulgence
set me free."
Those are the last lines.
[MAN]
Why'd you leave?
Tell me why.
Why?
Mitsuki.
Why won't you come home to me?
I need you.
Why? Why?
Why can't you come back?
Did you abandon me?
-[CHIHIRO whimpers]
-[MAN] Why? Why?
You left me.
Why? Why?
-Why? Why? Why?
-[CHIHIRO gasping]
[MAN]
Why did you kill your father?
[CHIHIRO]
I...
[CHIHIRO gasps]
Report on the AVAL
Science Foundation.
They've acquired some properties
in the city by force.
Numerous vehicles
have been coming and going.
They could be transporting
the machines
that Yuri Shiraki
mentioned before.
I'm going to get
a closer look.
Signing off.
How awful.
Uh...
This is...
[groaning]
Somehow they're
artificially creating barriers.
Imagine if there
are machines like this
on all the properties the
Foundation acquired recently.
If my hunch
proves correct, then...
Who's there?
Uh...
Quite beautiful,
don't you agree?
Feel honored I'm offering this
ultimate requiem in your name.
[groans]
Are you okay, Chihiro?
What happened to me?
I'm not entirely sure.
You touched the book
and collapsed.
Oh, right.
Did you remember anything?
-Not yet.
-I see.
It was worth a shot.
Sorry.
[gasps]
Wait a second!
I had a new dream.
Pluto!
[roars]
By my hand, I'll shatter
the demon's night...
and illuminate
the paths of darkness.
And now, Death has arrived.
Death has truly arrived.
[MARIE chuckles]
Don't think you've won just yet.
You underestimate my familiar.
Pluto!
Bringing a swift death
unto the undying.
Such is the nature
of the reaper's scythe.
You'll pay!
Tokotsu!
I shall sing your praises.
Death is kind to all!
You can't reach me from there.
[groans]
Death has arrived indeed.
[CHIHIRO]
Where's Kurokami?
[TSUBAKI] We can't seem
to get a hold of her.
She probably got
what she deserved.
Deceived by the enemy
until the very end.
Guess the Guardian State
isn't so special.
Be quiet!
Come on!
Didn't she tell you
where she was investigating?
Hey! Don't yell at me!
You can listen to her
last message yourself.
[grunts]
If she's in trouble,
it's all your fault.
Look, Chihiro.
Huh...
[KAKIHARA]
Kurokami!
What happened?
Who did this to you? Tell me!
This is...
Wait, did you
discover something?
[chuckles]
[whispering, indistinct]
[KAKIHARA]
Kurokami!
Marie, no!
She's gone.
As I expected.
One step closer
to fulfilling Chaos' plan.
This is what you wanted,
isn't it, Yuri?
[gasps]
But I didn't--
[SHOKO]
Kurokami was foolish enough
to believe in your words
and died
without even realizing
she'd been lied to.
No, you're wrong!
Yuri would never--
[clapping]
[YURI]
Father?
Splendid work.
I'm so proud of you, daughter.
So it really was you!
Wait! No, I--
[GRUMMAN]
She was just doing her job.
Now, time to come home, Yuri.
She's not going with you!
She's staying right here!
Now, now.
You must realize
the best place for you
is by your father's side.
Can't you see that?
You don't belong
with their kind anymore.
[SHOKO] He's right.
You can go home with him, Yuri.
Just hang on!
There must be some mistake!
I don't see one.
Kurokami told us that
she wanted to trust you.
In the end, she did.
And look where
that faith in you got her!
I'm telling you the truth.
Please believe me!
Yuri didn't betray her!
How blind can you be?
Marie was a really good person.
She didn't deserve this fate.
[sobs]
Kotetsu.
Don't keep me waiting.
Come along.
Everyone.
Listen. She didn't--
Yuri. Please, come back!
No.
Don't leave with them!
Don't go!
Stop and think about this!
You can't.
Hmm.
[GRUMMAN]
Insolent child!
Did you actually believe that
you could leave your own father?
Even with the death of one
of the Heroic Lineage.
I will never forgive you
for betraying me!
Listen closely.
That place is important
to me and Mitsuki,
you understand?
I'll tell you this once,
you are not permitted there!
[dripping]