Kotetsu!
[groaning]
We're out of time!
You have to remember!
Even with blood armaments,
he's still so weak.
[YURI]
But he's only just awakened.
Finish him!
[roaring]
I wasn't strong enough.
[CHIHIRO]
I don't want to lose anyone.
Not ever again!
What?
-[swords clang]
-[MONSTER screeches]
Wait. What are you doing?
I'm in control. Don't worry.
[KOTETSU]
Chihiro.
[MONSTER growling]
[KOTETSU]
I don't think I can walk.
It's the Diabolos' weapon.
-The spear poisoned you.
-Poisoned?
How can we cure him?
You have to say
my name out loud.
-What good'll that do?
-[MONSTER growling]
Hurry up!
Fine! You're Eiko Morizono!
No! Call me by my real name!
[roaring]
Please, remember!
You should know by now!
Don't you know who I really am?
Your name. It's Cerdid.
About time!
[CHIHIRO]
Who are you?
Leave Kotetsu in my care.
They have a defender.
That's just perfect.
I'll say this
about your beloved.
He's making our lives difficult.
Please don't.
[growling]
-[KOTETSU] Nice going.
-Hey!
You're walking!
How do you feel?
Better.
[chuckles]
-[camera shutter clicking]
-[CHIHIRO grunting]
[screeches]
I promised I wouldn't.
Impressive! You killed
that Diabolos with one blow.
-Don't start.
-Huh?
Those were university students,
no different than me,
and now they're dead.
You did what you had to.
I've had it up to here
with you!
Stop using that excuse.
It's my fault!
I understand how you feel,
but once someone becomes
a familiar,
there's simply no changing them
back to their original form.
You have to kill them.
Even if you're right,
-I don't want to.
-[camera shutter clicks]
[CHIHIRO gasps]
Not you again.
So the urban legends
are true, huh?
It's kind of hard to believe.
But how can a journalist
doubt his own eyes.
Right, Tsubasa?
What I'm seeing
is a huge scoop.
The dots are all starting
to connect.
Domyoji transforms,
then you kill him.
Afterwards, the body vanishes.
-No proof.
-[CHIHIRO gasps]
[CHIHIRO]
No. I didn't mean to.
-I just--
-Kid.
We all know
murder is your forte.
[KOTETSU]
Stop it!
Chihiro saved our lives!
Did he or did he not
kill your father?
The truth hurts, but the sooner
you accept it, the--
[gasps]
[growling]
Not again.
I can summon all day
if I need to
as long as I have humans
I can use to open gates.
[BOTH gasp]
How could you? Bastard!
The Lineage must die,
and I'll do whatever it takes.
-[snaps fingers]
-[chiming]
[KOTETSU]
Look out!
[EIKO]
Chihiro!
His blood armaments
protected him.
It's been empowered!
No way.
Stop! I'll take you on!
You haven't fully healed
from the poison yet!
Kill him.
[roars]
[groans, whimpers]
What's wrong?
Tsubasa, are you okay?
My head hurts.
Could it be?
He's lost control.
Hurry up and end it!
Astonishing, but still.
He mustn't.
If he uses his power this way,
his body won't last.
So what do we do?
[whimpering]
Your skin! What the...
Please, Kakihara, help me.
But how? I don't understand
what's happening!
[JUN] Not even an empowered
Diabolos can defeat him.
Just how much power
do you suppose is hiding
within that Vessel?
Dammit!
I don't know
what the hell I should do.
[WOMAN]
I suggest awakening.
[KAKIHARA]
Where did you come from?
There's only one way
to save her.
Use the Heroic Blood in you.
I'll do anything!
Whatever it takes to help her.
Please! Tell me how
to save Tsubasa!
Call out her name.
Not Tsubasa.
The one that's engraved in
the memory of your Heroic Blood.
Uh...
Her name's Aero.
But-- You're Tsubasa.
Not anymore.
[KOTETSU]
Wait, Kakihara, too?
[YURI]
A Vessel of Heroic Lineage.
Now there's three of 'em?
Heroic Blood calls out
to its own kind.
I wasn't prepared for this.
[roaring]
[yelling]
[screeches]
We'll cut our losses.
At least kill Chihiro!
[roaring]
[groans, screams]
Time to leave.
Yeah. We have no other choice.
Let's go and report this.
[groaning in pain]
You were too reckless.
Fighting that way
consumes a lot of blood.
You're lucky you didn't die.
[groaning]
[panting]
[CHIHIRO]
Who are you?
My name is Shoko Hanashima.
To meet a Vessel
of Heroic Lineage,
it's a privilege.
Chihiro!
[KOTETSU]
You're the Lord of Creations.
Hmm.
-[CHIHIRO groans]
-Easy now.
What on earth
just happened to me?
You lost control.
[CHIHIRO]
I did?
[SHOKO]
It's your own fault.
Jumping in the middle
of a fight
when you didn't even know
how to use your abilities.
Do you know
how dangerous that was
given the level of power
you can wield?
Chihiro Kamina! I know
you're responsible for this!
Turn her back to normal!
[EIKO]
Let go of him!
[KAKIHARA]
What did you do to Tsubasa?
Huh?
She can't change back, Kakihara.
What did you say?
Now that she's a familiar,
she can't become human
ever again.
You're a liar.
Give her back to me!
-As I've already stated--
-[KOTETSU] Chihiro!
Come quick!
-[groaning]
-[CHIHIRO] Ikuro?
[SHOKO] It appears he couldn't
transform into a familiar.
Tsubasa's lucky.
There was a chance she could
have ended up like him.
-How is she lucky?
-That's enough, you two!
Save him!
You can't leave him this way!
[INUKI]
Maybe I can help.
Why are you here, Doctor?
[SHOKO] It's all right.
Inuki is one of us.
One of you?
I know you must
find this confusing.
Please come with me.
[KOTETSU]
Where to?
The Maldeus Church.
[SHOKO] I welcome you
to our sacred stronghold.
The Maldeus Church is home
to the Heroic Lineage
who fight against Chaos.
And what is Chaos?
As the name suggests,
they're the forces that seek
to plunge the world
into darkness.
We are tasked
with stopping them.
Mmm, okay, you lost me again.
More importantly,
where's Tsubasa?
Aero is being examined
over at the hospital.
Cerdid is with her now, so you
have nothing to worry about.
[chuckles]
Right, Aero.
Hanashima, time to tell us
what's going on.
You can't avoid it any more.
Our leader will provide you
with the answers you seek.
Your leader, huh?
[footsteps]
[DUX] "We are such stuff
as dreams are made on."
"Yea, all which it inherit
shall dissolve,
and like this
insubstantial pageant faded."
[KOTETSU]
Where'd she come from?
[CHIHIRO]
No way.
Is that...
Welcome,
Vessels of Heroic Blood.
You may call me Dux.
It is her.
Wait, you mean
you know this girl?
I met her in a dream once.
A dream?
Dreams are mirrors
through which we peer
into other worlds.
Hello, Chihiro Kamina.
So we meet again.
Impossible.
[KAKIHARA scoffs]
I tagged along
for some answers
and what do I find?
Just some blindfolded bimbo
with a Shakespeare fetish.
Silence, blasphemer!
The only tool I require to share
the truth is this mouth.
Am I wrong?
I admit you got a point.
Judging someone off appearance
isn't very professional of me.
[SHOKO]
No smoking inside the church.
We want to know.
Why the hell's this crazy stuff
happening to us?
Everything is destiny.
[CHIHIRO]
That's not an answer!
It begins in the near future.
In 40 years,
this world will cease to exist.
[ALL gasp]
That's end-of-days nonsense.
Why am I not surprised?
[DUX] You asked me for
the truth, and I'm telling you.
[KOTETSU]
I think I get it.
You're saying
those monsters are invaders,
and we have to stop them, right?
[DUX]
You can't stop them.
Destruction is inevitable,
and a new world will begin.
[KOTETSU] Huh?
What kind of future is that?
[DUX]
The act of creation is painful.
Eliminating the antiquated
is necessary.
I still don't understand
what this has to do with us.
[DUX] The new world will either
be born from hope or chaos.
The vessels of Heroic Blood
hold the key that will decide.
It is up to you.
-The three of us?
-[KAKIHARA chuckles]
And what exactly are
the Vessels of Heroic Blood?
When destruction
finally arrives,
a hero named the
Lord of Vermilion will appear.
They will create a new world
overflowing with hope.
The Vessels of Heroic Blood
are those with the capacity
to become
this legendary figure.
The Lord of Vermilion.
If this chosen one is not born,
the world will be ruled
by Chaos.
There'll be war,
poverty, sickness.
Terrible things will happen,
and the Earth will sink
into despair.
Lady, not even
the tabloids would buy
the delusions
you're trying to sell us.
[DUX] I thought what you saw
with your eyes was the truth.
People became monsters,
and your dear assistant
changed into a familiar.
Were those delusions?
The ones who transformed my dad.
Who are they?
They are Agents of Chaos.
[rattling, clanging]
We've got three Vessels
wide awake and running around.
And you're saying that all three
of them have aligned themselves
with the Maldeus Church?
It would appear that way.
[MAN] Those fanatics
only have one goal.
Destroy the world.
Then build their vision
of paradise atop the rubble.
What else do we know?
Eh, Van Drayle.
Well, they operate
off the belief
the apocalypse will arrive
in 40 years.
So of course
it's going to happen.
After all, they're the ones
who'll be pulling the trigger.
And yet,
they've also been claiming
a world full of hope is
in the realm of possibility.
Sophistry.
The only way this utopia
of which they speak
could be born
is through utter destruction.
The foundation of this new order
must be stopped.
We will put an end
to the Heroic Lineage.
The world must be saved.
And we have the science
to prevent its destruction.
Death to the Heroic Lineage.
[KOTETSU] They're responsible
for the Great Collapse?
Correct.
And because this event occurred,
creatures from other worlds
are now able to cross over
into this one.
By using human beings
as a kind of gateway, right?
I don't believe this.
[DUX]
Tokyo's become a hunting ground,
overflowing with monsters
created solely
to capture and murder
the Heroic Lineage.
Okay, but what do we do?
[DUX] Survive. That's
the only thing that matters.
Against those things?
Easier said than done!
There is a way.
You must destroy Tokyo.
[ALL gasp]
[DUX]
Once the city is gone,
they won't be able to open
any more gates.
Sacrifice your home...
to save the future.
Chihiro!
Tsubasa? When'd you
turn back to normal?
-I was worried sick!
-[TSUBASA] Huh?
Tsubasa?
My name's Aero.
[EOKI] Only her appearance
has been restored.
She is no longer the person
you once knew.
I don't understand.
What I'm saying is we're both
Defenders of the Heroic Lineage.
We arrived here
during The Great Collapse.
But if that's true,
When you showed up at the dojo,
you were already...
[EOKI]
Cerdid, yes.
I merely pretended
to be Morizono.
Then whatever happened
to the real Eiko?
You're lying!
Even after the red mist,
Tsubasa never acted differently
until today!
Some of us have been awake
since the very beginning.
Others were asleep
and completely unaware,
like Aero.
But she was finally revived,
thanks to the waves
created by Chihiro.
You did this?
I should've known.
Of course you're
the one to blame.
How many people
do you have to kill
before you're satisfied?!
If it wasn't for you...
Turn her back!
Give my Tsubasa
back to me now!
[KOUME]
Will you shut up?
Keep on yelling and I'll throw
your asses outta here!
I'm sorry for the inconvenience,
but I'm--
Just tell me where
I can find Tsubasa.
All I can say for now
is she's nowhere.
You mean she's dead?
Not even we know
the answer to that.
The fate of those we switch with
remains unknown.
[KAKIHARA] You're going
to leave me alone in this world?
Of all people.
You always asked me
the same question.
Why was it necessary
to stubbornly pursue Kamina?
But I never gave you
a straight answer, did I?
Is this all my fault then?
Did this happen 'cause
I wouldn't stop following him?
What am I saying?
Chihiro Kamina's to blame!
I will avenge you!
Until I get my answers
and everything becomes clear,
I'll hold on,
even if it kills me!
[CHIHIRO]
How is he?
[INUKI] His transformation
has been halted.
Poor Ikuro.
For quite a while now,
I've been taking in
people like your friend
who have partially merged
with creatures
from different worlds.
Can he be cured?
It's not like flipping on
a switch, you know.
Hold up.
You can help him, right?
You must know something.
Don't be ridiculous.
The only thing we know for sure
is that we were summoned
from beyond.
[INUKI]
By the Great Collapse?
Yes.
[INUKI] We've discovered
that humans have
an unidentified gene
within them.
It's known as the Arcana gene.
[CHIHIRO]
Never heard of it.
The eternal scientific question
we've never been able to answer
is "what makes up the soul?"
Apparently, this gene is related
to some spiritual quality.
You all possess the Arcana gene.
However, creatures
from other dimensions
and worlds do as well.
They resonate with one another.
When that resonance strengthens,
entities from different worlds
cross over to our dimension.
They use humans
with strong connections
to their Arcana genes,
turn them into gates
and enter into this world.
And if you're not
a complete idiot,
you can guess why.
Because of the Great Collapse.
While there are some
who can coexist
with their human forms,
similar to Cerdid and Aero,
those who cannot withstand
being used as gates
seem to vanish,
turning into a red mist.
Ikuro. He's not gonna vaporize
like the others, is he?
We'll keep treating him.
There's got to be a cure.
Who're wearing
the lab coats here?
Like he said,
we're working on it!
I'm so sorry.
[CHIHIRO]
Is this my fault?
Were you hurt just because
of your involvement with me?
[DUX]
And if that's true?
[gasps]
[DUX] There's a cloud
of death that follows you,
enveloping anyone
who gets close enough.
[echoing]
Ikuro!
[DUX]
Such a tragedy.
Everything disappears and
all that ever remains is you.
-Alone.
-Show yourself!
You can't deny
it's all your fault.
No way! I didn't want this!
Then what is that
you're gripping in your hand?
[screams]
[shatters]
[DUX]
It was the same back then.
Don't do this. Make it stop!
[DUX]
Yes.
Ever since that day, your hand
has been stained with blood.
[CHIHIRO]
Forgive me.
You seek salvation?
Even inevitable tragedies
are sometimes worthy
of thunderous applause.
That is,
as long as the tragedies
you invite have meaning.
[CHIHIRO]
What?
Though your hands
are stained with blood
and everything
around you is destroyed,
as long as
there is hope beyond it,
the blood you spill
will shape the future.
There's no running away
from your fate.
You can't escape.
If you insist
on seeking forgiveness...
you must choose.
Don't go! Dux, wait!
-Something wrong?
-Where did she go?
Huh?
Uh... Chihiro! You're bleeding!
[KOUME]
Of all the places
you could've injured yourself,
a hospital?
What? Hold on.
This isn't a wound.
At least it's not fresh.
Looks like it's from
a long time ago.
[grunts]
Don't touch me!
What's your problem?
Sorry. I overreacted.
Yeah. I'll say.
So long as it has meaning.
Right?
-What?
-[EOKI] Hmm?