[rumbling]
[glass breaking]
♪
Don't underestimate me.
I'm still an instructor.
Tsubaki! Show yourself!
I'm right here. Hey, Kotetsu!
[grunts]
Tsubaki is the winner!
It's the best
I could come up with.
[TSUBAKI groaning]
A smart move.
[AKIRA] Look!
I don't want to fight you, Haru!
You're not messing
around, Akira.
Maybe I should go all-out too!
A shame. It would've been nice
to run with you again.
[gasps]
[HARU] Huh?
[screaming]
[AKIRA]
Sorry, Haru.
I'm sorry,
but you can't beat Chiyu.
Spare me your bullshit
and just die!
[gasps]
As planned,
it had to end this way.
[groans]
Nothing changes.
We were and always
will be broken.
[BOTH grunt]
You nationalist dog!
[scoffs]
You're nothing but a mutt
sniffing around, yourself.
[grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[JUN]
Not bad. I'm impressed.
I see you're a strong as ever.
You know, that really hurts.
I figured. But look at me.
We both need healing.
[KARK]
Listen!
This is the sound
of your requiem!
I won't hold anything back.
You've betrayed
your own country!
[groaning]
Suruga!
My apologies.
That looked painful.
Oh!
[gasping]
The death god's scythe
reaches all.
None are immune.
[grunting]
[groans, gasps]
[KARK]
A secret arrow? Of course.
[KARK groans]
[JULIA groans]
[YURI]
Was this the only way?
[CHIHIRO]
Fate is a shadowy figure.
Chase after it,
and it runs.
Choose to run,
and it chases you.
So, does that mean we're evil?
Who can say?
I don't have the answer.
Can we escape this twisted fate?
[YURI]
I don't know that answer either.
[BOTH grunting]
Yuri.
My Chihiro.
[KOTETSU yelling]
[yelling]
That's enough!
[KOTETSU]
Gimme a break.
You always go for the kote.
Why not try
something else, Chihiro.
Go for the head.
A win is still win, Kotetsu.
[RAKAN]
Never complain about a loss.
It reveals your immaturity.
[KOTETSU]
Dad.
Take your observation to heart.
You can use your opponent's
strengths against him to win.
That's the essence
of good swordplay.
Just keep in mind
that in a real battle,
kote strikes won't help you.
You can't rely on them.
I'm not too worried.
-[RAKAN sighs]
-Rematch time, Chihiro!
You and me. Let's go!
Sorry, but you know
I have to get ready.
No fair! You can't quit now.
[CHIHIRO]
You want breakfast or don't you?
[RAKAN] I've no idea
what to do with him.
If only he'd change his mind.
I could spend the rest
of my years in easy retirement.
Mmm. Mmm.
Nothing beats your rolled
omelets after a practice!
You eat them like that's
the last food you'll ever have.
Like fluffy, delicious clouds.
What's the secret?
I bet you stir
the eggs a hundred times.
Actually, the trick is
to not stir them too much
and keep an eye on the heat.
[KOTETSU] You know what,
don't ruin the magic.
I just know I love ‘em.
[CHIHIRO] Why don't you try
learning to cook sometime?
What for? I have you.
What am I,
your wife or something?
Hey, a partnership's
not a bad idea!
We both take over the dojo.
You're the instructor.
I'm the assistant!
What do you think, Dad?
Hmm?
Personally, I prefer
soft-boiled eggs.
That's not what
we're talking about.
Great, then I'll make
soft-boiled eggs tomorrow.
[KOKETSU] If we're
gonna instruct students,
we'll need to set
an example for them.
You gotta be strong
or they won't respect you.
Smack ‘em on the head.
That's the only way.
Listen, when it comes to Kendo,
you're actually better.
[KOTETSU]
Huh? No. I am? Really?
Uh...
[grunts]
If that's true, how come
I haven't beaten you
in a match yet?
[KOTETSU]
Hey, Chihiro.
Are you seriously
gonna leave us?
[CHIHIRO]
Yeah, I think so.
[KOTETSU]
How come?
I mean, if there's
something wrong.
You know I don't have
anything to complain about.
Since you took me in,
I've felt nothing but gratitude
to you and your father.
He raised me like a son.
Even sent me to college. But...
[KOTETSU]
But what?
You know,
"To be or not to be."
Not Shakespeare again.
I want to hear
a real answer out of you.
I should have kept my mouth shut
and not said anything at all.
I'm not even sure
how long it's gonna be.
[KOTETSU] What's going
to happen to the dojo?
[sighs]
Is that the reason?
I was trying to figure out
why you were being
so persistent today.
That's part of it.
[CHIHIRO]
I haven't decided yet.
By the way,
please don't tell your dad.
Uh! Hey, wait for me!
-[CHIHIRO] Ikuro.
-[KOTETSU] Good morning!
It looks like we get
first period off.
[IKURO]
So, the cafeteria?
[CHIHIRO]
Nah, we've already eaten.
[IKURO] Yeah, that's great.
But I haven't.
Thursday mornings,
they serve ginger-fried pork.
And who's gonna
say no to that?
Sounds like a pretty
heavy breakfast to me.
Nope! I'm totally in!
-You didn't eat that long ago.
-Uh...
Besides, Chihiro and I
are the ones
who don't have to go to class.
So run along, first-year.
[KOTETSU grunts]
College is supposed to be
about socializing!
Don't be that way.
[high-pitched whine]
[grunts in pain]
[KOTETSU]
What is that?
I'm covering my ears,
but I can still hear it!
-[grunts]
-[GIRL screams]
[grunting in pain]
[CHIHIRO]
Ikuro!
[KOTETSU]
Please, Chihiro, help.
Kotetsu.
Just hang in there!
[groaning]
[cars honking]
[ALL groaning]
[high-pitch continues]
That sound.
[groaning]
-[WOMAN] "We are such stuff...
-[CHIHIRO gasps]
[WOMAN]
...as dreams are made on.”
“Yea, all which it inherit,
shall dissolve
"and like this
insubstantial pageant faded,
leave not a rack behind.”
"The Tempest," huh?
If you're quoting
from that play,
I'm guessing this reality
is nothing more than a dream.
Fate, continuously woven
from a thread
of intertwining good and evil.
What're you trying to say?
[WOMAN]
Don't you like it?
After all, these are the words
that dwell within you.
[chuckles]
Even theater can be a killjoy
if it's taken too far.
While I do enjoy Shakespeare,
I don't enjoy
hearing it so twisted.
[gasps]
[WOMAN]
Man of vermilion.
Heroic power resides
deep within your blood.
The king jailed on an island
across the sea
puts his subjects to work,
continuously searching
for answers.
I don't understand.
Just tell me who you are.
You can call me Dux.
Until the end of time,
we will repeat
this heroic scene
again and again.
In the words of nations
not yet known.
[CHIHIRO groans]
[gasps]
[WOMAN gasps]
Good news, Inuki!
The holdout's finally awake!
[INUKI] So, the Sleeping Prince
finally woke up.
Did you sneak him a magic kiss?
Did you?
[INUKI]
No sense of humor.
Check his consciousness levels.
[beeping]
[WOMAN]
Hey, hot stuff.
You're the very last one
to wake up.
You remember who you are,
don't you?
My, my name...
[WOMAN] Ugh, terrific.
Don't tell me you have amnesia.
Kamina. I'm Chihiro Kamina.
[WOMAN]
Whew. There's a relief.
That matches up with
what your student ID says.
Jokei University
second-year student,
-English department.
-Hold on.
What happened to the--
[grunts]
You don't interrupt someone
when they're talking!
That behavior is typically
considered impolite!
[INUKI]
You know what else is impolite?
Striking a patient.
Hey, don't take his side.
Could someone tell me
where I am?
The Jokei University Hospital.
I'm the staff physician,
Inuki Akaya.
This is Koume Sakiyama.
Sure, you have a title,
but I get nothing.
Well, Sleeping Prince,
now that you're up,
it is my duty to inform you
that you've been sleeping
for five months.
Five whole months?
That long?
Yeah, which is odd
since the majority of people
woke up within the first week.
Now, what did you dream about?
What?
Another world, for example.
Or maybe you imagined yourself
changing into something else.
[CHIHIRO]
I'm not sure. Why?
What's this all about?
[INUKI]
After the Great Collapse,
a large number of people woke up
and reported
having similar dreams.
What's "The Great Collapse"?
I could explain, but it'd be
easier if I showed you.
[gasping]
[CHIHIRO] This is...
This can't be real.
[INUKI] Tokyo is a little
different than you remember.
[CHIHIRO] Tell me what
happened while I was asleep.
[INUKI] Surely you heard that
noise before you passed out.
We don't know what it was.
But, wherever it came from,
survivors were affected
the same.
When we woke up,
this is what we found.
A giant plant sprouting up
from the city
and Tokyo enveloped
in an unexplained red mist.
We have no way of knowing
what happened
during the week we were out.
It's lost time.
That's "The Great Collapse"
in a nutshell.
It doesn't explain
what's going on.
What about the plant
and what's happened to Tokyo?
Will you shut up already?
You're just like your friend.
If you want to annoy someone,
try him instead.
[KOUME]
You can come in.
[KOTETSU]
You're okay! I was so worried.
They told me
I couldn't see you.
I'm sorry you got stuck with
the rudest nurse in the ward,
by the way.
I didn't quite catch that.
[KOTETSU]
If they ended up dissecting you,
I swore I'd avenge your death
before committing seppuku.
Exactly what era did you
step out of, sweater vest?
It's a good thing you woke up,
for your friend's sake.
I don't know if I could take
another day of him around.
Sorry.
For making you wait.
[CHIHIRO]
I can walk without any problem.
[KOTETSU]
Everyone's surprisingly healthy,
aside from the whole
passing out part.
When I learned I'd been asleep
for a week, I didn't believe it.
[clapping]
Congrats on your recovery.
But what took you so long?
-It's Kakihara. Great.
-This guy. What a pest.
Journalists
have a keen nose
when there's
a juicy story involved.
I can see the front page now:
“Post-Great Collapse,
the last comatose patient
finally awakens.”
Now there's a headline
that draws you in.
So why were you asleep
for five months?
Hey!
Are you some
kind of misery junkie?
Or maybe you
don't have any fun
unless you're the one
doing the killing yourself?
It may have been thirteen years,
but no one's forgotten.
All right,
you got your pictures!
Clear off already!
Why won't you stop
following Chihiro?
You make it sound criminal.
I'm just doing my job.
I uncover the facts
and then print them.
Including the truth about what
occurred all those years ago.
Buddy, if looks could kill.
Let's go, Tsubasa.
[REPORTER] Nearly five months
after "The Great Collapse,"
"Save Tokyo" demonstrations
are being held
in the capital of Osaka
as the public voices
their frustrations.
Meanwhile,
the Japanese government
has sent the special autonomous
district of Tokyo
food and medical assistance
totaling trillions of yen.
Special autonomous district?
That's what they're
calling the city now.
The red mist seems to be keeping
everybody from leaving it.
How far does it reach?
Well, take a look
out the window. See it?
I mean, there're clusters
of it all over the place,
but it encompasses
Tokyo entirely.
The red mist, huh?
I heard at first people
were able to get
in and out of the city, but--
[MAN] Now everyone
stays away from the mist.
At this point, we might
as well be treated
as our own island nation.
[KOTETSU]
By the time I woke up,
it was already like this.
It caused a lot of confusion,
obviously.
[MAN] We're stuck here,
but on the bright side,
power and water are still on.
You know what they say,
home's where you make it.
I've missed a lot.
[groaning]
You just got out
of the hospital.
I know you don't
want to hear this,
but you should get some rest.
I'll try.
Like I haven't gotten enough.
[CHIHIRO] It's the dojo.
What's going on?
Sir!
Aah! Oh.
What was that?
You okay?
[CHIHIRO panting]
Yeah.
How's your dad?
What do you mean?
Same old, no complaints.
[KOTETSU] Home sweet home.
How's it feel?
Strange, to be honest.
Like we left to go to school
just this morning.
[tone ringing]
-That noise.
-[BOTH groaning]
My...
My body feels like
it's burning up.
[tone continues]
[snapping, tone ringing]
He's the one
making the sound.
[explosion]
[BOTH groaning]
[roaring]
Dad, no.
[groaning]
[KAZAMA]
Run!
The instructor!
He-- [groans]
That thing is your dad?
Could someone tell me what
the hell's going on around here?
[roaring]
♪
Use this!
[roaring]
♪
[growling]
[RAKAN]
Kote strikes won't help you.
You can't rely on them.
Chihiro!
♪