[wind whooshing]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[energy crackling]
[screaming]
[SHOKO]
His overpower is incredible.
Because he's inexperienced,
the rate of growth
is precisely as expected.
What a delight he's chosen
to ally himself
with the Maldeus Church.
Even though he doesn't know
where the barrier is,
it doesn't really matter.
How'd it get to this?
I'm starting to see
why we were waiting around
with nothing to do
for the longest time.
The fact is we had
no one on our side
strong enough
to complete this mission.
Now, that's changed.
I won't stop!
[CHIHIRO]
If the cost of saving our future
is destroying Tokyo,
then so be it!
How long will you keep
dragging your feet?
At this point,
whether the barrier
is destroyed or not
is of little consequence.
What I can't comprehend is
why you continue
to let the church's
Heroic Lineage
do as they please?
It's not as though we don't have
the intel to strike.
The problem is
we've hit our limit.
We're at
a complete disadvantage
and especially weak in places
where gates can't be opened.
My question is when can we
expect them to help?
Careful, Jun.
You should know better than
to refer to them so casually.
Fine, then you won't mind us
finding reinforcements
while we're waiting.
We'll return shortly.
[MAN]
Yuri, wait.
Please forgive me.
Placing you in danger's
the last thing I ever wanted.
But try to see it
from my perspective.
You're the only one
who can save me.
There's nobody else.
Yes. I know, Father.
[MAN]
Good girl.
[SHOKO]
Today was a huge success for us.
These are fantastic results.
Barriers in two different
locations were destroyed,
and in record time.
Isn't he expending
too much power?
He hasn't grown
accustomed to it.
[CHIHIRO]
No. It's fine.
If my abilities can help.
We know barriers
have been erected around Tokyo.
There's only one way
to remove their influence.
Destroy what protects them.
The spiritual sites
that keep us
from toppling the barriers.
Kamina's power is an asset.
I don't believe we'd have
a chance without it.
Yeah. But come on.
Chihiro won't last
at the rate he's going.
The agents of Chaos won't stop.
They'll continue turning people
into gates to other worlds
unless we act.
Yeah, but...
[SHOKO] We have to take down
the remaining barriers.
Once they've all
been eliminated,
Tokyo will crumble on its own.
Only then will we
be able to stop
further atrocities
from happening.
[CHIHIRO] We have to prevent
any more causalities.
-[CHIHIRO groans]
-[KOTETSU] Chihiro!
Are you okay?
I've been having this dream.
Huh?
I'm afraid if we ease off,
someone else will fall victim.
And the thought of that,
I can't stand it.
Until we get rid
of the barriers,
the future will never be safe.
But do you really think
that will...
Are you willing
to sacrifice yourself?
If so, you need rest.
Doctor's orders.
Can you see him to his room?
I wish I could accompany you,
but Sakiyama's waiting for me
back at the hospital.
Sure.
[INUKI] Let me know
if anything comes up.
[EIKO]
I'll get his bed ready.
[KAKIHARA]
Did you have fun?
Just what we needed.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Why don't you get
your facts straight?
[blows]
I think I'm right on the money,
given his history
of violent tendencies.
[KOTETSU]
You never quit!
He's doing this to help, not
because he wants destruction!
[scoffs]
I'm sure he's volunteering
out of the goodness
of his heart,
not for catharsis.
Is demolishing a city enough
or do you have
to personally kill someone?
Got it all figured out, huh?
You're a Vessel of Heroic Blood.
Join us on a mission
and see if you're right!
You believe he's doing this
for the greater good?
Maybe he's got you fooled, kid,
but I'm not getting sucked
into his death cloud.
[splash]
[CHIHIRO gasping]
[EIKO]
Are you feeling all right?
[breathing heavily]
I'm not so sure.
[EIKO]
What's wrong?
[AKIRA] Slow down, Haru!
Where are you going?
[HARU] It finally happened!
The head's recognized me!
He said tonight I'd get
to prove my strength.
No way! Are you talking
about that biker gang?
-Don't tell me you're still--
-They're not bikers!
The group's called Blue Skull,
and they're on the right side
of history!
-Hey, it's nearly time for...
-[clattering]
Uh... You okay?
-[grunting]
-[door opens, closes]
Inuki! I'm here.
How can I help?
[groans]
-Need medicine.
-Huh.
Let's not do this tonight. Okay?
Hate to ask this,
but will you be all right
going by yourself?
Without you?
Afraid so.
We can't afford to have
the both of us stay behind.
I have a feeling
they'll need you.
[engine revving]
[giggles]
She who controls information
has control over all things.
Second summer president
Tsubaki the Red,
aka Manazuru, is on her way!
[breathes deeply]
-What are they doing here?
-Jun.
Huh. Wait!
[screams]
[BOTH grunting]
There are no people around!
Try summoning monsters now!
[KOTETSU screams]
[JUN]
That won't be necessary.
You can't just
charge in like that.
Wait for backup!
[grunts]
[KOTETSU screams]
Kotetsu!
The barrier! Go take it out!
[KOUME grunts]
Gonna need cover, Koume!
Kamina!
Right, they have a defender.
What the hell
are those two doing here?
Damn it!
[CHIHIRO]
Who are you? Answer me!
[scoffs]
This boy is a novice.
Stop hesitating and hit him!
Finally, this is getting
more entertaining.
Yeah? Well, you can tell me
all about it
when you're in the ICU.
-No. He's mine.
-[motorcycle engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[TSUBAKI]
I have arrived!
And you are?
Wait, let me guess.
A newbie. Too bad.
I'm afraid I can't waste time
on small fries like you.
I'm after the head.
You know. The boss.
You're one of them, aren't you?
[thunder rumbling]
[CHIHIRO]
The barrier.
[CHIHIRO screaming]
Don't resist.
[straining]
Stay out of my way!
[gasps]
Take this!
[grunts]
[gasps]
What. Where am I?
This place. Are we...
[YURI]
This isn't a place.
If I had to guess,
I'd say...
we're in a memory.
What the...
They vanished.
Chihiro.
Hey, wait!
[KOUME screams, grunts]
What did you do to her?
You think I know
what's going on?
[TSUBAKI giggles]
You're not able
to summon here, are you?
What do you mean?
You can still hold your own.
Looks like I gotta pull out
all the stops.
Go, Densuke!
[KOTETSU grunts]
What the...
[YURI] Wandering aimlessly
won't help you
[CHIHIRO]
Yet you're following me.
Or maybe you're plotting
something back there?
If you won't answer
my questions, just keep quiet.
[YURI] Do you think
what you're doing is right?
[CHIHIRO]
What'd I just say?
If you know the way out,
tell me already.
No, wait. We're talking
about destroying Tokyo.
Do you think
it's the right choice?
Not like you care,
but I have to save everyone.
Everyone meaning who?
What about all the people
who are still living in Tokyo?
If you destroy the barriers,
then the city
will crumble to dust.
Most of the population
won't survive.
Does killing innocent people
mean nothing to you?
[CHIHIRO] What about you?
Turning people into gates.
[gasps]
Ending despair is immoral
but what you do is okay?
You turned them into monsters.
Ikuro. Kotetsu's dad.
You're responsible.
Not anymore.
I'm putting a stop to it.
[KOUME] Now would be a great
time to reappear, Kamina.
-What.
-[KOUME grunts]
Chihiro's Arcana.
I can't detect it anywhere.
[CHIHIRO] This fog.
I don't know where the exit is.
Maybe it's better
if we don't escape.
You want to die in here,
be my guest.
I wouldn't be opposed to it.
As long as I'm with you.
It's the best possible scenario.
We wouldn't have to fight,
and we'd both be saved.
[CHIHIRO]
Would you shut up?
It's not like
you'd ever understand.
[YURI]
Then tell me.
There's no salvation.
No matter where you look.
But, if somehow,
I can eventually find redemption
through fighting,
well, for me, that'll be enough.
The world's made of despair.
So who cares if it ends up
being destroyed?
Or if I'm the one who does it?
No one would miss this planet.
Was the world made
of despair and nothing else?
Let's become allies.
[CHIHIRO]
Huh?
[YURI]
If you're interested,
we can join forces
and change the world.
What are you saying?
I'm saying let's leave
this place together.
I'll vouch for you.
I understand.
In other words, you knew
how to get out
the entire time, huh?
[screaming]
-[JUN grunts]
-[glass shatters]
[screaming]
[groans]
[grunts]
I got her!
Didn't even see me!
So, have I proven myself?
Yeah, good job, Haru.
[HARU laughing]
Woo-hoo!
You just signed
your death certificate.
[CHIHIRO] If you're going
to keep playing games,
I'm walking away.
Don't follow me!
[YURI]
Wrong direction.
Come on.
[KOTETSU grunting]
[giggles]
Are you ready
to plead for mercy?
Like I hell I am!
I'm not losing to someone
who turns people into gates!
[TSUBAKI]
Gates?
You're dumber than you look!
What do you take me for?
An agent of Chaos!
-Yes.
-What?
Hold on. Are you saying you're
not working alongside Chaos?
No. You aren't either?
Talk about a comedy of errors!
Not like all this was my fault!
Anyone could have made
the same mistake!
[KOTETSU]
That's what you call this?
But just so you know,
if we kept fighting,
I would've won.
Catch you later!
Huh.
[YURI]
This is the center.
I knew its location was
the same as in the real world.
Deep within this rock,
a tremendous amount
of power is stored.
So much, that we were summoned
to a place that doesn't exist.
Which means, if we channel
an equal amount into it,
that should allow us to return.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[screaming]
Not like that.
Don't get in my way.
I can do this by myself.
If we entered using my strength,
we can get out the same way.
Isn't that what you said?
[YURI] Blasting it
without control won't work.
I can't change anything
from in here!
I have to destroy Tokyo.
Stop the future.
End despair!
Stop it!
Don't release your power
through force alone.
Imagine the energy
impacting the target,
then control the flow.
[grunting]
That's it.
Now concentrate your power
onto a single point.
Search for the resonance
in the beam.
[CHIHIRO grunting]
[rain pattering]
[groaning]
[distant clanging]
Wait, don't go.
[YURI] It's all because
of your mother.
What?
Who are you?