[GRUMMAN] You did well,
given the tight schedule.
Now that it's complete,
the Infinity Theater will become
a new symbol
of hope for Tokyo's future.
[FOREMAN]
Having Kaburagi Kark perform
at the unveiling ceremony
is rather extravagant.
The AVAL Science Foundation
is always striving
to bring joy and fulfillment
to the masses.
I trust his beautiful tones
will be able to reach everyone
who is in attendance?
A parting gift from my heart
to their ears.
It's really him.
Oh. By the way, Mr. Grumman.
What do you have planned
for this giant trapdoor
built into the stage?
Hmm.
This is
the ultimate performance.
So it requires
the ultimate spectacle.
Even now, I can hear
the sweet sound.
This is where the ending
will take place.
Individual notes
strumming together,
resulting in the awakening
of a new soul!
Smashing the vermilion
and offering up a requiem
that is fit for a king.
[motorcycle engine revving]
I did my best.
But I'm sorry to say,
Akira's the only one who's up
for joining our cause.
We thank you.
Both of you. Welcome.
Do you really know what
the Foundation's intentions are?
Yeah. Thanks to Kurokami
and Kakihara.
[TSUBAKI] I can't believe
he's dead, too.
For the longest time,
I hated that man.
He was always hounding Chihiro.
Turns out he was good.
It's not fair.
Our fight's far from over.
They forged the path.
Now the rest is in our hands.
We're going to put a stop
to Chaos's plans.
And survive, no matter what.
[SHOKO] I'm surprised a member
of the Guardian State
wants to work with us.
After what happened
to Marie Kurokami,
I would have figured
that they'd had enough.
Really?
You're bringing that up now?
Akira and I both know
she acted on her own free will.
And we're doing
the exact same thing.
It has nothing to do
with the Guardian State.
[CHIHIRO]
Yeah? Well, right now,
we need all the help we can get.
I'm sure you do.
The six installed machines
are projecting barriers
around each other,
making them impossible
to destroy.
And once this Big Dipper
is completed,
there will be
a Second Great Collapse.
Your chances of surviving
afterward are practically zero.
Then we just have
to stop them
before they connect
to the final one.
According to the information
Kakihara left me,
the last machine
will be installed
at the recently completed
Infinity Theater.
The performance hall
was built by AVAL.
-That puts any doubt to rest.
-[SHOKO giggles]
Kakihara was useless
when he was alive,
but in the end,
he actually helped us out.
-[CHIHIRO] You find that funny?
-What's this?
I figured his death would
bring you some sense of relief.
At long last, the nuisance
who kept digging
into your past is gone.
Don't start.
Before he died,
Kakihara told me to live.
The same as Inuki.
I'm going to fulfill their wish!
It's good to hear.
That you'll swing your blade,
and without
the slightest bit of hesitation.
Even if Yuri Shiraki is among
the enemies you'll be facing.
You need to work
on your motivational speeches.
Ignore her.
Nothing's going to make me quit.
I promise.
I'll change fate
with my own hands.
It's time.
Gentlemen, the Second
Great Collapse is upon us.
While the plan we've adopted
with Kark is infallible,
we still can't let
our guard down.
The final battle.
What about Yuri?
[GRUMMAN]
She is of no use to us.
Speaking of dead weight,
what about you-know-who?
Guess they're saving
their strength?
[DRAYLE laughs]
How disappointing
if they turn out to be
even more useless than Yuri.
You're talking about Chiyu,
my masterpiece.
Don't you dare compare
the two of them.
[DRAYLE]
Oh-ho! Scary.
Even your own daughter, huh?
Meaning?
You're so eager to abandon
your experimental subjects.
-Without a second thought.
-My test subjects?
[GRUMMAN chuckles]
I'm not in the habit
of remembering my failures.
If you don't want
to be scrapped,
you'd better show me
how useful you can be too.
Give me the chance.
Let me kill Chihiro Kamina.
You'll be defending
the other six locations.
But that's absurd!
If the Heroic Lineage wants
to destroy the last machine,
Kamina's guaranteed
to show up!
Grumman. This doesn't make
any sense!
-I want some answers!
-[DRAYLE laughing]
[DRAYLE]
He really doesn't get it.
I'll spell it out for you.
One of us might
ignore protecting
the artificial keystone.
Especially if they're
more preoccupied
with exacting their revenge.
My decision is final
and not up for debate.
[HARU]
Hold on, Jun! Wait up!
[JUN] That may have been
the only chance I had.
I should've killed you
the moment you stood in my way.
Chihiro Kamina would be dead,
and I could move on.
Instead I let you both live
because of my own weakness.
-Jun, wait!
-[JUN] Don't follow me.
This is your fault!
You've been talking
with Chihiro, right?
Then, lure him out of hiding
so Jun can finish him off!
Haru. I can't.
Don't you care about Jun at all?
What about how he feels?
[TSUBAKI humming]
[horn honks]
Head band!
Hey. I gotta admit,
that's pretty bold of you
coming here without any backup.
Or drive off, that's cool.
-Hmm?
-[KOTETSU] What's it mean?
[SHOKO] They're transporting
the artificial keystone
on the same day as the concert.
Chances are...
They're trying to create
the Second Great Collapse.
-[KOTETSU] We gotta stop it!
-Question.
He works for Chaos,
so why's he helping us?
A trap, obviously.
Maybe they're issuing
some kinda challenge.
Daring us to try and stop them.
[TSUBAKI]
Then they've underestimated us.
Yeah they did! Let's get 'em!
It won't be that simple.
Why is that?
[CHIHIRO]
It's a concert.
There'll be a lot of people
in attendance.
An audience. You mean...
Chaos is using them as hostages.
If we charge inside, they'll
transform them into monsters.
[KOTETSU]
That's messed up.
[SHOKO] If the Second
Great Collapse occurs,
Tokyo will be turned
into a hell, swirling with evil.
Sacrifices will have to be made.
You make it sound so casual.
[CHIHIRO]
Let's go.
You agree with her?
Chihiro, the hostages.
We know they use
some kind of sound.
A resonance that forces
people to transform.
With a full house,
they'll most likely use
Kark's piano music
as the source.
We'll have to take him out
before he plays.
I see.
Great idea, Chihiro!
That might actually work!
[CHIHIRO]
There's no other way.
But one mistake and countless
people will end up dying.
What are my choices?
What can I do?
Is this the right answer?
[DUX]
Who will be the next to die?
[CHIHIRO] You can even appear
in people's dreams?
[DUX] Dreams?
You still don't understand.
[CHIHIRO]
I guess I don't.
[giggles]
You foolishly believed
that you could alter fate.
Yet Kurokami and Kakihara
are both gone.
Expectations cause suffering.
[CHIHIRO]
I'm not giving up yet.
You'll have to put
an end to Kark.
This is the first time
you've desired
the death
of another person.
Murderous intent.
And you used to find
the thought
of staining your hands
with blood detestable.
You've changed.
[CHIHIRO]
I won't ask for forgiveness.
I'm choosing to do this
of my own volition.
This is my decision.
You sound confident
in your choice.
[CHIHIRO]
I'm not afraid anymore.
I can do it.
[indistinct chatter]
[buzzing, pulsing]
You shouldn't have come.
And you shouldn't be here
on guard duty.
You're fine with this?
You have your orders,
I have mine.
Go back to your post.
Tonight. Kamina will be there.
-I told them about our plan.
-You what?
I had to!
At this rate, you won't be
yourself anymore!
-Leave me.
-Just know--
I believe in you.
[MAN 1] It'll be starting soon.
Everything look good?
The audience have taken
their seats.
[MAN 2]
Let's sneak inside and listen.
We can't, idiot.
Jun's not here tonight.
No slackin' off.
Check it out!
[MAN 2] Huh? Are those people?
Th-They're flying!
Seems we have
uninvited guests.
[MAN 1]
Kaburagi Kark?
[chuckles]
The fools.
[ALL screaming]
What are you doing to...
[groans]
Densuke, go!
[roaring]
[KOUME]
Don't walk away from us!
[AUDIENCE applauding]
-[TSUBAKI] Densuke!
-[KOTETSU] Tsubaki!
My hero!
[grunts, screams]
Damn you!
Haru?
Akira? You're with them?
Enough. Stop this.
[grunts]
As long as Chihiro
keeps breathing,
Jun will never be able
to move on with his life!
Will you listen to me?
Apasionado.
[music increases in tempo]
[screaming]
[grunting]
Uh!
[HARU]
What the...
It was some kind of illusion?
Kark!
[CHIHIRO] We need
a single surprise attack.
It's the only way to stop Kark
before he kills the audience.
So what do you have?
Look at this.
Transform, Elsbernd.
Remember me?
You're mine, finally.
I won't let
anyone else kill you!
Why? Of all times, why now?
Jun Aoi.
You're an uninvited guest
as well.
But I shall allow it for now.
[music continues]
Bastard!
I don't have time to fight you!
Your death will be
by my hands!
No one else
will have your blood!
Die! Die! Die!
You made it!
Did Kark already...
I'm afraid
that we're too late.
We failed.
[KARK]
The concert is at its climax.
The sound calls to you
from the bottom of a deep abyss.
Sing, play, and exalt.
Death has arrived for all.
-Not good. What now?
-We got problems!
They're innocent!
You can't do this!
Death has arrived!
Feel its glorious crescendo!
[CHIHIRO]
Stop this. Now!
[KARK]
Death has arrived.
[roaring]
What is that?
[grunts]
Chihiro!
That's what I wanted.
How I've longed to see your face
twisted and filled with despair.
I will never give up.
I made a promise to Inuki.
As long as you never quit,
your wishes will come true!
I'll save them.
Every one of them.
The future's not written
in the stars!
Make it your own!
[CHIHIRO]
He believed in me.
I can do this!
Let's see you
save yourself first!
What? How did you...
[chuckles]
Beautiful.
Did you see that?
Could he be
The Lord of Vermilion?
-[roaring]
-[TSUBAKI screams]
[KOTETSU]
Tsubaki!
[KOUME]
Chihiro can handle himself,
but we need to stop that thing
from getting outside!
Damn you!
[CHIHIRO] Inuki trusted me
with his dying wish!
[JUN groaning]
And I'm going to see it through!
Who are you?
You'll never be able
to defeat me!
[JUN]
It's no use. I can't win.
I couldn't even
stop you, brother.
Of course I don't
stand a chance.
Is that why you chose him
instead of me?
[KARK laughing]
What a fool.
The source of their armaments
is the blood.
Use too much
and you'll wind up dead.
Is this how it ends?
By his hands?
You're mine!
[groaning
[clapping hands]
Bravo!
You successfully drew out
the Lord of Vermilion's
abilities.
I am a generous man,
but did you actually think
I would let you take
his head as a trophy?
Sipario.
Jun Aoi, he's...
[KARK laughs]
The truth is,
the more wretchedly painted
the subject...
The more beautiful the death.
You're gonna die for that!
Shall I paint you too?
Uhh!
Akira.
Haru.
I don't understand.
[KARK] How beautiful to watch
someone sacrifice themselves
to save the life
of the one they love.
However...
[BOTH groaning]
[KARK]
...it's even more beautiful
when it turns to despair.
Sorry.
[KARK laughing]
No more.
[KARK]
Chihiro Kamina.
The man who may have eventually
become the Lord of Vermilion.
Regrettably, you heard
my requiem,
same as the others.
Since your soul has been
purified to black by its melody,
you must meet your end too.
Death has arrived.
You've grown accustomed
to playing with human lives,
haven't you, Kaburagi Kark?
As if they're your toys.
That stops now.
Your life ends here.
Was that Chihiro?
No way.
That was someone different.
The Lord of Vermilion.
[roaring]
[KARK] Well, Kamina?
Don't keep me waiting.
Ahura Mazda.
Such power.
For the longest time,
I hesitated
to stain my hands with blood.
[shrieks]
[CHIHIRO] But I won't
hold back anymore.
Seems you have
forgotten one thing.
To whom do you think
Ahura Mazda's cry belongs?
That's right.
My adoring fans.
Are you willing to kill
thousands of lives to stop me?
It's not as if
they can turn back now.
Are you sure about that?
What if I told you
there was a way to save them?
And if there is,
you can't kill me.
-[KOTETSU] Chihiro!
-[KOUME] No!
People are so predictable.
So weak.
They cling to
a faint glimmer of hope,
then despair when it fails.
The only comfort
for them is death.
-[CHIHIRO] Including you?
-[KARK] Huh?
If becoming the Lord
of Vermilion requires
spilling more blood
then so be it.
And let forgiveness be damned.
That's my burden!
[shrieking]
[chuckles]
Much stronger than I expected.
You truly are the supreme one.
[rumbling in distance]
[SHOKO] The victory was mine.
Mine alone.
Are you watching, Dux?
Did you see me?
I'm the chosen one!
[chuckles]
This is the finale.
Kark!
Show yourself!
I'd very much like to see
what kind of world you'd create,
but granting you death
offers me far greater joy.
You won't want
to miss the encore.
Everything we worked so hard
to create has been ruined.
What should we do?
I need you to guide me, Chiyu.
Yes, my father.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, Mitsuki.