[gasps]
[CHIHIRO grunts]
Chihiro, what...
[roars]
[grunts]
[MONSTER roaring]
He has awoken.
This is gonna make
things difficult.
Yes.
That's too bad.
Chihiro.
Huh?
What the...
What happened?
Did I just...
kill this thing?
Kotetsu.
[shuddering gasps]
Wait a minute.
That thing was...
your dad.
Which means I killed...
[screams]
[CHIHIRO crying]
Hey.
Wait, hold on.
[groans]
It's going to be okay.
Hey. What did you
just do to him?
[GIRL] Don't worry.
He's just sleeping.
I don't get it.
He's hurt. Isn't he?
[KOTETSU]
So, where did all the blood go?
I saw him slashed,
nearly in half.
Wait. Where did it go?
That-- That monster.
Was it really my dad?
[GIRL]
Yes, I'm afraid so.
That's insane!
How is that possible?!
[GIRL]
Please calm down!
[police siren blaring
in distance]
Don't say a word
to the police.
I'll explain the rest to you
in detail later.
[OFFICER 1] Officer requesting
additional units
at the Domyoji Dojo.
Kurokami! Marie Kurokami!
What the hell's going on?
-Keep him away from the scene.
-[OFFICER 2] Yes, ma'am.
-Gimme a break!
-Sir.
So. Did you see what happened
to the freakshow?
I wish I could say, but I
lost consciousness pretty quick.
[MARIE]
You're the owner's son, right?
Where'd this monster go?
I don't know.
[MARIE]
You sure?
I can't help. I'm sorry.
And I bet this random girl
didn't see anything either.
I'm Eiko Morizono.
Kamina and I share a class
at Yokei University.
I stopped by
to ask him a question
and found
this disaster instead.
It's simply a coincidence.
Pure luck, huh?
[EIKO]
Of course.
[MARIA] Kamina was living here
with you, isn't that right?
I'd like to talk to him.
Unfortunately,
he hasn't come to,
but I doubt he saw
anything unusual.
You seem
awfully certain of that.
We don't know
what happened, officer.
Of course not.
All we have is a broken gate
and a father who seems
to have disappeared.
File a missing person report
if he doesn't come back.
Hmm.
There has been a rash
of similar disappearances
in the city.
It's not unusual these days.
After all, tens of thousands
of people vanished
into thin air right after
the Great Collapse.
We don't know what happened
to them, either.
But there's a disturbing rumor
going around.
Some think the missing became
the red mist.
The red mist.
Speaking of disturbing rumors,
we've received several reports
of humans transforming
into monstrous beasts.
Thing is, every time
the police show up,
these creatures
have disappeared.
They're probably urban legends,
but I can't shake this feeling.
Like something big is about
to go down in Tokyo again.
All right. Who are you?
You weren't there
'cause of blind luck.
You said you'd tell me
the truth.
So I'm waiting.
For starters,
who was that monster?
And how did Chihiro survive?
Maybe I've just gone crazy.
Or maybe I'm dreaming.
[EIKO]
You're not dreaming.
You must accept this reality.
If that monster
really was my dad...
can you tell me why he suddenly
changed like that?
He was transformed
against his will.
But what could cause that?
You've seen the man who did it.
He was wearing a blue jacket
and sunglasses.
(gasps)
[KOTETSU]
He's responsible?
Why did he do it?
How'd he do it?
[CHIHIRO groaning]
Shh! I'll tell you
in a little while.
[EIKO] I'm sure the master
would like to know
the whole story
as much as you.
[GIRL, echoing]
Chihiro.
[grunts]
[CHIHIRO]
Where am I?
Kotetsu?
You're finally awake.
Who are you?
[winces]
[EIKO]
Hold on, don't move too fast.
I know you. I've seen you
at school before.
You've already used up a
dangerous amount of your power.
If you don't rest,
your strength won't come back.
What power?
[groans]
[EIKO] As you can see,
your wounds have healed.
Kotetsu's dad.
What about him?
I'm sorry, but...
[gasps]
You mean, he's dead?
So, I murdered him.
-[grunting]
-[stick whooshing]
[door opens, closes]
[TSUBASA] There you go,
back down the rabbit hole.
And now his instructor-
slash-foster father
has gone missing.
Are you aware
the rent's two months late?
How about we switch focus
over to a story
that actually pays us?
We finally got permission
to start the investigation.
Here, all the info I found
on the university
and the Foundation.
I'm counting on you, Kakihara.
[door opens, closes]
Ta-da! Dig in
before it gets cold.
Problem?
[KOTETSU] I'm confused.
Why did you cook us breakfast?
Well, the master has to eat.
[KOTETSU] Whoa. Master?
Who do you mean?
Him, obviously.
Yeah. About that.
I need you to explain
what's going on.
-Hmm.
-We've hardly spoken.
Not to sound ungrateful,
but we barely even know
each other.
Ah.
So that's the extent
of your relationship
with Eiko Morizono, huh?
Such a terrible shame.
What does that mean?
I'll explain more
when the time is right.
[KOTETSU]
I've had enough of this crap!
If you know something, tell us.
You can't keep us
in the dark!
Well, it's not like
you'd understand anyway.
-Seriously?
-As I said, later.
[EIKO]
Are you going to eat or what?
Just tell us
who you really are.
You're upset,
but you shouldn't be.
Besides, I think
it would be best
if you remembered
on your own.
Remember.
[EIKO] Enough chit chat.
Let's chow down.
We need to help your body
replenish its blood supply.
And don't even think
about skipping a meal.
There's no telling
what's going to--
[CHIHIRO]
Stop talking.
Could you please
give me a sec.
Kotetsu.
I'm sorry.
The food looks great.
We're just used
to Japanese breakfasts.
You gotta try
Chihiro's rolled omelets.
They're the reason
I get out of bed.
Can you forgive what I've done?
[sobbing]
You can't, can you?
Since that day,
my hand's been covered in blood.
And nothing can wash it away.
We're going to the
inter-school meet this year!
We just gotta work hard
to keep the Neo-Triathlon Club
up and running.
[groans]
It's too early to be upbeat.
You've got zero focus.
It's not my fault.
I haven't slept a lot.
It serves you right for
hanging out with a biker gang.
Not like you're listening to me,
but you should quit.
They're not a biker gang,
Akira!
They're Blue Skull!
You wanna tell me why we're
showing up to school today?
We still have class, don't we?
I'm not exactly
in the mood to learn.
At least this could keep
your mind off things.
Would you rather be
sitting at home,
wallowing in despair?
You'd just let your
pent-up emotions wear you down.
I can't let you do that.
Things are dangerous enough
around the city as it is.
[BOY screaming]
Oh, crap! This dude's
having a seizure!
What do you think's
gotten into that guy?
It's the same behavior
your dad displayed.
[BOY continues screaming]
Stand back.
A gate could be opening up here.
Well, you coming along?
-Yeah, sure.
-[KOUME] Clear a path!
I said move it!
Gonna need you
to dial it back, sir!
[BOY groaning]
Take him to the hospital.
As fast as possible.
Yeah, don't help at all.
[INUKI]
Well, well. The Sleeping Prince.
I forgot you're actually
a student here.
Hope you're doing well.
Why are you
at the university, doctor?
What, are you sleepwalking
or something?
Did you forget.
I work here on campus?
Over at the hospital.
I'm teaching a class
later on today.
Yo! Inuki! Any day!
Sounds like that's my cue.
Um, everything okay?
It's you.
I see.
So you are.
[KOUME]
Inuki!
You said your name
was Chihiro Kamina?
I think we'll be seeing
a lot more of each other.
What's that guy's problem?
Vessel of Heroic Blood.
[CHIHIRO]
You said that kid from earlier
would transform
like his dad did.
You were wrong.
[EIKO] There was a chance
he could have changed.
If the gate had actually opened,
he would have.
He's lucky.
What gate?
It's the portal that all
the monsters come through.
And on the other side is?
To put simply,
it's another world.
What?
[EIKO] I don't get
why you would doubt me.
It happened to your own father.
We get the picture.
They'll never stop
threatening our world.
We can only fight
and defeat them.
Yeah, right.
You make it sound
like it's easy.
I know you can't stop thinking
it was somehow your fault,
-but there was nothing you--
-[grunts]
Give it a rest!
I lost someone important to me.
Worse. I'm responsible, again!
[STUDENTS gasp]
Chihiro.
[CHIHIRO grunts]
But you survived it.
I don't ever remember
asking to live.
Like it or not,
you're an essential part
of the new world,
and I'm going to ensure
your continued existence.
That's my entire reason
for coming here.
Tell us the truth,
who are you?
[EIKO]
You already know.
I'm done playing games!
The truth!
[groans]
You all right?
I'll be fine.
Come on, man.
What's going on
with you, Chihiro?
[bells chiming]
Where'd that sound come from?
[groaning]
That was her.
Hey! Come back here!
He's taking a while.
Should we be worried?
Yes.
[panting]
[KAKIHARA] If the donations
to Jokei University
were in exchange for providing
the Foundation with workers,
that could end up being
a major story.
I wonder what the students here
would think if they knew
their futures were being decided
behind their backs?
Is it necessary to talk
about this now?
That's fine, if you're gonna
give me the silent treatment.
Maybe I'll just talk
a little louder.
I want to know what's going on
between the college
and the NAVAL
Science Foundation!
Look, can we find
somewhere private to talk?
[CHIHIRO panting]
Chihiro?
You're out of breath.
Is there something wrong?
I'm... not sure.
-[bells chiming]
-[groaning]
[ALL groaning]
[CHIHIRO] Fight it, Ikuro!
Don't give up!
I know you.
If you had just died, this all
could have been avoided.
[bells chiming]
[screaming in pain]
Ikuro!
[ALL screaming]
Stop it! Don't do this!
[IKURO screaming]
Hold on, Ikuro!
Please don't!
-You're hurting him!
-[bells chiming]
He's my friend.
I'm begging you to stop!
[WOMAN gasps]
[MAN]
Death to the Heroic Lineage.
Yuri. Those are your orders.
Do not defy them. Finish him.
[KOTETSU]
Chihiro!
Is that Ikuro?
[ALL growling]
Guys, it's him.
Fine. Step aside. I'll do it.
-[snaps fingers]
-[chiming]
[growling]
My head's gonna explode!
Kotetsu!
[EIKO]
Hurry and wake up!
You need to remember
who you really are!
What do you mean by that?
Give yourself to
the Heroic Blood inside of you.
Once you do,
it'll take care of the rest.
[screaming in pain]
I can't.
I won't do it.
You don't have any choice!
No!
And what if Kotetsu turns
into a monster?
Does that mean I'll kill him?
-[growling]
-[CHIHIRO and EIKO gasp]
Change or we'll all be killed!
[CHIHIRO]
I won't do it!
If living means
my friend has to die...
then I'd rather be the one
to die instead!
Kotetsu.
[EIKO gasps]
You killed him. It was you.
You're the one
who murdered my father!
Kotetsu.
[growling]
[screaming]
This whole time, he was
a vessel of Heroic Blood.
[KOTETSU]
Where'd he run off to?
This way!
[ALL crying]
[MAN]
To think there was another.
Doesn't matter.
I'll kill both of you
at the same time.
-[snaps fingers]
-[chiming]
[crying]
You can't!
[ALL screaming]
That's enough.
I warned you!
Death to the Heroic Lineage.
[growling]
[screaming]
Dammit! It's strong!
He can't keep this up for long!
But I-- I don't know how.
[CHIHIRO] When I killed his dad,
what did I do?
[blades clanging]
I don't remember anything.
I don't want to wake up
and find another person
I've killed.
I can't.
No. I don't want
more blood on my hands.
[MONSTER growling]
[BOTH gasp]
Kotetsu!