[TSUBAKI groans]
I thought I was dead.
Talk about a close call.
Did you witness Jun Aoi
in the alley?
[TSUBAKI]
Nah. By the time I arrived,
all I saw was the victim
and his familiar.
Are you saying it was acting
independently of him?
What'd it look like?
Uh, I'm not sure
how I would describe it.
Other than the fact
that it was totally different
from the familiars
we've seen before.
Yeah.
It also had the ability to
completely erase its presence.
[BOY 1] How're we supposed
to find this guy
when all we have is a picture?
[BOY 2]
You're defying Jun's orders?
I never said that,
I'm just being real here.
And what's so special
about this guy?
Doesn't matter. Jun says
"find him," we find him.
Don't we get
any more details?
Like are we allowed
to kill this dude?
Negative. And if we
do run across him,
we're supposed to, quote,
"keep our distance."
I'm starving.
Hey, losers.
I bought us some dinner.
Hmm.
The hell?
What's that?
Hmm?
[BOY screaming]
Hey, I'm sorry I wasn't able
to answer the phone earlier.
So what was going on
over at the hospital?
[KOUME over phone]
Oh. I-It was nothing.
Well, is Inuki there?
Not at the present moment.
He... He stepped outside.
[CHIHIRO] I have a bad feeling
about this.
Like something's gonna happen
to him if we don't intervene.
You're being paranoid.
Everything is perfectly normal.
[KOUME] He's just exhausted
from all the research
he's been conducting.
I suggest
you leave him alone.
[SHOKO over phone] Why are you
calling at this hour?
[CHIHIRO over phone] I need
to know if Inuki stopped
by the Church.
[SHOKO]
Not that I know of.
[CHIHIRO] Do me a favor.
Could you ask the others
to keep an eye out for him
in case he shows up?
[SHOKO]
What's this about?
[CHIHIRO] I... I dreamed
that Inuki was going to die.
[SHOKO] A dream?
What're you talking about?
[CHIHIRO] I'm serious!
You have to believe me!
[SHOKO] I'm too busy to listen
to your divinations.
[CHIHIRO]
This is real.
[line disconnects]
[line beeping]
[sighs]
[water running]
[CHIHIRO]
What can I do?
How am I supposed
to save him?
[INUKI]
No matter how crazy it is,
as long as you never give up,
you can uncover
the solution eventually.
As long as I don't quit,
there's a way.
But first,
I need to find where he is.
[KOUME]
What's your location?
Kamina's looking for you.
[INUKI over phone]
Sorry, I'm busy.
[KOUME]
What about your research?
[INUKI laughs]
I've got you, haven't I?
Don't be selfish.
[INUKI]
You're right.
[groaning]
[growling]
[BOY]
Try getting away now.
[ALL laughing]
[panting]
[HARU]
They got him!
Where is he?
[HARU]
First.
What about the Blue Skulls
he killed?
I'll settle the score.
You can leave it to me.
We're all gonna
wait here patiently
until Jun arrives.
[INUKI]
Jun's coming here?
[groaning]
If so, then I suggest
you leave right away.
Ha. Nice try, old man.
Why don't you stay
right where you are?
-[CHIHIRO] Inuki!
-Huh?
[INUKI straining]
Why're you here?
[BOY]
Who's this guy?
I'm glad you're all right.
Stay away! Far away!
But you don't understand.
I've been looking
all over for you.
Look. I care about you,
which is why you shouldn't
get involved here.
I had a dream
that you might be in danger.
[groaning]
Enough small talk.
Time for you to get lost.
[CHIHIRO] I have
no business with you.
Stay out of my way.
[BOY 1]
Oh, a tough guy.
[BOY 2]
Sounds like a challenge.
[BOY 3]
Let's take him!
[groaning]
[soft growl]
[CHIHIRO]
Inuki!
-[BOY 1] He's getting away!
-[BOY 2] Damn!
[BOY 3]
Go in after him!
[BOY 2] You were supposed
to be watching!
[BOY 4]
Like I could've predicted
he'd jump into the bay.
Jun's not gonna
be happy about this.
No way I'm the one
telling him.
Why did you run?
[SHOKO]
Any luck?
I'm not surprised.
[KAKIHARA] I managed
to identify our traitor.
It's Inuki Akaya.
[KAKIHARA]
This is the orphanage, Hikari.
Both Inuki Akaya and Jun Aoi
were raised here.
It wouldn't be an exaggeration
to say they were like brothers.
So he was working
for Chaos the entire time.
No wonder he opposed
every decision the Church made.
Hold on a minute.
We can't determine
that he's a traitor
based on a single photo.
Guess who managed
the orphanage he was raised in.
None other than
the AVAL Science Foundation.
Hold on! Not that AVAL!
From manufacturing everyday
necessities to public works.
On the surface,
their image is clean,
but in reality,
they're in the business
of weapons development
and illegal experimentation.
The truth behind
the AVAL Science Foundation
has been revealed.
The company is operated
by Agents of Chaos.
-[CHIHIRO] What?
-Thanks to the good doctor,
now we know
who's pulling the strings.
I'm still not convinced.
[KAKIHARA chuckles]
[KAKIHARA]
Here.
This is
the foundation's president,
Aldo Grumman Shiraki.
And the young woman standing
beside him is his daughter.
Yuri Shiraki.
She look familiar to you?
[KOUME]
Yeah, that's right.
Inuki was the one who leaked
our strategy to the other side.
[CHIHIRO]
But why?
He wanted to protect
the children of Hikari.
Remember the barrier
near the tower?
It's located
within the same area.
If we had managed
to destroy it,
those kids,
they would've been...
Wiped out.
[KOUME]
It's not your fault.
You didn't know.
Inuki's only concern
was protecting
the lives of our family.
Saving our home
from destruction.
What?
You heard me.
I was raised there,
the same as him.
[KOUME]
It was a facility used
for experimental education.
[KIDS screaming]
Because we were branded
as failures,
we were ultimately discarded.
That's pretty much
the only reason
we're all still alive.
But Inuki, he's still suffering
from the aftereffects
of the procedures.
And I'm worried he doesn't
have much time left.
[CHIHIRO]
Yuri, did you know?
[BIRDS chirping]
[CHIHIRO]
Why were you smiling?
[YURI]
Pretty, aren't they?
This is the Rosemary garden.
You're Yuri... Shiraki.
[gasps]
Remember the hot cocoa
we used to drink?
I can't get it out of my head.
I tried to make some myself,
but I could never get it
to taste quite the same
as your mother's recipe.
I'm sorry.
I don't remember.
The truth is,
someone told me your name.
I see.
I have nothing.
I can't do anything.
I'm about to lose
someone important to me again,
and I'm powerless.
But that isn't true.
I know you'll be fine, Chihiro.
Trust me.
If you don't have
any objections, I'll help you.
[CHIHIRO]
It's strange.
Whenever we're together,
I don't care
which sides we're on.
It seems unimportant.
Listen, Yuri. There're a lot
of questions I want to ask.
Like what?
[CHIHIRO]
About my past.
And all the things I've lost.
We're alone, so what's
the harm in talking?
I don't want to think
about fighting.
Mind if I... sit by you?
[water splashing]
[phone buzzing]
[JUN]
Talk to me.
[grunting]
-Got word from Jun.
-Hmm?
We're meeting up with the gang.
Huh?
Yeah, about that.
You wouldn't mind
if we tagged along, right?
[INUKI]
Your friends...
I'm sorry
for what I did to them.
[JUN]
I know.
[INUKI]
My Heroic Lineage power
is barely keeping
the monster at bay.
Do it.
[JUN]
Come with me.
There has to be a way
to fix this.
[INUKI] No. I'm not going back
to the Foundation.
[JUN]
We don't have time to argue!
[INUKI] You're the only one
I can depend on!
[JUN]
Stop being so selfish!
Don't you realize
you're the closest thing
I have to a brother.
I know.
That's why I'm asking.
[groaning]
Inuki!
[INUKI]
Quick! Before it's too late!
Let me die as your brother
and not a monster!
Inuki!
Chihiro?
[grunts, screams]
Even his Heroic Lineage
is out of control.
He's using
his blood armaments.
No telling what
they'll do in that form.
What is he?
[roaring]
Impossible.
So who's going to tell me
where to find Jun?
[BOY]
Haven't seen him around.
[MARIE]
You don't say.
That's hard to believe.
[KOTETSU]
Heroic Lineage?
[MARIE]
Yeah.
It looks like things
just got complicated.
We'll wait, see what they do.
Don't attack first.
Since when do I
provoke fights?
[growling]
[BOTH grunting]
Don't you recognize me?
Stop! I don't want
to hurt you!
I don't understand.
Why is this happening?
[yelling]
[JUN]
What incredible power.
-[growling]
-[CHIHIRO grunting]
[straining] I know
you're in there somewhere.
I'm going to save you.
[CHIHIRO] I just have to control
my energy like I did then.
I need more!
It's not enough!
The idiot. He's gonna overflow
if he uses his power like that.
It's not working
like it was before!
Why isn't my power
listening to me?
[grunting]
[screaming]
It vanished?
[growling]
[grunting]
So, the kid's trying
to amplify his power.
It's almost as though he's...
The Lord of Vermilion.
[growling]
Stop!
Inuki?
Hey, you guys.
What are those lights?
Whatever they are,
it doesn't look good.
It's Jun.
He's forcing him
to absorb his power.
What're you planning to do?
Promise me
you won't share my fate.
That you'll keep fighting
and never give in to despair.
[JUN] Stop it!
You'll kill yourself!
As long as you never quit,
your wishes will come true!
Learn to control your power.
Save the others.
[JUN] Stop, Inuki!
Don't do this!
The future's not written
in the stars!
Make it your own!
I believe in you, Chihiro.
Inuki! No!
[clinks]
Why did you...
Inuki, you really think
I can save everyone?