No, I can see your point.
I just wouldn't buy it.
The truth is I'm looking for
someone with a stock of pyrite.
Pyrite?
Yes.
Do you remember what I said
about Amarty and his method
of bringing in money,
in particular the money
he'd be giving you?
Yes...
Of course I do.
Amarty would be devastated
if he knew I was helping you,
so I won't go into details.
I not only remember that.
I also recall that
Diana would rather not
be involved in
business discussions.
I thought this
was to be business.
No, it's a social call.
I know this is a huge favor
to ask of you Batos...
but I need to know how
I can get Diana to help me.
I'm assuming this has to do
with getting your hands
on the alchemists' stockpile.
That's right. It does.
Of course, it is very
profitable right now.
That's not why I want it.
Well, why even
have the stone, then?
Unless you want
to tell the future.
Well, you could certainly
call it a personal gain.
I won't deny that's a factor.
However, you should know
the profit I'm looking for
is in no way related to
the current value of pyrite.
I guess it's...
I guess it's more of
a basic need you could say.
When our cart
sinks into the mud
and ends up getting stuck
we use a sort of scale
to determine the best
course of action.
Do we leave it behind
or do whatever is
necessary to save it?
We weigh the value of the goods
we are carrying, the profit,
the amount of cash
on hand, our travel route,
not to mention the cost
of paying for assistance.
And we have to consider
if it is worth it to risk
the danger of being discovered
by pillagers and criminals
while we're in such
a weakened position.
We measure both
sides of this scale
when deciding whether
or not to abandon our cargo.
Is that the situation
you find yourself in now?
Yes.
And I do not want
to abandon my cargo.
I will do whatever it takes
to get those goods in my cart...
I don't intend to
leave here without them.
That's what I was
waiting to hear.
Any merchant worth his
spices will wait patiently
no matter how small or out of
reach an opportunity may appear.
Then... You mean...
When you talk to Diana,
say the following:
I have come here today
to purchase a crate
of white feathers.
Thank you so much,
Batos... I will repay you.
All you need to do
to call this even
is to share another
ancient legend with me.
What do you think?
I sounded just as dignified
as Diana, didn't I?
Is anyone there?
Who is it?
Please forgive me for calling
at such a late hour...
My name is Craft Lawrence;
we met the other day.
I know this is rude,
and I'm very sorry.
I've come here tonight
to purchase a crate
of white feathers.
It appears festivals
really do attract people.
I've had several
visitors today.
Having more than
one of you is a rarity.
You said you
wanted to purchase
a crate of
white feathers, correct?
Did Batos tell
you to say that?
He did... He was
extremely patient with me.
Well isn't that wonderful...
Although I find it difficult
to believe he would give
in to mere persistence...
What kind of business
proposal did you have for me?
I'm curious as to what would
sway that stubborn old mule.
My plan was to
ask your permission
to buy some of your pyrite.
Oh, not the escalating
pyrite everyone speaks of?
It is... but it's not just--
You have a special reason
for wanting it, right?
I know Batos well enough
to know he would not
have sent you to me if
you were a simple profiteer.
You are right
about that much...
Mere profit is not
what brings me to you;
I am here to settle a duel.
Of course you are-- With whom?
With whom...
That's wrong.
It's with my cargo.
Your cargo?
A good merchant is always
at odds with his cargo.
Always weighing its value,
considering how
best to handle it.
Researching where
it should go...
If he misjudges
any of these factors,
a merchant will lose every time.
Right now, I'm attempting
to steady a piece of cargo.
A piece that's about
to fall out of my cart.
I've thought about it...
I've reconsidered its value,
delivery, and destination...
And I've come
to the conclusion
that I cannot allow
this piece of cargo to go.
Yes.
I would like to purchase
a crate of white feathers today.
It is such an
overly dramatic password.
Would you like to
know to what it alludes?
It means you have to
entertain me for a little while.
After all, a happy
bird will drop its feathers
when it flaps its wings.
Those who know the password
determine who
is allowed to see me.
I simply get to enjoy
the stories told by my guests.
I don't mind.
If pyrite is what you desire,
I will allow you to buy it.
Thank you so much.
However, someone else
has already bought some.
How much? And at what price?
Calm yourself, please.
The customer bought
on credit alone...
They did not actually
take any goods with them...
The order has been
placed but not yet filled.
On credit?
Personally, I would not mind
handing it over to you instead.
It was approximately
1,600 Irades-worth
according to
the market value today.
That's the same as
400 Trenni silver coins.
I can do that...
What is your customer's name?
Please allow me
to handle negotiations.
Why?
For obvious safety reasons,
we do not divulge the names
of those who contract
business with alchemists...
I am sure you would not wish
for your name
to be shared either.
No, but still...
Do you object?
No.
This is clearly not
an everyday transaction
considering there
is a duel involved,
so I will do my best...
I shall let you know
the results as soon as possible.
I'm sure I will know
something by tomorrow
but I'm afraid I don't
know where to find you.
Oh...
In front of
the mineral merchant's stand
at the marketplace
should be fine.
I will stay in that area
throughout the day's trading
and wait until
I get word from you.
Money is no object...
well, so long
as they don't ask
for double or
something outlandish.
You can let
your customer know
I am more than willing
to pay quite generously.
Again...
I apologize for
coming here so late.
I would not
have minded if you
stayed for the entire evening.
Provided that you had told me
some more old stories of course.
Are you all right?
I'm fine...
It's just...
Can I ask you something?
Yes, please do. Go ahead.
Okay...
Well...
Have you by chance
heard any legends
about pagan gods
becoming mates with humans?
Yes. There are many like that.
Many of them?
Unfortunately you
were just leaving.
We will have to discuss
those stories at another time.
Enjoy your evening.
Yes... You too...
I look forward to hearing
from you tomorrow.
Do your best.
So, how did it go?
Well, Diana wanted
to work with me...
But someone else
got to her first,
so we'll just have
to wait and see.
Got to her first?
Yeah...
at this point, I'm relying
solely on what you told me.
Yeah... about
what I told you...
Go ahead...
Tell him what you found out.
Right.
If you pay in Trenni silver,
they'll sell
370 coins worth of py--
Hey now!
We don't want
everyone to hear!
Well, that's what
it's going for right now.
You're kidding me,
370 silver coins...
That's unbelievable.
It's not that much...
I gave it some
thought after you left.
And I came up with
a very interesting notion...
Take a person like me
who isn't exactly rich,
I'm buying,
but I'm just spending
a little extra pocket cash.
Now what do you think
I would do if I was rich?
Would I be able to hold back
in the middle of this racket?
Well.
I'd be willing to bet there
are quite a lot of people
who stocked up
on it on the side.
Those would be local
merchants who have
their reputations on the line.
They are not like
you travelling merchants
who really don't
have anything to lose.
Buying wasn't a problem,
but the price
has gone up so much,
they're afraid they
won't be able to sell.
Even if they only
sell a small amount,
their profit would be huge.
So it's still worth
it to them for now.
But if for any reason
people started to get nervous,
they would end up desperate
to get rid of their stock.
So I just--
You just sent out your
apprentice to spread the word.
"I met a travelling merchant
blinded by greed.
He told me he'd be willing
to buy pyrite with cash."
Is that about it?
Yep, you guessed it...
So, what do you want to do?
If you're okay with it,
I could start negotiating
for you immediately.
That's perfect...
Let's get this.
What is it?
It's nothing.
I'm sorry for
everything that's happened.
You idiot.
This is the part where
you're just supposed
to say "thank you."
You're right,
I'm sorry, I didn't.
Okay then.
Thank you very much.
My friend,
you are a changed man.
Up until recently,
you were the epitome
of what a travelling
merchant should be,
and I've seen enough
travelling merchants to know.
Just take me...
It never once occurred to you
that I might actually be
a good friend, now did it?
What? Of course.
Well, I bet it's occurred
to you now. Or has it?
Am I still just another
convenient contact
to trade with?
A business associate?
You're not.
That's why merchants
who've become
local business owners
have a tendency to fail
after spending so
much time travelling.
But would you like to know
something even more fascinating?
Let me ask you this,
if you were faced
with the possibility
of never seeing me again
would you be running
around town in a panic,
looking for me everywhere?
No... I wouldn't.
Do you realize...
You're doing that right now.
You're going through hell
to save your companion.
When you started
travelling with that girl,
even the way you met,
it was simple
coincidence, wasn't it?
It was... I didn't think
about it too much,
I just accepted that
she was there.
I feel like I'm watching
myself when I first met Adele.
Poets are famous for saying
you can't buy love with money.
And preachers tell us
you cannot use money
to get into heaven either.
So even though we all
work as hard as we can
just to get as
much money as possible
we should achieve
something far more important...
something that doesn't
cost you any money at all.
[MALE VILLAGER]
Tell that to my wife!
If something ended up taking
us a lot of effort to obtain
we would naturally
consider it precious, right?
But, there are also
times when precious things
enter our
lives unexpectedly.
I can see you
still don't realize
what I've been telling you.
You've been
saving your princess.
It was not just about
physical power, you know.
Maybe it's because Amarty
is the one from a good family...
but you've been thinking
of him as the prince
running off with
the princess instead of you.
Don't be discouraged.
This is your story, and you
get to be the lead in it.
[HOLO]
And who are you to me?
So do you get it now?
Tell me, Lawrence.
Who am I to you?
I believe I know the answer
to that question now.
[LAWRENCE sneezes]
Holo, Can I please
have your tail?
Good morning.
So did Marc happen to tell you
what our plan for
today was going to be?
Yes, sir. He sure did!
I'm helping you lay
a trap for the evil villain!
Or, at least
that's what I heard.
Yeah, that's right...
I can't go into details,
but you have the gist of it...
Although I might
still need to ask you
to do something
rather difficult.
Now, what's your name again?
Sir! My name is Lunt...
Well, it's Ew Lunt actually.
You were born even
farther north than here, right?
Yes, sir.
The best way I can describe
my hometown is frozen.
All right, Lunt.
I'll be counting on you today.
Now then, don't you
think we should start
this day with a proper meal?
Do you want me to
go buy something?
Um, sir...
Just one coin
is more than enough.
The other is for you.
Consider it a tip.
Perhaps that will tide you
over until I'm finally able
to pay you that
handsome reward later on.
Wait... Do you mean?
You should get going
before your master gets back.
He probably thinks breakfast
is a luxury, doesn't he?
Yeah... Thanks,
I'll be right back!
Please don't
go spoiling him.
You had the power to stop me.
I do need to have him here.
He'd probably have to stay home
if he ended up malnourished.
Well, it was a win-win then.
True...
And I suppose you need
him to be healthy as well,
if you want him
to help you today.
That's correct...
In the meantime I'll watch
the market like a hawk...
until around noon
or so, I think...
If it looks like
it's rising too much,
I'll sell enough pyrite
to drop it back down again...
There's no telling how
all of this will turn out.
It's possible my fate lies
on Lunt's narrow shoulders.
Look at how many
prospective buyers there are!
But no sellers at all.
This could keep
going on forever.
I know, it's averaging
800 Irades now!
That's 80 times
the starting value.
I'm glad I held out, then.
Sir...? Can I ask a question?
Of course.
I don't think I get it.
How can Lawrence win this thing?
Well, let's think
about it for a second,
how does an item's value rise?
Well, if there's a big
demand for people to buy it...
like if there's not
enough of it to go around.
And how does it drop?
I guess the price would drop
if there were
a lot of that item.
Yep, you've pretty much got it.
But if you want to
overheat the market,
you'd need to make sure some of
the item is sold.
If no one is selling, the only
ones who benefit
are those who already have the
product in stock...
Does that make sense?
I think it does, because if some
are still selling
it means there are new people
who are obtaining the product,
which is why the price
gets higher and higher.
You got it.
There's something
important to consider here;
he's not trying
to make a profit...
Lawrence's goal is to
keep Amarty from profiting...
Which means that
he needs to sell
a large quantity of pyrite
at exactly the right time.
And that in turn will force the
price to drop.
But if Amarty sells even
a second before Lawrence
and gets those
1,000 silver coins,
Lawrence would be
completely out of luck.
He has to have
the wherewithal to hold back,
then make a big move all
while timing it perfectly.
At this rate,
it'll never stop!
The buyers just keep coming.
How many are there now?
Hold on, let me check...
Hello!
I hope your morning is going
well, Lawrence.
Good morning to you, Amarty.
Once the market bell rings...
even more people will
be gathering in the square,
so I just figured
I should give this to you now.
What is it?
The payment I promised
you, of course.
These are Lima gold coins!
Yes, I prepared 14 coins for you
at this morning's
opening market rate.
I do apologize if it seems
presumptuous...
I was just thinking it might
be a little
inconvenient for you...
Carrying around
500 silver coins and all.
The exchange rate for this must
have cost you quite a bit.
Well... I won't say.
But you can't put
a value on good manners.
Oh I understand...
I'm just glad you made
the payment on time.
And please go ahead and count
them; I will not be offended.
Now that that's
all taken care of,
I'd like to take the
contract for the 500 silver.
Yes, of course
you would. Well?
This is perfect.
Next Episode:
Wolf and Trustworthy God.