[HOLO] Lawrence...
Lawrence... Lawrence...
Lawrence...
Lawrence!
Wash with this.
Sorry... what's this...?
It is a wise choice
to have my scent on you.
You are beginning
to concern me.
She wants me to help her
with an ambitious plan.
You mean that fox?
Her name is Eve.
And she's working with
the landlord of this
establishment, Aroldo.
I still have to check it out...
And 'no' I haven't
agreed to it...
Not yet...
Is that so?
It could be worth...
...enough to alienate me?
And more...
The 50 man meeting
has decided to allow
foreign merchants
to purchase furs
with one conspicuous condition.
Who said this?
The church did.
Even though they
kicked you out?
Just because things ended badly
doesn't mean I can't keep
my contacts on the inside.
So what are the conditions?
If the foreign merchants
wish to purchase fur,
they'll only be allowed
to buy with cash.
They know that nobody
brings that much cash
with them when
travelling from so far.
Exactly.
So if some enterprising
merchant can find a way
to come up with enough cash
to buy a huge load of furs
all he'd have to do is sail
them down the Rohm River
before anyone else gets there
and the market would be his.
You could sell it
for triple your cost.
So the profit is
twice the capital?
I see...
You didn't even
know there was a man
named Rigaro until
I mentioned him, did you?
Do you have any way of
getting that kind of money?
Not here, but back
in another town.
If I travel there
I'm certain I can get it.
I'm afraid time is not one
of our luxuries right now.
The fur in this town
would be bought up
long before you got back.
But nobody'll be able
to buy...
I thought that was the
purpose of the meeting.
Initially, it was.
But only to set up the complete
collapse of the fur trade.
There are wealthy people in town
who are eager to
buy up the stock.
One last trade to
finance their exodus.
That's why I want as much up
front capital as possible.
Expect trade to go
down very quickly...
This is going to be a
brawl between merchants.
An all-out trade war.
You're serious.
The people behind this have
been preparing for some time.
Naturally.
That's why your companion
is our only option.
We need collateral...
and all we have to do is
claim she is a noble.
You don't think we can do it?
Watch and learn.
My name is Fleur Fon
Eaterzentel Bolan.
I am eleventh in succession to
the head of the Bolan Household
whose fealty is owed to
the King of Winfiel.
My family is truly
born of noble blood.
Of course, that couldn't keep us
from hard times and poverty...
but the name is
impressive, isn't it?
Our family became
so desperately in debt
that their only choice
was to sell me off to
an upper class merchant.
I maintain my name...
and that means I have the right
to sell off a daughter of my own
if I should ever
choose to do so.
Smart, yes...?
With your companion's
looks and demeanor,
no one would question
her noble roots...
of that I can assure you.
Of course...
I know you would never
actually want to sell her,
but I do know a trading company
that will lend us the funds
so long as they get a
share in the profits.
They will expect there to be
sufficient collateral
to cover the loan...
but we'll only use her as the
security to back the venture...
A noble's daughter should be
worth more than enough...
As long as I give my word
as the head of the family.
It's not like I'm asking you to
actually sell your companion
in order for us to
pull this deal off.
This will be my last chance to
go on a pilgrimage, I suppose.
I have had plenty of chances
to go in the past...
but I always let them slip by.
I can offer you my inn as well.
In truth this is exactly
what you have always
wanted, is it not?
You're right.
Then why are you hesitating?
For as long as I have known you,
it has been your dream
to own your own shop.
What right do I have to
place myself before that?
I can't ask you to do this.
You fool.
How so?
As I recall, you didn't even
want me to trade in this town.
Oh Lawrence...
I am loath to admit
this to you, but-
'Tis true...
I am always most at peace when
I am traveling by your side.
Being your partner
on this journey
has been my greatest reward.
I always gain more from
you than I ever give.
And if I lost that...
my heart would break.
It is your business to
examine profit and risk,
make the choice you think is
going to be best in the end.
When a deal shows promise,
I never see you hesitate for
some other reason.
Even if you think
your new associate
is trying to deceive you,
you are always a step ahead of
them and profit nonetheless.
You are a man who makes trades
without fear or apprehension.
What happened to your courage?
What is this sudden need
for caution?
I have been nothing but
selfish up till now.
I believe it is your
turn to be selfish.
Even so that still that doesn't
give me the right to pawn you.
Is this business
deal the reason you
were crying out in your sleep?
Won't you get mad?
I would only be mad because you
would think me so shallow.
Are you saying you
do not understand?
Yes,
You creatures never
cease to baffle me.
Am I your equal
partner or am I not?
Perhaps I am just a little
girl who amuses you?
This would not be the first
time
I offered myself as
a sacrifice for you.
Before it was in gratitude.
But the circumstances
have changed greatly.
Holo...
Now, is there any other way
to put your mind at ease?
You could help me figure out if
this is really a double cross.
As if a double cross
would matter to you...
just plan ahead for it...
"The more intricate the plot
ends up being."
Then the bigger the score
is when you uncover it...
You actually listen to me...
I'm surprised.
Well, I am still
Holo the Wise Wolf.
I could not have some
dullard merchant
for a partner, now could I?
Shall we go?
Sure. How 'bout breakfast?
It looks more like
a fort than a church.
I pray God keep you safe today.
[BEGGAR] You're a little
scruffy for a nun.
No, I'm definitely
not with the church.
I just have something
I'd like to ask you
So... ask me your question.
It has to do
with the church.
Guys like you used to be
everywhere back in the day.
You want their
business connections.
You sure are a perceptive man.
This is the biggest
church around for miles.
They pride themselves
on their charity.
Beans, bread... anything
for the poor... it's just...
Just what?
The Bishop hasn't
limited himself
to just passing out food;
he also deals in money.
And how do you know this?
Why wouldn't I know?
All the fancy carriages that get
lined up here week after week.
All those finely
dressed people
from the city
climbing out of them.
The stuff they
throw out from dinner
tells me it's not just beans
and bread they're getting.
I know.
Couldn't you leverage
that information
to climb up out of
where you are now?
Haven't you ever heard it
said "Blessed are the
poor in spirit."
I'll bet you have no idea
what it's like to rejoice
over brown bread
and two bronze coins
the way I do,
and you never will.
I rejoice like that daily.
I don't know what it is
you think you're doing...
but their good graces will
leave you robbed blind.
That's a bit of wisdom I can
give you from experience.
There's only one
person I've ever seen
who was able to stay
in their graces
for an extended
period of time.
And even that ended with him
screaming himself hoarse
at the front of their gate.
Was it a man trading
stone statues?
Statues?
Yeah, I think he dealt in
those among other stuff...
So was this a friend of yours?
In a manner of speaking.
I always assumed that his
primary trade was in salt.
In salt?
What is it makes you say that?
Sometimes I used
to see salt spill
from the loads he was
bringing up to the church.
I can tell the quality of
the salt from the smell,
and this stuff
was not high grade.
The farther from the
sea a merchant travels...
the more valuable any
salt traded becomes.
Interesting...
a salt merchant?
[HELENA] Coming to see
me early again, huh?
You're not the
only smart one...
Plenty of other merchants
come to see me too.
I'd say most just want to get a
look at those beautiful eyes.
People think a few bronze
coins give them the right
to lose all their manners.
I'm afraid that I've come
to be impolite as well.
You don't think I know that?
Well, go ahead and ask...
About the 50 man meeting.
I guess they've
wrapped it up already.
Everyone's saying
they're going
to make it okay to
sell furs for now.
But they won't let any foreign
merchants buy on credit.
Foreign merchants can
only buy fur with cash.
Like she said.
Oh... Nothing...
I also wanted to ask you about
the church in this town.
Okay.
I won't speak ill of them...
but you shouldn't get
involved with the church.
So they really are in the
middle of some power struggle.
I don't know the details
of what's going on...
but I know powerful people
keep coming to dinners
at the Chancery.
They hired me on for two
full days and nights,
and I found out
it was because
they were hosting some important
visitor from the church.
It looks like they're gathering
their strength about them.
And they seem very concerned
about their standing
with the people.
They've become really generous
with their charity...
but if you wonder aloud
where all the money is
coming from to fund it...
Well, I'm not sure
what would happen,
but I can't imagine
it would end well.
Once the church has
turned their eye on you,
being forced out of town
won't be far behind.
At least that's what
everyone thinks.
You're taking a big risk
telling me all this.
I like talking to you,
that's all...
It makes me feel
like I'm special.
I don't understand...
What about that would
make you feel special?
If I narrowed it
down to one thing...
It would have to be that other
woman I can smell all over you.
Be honest.
I'm not the first girl
with half a mind
who's tried to flirt
with you like this.
But I'm the prettiest.
I hate to say it, but
this has never happened.
What that tells me is that
you and your girlfriend
haven't been
together for long...
no, not very long at all.
I can tell by your eyes
that you're very kind.
When you travelled
around by yourself...
I'm sure women hardly took
any notice of you at all...
But put a beautiful
girl by your side...
and they just can't
help but wonder
what it is they're
missing with you.
Stick a sheep out in the middle
of a field all by itself
and nobody really
cares to hunt it,
but as soon as another
wolf draws near
suddenly everyone else
wants to have it, too.
And because I know that
I'd like invite the two of
you here so I could meet her.
Why thank you, glad to accept.
I can never tell...
Are you serious or not?
And you are certain that is
everything that
happened with her?
I don't have anything to hide.
I should give this girl a lesson
in the dangers of crossing
into a wolf's territory.
But I have to say that
I am very impressed
with how well you have
handled the situation.
Well, if you want a horse to run
quickly
sometimes it's best just to let
go of the reigns for a while.
Alright then, what do your
horse instincts tell you?
The clergy are trying to
have a cathedra installed
in their church so they can
increase its influence.
A cathedra?
It's Latin for 'chair' but
it represents the seat
of a new diocese and
requires that a Bishop be
elevated and seated upon it.
Then the church's
influence extends
to all the towns in
its diocese as well.
I can understand why that fox
of yours would be so eager
to leave since
she's no longer
going to be part of the
growing power structure.
I'm still curious as to why
she's no longer in
their good graces.
If I were in her place
I think I'd put up with it.
The power the church wields
would make it
worth it in the end.
What's your take on it?
That almost sounds like
you would like to
know what I think.
Not really...
It just helps me think
to hear someone's voice.
Particularly when I'm faced
with a conundrum
like this one.
You would not change your mind
if I cried and
begged, would you?
I'd have to ignore you.
And you'd be waiting
for me at the inn.
We would make up after
I came back successful.
This one isn't up to you.
That will be more convincing...
when your face does not redden.
I'll work on it.
You are so energetic today.
Men come into their own when
they are on the heels
of their prey only...
You'd like it more if
you were being hunted.
Perfect marks, however,
have you stopped to consider
my fate should your deal
not go exactly as planned?
You are acting
as the collateral.
If we fail they will sell
you off to satisfy our debt.
And this is why your sleep has
been so troubled as of late.
That's part of it.
If that happens...
I hope they sell me off to
someone who is not quite so dim.
Yes, those who cannot repay
the money they've
borrowed are idiots.
They deserve all
the hardships that come.
Such boldness
from the little boy
who desperately begged
me when I was trying to leave.
I am helping you because I
believe in you
with all my heart.
Of course you do.
Okay... It's time for us to go.
Really...
You so enjoy letting your nerves
have their way with you.
Well if not in the privacy
of my own room,
when do I ever get to be myself?
When we first met,
even up until recently...
it always seemed to me
like you were attempting
to put on some kind
of a show for me.
You know I'd never travelled
with a woman before...
You take some getting used to.
In the early days
of our travels,
even the thought of
taking me in public
would quicken your breath and
make you nervous.
And if I started keeping the
company of other women now,
would it still make your tail
bristle like before?
Men are onions.
Many layers and all
of them make you cry.
In the end, you just
end up exclaiming
how it should not have
turned out this way.
But isn't that the
case with whomever
once you allow them
into your heart?
You are wasting your bait on a
fish you have already caught.
Now why would you
bother doing that?
I think 'caught' belies the fact
that this 'fish' fought its way
on to my boat despite my
best efforts against it.
It's not bait I
should be giving you
but a bill for your
enormous boarding fee.
What's wrong?
Remember, you felt much
differently when we first met.
Come on, time to go.
Um... right.
I only dare to hold
your hand like this
because we have been through so
much together on this journey.
It is curious...
Poets sing of changing things
back to how they once were,
but I am not sure
it would suit me.
A woman like you
might actually like it.
But if things
stayed that way for me.
I'd end up collapsed
dead from anxiety.
You worry too much.
You will have me for your nurse
when your end finally comes.
So, have you made up your
mind about the plan yet?
I've done my share of
due diligence...
and my instincts tell me
what you say is true.
And?
However, one thing
still concerns me.
What's that?
I don't know the conflict
that caused you to
part with the church.
Well... I guess that's
reasonable enough.
The Chancellor for
the church is in love
with the idea of power.
Not only is he
trying to establish
a Cathedra out
of this diocese,
but he'd like it to be
the Metropolitan over
the whole region.
An Archbishop?
Exactly.
While sniffing around for
a lucrative business deal,
I happened upon his network of
backroom money transactions.
He was siphoning off donations
for use in his fur trade
through a shell company
he'd established
before he was ordained.
But he had gotten himself
into financial trouble.
So, I came along with a way
to kill two birds
with one stone.
Your trade in stone statues.
Correct.
But we weren't just selling
stone statues...
I'm not just some merchant.
I am Winfiel
nobility after all.
Through my family I
have a connection
with the Cardinal who
oversees political assignments.
So in return for using your
connection with the Cardinal,
the Bishop agreed to
sponsor your statue trade.
You had a captive
market in the church
and all the support
you could ask for.
The idea of the bishop
moving up in the ranks
made the low profit
margins easier to cope with.
But as his path to
ascension became more secure
he began to sift the wheat
from the chaff as it were,
cutting me off without
so much as a farewell.
He came to his senses then.
He realized you'd be
a costly ally to keep.
I would have troubled him,
to be sure.
But no.
Rather than train his own
trader from within his circle...
He chose to seek
out an established company
instead and so
I became obsolete.
Just because I
understand why he did
it doesn't mean
I have to like it.
I get it.
So your stock of statues
had become harder
to sell over night.
And waiting around for
another expedition
to the north is just
not an option.
I see it clearly...
Let's set a meeting to discuss
the details of the plan.
It'll be my pleasure.
Your fox's hands were
shaking, were they not?
Nerves can get even the best
of merchants, I suppose.
Let us hope that
is all it was...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
We should get about
1,500 silver coins for you.
Next Episode:
Wolf and the Decision to Part