Holo...
I said I was sorry...
Geez...
C'mon don't be like this...
I know I was gone too
long and I apologize.
I guess I was hoping
you'd understand.
'Tis narrow here.
Far too narrow.
You're right.
It is a little inconvenient...
But I have to admit, I actually
like old places like this.
Why is that?
It has character from the wear
and tear it's experienced
over the years.
Think of how a tool
slowly changes as you use it.
Gradually, it gets worn down,
but it ends up being
the only one you want to use.
It sounds similar to the way
a river changes shape
throughout time.
No, that's not quite the same.
Sorry but I'm going to have
to disagree with your analogy.
Oh...
Well what about
a person's heart, then?
You refer to it
as a soul, right?
Huh? A soul?
Possibly...
Although, I guess you'd
have to look at it somehow.
One would need
to see all the places
where it's been chipped
away, injured, and repaired.
Then, you could
recognize it as your own.
You could say, "this is mine."
May I help you, princess?
Very well.
If we could find a way to pull
out your soul and look at it.
I believe I can
say with all certainty
that it would be
the same color as me.
I could see that.
I think it's reasonable to say
you've worked your way
into my soul somehow;
kind of like a poison.
Yes, of course!
I am the poison.
You did fall for
my smile, did you not?
That makes me wonder what
the color of your soul must be.
Let me think...
It is multi-colored.
It sounds as
if you are feeling
a pang of possessiveness,
is that it?
If I were in your shoes,
I would probably
feel the same way.
It's right.
No, but it is
a fork in the road.
You should tell me how you will
manage to subjugate
your egotistical passions.
Ok well, let's see...
This is indeed
a very sensitive issue.
I'm sure most people
suffer from their passions
in one way or another.
But might it be you
are only asking me this
because you are by nature a
jealous and dominant creature?
It seems to me,
you madam, are projecting.
And if that was the truth?
Well, first I'd have to consider
the situation from
your point of view...
Then I could come up with
the most accurate solution.
I got it...
You cannot
control your emotions.
Even if you know you'll
hate yourself later for it.
So, you think it's right, then?
Yes.
However...
Possessiveness
and self-hatred...
What a shame.
I do appreciate
your noble attempt
at stepping into my shoes
to determine
my innermost desires...
But unfortunately...
The only thing you figured
out is what you want me to be.
I will never
understand why males
are attracted to jealousy
and weakness in females...
Oh, I am a mere
woman who is so distressed
by wanting you
that I hate myself!
You wish for them
to desperately cling
to your terribly generous hand.
'Tis pathetic.
Well, shall we go?
I wonder...
What?
Now, I am only asking
this to tease you, but...
Would you like to
know how many I've had?
My heart is far too delicate
to suffer that specific
bit of information.
Okay...
I heard he can
be pretty difficult,
so let's try to behave.
I do not know what
you could possibly mean;
I always behave...
But I shall
certainly watch over you.
Maybe you should just go back
to the inn and take a nap.
That is not a bad idea...
Of course...
I would not be counting sheep
on top of the bed,
if you know what I mean.
Fine.
So just how many is it?
You're right...
And evidently it
seems that I am even
an idiot amongst my own kind.
[MERTA] Hello there.
Who might you be?
I'm Craft Lawrence.
Miss Eve Bolan
said I was coming?
Yes...
We've actually
been expecting you.
Please come in.
I'm sorry about the wait.
[RIGORO] You know, I can't
get enough of that reaction.
I agree, Rigoro.
It's quite nice.
It amazing isn't it?
All you need to do is give
it a little bit of effort,
and you can keep the plants
green for the entire year!
Yes, Fleur did
tell me about you.
Something about
a strange request
that only I could help you with.
Yes, it's very
nice to meet you.
My name is Craft Lawrence,
but everyone calls me Lawrence.
And I'm Rigoro, Rigoro Dedri.
Nice to meet you.
This is my travelling companion.
My name is Holo.
I love it! That was hilarious!
It is wonderful to meet you.
Likewise.
I have to admit it...
Your reaction to my prized
garden made me very happy.
What can I do for you
to show my gratitude?
Well actually,
what Eve told you was right.
She said you would be able
to help me find books
that tell the old stories
and legends from this town.
Is that true?
Yes, that is true.
But I can't believe that's
really what you came here for.
Fleur told me...
I guess it's Eve?
She may act tough but
she can be quite mischievous.
Which make sense...
After all, you're not
frowning with a long beard.
You're quite a bit
friendlier than expected.
Looks like she got us both.
Who knows what
she'll say about me next?!
Although, I suppose
some people don't find me
to be very friendly at all.
I guess that's
because recently
I've been refusing meetings
as much as possible.
I should tell
you I am a merchant
from outside the city.
Are you sure it's
okay for the two of us
to be talking like this?
Yes. You came
at the perfect time.
Maybe this is what
they call God's providence.
I actually just
returned from the meeting...
It concluded and finally
adjourned not long ago.
Well...
As one would expect of
a merchant who is travelling
with such
a beautiful companion.
You don't let your guard down.
I imagine constantly
protecting yourself
with wit and finesse
can get exhausting.
The back of the back
is the front, am I right?
I could see you were
surprised that the meeting
ended early,
it flashed across your face.
Don't forget I'm the scribe
for the 50 man
meeting for a reason.
I can understand
what is behind
a person's
changing expression.
Now, your expressions
are more difficult to read,
but when I combine them
with the movements of
your lovely companion,
everything starts
to become clearer to me.
That was impressive.
It's really not.
That's just
a little trick of sorts.
And if I'd had ill intentions,
I wouldn't have told
you the truth, right?
Besides, even if
I did know what people
were thinking,
what good would it do me?
I'm a terrible communicator!
So does that make me
a failure as a merchant?
Yeah. I'm sorry but it does.
It's also why I'm not
too popular with women.
All the books that you're
wanting are in the basement.
Looks like the back
of the back is the front.
I do like that he
was looking at my face.
I've never seen anyone
do a trick like that before.
I believe he was telling the
truth about no ill intentions.
He is almost like a child.
But, for someone with
such a skill by your side,
I am certain that you would
lead a worry free
and relaxing life indeed.
Do you ever not
have ill intentions?
By the way...
I'm dying from curiosity.
So I'm sorry,
but I have to ask you...
Why do you want to know about
the legends from this town?
She's searching for her legend.
Her legend?
She's tracing back her lineage,
and I'm helping guide
her back to where she's from.
That's the reason
why we're here.
I understand.
You must be headed north then.
We are...
But we don't know
the exact location yet.
Right now we're
just using a legend
she remembers to try
and find our way there.
How very fascinating...
I'm not sure why,
but I'm sure you have a reason.
Such is the way of
the world, I suppose.
Did anyone tell
you that children
who are brought from the north
sometimes end up
staying in this city?
It's hard to
imagine anything better
than returning
safely to one's home.
Now this is all of them...
I thought it would be easier
if you went ahead
and took everything with you.
I won't feed you for
3 days if you drop those.
Why don't you
hand a few over to me?
That is why I normally
would have you read them here.
However, I trust
Fleur implicitly...
And if she can
trust you, Lawrence,
then I will trust you as well.
I think It would be nice
if we all thought that way.
True...
I promise to
be careful with them.
It must be easy
to wave your hand
like that when you're
not holding anything.
And it must be easy to babble
like that when
you're being a big baby.
I hope you do not
expect flattery.
It would only overexcite you.
I have no idea what you mean.
Flattery annoys me.
Good grief.
You do know even gluttony
has its limits, don't you?
What a nice evening.
Yes. What a nice evening.
True, but if every
night was like this one...
I'd get way too spoiled.
It is truly bittersweet
sometimes, is it not?
Yes, it is quite bittersweet.
[EVE] Are you sure...?
The master will not be happy
if you go to another inn.
It will only be for one day.
We would never be so rude
as to change our lodgings.
Good...
Do you drink a lot?
Look at the two of us
and take a wild guess.
[AROLDO] I talked with a fur
trader from the north earlier.
He said there wasn't
much snow on the ground...
So travelling up there should
be fairly convenient for you.
Thank you for finding
that out for us.
If you want to know more
details, his name was, uh...
Kolka Koose.
Oh was that what his name was?
It doesn't
really matter, does it?
He's staying on
the fourth floor...
He might have
mentioned that
he's normally
free in the evenings.
If you need to know more,
you should go ask him.
Thank you both...
I wish the two of
you a good night.
You are such a mess.
I'm scared.
Of what... I'm right here.
Yes, I know.
Ya know I didn't think
anything could scare you.
Everything is going
fine now, isn't it.
We haven't gotten into
any trouble to speak of...
And the road north
should be easy...
Did you notice?
The two of us haven't
been fighting at all.
I am still afraid, though.
And this is precisely
what I am afraid of.
You have to know.
It's the end of
our journey isn't it?
Well, yes, that is scary.
However...
There is something
that is much worse.
'Tis all right if
you do not understand.
Because it would
disturb me greatly
if you knew what I was
thinking all of a sudden.
I do not mind if
you go downstairs.
Just please do not
try to make me jealous.
It's a lucky thing
for you I like selfish,
possessive girls
who hate themselves.
Did you two have
a big fight or something?
Does it seem as though
we don't get along?
Absolutely.
Well, I'm a merchant, you see.
The old man isn't...
We don't have
much to talk about.
Oh, yeah, I met with
Rigoro today, by the way.
You were right...
His beard was quite gloomy...
I'm sure...
I don't know how you
handled someone so depressing.
That skill of his
was pretty impressive.
Well...
He must have really liked you.
You realize if you
partnered up with him,
the other merchants
wouldn't stand a chance
against the two you.
Possibly, but that wasn't
what our visit was about.
I see.
That makes sense.
He is far too committed to
that dilapidated mansion of his.
I assume you saw the garden.
I did, and it
was equally impressive.
Those glass windows were huge...
I've never seen
panes that big before.
I don't know how he stands them.
They would drive me crazy.
Well?
Well apparently
they came to some sort
of conclusion
at the meeting.
What did they conclude?
Actually, I didn't even ask.
And you did you
manage to find out?
Did I?
That guy doesn't
tell me anything...
But it would certainly
be nice to know what happened.
Especially if we were able
hear it directly from him.
I can appreciate why
you would feel that way.
I'm afraid I'm interested
in something else, though.
What do you really want?
I'm sure you have
some other motive
beyond using me to find out
what happened at a meeting.
You get right to
the point, don't you?
Didn't you come here to
do a little bargaining...
Take care of some
business, something like that?
I'm just like everyone else.
I'm trying to make
as big of a profit
as possible off this thing.
What else would
I want besides that?
Perhaps avoid
a devastating loss?
I wish people
had only one eye...
It's hard to watch
2 at the same time.
You're right.
I'm trying to keep a loss
from happening as well.
Meaning what?
I've been doing some
trading with stone statues.
You mean the Holy Mother.
You saw one.
Unfortunately,
I'm just dragging stone.
The profit margins aren't all
they could be at the moment.
That won't change
unless the church approves
an indulgence for
praying with the statue.
A considerable number
of people buy them already
thanks to the Northern
Expedition every year.
Another reason religious
belief is a blessing.
True.
Although I can't
exactly make a profit
from a blessing, now can I?
At least for
a time I was selling
a decent amount of statues.
And then they suddenly
decided to cut me off.
Now I realize
no one will turn their back
on you faster
than the church.
I heard their
authority in the south
has been rapidly deteriorating
over the past months.
I saw that I and
my goods were going
down with a sinking ship...
and I knew I couldn't
let that happen.
So I thought
I could make a decent
profit and move
somewhere else.
Naturally.
If I can make enough coin
off of what's going on here,
I'll be able to head south
and forget about the church.
Might be time for me to go
on a pilgrimage myself.
With that being said...
I don't suppose you
would lend me some money.
You see, I get to
the point quickly as well.
Would you consider
selling your companion?
Next episode:
Wolf and Lonely Smile