No. I do not wish to be alone.
Holo, please.
Oh, wait, I remember.
There is another who loves me.
And who are you to me?
No... Who am I to you?
Please tell me!
[HOLO] I do not know
what I saw in him.
In the end.. he was really just
an ignorant merchant, no more.
Yes he was. If he
couldn't find a way
to maintain the affections
of someone as beautiful as you
I would have to conclude
that he was a failure as a man.
Unlike Lawrence,
you will stand by my side
and protect me no matter
what happens, will you not?
I will.
This world could take from me
all the riches I've acquired
but I would still
have you to love me.
Craft Lawrence is nothing
but a spineless coward.
[LAWRENCE]
Shut up!
You can't say
I didn't warn you.
You were so cock
sure of yourself
when all this
started but now...
I never even saw it coming.
How could I let this happen?
You let down your guard.
Tell me I'm wrong.
No, you're right.
Anyway, what did
you want to ask me?
If you're looking for a loan,
I'm afraid I can't
help you out right now.
I'm trying to see
which way the wind blows.
I feel like a navigator.
Like I'm in
the middle of a storm
plotting a course to dry land.
The market is just
so hard to predict.
Don't bother trying.
You can't keep pyrite's
value from rising
anymore than you could
control a rising tide.
The more people who
want to buy the pyrite,
the longer those holding out
are willing to wait to sell.
I don't see the signs
that the prices will
drop off any time soon.
Unless you can
convince our Almighty God
to tell you what's
going to happen tomorrow.
I'll just have
to turn myself into a god.
Amarty won't let
himself be snared
by any typical drop in prices.
Wait, are you planning
on crashing it?
Can you think of a better way?
No choice, be it
one way or the other,
I've got to make sure
all his precious rocks
are worthless by the time
the sun sets tomorrow.
It's got to be a plan
Amarty will never see coming.
One that will crash the market,
is that even possible?
Now feast your eyes.
You've got a lot
of faith in rocks.
You can't drop
the wheat trade for mining.
My sources say it'll
double in value tomorrow.
You sure about that?
Practically certain.
If you don't keep your
shops open for the festival
you'll miss out on
a golden opportunity.
So you're telling us
we shouldn't be buying
wheat now, is that it?
Ah, Master Lawrence.
A letter?
Yes sir, your friend asked
me to write it down for her.
She only left
a few minutes ago.
But don't worry,
I was very happy to help sir.
What?
200 silver in cash.
300 silver-worth
of iron pyrite
and properties totalling
another 200 silver.
This is Amarty's net worth.
Yes.
This looks like
Amarty's handwriting.
Holo... I'll bet
she was able to talk
him into signing another bond.
Give me all the cash I have
stored with you immediately!
I said now!
What's wrong with him?
He's that merchant.
Hey!
Watch where you're going!
Excuse me.
Sure.
Good evening.
There's nothing for you
to look so nervous about.
I'm only here to talk business.
Which is all the more reason
for me to be concerned.
May I bend your
ear for a moment?
Why not...
I presume this has
to do with the contract.
It does.
Well? What exactly
did you have in mind?
Let's get straight
to the point then,
I would like to sell you
a certain amount of iron pyrite.
500 Trenni silver-worth of
Iron Pyrite, to be more precise
and to be fair, I'll accept
its current market value.
You're joking.
I'm completely serious.
You must be aware
by now of the profits
I'm making off
the sale of iron pyrite.
What could you
possibly hope to gain
by increasing
my wholesale stock?
Are you saying
the rumors are true?
Do you care more
for your precious silver
than you do for Holo?
Are you really that cold?
In the name of Saint Francis,
saint of merchants and this
Lohen Merchants Association,
I swear I shall
do the following:
I will profess
my undying love!
He is just like
a heroic prince!
There's only one thing
to do, we have to find
a way to observe our
competitor's actions directly.
Sounds sneaky.
You are a heroic prince, Amarty.
Oh, don't mind me.
You can be sure, I do
still care about the girl.
Holo has already woven herself
into the fabric of my life.
Then why?
I'm not giving you the pyrite
in what would be considered
a traditional sale.
I'd like to sell
it to you on credit.
It's like this, I
want to give you
500 Trenni silver
coins-worth of pyrite
tomorrow evening, but at
its current market price today.
Well, then shouldn't
we wait and discuss
this transaction
tomorrow evening?
No.
Not for this deal,
you pay me right now.
I will take 500 Trenni
silver from you tonight,
and tomorrow evening,
I will give you the amount
of iron pyrite
that 500 Trenni buys
at today's closing price.
Understand?
So if the price for iron pyrite
happens to go up tomorrow,
you're still agreeing
to sell it back to me
at the lower price
the pyrite's fetching today.
You are a really smart kid,
exactly right.
However, if the value of
iron pyrite goes down tomorrow,
I'm agreeing to buy it from
you at today's higher price.
Right.
So it's really no different
from any standard exchange.
When you sell
something before
the price jumps,
you're angry.
But if you sell before
the price drops you're happy.
There's nothing
different about that...
Hold on, that's wrong.
That's correct, but why?
Because you don't need cash.
You just buy the pyrite today
with the promise
of tomorrow's sale.
Once you had it, regardless
of how its worth fluctuated,
you simply had to pay
back the original price.
If pyrite becomes more
valuable you make a profit.
That's how credit works.
So when tomorrow comes,
if the price of pyrite
has dropped by any amount,
I'll make a profit
on the exchange
because I already sold
it to you at today's price.
Wow, there's no end
to ways we can make money.
Well, do you think
you understand it now?
I guess so, but let
me just say it again
to make sure we're clear,
I'll buy 500 silver-worth
of pyrite from you now
and if its value goes up
tomorrow then so do my profits.
But if the bottom
should fall out tomorrow,
then it's too bad for me...
I could lose everything.
It's sort of like--
No.
This is exactly like
I'm challenging you to duel,
winner take all.
The deal's
still in my favor,
even if we assume
the price of pyrite drops.
I simply gauge
the heat of the market
and sell my stock
before it goes down again.
I can bail out at any time
but you have to
stay until the end.
It doesn't seem
fair that my side
of the trade is
protected with
a moderate increase in value
while yours
offers you no way out.
A contract like
this is dishonorable.
I have to sign
my name in a bet
where I can only
gain if you lose.
I disagree.
It seems to me the risks
weigh evenly on both of us.
You're still forgetting
one of the most
important variables here.
Holo could shred that
contract she signed with you.
Even if you manage
to pay off Holo's debt
of 1,000 silver coins...
for you, everything
hinges on whether or not
she'll accept your proposal.
The risk which I am facing
is vastly inferior to the one
you've chosen to bear.
The two of you have
had a serious falling out,
or so I've heard.
Since we've been together,
Holo has cried in
my arms only 3 times.
She is irresistible
when she's like that.
But she's also
as stubborn as a mule.
She ends up saying
things she regrets later.
So I wouldn't rely on rumors.
I'll take your bet.
Because... Because...
At first I was certain
I would turn down
your challenge because
I thought it would
appear spiteful.
I knew I'd take
everything of yours,
but now I see
you leave me no choice.
So, if that's the way you want
it to play out, so be it.
By the time
I'm finished with you,
there'll be nothing left
of you except your shame.
Fine. Then let's make
this official with a handshake.
May the best man win.
Cheers.
That's good beer.
Any bright ideas?
Wheat sales usually pick up
at the end of
the festival, don't they?
They do.
At that time, there's a rumor
I'd like you to spread.
If it's risky,
you can count me out.
There's a risk if you
go spreading it yourself,
but there's no harm if it
comes from the boy, right?
When the time's right,
do me a favor...
I need him to
say this loudly.
"Looks like the price of
wheat's gonna keep going up."
Hold on, that's your big plan?
You want to lower the price
of pyrite with a rumor?
Yes.
Most of the people
buying pyrite
came to the festival
to sell their goods.
Normally they purchase wheat
with the profits they've made,
in order to stock up
for the winter.
If they hear that the price
of wheat is going up,
everyone will panic and sell off
their remaining pyrite
and purchase
what they came here
for in the first
place, the wheat.
I'm hoping that the rumor
of increasing wheat prices
will cause a run
on the market
and the price of pyrite
will inevitably fall.
And when the run
reaches a certain point,
the pyrite will plummet down
to practically nothing.
I'm sorry to
hear that, Lawrence.
I had you pegged as a much
smarter merchant than that.
What if I told you
I could start the run
by selling off
a huge stock of pyrite?
How much?
Well, 1,000 Trenni.
1,000? No, think of the risk
you're taking! If it drops--
I don't care how much
its value drops.
Have you lost your mind or
are you really that stupid?
No, I just need
500 silver-worth
of pyrite by
the time the dust settles.
And if I can
manage to do that,
how far it falls
won't matter to me.
I see!
You're selling on credit!
Precisely.
So, I guess
that's my only part
in your little scheme, huh?
There's just one more thing.
I need you to buy up
pyrite for me.
Wait, please don't tell
me you found the buyer
before you found
the iron pyrite.
I've been so busy lately,
I didn't have the time.
You're dead.
I have to buy in a way
that can be kept secret
so I don't spook the market.
Lawrence...
You know all
the local merchants.
How hard would
it be to get each of them
to buy a little
extra iron pyrite?
You may have to pay a premium
to get them to do it
and that's okay.
You can tell them if
they buy a larger amount,
I'll pay them in
Lumione gold coins.
Of course, I would
pay you for your efforts,
which would make
it worth your while.
I can't do it.
Perfect, we can--
Marc, you do realize
I'm paying you, right?
It'll be much more
than you're used to making.
How can you turn down
such an easy score?
Easy score.
You know I'm right.
I'm not asking for
an investment from you.
You'll get paid in cash.
What could you
possibly have to lose?
My guess is you could pay me
10 Lumione gold coins at most.
That's an unbelievable price
for simply acting as my buyer.
What's the problem?
It's not like I'm asking
you to go climb a mountain,
dig a new mine, and bring
the stuff back yourself.
You want me to go around
my market and buy up
a lot of pyrite.
That's much worse.
What's worse about that?
You have no risk in this deal.
You're buying pyrite
through your connections.
Is that really
so much to ask?
Okay, I could see
why you'd think that,
but that's because
you're a travelling merchant.
But I'm a town merchant
so this marketplace is
the whole world to me.
Town merchants who
try to make quick money
at the expense of others suffer
for it in their daily business.
This store is my life,
but it's not just my good
name at stake here.
There's the question
of my honor.
Not to mention the honor
of my wife, our families,
even my regular
customers would suffer.
Everything's on the line.
You have to
understand, Lawrence.
I've built a life here
and nobody will
trust a town merchant
who jumps at every chance
to make money the easy way.
Sure, it's no big fault
if we make a little money
on side deals from time
to time. Everybody does that.
But buying up pyrite
to help you crash the market
for a mere 10 gold coins
is totally different.
How do you think people here
would treat me after that?
To them I'd be
nothing more than a leech
that destroyed his business
because he wanted
to take a stupid gamble.
What can you possibly offer
me that would match that loss?
I know I'm just a small shop
but that makes my name
that much more important.
If I lost my reputation
I don't think there's
any amount of gold
that would be enough
for me to buy it back.
I can't risk that...
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
After meeting your companion,
I understand.
A girl like that is only
going to have her heart
changed by
the grandest of gestures
and even that may not work.
I only saw you together once
but I could already tell
how much trouble she was.
Just show a little backbone.
The innkeeper showed me
a signed marriage certificate.
As her guardian, all I have
to do is add my signature
and their marriage
will be complete.
If I hadn't seen that
I might feel a little bit
more certain about all this.
In life, the only
certain thing is death.
But you would have
already quit by now
if you didn't
still have some hope.
Yeah.
You're a complete ass.
Is there anyone else
who can help?
I guess I can try asking
Batos to see if he has any.
You know,
why don't you ask him
if he'll go and talk
to that woman for you.
Wait, what woman?
Diana, she's the
chronicler you met.
You didn't forget her?
She's the de facto
governess over that district.
For as long as I can remember,
anyone who wants
to get to the alchemists
has to do it through her.
As a group, they make
easy targets for the church.
You wouldn't believe
what they do to maintain
some amount of privacy.
There wouldn't be
nearly as many of them
around here if she didn't
watch over them like she does.
And?
And don't you think
alchemists might have pyrite?
It's the perfect way
to make a trade
without affecting the market.
You simply get it from people
who couldn't care
less about the market.
Yes, I'm a genius, I know.
Of course,
the alchemists' pyrite
will have been
completely untouched.
I'm sorry, I wish
I could do more for you.
I can't be seen
as a part of this plan
but you know
I'm pulling for you.
Please, you've helped me
quite enough, thank you!
Your idea is
money in the bank.
Now that I think of it...
It'd require some
finesse on my part...
but I can probably
crank up the old rumor mill
without it coming back on me.
Really?
Check back,
I'll do my best to see
if I can find some
interested buyers for you.
The wind will blow your way.
Knock 'em dead.
Sure.
Yeah!
Oh, Lawrence, you're
so cute when you're excited.
If she could see the look
on your face right now,
your little princess
would be yours for sure.
What does that mean?
Next Episode:
Wolf, Hope, and Despair