There are so many people.
I could stay here
and watch this all day.
Somehow it all comes
back to food and drink.
At least this town looks
pretty normal for a change.
I mean, everything appears
to be running smoothly.
Even as the wolf
packs battle fiercely
among the trees for
the land they claim...
From far away
the forest may appear
surprisingly peaceful
depending how you see it.
If someone had
exceptional hearing
couldn't they tell what
was going on from afar?
Do you see that
ship over there?
It seems the tax
they are levying
on its goods is too high
and so the ship's owner
doesn't want to sell.
"I already told you the price
for these nails is set."
They call that a hostage tax.
They can see from his fur
that he's got money so they
try to slip in extra taxes.
The skinny man
is saying something
in response
about the expedition
to the north being cancelled
and how that has
thrown off the markets
in the whole city.
He's telling the man he should
be happy to get anything at all.
That cancelled expedition
is causing trouble everywhere.
He is threatening
to take the man
and his fur to
the courts to settle it.
There are four other groups
all having a similar
conversation.
The tax is too high.
The cancelled expedition.
The status of
entering the town.
You did not really order
those for my benefit, did you?
My drinking serves
you in some way.
If I am drunk on
alcohol then you are free
to get drunk on
the prospect of future profits.
Thinking about business
is cheaper than alcohol
and to be sure it has
less of a hangover.
When I am drunk
I am less likely
to interrupt your planning
with my obstinate
chattering,
and more compliant
to your whims.
It is a relatively
inexpensive investment.
You are a wise wolf.
Well, your face always
appears so much less
of a frowning mask when you
are thinking about business...
and that makes my
drinking all the more fun.
No!
How could this
great wolf be undone
by as few as 7 drinks
of such a watery stash?
You're worn out from
travelling too, remember...
Try to get some rest.
Don't you worry...
I won't do anything too
ridiculous while you're asleep.
Oh, I very much doubt that.
Time for her highness
to close her eyes.
Open for business?
[HELENA] Yes, sir! Come in.
I just finished
patching my apron.
Like it?
It's so nice I can't
take my eyes off of it.
That's why.
I always wondered why people
had so much trouble
looking at me in the eyes.
It's because my apron
is too pretty...
Or, they could be
afraid of your eyes...
After all people
do tend to get
a bit intimidated
around beautiful things.
Too bad because I can tell
instantly if I trust someone
by looking in their eyes
but if they never look,
I'll never know.
And do you trust me?
Travelling merchants
are much better flirts
than regular townspeople.
So, will you be
eating or drinking?
I'd like two orders
of roasted tail
packaged to take with me.
The cook just left to purchase
supplies at the port.
I don't have
anywhere else to go.
There's really no rush
In that case...
There's no better
way to pass the time
than with something
to drink in your hand.
Okay, might as well.
It's unusual that a travelling
merchant actually
stops in for food,
normally they come by
looking for information.
I usually pay for both.
I was curious about
one thing in particular.
What's with all the merchants
camped out in front
of the town entrance?
Oh, those are all the merchants
who are involved in trading
furs this time of year.
Is that so?
Yeah, it's about the fur.
Most of them are
the foreign merchants
who come from
all over to buy fur,
and the rest of them
are craftsmen who sell tools
to make the fur into
pretty things to wear.
The reason they're
all waiting so patiently
is because the town council
is having its big
meeting right now
to decide whether or
not even to sell the fur.
You mean the 50 man
meeting, right?
That's right.
Trading fur is
forbidden until its over.
The ban on fur trading
means those craftsmen
will sit on the money
they've saved to
buy processing tools
until they're
sure it'll be lifted.
I don't understand why people
are so hesitant
to sell the fur.
I've heard it has to
do with the expedition
to the north being cancelled.
So nobody wants to be first
in the market
with a large amount.
That's business. Like me.
My place is usually
packed with people
at this time of year.
I wonder if it'd
be okay to sell furs
to the merchants
gathered outside the town.
Those merchants only
buy for a good price...
unlike the knights and
mercenaries going on expedition.
Sometimes they even pay me
with beautiful fur clothing
that's really only fit
for a princess to wear.
I make double when
they pay me like that.
But before the fur
becomes clothing
it is relatively inexpensive.
If it gets sold
before being processed
the towns people miss out
on most of their profits.
You're a really smart guy.
But I haven't told you anything
you couldn't have learned
from any other hostess in town.
If you repeat to anyone
what I'm about to tell you...
I'll deny it.
Deal.
There are about
40 men in that meeting
who are thinking
about barring
the merchants outside
town from buying any fur,
even though they know it might
enrage the rest of
the people in the fur trade.
Who gave you this information?
Who knows?
Men usually show
their appreciation
of a bar by leaving
good and drunk.
Are you sure you
don't want another drink?
You're definitely putting me
in the mood to lose myself.
[COOK] Two
roasted tails ready!
Okay! Now I have
a question for you.
Do you have a wife?
I'm free to do what I want
when it comes to trade.
However, she does keep me
on a pretty short leash.
Well, whoever she is,
she's the luckiest girl I know.
Darn the luck.
Those are loaded with furs...
and those... and
those... and those too.
And that's good news...
There's lots of money.
I will not allow it.
You may never sell my tail.
You'd be too tough to skin.
But I can see in your eyes you
are willing to sell anything.
Come on that's only
half the story.
Think about the strawberries
you've seen me pick
from town to town
while we travel have you
ever seen me sell one of them?
I only ever resell what
I first have purchased,
It's one of the few hard
and fast rules I live by.
So I trust your
information expedition
was fruitful as always.
Yes, it seems as if things
are about to get quite
interesting around here.
Oh yeah. Care to make a wager?
A bet?
I have some meat
in this package.
Tell me which animal and
what part without opening it
and you can eat
anything you want tonight.
You saw all those
travelling merchants
camped out
in front of town, right?
There has to be
something going on with them
or they'd never waste so
much time just waiting there.
They must have
already gotten wind
about the 50 man
meeting's decision
not to let foreign merchants
in on the fur trade this year.
My ears aren't
great but I will hear
if you try to
open that package.
I know that.
Have you got it?
Give me time.
Well, then I'll talk
this out some more.
To orchestrate
something on this scale
would take a large
and powerful group.
The Western
Merchants Association
is known for their fur craft.
Or it could be
some large company
looking to monopolize
the entire fur trade business.
Regardless of that...
You...
Have you figured it out?
I think the preconditions
of this bet we made
were unfairly tilted
before we made it, Lawrence.
Well it's a little too late
to be mentioning
that now don't ya think?
I suppose so, but...
What's your guess?
I don't know the name
you have for it...
but it is from those river
rats with the big flat tails.
Yeah.
I told you the wager
was unfair from the outset.
You already knew?
When we first
came to this town
it puzzled me because
I had no memory of it.
But that has changed now.
All of my memories came
flooding back to me.
When I smelled it,
the memory brought back
tears to my eyes
and I knew in an instant
what was in your package.
You did that on purpose.
Do you think
I would take advantage
of your kindness
with a deception?
Yes, You always
manage to do this to me.
I know I will never
be able to forget your scent.
Nor I yours.
You sound foolish
when you are serious.
Well excuse me for trying.
Does it truly
bother you that much?
You made more than enough
money when we were in Kumersun
to open up a shop
of your own, did you not?
Yeah... plenty in fact...
I do not have any right to keep
you from opening up your shop.
You should be free from trouble
so that you can settle down.
That is all
that I want for you.
Settle down, you've
got a point there.
[AROLDO] A road to the north?
Yes.
Well there hasn't been
all that much snow this year...
so the journey
shouldn't be too bad.
My plan right now
is to go to Nyohila.
So, you're going into
lands that are pagan.
Well, I suppose that is
the life of a merchant.
You carry a bag of money around
to wherever the profit leads.
No matter how big
that bag of money gets
none of us can take
it with us when we die.
Then why even bother
making money at all?
It's a waste of time
if you ask me.
Why bother having any job
at all for that matter,
like running
an inn for example?
Well, that is true.
Will you be
leaving us soon, then?
Not yet...
I want to wait till
the 50 man meeting is over.
You'll only be able
to make half the journey
with the horse
you have right now.
After that
you'll have to trade
it in for
a longer haired breed.
I think I saw one in the stable.
The man who owns that
horse is a northerner.
He probably knows more details
about the road
you'll be travelling too.
What's his name?
His name?
The man's lived here for years
and I can't believe I've
never bothered to get his name.
The only thing
I really know about him
is that he gets
fatter with each passing year.
I'm sorry... but getting
old is not for the weak.
If I run into him I'll mention
you'd like to talk with him.
I'd appreciate it.
Of course, if you're
determined to wait
'till the 50 man meeting is over
you might be here 'till spring.
Their meetings can go
on for that long huh?
A town's fate is directly
tied to the men who run it.
Some years these
meetings are easy
and other times it
can turn out to be
bad for the whole town.
But we all have free will...
We can act against fate.
We're all accountable
for our mistakes
but we make up for
them as best we can.
I can't disagree
with you on that.
You've been here for
three nights, right?
What's your name?
The name's
Craft Lawrence, sir.
My name is Aroldo Ecklund...
In my younger days I could
have made you a belt
that you'd have
been proud to wear...
Now all I can offer is a warm
room and a good night's sleep.
Well that's better than a belt.
He took 5 days to ask me.
Why did it only take you
3 days to ask his name, Aroldo?
If you remember,
your fifth day here
was also the first
time we spoke.
You are not what
I would consider
an excellent
conversationalist.
[EVE] ...and you?
I talk...
Then how about
we have a chat.
Don't you have
business with Rigoro?
Yeah.
Something to drink.
Excuse us.
I don't know why
that man insists
upon heating up his wine.
You appear hesitant with me.
Would you mind telling me why?
It's not every day that I get
to talk with a female merchant.
I'm always more cautious
when I am dealing with
things that are unknown.
You're the first to
see through my disguise
in the past couple of years.
Well, we passed each other in
front of the inn this morning.
My companion has good
instincts about these things.
One should never underestimate
a woman's intuition...
Though I'd normally never
say that dressed like this.
I've come to trust
the instincts of--
My name is Fleur Bolan.
Though the name Fleur isn't
really suitable for business,
so around here I'm known
mostly as Eve Bolan.
My name is Craft Lawrence.
Well, which is it?
Craft or Lawrence?
For business I go by Lawrence.
And I just go by Eve...
I don't like the way Bolan
sounds... And trust me...
I know exactly how much
respect I'd get as a merchant
if I went to work a frilly
pink dress and some make up.
So don't even bother trying
to compliment my looks.
Sure I understand.
I'd prefer not to be
seen as a woman at all
but unfortunately
I'm rather gregarious
so I'm usually the one
who blows my own cover.
I'm quite charming
and I like to talk.
Well I'll let you
know whether or not
you're charming
a little later on.
However, we're only really
meeting each other tonight
and I still don't know why
you'd have any interest in me.
It starts with the fact
that for whatever reason,
Aroldo really
seems to like you...
He's a stubborn old fool
but he has
a good eye for people.
Though he isn't
very likeable himself.
What's that thing
he's always saying?
I'm going on
a pilgrimage next year.
So this girl with you...
Girl?
You know, your companion.
She's a woman.
It's odd for
a merchant to bring
a woman along
with him isn't it?
We just travel together.
I don't think I could explain
it to you even if we were drunk.
I'm not trying to pry.
It appears that you two are
very comfortable with each other
and I can tell it isn't
money that keeps you together,
so she should be fine
with our conversation.
At least I hope so.
Business can
be complicated around here.
I couldn't
just walk up to you
on the street
and say 'let's talk.'
That wouldn't
have worked at all.
It's why I mentioned
Rigoro first.
But the only reason I said
that was to get your attention.
You do want to meet
with Rigoro, don't you?
Yes.
Do you mind if I ask
what interest he is to you?
Rigoro is this
town's chronicler.
I was hoping he'd
be able to tell me
about the old stories
and legends from this area.
That is definitely
a new one to me.
Not an angle
on the fur trade?
Of course, I am
a merchant after all.
I would never turn down
any insights that could
lead to a greater profit...
But one should be cautious.
My companion
would prefer I... not.
To be sure, his library
is filled with stacks of books
that date back many generations,
past anyone's recollection.
He's a gloomy
bearded sot who'd love
to lose himself
in his books all day.
But first
he'd resign as secretary
of that meeting if he could.
He hates it.
Is that so?
All the townspeople
who'd like to sit down
and talk with him would
make a long list indeed.
If you were just to
approach him out of the blue
you'd be greeted
with blank stares
and get thrown
out for sure.
I have a business relationship
with the church in town here.
It's been ongoing and
we've remained on good terms.
In addition to
his other duties,
Rigoro has a regular
job as a scribe
for some of their
administrative needs...
so we've known each
other for some time now.
I know I've only recently
made your acquaintance
Mr. Craft Lawrence
but if I may be so bold,
you seem to operate
on a different level
from your average
merchant in the square.
You're giving me
too much credit.
It's premature to
shake on it just yet.
You don't strike me as someone
who'd get sweaty palms
over a business deal.
I haven't been able to
read anything off you
throughout this
entire conversation.
Let's try this.
I don't really
need to know what type
of business you're in,
but I do have another question.
Go ahead.
What do you charge
for introductions?
I'm not after money if
that's what you're saying...
but I would like someone
to talk to every now and again.
I'm absolutely serious.
I know... it sounds
a little strange...
But you wouldn't
believe what comfort
it is to me to
have a fellow merchant
I can talk to without having
to keep up this
troublesome disguise.
It's worth more to me than
any of your Lima Gold coins.
I notice you didn't
say Lumione gold,
so it must have its price.
A girl's got to make a living.
In the end it all comes
down to money, doesn't it?
Of course...
I've never met this companion
of yours so this is just us...
I hope she's fine with that...
I've heard a jealous woman
can ruin even the best wine.
Oh I don't think
she'll get jealous.
Are you sure...?
I've never known any man
who could predict
the thoughts of a woman.
Or one who understood
what she really meant.
It's not like there's anything
salacious going on between us.
I just wouldn't
mind having someone
to talk to every so often.
I may look rough--
but you're charming
and like to talk.
I'm guilty on both counts.
As long as my companion
doesn't get angry about it.
Of course, we wouldn't
want that, now would we?
Next Episode:
Wolf and Reckless Negotiation