How is Lawrence going
to make it through?
To be honest,
I really don't know...
I'm afraid he doesn't have
enough pyrite to
make a difference.
We'll just have to pray that
Diana's assistant comes in time.
If he sells too little
it could just get
people's hopes up that
there'll be more to buy.
If that happens he could end up
pushing the price even higher,
which is exactly the opposite
of what he's trying to do.
Can't Amarty just
act like he's going
to make his sale in
order to trick Lawrence?
That's what I'd do.
He sure can.
You're a smart one.
Where could Holo be?
It is only the foolish
who frustrate at every turn.
Your calmness is a sure
sign of your control Amarty.
Holo.
My love.
Just shut up.
[MARKET CALLER]
We have a buy!
How much is it going to go up?
Really? I can't believe
it's gone up that much.
Yeah, if it keeps
going like this,
it could move another
20 percent by this afternoon.
I cashed out too early.
I should have held on.
The price keeps
creeping up, doesn't it?
Amarty is holding on to
800 silver-worth of pyrite ...
that is, if I remember
correctly, of course...
And 20 percent more?
That would be 960 for him.
He'd sell what he's holding
for sure if it got that high.
Another 40 would be pretty
easy for him to scare up.
Amarty's contract with Lawrence
would have to
be sealed after that.
And all that could happen
before the poisoned
credit can take effect.
The poisoned credit?
Huh...
Still no word.
Where is Diana's assistant?
If Holo's been with
Amarty all this time...
then she could have picked
up quite a lot from him.
Stop it.
[MAN A] Here it goes.
[MAN B] I never
thought it'd get this high.
[MAN C] I still
think I can do better.
Not good.
It must have been Amarty
who made the deal with Diana.
I don't get it.
Doesn't Lawrence get paid
even if he loses to Amarty
in the pyrite market?
That's correct.
I thought merchants
liked making money.
What's his problem?
Because he would
also suffer a huge loss.
And this is the type of thing
that can't be bought
back with gold coins.
Pyrite?
I'm assuming
this has to do with
getting your hands on
the alchemists stockpile.
Please don't
tell me you found
the buyer before you
found the iron pyrite.
I've been busy.
I didn't have the time.
Someone else has
already bought some.
Please allow me to
handle the negotiations.
I'm sure I'll know
something by tomorrow
but I'm afraid I don't
know where to look for you.
Oh, in front of
the mineral merchant's stand
at the marketplace
should be fine.
Come on.
[MARKET CALLER]
Another buy!
You have already traded me for
1,000 of your precious coins.
Say something!
He doesn't know
where Holo is either.
[MARKET CALLER]
We have a sale!
Is it Amarty?
Make way... Please...
I have to get through.
[MARKET CALLER]
Yes?
It wasn't him.
[MARKET CALLER]
Another buy!
[MAN A] It's moving quick.
[MAN B] Things could
really pick up now.
[GOATEE GUY] It's time to sell.
[BEARD GUY] Nah,
I think we should wait.
Holo! Oh, it's you.
I didn't mean to startle you,
but one of our customers
wants to purchase his
barley using the iron pyrite.
How much of it?
He wants 250 Trenni.
Get back here as
fast as you can.
Right.
[BEARD GUY] It's a sale.
[MOUSTACHE GUY]
I'm holding out.
It's got to go up more.
So you know Amarty
bought 500 silver-worth
of pyrite from Lawrence,
but he only bought it
on paper-- on credit.
The actual exchange happens
when the market closes tonight.
What does that mean to you?
It means that if
the price goes up,
his paper is worth something
but if it drops he'll never
be able to sell it... right?
That's exactly right...
Who would want something
that might be worthless?
If the iron pyrite
happens to return
to its original value as a rock,
the 500 silver they have on
paper becomes worthless junk.
So then whoever has the
certificate at the end loses.
That's right.
And that's why it's dangerous
to deal in poisoned credit.
Holo? Where are you?
You better hurry up kid.
[MAN A] Another buy!
[MARKET CALLER]
More iron pyrite!
It's way too high.
Fewer and fewer
buyers on the board.
I could sell
everything I have now.
I'm selling!
I need that 400 silver-worth
of pyrite from Diana,
then I could really start
the market flowing my way.
If only she'd come right now.
Lawrence, I've got it!
I'm sorry it took so long.
250 silver-worth of rocks.
Hey, what's the
matter Lawrence?
Oh, nothing...
Thank you, Lunt.
To be safe I should wait
for the rest of the pyrite
from Diana's assistant.
But...
If she doesn't come...
and she might not.
Yeah... That's true...
Just a minute ago
I sold thinking
that she'd never
make it in time.
But I'm already
in it this deep.
It's now or never.
What just happened?
Someone placed an order.
The winds are changing.
I'll have to wait
for Diana's pyrite now.
Hey, that's Amarty up there.
He must have figured out
what I'm trying to do.
She'll be here...
Just hold on for
a little bit longer!
It doesn't matter.
We're out of time.
Please. You have to hurry.
[DIANA'S ASSISTANT]
Are you Mr. Lawrence?
You are, are you not?
Yes, I am
I have a message for you
from my mistress, Diana.
Yes, what is it?
The negotiations have failed.
The seller backed out
at the last minute...
That's all she had to say.
She sends her regrets that she
couldn't come through for you.
[DIANA'S ASSISTANT]
I'll take my leave.
I have been looking
all over for you.
Lawrence... Lawrence...
Hey, Lawrence!
Lawrence! Listen to me!
Oh, sorry, Lunt...
I'm jus-- sorry...
This has all been a lot
of work for nothing.
Would you take
a message to Marc for me?
Tell him it's over,
and that the plan didn't work.
I'm happy though.
At least I still get
1,000 silver from Amarty.
That's a huge day's
haul for any merchant.
Well...
Here's your share anyway.
Stop it!
It can't be true... You can't
just give up like that!
My master taught me that
a real merchant never gives up.
He keeps on fighting.
Fortune and gold
don't favor those
who sit around praying for
it to fall from the sky.
They come to those who don't
have any idea when to quit.
I should shut up.
Marc told me you'd beat me
to a pulp if I told you this...
but I just can't hold it in!
I fell for her
the first time I saw her.
I am madly in love with
your woman friend Holo!
You can hit me now.
You're right...
I do feel like
beating someone...
Fortunately for you,
it's myself.
I almost forgot...
People who don't
know when to quit
are also the ones who end up
achieving their
wildest dreams in life.
And you're looking at someone
who does not quit.
Merchants are constantly
making plans, guessing profits,
and doing the math
once reality sets in.
If I trade in 'this'
I can make 'that' ...
If I sell now, I'll "win."
It's important
to think that way.
Honestly, I don't
think there's an end
to the number of outcomes
that you can dream up.
Too much
thinking as a merchant
can drive you crazy, though.
Soon, it starts to look like
every trade has too much risk.
The only way not to
get lost in all of it
is to have
something that guides you.
Whatever that is, as a
merchant you have to find it.
And once you do,
and you know its worth...
even the craziest ideas
don't seem too risky.
You just believe them.
Because they're true.
Once I sell these stones,
it'll be time for you to
spread the rumor I taught you.
Okay?
Yes! Right
Tell me, Lunt,
do you still believe in God?
Oh, never mind.
[MARKET CALLER]
You're back again, huh?
Selling...
I am selling too.
You fool.
Hey, don't look at me.
Unlike someone I know,
at least Diana has class.
When it was over,
Amarty didn't take
that much of a loss.
I'd say the blow to
his ego was far greater.
[BARTENDER] That's
your payment when you
mess with someone's woman.
That's all you really missed.
I was rather hoping
we would have completely
drained him
of all his resources.
I can never forgive him
for what he said to me.
I will never tell you.
Please don't.
I actually think
it's better that way.
However, that hardly means
this unfortunate
matter is settled between us.
My apologies.
Do you even know the place
where you went
astray with me?
Yeah.
Believe me
I know all too well.
Well, sort of...
When I saw that contract
between you and Amarty,
it was just plain stupid of
me to go it alone, wasn't it?
The only real mistake I made
was not believing in you...
I should have realized
you were trying to tell me
you were Diana's other buyer
when I saw those
white feathers in your cloak.
I panicked.
When Amarty went
up to the vendor
I became convinced
I was in a trap you'd set.
What?! What do you mean?
Nothing...
I thought maybe
you were tricking me
into selling
before it was time.
You have to understand,
I really believed
you were with Amarty then.
Lucky me...
It turns out
I was wrong about that.
You were really trying
to signal me that Amarty
already had enough and
it was time for me to sell.
But I was stuck in my head
and couldn't stop
second-guessing.
And the marriage
certificate...
You actually signed it...
but I thought
about it... a lot.
And I figure
that was just to get me
angry enough to
confront you, am I right?
Idiot, I was
waiting for you up...
Never mind. Go on.
When we were in
Lubinheigen you told me
that things would be easier if
we didn't beat around the bush.
Do you remember?
You said you would rather
we just got things out in the
open, even if it meant fighting.
I misjudged you
from the very beginning.
The other night,
when you got upset over Yoitz...
the last thing you said was...
I'm sorry.
I really thought
you were through with me.
But it wasn't like that.
You were coming to your senses.
Right?
How can one man
be so clueless?
Honestly, I have seen
clearer thinking
from beasts of the forest
than I have from you
in the past two days.
You nearly ruined my plans.
You actually
thought I was plotting
against you for
your destruction?
And on top of that
you could not just back off
and let me handle it!
It is true that we
have only known each other
a short time... but I did
not think the connection
we shared was so
completely ephemeral.
I guess I am
eternally optimistic.
Or would you
really cast me off.
You're the only travelling
partner I want.
There's only one thing
I've ever been any good at,
and that's trading... and
it takes time to change...
So whenever it comes to anything
outside the world of a merchant
you would do well to
think of me as a child.
Even still, I do want to
continue travelling with you.
Okay then...
Tell me who I am to you, first.
It's impossible for me to put
into words.
Is that so?
Perhaps when your
brain has matured.
Believe me, a couple more
weeks like this and I'll be old.
Pain makes one wise.
Do you mind if
I ask you a question?
It's just...
I was wondering...
What exactly did
you say to Diana
to convince her
to sell you the pyrite?
It was easy enough to
figure out your entire plan
from the half
Amarty told me about
though I must say
that I was impressed
with what you had devised...
You can be quite the merchant
when you put your
mind to it Lawrence.
You called her Diana, yes?
My visit had nothing
at all to do with your plan.
So? Why did you go see her?
I sought her help on
a matter very dear to me.
I found her from
the scent on the letter.
Which was no mean feat
considering the smells
which surrounded her.
Well, that must
have been fun for you.
I asked her to make up
a new story about Yoitz
and how it still
existed in the north.
I also asked her to help me make
sure it got back to you somehow.
But all she did was convince me
to tell her loads of my stories,
which I did,
and then she refused
to do what I asked of her.
Really?
The very moment I concluded
my humiliating tale
of our situation
your boorish hand was
pounding at the front door.
Is anyone there?
Afterwards, that heinous
woman thought better
of the plan that she
herself had formulated...
She concluded that
the best way to divine
your true worth was
to test your resolve.
That would explain
what she said when I left...
Do your best.
I was also privileged
to hear that final
inane question
you asked of her.
Have you by chance
heard any legends
about pagan gods
mating with humans?
Yes, there are many like that.
Apparently there are all
sorts of scintillating tales
of gods and humans mating...
If that is your desire...
I could grant it.
Will you be gentle to me?
But not now...
I have completely
lost my appetite
after talking to that woman.
You are aware she is
not human, are you not?
Not a human?
Those feathers you saw that
were scattered about the room?
Those were hers.
She is actually a giant bird,
much larger than you.
She fell in love
with a travelling priest
and spent a life with
him building a church.
Eventually the priest
became suspicious of her
since no matter how much
time passed she never aged...
The end of the story is
too sad to tell again.
I want to see
my home again, Lawrence.
Even if it is no longer there.
What will you do
when we get to Yoitz?
Humans are capable
of amazing things.
That we are.
If only you were on
fire for me that way.
Well, if I was drunk enough,
I guess I might
be able to get close.
If you get drunk
who will carry me to bed,
did you think of that?
You are an idiot.
Next Episode:
Wolf and Playful Days