You know, this is not bad.
So you are awake.
This is not bad at all.
Luckily in here I will
not be as cold as you.
Wow, that's great;
I'm really happy for you.
It may help to
know I am still cold.
Remember, I am more
delicate than you.
Geez.
Look, stew!
What?
It looks just like
the burnt part of a stew!
[stomach grumbling]
You say there is a variety
of high-proof alcohol
to be found in Laynos?
That's right.
And they should
have plenty on hand,
in case we get
stranded by the snow.
Then I hope it
starts snowing harder.
Of course you do.
There's just one thing...
Laynos is widely
known for its fur trade.
They might sell wolf fur.
Promise me you won't get upset.
Do you know that I am
often hunted by wolves?
And I am known to
sometimes hunt rats.
What I mean is that
hunting and being hunted
is quite normal to me,
why would I become upset?
If you think about it, though,
humans are the
incomprehensible ones.
After all, you trade
your own people, do you not?
Are you talking
about slave traders?
It's a profitable
and very necessary trade.
Do you see how
you do not hesitate
to speak of this slavery?
Well, I share a similar
indifference to hunters.
However, you get anxious
around male hunters, do you not?
Especially when
they are hunting me.
Yeah, I suppose I do...
I get kind of panicky.
With more feeling.
I get panicky.
And why do you?
I'd rather not say.
Because you are embarrassed?!
What do you think?
Looks like they're in
the same line of work.
I think we still
have a little while to go
before we get into town though.
All of these people...
Are they what you would
call a market for believers?
They would be gathered outside
a church if that were the case.
But it does seem
odd to be setting up
shop right outside
of the town's walls.
I most certainly do not
believe they are doing business.
The good news is
the gates are still open.
That means whatever this
is isn't a political thing.
Apparently excitement
always follows us.
Which isn't exactly,
a good thing.
Why are you making that face?
For your information,
I am quite aware
that you have been put
through extraordinary distress
after extraordinary distress
since we began
travelling together.
However, I do
hope you will remember
none of the trouble
we experienced was my fault.
For example...
Well, yes, I do suppose
that was partially my fault...
But if you were not so greedy,
it never would
have been an issue...
The following disaster was due
solely to your
extensive greed...
After that, you panicked
and can only blame
your failure on yourself...
Am I wrong?
The words you are speaking
make sense, but still...
Still what?
I'm just not entirely
convinced...
You may not be the direct cause
but you're most definitely a
common denominator.
It is far too easy for you to
avoid the obvious conclusion.
What does that mean?
You only ever consider the way
in which you make a decision
when contemplating my choices.
That is why you are
always convinced
you are being fooled by me.
That is not true.
Of course...
You must save face.
Shut up!
I think this means
you admit it!
I'm not admitting anything.
Well no.
Of course not.
I would like stew.
That does sound good.
It is pretty cold.
We'll have to check
the price, then.
When it comes to the
cream used to make it,
I would rather have
the really thick kind,
you know, like what
they use to make butter.
Yes! That sounds perfect!
Do you know, the
scent of milk to me
quite frequently
surpasses that of
alcohol. Oh yeah? Well,
in that case you should try
putting it onto some
seasonal vegetables, then.
Cream mixed with vegetables?
Why waste space with vegetables
when there could be so much meat
mixed with that tasty cream?
Oh, my mouth is watering!
True.
Although some people
can't stand the thought of it.
Well, I haven't eaten it
in several hundred years,
so what do I know?
I'll have to discuss it
with my wallet first.
This is your foreign merchant
identification tablet.
We hand them out to
travelling merchants
that pass through our town.
In order to conduct business,
it's imperative
that you have one.
You only get one,
so don't lose it.
[SOLDIER AT GATE B]
What is this?
Everyone has cheap
wolf fur these days.
I do not assume I am better
than or superior to anyone else.
Although, I would
imagine that trait
is common among every species,
even though it means
nothing in particular.
Right. Okay.
Between a weak member
of a superior species
and a superior member
of a weak species,
the latter will always
be respected more.
Okay.
That's true...
If you think about a noble
without fame or fortune,
he's really only
a noble in name.
On the other hand, a commoner
who does have fame and fortune
is going to be
respected more every time.
Why aren't you more excited,
I'm agreeing with you?
[door knocking]
[AROLDO] Are you checking in?
Do you have goods to store?
Yes, there's two of us.
Would you rather stay with
me or go on up to the room?
I am cold so I would prefer
to warm up in the room.
All right, suit yourself.
Then I'll go ahead and
take him to the stable.
You go in and deal
with the room.
You should ask the owner for a
warm one and see what happens.
Be gentle with him alright?
Third floor. Closest
to the window.
Third floor... Thank you.
Closest to the window.
You have a wonderful tail...
It doesn't look cheap
in the slightest.
I'll see about drying
the clothes now.
After that, we'll go
get you some stew.
Foreign merchant
identification tablet...
I've never seen something
like this before.
Oh no! This is not good!
Ahh... Sorry.
What is the matter?
Do not tell me you
are not hungry.
I'll go tend to the fur
on my face.
If I'm lucky, maybe it will
sell for a good price.
I believe the price of your fur
to be much too high already.
In fact, I doubt you
will ever find a buyer.
No one has purchased it
from you yet, have they?
Not yet.
Oh, please excuse me.
So? What are you off to do now?
Well, my priority
is to find out
more information
about your hometown.
The legends about me,
Yoitz, and what not?
All of that,
especially the what not part.
So... we'll look for
chronicle writers.
You can be in charge of that.
You seem to know more
about my stories than I do.
Is something the matter?
No...
I'm just well aware
of how you work.
Come on, tell me
what you know.
So there's this old saying...
Those who know how
things work will find work
and their employer
will never forget
why they were chosen for work.
That does make sense.
I imagine this saying is why
you always work so hard,
am I right about that?
There is truth in everything,
especially old sayings.
If I were your
employer, Lawrence
I would give you a reward.
Is that so?
Take the hint...
Well, is there anything
specific that you desire?
Not especially.
Does it count if all I want
is for you to be happy?
I do not appreciate being
treated like a child!
Children will behave if
you scold them, so...
You're worse than a child.
Ready?
Let's go talk to that
old innkeeper first.
Somehow those guys
know everything.
Are you coming or not?
Yes.
You should be more careful or
you'll end up in trouble!
If I decided to clap now...
do you think the spell I cast
on you would be dispelled?
Hark! What am I doing here?
Oh, I remember now...
I am in a town called Laynos
which is famous for its fur.
I shall purchase
some of this fur
and move on to
the next town!
I have wonderful news for you
o' travelling
merchant from afar...
I am blessed with a rare
and exceptional ability
to determine a fur's quality!
Well you must certainly
have good eyes then...
however, how do your eyes fare
when you're dealing with people?
I do not know...
Unfortunately I have been
cursed with the dark magic.
In that case, I should
probably not clap my hands
to make sure the magic
remains effective.
I already clapped once.
Does that mean this magic
of yours is wearing off?
Yes.
If you could cast
another one on me,
I would be very
much appreciative.
Consider yourself
under my spell.
C'mon. Let's go.
Ouch!
You see? My magic has
clearly overpowered you.
I think you are too powerful.
Very foolish.
What must I do to get you to
lose your composure again?
Eh, we'll see...
If you'd stop teasing me, maybe
I'd have the chance, you think?
I am probably wrong, but I think
your quips are getting faster.
Oh? Thanks.
You do know I was not at
all trying to compliment  you...
Have you been taking
remedial wit lessons?
No, actually it just
kind of came to me.
Well... then there is
hope for you after all!
What?
I was trying to stop
teasing you... you like?
Now what could be wrong?
See how you lie?
You, sir, are desperate for
me to tease you.
I still believe you
to be adorable.
Chronicle writers you say?
Yes.
Anyone who knows
legends from various towns
would be fine though.
I happen to know
a man called Rigoro
and he happens to be
a chronicle writer too.
Unfortunately, he's involved
in the 50 man meeting.
I don't think
he'll have time for you.
What's the 50 man meeting?
Didn't you see it when you
were entering the town?
I think I did.
There were a group of people
who looked like merchants
gathered together.
Was that the meeting
you're talking about?
So... obviously...
there's some kind of
complaint in this town?
Yeah, it's about the... fur.
About fur?
Rigoro is the secretary
of that meeting.
However, there is someone else
who knows legends
and old stories...
Volta, the old fur tanner,
knew a lot about that
kind of thing, but...
Is there anyone else?
Anyone else uh...?
Oh yeah, that's right...
Well there is the old
man of the Ratton firm.
Wait-- 2 years ago we had a
really hot summer, and he died.
How sad? Don't you think?
It's a shame when
our storytellers go
because the memories
die with them.
All we have left are
what's written down.
So in other words,
we should probably meet
with Rigoro himself
so we can see the
written records.
Probably, yeah.
Time can turn even stone
buildings into dust.
Our memories don't
stand a chance.
It's frightening if
you think about it.
Hey, let's go get some food.
You do know the way to
my heart, don't you?
[EVE] Excuse me.
We are not as surprising
as all that, are we?
Do you think he knows
you're not human? Uh oh.
I did not get that
impression at all...
I think 'tis more
likely that girl
was simply overcome
by my stunning beauty.
'twould not
be the first time.
Doubtful. That girl?
She's a woman?
You dare to gawk at another
woman while you are with me?
What are you planning?
I don't think I like it
when you're that direct...
You're much more attractive
when you show how you
feel with your attitude.
I have found that
type of subtlety
does not quite get
through your thick skull.
So, what is it you want to do?
Do you think it
will it be too difficult
for us to speak with that
person in the meeting?
Huh... His name is Rigoro.
If he really is the secretary,
we might not be able to...
but... I guess it depends on
what the meeting's about.
I can tell by your expression
you are dying to know
the answer to
that little question.
You're wrong... I'm not at all.
So now... you will
play a pretend game...
While acting as
if you do not care,
you will tinker
around until it ends.
Ah, I cannot escape
the wolf girl's wisdom...
If you must know,
I really am curious
about what's
going on in this town...
Not only that but--
You would not mind
making a profit.
They gave me
this wooden tablet.
It kinda makes me
suspicious of this place.
Be careful, though.
You do not want
to get in too deep.
What ever do you mean?
You never listen.
Before we do anything else,
why don't we tour the town?
All right, my princess?
Yes... I suppose so.
Consider your prince delighted.
What will I do with you?
Do you know, I cannot remember
if I have been here before.
Perhaps the town has changed
too much for me to recognize.
We should go to the port.
The port?
I heard shipments by
boats are mainstream now.
Which could spell adventure.
Oh? Did you say boats?
Yep. Boats.
Next Episode: Wolf and an
Enchanting Traveler.