[RIOTERS yelling]
[EVE] Everyone revolted
at the same time.
Fur traders,
fur processers... everyone.
[LAWRENCE]
What happened? Why?
They made the
mistake of deciding
to meet the public too soon.
When they were
putting up a sign
in the middle of town
to make the announcement
a mob of merchants,
with their fur tools
in hand as weapons,
rushed them and demanded
for the decision
to be withdrawn immediately.
They did?
There's no need to worry...
They may not be happy
with the meeting,
but they have no reason to
attack a simple scribe's house.
Thank you.
It's too late for them to
change the outcome, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
The authority of
the meeting means nothing
if they go back
on their decision now.
Unfortunately, merchants
from outside the city
have already
found their way in.
At this point, they're
resorting to violence
to try and stop the uprising,
but it won't
make a difference.
What about our arrangement?
We're fine.
It turns out my sources
were right about the decision.
If that outcome gets sanctioned,
we won't have a problem
making the trade.
So what now?
Do we go ahead
and get the furs
and just worry
about the cash later?
No; I think that would
give them an easy way out.
We can't negotiate if
we don't have the cash with us.
You two go ahead and get the
money from the Derink Company.
I'll go find a boat for us.
We have to find
a way to operate
around all of these people.
It's not like we'll be able
to fight our way out of here.
Let's separate and
meet back at the inn.
Unless we're
100 percent ready,
there's no point
in even trying.
That makes sense.
Come on we should go.
I can tell you are
concealing something from me.
I assume you have
realized how terribly
dangerous this plan is...
Am I correct?
Yes, you are.
Look... I know
the risks involved,
but trust me,
this really is worth it.
Good. Then tell me
what you are concealing.
I... can't say.
You cannot or will not?
You'll stop me
if I tell you.
Try me.
If the deal goes
through as planned,
and I get to own that
shop I've dreamed of,
I know you'll be happy for me,
but you will
leave all the same.
On the other hand,
if something goes wrong,
you won't allow
yourself to be sold.
You would be forced to change
into your wolf form
so you could escape,
returning home and leaving
your failure of
a companion behind.
Basically, the only way
I can keep you in my life
is to ignore this
opportunity all together.
And I know... I know
what you'll tell me
"Don't throw it all away.
'Tis not worth it to miss
a chance due to fear."
That's why
I couldn't tell you.
Do you honestly
believe this Lawrence?
Yes.
You think that that
would make me happy?
I do.
I will not say you are wrong.
But you are not
entirely correct, either.
If we do this,
there won't be any chance
for us to travel together again.
Is that really
what you want, Holo?
When I think of you,
I will remember you
as a talented merchant.
Shall we?
'Tis impossible for
there to be a God.
Yeah.
If what they say is true,
and there is
an omnipotent One...
Then why would He
allow for there to be
such incredible
suffering, he created?
I have no idea.
[ELINGIN] And I assume
you've confirmed the total yes?
Yes I have.
You know if you end
up profiting from this,
I expect some wine.
Well yes, naturally...
The next time you lay eyes
on me, I'll be a success.
Of course you will;
no companion of mine
would be anything less.
What am I doing?
God, I hope I didn't
make a mistake.
What other choice
do I have though?
As a merchant
what else can I do?
The amount of money I can make
will afford me
everything I've always wanted.
So why do I feel this way?
Why am I so damn miserable?!
Eve.
I got the capital
without any problems...
You may count it.
I don't need to.
I trust you, don't I?
We need to hurry.
Come on lets go.
I was able to find a boatman
who knocked
down his cargo fee
due to all the
commotion over the fur.
The captain told me as long
as we paid him enough,
he'd ship out even if it was
against a full
military blockade.
All we have to do now
is just throw a few
gold coins at him,
and he won't be able
to turn us down.
His eyes would be
glued to that money,
and he'll say yes whether
he likes it or not.
I can almost see it, too.
Then let's go.
This deal is so good;
it's ridiculous...
You okay?
The fur we purchase
using this gold...
We've calculated
a profit margin
of 4,000 silver
coins, correct?
That's right.
The boat is waiting for us,
so all we have to do
now is buy the furs?
That's right.
And you know exactly
where to sell them
in order to make
the return we expect?
That's right.
I'm getting the impression
that you don't trust me.
I do.
Then what's wrong with you?
Don't tell me you're scared?
I think you should
ask yourself that.
I already have.
Of course I'm afraid.
Compared to this kind of money,
killing a person means nothing.
How can I be confident?
I'm risking everything right
now including my life.
And you can't guarantee
I won't change my mind
and attack you either.
No...
And you really can't be
sure I won't do the same.
I've gotta tell you
I find it comforting to know
we're both so
unbelievably paranoid.
It doesn't
really matter though.
That bridge is far too
dangerous for us to cross.
You look like you're about
to ask me something stupid.
Well, you don't have to, I
already know what it is.
"Why am I risking so
much just for money?"
Unfortunately for you,
I don't have time for
those kinds of questions.
I honestly didn't want
it to come to this...
But I've come too far.
I can't have you running
away at the last second.
You understand.
Compared to 60 gold coins...
killing a person
means nothing, right?
See, you do understand...
You don't have to actually
experience it, though.
When pride comes,
then comes disgrace.
But with humility comes wisdom.
Allowing my cover to be blown
was a mistake on my part.
You may have been right ...
but I'll worry about
being afraid later.
You were only pretending
to trade in statues...
The truth is...
You were smuggling
rock salt the whole time.
And you did it by molding
the salt into those statues.
You even had an arrangement
with the church for
a while, didn't you?
But, it was
too good for them.
People started to wonder how
they were making so much money.
The church couldn't
afford the risk anymore.
Then, tragedy really struck.
I don't think I'm wrong
to assume the cancellation
of the Northern
Expedition was to blame.
What's your point?
It seems to me the church
must have been
desperate for money.
That's why they
got into smuggling
and investing
in the first place.
But then, they ended up
growing more powerful.
And you showed up to
offer them even more.
You laid out a plan to prey
on the foreign traders
who wanted to purchase
fur in this town.
You told them to create
a monopoly and buy it first.
What would make you think that?
Your skills as a merchant
are extraordinary.
Although you did tell me
you had connections
within the church...
your plan would have taken
longer to put into action.
Once I knew that...
I assumed there
was another plan...
A plan you must have set into
motion before you met me.
I asked myself,
"who would profit the most
from restricting
fur trade to cash only?"
Let's see...
It would have to be someone
who already has cash
readily available.
And I can't think of
a soul with more cash
on hand than the church.
On top of that,
you seemed anxious.
I think by then
you had realized
the church had
embraced new partners
and was going to shut you
out of your own plan.
They had utterly betrayed you,
joining forces with a company
who was intent on the furs.
When you initially
proposed the deal,
you weren't
exactly lying to me...
But you were
conveniently leaving out
a large portion of the truth.
Tell me that I'm wrong.
Then I'm sure you figured out
why I wanted your
help specifically.
Because I could be
a shield to protect you.
I am certainly aware of
the sins of the church...
Of course...
I was under their guardianship
before they
decided to abandon me.
At the time,
they wanted insurance
that I would be readily
available to them.
I knew you would
feel the same way.
I could offer salvation
and, at the same time,
give you the chance to make
money off your original plan.
Yeah.
It would certainly
undermine the church...
but I couldn't sit there
and let an opportunity
just pass me by.
After all, it would be easy
for them to take you
down without question.
But if you had a partner,
it could be bad for them.
Taking out a well-known
traveling merchant
like me would
be too controversial.
So, what will you do now?
You'll see.
Are you really that
desperate for money?
And you're not?
I am...
No...
I can only say I want it.
You have to be kidding me.
Let's say you killed
me and hid my body.
No one would have
been the wiser...
at least not until
the deal was over.
And by then, we would
no longer be connected
making it appear
to be random.
Or maybe, you had just decided
to take the money and run.
No, that would've been
too cowardly for you...
You needed to kill me if
you wanted to use the money
you stuffed into your pouch
when I walked in here.
That was the plan, wasn't it?
I assume it's the money you
made from smuggling the salt.
I figure the amount you
were taking from the church
was as much or
more than the amount
I was bringing to the table.
Regardless, you
were planning to use
all of it to buy out
the fur without involving me.
Then you would continue
to raise the stakes
until the church couldn't help
but do whatever was
necessary to take us out.
You didn't care
about your own life,
much less anyone else's.
The only thing you were
thinking about was money.
The love of money
is the root of all evil.
What kind of hell do
you think awaits you?
A fiery one.
What kind of hell awaits me...?
You actually believe in
that stuff, don't you?
I used to watch that
nobleman who bought me...
and I thought to myself...
What is the point of working
so hard just to make money?
It doesn't matter how hard
you work or how much you make,
you still have to go back
and make more the next day.
It made me think rich
people were pathetic.
Although I imagine right now...
I must look incredibly
pathetic in your eyes.
It's easy to sit there
and judge me
for following a path
I hated, isn't it?
I watched him
suffer like a fool...
I saw his choice kill him.
And still, this is
the life I've chosen...
If you really want to know why
I don't mind telling you.
Are you all right?
Kolka Koos.
I've failed again.
Were you robbed?
Not exactly.
Negotiations fall through?
Yeah, something like that.
Is that yours?
Well man, what is it?
Obsession...
Desire... can't be...
Because I still have hope.
You're welcome?
I told you to leave me!
It... It's you.
Why are you such a idiot?!
Please tell me you did not
go back on the contract!
No... I didn't go back on it.
I just managed to lose it all.
What are you talking about?
That was your dream!
It was my dream...
You're right.
It still is my dream.
I do not understand you.
I suppose I am a bit calm.
Let's just say there were some
interesting trade
developments that unexpectedly
left me with a gift
that could buy you back.
The owner has signed
over the inn to me;
and this document proves it.
Do you remember
when I told you
what it was
that frightened me?
It's embarrassing,
so I don't want to answer.
You know exactly what
I meant and yet you did this!
How will you explain yourself
in front of
the wise wolf Holo?!
What do you want?!
Tell me what you want!
I want you.
I want you to get
into your wolf form.
That is not a problem...
I shall make you into
the prosperous merchant
you have always wanted to be!
This fairy tale
will end happily!
I will make sure of it.
"Please turn into your wolf
form and get it back."
Is that what
you thought I'd say?
It turns out Eve is
on a suicidal mission.
When the church
catches wind of it,
we'll be in serious danger.
I wanted you to change
into your wolf form,
so you could get us out of here
while the town
is still in chaos.
You did...?
Idiot!
I love you, Holo.
You do not know
anything about anything.
You're right;
I don't know much...
Although, something
does come to mind.
It's possible
my wish won't come true.
But if I never make that wish...
Then how expect
to know the truth?
Eve is risking
her life for profit.
And she knows
where that will lead her,
no amount she
attains will be enough.
I thought I could be a better
merchant if I had that quality.
So, I was trying
to force it out of me.
You are stupid.
Promise me...
That you will be careful?
I know this journey
can't go on forever Holo...
...but it's not over yet.
You do realize
how dramatic you are, right?
But I thought you liked
your women like this...
I am weak and vulnerable.
You do know you have
ruined all of my plans?
You must take responsibility
now; I wash my hands of this.
Of course.
You have defied my foolishness
with every fiber
of your being...
Which is why... Why I...
Why I shall be more gracious
than you and
go along with yours.
However!
I do not wish
to spend my time
with a worthless
merchant, so...
Running away with
your tail between your legs
simply because you were
robbed is unacceptable.
Your kindness
continually terrifies me.
Well? How are we
going to get it back?
I honestly don't
care about the money...
I'm more concerned
with having you back.
Idiot.
Do you think I would
allow you to be betrayed?
This will be troublesome.
That is, if I were
to fall in love with you.
For once I agree.
Well then...
Shall we go... princess?
Yes.