[MERCHANT A]
Hey!
Looks who's
headed this way!
[MERCHANT B]
A round of applause
for this brave merchant!
[AMARTY] Let me repeat
my vow for our new arrival!
I shall pay off all debts
owed by the travelling nun,
and when she has been
released from her contract.
In the name
of Saint Francis,
saint of merchants and
this Lohen Merchants Association
I swear I shall
do the following:
I will profess
my undying love!
Holo told me about
her unfortunate debt
as well as the way
you've been treating her.
I will use my fortune and
social standing to release her
from you and
restore her freedom.
And then I will ask
for her hand in marriage!
[LAWRENCE]
You've sealed it with blood?
You can pay off her debts,
but that doesn't
necessarily mean
she'll choose to stop
travelling with me,
you know that, right?
Yes, but I am confident
that she will.
And don't forget,
Holo is still a nun.
You cannot marry her.
Yes, so you say,
but she does not
belong to any
convent, does she?
Because she
isn't really a nun.
It's just convenient
to say while travelling.
She isn't bound by any
oaths forbidding marriage.
I see you've done
your research.
According to Kumersun city law,
when a woman is in debt,
her creditor holds all rights
to her, including guardianship.
So, if you were to decide
to accept my marriage
proposal on her behalf
we would not have to worry
about this contract at all.
Well, then?
Will you accept
the contractual knife?
[MERCHANT C] Don't let
him scare you off!
[MERCHANT D] Be a man!
Take the knife!
I'd like to read
the contract, may I?
1,000 Trenni silver coins?
I agree to repay the entire
sum that Holo owes to you
before the end of
business tomorrow.
It appears there's no release
clause for the expiry period.
No.
You will receive all the money
you're owed tomorrow evening.
Cash only...
I won't accept loans
or any kind of bargaining.
Are we in agreement, then?
I accept your terms.
Then the contract
is established.
I will see you
tomorrow, Lawrence.
Don't get ahead of yourselves.
Holo wouldn't mind having
her debts paid in full.
But know this...
She won't leave me.
[MERCHANT A]
All right...
My money's on Lawrence.
[MERCHANT B]
I'll take double for Amarty!
[MERCHANT C] Triple!
[MERCHANT D] Give me
12 Irades on Lawrence!
You surprised me.
[BATOS] Looks like
you've gotten yourself
involved in some excitement.
Yeah, you're telling me.
[BATOS]
You should know,
I think Amarty
has discovered
a way to make
good on your money.
And most likely...
It's not going to be
in a particularly honorable way.
Amarty would be devastated
if he knew I was helping you,
so I won't go into
details... but, well...
I did want to make
sure you knew about it.
Right, why?
Let me put it
to you this way.
I can fully understand
why having a companion
to travel with
would be important.
And I would never take
that away from someone.
Interesting...
And what is it
you plan to do
if the boy actually
gives you the money?
I'll take what you owe me
and give you back
whatever's left.
It's the only
fair thing to do.
I do not like it
when you tease me.
I'm not teasing you,
if he holds up his end
of the deal with me,
I'll hold up mine with you.
You seem terribly confident.
It's not confidence.
I just have absolute
faith in you, Holo.
Good grief...
I believe you to be much
cuter when you are panicking.
Thank you.
I guess that means
I must be growing as a person.
Ha...
Staying calm does not
mean that you are growing.
It doesn't?
Your composure
came from evaluating odds...
and from
believing that you had
an advantage in the gamble.
That is not growing;
that is only being cunning.
I prefer to think it's
being a skilled merchant.
Refusing the contract entirely
would have been the simplest
way out of the situation.
Perhaps...
You waited to decide
until you judged
the spectator's reactions?
It would have
ended differently
had our roles
been reversed, yes?
Hear me, all!
I wish to stay
with Lawrence forever!
I may be indebted to him,
but I believe that my debt
is simply a bond
that connects us.
If you were to
sever that link...
Then you would
destroy us both...
So yes, you may
shame me, nay stone me,
but I shall never
ever accept that contract!
End of scene.
Yeah, that would
definitely be the most
masculine way
to handle things,
but you're not selling
me on it being more mature.
Yes, well...
It may be what I would prefer
but I never said anything
about it being more mature.
'Tis overdoing it, really.
Blech.
No, I do not believe it
possible for your masculine way
to be combined
with the mature way.
Proper masculinity
seems childish
while proper
maturity seems cowardly.
Well, in that case,
if I were a feminine
and mature wolf,
how would I handle
that situation?
You would smile
and take it, naturally.
After accepting the contract
and returning to the inn,
you would kneel, like so.
I know you
accepted the contract
because you honestly
thought it a good deal.
And I am positive
that you will make
additional arrangements
to secure the outcome.
Misinformation in
the shadows, perhaps?
So you want me to take
you to the festival.
You should bribe
me if you truly
desire this
contract to go your way.
[MARC] Are you
sure it's a good idea
for you two to be seen
together right now?
If I kept her
locked in the hotel,
people would think
I really was using her debt
as an excuse to take
away her freedom.
Yes, well that's
what you're telling me,
but I have to wonder,
what does the lady say?
'Tis the truth, good sir!
I am bound by the painful
chains of an enormous debt!
They are far too
heavy for me to bear.
I shall never escape
them in my lifetime.
If you could only find it
in your heart to unlock them,
I would joyously douse
myself with buckets of flour.
No wonder Amarty fell for her.
I can tell who the real
one being tied down is.
Master!
Nice job.
So, what happened?
Okay, well, there were
at least 200 Irades-worth
of taxes recorded
in the tax ledger.
Which, as far as the city
council is concerned,
tells us quite a lot
about his finances.
That's about 800 Trenni
silver coins in assets.
What kind of gambling
is there here?
The usual: cards, dice.
Hare and Hounds
is fairly popular.
There is a limit
on the stakes, though.
Speaking of gambling...
Rumor has it that there
are more than a few bets
on who she'll end up with
if Amarty actually
comes up with that money.
Oh, really?
Yeah, really.
You've got nearly one
to one odds right now.
It's pretty close.
I should really find
a way to get in on that.
Do you think they'd let me?
What's the real story
between you two anyway?
Even if you have answers,
you cannot always
tell them to others;
it is the way of the world.
Example, What is the
purity of your flour?
The purity?
Well, you see that's...
it's hard to...
But I am positive you
would still like to know
exactly what I would do
if my debt was cleared.
You are dying to know.
No, where did you get
an idea like that?
There's only
one thing to do,
we have to find
a way to observe
our competitor's
actions directly.
Sounds sneaky.
It's not sneaky;
it's called being prudent.
I mean, think about it,
if he really wants to win,
there's no way
he won't be trying
to do the same thing to us.
I wouldn't be so sure.
See, from what I heard,
Amarty was the heir
to a very rich family.
He left home and came
all the way out here
with this idea of
making it on his own.
He looks down on
the way the rest of us
make connections with
other merchants in town.
No one helped him;
that kid made a fortune
on his own strength.
He is just like
a heroic prince!
Exactly.
Maybe that's why he fell
for a pretty little nun.
That's a very heroic
prince thing to do.
Although it probably helps
a lot that the women
in this town
are not very friendly
and they don't take
too well to outsiders
if you know what I mean.
It doesn't make
them very desirable.
That's admirable.
But I'm a merchant
not a prince...
and unlike him,
I have no problem
making use of my connections.
So it might be sneaky
for a little prince,
but between merchants
there should be
no complaining.
In the meantime,
do you think
you could find out
some more
information for me?
Batos seems fairly confidant
Amarty will be able
to collect the money.
If he doesn't
collect the funds,
you won't have anything
to worry about, though.
Yes, I suppose that's true.
But I think I just
might be able to turn
a profit from
Amarty's little scheme.
Is that a shepherd's
horn I am hearing?
It is.
Strange, they're not
normally blown in town.
What would you do
if that little shepherd
girl followed us here?
Uhh...
I'd probably say
"Hi, how are you?"
Well, that was not fun.
I thought you
would get flustered,
but now I just seem jealous.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
That was
extremely fun for me.
Oh, great!
Looks like
the festival's started.
I am bored with eating.
Perhaps it is time
to join the throng.
I cannot see.
Come on!
'Tis as if we
have balcony seats!
I'll remember to
thank Amarty for this.
What a wonderful performance!
The costumes are very admirable.
[music playing]
We should go dancing.
Why not?
I am delicate.
Do not step on my feet.
I promise nothing.
What are we
going to do next?
We are going to bed next.
Hold on, we're almost there.
Bed? You must
promise to be gentle.
Oh, please.
Excuse me.
But this came
while you were out.
Marc asked me to
make sure you got it
just as soon as you returned.
Oh, really?
It can wait 'till tomorrow.
No, on second thought...
Sorry, did I wake you?
I have to go meet
Marc again for a bit.
With a letter that smells
like a woman in your pocket?
What woman?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Is there anything
you would like to tell me?
Actually, yesterday
I went to meet with someone
who knows a lot of the
legends and stories about Yoitz.
Yes, she happened
to be a woman.
And then?
I got some helpful
information from her
and I heard
a story about you.
You did?
That's what I said.
There was a legend
about you in Laynos.
[DIANA] They called her
Holo of the Wheaten Tail.
That's you, right?
Oh, I cannot be sure.
Guess what...
The story did talk about
the direction you
came from, that's good.
Are you being
sincere with me?
Yes, I am...
Apparently you came
from a little forest
just to the east of Laynos.
According to the story,
that's where Yoitz is located,
in the mountains east of Laynos
and southwest of Nyohila.
Did you choose to
keep this from me
in order to surprise
me with it later?
I only wish you
had told me sooner.
I'm sorry.
We had to worry
about travelling
over so much land before.
Now it's not so much.
This letter might
narrow it down even more.
I'm hoping we'll be able
to get there earlier.
Oh.
If we got to Nyohila,
could you go the rest
of the way yourself?
I don't care if it
takes us half a year,
we should find
your home together.
I'm off to go see Marc now,
but I'll be back
before too long.
With a letter that smells
like a woman in
your pocket, of course.
You seem pretty
relaxed for someone
who's relying so
heavily on others.
Don't you think?
But I have free time...
Not to mention, I'm making
a ton of money off of you.
What are you talking about?
What did you do now?
It was easy money,
I cleaned up.
I knew what the deal
was as soon as you told me
Batos thought
there was a scheme.
So you believe
they're precious stones?
Not exactly, but close.
Let me put it another way,
they're not precious,
but they are
definitely stones.
It's pyrite?
So why are you asking
me if you already know?
I'm assuming this came
from the fortune teller.
Yeah.
They say she attracted the
attention of the inquisition.
So she did the smart thing
and got out of
town immediately.
I see...
If the church had come here,
the town would
have been in chaos.
You got that right.
Now there's too much
pyrite going around.
She probably bought
it in bulk somewhere
and disappeared
as soon as it sold out.
And, thanks to her sales pitch,
the church is after them, too,
so its value is escalating.
What do you think
it's worth right now?
I'm not sure,
but I would guess about 100?
270.
What?
I know.
But when the market
opens tomorrow,
the price'll be even higher.
That cheap stone
brings in 270?
As long as
there's a good story
that will make people buy,
even worthless junk
can go for a high price.
And now, the women
around here can't
get enough of
these things either.
You know how
competitive they are.
Some are making a game
out of how much they can get
wealthier men to pay for
the "mystical miracle stones."
That's making the
price go up even more.
Who would have
imagined pyrite
would be such
a huge business?
And we aren't just talking
profit in terms of mere
percentage points here,
this could bring
in 10 times the return.
Amarty is most likely making
money faster than lightning.
You're kidding me.
I only got into
the trade a little while ago
and I've already
made 300 Irades.
Nobody wants to let this
opportunity pass them by.
Okay, so who all
knows about this now?
It was all over
the marketplace this morning.
While you and the princess
were busy dancing,
there was a huge scene in front
of the ore merchant stands.
I've failed...
I'm a failure as a merchant.
No, you'll be all right.
With all the
merchants running
around like
crazy over these,
the prices just
keep getting higher.
And besides,
if you did fail,
you'd still
have enough cash
to purchase a new
princess, right?
Well, in the meantime
I guess I can go ahead
and buy some of these from
you with the credit I have.
Tell me the truth,
How are things between
you and your princess?
You have to know by now,
Amarty might actually be
able to pay off her debt.
There's no need to worry.
With the money
from this deal,
I'll make more profit.
And afterwards, the newly
freed princess will choose me,
and we'll continue
our journey together.
You are disgustingly confident.
What else would I be?
Holo, you can read?
Hello.
Please tell me,
what do I do when I have
no home to go back to?
Tell me what to do.
It's only a story.
A lot of those old legends
are far from accurate.
Far from accurate?
That's right.
You know, sometimes,
when a town changes leadership,
they spread
stories like that.
If so, then
why did you not
say anything
to me about it?
Because I...
I just didn't
want you to get upset.
I really wanted to
tell you, believe me,
but I didn't know how.
To think, I have
been talking about
going home this whole time.
I am sure that was fun
for you to watch, was it not?
Did you have a big laugh?
Holo!
What?!
I... calm down, please.
I am calm!
I cannot stop
my mind from racing!
You knew about Yoitz
this whole time, did you not?
Admit it!
You knew it all along!
You knew it the very
first day we met!
Yes. That certainly
explains a lot.
Holo...
You...
You do like your lambs weak
and pitiable after all.
Oh, how wonderful it must
have been for you to hear me
talk about returning home,
ignorant that it was no more.
How delighted
you must have been!
That must be why
you were always
so kind to me for no reason!
You want me to return
alone after Nyohila
because you have
already grown tired of me.
Admit it!
That's not true.
And now I am alone again...
I have no one
waiting for me anymore.
I will be alone forever, now.
I'm here, aren't I?
And who are you to me?
No. Who am I to you?
No, I do not
wish to be alone.
Holo, please.
Wait, I know...
You will have to mate
with me, Lawrence.
Holo.
I am alone now.
But I would not
be if I had a child.
I am in my human form,
it would be so simple
to do, really.
Please!
Stop it!
How could I forget?
You are a gentleman, right?
You would never
take advantage!
Oh, wait, I remember.
There is another
who loves me.
And you are not
panicking right now
because you have
already traded me
for 1,000 of your
precious coins, correct?
Well?!
Say something!
I'm sorry.
Next Episode: Wolf and
the End of Shallow Thinking.