[THEME MUSIC]
[NARRATOR:] To facilitate it's
reign over the world,
Romefeller Foundation
promoted a new Oz,
with it's main power consisting of
unmanned units
called mobile
dolls.
Certain changes within the
Foundation
followed Treize Khushenrada's
retaliation,
including his being
stripped of all power.
At the same time, the Foundation
was rapidly
expanding its area of
rule,
thanks to the highly
skilled mobile dolls.
The year is After Colony 195.
After the space colonies
accepted the Foundation,
execution orders were released
for the
now isolated Gundam
pilots.
For them it looked like the future
would take a turn for the worse.
I'm fighting through this
longer than anyone,
longer than anyone on earth.
Longer than Relena, of the Sanc
Kingdom
The Glass Kingdom
Let's go in, Miss Relena is in the
directors room of the institution.
We'll find our way in
alone from here.
You know I don't like lying at
all,
but it certainly doesn't suit you
either Pagan.
Well I'm not gonna stay,
so once I get my Gundam I'm
getting out of here on the double.
Don't go Heero! The nation
desperately needs the Gundam.
And we've gotta make sure
that we keep that fact a secret.
Relena sure doesn't
need any Gundam.
It's necessary to protect the
princess!
Please understand Heero.
You're such a kind person.
Who are those people?
[GIRL:] ‐Some boys for a change.
[GIRL 2:] I wonder which
country they're from.
[GIRL 3:] Isn't the one in front a
servant?
[GIRL 4:] ‐Looks young for a
bodyguard.
On behalf of this institution,
I welcome you both to the Sanc
Kingdom.
Heero, have you still not
received your school uniform?
I don't plan to stay
here too long.
Once I'm done here, I'm leaving.
‐ Heero!
Hmm. Trowa Barton,
a former Gundam pilot
and on officer in Oz space
forces.
He was last confirmed at
0‐X point of L2‐LE area.
Noin told me about him,
that he's a very important person.
Many friends in the Sanc
Kingdom could help us.
I have taken on the
search for him.
Heero, couldn't you at least
stay until the search is over?
Don't you think Gundam pilots
would
end up being a burden to the Sanc
Kingdom?
I don't plan to make a big
announcement about it,
but hiding the facts
won't solve anything either.
Besides, there's no battle
in this country.
That's why you're here, you're
nothing more than male students.
[DOROTHY:] Miss Relena, I applaud
your prompt decision
for these fateful
arrangements.
I would like you all to meet your
two new classmates.
Would you please
introduce yourselves?
Quatre Raberba Winner.
[DOCTOR J:] Operation Meteor
is about to commence,
I'll contact you on the targets to
attack, and on the enemy data.
[HEERO:] Roger.
[DOCTOR J:] Then quickly
proceed with the mission.
Roger.
[DOCTOR J:] We should decide
on a codename for you.
Let's use the name of the peace
minded leader of outer space.
Understood?
Understood.
My name's Heero Yuy. Pleasure.
[QUATRE:] They're all girls!
I guess it's really true then.
They say that men don't believe in
solving all matters through
discussion.
You can't make such a
generalization.
Some women enjoy battles
just as much as men.
[DOROTHY:] Mind if I challenge you
to a fight?
[HEERO:] ‐Hmm?
[DOROTHY:] You introduced
yourself to us
but I haven't had the
chance to do the same.
My name is Dorothy Catalonia.
I'm related
to the leader of the
Romefeller Foundation.
[HEERO:] Hmph.
Despite that, Miss Relena welcomed
me as a student.
I hope we'll get to
know each other.
Which means I'll have to be
strong,
cause I hear you hate weak women!
Once upon a time there were two
people with the same name.
One of them risked his life to
bring peace
to outer space and became
legendary.
Many people were saddened by his
death and
they angrily swore to take revenge
for him.
And now, the other person with the
same name
is also about to become
a legend!
This warrior is known for his
superhuman abilities and power.
And he too will probably
fight for peace!
But I wonder if he'll end up
losing his life
becoming a legend
too!
No good. A legendary knight
doesn't lose on purpose.
There's no way you should lose to
a woman
just to hide your identity.
You must first live a strong,
noble, and intense life.
You can save dying for later.
You should be able to make
yourself
into a much bigger
legend.
Isn't that true, Heero Yuy!?
Hmmm. Impressive. But I'm not
too bad myself am I, Heero?
I'm having a tough time
following what you're saying.
There must be two guys named
Heero Yuy besides myself.
Hmmm. I knew you'd try to
hide your identity.
And now we'll be together in the
Sanc Kingdom.
Glad to meet you, Heero.
Did you call for me Relena?
I just received an
application from Romefeller
for approval to start a battle
in the Sanc Kingdom.
What's this all about Noin?
A Treize Faction unit running from
Oz is in the southern forests.
I contacted them earlier today
ordering them
to move out
immediately.
Can they escape if they were
forced to leave?
A number of them are injured.
But they also have the option of
surrendering.
It's not something that
concerns this nation.
Some are injured?
Romefeller's assault troops
are hunting them down.
I'll contact the Treize Faction
again
and have them leave
the country at once.
No wait! Pagan,
couldn't we somehow
treat them as temporary refugees?
Then we'd also avoid any attacks
from Romefeller.
‐NOIN: Relena!
I am well aware of the fact that
the Romefeller Foundation
holds the Sanc
Kingdom in contempt.
But we still can't simply
ignore the injured.
I won't sacrifice my humanity
just to avoid chaos.
Please Noin, understand.
I follow you. I'll tell the
Treize Faction members.
Damn! Why'd we have to end
up escaping into the Sanc Kingdom?
The attacks by the new Oz were
staged to lead us into this area.
We've been used like puppets.
We gave the Romefeller Foundation
an excuse to enter
the Sanc Kingdom.
There's no time to sit
around like this!
We've caused enough trouble
for this country. Let's go.
Captain! You can't expect yourself
to cross the border
in the state
you're in!
Nonsense!
We must leave here as soon as
possible
so we don't smear the Treize
Faction's name.
Captain!
The Sanc Kingdom is on the line.
They have instructions
from Princess Relena.
This is Lucrezia Noin of the
Sanc Kingdom imperial guards.
Our nation is prepared to
temporarily
accept you into the country.
[NOIN:] Princess Relena's
instructions are for you
to discard your weapons and become
refugees.
[NOIN:] We believe this is
the best solution
We've got a lot of
injured men here.
Under normal circumstances we'd
be glad to accept your kind offer.
But we've been led into a trap!
I can't see Oz leaving us alone.
[NOIN:] ‐A trap?
As soon as we retreated here,
they stopped attacking.
They should have no problems
eliminating our troops,
considering our state
yet they're getting
reinforcements.
At this rate the Sanc kingdom
could get involved in this battle.
The only way to avoid that
is for us to leave this country.
Captain!
[NOIN:] The daughters of many
pacifist nations
are currently living here.
Romefeller wants to start a battle
and stir up peace oriented nations
which would lead to their
anxiety and disunity.
I understand. But by staying we'd
be giving
the Sanc Kingdom an Achilles heel.
However, we're grateful for
the support of the princess.
[NOIN:] But... what do
you plan on doing?
[CAPTAIN:] Any further contact
would be an added burden on you.
I'd like to terminate
communication.
[CAPTAIN:] Just leave
the rest to us.
Very well. I wish you the best
[CAPTAIN:] Over and out.
Their lives have to be sacrificed.
Forgive us, for the country‐
No!
The future.
Found it. Hmm?
There's Noin's mobile suit.
That's handy.
[SOLDIER:] The Sanc Kingdom is
contacting us again,
what shall I do?
Just bring them online!
‐Sir!
This is Relena Peacecraft!
We have decided to accept the
Treize Faction members
as refugees.
Any further infringements
on their rights will result in
actions against the Foundation.
I believe you're slightly
misinformed!
The Treize Faction is intending
to take over the central part of
the Sanc Kingdom and remain
besieged there.
[COMMANDER:] We believe we'd be
cooperating as peacekeepers
by attacking them before
they enter the city.
The Treize Faction has no plans
to attack!
They've told me so
themselves!
Those are their words?
Well clearly we can't
trust that to be true.
I'm ending transmission,
since the enemy could be
listening to this conversation.
Wait a minute! Take a
moment to reconfirm!
What shall we do sir?
Chase them into the city!
The greater the damage to the
city,
the greater the message on
pacifism's shortcomings!
They just do as they wish! Pagan!
Take me to them. And let's hurry.
That's dangerous! You must
stay here, I implore you.
I'm gonna go and stop them!
It's the only choice I have!
Once the battle starts,
this area will be in chaos.
A perfect place for the new Oz
to cover up their crimes.
There's no telling what they're
planning
to achieve in this
battle.
So you're saying they
may target me.
But no matter what happens,
right now I must stop them!
[PAGAN:] Miss Relena!
Dorothy!
[DOROTHY:] Miss Relena! Come on,
hurry!
Let's get going, or else
we're gonna miss the fight!
Oh!
[NOIN:] Yes, armed suits that
shouldn't be found
in a pacifist
nation.
[NOIN:] They're space mobile suits
redesigned for battle on land.
Does the princess know
about these units?
[NOIN:] No. People think about
fighting
because they possess weapons such
as these.
In order to cling to peace which
is really as fragile as glass.
Those would be her words.
But right now we have no
choice but to fight!
Heero's already headed out.
I'm sure his actions'll be in the
best interest of the Sanc Kingdom.
[QUATRE:] Let's head out after
him with these Tauruses!
[NOIN:] Right! I'll prepare them.
[SOLDIER:] The setup is complete
CAPTAIN: Good job! If we're unable
to escape
from this country,
then we'll have to disappear.
[SOLDIER:] The mobile dolls that
landed
are taking further steps to
push us into the Sanc Kingdom.
[CAPTAIN:] Then get a move on!
Blow up every last trace of our
unit!
[SOLDIER:] Who are you??
Huh?
[SOLDIER:] A kid??
‐It's a kid?
Self‐detonation. Not a bad idea.
But if you're intending to die for
this country,
there's a better way to make
use of your lives.
Just what are you
talking about kid?
Would you consider protecting
this defenseless country?
Our unit doesn't have
much military power left.
Those who want to ruin
Romefeller's plans,
follow me, you might even survive.
[SOLDIER:] Who do you
think you are?
Hmm? I'm returning a favor.
It's simple.
Okay, two or three of you,
come with me.
Captain, do you really trust him?
Not many people have the
confidence
to defeat a mobile
doll.
He's the one that
Romefeller fears so much.
You mean that kid is a
Gundam pilot?!
Pretty sure.
[EXPLOSION]
They're hardly putting up a fight!
Okay, after we've wiped out
some of them in the forests,
we'll presume they're headed to
the city.
We'll pursue the main troops!
Unidentified crafts are speeding
straight for us sir!
‐What did you say??
We'll face them in the air!
Right now we've got the advantage!
Miss Relena, have you ever had the
opportunity
to see a real battle
in person?
It's something I've gone out
of my way to avoid.
That's natural, since people
do end up dying.
Nobody actually wants to die.
That's why those who are
fighting are so ndesperate.
[DOROTHY:] I think that's what
I find attractive about battles.
Oh I get so excited!
I'm certainly thankful that I'm
living in this era.
Whats with that white mobile suit?
Which country owns it!?
Commander! There's a
mobile suit carrier!
Headed straight for us!
‐What?!
COMMANDER: Give orders to
the mobile dolls!
[EXPLOSION]
[COMMANDER:] Good, we've shot it
down!
Tricks like that won't work on us!
[EXPLOSION]
Can't be!
‐A GUNDAM!!
Look! Stop the car!
[SCREECHING TIRES]
[EXPLOSION]
Dorothy! Are you okay Dorothy?
Huh?
[EXPLOSION]
[NOIN:] You'd probably say these
things are
unnecessary in the Sanc Kingdom
Relena.
[NOIN:] But Romefeller's actions
are getting
more and more aggressive by the
day.
I'm fully aware that this is
contrary to your beliefs.
But I've come to the conclusion
that we'll surely be destroyed
without our own defensive force.
[NOIN:] I take full
responsibility,
and am prepared to accept any
punishment.
You shouldn't feel remorseful.
This level of military power isn't
enough to
directly fight the Romefeller
Foundation.
We can't sit here and let them
destroy us
as the nation's former leader
did.
Heero. Is my idea just a dream?
Or could it even be a mistake?
Romefeller makes a point of
eliminating
anything they find inconvenient.
Like the colonies. Or the Gundams.
And now Relena, you have
become their target.
I'm a soldier, I'll crush
them in battle.
But the Foundation's current
targets refuse to fight back.
These times are changing fast.
All aspects of this battle
are attributed to
their impatience.
You propose total pacifism.
The whole world is heading in that
direction.
You have to understand what
Noin is saying.
Right now, defense is needed
to make time for discussion later.
Where are you going? Hold on!
I'll go where my mind takes me.
I've paid you back for your help
searching for Trowa.
For me, there's no
place for pacifism.
The Gundams exist for
battles and nothing else.
If you were me, how would you
lead the Sanc Kingdom?
The same way as Noin.
Build a defense unit.
That would be the best way
to confront
the Romefeller Foundation now.
Heero, and Noin, I approve.
I give you permission to do
as you see fit.
[NOIN:] Relena‐
‐How can I expect to come up with
the position
that the world can agree to if I
can't even
agree with the people closest
to me?
Someday I'm gonna find out what it is
that gives everyone the urge to fight!
[DOROTHY:] Mmmm. Impressive Miss
Relena.
You're not giving the Gundam
pilot the upper hand.
That's what I find so charming.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] Aside from Heero and
Quatre,
who had descended to earth,
the other Gundam pilots
remained in space.
Oz closes in on Duo, who had
been retaliating from the shadows.
The Wing Zero challenges Duo's
still incomplete Deathscythe
to a
battle.
During the battle, Duo begins to
have certain doubts
about the Wing Zero's
abilities
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 32:
The God of Death Meets Zero.