[THEME MUSIC]
In the year After Colony 175,
the leader of the colonies
was assassinated.
Five Gundams
were supposed to have been
sent to Earth to take revenge.
However, since OZ's
activities in space
took the form of cooperation,
rather than control,
the colonies decided to accept OZ.
In the year After Colony 195.
As OZ moves to take over
both the Earth and outer space,
the Gundams are labeled as rebels
and are isolated from society.
With no place to return,
the Gundams and their
pilots are forced to fight
for a reason to exist in
the ever‐changing world.
It's an astro suit!
The astro suit has been
set as a target!
Cancel it! Hurry!
[HEERO:] I’ll eliminate
all obstacles.
[NARRATOR:] The Lunar
Base Infiltration
[DUO:] Did you say lunar base?
[HEERO:] Yes.
There’s a large amount of
Gundanium alloy
being brought into the
Lunar Base factory.
It's probably for making a
new type of mobile suit.
[DUO:] So what are your plans?
You'll get in the way.
Just stay here.
What do you mean?
Considering everything
that's happened lately,
I am gonna need time to recover.
But don’t you think you could be
a little kinder to me
once in a while?
[HEERO:] Why not go to
school instead of me?
I've already got the
enrollment taken care of,
under your name.
[DUO:] What?
You've gotta be kidding!
Sure, your name would stick
out too much here, but still!
[HEERO:] Instead of complaining,
why not spend your time resting
and concentrating on getting
better?
[DUO:] Don't overdo it.
Like he's gonna listen.
Of course he’s gonna overdo it.
[HEERO:] I'll decide once I
get to the moon
whether to steal the new
mobile suit or destroy it.
[NARRATOR:] With only one
sixth of the gravity of Earth,
the moon was not an appropriate
place for humans to reside.
Upon completion of the
Space Colonies,
construction was started
on lunar research facilities
and major factories for
various uses.
The moon further developed
into a popular outer space tourist
destination for people from Earth,
and prospered significantly until
the suppression by the Alliance.
After OZ’s dismantling of the
Alliance Military was complete,
the moon was again
allowed to conduct business
as a tourist destination.
People took this to be a sign that
peace was returning to space.
[DOKTOR S:] People are now free
to travel between the colonies.
It seems that OZ has already
seized much of outer space.
They've been handing out
a lot of gifts these days
to try and win the people over.
Once the people trust OZ,
the rest is easy.
Before you know it, the
resources and labor
will all be controlled by OZ.
[PROFESSOR G:] Why
don’t we build OZ
a real rascal to keep
them occupied?
My, the defense system
for the Mercurius
is looking pretty impressive.
And the Vayeate should
start taking shape
once the mainframe is
finished being built.
[PROFESSOR G:] It’s only a matter
of time before it's completed,
I don't intend to work
under OZ’s orders forever.
Officially speaking,
this is Lady Une's project.
But I understand they'll
be selecting mobile suit pilots
from among the colony citizens.
This could all become
quite interesting indeed.
Oh, I doubt if things are
going to work out that well.
Heero for one won't bother
with the selection process.
It's more like his style to
go straight for their throats.
In any case we'll complete the
powerful
mobile suits that OZ wants so bad.
And then prove to OZ that even
they can
be destroyed by their own weapons!
[CHATTER]
Is OZ really thinking about
establishing
a nation in outer space?
Now that we're free from
the control of the Alliance,
civilians are once again able to
communicate
between the colonies and with the
Earth.
It’s true that we have OZ
to thank for that.
But I can’t see any need for them
to tell us what to do with our
future.
Perhaps, but given the present
size of the Space Colonies
it'd be unnatural for us not
to consider becoming a nation.
That's right, but this is our
problem right here.
It says our main industries
will be military technology
and mobile suit production.
[NICHOL:] Colonel.
The colony delegates
seem to be having problems
with that document, as we feared.
That seems natural.
They've seen the Alliance's
reckless use
of armaments time and time again.
To them, a mobile suit
manufacturer is
probably like a merchant of death.
The nations supporting OZ are
only interested
in space
technology
because they can use it
to improve military power.
I can't see the peace‐minded
colonies going along with it.
Well, they can think of our plan
for
the armaments as a kind of
deterrent.
Arrangements will be made soon
enough
to bring in what space is
lacking.
What space is lacking?
Proper public order.
[COLONEL UNE:] Sorry to
keep you all waiting, everybody.
Have you had a chance to read
through
the document in front of
you?
I believe one of the reasons
the Space Colonies
were considered a threat to Earth
was due to the fact that the
colonies
lacked a clear organizational
structure.
I think forming a nation is a
step in the right direction.
But you're having problems with
the major industries, aren’t you?
That’s just it.
How can there be world peace based
on this idea
that armaments are needed as a
deterrent?
We’ve learned otherwise
from past history.
It’s possible we can establish a
new
public order different from the
Earth.
We're proud that this technology
will be the source of our capital
but we shouldn't be
thinking about military power.
Deep in my heart,
I honestly feel this war has
already come to an end.
OZ is a military organization.
We've made an effort to settle
repeated disputes on Earth.
There was a time when the goal
of the
United Earth Sphere
Alliance
was to achieve peace without
relying on military power,
like you're suggesting today
But just think what those
strategies gave rise to.
There is no need for
reckless battle.
But how can you talk about
the beauty of humankind
without acknowledging the
will to fight?
Am I the only one who
admires man's will to fight?
[SALLY:] I hadn't expected
OZ to restore it to this extent.
But I can't hand this
Gundam over to OZ!
[GUN COCKS]
Who's there?
That’s just what I was
gonna ask you.
You've gotta be some
kind of expert
to sneak in here at night
and set explosives.
First things first, hand
over that detonation switch.
I don't care what happens to me.
You're not getting that Gundam!
[EXPLOSIONS]
No way!
All those explosives and they
didn't even make a dent!
That doesn’t make me happy,
but that Gundam's impressive!
Damn! She's pretty aggressive!
OZ has found us!
Let's get outta here!
No way!
We've gotta be at least as
brave as that lady just was!
We have to take back Master
Quatre's
Gundam if it means our lives!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Leo troops,
get a move on!
The enemy's in the
hangar with Gundam 04!
There it is!
We barely managed to sneak in
and look what happens!
Abdul's plans never work the
way they’re supposed to!
What was that you said?
I don’t have much time, buddy, so
get
Master Quatre's Gundam here
pronto!
Come on! What's taking
you so long, Auda?
You fool! Don't fight
right beside me!
It wasn't easy swiping
this carrier!
Don't blame me!
We were initially supposed to wait
it out until
OZ rebuilt the
Gundam!
I didn't expect things would
get moving this quickly!
Hurry up, Ahmad!
I hear you!
[EXPLOSIONS]
How’s that?
Perfect! We did it!
Mission accomplished!
What's that?
What's the matter?
Why'd you stop?
Damn it all!
[SALLY:] Don't even think
about fighting!
It's that bloody woman again!
Hey, that's Auda!
I really don't think that
we're enemies!
I sensed that.
But the guy I know would try to
destroy
the Gundam in this
situation.
Well, the guy I know would
be sad if it were destroyed.
We're hoping to restore it to its
original state to make him happy.
Does she know a Gundam
pilot as well?
Hey! We belong to the Maguanac
Corps of the Middle East!
I beg you, please leave this
Gundam in our hands!
Sounds like a great kid,
this pilot of yours.
As does your pilot.
Now, I'd better go and pick up
what
the next great kid left behind.
[NEWSCASTER:] The following
footage is of an event held today
that is very significant for the
defense of the colonies.
These young volunteers
are vying for a position
to fight for the safety
of the colonies.
Why is everyone going along
with OZ's every word?
[NEWSCASTER:] The youngsters
produced satisfactory results
in a firing test designed
to reflect a real battle.
In the next test,
obstacles representing enemies
will be
placed along each mobile suit's
path.
The bombs we’re using
are imitations.
But they’ll give you quite a
significant shock when they hit.
Be careful!
[INITIATES:] Yes, sir!
[NICHOL:] Here they come!
Commence counter‐attack!
What a disaster.
But they are just amateurs.
Wow, I don't believe that guy!
What's with him?
This is test pilot 1.
I'm finished with the test.
Test pilot 1, confirm your name!
I told you: Trowa Barton.
[NICHOL:] Colonel, Trowa
Barton is extraordinary!
Even though this is a simulation,
it’s unthinkable that he’d be able
to make
maneuvers like that in his first
battle!
What are you implying?
[NICHOL:] He must've had
some previous training.
At an extremely high level, too!
But his background has
been checked hasn't it?
[NICHOL:] Yes, and there
were no problems.
Then it sounds like he's got
some natural talents.
Talents that he never had the
chance to use up until today.
[NICHOL:] But isn't it possible
that he's been sent to destroy OZ?
He might even be a Gundam pilot!
We'll find out about
that soon enough.
[COLONEL UNE:] Trowa Barton.
We have one additional test.
Completely destroy
the next target!
[TROWA:] But that’s the...
What the hell?
[NICHOL:] What's the matter,
Trowa Barton?
Fire at the target!!
Colonel!
He is a Gundam pilot,
just as I figured!
I'll get rid of him!
[TROWA:] Lend me that beam cannon.
[NICHOL:] What?
It's made of Gundanium alloy.
A Leo rifle isn’t
gonna do the job.
[NEWSCASTER:] A Gundam,
responsible for the
misunderstandings
between Earth and the colonies
is about to be destroyed by
the hands of a colony citizen
who wishes for peace.
Ladies and gentlemen, stand by to
witness
this very exciting moment in
history.
Hey, listen Deathscythe!
Don't give up too easily.
You’re gonna be okay, right?
You're gonna come out just fine.
About to commence the second test.
[DUO:] No! Noooooo!
Trowa Barton: brain waves and
pulse both remain unchanged.
Then he's the perfect pilot.
But I still have some doubts
about him, Colonel Une.
That boy is clearly willing
to cooperate with OZ.
Talented people are capable
of understanding us.
[TROWA:] Huh? What's this?
Those sparkles...
They're my tears.
The most recent version
of mobile suits.
Many of the parts are still
being designed.
I'll go destroy them.
[NICHOL:] No. 1 test pilot,
Colonel Une wishes to speak
with you, wait right there.
I understand.
Wait, Colonel Une!
Be careful!
It's possible that he could
still be a Gundam pilot!
I think it would be wiser for me
to meet with him by myself.
Huh?
He's come to try and
understand OZ.
It'd be rude not to meet with him.
I'm sure we'll have a lot
to talk about,
as two individuals who
love outer space.
Colonel?
Lieutenant Nichol, what
are you so afraid of?
Please, Colonel.
Let's put an end to the fighting,
shall we?
My name is Lady Une.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[TROWA:] So this is Lady Une.
Chief Commander of OZ's
Space Operations.
I understand you've had
experience with labor mobile suits
in your job repairing the
colony's outer walls.
Your outstanding test results
today have
even the OZ soldiers completely
baffled.
I've always felt I that had what
it would take to be a soldier.
So does that mean you’re
going to hire me?
Let's work together to bring
peace to outer space.
I'm just hoping that my
abilities will come in handy
in defeating the
Alliance's Space Forces.
I'd never really given thought
to peace in outer space.
I thought that alone qualified me
as the right type of person for
OZ.
The right type of person?
[TROWA:] I'm
impressed with the way
OZ is gradually taking over space
while
appearing to act out of
friendship.
People may think of it as foul
play, but it suits me just fine.
Taking over?
What do you mean, “foul play”?
OZ is a place where the
crafty are acknowledged.
That's what it's about.
No.
Oh no.
It's not true!
[UNE HYPERVENTILATING]
Colonel!
She really needs to get some rest!
Please, this way, Colonel.
What happened to her?
You might have tricked the
Colonel, but you didn’t trick me.
Trowa Barton.
The Colonel has ordered you
to come back in two hours
to test OZ's new mobile suits.
But just now the Colonel...
Lady Une is a much stronger
person in her uniform.
She might feel like killing
someone as questionable as you.
So I'm Lady Une of OZ?
Or do I work under Mr. Treize?
[PROFESSOR G:] Didn't take you
long to find your pilots, did it?
These five have been selected
from the citizens of the colony
as prospective pilots.
And meet Trowa Barton.
He's got outstanding skills.
He should be able to
control any suit.
These mobile suits of ours
won't be simple to control.
I hear they're better
than the Gundams.
I can't wait.
How far have you progressed?
[DOCTOR J:] The Mercurius
is 80% complete
and the Vayeate is
about 50% complete.
[COLONEL UNE:] What is the reason
for developing two
different models?
With these two models we
designed the mobile suits
with the basic attack and
defense stances in mind
and took them all to
their extremes.
With the Vayeate, we added
the largest beam cannon we could
without affecting its mobility.
And with the Mercurius
we added a defense shield
capable of withstanding an
attack by the beam cannon.
Which would win if they were
to fight against each other?
[DOCTOR J:] Naturally, the one
with the better pilot would win.
Who are you kidding?
So the race to determine
the superiority
of mobile suits is meaningless,
since their value is directly
dependent
on the abilities of the pilot?
You're pretty sharp, I see why
you were selected by OZ.
You're exactly right!
Silence now!
Leave him alone!
He'll be piloting one
of those suits.
I'll allow his questions.
Uh, yes ma'am.
So what kind of tests will you
be demonstrating for us today?
Right!
I'll show you the defense system
employed by the Mercurius.
It creates an electric field to
allow it to reflect any beam
fired by the enemy.
What about the Vayeate?
The Vayeate still needs
some work done.
The energy charger isn’t
even installed.
Hmm? What's that?
The Vayeate's moving!
Activate the Mercurius shield!
I’ve got it!
Colonel!
Hey, you gonna make it?
Ouch, that hurt.
What'd I tell you?
My weapon is something,
don't you think?
That's for sure.
The suit came after us!
That's some weapon, all right.
[ENDING MUSIC]
A white mobile suit is
seen approaching a colony.
Once it's determined to be the
Tallgeese belonging to Zechs,
Lady Une orders Trowa
and Heero to attack it.
About that time, the injured
Quatre
returns home to the Winner
residence.
But what he finds is the
sad image of his father
being solely blamed and
criticized by the people.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 21,
Grief‐stricken Quatre.