THEME MUSIC
You'll die right now and the
glory will be mine!
If you were to lose you it
wouldn't be to me,
you'd be losing to the Wing
Zero!
You still don't get it, do you!?
I can handle a system like
this no prob‐ AGHH!!
The Lonely Battlefield
[PIANO MUSIC]
[CLAPPING]
That's beautiful! I didn’t expect
you
to be a talented musician Quatre.
[QUATRE:] I have been fond of
music since I was a young boy.
I enjoy playing instruments
because
they always make me feel relaxed.
[NOIN:] That song was very
melancholy though.
You must not keep blaming
yourself for what's happened.
When there's a war going on,
some things can’t be helped.
It can't be brushed aside as
something inevitable.
Wars are paid with human lives!
If I'd been a stronger person
then that wouldn't have
happened to Trowa.
[DISTANT GIGGLES]
Miss Noin don't you have some
information for me about Oz?
Of course.
The whereabouts of Treize is
still unknown but Oz considers the
Treize Faction as retaliators and
battles
around the world are intensifying.
[NOIN:] However, Oz still
has the advantage.
There's no way the average pilot
can compete
with the capabilities of mobile
dolls.
I'd think we stand a decent
chance against the mobile dolls.
I'm not merely bragging.
We could only do it with superior
mobile suits like the Gundams.
That's a fact!
But even if we destroyed the
mobile dolls in battle,
the war wouldn't come to
an end.
If there's one thing we've learned
through our experiences,
it's that there's a limit to what
a pilot can accomplish.
Won't Miss Relena, won't the Sanc
Kingdom
be able to comfort
soldiers,
such as yourself Quatre?
I'm sure that one could
feel relaxed here.
Perhaps that's why people like
ourselves
who are tainted with blood
shouldn't be here.
I think Heero feels the same way.
[NARRATOR:] Operation Nova,
the plan to send
mass produced
mobile dolls
from outer space to strife torn
areas on earth,
was steadily producing results.
By displaying the threat of the
mobile dolls,
Oz was able to increase its
influence
over the people.
While the Romefeller foundation
was
establishing its position
to rule the world.
[PILOT:] We are ready to
enter the atmosphere.
[SOLDIER:] Captain, looks like we
won't have interference this time.
[CAPTAIN:] Right, I
think we're safe.
[SOLDIER 2:]
Detecting strong heat!
[SOLDIER:] A mobile
suit's approaching!
[CAPTAIN:] Damn!
[SOLDIER:] It's the Tallgeese,
I'm sure of it!
[EXPLOSION]
Spaceships 2 and 3 have been
destroyed,
we're the
only ones left!
[CAPTAIN:] Send out the mobile
dolls to counterattack!
[CAPTAIN:] They’re all defeated!?
A human pilot can’t
defeat a mobile doll!
AHHH!!!
[EXPLOSION]
[HOWARD:] This is Peacemillion.
Mission accomplished.
We'll leave this area after
taking in the Tallgeese.
[HOWARD:] Heheh, that was
impressive Lightning Count.
Well that's all I'm really
capable of doing right now.
I cannot begin to thank you
enough there, Howard.
Hey, we're only helping each other
out here,
don't worry about
thanking me.
[ZECHS:] In that case Howard,
could I ask you to tune up the
Tallgeese?
Huh? What for, you didn’t
receive any damage?
It just seems to be
responding a little bit slow.
[HOWARD:] That's because your
reaction time is too quick.
Your skills have surpassed the
capacity of
the Tallgeese in a short period of
time.
[HOWARD:] I'll take it in.
[ZECHS:] Forgive me Relena.
I'm going to
continue living as Zechs Marquise.
It's in the best interests of
the Sanc Kingdom.
[DERMAIL:] Did you say
Zechs Marquise?
Yes, he came to outer space as
ambassador Milliardo Peacecraft
of the Sanc Kingdom
and has been hiding
out ever since!
The Sanc Kingdom you say.
This is annoying.
[TUBAROV:] I agree.
Many countries out there still
support total pacifism, practiced
by the Sanc Kingdom's
deceased king.
What's even worse is that many
people within the Foundation
are leaning toward
the idea.
How could that be?? There is no
need for such ineffective ideas.
Romefeller has possession of
the invincible mobile dolls!
Ha! Invincible you say?
Don't you see that Zechs Marquise
is destroying them?
[TUBAROV:] Yes!
[DERMAIL:] Our next target point
is Luxembourg base, am I right?
[TUBAROV:] Yes! We’re all
prepared.
This time Zechs won’t get his way.
I'm counting on you there. I'll
see what I can do on this end
to crush his
home base.
The Sanc Kingdom, huh? This might
be the right time to destroy it.
[RELENA:] I thought I
might find you here.
[HEERO:] Relena!
[RELENA:] Can I sit beside you?
Its your country, you can
do what you want.
Guess so.
Why were you kind enough to
stay here in my country Heero?
In the past you would’ve just
gone off to fight battles.
[RELENA:] No matter how much I
tried to stop you,
you went back into outer space.
But your homeland sure didn’t
treat you very kindly at all.
It must’ve been so hard.
Yet despite that you continue
to carry on fighting.
You’ve got an intensity in your
eyes
that hasn’t changed since the
first time we met.
Huh? I’m just...
Oh I'm sorry for
interrupting you Miss Relena.
Hi Dorothy. Were you
looking for me?
This is an invitation from
the Romefeller Foundation.
[DERMAIL:] Thanks to Oz's
undertakings, we're close to
resolving all disputes
around the world.
As such, we would like to learn
more
about the Sanc Kingdom's
pacifism,
to prepare us for the world peace
that
would likely follow the end of the
war.
We are therefore sending this
invitation
requesting your
presence,
Miss Relena Peacecraft, at our
conference to be held in Bremen.
I have been asked to escort you
to the conference Miss Relena.
I can't tell you what a thrill it
is to be able to accompany you.
Please,
get in.
That's very kind of you Dorothy.
Miss Relena, please allow me
to accompany you.
DOROTHY: No, there's no need for
that!
Miss Relena is our special
guest.
Romefeller will take the
responsibility
of getting her
there.
[NOIN:] Miss Relena‐
[RELENA:] ‐Miss Noin,
[RELENA:] take care of things
here while I'm gone.
[RELENA:] Heero, I want you to
make me a promise;
don't leave here without telling
me first!
We should be on our
way Miss Relena.
Let's go.
Are you going to just
let her go then?
As far as Romefeller is concerned,
this country's ideas are
dangerous,
who knows what they might do to
her. Heero!
[QUATRE:] Heero, what are
you trying to do?
A large number of mobile dolls are
expected to arrive in Luxembourg.
What?
[HEERO:] The Treize Faction’s
headquarters are in Luxembourg,
it looks like Romefeller is trying
to crush them all at once.
They’re gonna send this many
mobile dolls to earth?
Even Luxembourg won’t have
a chance!
Once the battle is won those
mobile dolls
will be dispersed across the
world.
You’re crazy!
Even you can’t defeat
so many Mobile Dolls by yourself.
If you’re going, then I’m
going with you.
[HEERO:] No, you stay here.
[QUATRE:] But why??
You can’t afford to get killed
this stage in the game,
not until you
find Trowa.
What’s going on here Quatre?
Where's Heero?
Heero has made a decision.
He’s chosen to fight where
he has the least
chance of survival.
That’s an unbelievable number of
suits just to destroy one base.
Which merely proves what a
strategic point
the Luxembourg base is.
I guess if they were fighting
against the Lightning Count
then they would have to have
that many dolls.
I'm going to fight them with
everything
I've got no matter what their
plans are.
[ZECHS:] Luxembourg.
I previously fought
to take it over from the Alliance,
now I'm fighting to defend it.
Talk about irony.
Zechs has arrived, just
as we suspected.
All shuttles ignore the Tallgeese
and head straight for the
atmosphere.
We must conquer
Luxembourg at all costs!
[DERMAIL:] Welcome, Miss
Relena Peacecraft!
[RELENA:] Thank you very
much for inviting me today.
I'm so pleased to be able to meet
with you.
Many thanks for your help Dorothy.
I am delighted to be of
assistance.
I shall excuse myself now.
I wish you the best of
luck Miss Relena.
[DOROTHY:] Now Miss Relena,
you can show us
just what you’re
made of.
Don't disappoint me.
[RELENA:] It's a fact that the
Sanc Kingdom can’t employ its
peace initiatives without
your assistance.
But your Oz organization is
initiating
wars all around the world.
How could the Romefeller
foundation power
produce two completely different
results?
It’s because the decision on how
to use
all this power is made by people,
right?
If peace is truly your objective,
I ask that
you use our Sanc Kingdom as your
model.
I am fully prepared to assist you
in
achieving your peace objectives.
That was wonderful.
You have very sound beliefs
for a woman as young as yourself.
But I can’t ignore the hypocrisies
within the Sanc Kingdom.
What hypocrisies do you mean?
[DERMAIL:] Let me explain:
recently a certain individual has
been attacking Oz troops
and leaving us with
considerable damage.
He’s approached the colonies as
ambassador Milliardo Peacecraft
of the Sanc Kingdom
but later he appeared as
Zechs Marquise,
the Tallgeese
pilot.
[DERMAIL:] He’s currently
considered an enemy of Oz!
[ZECHS:] Damn it is responding
too slowly. Huh??
Fighting against Oz is the
same as opposing Romefeller.
Is it safe to assume that the Sanc
Kingdom
has some aggressive
ambitions?
Is that pilot still calling
himself Milliardo Peacecraft?
Well, no he isn't.
Then he's clearly not
my elder brother Milliardo.
[RELENA:] ‐The Peacecraft family
wants nothing more than peace.
As a family member it's impossible
for him
to pilot a mobile suit and
fight.
[DERMAIL:] Then you don't
care what happens to him?
[RELENA:] It has nothing to do
with the Sanc Kingdom.
I understand that it appears that
we've made some false assumptions.
We'll take appropriate measures
and deal with this traitor Zechs
on our own.
My apologies for ever doubting
the Sanc Kingdom.
[RELENA:] Now if you'd please
excuse me
from this meeting, gentlemen.
The Sanc Kingdom. How frustrating.
That was quite the show Miss
Relena.
I could tell there was something
special about you.
[DOROTHY:] You can't use
dolls in a war,
it's meaningless unless its
fought between people.
And for that to happen.
There's a lot more for you
to do Miss Relena.
And for the time being,
you can count on my assistance.
[RELENA:] Milliardo, you
knew exactly what I would say.
That's why you chose to
fight as Zechs Marquise.
The escort mobile dolls
have been destroyed sir.
But we sent the target number of
shuttles to earth.
Luxembourg will surely
fall!
That's my limit.
Luxembourg, don't be defeated.
Damn! That's gotta be one of
those new mobile dolls!
Whats that? Gundam 01?
What’s it doing here!?
[NOIN:] They’ve started fighting
in Luxembourg.
I thought that you wanted to go?
Heero talked me out of going.
I'll stay here and protect Relena
on Heero's behalf.
Maybe we're being overly cautious,
but if something
were to happen to Miss Relena,
I couldn't bear the thought of
facing Zechs again.
[SOLDIER:] Captain Noin!
We just received an anonymous call
that Miss Relena's car
is about to be attacked by mobile
dolls
conducting a fake test flight!
[NOIN:] What!?
[QUATRE:] ‐Huh!?
[PAGAN:] Miss Relena!
I apologize for picking you up
without your asking me to
Don’t worry about it Pagan.
You don't seem too pleased,
didn’t the conference go well?
What's that? Mobile dolls?
[GUNFIRE]
Ahhh!!
Pagan, say something. Pagan!!
Miss Noin!
[AMBULANCE SIRENS]
I can make a well thought out
speech
but I can’t even do a single
thing to save one person.
It's true isn't it? I'm always the
one who's being saved, aren't I?
Is it possible to have peace
without using force?
[RELENA:] Maybe Pacifism is just
nonsense
mouthed off by those who are
unable to fight.
Get a hold of yourself!
What do you expect us to do
if you start talking like that?
[QUATRE:] You have to keep going
down the path you believe in.
People like us don't know any
better than to fight,
however you've got the ability to
provide us
with a peaceful place
to live in.
That's what Heero, Miss Noin,
and I truly believe.
In peace? a place... to live?
That's right. One day you'll
achieve peace and
we continue to fight with that in
mind.
We will achieve that peace.
One day.
TREIZE: Don’t die. Don’t give up.
You mustn’t die yet.
TREIZE: Fight. Keep fighting
and prolong your life kid.
You pilots, you mustn't die yet.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] Heero enters
a castle in Luxembourg,
where Treize gives him
a new Gundam.
But the new mobile suit is evil,
much like Zero.
About that time, Zechs gets his
hands on the Wing Gundam Zero
and demolishes the space
Taurus troops.
Next on Gundam Wing Episode 34:
And it's name is Epyon.