[OPENING THEME]
GUNDAM WING
[TREIZE] Fellow comrades: Only
warriors exist in this world.
That purity is what makes this
battlefield so beautiful.
Let us finish the final battle
of mankind and keep the
horrors of war
away from our home.
[VOICES] Yeah!
[LADY UN] This battle is a
crucial moment in our history.
It must be something that
people will talk about for
generations to come. For that
reason many warriors here
will end up having to
sacrifice their lives.
[VOICE] All mobile doll troops
have entered battle with the
enemy's main force
and commando unit.
This battle is only the
beginning. We must make Earth
and all its residents
know the strength and
determination of the
space colonies.
[NARRATOR] Collision In Space
[ALARM] [SOLDIER] Have you
checked the system?
[SOLDIER 2] Yes sir!
Heero...
I'm going to stay here until
this battle settles.
It'll be hard for Treize to
destroy Libra right now so when
the time comes I'll
do it myself.
But I still think we have to
stop this battle. Dictators
are the only ones who
sacrifice lives in order
to achieve peace.
But Zechs and Treize are ready
to sacrifice their own lives.
That's why I have no intention
of stopping them.
Yeah, but‐
You stay right here with me.
You're going to look
after me Heero?
I just don't want to feel like I
owe Zechs something when we
end up fighting.
If this battleship does go down
there wouldn't be a
reason left for you
to fight my brother.
[HOWARD] So far the two sides
seem to be pretty even. So who
will we side with?
Well it looks even now but
that's only because Libra hasn't
shot its main weapon.
'Cuz every time they fire it it
needs to be fixed. That's
helping out the Earth's side.
But once it's fixed then the
White Fang will have
the advantage.
The White Fang only represents
the opinions of a portion
of the colonies.
They don't stand for the
colonies as a whole. I'm sure
many people in the colonies
are hoping for peace.
Maybe. But would helping Treize
really be in the best
interest of space?
Treize is only fighting against
Libra and the mobile dolls.
Not the colonies.
That's a good point. The main
threat right now is definitely
the White Fang and Libra.
You sold me. Libra has got
way too much power.
But what about Heero and Ms.
Relena?
They'll be just fine,
knowing him.
OK. Then it's settled?
You bet. Just keep Peacemillion
headed straight for Libra.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SOLDIER] We've confirmed
Peacemillion's location.
They're going around the battle
zone and coming toward us.
Those idiots! The Gundams are
still regarding us as enemies
even at a time like this!
[LAUGHING] That's no surprise.
From their perspective every
force is an enemy.
[QUINZE] This is no laughing
matter. We can't afford to
send our front line
mobile dolls to face them. We
have no means to stop them.
I'll face them.
[QUINZE] What?! You will?!?
[ZECHS] I'm taking 3 Virgos with
me. [QUINZE] Only 3?!
That's crazy!
[ZECHS] It's enough to keep me
alive. [QUINZE]
Commander Milliardo!
Listen up! Is the main
cannon fixed?
[QUATRE] Noin please stay and
guard Peacemillion. The
Taurus doesn't have the
mechanical abilities of the
other suits and I think I know
who we'll be facing.
Roger that.
[DUO] Huh? It looks like they've
come. It's him but he's only got
3 Virgos with him.
This'll be a snap!
I'll teach you. This is how
mobile dolls should be used.
[DUO] Here goes!
Hang on a sec!
[DUO] What?! [LAUGHS]
[DUO SCREAMS]
Duo!!
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSIONS]
Fighting mobile dolls is
certainly dull.
[BEEP]
Your excellency. The Gundams
have entered a
battle with Epyon.
Seems like Zechs is truly hated
by those Gundams. I would
gladly thank them for
their help but the fact is
they're not necessarily
fighting for my sake.
Please be careful.
Thank you. But our objectives
are the same. Libra must go
down. That's for certain.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[WU FEI YELLS]
What the?!
Get those guys!
[DUO YELLS]
Why do they keep going
after Quatre?
They wanna decrease their
enemies. Maybe
they think I'm the
easiest to knock off?
[ZECHS] Just trying to crush
the brain first.
In that case if I keep
them close to me...
[TROWA] Duo! Wu Fei!
[DUO] Right! [WU FEI] Right!
[ZECHS] I won't let you get
into any formation...
Nice work Milliardo. The mobile
suits are right where
you want 'em.
[TREIZE] Even our commando unit
can't get any closer to Libra.
[QUINZE] Has MO‐2 still not
moved during the battle?
[SOLDIER] No they've done
nothing but take in damaged
mobile suits sir.
I thought they might have a new
weapon but maybe they're
nothing more than a
supply base. OK! We'll
move the Libra.
[DOROTHY] Wait!
Are you gonna destroy this
beautiful view of the clash
between the two forces?
Ms. Dorothy Commander Milliardo
declined Treize's
offer to a duel.
[QUINZE] Calculate a course that
will take us around
MO‐2 to Earth.
And don't forget to
inform the commander!
That was the correct decision.
But can you tell the people of
space that this decision is
also a very sad one.
Milliardo?
[ZECHS] No problem. Right now we
must show Earth how sad it
is here in space.
[SOLDIER] Libra's leaving the
line of battle! It's
heading for MO‐2.
At the moment MO‐2 has very
little military force and it
can't move on its own.
I'm guessing Libra will go
around MO‐2 and head
straight for the Earth.
Then let's go after them!
What's the point if we don't
even have the weapons we need
to destroy Libra?
Sure we have the weapons! Enough
to destroy Libra's main cannon!
Wait a sec, you're not ‐
Evacuate all civilians! MO‐2
will take them in!
Alright... very well then.
Right! Everybody move to
the sub‐bridge now!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I suppose that's the obvious
decision. But I'm not going to
let you take Libra down.
They're after Peacemillion!
[DUO] We have to stop 'em!
[GUNFIRE]
Damn how can they keep dodging
Nataku's assault?
It's no use! The 3 mobile dolls
are working together to
form a single
powerful shield. We've gotta
move in and destroy them.
[BEEP]
[ZECHS] Noin get out of my way.
No Zechs. I'd really rather not
have to fight you. But I...
[ZECHS] Noin! Get out of here!
[NOIN] I'm not moving. Even if
it means having to kill you...
[ZECHS] Noin...
[NOIN] Zechs...
Miss Noin!
What're you waiting for?!
What're you doing? Shoot him!
[QUATRE] Miss Noin!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[ZECHS GRUNTS]
[THUD]
I don't understand! Why am I
still so spineless?
Oh Zechs...
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
The Peacemillion is about
to plow into us!
What? You're kidding! Are we
able to dodge it?
[SOLDIER] No! There
isn't enough time!
Deploy all cannons! Shoot that
ship out of the sky!
[MAN] You sure about
smashing into them?
[SALLY] Yeah so we'll wipe out
their main weapon.
[HOWARD] Use the BTY booster as
well! I don't care if it
wrecks the engine.
[MAN] Roger!
[DUO] Hey! Have they gone
out of their minds?
No chance. It's the only
option that's left.
I have to applaud your courage.
[QUINZE] They're gonna hit us!
Stop the engine now! All units:
Prepare for collision.
Heero what's happening?
Get down now and cover up your
head. Peacemillion's
plowing into us!
Engines one and three damaged.
Well I guess now we don't
have to turn 'em off!
[MAN] Alright! How about
some excitement?!
[SOUND OF IMPACT]
[PAINED GROANS]
[INTENSE MUSIC]
OK! Leave the damage report for
later. Extinguish the fires
around the fuel tank!
The main cannon. It's been
completely destroyed.
Luckily it didn't explode
because it wasn't charged up.
I don't believe it! How
could this be?
This is the end for Libra.
We still have not
lost this battle!
[EXPLOSION]
That's right. This battle will
continue until every mobile
doll's destroyed.
All units keep fighting.
[ALARM BEACON]
Hey... thank you Heero. Thank
you for protecting me.
[RELENA] Heero you're hurt.
It's not serious.
But it's bleeding.
Now Zechs won't have
his victory.
What do you mean by that Heero?
Forget it. I'm gonna need Zero.
[ZECHS] What's the damage?
[QUINZE] The main cannon is
completely useless.
And the engine?
Well it has been damaged sir.
But it still can get up to
about 70% capacity.
Then we still have a strategy.
[DUO] Oh man that was one big
collision if I've ever seen one.
As it stands now it'd be hard to
destroy just Libra.
[SALLY] This is Peacemillion.
We're not at any risk of
exploding right now but we're
pretty much stuck here.
I understand. We'll board Libra
and take over the
ship from within.
We'll destroy the mobile doll
control system &amp; then order
the White Fang to
[QUATRE] surrender. Also we've
gotta find Heero and Ms. Relena.
So we're going in? This reminds
me of the old days.
[DUO] What's wrong Wu Fei?
I'll leave it to you.
Hey hang on! Wu Fei!
Just let him go. He's
keeping an old promise.
We should hurry and
get to Libra.
Miss Noin?
[NOIN] I'm sorry but I...
I just...
Feel free to go Miss Noin.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
Gundams are entering through
gate 17. There's no way
to stop them.
Can't help it with the Gundams.
But make sure that none of
the Gundam pilots
get anywhere near our
principle sections!
Ugh! Damn those cursed
mobile dolls!
[WU FEI YELLS]
A Gundam? Is that
Gundam backing us?!
An upgraded Gundam 05. The pilot
has to be that kid...
Listen Treize when I'm finished
here I'm going to put your
integrity to the test.
[ALARM BEACON]
Once we're on Peacemillion
follow Howard's instructions &amp;
get your butt outta here.
I want to talk to my brother
just one more time.
[HEERO] It won't help. Zechs'
decision is final.
This area's obviously used
for confinement.
Alright. I'm here. Step away
from the door if you don't
wanna get hurt!
[SMALL EXPLOSION]
[DOOR CREAKING]
Hey Heero is that you? What the?
That definitely wasn't what I
was expecting to find.
[ALARM BEACON]
[DOOR NOISE]
[SOLDIER ONE] Hey! Got him.
[SOLDIERS] Huh?!
So it's you Dorothy Catalonia?
That's right Quatre
Raberba Winner.
[GUNSHOT]
So Zechs wanted to send a
tremendous blow to the Earth
and by using such a
significant impact he wanted to
awaken the fears of war and an
earnest desire for hope in the
hearts of the people.
That's the reason we ended up
helping build Libra.
And we even redeveloped the
Vayeate and Mercurius.
[DUO] So I've got you to thank
for the trouble I went through?
Well we did add a little
something to the
Libra's main cannon.
We built an error into it so it
can't fire consecutively.
No kidding? Is that so?
And you think that atones
for your sins?
No of course we don't.
Right it's not payback time yet.
[LAUGHTER]
I knew it. Wish I hadn't
found these guys.
[HOWARD] OK! MO‐2 acknowledged
us. All units prepare to escape!
Howard Heero says he's
leaving with Wing Zero.
[HOWARD] What? When
did he get back?
[MAJESTIC MUSIC]
Heero...
[ZECHS] Noin...
It's me. I won't try
and stop you.
[NOIN] Just let me stay
here by your side.
Do as you desire.
Planet Earth.
[ZECHS] You are about to learn a
lesson. The real crushing
blow is yet to come.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR] Wu Fei takes on a
duel. Quatre responds to sorrow.
And Trowa defies his destiny.
Duo helps pay back past debts
and Heero proceeds to the
battle where Zechs awaits him.
The thoughts of the warriors
vacillate between
affirmation and denial amidst
the chaos of outer space.
Next on Gundam Wing Episode 48:
Takeoff Into Confusion.