[♪♪]
Narrator: With high
expectations,
human beings leave earth...
...to begin a new life in
space colonies.
However, the United Earth
Sphere Alliance
gains great military powers...
... and soon seizes control of
one colony after another...
...in the name of
justice and peace.
The year is after colony 195.
Operation Meteor.
In a move to counter the
Alliance's ternary,
rebel citizens of
certain colonies...
... scheme to bring new
arsenals to the earth...
... disguising them as
shooting stars.
However, the Alliance
headquarters catches on to
this operation.
We've heard everything
you have to say
I'd like you to leave the room
now, Vice Foreign Minister
Isn't it about time you
people realized,
the ones posing the most threat
are none other than yourselves
Silence we've had enough!
Heero!
I'm right over here so
come and kill me!!
Relena's Secret
Lady Une: Vice Foreign
Minister Darlian.
I hope this'll be a very
successful trip for you.
Nothing wrong with a little
socializing now is there?
I can't imagine having anything
appropriate to discuss with a
specials officer.
Pretty nasty words Minister.
I'm just here on orders
from my superiors.
I'd appreciate it if you didn’t
take your
frustrations out on me.
Relena look carefully.
Never forget how beautiful the
earth looks from afar.
Get a good look cause you will
never see it again.
What are you sighing about; is
there something bothering you?
I was just thinking the colonies
are in the middle of a
beautiful sea of stars.
And yet they don't even
seem to sparkle.
don't you agree?
No. I don't agree
with you at all.
Relena's on the colonies
this very moment.
they should be sparkling much
brighter than usual.
Target is North Pacific Ocean,
OZ supply base.
Roger that mission.
Mr. Darlian! How
nice to see you.
I take it rumors of Earth's
chronic financial
crisis are false.
otherwise you couldn't afford to
launch a shuttle for
yourself yes?
I truly wish that were
the only rumor.
The latest fase rumors spreading
throughout the Alliance...
...are much more grave.
You mean the rumors we were
planning an attack
against earth?
Where would the Alliance
get that idea?
Nothing good could come from
our attacking them.
The purpose of this visit is to
find out for ourselves...
... wether those rumors
are accurate.
Let's hope there's no
truth to that.
Relena: The people in the
colonies are so peacful
and courteous.
How could people on Earth
believe that the colonies would
want to start a war.
How could they?
Excuse me, Miss Une.
You don't have diplomatic
authorization from Earth.
Please understand that I can not
allow you to sit in on
this meeting.
I understand.
But I'd still like to get the
report after you meet.
Of course.
Fine. I'll excuse myself.
Ten minutes.
That's when it all ends; or
should I say when it begins.
It's Relena.
what is it?
I'm going out to do
some shopping.
Darlian: Be careful
out there dear.
I'll get you an escort.
No. i'm fine.
It's much safer here than it
is on the Earth.
Oh. She forgot it.
Diplomat: These
accusations are unjust!
We've never even heard
of most of this.
Like Project Meteor or the new
type of mobile suit.
Mr. Darlian.
Why does the Alliance is finding
it so difficult to
believe in us?
Ten more seconds.
Excuse me, ma'am!
I think you forgot this
back in there.
You idiot!
[explosion]
Oh god, father!!
That was a close call.
Go after the girl and kill her
if she tries to resist.
Father!
Where are you, father?!
Relena...
Father!!
Talk to me, father!
Is he alright?
Huh?
Well?!
I can't find any
other survivors.
Relena: Who are you people?!
Okay. we'll carry Mr.
Darlian out.
Man: right!
OZ troop: Stop Right there!
What are you doing?!
move!
Someone's taken Darlian's
daughter and they're
trying to escape.
Block all of the exits.
Let go of me!
you're gonna have to
come with us.
It's the only way you'll make it
out of here alive.
I don't care what happens to me.
what are you going to do
with my father?!
Just do as we say for the
time being miss.
Get in!
Are you hurt lady Une?
This injection should
help you relax.
Get father to the hospital.
He will die for sure
unless you do.
The hospitals too risky!
What do you mean?
They're already guarding
the hospitals.
We have qualified doctors in
our organization.
Organization?
Who are you people anyway?
Relena...
Father...
Listen to me, Relena...
Don't try to talk!
You have got to lie still!
I have a confession
to make Relena.
I'm not your biological father.
huh?!
You've got to believe what
I'm telling you.
your real name is
Relena Peacecraft.
you're the daughter of the
Peacecraft family...
...that was so well known for
it's total commitment
to pacifism.
wha... I don't know what
you're saying?
I am a member of the senate that
served their country
in the past.
But long ago the kingdom was
demolished by the Alliance.
And I decided to take you in as
my daughter when I
made my escape.
Father that's not possible.
Relena...
watch out for the OZ
organization.
Don't die on me, no father!
No!!
The medication's working.
She's deep asleep.
The mobile suit has
been repaired.
Thanks pal; I owe you one!
No problem, as long
as I get paid.
You're an excellent
client young man.
We made it just in time for
my next mission.
Do you really have to leave?
I won't stop you.
But at least tell me what your
name is before you go.
My name's Quatre Raberba Winner.
I have no name.
But if you must call me
something, it's Trowa.
Call me Trowa Barton.
Goodbye friend Trowa.
We'll meet again.
Quatre...
Should we be letting
him go like this?
He knows the location of
this base after all.
I wouldn't worry.
He's not the type to go
around telling anyone.
But what if he attacks?
I almost wish he would.
Then at least I'd be able
to see him again.
‐Nothing to report
‐Roger!
What a drag; boring guard gaurd
duty for two whole hours.
Troop: Hey,
something the matter?
No problems here.
Everything's in order.
Now I just have to get to the
targer point to carry
out my mission.
[♪♪]Gundam Wing
I'm counting on you, Otto.
Don't worry about a thing.
The staff here are
highly skilled.
I'll make sure it
gets completed.
Are you sure this 20 year‐old
suit is gonna be any use to us?
It's probably more advanced than
any OZ mobile suit...
...that's currently available.
You're kidding.
No way.
Think about it.
This Tallgeese suit is the
prototype for all mobile suits.
Even those Gundams were built
based on this Tallgeese design.
The Gundams?
Father!
You've woken up.
I'm terribly sorry
for your loss.
If only we'd become aware of the
situation earlier...
... We could have
avoided this tragedy.
Reporter: Lady Une, any comments
on this terrible accident?!
I am terribly saddened by what
has happened here today.
I had no idea there were such
evil terrorists residing
in this colony.
Reporter: We're told that Vice
Foreign Minister Darlian...
... and his Daughter
were kidnapped.
We're investigating
the situation.
We are unaware of the terrorists
true objectives...
... but if these actions reflect
the feelings of the
whole colony...
... we'll be forced to take
military action.
Reporter: Wait a minute,
lady Une!
Une: excuse me.
I have a terrorist
investigation on my hands.
Dammit!
She's making us out to be a
bunch of terrorists!
That's just what you are!
You let my father die because
you wouldn't take him to the...
... hospital in time.
I told you the hospital...
That's enough.
I'm terribly sorry for
what happened.
I'll get revenge for his death.
It's OZ right?
OZ is responsible for
killing my father right?
Don't be stupid!
You'll just end up
getting killed!
Can't you see its suicide
I don't care if I do get killed.
I'll kill you.
Stop it!
What do you wanna shoot him for?
No need to apologize Father.
I'm old enough to understand how
important your
business is to you.
Heero...I want to see you,
Heero.
Dr. J: did you say, Heero?
Now!
Let go of me!
Are you talking about Heero Yuy?
Do you know him?!
Do you know Heero Yuy?!
[chuckles]
That was some
performance by Lady Une.
What happened to Mr. Darlian?
I believe he was killed.
Poor girl.
You're still worried aren't you?
Worried about what?
Open up Zechs.
You're hiding far too
many secrets.
[explosion]
Commander!
We're reading an enormous
heat source...
... and two guard Leos
have disappeared!
Enemies?!
It looks like it might
be a Gundam sir!
Get all mobile suits ready
for combat at once!
Yes, sir!
Visibility is poor, I can't
confirm anything.
A Gundam!
Uaagh!!
Please feel free to call me Dr.
J, young lady.
Believe it or not,
I'm a scientist.
Dr. J.
You're the one that sent Heero
to Earth, aren't you Doctor?
Yes that's right.
But who in their right mind
would've thought that...
... he'd end up in the same
school as Darlian's daughter?!
How's that rascal doing anyway?
‐What a kid!
‐What are you trying to get him
to do on Earth?
I'll say this, That young lad
is an agent of ours.
An agent?
Since Heero was very young,
we've taught him...
... a wide range of
battle strategies.
We brought him up as a
professional assassin.
Relena: Why would you do
such a thing?!
Don't you see?
For the peace of the colonies,
of course.
The peace?
how in the world could killing
someone possibly lead
us to peace!
It leads directly to peace!
Wars are started by people and
they end with people.
Heero's ordered to attack the
dangerous, evil people...
...responsible for
starting wars.
But there must be more
peaceful solutions!
Twenty years ago, we
believed that ourselves.
We thought humanity
couldn't be so foolish.
That no one could possibly
wish for a war.
The colonies were started by
scientists like myself...
... and by laborers.
Our ancestors did everything
they could to form the colonies.
After over 100 years
of hard work...
... we could finally enjoy a
normal lifestyle there.
And exactly twenty years ago,
we were living peacefully...
... under the ruler of all
colonies, Heero Yuy.
Heero Yuy?
His name still lives on
today as a legend...
...among the residents
of our colonies.
That's where we came up with the
young lad's code name you see.
His code name?
times of peace in the colonies
didn't last for long.
I suppose they felt a leader
promoting peace was
too dangerous.
Heero Yuy was assassinated by
some organization.
From that point, communication
ceased between the colonies...
... and this became an excuse to
strengthen the
Alliance Military.
you see, OZ was responsible for
Heero Yuy's assassination...
... and wanted a war with Earth.
OZ?!
Do you know OZ?
That was the last
thing father said.
To watch out for OZ.
So who are you making
Heero fight against?
All of OZ.
We must stop them before they
fulfill their ambitions...
...to take over the United
Alliance Military...
... and dictate the Earth Sphere.
But, why does Heero have to take
on that enormous task?
Why should he be responsible for
doing all that by himself?
We have no choice!
He understands the emotional
pains that the colony
residents...
... have been forced to
endure over the years.
But still...!
It looks like we're both
after the same thing.
Well, aren't you gonna at
least respond?
Locked on target.
Seems like the two of us are
gonna have to fight it
out after all.
They should be able to return
you safely to Earth from here.
May I ask you why you saved
my life Dr. J.?
Is it Because of my father?
Because I'm Darlian's daughter?
Not at all.
It's because you had the same
look in your eyes as Heero did.
That genuine expression.
Heero's actually a
kind‐hearted young boy.
Yes I know that.
But Heero's very dedicated
to his mission.
Stay away from him if you
value your life.
Aah!!
I've returned the favor.
[laughs]
Damn you!
I'll get you back!
Father...
I'll always be your daughter.
To be continued
Next Episode
Having been thrown into a new,
uncertain destiny...
...Relena returns to the Earth.
What awaits her is a
splendid class party...
... and notice of Heero's
transfer to another school.
Knowing Heero's secret,
Relena figures out...
...that the transfer is somehow
related to his next mission.
OZ assassins come for
Relena life,
and Heero finds
himself saving her.
Next, on Gundam Wing, episode 6
Party Night