[MUSIC]
We are now positioned to
stage an all‐out
missile attack on the colonies!
You guys can fight,
well can't you?!
Mission accepted.
[Narrator:] "The
Whereabouts of Happiness"
There's really no way out, with
all this security.
Besides, to swipe a carrier...
...I'd have to cross the entire
desert to get to the
closest airport.
Huh?
That guy...
We're in the same boat.
With all those planes
looking out for us...
...there's not much you
guys can do either.
A fairly large sandstorm
is on the way.
we'll be crossing the
desert then.
Wanna join us?
Yeah, I do.
I could use some sympathy now.
And I need time to think too.
We've collected what we could.
But the important parts have
all been destroyed.
I thought so.
That's why he self‐destructed.
Even Gundams can end up as
mere scraps of metal.
Or rather, scraps of Gundanium.
This Gundam design was based
on the Tallgeese.
So the fundamental technology
for the Tallgeese
should applicable.
Colonel?
Yes, Noin.
Would you mind if I took this
Gundam with me...
...to the Lake Victoria Base?
Huh?
Are you planning to fix it?
Yes...
Why bother?
Perhaps I'm just preoccupied
with that pilot.
But the Gundam pilot
died didn't he.
I just have this feeling
that he's alive.
It's pretty well impossible
after that explosion.
But I honestly hope
that he is alive.
As a fellow mobile suit pilot,
he was someone
that I was destined to
do battle with.
I'm terribly sorry!
Your Excellency...
I shouldn't have acted
on my own to plan a direct
attack on the colonies.
Well that's all water under
the bridge now.
At least we know that the Gundam
attacks were planned...
...by certain extraordinary
people, to retaliate
against our actions.
Our target is still to destroy
all of the Gundams.
But their supporters concern me.
In outer space.
I'd prefer to keep the enemy
from becoming any more powerful.
Can I rely on you, Lady Une?
Yes.
I'll eliminate them at once.
Uh, Your Excellency...?
The peace‐minded people of
the colonies...
...will not prefer any
sign of militarism.
You can do away with some of
your formalities.
You can announce your trip to
outer space in Moscow.
Many noble people who understand
OZ live in Moscow.
Huh?
They should be able
to assist you.
Sir!
The radar hasn't
picked up anything.
That doesn't mean a damn thing.
Spread out and look
out for enemies.
Crap, I can't see a thing
in this sandstorm!
What could be in a
place like this?
There's a base belonging to the
middle east nations..
...unassociated with the Earth
Sphere Alliance or OZ.
Why don't we take refuge there?
A base?
No problems here.
No problems here either.
None here.
I understand.
An underground base?!
Let's go.
H‐Hey!
This base belongs to our
homeland the Maguanac Corps' .
It's your base?
Good of you to come, Quatre.
It's been a while,
Commander Sadaul.
The missions have been tough
since you got to Earth,
haven't they?
Well, I owe the Maguanac Corps
for all their help.
I don't know how to thank you.
It was their personal decision;
they wanted to help you.
If only we had more strength we
would've been able to...
...do a lot more damage to
the OZ organization.
That troublesome OZ!
Using the colonies as a shield
is irresponsible!
We're to blame, for
failing to stop them.
Yeah, we're totally to blame.
Oh, no, Quatre.
No one is in a position
to blame you.
Here, come this way.
Master Quatre, we'll get started
with the mobile suit repairs.
Yeah, thanks.
Oh, and Rashid...
Yes, I know.
We will take care of
both Gundams.
That's ok, isn't it?
Just fine by me.
I appreciate your help.
I haven't introduced myself.
My name is Quatre
Raberba Winner.
Winner?
You mean you're the heir to
the Winner family?
One of the few influential and
financial powers of the
Arabic Nations?
No wonder everybody looks up to
you around this place.
Our family were all pacifists.
I've disinherited myself
to come out here.
Yeah?
It takes all types, I guess.
I'm Duo. Duo Maxwell.
I might run and hide, but I
never tell a lie. That's me
in a nut shell.
We were told that the colonies
have sent mobile suits to Earth.
That's her!
It's true that a number of
mobile suits...
...were sent to Earth and took
part in an attempt...
..to destroy certain targets.
However, OZ is presently taking
steps to expose the rebels...
...in order to
maintain world peace.
It's only a matter of time
before we solve this issue.
That rose doesn't
suit her one bit!
Thank you.
My pleasure.
My, isn't she cute!
Excuse me.
Do you have an invitation?
No.
Forgive me Miss, but this party
is open only to invited guests.
Hmmm? Katrina...
Well, do you know any
other guests?
Relena, you're early.
Marquis Weridge!
I'm terribly sorry; I had
absolutely no idea she was a
relation of yours.
Not to worry.
Shall we go, Relena?
The party's about to begin.
Thank you...
Don't mention it.
This place is full of old folks.
Young people like
yourself are a rarity.
My, Mr. Weridge.
What a pretty young date.
How do you do. I'm Relena.
May I have this dance
please miss?
I couldn't allow that.
The first dance is
already taken.
If you wouldn't mind, could I
have this dance, dear?
Why should I mind; I'd
be delighted.
It would be my pleasure.
Huh? What's this?!
We're guarding the
front entrance.
Nothing to report at the rear
gate or along the channel.
Radar picking up
nothing in the sky.
Roger.
Continuing to post guard.
Hmm...
Relena, I can see the
Peacecraft influence in you.
Do you know the Peacecrafts?
Yes, of course I do.
[GASPS]
Thank you.
Yes, I was very close indeed
with the Peacecrafts...
...the monarchy of the
Sanc Kingdom.
Till 13 years ago, when the
family was overthrown.
Why was the Peacecraft
family overthrown, Sir?
It seems absurd, but while some
people hope for peace...
...others try to gain
through disputes.
The former was the
Peacecraft family...
...and the latter was the United
Earth Sphere Alliance.
So you mean their talk of
peace interfered
with the Alliance's objectives?
Yes, and even the
Romefeller Foundation...
...who had differences with the
Alliance, started
developing weapons.
Blasted OZ!
OZ?
I invited Treize today to
personally ask what he was
trying to pull off.
But he sent some representative!
What's wrong?
Don't worry; I'm a guest too.
Show me to Marquis Weridge.
I must see him personally, on
behalf of His Excellency.
Roses don't belong on
military uniforms.
A rose is a flower more suitable
for someone kind like you,
Relena.
Marquis Weridge.
My name is Lady Une and I come
on behalf of Treize Khushrenada.
I need to discuss some
things with you.
Of course, before that, would
you give me that rose of yours?
I'd love to give it to my
granddaughter.
Relena Darlian!
What're you doing here?!
Grandfather, roses just don't
look good on me either.
I'd look better soaked in
the blood of OZ!
Here's for my dad!!
[GUN SHOTS]
Huh, what?
Freeze!
After her!!
Marquis!
Standing in your way is the
only thing I can do!
I can't even come close to
matching the courage she shows!
How dare you all!
We're all great fans
of that girl.
Well, take the main entrance!
Yes, Lieutenant!
The courage she's shows is just
what's needed for us to
move forward.
There's still so much
for me to learn.
Are we all clear?!
Yes!
Wow!
It's a festival!
Looks like a gas!
They're celebrating the safe
return of us 40
Maguanac soldiers.
Yeah?
The nation has opposes the
Alliance Military and is
defending itself.
The Maguanac are the
front‐line soldiers.
They are?
[GIGGLING]
You bet, I'll go!
Don't push!
You're more like heroes than
front‐line soldiers.
Everyone's
completely united now.
That's why our
nation's so positive.
So your country is going to
gonna stick it out...
...to the end of the battle.
What's your impression of us?
There's a lot I wanna
talk to you about.
You got some time, Quatre?
Of course.
I've got questions, myself.
Now we're all alone. We
can talk in here.
There's five, right?
That's right.
Just the five of us that
met at New Edwards.
I came here from the colonies.
I did as well.
The five of us are just the
same, don't you think?
Our mobile suits and
our missions.
Not to mention our
objective to destroy OZ.
OZ destroyed peace in
the colonies.
This mission is revenge.
I've been fighting
under those orders.
Same with me.
That's when I was given the
mobile suit I use.
Same here.
Don't worry about the colonies.
[TOGETHER:] "Destroy
them first."
"That's your responsibility."
Just the same.
Yeah word for word.
I've always fought believing I'd
be better off dead...
...rather than live
under OZ's rule.
Me too.
But to kill yourself...
Heero ended up doing it.
He took his life.
The colonies have no
intention of fighting.
The colonies can't
be sacrificed.
Your friend was the
perfect role model.
I never would've imagined
that Heero had such
a stubborn streak in him.
It was clear the colonies were
targeted once the
Gundams got going.
A battle where the nation is not
unified as one body.
There's nothing more difficult
for a lonely soldier.
Captain!
Come to the headquarters!
OZ's mobile suit troops
are headed here.
They're what?!
Look, Rashid! Here
on the screen.
Looks like their recon troops!
What do you think, Rashid?
If we start fighting here, the
civilians will get involved.
Then keep on guard but send the
soldiers underground.
Sir!
Is this some kind of festival?
Some nomadic friends stopped
by at the village...
Is something wrong?
I was hoping you could let our
troops rest and maybe share
your food and water.
We'll do what we can.
Thank you, sir.
Still you're quite intimidating.
We've been informed that
rebelious middle east troops
are hiding out in this area.
We're here for
precautionary purposes.
Damn them!
All right!
Oz has left.
Check those boxes!
Well?
We can't move it.
It's set so any movement
will trigger it.
Rashid, what's the matter?
Master. Quatre
OZ played dumb.
And the whole time they were
setting twenty bombs
all over town!
Huh?!
If they're time bombs we just
need to trash them all!
They're designed so we
can't move them.
They've narrowed our troops'
location down to this town.
Which means they're gonna
force us to surface.
They've set the bombs to go
off at 12 midnight.
They must be hoping for a
nighttime battle.
It would seem OZ is preparing to
battle with us overnight.
Or else they think we're gonna
surrender before then.
Aren't the Gundams
causing this problem?
That's right!
I'm sure it's us they're after.
Their attack is very
well thought out.
They've probably been watching
this town for quite some time.
Everyone, listen up!
OZ has discovered this town and
will be attacking.
I doubt if we'll be able to
deceive them any further.
Therefore, we'll aim at one area
of their barricade...
...and resist their attack while
the civilians escape!
One other honorable
duty remains.
We must get the two Gundams
suits out of the vicinity.
The Gundams are heroes that
arrived on Earth to destroy OZ!
Because of OZ's scheming, the
Gundams will not be able to
fight this battle.
However, there will be a day
when the Gundams will
save us all!
Be thankful that you can return
the favor in advance!
Do you understand?!
[CROWD:] YEAH!
All troops, to battle!
Hover suits from the middle east
troops are attacking!
Tragos troops, fire!!
The enemy's hover suits
are too quick!
Tragos Hover suits,
shift to the back!
Close combat's too dangerous!
Yes, sir!
Tragos ready to fire at
enemy's underground exit!
Huh? What's going on?!
Did you think that was
our only exit?!
Found them!
By the North Gate!
There are lots of enemy
carriers to choose from!
Good job.
Take them all at once.
Yes sir!
Do not rush.
Go to the North Mountain Gate.
Do not get separated from
your families!
Go with this to the North Gate,
where Abdul's waiting.
Thank you.
Sorry I can't do
anything in return.
I'm so ashamed, I could die!
Huh?
For me? Wow!
The Gundams are our heroes!
Never forget that.
I know we'll fight together
again some day!
For the future!
Hey, Quatre!
Yeah?
I've got some flowers
here for you!
I promise!
One day my Gundam will
definitely fight again.
Decoy operations are now
complete and we are
retreating to the hills!
We cannot have
civilian casualties.
It would blemish the
Maguanac Corps name!
Secure a path for Master
Quatre's carrier immediately!
All Maguanac Corps,
gather up ahead!
Do not let the enemy
through the barrage!
Quatre...
Yes?
Could you circle the
sky just once?
I can't help them now.
But I still wanna do something.
Sure thing.
Hang in there!
Keep firing!!
Master Quatre...
Good! Mission complete!
Maguanac soldiers,
retreat at once!
See you again, Maguanac Corps.
The next time we meet, I'll make
sure the colonies'
thoughts are united.
Count on it!
There she is!
Silly girl! Keep still!
Let me go!!
Who are you?!
I'll be taking care of
her from now on.
We have special orders
from Colonel Une.
I can't take orders from you,
Lieutenant.
[GUN SHOTS]
If you are concerned about
authority, these orders are
from His Excellency.
You satisfied?
Yes, Lieutenant.
Excuse our misunderstanding!
You're being reckless.
I wonder who your
temperament takes after.
You're part of OZ. aren't you?
So who are you?
I have come to help you.
Miss Relena Peacecraft.
[To be continued]
[MUSIC]
[NARRATOR:] The Gundams must use
weapons to win back peace.
In a battlefield filled with
inconsistencies...
...Wu Fei meets Sally Po.
Wu Fei states that the weaker
should not be fighting.
But with those words...
...Sally senses the complexity
of a cornered warrior.
Still lost in his emotions,
Wu Fei once again get
into his Gundam.
Next, on Gundam Wing,
episode 12:
"Bewildered Warriors"