[OPENING THEME]
Outer space has lost all reason!
That's why I'm gonna
destroy everything!
Quatre... I'm not leaving.
There's a colony that needs
to be defended.
Trowa!
The five of us have become
nothing more than redundant
soldiers Quatre.
[EXPLOSION]
The Eternal Flame of the
Shooting Stars
[SIRENS SOUND]
[SOLDIER:] Carriers have entered
the atmosphere and are
approaching us!
Their target is
obviously this base!
Must be the new models.
Do you think that they're
all mobile dolls?
Probably. They're sending a very
small number to try and
crush this base.
But we are members of the Treize
Faction though. We
can't be defeated.
[NARRATOR:] Operation Nova.
The Operation where,
upon completion of their mobile
doll assembly line,
Romefeller Foundation sends
mobile dolls to Earth,
to try to eliminate the
Treize Faction.
To gain complete
control on Earth,
they attack areas where there is
a chance of retaliation,
and force the people to
obey the foundation.
Get as close to them as possible
before they use their
beam cannons.
That's the only way we can win.
[PILOT:] The enemy's
approaching. Go get them!
[EXPLOSIONS]
Operation Nova? Outer space has
a bad habit of sending
menacing objects to Earth
[EXPLOSION]
[NARRATOR:] The Romefeller
Foundation was successful
in it's production of
unmanned mobile suits,
known as mobile dolls,
developed to increase the
Foundation's military power as
it took over the world.
However, there was a voice from
within the Foundation,
that denounced the use
of mobile dolls.
The voice of Oz's leader,
Treize Khushrenada.
[TREIZE:] Duke Dermail, I'm
sorry but I cannot support
the Romefeller Foundation in
the path it's taking.
What!?
Tradition is a history.
It's the history of caring,
built by deep true
feelings of people.
I do think that fighting in
battles can at times indeed be,
beautiful.
But at the same time I'd like
to express my regret
[TREIZE:] over the lost souls by
appealing to you to recognize
how priceless man's life is.
[NARRATOR:] Treize objected to
the idea of battles which
employed mobile dolls
and made human presence
unnecessary, and he thought
to dissolve Oz.
[NARRATOR:] However, with the
desire to maintain their
present force,
the higher powers within
Romefeller tried to
resolve the situation by
confining Treize.
This resulted in encouraging a
group of OZ soldiers,
who also disagreed with the
introduction of mobile dolls,
to unite. They called
themselves, the Treize Faction,
and rose against the Romefeller
Foundation's strategy to rule.
[TUBAROV:] Is that so sir? It's
not going to be easy
to deal with
the soldiers who respect
Colonel Treize.
Damn that Treize, we've got more
important things to do!
Tubarov this means we're going
to have to increase
the production
of mobile dolls to be
sent to Earth.
[TUBAROV:] Not to worry sir.
Things are going quite
smoothly here in space.
We have managed to capture the
new Gundams that showed up, as
well as their pilots!
I shall destroy them right here
at the Lunar Base.
[DERMAIL:] It's possible that
the Gundams are being used as a
symbol for the rebels.
Tubarov, get rid of them
immediately! ‐
[TUBAROV:] Yes sir!
[TUBAROV:] Things can only get
worse by just confining
Colonel Treize.
Our opposition must
be eliminated.
That's the easiest and the
surest way to deal with
these situations.
Get out.
[SOLDIER:] Stop!
Trowa! I'm the one who
did this to you.
Please forgive me Trowa...
[CRYING NOISES]
We have permission from
Commander Tubarov to execute
you Gundam pilots.
Try that again and you can
kiss yourself goodbye.
Heero!
[SOLDIER:] I take it you'd
prefer to die here.
[GUNFIRE]
The Treize Faction!?
[TECHNICIAN:] He's caught up
with all the targets! He's
extremely fast.
The speed of his reaction
surpasses all expectations.
Keep testing him!
‐[TECHNICIAN:] I'm increasing
the simulation level.
[COMPUTER NOISES]
[SOLDIER:] Lieutenant Trant?
Commander Tubarov is
on the line.
‐[TRANT:] Right.
[TRANT:] Commander! This
cockpit utilizes a
system that penetrates the
pilot's brainwaves
and increases his
combat abilities.
Our test pilot is reacting as
quick as the mobile
dolls commander.
Then you haven't been listening
to my orders, have you Trant!?
The orders I gave were to
destroy that Gundam!
[TUBAROV:] Because of
Lady Une's revolt,
the five Gundam engineers have
disappeared somewhere
within this base!
I can't have you
wasting your time!
[TRANT:] But sir! I'm convinced
this could be utilized with
the Oz mobile suits!
We could use this
Gundam's system!
Our purpose here is to
completely eradicate the
Gundams you fool!
What's the point of
depending on it's systems?
Erase the Gundam from the
memories of the universe!
Now follow my orders!
[TRANT:] Commander Tubarov is
betting everything on
the mobile dolls!
Our hands are tied!
So what should we do now
Lieutenant Trant?
Scrapping it will be
quite simple.
But there's one piece of
data I'd like first.
The data on the pilots that can
fight at the same level as
those mobile dolls.
[DOKTOR S:] Good. His brainwaves
haven't been affected.
What's this test
supposed to determine?
[MASTER O:] We're checking how
the cockpit system of Wing Zero
infuences the
Pilot's brainwaves.
[INSTRUCTOR H:] There's no
problem, that system
is flawless.
A decision was made by the
Romefeller Foundation to confine
Treize Khushrenada.
And as a result, Oz's forces
have split into two factions.
Lady Une has been shot.
It hasn't been confirmed whether
she is dead or alive,
but she's regarded as a offender
by the Romefeller
Foundation now.
The other two pilots; Duo
Maxwell and Wu Fei Chang,
escaped during Oz's
internal unrest.
However both of their Gundams
are still only about
80% complete.
Only minor adjustments are
needed to complete them.
With a little time, those pilots
should be able to finish the
Gundam on their own.
How about Trowa Barton?
[QUATRE:] Huh?
He's been Missing in action
since the Vayeate was destroyed.
Probably dead.
The possibility of his
surviving is quite low.
Our force will be diminished but
there isn't anything we
can do about that.
And that's the present
situation we're in.
Did you get all that Heero?
[HEERO:] Got it.
[PROFESSOR G:] Now, I'll explain
the situation with the Treize
Faction on this base.
[QUATRE:] Wait a minute! Please
look into Trowa
Barton's whereabouts.
I know he's alive! There are
lots of colonies in that area.
I know he'll be able to make it
through, I just know it.
That's some personality.
A little questionable for a
soldier though,
wouldn't you say?
That's why the Gundam Zero ended
up in the hands of the enemy,
even with that system installed.
What?
The system has a device which
amplifies and controls
brainwaves associated with
fighting and brings about battle
results greater than the
pilot's normal skills
could achieve on their own.
It would've been alright if the
pilot saw Oz as the enemy,
but the mind warping side
effects of the system caused an
error in his target.
The fact that the pilot was
incomplete as a
soldier resulted in his
attacking his own allies.
Extremely regrettable.
Especially considering that with
the combined power of
the Vayeate,
the Mercurius and the new
Gundam, the Lunar Base could
have been demolished
all at once.
Because of the training you five
have undergone, your
physical power and
tactical imagination are and the
art of war are no less
than perfect.
[MASTER O:] But we find that as
soldiers, you're mentally
far from perfect.
[MASTER O:] This latest incident
has brought that flaw out
into the open.
[PROFESSOR G:] You must become
the perfect soldiers!
Otherwise you won't survive the
golden age of the mobile dolls!
[PROFESSOR G:] Or if you'd
rather, go insane! That's what
wars do to people.
What's your opinion of
Wing Zero's system?
[QUATRE:] I had no idea! I never
knew that unit had
been completed.
I was focusing more on the
large beam cannon and
didn't pay as much attention to
the system installed
in the cockpit.
The beam cannon hasn't been
retrieved yet. The main
weapons right now
are the beam saber and wing
vulcans on it's shoulders.
You planning to fight Heero?
In either case we can't leave
Gundam Zero in the
hands of the enemy.
Heero, I've been wondering who
our allies are and our
enemies are in this war.
I get confused
thinking about it.
Quatre...
The ones after your life and the
targets you aim to defeat are
always the enemy.
Yeah, but what if you find
out you're mistaken?
Quatre, we're not
mistaken about this.
But it's possible this period of
war has gone nuts.
[GUNFIRE]
[SOLDIER 1] They've located the
gates to Blocks A and B!
[SOLDIER 2] A large number of
soldiers are headed this way!
[TRANT:] Members of the Treize
faction we have
surrounded your hideout!
I must say, I have some
reservations about fighting
against former comrades
without first talking
things over.
I think we can avoid
senseless bloodshed.
[DOCTOR J:] We are
completely surrounded!
So I take it that means they
want to negotiate with us.
[TRANT:] First of all, I can't
promise to release all of you.
However, I guarantee that you
will all live, as long as we can
cooperate with each other.
I didn't know that you doctors
were in there as well.
So what are your demands?
We'd like you to hand over the
Gundam pilots to us.
Because we want to record combat
data on the Gundam.
It looks like they noticed. I'm
sure the system is just as
attractive to Oz.
There's no choice. We will
surrender the pilots. Huh?
[TRANT:] Unfortunately I don't
think I can save your lives,
doctors.
Headquarters was pretty adamant
about their decision.
We've been fortunate to survive
this long! But I guess this
ends our lucky streak!
I'm prepared for the worst!
First they want us as hostages.
Well, that's a good
way to treat us.
But the fact that we're being
held as hostages isn't
going to stop Heero!
[QUATRE:] Heero, is
there a problem?
[HEERO:] Not really.
Tell them to get started.
[TRANT:] Right. Make him fight
against the mobile doll data.
[TECHNICIAN:] Yes, sir!
[BEEPING NOISES]
It's at a high level. He isn't a
Gundam pilot for nothing.
He's better than the
mobile dolls?
He hasn't reached his limit yet.
Check his fastest reaction.
[QUATRE:] A system that can
beat mobile dolls...
[QUATRE:] To say that humans are
unnecessary in a battle...
Heero, it's human being's that
fight against each other.
But those humans are now
depending on machines to give
their strength to fight.
[QUATRE:] Heero, it's mistaken.
This Gundam is a mistake.
[TECHNICIAN:] These combat
abilities are extremely high.
It's amazing!
[HEERO:] Who... who are.
[BEEPING INTENSIFIES]
[HEERO:] My enemies...
[HEERO:] My enemies... are the
ones after my life.
[TRANT:] What!?
[QUATRE:] Heero!
[TRANT:] Hey! Remember,
we have hostages!
[QUATRE:] Heero!
[EXPLOSION]
[TRANT:] Get me more
mobile dolls!
[TECHNICIAN:] Yes sir!
Heero... No! You're not Heero!
[HEERO:] My enemies are the ones
after my life... and the ones
that toy with my life.
[EXPLOSIONS]
They're all my enemies.
Hostages don't mean
anything to those guys.
That's because we made targets
for Heero to fight against!
Oz and ourselves aren't
needed in outer space.
That system disrupts the
cerebration balance that's in
the human psyche.
And the fact that we're trying
to use it to beat the
mobile dolls proves
that our minds have already
been warped by it.
Well then, shall we go?
To get ourselves killed?
As long as they're defeated in
the end, during this war.
Please contact Commander
Tubarov for backup now!
We can't tell him of this
blunder that we've
created you fool!
What is that Lieutenant!?
[TUBAROV:] Stop! What
are you doing!?
[TUBAROV:] I'm
telling you to stop!
You people don't wanna die here,
do you!?
I'm gonna stop him
from attacking!
What?!
He might destroy this
entire base!
Trowa himself said there's no
sense at all having just
one pilot go running amuck
in a mobile suit.
This war will never come to an
end if people keep trying to
fight it all by themselves.
[EXPLOSION]
Heero, that cockpit increases
your fighting abilities.
[QUATRE:] But at the same time,
you lose control.
[QUATRE:] If I lose control
because of that cockpit, then
I've lost something important
because of a worthless
piece of machinery.
I don't want to lose any more of
what's important to me.
Quatre. I've got a very clear
view of the enemy.
If you're going to be an enemy,
then I'm going to
have to kill you.
That Gundam is all on it's own.
But we musn't fight alone,
right?
You lose sight of the target
when you fight by yourself.
I can see my target.
[HEERO:] I see my enemy.
There's still a self‐detonation
system left in this suit.
If you don't stop fighting, I
will destroy these two mobile
suits right here!
[QUATRE:] These mobile suits are
the least necessary things in
outer space right now.
But there's something else that
outer space needs even less.
Outer space needs the Gundams.
And I'll fight to
defend outer space.
We aren't needed.
We aren't needed in
outer space Heero!
[PAINFUL SCREAM]
What!? What's the
matter with me.
[QUATRE:] We mustn't fight each
other. It's just not right!
We mustn't fight each other.
It isn't right. Huh?
Relena.
Are you okay Heero?
Who is it?
Is it someone from Earth?
Am I right? Heero, let's
go to the Earth.
The Earth was very
kind to us all.
[EXPLOSION]
[ROCKET ENGINE NOISE]
[DOCTOR J:] We ended up
surviving again! And so
did this guy!
Is it necessary for the future?
We'll leave that for the
next pilot to decide.
They're not about to be defeated
by this suit. They'll prevail.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] The rise and fall of
the victorious endlessly
repeats itself.
And people get tossed around by
a history of disputes.
Caught within the flames of war,
the Gundam pilots wander
without a destination.
What did they lose, what were
they able to gain,
and what words does Relena have
after observing them?
Next on Gundam Wing Episode 27:
The Locus of Victory and Defeat.