[OPENING THEME]
[GUNDAM WING]
[NARRATOR] By having Relena
Peacecraft join the
Romefeller Foundation as
their representative and a
symbol of peace they are
able to gain the
support of the people and are
justified in making the World
Nation a reality.
Meanwhile in outer space, an
uprising. An armed
organization called White Fang
directs all forces to fight for
the independence of
the colonies.
The White Fang organization
welcomed its new leader.
[ZECHS] Earth and space. The
two exist together
and form a pattern of
confrontation.
My name is Milliardo Peacecraft.
I declare that we will
eliminate the Earth,
the force that
conflicts with space.
[HEERO] Zechs you've chosen
one of the futures
Epyon showed you.
Well out of the futures that
Wing Zero showed me I've
chosen this one...
[HEERO] Crossfire at Barge.
Enemy dolls have crossed the
space minefield. ETA
to defense line
is two minutes.
[MAN] Our Taurus mobile doll
troops will take their
defense formation.
[SOLDIER] They'll be fully
deployed in t‐minus 30.
[COMMANDER] Isn't the Barge
cannon ready yet?
[SOLDIER] Connections are
complete. We'll bring
in the workers.
[COMMANDER] Increase energy
level on the double!
[MAN 2] Yes sir! All units
assume phase 3 battle positions!
Send out every Taurus suit and
don't let the enemy
get near Barge.
This is our last fortress in
space and we can't afford
to lose it now.
[MAN 2] The laser beams won't
work against the Virgos.
Arm the Taurus suits with
laser cannons!
[MAN] They're not programmed for
the additional output. They'd
overheat in no time!
[MAN 2] Doesn't matter! As long
as they wipe out some
of the dolls!
[SOLDIER] The enemy mobile dolls
will reach our first
defense line in
[SOLDIER] 10... 9... 8... 7...
6... 5... 4... 3... 2...
[SOLDIER] One! The battle has
begun! [DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[NARRATOR] The White Fang
initiated a battle with the
space fortress Barge.
It was obvious to everyone that
the winner would claim
supremacy through outer space.
For this reason both the Oz
space forces and the White Fang
fought an extremely fierce
Battle employing
their full forces.
Mobile doll unit five moving
to the left wing.
35% have crossed the
enemy defense line.
That's the way! Now keep on
applying pressure!
There's something approaching
us from behind, sir.
[SEDICI] What?! That's the
Epyon! It's Commander Milliardo!
Wait Commander Milliardo. What
are you doing in your
mobile suit?
You're the chief commander of
the White Fang aren't you?
Just give
out the orders and leave the
fighting to the mobile dolls.
[ZECHS] You do just that.
Commander Milliardo still thinks
of himself as the
lightning count.
Hang on a second
please Miss Noin.
I know you don't want me to do
this but I really have to
meet with Zechs
and talk to him in person. I am
positive he has to have
a good reason. He must be
rebelling for the Sanc
Kingdom and Miss Relena.
Still it's too dangerous to
approach Barge alone.
Sandrock's been completely
repaired. I'll go with you.
Quatre...
[DUO] There's lots of civilian
colonies around Barge!
Shouldn't be too hard to
approach the fortress unnoticed!
[NOIN] Duo! [QUATRE] Will
you come with us?
I wanna let Oz and the guys at
White Fang know the God of Death
is back and he's come
with a bang!
Thanks a lot Duo.
Catch all that?
Well at the very least I guess I
could cover for you guys.
Trowa! ‐ You guys
came back here.
[NOIN] Right!
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
Enemy forces destroyed.
Base controlled.
My enemy's in space.
[ALARM BEEPING]
[HEERO] Sally Po...?
I'm so glad I made it
here on time.
Don't go firing on me I've got
something important to give you.
It was a pain finding it so I
want to make sure you get it.
[SALLY] Heero... you were
planning to return to
space weren't you?
Would you mind taking this
along with you?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Does this mean you found
out where Trowa is?
No but I think that the Gundams
are essential to our
present era.
That's why I want to do whatever
I can to help you guys.
Listen Heero: Fighting by
yourself is so lonely.
I'm sure you don't
like getting sympathy but won't
you let me help you
out a little?
[BEEP] [HEERO] Enemy's here.
What?
[HEERO] Prepare your shuttle for
takeoff. I'll take care
of these guys.
[BLASTOFF]
I don't see anyone. Ah!
He seems kinda different this
time. He used to have
such an abrasive
personality. He was so
hard to approach.
Ah! Get a move on and load
up that Gundam!
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
[MARQUIS] How could this have
happened? I can't believe it.
The direct
descendants of the Peacecrafts
are battling against each other.
[MAN] Marquis Weridge are you
sure he's really
Milliardo Peacecraft?
I didn't want to believe it. But
it is him alright.
What does Queen Relena plan to
do about it? Now that
Duke Dermail's been
killed Miss Relena's the only
one who could hope to control
the new Romefeller.
King Peacecraft in heaven I
offer you my deepest apologies.
In an effort
to attain our ideal world we've
guided your children to a
very cruel destiny.
[TREIZE] If you truly feel that
way then I ask that you
abide by my orders.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[RELENA] The Earth is finally
heading towards peace.
What could you be
thinking Milliardo?
Well regardless of what you have
up your sleeve dear brother...
fighting isn't the solution. And
it's my responsibility
and my duty to make you stop.
[FOOTSTEPS]
Is anybody here?
Huh?
Long time no see, Miss Relena.
It's you Treize Khushrenada.
Why are you here?
[TREIZE] I thought I'd inform
you of a decision made
by Romefeller's
top executives.
[RELENA] I don't know what
you're talking about.
As of this day you're to be
dismissed of your duties
as representative
of the Romefeller Foundation. I
must therefore ask you to
resign from your
position as queen.
I understand you. I will give up
my rights as the representative.
[RELENA] But there is still one
last thing that I have to do
before I resign.
I must convince my brother
Milliardo to stop fighting
against the Earth.
[TREIZE] You're not
capable of doing that.
What's that supposed to mean?
[TREIZE] It's a crime to confine
you within this
antiquated cage‐like
foundation. I will be
Romefeller's chief
representative.
I'll personally lead the battle
to its conclusion.
You're free. Free to go wherever
you please. [DRAMATIC MUSIC]
So Miss Relena's going out to
outer space. In that case I'll
have to get a space
shuttle ready myself.
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
They're nothing but lifeless
dolls. They're no enemy of mine.
[COMMANDER] Damn that Gundam! We
can't afford to let the
enemy get any
closer to us than this. Prepare
to fire the Barge cannon now!
[SOLDIER] But the energy level
is only at 80% capacity!
I don't care! That's still
enough to fire.
[SEDICI] OK move units 8 to 24
to the left. The remaining
units will continue
to advance. We'll leave the
central units to Commander
Milliardo &amp; the Epyon.
That's right the Gundam is our
organization's symbol.
and it's combat abilities are
much greater than those of
the mobile dolls.
[DUO] Whoa look at 'em go!
What do you think? I don't have
any idea where Zechs might be.
We'll be right behind ya, so
let's go. Trowa?
I'm taking off to go and protect
the civilian colonies .
Hey! Hang on! Man talk about
making fast decisions...
Trowa... [NOIN] Quatre! Enemies!
Well... I'll give ya my
self‐introduction for starters.
[DUO] Here it goes.
[DUO] What?
Isn't that the‐ ‐It's
the Epyon Gundam!
What in blazes are they
doing out here?
Col Sedici we are detecting a
very strong energy
coming from Barge.
What?
[SOLDIER] Adjust booster firing
angle completed.
HKS pressure
balance stable. TRD bypass
unit connected.
Final safety lock disengaged.
Ready to fire!
Fire the Barge cannon right now!
[CANNON FIRE]
[DUO] What is that thing?
[SCREAMS]
No! How could they do that?!
[ALERT BEEP]
Hey hold it! Is this
guy an enemy?
Hey! That Gundam
pilot isn't Heero!
You finally made it...
Is that really you Zechs?
It's Zechs?
Zechs is piloting that?
[DUO] Take this!
[GRUNT] Talk about speed and
power. That thing is as
powerful as Wing Zero!
It's incredible! What strength!
No how could you Zechs?
[DUO SCREAMS]
[COMMANDER] What's going on?!
Why are the Gundams
fighting each other?
In any case this is our big
chance! Ready the cannon
to fire again.
We'll completely wipe them out
with our next attack!
[CANNON POWERING UP]
[GRUNT] He has got
the upper hand!
[QUATRE] No, not again!
Duo! Check out Barge!
They're gonna fire that again?!
I haven't got time to be
playing games with you...
[ENERGETIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[QUATRE] Miss Noin! Out of the
way it's dangerous!
I'll stay and take care of 'em!
You go stop the barge cannon!
Noin! ‐ Get going!!
[DUO] Quatre we
haven't got time!
[NOIN] Zechs. Zechs! Don't you
recognize my voice?
[Zechs] I can hear you.
Zechs that's better. You owe me
an explanation as to why you've
been acting this way.
[NOIN] Under Miss Relena's rule
the Earth is finally moving
toward pacificism.
So why would you choose to
become Miss Relena's enemy?
[ZECHS] It's just as I've
declared. From outer
space's perspective the
origin of all disputes is the
Earth. And none other.
Wait a second!
[NOIN] Ugh!
And that's why I'll set
everything right.
You're serious...
Zechs! Don't!
Look out!
Watch out for yourself. There's
no sense dying here.
Oh, but Trowa...
[DUO YELLS]
Just get outta my way!!
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
Come on! We've gotta hurry!
Pressure within the DFV chamber
is stable! Connection with the
BBS system confirmed.
Pressure is rising inside the
cylinder. 10 seconds left to
reach the critical level.
They're finished! This is the
end of the line for
those Gundams!
Have a taste of our Barge
cannon at full power!
[DUO] We're not gonna make it!
There goes Zechs!
What?
[ZECHS] You're not needed here.
[ZECHS] We have no need for
you in outer space!
[EXPLOSIONS]
No... Barge is finished.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
That's the end... it's sinking.
Oh Zechs...
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR] Wu Fei continues to
fight alone and Wing
Zero shows him
the future he's meant to take.
On Earth, Treize's subordinates
who were able to escape from
Barge return to him. Among them
is the still
unconscious Lady Une.
Meanwhile Zechs orders the
now‐completed
battleship Libra to be
directed towards Earth.
Next on Gundam Wing Episode 42:
Battleship Libra