[THEME MUSIC]
In the year After Colony 175,
the leader of the colonies
was assassinated.
Five Gundams were supposed
to have been sent to Earth
to take revenge.
However, since OZ's activities
in space
took the form of
cooperation,
rather than control, the colonies
decided to accept OZ.
In the year After Colony 195,
as OZ moves to take over
both the Earth and outer space,
the Gundams are labeled as rebels
and are isolated from society.
With no place to return,
the Gundams and their pilots are
forced to fight
for a reason to
exist
in the ever‐changing world.
Hurry up and return to me, Zechs.
Because if you're not
around to help,
OZ will allow worthless
actions by worthless people.
And now, I cannot be your
friend any more.
[NARRATOR:] Assault On Barge
I'm alive.
[VOICE:] Hey, sir!
Howard, take a look at him!
[HOWARD:] Give me a minute,
would ya?
Hmm. You don't look too bad.
Can you get up?
You were piloting that
interesting‐looking machine.
I picked it up as well.
I never would have
guessed in a million years
there’d be any pilots
other than those kids
who’d be capable of
piloting the Tallgeese.
So who are you?
I'm one of the people who
was involved in its design.
Although that was a long time ago.
You mean you made the Tallgeese?
I was sailing through this area
and I caught sight of a
pretty intense‐looking battle.
I decided to stick
around and watch.
Are you in a lot of pain?
Why did you bother to
save me anyway?
You have become OZ's enemy.
Zechs Merquise.
OZ's very own hero has
broken away from them.
There's no harm in
taking care of you.
That man is dead, Zechs Merquise.
It seems like it.
[HOWARD:] The times are changing.
I'd love to see the new
era while I'm still alive.
It's a fabulous piece
of machinery.
There’s good reason it's the
prototype for the Gundams.
Those rockets,
are they vernier rockets
for atmospheric clearance?
To tell the truth, they
were originally manufactured
for the purpose of
getting the Gundams
back into outer space.
Oh, by the way.
Do you think you’d be able
to make it to outer space?
Outer space?
It's about to undergo a
drastic transformation.
And there's a growing need
for highly skilled people
like yourself.
[NARRATOR:] OZ, which was
applying pressure
on the former United Earth
Sphere Alliance Space Force
stationed at La Grange Point,
was steadily increasing its
strength within the colonies.
The Space Fortress Barge
was symbolic of this strength.
However, OZ would not
show its aggressive side
to the citizens of the colonies.
Instead, it showed a completely
different aspect of itself.
OZ's Colonel Une replaced
the former Commander
of the Alliance Space Force
and succeeded in forming relations
with representatives of
the colonies.
Coupled with a sense of liberation
from the militaristic
pressure of the Alliance,
the colonies were welcoming
OZ to its new establishment.
[COLONEL UNE:] In order to attain
peace and to coexist,
not only in the colonies but
in the whole Earth Sphere,
we must have your cooperation.
Unfortunately though, there are
still those within the colonies
who are doubtful of OZ.
And who insist in pointing out
the mistakes made in the past.
However, I believe that
the day will come
when these people will
understand the efforts made by OZ.
That’s my belief.
We feel they'll change
their minds as well.
And we're desperately trying to
convince each of the colonies.
On the other hand, we have
no means to counter violence.
That's what OZ is here for.
As long as OZ is present
I have no doubt that justice
will be served, Gentlemen.
If Colonel Une says so,
then there's no need to worry.
Once peace spreads into space
even those who still
harbor doubts toward OZ
will awaken to the truth.
Yes.
[OZ SOLDIER:] Colonel Une!
We now have the item in question.
Huh?
[OZ SOLDIER:] Colonel,
please return to Barge.
[COLONEL UNE:] To Barge?
[OZ SOLDIER:] They’re
orders from His Excellency.
His Excellency Treize...
[COLONEL UNE:] I'll
return to Barge.
[COLONEL UNE:] Are you certain?
There’s no question.
It's the HLV carrier that left
Earth carrying a Gundam.
The Gundams are evil
and will cause damage
to the colonies.
They'd be valuable
as our scapegoats of evil.
Bring out the Tauruses!
Capture it!
What do we do with the pilot?
Depends on his looks.
Huh?
[COLONEL UNE:] If he's ugly,
let him live.
If there’s a chance people
might sympathize with him,
then kill him.
We can't have anything
get in the way
of changing the general
public’s minds.
Let him live if he's ugly? Really?
[LAUGHS] Just kidding.
[SOLDIER #1:] We have
confirmation on the carrier.
It's an HLV from Singapore
used to transport a Gundam.
No energy detected.
It's a miracle that it was able to
fly this far without refueling.
[SOLDIER #2:] It’s possible
that nobody’s on it.
[SOLDIER #1:] Regardless,
orders are to capture it.
We'll tow it along to
Colony C1102.
[SOLDIER #2:] Roger!
[SOLDIER #1:] What?
It’s quite an honor, being
greeted by your latest model.
But let me warn you
that anyone carelessly
approaching is gonna die!
[SOLDIER #1:] Taurus mobile dolls,
attack!
They're fast!
So that didn't work either!
Zero output, huh?
Well, if Deathscythe goes down, I
don't have long myself.
But still, I'll die fighting!
Gundam, you're just lucky
I wasn't a mobile doll.
[DUO:] I don't want to copy Heero,
but...
Tag along, on my
journey into hell!!
Not my lucky day.
Can't even self‐detonate.
Or maybe I am lucky.
[NEWSCASTER:] One of the
Gundam mobile suits
known for their destruction
and threat to peace
was shot down by OZ's Taurus unit.
The Gundam pilot has
been arrested.
The background of this pilot
has not been confirmed.
But OZ has commented
that their arrest
will assist them as they
increase efforts
to eradicate rebels and their
respective organizations.
The colony governments
have responded
by announcing full
cooperation on this matter.
It is hoped that with the
joint cooperation
of OZ and the colony governments
we will soon be able to
return to total peace.
Are the people of the colonies
so accustomed to being controlled
that nobody can figure out the
Gundams
are the only ally that they’ve
got?
Still, I have no choice
left but to fight.
[TROWA:] It's just too far
away from here.
But it's close to the
colony Heero went to.
He'll do something, for sure.
[HEERO:] After Colony 175.
No major incidents
within the colonies?
The history on the assassination
of the
leader Heero Yuy has been deleted.
OZ's methods haven't
changed one little bit.
[NEWSCASTER:] OZ has commented
that this will assist them
as they increase efforts to
eradicate rebels
and their respective
organizations.
[HEERO:] Now would not be the
right time for battle.
All negative factors from now on
must be eliminated.
[FLIGHT DECK:] Flight 0904,
proceed to R28.
Proceed to R28.
What's this?
[NEWSCASTER:] Following the
capture of the mad scientists,
foes to the colonies and the
people of Earth,
one of the Gundams and its
pilot have now been caught.
[HEINOUS JEERS FROM CROWD]
The authorities of colony C102
are calling OZ's latest
actions a great success.
And say they'll
continue to promote
cooperative efforts
with each other.
[NICHOL:] I wasn't expecting
the pilot of that Gundam
to be just a kid.
Well, excuse me!
So I wounded your pride, have I?
That’s nothing compared to
how your pride has suffered.
[NICHOL:] You'll be executed.
The people's feelings toward the
execution will unite the colonies.
I never expected to be able to
utilize
the Gundam pilots this
way.
Why you!
Damn all of you to hell!
They did me over. They
could’ve been more gentle.
[COUGHING, HACKING]
This isn’t good.
What a surprise, hey Heero.
You really are superhuman huh?
Just in time.
They were about to use me and my
Gundam for their wicked plans.
If I'm gonna die, it’d seem
appropriate for you to do it.
Here, go right ahead and shoot me.
[DUO:] Hey, you're really gonna
shoot me, aren't you?
If that's what you want me to do.
Your right hand's still okay,
isn’t it?
So, which way is it?
Where’s your Gundam?
I left it on Earth.
It'd stick out too much in space.
So I'd wind up getting
caught like you did.
Yeah, well pardon me!
So how do you plan on getting
us out of here anyway?
I came here so I could kill you.
I hadn't gotten around to
thinking up an escape plan yet.
If we don't make it?
It's as simple as
silencing the two of us.
[EXPLOSIONS]
[OZ SOLDIERS:] What's going on?
What happened?
Why is it always the quietest guys
that end up doing
things the
flashiest way?
A number of minor bombs have
been set
in the supply shipping
block!
[NICHOL:] What about the Gundam?
Increase security around
the Gundam pilot!
[OZ SOLDIER:] This is the
observation room!
The Gundam pilot has escaped with
the help of someone from outside!
[NICHOL:] Damn it!
What about the Gundam?
[OZ SOLDIER:] There
were explosions in the area.
But no sign of intruders.
Show me the explosion points.
[NICHOL:] Explosions are centered
around the storage area and gate.
The mobile suit gate is untouched!
The enemy will be
escaping from there!
Send out the dolls!
Wouldn't target settings
be difficult within the colony?
The mobile dolls aren't
some rickety old system!
They're annihilation machines!
Deploy them at once!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Enemy attack
on Colony C102.
Backup troops, head there at once!
[NICHOL:] What’s this?
I finally found you.
So now you can show me what
you're made of!!
We're sending some
Tauruses to attack!
Colonel? Colonel Une!
You’re in danger!
[NICHOL:] A Gundam is
right by the base!
The Colonel must be
heading for a new district
to attend a colony meeting!
Colonel!
This couldn't be all you've got.
You people are strong enough
to control the minds
of the colony citizens.
So I know you’re underhanded
and a lot stronger!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Lieutenant Nichol!
Gundam 05 and the Leos in pursuit
are entering the firing range
of Barge's Beam Cannon!
[NICHOL:] Okay, fire!
But we'd be firing on
our own Leos!
Who cares?
Do it before the Colonel leaves!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Gundam 05
now within firing range!
[NICHOL:] Fire!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Yes sir!
Sacrificing your own men?
I've never seen the enemy appear
as large and foul as
they look now.
I can fight! When deceitful guys
like you are strong,
I can fight
you!
[COLONEL UNE:] Please
stop. Stop this futile battle.
Let us together greet a new age.
Who's that?
Let's do away with any
desires to battle
that were left over from
the passing era.
There’s no need for such
destructive desires in the future.
Who are you?
[NICHOL:] Taurus troops,
we're moving in on the Gundam!
This battle is futile.
Please end it.
Colonel Une, please give
us orders to attack now!
[GIGGLES] I just can’t.
Peace should prevail in
outer space from now on.
[NICHOL:] Colonel?
Never mind, attack O5!
Just you wait there OZ, because
I’ll return and I’m going to get
you!
— [NICHOL:] After 05!
— [OZ SOLDIER:] Yes sir!
No, wait a second! Forget it!
Which Colonel am I
supposed to follow anyway?
So those new models
are the mobile dolls, huh?
No wonder their reaction
time is quick!
Once they're locked onto a target,
there's just no escaping them.
Then how are we going to get away?
I'm not thinking about escaping.
What are you saying?
Duo!
Right.
[EXPLOSIONS]
We could use this.
Hey, what the heck is
going on here?
Why are the mobile dolls
attacking the Leos?
I got it.
A Leo was scrambling to get
off the premises.
So the mobile dolls set
it as a target.
Huh?
According to this, another
target has been set.
It's an astro suit!
The astro suit has
been set as a target!
Cancel the auto command!
Cancel it! Hurry!
[SCREAMING]
I left my Gundam
behind back there.
I've gotta destroy it!
The Gundams are worthless.
What?
Dr. J and the other scientists who
originally designed the Gundams
have all been caught by OZ.
I'll kill them all.
Oh Heero.
[HEERO:] I’ll eliminate
all obstacles.
This is going a bit overboard
just to get one person into space.
Outer space is rejecting humans.
And come to think of it,
perhaps the Earth is trying
to tell us we're mistaken
by pulling us back down toward it.
[ENDING MUSIC]
The five scientists start
developing
OZ's newest mobile suits:
Mercurius and Vayeate.
In an attempt to stop them,
Heero sneaks into the Lunar Base
by himself to assassinate them.
But he's stopped in his tracks
by none other than Trowa.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 20:
The Lunar Base Infiltration