[OPENING THEME]
GUNDAM WING
[NARRATOR] Zero system. The name
given to a cockpit system that
quickly calculates battle data
and feeds the large amounts
of statistics on estimated
values directly back
to the pilot.
but this system also drives a
pilot to his limits.
To the extent that he won't even
fear his own death.
Thus helping him gain
absolute victory.
The year is After Colony 195. As
the world constantly changes
in the chaotic era, there are
two mobile suits that could
turn humans into the
ultimate weapon:
The Wing Zero and the Epyon.
[HEERO] The Birth of
Queen Relena.
[NARRATOR] The chaotic situation
on Earth in turn
brings chaos to the
space colonies. Citizens of the
colonies, retaliating
against the Romefeller
Foundation's dictatorship,
form an armed group calling
themselves the White Fang,
and they are determined to
free the colonies.
Despite having lost Commander
Tubarov, Oz fights back
with force and
sends in their mobile dolls.
Consequently, battles start up
in a number of locations.
[EXPLOSIONS] [GUNFIRE]
Do not fly straight for
the mobile dolls.
Lure them into range of the
beam cannon now!
[VOICE ON RADIO] Roger!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
Why are you guys bringing this
meaningless battle out here
to outer space?!
[PILOT] A Gundam?!
[PILOT SCREAMS]
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
A Gundam seems to have arrived
in the battle zone.
He's come.
Miss Noin we can't risk getting
any closer in this shuttle.
You're right. This is
close enough.
[NOIN] I'll go alone from here.
Be careful.
[MOBILE SUIT LAUNCHING]
It must be the pilot of
Gundam Zero Five.
He's fighting with a strong
sense of justice as well.
[MUSIC PLAYS]
The entire mobile doll unit has
been defeated by a single suit.
This Gundam is incredibly
strong. [GASP]
[WU FEI] Discard your weapons!
Huh?
[WU FEI] Throw away all
your weapons!
When the weak have weapons
they give into their own minds
and start going wild.
The weak shouldn't be fighting!
[NOIN] You haven't changed a bit
Wu Fei Chang. Do you
remember me?
I met you at the Lake
Victoria base, remember?
So you're that woman.
My name is Lucrezia Noin.
It's pretty strange.
I don't have any hard feelings
toward you any longer.
[NOIN] When you think about how
enormous this universe is
the humiliation I've felt
seems so irrelevant.
I get the feeling you didn't
come here to battle.
[NOIN] I need your help.
Huh?
Actually I need the help of all
the Gundam pilots.
[NOIN] I love outer space but I
also love the Earth. I don't
want to harm either.
And that's why I need help in
order to create peace.
I'm sure you Gundam pilots can
understand just how I feel.
Won't you help me?
Hmm...
For the Sanc Kingdom? But that
country's already
been demolished.
Why are you still
fighting over it?
The country was demolished. But
the honorable spirits of
the Sanc Kingdom
can never be killed off. That's
what I wanna protect.
Sounds like something a
woman would say.
Well I'm still gonna take my own
path. I'm not taking any orders.
Hmm...
Hmm... huh?
[HILDE] Duo?
Oh sorry. I'm done
filing my stuff.
[HILDE] Duo you're still
thinking of that guy,
aren't you?
It's just depressing to think
that that could happen to a
fellow Gundam pilot.
And I've been wondering what's
going to happen to the
colonies too.
Does kinda make you think.
[HILDE] Why are you
getting so depressed?
You're gonna live the life you
believe in right? That's what
you told me yourself.
Yeah that's right. Well maybe I
should start out by
finding a decent job.
Look here's a new job.
[HILDE] They're looking for
mobile suit workers at a natural
resource satellite.
Huh?
What is it?
Look! This satellite belongs to
the Winner family.
The Winner family?
I heard that all operations had
been suspended indefinitely
[HILDE] ever since the
owner was killed.
Then it could only mean one
thing: The son in the
family's back!
[SOMBRE MUSIC PLAYS]
[BUSINESS CHATTER]
[DUO] Nice digs!
Yo Quatre! How ya been?
Duo!
[DUO] What an impressive
building. Your family's
really something!
This is all yours now, right?
No not yet. My sisters are
managing all the assets of the
corporation right now.
As far as anyone else
knows I'm missing.
Because you're a Gundam pilot?
Quatre where were you anyway?
On the Earth. I went with Heero
to figure out what we
should be doing.
That's that reason I went.
So did you come up
with anything?
[QUATRE] I think we've gotta
fight. That's why I came
looking for you guys.
There are lots of kind people on
Earth, Duo. And the same is
true for the colonies.
[QUATRE] I want to help build a
world where everyone can
live in peace.
I want to protect the total
pacifism upheld by the
Sanc Kingdom.
[DUO] Total pacifism. Do you
really think such a
world is possible?
Duo?
I've been fighting for the
colonies all this time.
They should leave the
fighting to me.
I should be the only one who has
to suffer as much as I did.
But now the colonies have
decided to start up a war.
[DUO] Which means that a lot
more people will end up dying.
Maybe I've lost faith in what
we're fighting for
and the future that we
dreamed about.
Maybe in the end peace is just
an impossible dream.
[QUATRE] I made a grave
mistake once.
I don't expect to ever be
forgiven but I'll risk
everything to show my remorse.
And I'll do that by fostering
my hope for peace.
Because once a dream is lost,
then really everything is lost.
You may be right about that.
Although a dismal future might
be more suitable for the god
of death huh? Ha!
Duo?
[YAWN] Well Quatre this place is
just a little too
high‐class for me.
I'll see ya around buddy boy!
If you're really gonna keep
looking around for the
Gundam pilots
I guess you'll see
what's‐his‐name...
Duo, do you mean...?
[SIGH]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Hmmm.
[RELENA] Come on Relena.
The destiny of the world is
resting on your shoulders.
Heero...
Mmmm...
He's here?
[TROWA] OK. OK I'll go
get your food.
Trowa?
[QUATRE] Trowa it's really you!
Who are you?
[QUATRE] Trowa!
Sorry do you know me
or something?
[QUATRE] What? Don't
you recognize me?
[BUCKET CRASHES]
Trowa get back to the tent!
Yeah sure, but sis?
Sis?
Get going! [SIGH] I'll look
after feeding the animals.
You go and help the manager. OK?
OK.
Wait!
Why'd you come here? Are you
planning on taking him out
to fight again?
[QUATRE] Who are you?!
Trowa's like my brother. He
belongs with us!
But Trowa's...
I can't bear to see him suffer
any more than he already has.
He's lost his
memories of the past because
they're too painful for him. He
doesn't want to remember.
It's my fault. It's all my fault
and I'm truly sorry.
Trowa sacrificed
himself to correct a mistake
that I had made myself.
I know apologizing won't fix
things but I really am sorry.
If that's the way you feel
just leave him!
Trowa's a lot happier now being
here at the circus with us.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Trowa... I'm sorry.
[PAINFUL GROANS]
[TROWA] Who... is that?!
I... I know that guy! I've
met him before.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Hey old buddy! What do you
think we should do?
[DUO] Can you still fight?
Yeah, I guess you got a point.
This isn't like me at all,
is it?
I wonder if Quatre got
to see Trowa...
[CIRCUS MUSIC]
Catherine! Trowa! We've got a
great crowd today so give
it all you've got.
Leave it to us. We'll give 'em a
performance they won't forget
for the rest of their lives.
Right Trowa?
Huh?
Trowa?
Huh? What is it?
Master Quatre a battle between
Oz and White Fang troops is
starting to spread into this
area. If it continues the entire
colony could get involved.
[QUATRE] Why? The people here
just want to live a quiet
trouble‐free life.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
How dare Oz bring the colony
into the line of fire!
[PANIC AND YELLING]
Help get the audience out
safely. And a few of
you better take
care of the animals as well.
Let's go.
Hey look out!
[CRASH]
Are you OK, Trowa?
I'm cold. And I'm scared.
Something's coming.
There there. It's alright. I'm
here by your side.
Thanks Cathy.
Poor Trowa.
Trowa!
[QUATRE] It's dangerous here.
You've gotta hurry to shelter.
What in the world's going on?
It's a battle. Mobile suits have
started exchanging fire
near the colony.
But why? We're just trying to
live out our lives
here in peace.
How many more people have to be
sacrificed before this ends?
[CATHERINE] I don't wanna lose
any more people who are
important to me.
I just couldn't stand it.
No need to cry, Cathy.
I promise to protect you myself.
Trowa...
[QUATRE] I don't wanna lose
anyone else, either.
You saved me Trowa. You
really saved my soul.
So now it's my turn to try and
save some people.
That's what the Gundam was built
for in the first place.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Hold your positions until
reinforcements arrive!
More troops!
No it's the Gundam!
I won't allow you to harm the
colony any further.
[QUATRE YELLS]
Hmmm...
[CATHERINE] Trowa!
Trowa where are you going?
He's calling me.
I don't hear anybody.
He's crying. I can
tell from here.
[QUATRE YELLS]
You can't! You went through so
much pain the last time.
Are you really planning
to fight again?
I have a faint memory of
someone once telling me
that the only way for anyone to
live a good life is to act
on their emotions.
You're gonna go. No matter what.
You're so stubborn.
That side of you hasn't changed
one bit. You're nuts.
I promise you I'll come
back alive, Cathy.
Oh Trowa...
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
You're nuts. I really mean it.
We've gotta try putting an end
to this kind of nonsense.
Trowa?!
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[DOOR KNOCK]
Come in.
Hello Miss Relena. Are you
almost finished getting ready?
Yes thanks.
Then let's be on our way.
[DOROTHY] Today's the day you'll
become the leader of the
world Miss Relena!
Everyone will be so surprised.
I'm as thrilled as if it were
happening to myself.
Oh... that won't do. That
expression is simply not right.
You must show them all your
elegant smile...
[DOROTHY] ... because from this
day on you're the queen
of the world.
I wish to make an announcement
to the entire world.
[RELENA] As of this day I,
Relena Peacecraft, have
taken on the duties
as chief representative of the
Romefeller Foundation.
However I am not doing this for
the sake of the
Romefeller Foundation.
I think of this as the first
step along a very positive road.
And upon this road we can
all walk together.
We can eliminate wars
and create peace.
At this time I ask that you all
discard your weapons
and stop fighting.
Because I am sure that we are
all hoping for the same future.
So together let us all advance
toward these objectives.
I am announcing the elimination
of all national borders.
These borders have been the
cause of wars around the world.
I declare there is one nation:
The World Nation.
[MUSIC PLAYS] [APPLAUSE]
The Foundation was clever. She
certainly has the ability to
attract the hearts of the people
to Romefeller. But I seriously
doubt that the Foundation
realizes just how much of a risk
this move will be.
Relena...
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR] In his move to
retaliate against Romefeller,
Quinze, the leader of the
colonies movement,
contacts Zechs
and requests that he bring his
Gundam, the symbol of rebellion,
to outer space. Meanwhile
Quatre's shuttle is attacked
in space. Although still
suffering from his amnesia,
Trowa heads out with
a Taurus suit.
Next on Gundam Wing episode 39:
Trowa's Return to the
Battlefield.