[MUSIC]
The attacks by the five Gundams
sent by the Space Colonies...
...reflected their
retaliatory intentions.
The Gundam's target is OZ who
had masked its identity
within the mobile suit troops of
the Alliance Military...
...and the Gundams' had a number
of missions to attack OZ.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken
center stage.
With an army of elite soldiers
at his command...
...Treize Khushrenada
carries out his plans
to destroy the
Alliance Military.
The battle between the
mobile suits sent to Earth...
...and OZ, causes the Earth to
shudder violently.
It's up to you now, go
for it Heero!
He's got a 10 percent chance of
success, but that guy can
do it for sure.
What a mission.
I failed...
...I totally failed!!
[NARRATOR:] Portrait of a
Ruined Country
Thanks to the Lightning Count,
we were able to keep the town
from being demolished.
The Alliance is likely
regrouping their
remaining force...
...following the
unexpected attack.
We'll use this base as our
headquarters for
subsequent fights.
The beauty of these towns
doesn't change no
matter who rules.
Noin...
OZ's objective isn't to rule.
It's to free countries from
the United Earth Sphere
Alliance stranglehold...
Currently, you mean.
This might be somewhat unnatural
coming from me...
...but I believe that due
respect should be given
to OZ for allowing countries
a second chance...
...to correct the mistake of
forming the Alliance
in the first place.
The mobile suit carrier from
Victoria Base is about
to arrive, Sir.
They're here.
Otto, I'm so glad to see you!
I've returned, Lieutenant.
You need to rest.
Are you alright?
Lieutenant Otto shouldn't
even be standing!
His ribs are broken, and
he has internal injuries.
Keep it to yourself.
Lieutenant Zechs.
This Tallgeese you've been
waiting for is one vicious suit.
This is Tallgeese...
It doesn't look anything at
all like a thing that
was scrapped midway
20 years ago.
The revolution speed
applied by the verniers...
...allows it to reach more than
three times that of the Aries.
We were unable to determine
its maximum speed.
I passed out during the trials.
You were the test pilot?!
The Tallgeese is not a
suit that can be
controlled by just anyone.
Excluding you, Sir.
Aren't you overrating my skills?
No, I trust your abilities.
All right.
I'll be using this right away.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Take him to the medical room.
Sir!
Noin.
Have the mobile suit troops
ready to leave at once.
We'll head for the
Sanc Kingdom base
of the United Earth
Sphere Alliance.
The Sanc Kingdom?
We're freeing them from
the Alliance.
Any objections to this mission?
No, Lieutenant!
I'm going on the Tallgeese.
Without even a test ride?
Isn't that dangerous?
Don't worry, I'll be taking it
easy, but you know
I'll be taking my chances with
this mobile suit.
Sanc Kingdom.
Zechs' home town.
Heero!
Hey!
Nice shot, Heero!
Amazing Duo! Great job...
way to go, Heero!
Hey! Wave back or something!
They're cheering for us,
superstar!
So this is where you went.
You know, that's pretty smart.
Changing schools when
you've gotta move on.
And after all, it's natural for
people our age to be in school.
What's the idea?
I'm just trying to act normal.
You stand out.
You wouldn't be as suspicious...
...if you acted natural instead
of being so secretive.
Why don't you just
chill out a bit
and have fun as a student?
Leave me alone.
And stay outta your way, right?
Hmm?
The two of us are going after
the same thing, here.
You can't hide it from me.
I can see it in your eyes
as plain as day, pal.
What do you say the first one to
destroy that ship wins?
Hey, that's...
Relena...
I've found you, Heero.
Heero. I wanted to see you.
Well, she's not you're average
chick, wanting to
see the guy trying to kill her.
Hm...
Three mobile suit carriers,
seven escort planes
heading this way!
All OZ troops!
What's going on?!
What are the OZ troops
trying to pull here?!
The suits have been released!
Keep the assault centralized.
We just need to take over
the main facilities.
Following coup d'Ètat by OZ's
...the Earth Sphere
Alliance Military...
...enters a state of confusion.
Alliance Military
soldiers remain
confined in their
respective bases...
...without an understanding of
what in fact is happening.
The United Earth Sphere Alliance
was initially formed...
...to handle disputes
between the countries.
However, with its expansion in
military power, the Alliance...
...soon took over governments
with militaristic control.
OZ was now planning to
free the many countries...
...that were forced into the
Alliance in this manner.
However, the increase in the
Alliance's military power...
...was a direct result of the
mobile suits provided by OZ.
As such, there were
many countries
that questioned OZ's
activities...
...noting that after
the coup d'Ètat,
military control would continue
and conditions would
remain the same.
Except now, ruler would be OZ.
[OS:] All mobile suits have
left the carriers.
Then I'll leave as well.
I'll be backing you up.
Concentrate only on achieving
your mission, Lieutenant Zechs.
I'm totally focused, Noin.
We'll lure away
ground troops away,
but a few will probably be
flying toward you.
Don't worry, if our data's
right, I should
be able to outrun them.
Good luck!
The mobility of this heavy suit
depends on the vernier output.
It's going to be tough...
This is going to take
a lot of effort.
But I can't falter now with
the Sanc Kingdom right in
front of my eyes!
Take over the runway on
the east side!
This speed is deadly!
I could get away by
increasing the output.
Then why?
Why am I hesitating?
Transmission from OZ, Sir!
What?!
Disarm your weapons
and surrender!
We have no wish to
continue this battle!
You're the ones that attacked,
so you should be the ones
who are retreating!
Standby to fire laser canons!
Sir!
Headquarters didn't
mention those lasers!
Retreat!
Damned lasers!
Noin, order all
units to withdraw
from here at once.
I had no idea they had this
much firepower...
...but we're still in the fight!
No.
We should leave the battle
for now and regroup.
Everyone withdraw to where
we landed the carriers.
Yes, sir!
Why am I acting like
such a coward?
I could defeat them with
this Tallgeese.
I could ignore the lasers and
destroy their headquarters!
Lieutenant!
I've mastered
numerous mobile suits
in the past, so why? What
am I afraid of?!
I'll die if I keep going.
This mobile suit is capable of
defeating any enemy it faces!
But it does have one weak point;
the pilot is a human being!
Is this the end?
Lady, won't you join me?
Mr. Treize, what would you
suggest for our next target?
Let's just continue
fighting and winning.
Shall I interprete that as
meaning we should conquer
the Earth Sphere?
That would be plenty.
OZ would then be hated.
It'd become a target
for the entire world.
What are you saying?
Those that are hated must
remain strong.
It'd be the perfect
motivation for OZ.
Master Quatre, if anything were
to happen to you...
...how would we
possibly explain it...
to your father in the colonies?!
Don't you have confidence at
all in us, Master?
No, it's nothing like
that at all.
Our sole purpose is to
protect you, Sir.
Do you understand this?!
Master Quatre!!
Y‐Yeah.
Right, that's enough.
But Captain Rashid, we're
just trying to...
Master Quatre has given us his
word that he won't leave on
his own any more.
Yeah, I promise.
Go on, there's no time
to stand around.
Load up the weapons on
your mobile suits or something.
Thanks, Rashid.
I'm upset with you myself;
don't forget it.
R‐Right.
So how was it?
There were five suits in all.
I'm pretty sure they're all
called Gundams.
They're all Gundams?
They're violent and dangerous
but they're all
really nice guys.
How can you be sure of that,
Master?
I can tell.
The soul of outer space
tells me.
The soul of outer space...?
The soul of outer space...
Gee, you two!
You call that fun,
just sitting like that?
You haven't said a word
for two hours.
What do you want?
Nice greeting.
And here I thought I'd be doing
you a favor bringing this.
Eat it right up before
it gets cold.
I'll just leave it here
so you guys help yourselves.
And clean the dishes after
you're finished.
Gotta learn your manners while
you're still young, right?
Bye!
I guess quiet people
attract quiet friends.
This might not be the best java.
I've got no right
piloting the Nataku.
Oh yeah?
Thank you.
You're recovering nicely from
a heart attack...
...but there are numerous
signs of irregularity
in the circulatory system.
You mean I should just be
glad to be alive.
Zechs, what in the
world happened?
I really underestimated
the Tallgeese.
It completely ignores the
commands of the pilot.
It has an audacious design...
...that far exceeds today's
most advanced equipment.
It ignores the pilot?
It takes into consideration
all types of battle patterns...
...and makes it possible for the
one suit to achieve
victory on its own.
At least that's how I found it.
But I've become such a coward.
The more I try to utilize the
abilities of the
mobile suit's ...
...the more I start doubting
my own abilities.
I start asking myself, "is that
all you're capable of doing?"
Rather than a suit for battle,
you could say it's a
suit for dueling.
It takes a brave pilot to bring
out its true potential.
A brave pilot?
Brave enough to risk
death for victory.
I still have a long way my own
fears are putting me in
the hospital.
Now, I've got to get back to
the Sanc Kingdom.
You rest! Any normal person
would've been dead by now.
I'm leaving, but you have to
stay here and get some rest.
But I have to go.
Okay, but not on the Tallgeese.
Noin!
The Tallgeese is
essential to victory.
I'm positive its design is the
same as the Gundams.
It is?
As I told you, I believe the
Gundams inherited...
...the reckless design of
the Tallgeese.
The origin of all mobile suits.
That's why it's crucial for me
to successfully pilot
the Tallgeese...
...in order to be able to
defeat the Gundams.
Tallgeese is for
suicide missions.
Now I understand what the
Gundams are up to.
They're searching for a place
suitable for their own deaths.
I know it's very difficult for
you to lie still...
...with the Sanc Kingdom close
by, but you must do as I say.
We'll attack tomorrow evening.
Sir! Tomorrow evening!
What's the matter?!
The Tallgeese has taken off!
By who?!
What's gotten into you, Otto?!
Return immediately!
This Tallgeese should be
able to take over...
...the headquarters of
the Sanc Kingdom!
I should know; I
understand its strength!
Stop now! You'll die!
I'd be honored to sacrifice my
life for you, Zechs.
Please allow me to assist in
fulfilling your dreams, Sir!
I want to do this for your sake
Lieutenant Zechs and not for OZ!
Otto...
I will attain victory in
return for my life!
You're not making sense Otto!
Return at once! Otto!
I've come all the way here just
to chase after a guy.
Are you surprised, Father?
But I couldn't help myself; I
wanted to see him so badly.
Can you understand how I feel,
Father?
Heero's is the support I
need to have around
...until I can get over my
sadness over you.
But he keeps running
away from me...
Heero?!
All right! Looks like I
got here first!
What took you, Heero?!
Don't worry, I left
you some action!
I can't see a thing!
Mission complete.
Out of my way! I can't
withstand much more!
Hurry up!
Yes, sir!
If only I'd been able to
pilot the Tallgeese...
...this would have
never happened!
The new type of mobile suit is
approaching fast!
Direct all laser canons
at that suit!
LONG LIVE KING ZECHS!
Otto...
It took me 13 years to return
to these grounds.
Father, forgive your son.
There's been much bloodshed
along the way...
...and I've only been able to
live a lifestyle...
...that counters your teachings
based on the principles of
total pacificm.
My hands are too
stained with blood.
I'm completely unfit to lead the
Peacecraft monarchy.
But I'm sure she would be able
to lead the country...
...in the manner you'd intended.
I'll fight to make that happen.
I've failed you.
Please forgive me.
I hear it was attacked!?
Heero!
Hey, good looking!
Pretty nice day today, huh.
Well, gotta get to class.
I'll see you later.
Let me stay by you a
little longer.
I wanna be stronger,
just like you.
[To be continued]
[MUSIC]
[Narrator:] Battles that risk
lives only produce mistakes...
...then what meaning does
Otto's death have?
Lady Une announces a plan to
transport Taurus, the space
mobile suit,
to the
Siberian Base.
However, this is in fact a
pretense to wipe out
the Gundams.
In his battle with Zechs, Heero
makes a final decision.
Next on Gundam Wing Episode 10:
"Heero, Distracted by Defeat"