[MUSIC]
[Narrator:] The attacks by
the five Gundams...
...sent out by the Space
Colonies reflected
their retaliatory intentions.
The Gundam's target is OZ, who
had masked its identity
within the mobile suit troops of
the Alliance military.
The Gundams' had a number of
missions to attack OZ.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken
center stage.
With an army of elite soldiers
at his command...
...Treize Khushrenada carries
out his plans to destroy the
Alliance Military.
The battle between the mobile
suits sent to earth and OZ
causes the Earth to
shutter violently.
[Narrator:] The Treize
Assassination
Explosive devices with
infrared sensors.
That won't stop me! I'm
going after Treize!
[EXPLOSIONS]
Treize Khushrenada was using us
like a bunch of puppets.
We totally screwed up this
entire mission.
[GROWLING]
Let's go after Treize! We can
still catch up with him!
That's not wise!
Stay outta my way, you want
me to shoot you?!
Our missions have always focused
on attacking when they
least expect it.
But now the enemy clearly has
the advantage right now.
Yeah I see what your saying,
kid.
So we didn't get them all!
Either way, Let's get
out of here!
Right!
Hey kid! Look out!
You'll get shot!
(huh?)
Don't just stand there!
[SIRENS]
I ordered Lieutenant Zechs
to take control...
of the Luxembourg
Headquarters...
...where they continue
to retaliate.
Good. He should be able to get
things under control.
How are we going to handle those
Gundams at New Edwards base?
I'll leave that up to you.
Sir!
This base is completely
under our control.
Request permission to head
for New Edwards.
To New Edwards?
That won't be necessary.
All you need to do is to
activate the missile
self‐detonation devices...
... which are at New Edwards.
Self‐detonation devices?
[OS:] If I remember correctly
you can activate them
from where you are.
That's correct.
Then get to it!
That's over‐kill.
Demolishing an entire base just
to kill off a few mobile suits?
The Earth Sphere
Alliance Military
didn't even have the guts to do
something this simple.
What's all this commotion?!
There's an unusually
large number
of aircraft asking for
permission to land.
Probably the ones that escaped
from New Edwards!
This just doesn't make any
sense. It's far too chaotic to
be a mere Gundam attack.
Major Sally!
I've intercepted an OZ
transmission!
They're planing on activating
the missiles at the New
Edwards Base!
I don't believe it.
It appears that they're going to
destroy the Gundams along
with the base!
We must land this at once!
We should be able to make a
belly landing on the sand.
System locked on.
[OS:] Preparing to activate
detonation devices. All
personell leave the premises.
These babies should get rid
of those Gundams.
Stop!
You can't be serious!
Many of your colleagues and
injured officers are still
there on the premises.
I'm sure they'd be glad to
die with such honor.
You're out of your mind!
I think I'll take that as a
compliment, ex‐Alliance
Forces Major.
But how could you?!
Final safety device deactivated.
T minus 900 to detonation.
Major Sally, what are
you trying to do?
There's a lock on the system.
There's nothing more you
can do from here.
You can try if you'd like but it
won't make any difference.
There's only 10 minutes before
the base is wiped out!
There's one person out there we
couldn't be able to eliminate
even if we wanted to
get rid of him.
A Gundam?
A Gundam pilot I'm
interested in.
I was hoping I could
see him again.
Who would have thought
this would happen.
So how long do you expect us
to look after you?
Your friend's just gone a little
too much it seems!
Heero! I know you can hear me!
Listen to me, Heero!
Heero? So his name's Heero?
Detonation devices on the
base's large missiles
were activated a few
minutes ago!
OZ is planning to blow the
entire base apart
in order to kill you
Gundam pilots!
I've confirmed that.
Apparently there are 47
large missiles
situated at the New
Edwards Base...
...and if they were to
explode at once...
...it would instantly wipe out a
radius of about 300 kilometers!
I'm not sticking around! Let's
blow this place right now!
There's 10 minutes
before it blows up!
We can't possibly get a
way safely now!
You'd be able to cover that
distance in time.
But please, grant me my
one last wish!
Deactivate the missiles, Heero!
Hey Heero, you coward! How
can you leave us?
You're wrong! He isn't
trying to run away!
Missile base location confirmed.
Proceeding to enter base.
What's that guy
trying to prove?!
Roger that, Heero. I'm going to
stake my life on you!
A failed mission means death,
but my card hasn't come up yet!
[AUDIBLE STRUGGLE]
The detonation device has been
activated on the
largest missile;
the model 304.
It's set up so that Model
304's explosion...
...will trigger the explosion of
all the other missiles.
Hurry to the model 304
control room.
All right, they're in good
shape. I've secured
two carriers!
The runway will be
cleared in a minute!
Let's hope we're not
wasting our time.
Oh and could you get your hands
on one more carrier
and get it ready for departure?
Another one?!
Heero's gonna need one too. His
mobile suit's
probably low on fuel.
You're totally confident that
he's gonna succeed, aren't you?
Yes.
It's up to you now, go
for it Heero!
He's got a 10 percent chance of
success. But that guy can
do it for sure!
It's futile, the detonation
system hasn't stopped yet.
Major Sally! I still can't
believe anyone is capable of
stopping the explosion
at this base!
I understand. Who would ever
believe such a thing?
But I can believe it. I'm
proud of that kid.
I wanna brag that I knew Heero,
the person who prevented
the explosion.
Hm...mh.. Arrgh!
I gotta say you're quite the
guy, Heero ‐ way to go.
What a miserable mission.
I screwed up, I totally
screwed up!!!
Sir, I'm very sorry that I could
not eliminate the Gundams.
I'm surprised. That's
not like you.
How were you planning
to destroy them?
I attempted to activate the
self‐detonation devices...
...at the missles at the
New Edwards base.
And so?
The Gundams deactivated the
bombs and prevented
the explosion.
We were saved by the Gundams.
Hmm?
The Earth is a confined area. We
can't go around
thoughtlessly polluting it.
Human beings are weak and
vulnerable. Anybody is capable
of killing anyone.
But we mustn't abuse
this capability.
This time around we'll just have
to give our thanks to
the Gundams.
Oh and Lady Une, you must learn
more about the OZ organization.
I'm sorry. I'll try harder.
Even after all this damage
there's still no sign
of surrendering.
Brigadier‐General Daigo
Onegell's such a tenacious man.
But I hope he's also a
hateful person.
Otherwise Zechs feelings
could be undermined.
How dare you!
Were you expecting the Alliance
Headquarters to fall
that easily?
I'm not letting OZ come one step
closer to this base!
I agree that security at this
base is splendid.
But if there were even a brief
moment of carelessness
among your people...
...this base would be taken
over immediately.
Lieutenant Zechs Marquise!!
So you did know it was me
afterall. You were extremely
cautious around...
...me during the
Alliance days...
...so I thought you could tell
me apart from all the
other people.
It was the era we were in. The
war made me do those things!
It wasn't my personal desire,
but the Alliance's
decision as a whole...
...to annihilate the
Sanc Kingdom.
The Sanc Kingdom had no
intention of resisting
against the Alliance.
But you staged an attack and
destroyed the Kingdom anyway.
When at the time many countries
opposed the expanding
military powers...
...of the United Earth
Sphere Alliance.
The Sanc Kingdom was only one
of those opposed.
You declared that you could
eliminate the cause of
the retaliation...
...by sweeping away the Royal
family since it had an influence
on the neighboring countries.
You personally lead the attack!
Milliard Peacecraft
May you rest in peace the
betrayed and outraged
Milliard Peacecraft.
Learn about OZ...
Is it possible that I don't
understand Mr. Treize?
That just couldn't be.
Captain. Two carriers from the
505 support troops
are trying to establish
contact with us.
What type of carriers?
Aries, from our own forces.
Contact approved.
This is Big Nose; please
begin communication!
Hold on, just which base did
those carriers come from?
From the New Edwards base.
You fools! Those are enemies!
The other carrier's headed for
this Mother Ship!
Then shoot it down!
[GUNFIRE]
I'm starting to run out of fuel.
This carrier wouldn't cause too
much of an explosion.
So I'm going to have to exit
on the mobile suit.
[EXPLOSIONS]
It's a Gundam! A Gundam
is on the ship!
What?! On the ship?!
Fight him with the Leos!
Twenty Leos have been destroyed!
What is your problem?! Throw him
into the sea and get him
with the Cancer!
Where is Mr. Treize's ship?!
It sailed away from the
rest of the fleet!
Good!
Must be this one!
It's a Gundam! This one came out
of the carrier that went down!
It... what?!
The Gundam on the ship has
destroyed the bridge!
70% of our Leos have
been destroyed!
Can't we use the Aries?!
No Sir, all of our elevators
will be targeted!
Why now; on this happy day of
our new beginning!
Lieutenant Colonel Lady Une!
Gundam's still
attacking on the ship!
I told you already, throw him
into the sea!! There's no need
to inform me of his every move,
you just follow my orders!
Right... Yes, ma'am!
Gundam's on the takeoff
catapult line!
Good! Get a Leo on the catapult
and shoot that Gundam
into the sea!
How are preparations?
Complete!
With this advanced mobility
option, it should move
like an Aries!
Just as long as I can shoot down
that other Gundam!
And that Gundam's attacking Mr.
Treize's ship?! Well, not
for much longer!
Destination reached! Here I go,
Nataku!
Don't be so sure of yourself,
Gundam!
You're not getting one step
closer to that ship!
Nobody can stop me, even you.
I wasn't expecting this much
resistance, but it's
game‐over now!!
You die!!
Stupid move, getting emotional.
Step aside! You can see for
yourself that you'll
never beat me.
I never knew Gundams were so
powerful. I want him dead.
[FOG HORN]
Huh? Mr. Treize!
Looks like your superior wants
to fight with me!
Fine by me!
I'll stop him in his tracks!
Mr. Treize, it's dangerous!
Get away from here!
Lady Une...
...Leave him to me.
But Mr. Treize...
So you're Treize. You
better be my guy.
I'll gladly accept.
My name is Wu Fei!
I'm Treize Khushrenada.
The duel is mine.
Kill me!
It was a good fight.
If you don't kill me right now
I'll keep on coming back until
I get you, Treize.
That sounds interesting.
I hope we can battle again.
Arrrgh!
Mr. Treize, how can you let that
Gundam pilot make his escape?
He's the pilot of one of those
mobile suits therefor I thought
it'd be fair for me to give
him another chance.
It was honorable of him to get
off the mobile suit and
duel with me.
I respect that in him and I can
see why he makes such a
good Gundam pilot!
Next time we'll have to fight
using his specialty:
the mobile suits.
But Mr. Treize...
Did that guy actually
accomplish his mission?
Hey you, can you hear me?!
I understand. Let's
just drop it.
[To be continued]
[Narrator:] The United Earth
Sphere Alliance collapses...
...and the world heads down
a path to chaos.
With all their might, Heero and
Duo must continue to
battle OZ...
...the reason behind this chaos.
While this is happening, Zechs
heads for the Sanc Kingdom
with his Tallgeese...
...to reclaim the home town
of the Peacecrafts.
But Tallgeese is an
extremely dangerous suit.
Next, on Gundam Wing episode 9:
"Portrait Of A Ruined Country"