[OPENING THEME]
Zero System, the name given to a
cockpit system that quickly
calculates battle data
and feeds the large amounts of
statistics on estimated values
directly back to the pilot.
But this system also drives a
pilot to his limits,
to the extent that he won’t even
fear his own death, thus
helping him gain absolute
victory. The year is
After Colony 195.
As the world constantly changes
in the chaotic era, there
are two mobile suits
that could turn humans into the
ultimate weapon. The Wing Zero,
and the Epyon.
The Return of Wu Fei
[RAINFALL]
[CATHERINE:] Trowa? Is
that you Trowa?
It’s me Trowa, Catherine! You
haven’t forgotten me, have you?
Catherine?
Oh Trowa...
BRAVO: This is Bravo, I’m about
to enter! ‐ [SOLDIER:] Roger.
That’s enough!
Wu Fei...
Ah, Master Long. You’ve provided
me with a place to train. I’ve
been very grateful.
Don’t mention it. You’ve done
well to improve as
much as you have.
And I’m positive that Altron
will happily welcome you too.
The new Nataku is very strong,
but I don’t think I’ve acquired
the necessary skills
to handle it’s strength.
One’s strength is in the mind.
And one’s mind is a
battle with oneself.
Unless you can win against
yourself Wu Fei, you will never
be able to defeat your enemy.
For over 100 years we have
fought the evils of outer space,
but even this colony, which has
protected us for all that time,
no longer has the
strength to endure.
It’s been leading us on a path,
headed for destruction. Even so,
we will
follow our destiny and see that
we live with integrity. Do you
understand, Wu Fei?
[WU FEI:] Integrity?
Believing in yourself. Not lying
to yourself. And also never
betraying yourself.
[MAN:] Master Long!
[WHISPERS]
[LONG:] What?
There’s no mercy for those
being destroyed.
Master Long, I must conquer and
defeat my enemy! The enemy I am
fighting is pure evil!
Then there is no need to waver!
It isn’t evil you’re defeating.
The ones that you defeated are
the epitome of evil.
Think about your integrity. That
is our determination,
and it's also
the determination of Altron.
[BRAVO:] We know you’re here 05.
Huh?
It’s there!
Is it the Gundam?
[BRAVO:] We’ve lured him out,
proceed to stage 2 of our plan!
Say bye bye 05!
[WU FEI:] Nataku. Guide me in
the correct direction.
[PILOT:] We’re in position
to attack 0200!
[SHUTTLE PILOT:] 05
is on it's way!
[SHUTTLE PILOT:] This is a
warning to the Gundam Pilot,
surrender at once!
[SHUTTLE PILOT:] We’re prepared
to attack 0200! Should you
continue to retaliate,
you risk involving the
entire colony.
Goodbye dear Wu Fei. see the
last of our clan go. Witness
it for yourself.
Is everything set?
Yes, we’re all ready.
[LONG:] Our clan will live with
pride, right until the end.
Wu Fei will succeed
us from now on.
Do it.
Yes.
[SOLDIER:] What??
Ah! Master Long!
Wu Fei! Don’t waver! The moment
you do, you’ll give rise to
yet another battle.
Please, continue fighting.
MASTER LONG!!!
[LONG:] Keep fighting Wu Fei,
for your own sense of integrity!
[WU FEI:] No. NO. NOOOO!!!
It is up to me. I’ll decide
what integrity is.
[HOWARD:] It appears that there
was a significant battle
in the L5 colony.
Wu Fei might have
something to do with it.
The pilot of 05 I recall.
Right.
Our force consists of this ship
and the Wing Zero. That’s
not nearly enough
to confront the Romefeller
foundation. Couldn’t we invite
Wu Fei to join us as an ally?
That’d be difficult. The Gundam
pilots have the courage and guts
to fight on their own.
Who knows if he’ll help someone
like you who’s
fighting for a cause.
But we are fighting the same
enemy! I just want a
chance to talk.
Alright then. Alter course
to the L5 colony.
[DERMAIL:] Thanks to the success
of operation Nova,
practically all of the world
is under Romefeller’s control.
We will therefore
discontinue Operation Nova.
[DERMAIL:] Tubarov, I would like
you to personally take charge
of our next plan.
[TUBAROV:] The next plan sir?
We have a responsibility to
maintain peace.
In order to do this we need
overwhelming power.
The mobile dolls should
more than suffice.
[DERMAIL:] The mobile dolls are
of use only when employed in
limited battles.
Right now we need something that
will give us results on a
much larger scale.
Chief Engineer Tubarov,
you will head the construction
of a Peacemillion caliber
space battleship.
A space battleship?
I’ll be on my way.
[NOIN:] Quatre, Sally Po's
information is reliable,
we can trust it.
Yes. I needed to keep a low
profile until now so I wouldn’t
cause the Maguanac
comrades more trouble.
But the situation's not
the same anymore.
Romefeller has destroyed most of
the Treize Faction.
So power has drastically shifted
in Romefeller’s favor.
The Sanc Kingdom is like a
candle flickering in the wind.
Yes! That’s why I have to get
Sandrock back, and help protect
this nation from the evil.
[PILOT:] This is a warning. You
are entering a war zone.
Detour to point URW.
If you do not follow orders
then we'll open fire.
Open fire without even
guiding me out of here?
We’ll commence attack!
[EXPLOSION]
[QUATRE:] Wait for me, my dear
Sandrock. I’ll be there shortly.
It’s true that we used to be
part of the
Romefeller foundation.
But now the Romefeller
foundation does nothing but
squeeze war funds out of us.
We can’t take this much longer.
All the Romefeller foundation
does is satisfy their
desire to rule!
They've intensified battles!
They’re no different than
the former alliance.
[RELENA:] Trust me, I fully
understand what
you’re all saying.
And doesn't this prove
my point that
true peace cannot be obtained
through military force?
I believe it does.
Princess Relena, we need your
guidance now, lead us on to the
right path to peace.
My influence is extremely
limited. However, if each one of
you truly wishes for peace
I believe it’s possible to
have the Romefeller
foundation terminate their
military activities.
[APPLAUSE]
[PAGAN:] The foreign delegates
have left safely. They all
seemed quite satisfied!
Pagan. do you think I was out of
line, promising peace to
the other nations?
Considering what a hard time I’m
having maintaining peace here
in the Sanc Kingdom.
Miss Relena, the kind of peace
promoted by Romefeller is just
an empty promise.
[PAGAN:] The pacifism upheld by
the Peacecrafts is peace in
it’s truest form.
And it’s what the other
nations are relying on.
But the military force of
Romefeller is so powerful!
Ever since Treize Khushrenada
lost his position in
the organization,
Romefeller has had no unifying
force. Their chief
representative, Duke Dermail,
is unlikely to
fulfill that role.
[PAGAN:] There's nothing to fear
with the present Romefeller.
Have more confidence
in yourself,
and make your ideal
world a reality.
[SOLDIER:] Welcome back from
your escort duties
Lietenant Noin!
I’m no longer a lieutenant. I’m
an imperial guard, just
like each of you.
But it's hard to break old
habits from our days in
Oz’s Treize faction,
if you know what I
mean Miss Noin.
Will you at least allow us
soldiers to call you
Captain Noin?
That's okay if it makes you
all feel better.
But we're not a military
organization bogged down
with discipline.
Just don’t forget that. ‐Ma'am!
[HEERO:] Captain Noin.
What is it Heero?
An increase in this nation's
military power will attract
Romefeller’s attention.
Why have you taken them in?
That issue huh? Follow me and
I’ll show you why.
[NOIN:] The main forces of the
Romefeller Foundation
are currently gathering around
the Sanc Kingdom.
After the Luxembourg plan to
destroy the Treize Faction,
their remaining military force
from that battle has been
standing by to invade
the Sanc Kingdom.
Which suggests that right from
the very beginning,
Romefeller had no intention
whatsoever of overlooking us.
[HEERO:] Hmm.
[NOIN:] At this rate we'll end
up suffering the fate of the
previous Sanc Kingdom.
It may not be a significant
force yet, but in order
to confront the
Romefeller Foundation,
we need to take in past members
of the Treize faction and
the former alliance.
Does all this answer your
question, I wonder?
Aren't you a bit laid back? This
military power could start
attacking us almost any day now.
But having a Gundam on our side
is like a symbol of hope for us.
Don't count on that too much.
Unlike Quatre I don't see much
sense in protecting
this country.
But the right honorable
Treize's Gundam
that you brought here has guided
many soldiers to us!
[NOIN:] It’s a symbol of
opposition towards Romefeller.
[HEERO:] Treize. What’s the big
idea, giving me this thing?
I hate fighting mobile dolls.
Doesn’t anyone want to
fight me directly!?
[PILOT:] The Taurus mobile
dolls are destroyed!
[CAPTAIN:] That leaves no
choice. Retreat at once!
People degenerate using machines
instead of risking
their own lives.
This may be the perfect time
for us to defeat Oz.
[ZECHS:] Gundam 05! This is
Zechs Marquise! Calling from
the Peacemillion.
That’s Wing Zero!
[ZECHS:] I’d like to
discuss an offer.
AHHHH!!
Hang on! I am not your enemy,
kid!
All evil that chooses to fight
in outer space is my enemy!
I agree kid, that’s why you and
I must fight together
against Oz and the
Romefeller foundation.
[WU FEI:] You’re a member
of Oz yourself!
[ZECHS:] In the past I was!
But no longer!
[WU FEI:] I don’t
trust traitors!
[ZECHS:] How can I get you
to LISTEN to me?!
By defeating me.
That’s fine.
Just the position that any
Gundam pilot would take.
[BOTH SCREAM]
This Gundam 05 has become
considerably stronger!
I need to come out on top this
time, I must win!
Peacemillion, NO!!!
[ZECHS:] It's... unharmed.
What??
What? What in the world are
these images here?
[ZECHS:] My enemy... No!
He’s not.
The boy is not the enemy I
should be fighting.
You can’t fool me. You are evil!
Zechs no!
Hey Zechs, get a grip, the Zero
System is messing
with your head!
No mistake about it, this man
will be an enemy to me.
[HOWARD:] This system displays
numerous sets of data
to do away with a
warrior’s insecurities.
Such a system will only
lead to tragedy.
Because there’s nothing sadder
than a soul being toyed
with by a machine.
Telling Zechs to overcome this
now may be too harsh.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERS]
Get a move on. We'll be
leaving here tomorrow.
[CATHERINE:] Hey,
But you saw how happy we
made everyone?
Why did you suddenly make
this the last show?
They say that a Gundam showed up
not far from here.
A Gundam showed up?
[TROWA:] Hey Sis ‐Huh? What’s
the matter Trowa?
Umm... Where am I
supposed to put this?
Oh that! You don’t need to
worry about it,
I’ll put it away
myself later on.
But I‐
You have to listen to what your
sister says, okay?
Mhmm. If you say so.
[RINGMASTER:] As long as he's
around
you never know what
trouble we could find
ourselves in.
We have no choice but
to move on now.
You’re right. I pity him having
amnesia, but Trowa’s better
off this way I think.
Gundam. What’s that? I’m sure
I’ve heard of it
somewhere before.
Not again! I’m so cold!
[CATHERINE:] Trowa... you’re
safe here. I’ll never let you
get near a battlefield.
I’ll protect you no matter what.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] In space, Duo finds
Trowa, while on Earth,
the Romefeller Foundation moves
in to invade the Sanc Kingdom.
Reunited with the Maguanac Corp,
Quatre hurries back to the front
with his Sandrock.
To put an end to what she
considers a foolish battle,
Relena submits herself to
the Foundation.
Next on Gundam Wing Episode 36:
Sanc Kingdom's Collapse.