[THEME MUSIC]
What's this?
Are...are you telling
me to get off?
Thank you Sandrock!
I thank you, my dear Sandrock.
[NARRATOR: Tallgeese Destroyed]
[OZ SOLDIER:] We've
confirmed the engineers' identity.
[LADY UNE:] All five of them?
[OZ SOLDIER:] Yes, ma'am.
As suspected, they
were all involved
in developing OZ mobile
suits in the past.
[LADY UNE:] Is that right?
[OZ SOLDIER:] All five of them
disappeared during the
development of the Tallgeese.
Or more accurately,
since completion of the Tallgeese
blueprint,
and have been missing
since.
[LADY UNE:] Tallgeese?
Isn't that the mobile suit
Colonel Zechs is using that’s
also called the Leo Prototype?
[OZ SOLDIER:] Yes, it
was built twenty years ago.
But it's still regarded as the
most powerful mobile suit on
Earth.
Most powerful is hardly the
appropriate term, now is it?
[OZ SOLDIER:] Ma'am?
It wouldn't be the most powerful
unless all soldiers described it
as such.
We'll have them make us a suit.
A mobile suit that's more
powerful than the Tallgeese.
No, more powerful
than the Gundams!
Captain, sir, I’ve brought Colonel
Zechs here to see you, sir.
[OZ CAPTAIN:]
Thank you.
You’ll have to excuse
the small room.
Please, have a seat.
[OZ CAPTAIN:] You don't
need that for Colonel Zechs.
[SOLDIERS IN UNISON:] Huh?
You're dismissed.
[KHUSHRENADA:] Sorry to
make you uncomfortable, Zechs.
Don't concern yourself,
Your Excellency.
I am prepared to face a
court martial.
[KHUSHRENADA:] As long
as you continue
to be a strong force
for the Romefeller Foundation,
I see no problems with
the court martial.
[ZECHS:] A strong force?
Right now, the Romefeller
Foundation
is concerned about the Gundams:
the most powerful mobile
suits on Earth.
Would you continue to
fight as our knight
to defeat the Gundams,
Colonel Zechs?
[ZECHS:] Your Excellency.
I'm sorry to say this,
but I don't believe I can follow
the
Romefeller Foundation’s ideas any
longer.
[KHUSHRENADA:] What?
[ZECHS:] I've been
fighting the Gundams
out of personal feelings.
And that's something
which has no place in a war.
My battle with the
Gundams is over.
[KHUSHRENADA:] I see.
In that case, Zechs,
sacrifice your life for OZ.
[KHUSHRENADA:] A guilty
verdict in court
for your conduct would be a
big blow to OZ.
But if you died an
honorable death during battle,
many soldiers would
mourn your death
and develop a stronger
will to fight.
Naturally, the higher powers
in the Romefeller Foundation
will also be satisfied with this.
The name Lightning Count will
live on as a legendary hero.
That'd be wonderful.
[KHUSHRENADA:] Your death
would have that much value to it.
If you died, you'd be free.
Farewell, Zechs Merquise.
Once everyone has left this ship,
fifty Aries and twenty Cancers
are scheduled to attack it.
[OZ CAPTAIN:] They'll be manned
by Alliance survivors trying to
win the Foundation's attention.
I heard this mission is
to allow you to escape
unnoticed by the higher powers.
But given the enemy and
the sheer numbers,
there's no room for escape.
[ZECHS:] That's right.
This is a test in order to
survive as Treize's friend.
No matter what I do,
I’m not able to escape from
what he has planned for me.
[TUBAROV:] Commence simulation!
[DERMAIL:] So this is the
mobile doll system.
We used an old model of the Leo.
So we’re having to program
them from a distance.
But no such problem exists
with our Taurus space mobile doll.
Wonderful abilities.
These would reinforce our
soldiers,
would they not, Chief Engineer?
In fact, they'll replace soldiers
as the main force in the future.
[DERMAIL:] What's that?
[OZ SOLDIER:] Someone's
attacking us!
But they're not responding!
Order to attack!
It’s the perfect target for
the mobile dolls.
Enemy spy. How foolish!
Sir, transmission from
the enemy Leo!
[OZ SOLDIER:] It’s Colonel Treize!
[TUBAROV:] What?!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Discontinue attack!
Stop firing!
I thought I would
represent human soldiers
and come here to propose
a battle against the mobile dolls.
[TUBAROV:] Are you trying to
kill yourself, Colonel Treize?
Mobile dolls show no mercy!
If mobile dolls are superior,
then there’s no place for
me in this world.
I think we could vie for
superiority here and now.
Here goes.
He's insane!
Never mind, attack the
Colonel and kill him!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Sir?
[TUBAROV:] That’s an order!
He's trying to kill us!
Go ahead! Get him!
[OZ SOLDIER:] No! I can't!
[TUBAROV:] Then I’ll do it myself!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Stop it,
Chief Engineer!
[TUBAROV:] Silence!
This is Treize Khushrenada.
Murder Tubarov!
Sir!
[TUBAROV:] What the hell?
No, please stop this!
[OZ SOLDIER:] I'm assassinating
you
under the orders of Colonel
Treize!
It's over.
Chief Engineer Tubarov.
There’s a lot more to wars than
simply fighting with mobile suits.
[KHUSHRENADA:] We claim victory.
I retract my order.
Mobile dolls and soldiers both
take their orders from humans.
I ask that you place more
value on humans
and learn to love them, Tubarov.
[KHUSHRENADA:] Hurry up and
return to me, Zechs.
Because if you're not
around to help,
OZ will allow worthless
actions by worthless people.
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER:] The shuttle
that
avoided OZ's surveillance is
coming!
[ALLIANCE COMMANDER:]
Just as I thought.
This course isn't
frequented by OZ.
Then we can capture ourselves
a Gundam, isn’t that right sir?
More specifically, a Gundam pilot.
[ALLIANCE COMMANDER:]
The shuttle on its way here
isn't equipped for mobile
suit transport.
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER:] Then
what do you plan to achieve
by restraining the pilot?
I’m sure the reason the Gundam
pilot
has returned to outer space is to
fight OZ.
We're after the same enemies,
so I'll negotiate with the
pilot to join forces with us!
Wouldn’t it be a good idea
to hand the pilot over to OZ
in exchange for a
guarantee of our safety?
Vague negotiations are meaningless
with an organization that has
a record of always fighting dirty.
Our only chance is to
fight head on!
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER:] Five
objects approaching at high speed.
They’re believed to be
Taurus mobile suits.
[ALLIANCE COMMANDER:]
Five of them?
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER:] We have twenty
space Leos, we have the advantage!
[ALLIANCE COMMANDER:] I told you
not to underestimate OZ!
OZ already knows that no survivors
from the Alliance Space
Forces are hiding here!
They can defeat us, with
just five Tauruses!
We'll fight for the survival
of the Alliance.
Don't let them get their
hands on the Gundam pilot!
[NICHOL:] The Alliance mobile
suits are being deployed, but why?
[OZ SOLDIER:] Flying object is
approaching the retreating troops!
What?
Is it the Gundam?
[NICHOL:] Did these guys find
the Gundams after they left Earth?
[OZ SOLDIER:] All the enemy
suits headed here
are Leos for normal space battle!
[NICHOL:] Roger.
Provide the mobile dolls
with all target information.
Take over from here.
[NICHOL:] I'm going
after the shuttle!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Yes, sir!
[DOCTOR J:] So, now they can
utilize unmanned mobile suits.
[PROFESSOR G:] They
probably saw them
as valid weapons since
outer space has no obstacles.
[DOCTOR J:] Battling people
without getting your hands dirty
is nothing but a game.
Foolish are those who start wars.
But the blood shed during
battle is never a waste.
[PROFESSOR G:] Foolish
people see the bloodshed
and learn to regret
their actions just a little.
But once war turns into a game
it becomes mere
entertainment to them.
[DOKTOR S:] Actually I wish
they'd just declare a winner
to this game.
So that way nobody
would have to die.
Assuming the opponent has
the technology.
We all have the technology!
But soldiers sense the
responsibilities of combat
if he doesn’t use
automated functions!
You've got the technology?
Looks like you guys could
earn yourselves
the right to live
longer after all.
[INSTRUCTOR H:] I can't do it.
I'd rather die than
construct such a thing.
[MASTER O:] Youngsters always
want to
think things out
rationally.
But war itself is
anything but rational.
[LADY UNE:] And here I was
going to give you the chance
to build a mobile suit superior to
the Tallgeese
and Gundams you
built.
Go ahead and kill us!
I have no intentions of
lending a hand
in an empty war drawn out
on a game board.
Negotiations are over.
Colonel.
Chief Officer Nichol
is on the line.
What is it, Nichol?
[NICHOL:] I’ve intercepted
the Alliance's transmission
and found out they’re planning
to team up with a Gundam pilot!
Those imbeciles, go ahead
and wipe out the lot of them!
[NICHOL:] Yes, ma 'am!
They're fast!
Five suits at once?
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER:]
The enemy mobile suit speed
has accelerated to 8G!
What kind of superhuman
could be piloting that?
[NICHOL:] Alliance main forces
have been demolished!
We'll move on to
seize the shuttle!
[LADY UNE:] Seize?
What's the point of that?
We’ve got no need a Gundam pilot
without his Gundam.
Get rid of
him!
[NICHOL:] Roger!
Wait!
Hand me the communication system.
Okay, sure.
[QUATRE:] This is Quatre.
My good friends who have
returned to outer space.
Together, let us do our very best
to protect the space colonies.
[DOCTOR J:] He's using
Heero's frequency.
He's an outstanding soldier.
He has the ability to bring the
five Gundam pilots together.
This is Quatre. Quatre speaking.
My good friends who have
returned to outer space.
Together, let's do our very
best to protect the colonies.
Tell them to stop firing
at the shuttle!
[LADY UNE:] Well, well.
So you did have the heart
to pity your men.
Then I guess we have an
understanding now.
Who'd have thought we'd end up
having to make a Gundam for OZ?
Not exactly.
I am telling you to make a mobile
suit better than the Gundams.
He's just a kid!
[ALLIANCE COMMANDER:]
This is a Gundam pilot?
But he's so young!
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER:] Captain!
All the Tauruses are
headed this way!
That's fast.
Engage them as far away
from the shuttle as possible!
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER:] Roger!
[ALLIANCE COMMANDER:] I'm not
gonna let you die.
[NICHOL:] We've caught up
with the shuttle!
[OZ COMMANDER:]
Stop your attack on the shuttle!
All Taurus units, move away
from the shuttle's route!
What was that?
Stop our attack?
Orders are to leave the
shuttle alone.
We're all free to roam
about in space.
But we must get rid of the
garbage we find along the routes.
Nichol.
Blow it up, of course.
Roger that, Colonel.
[NICHOL:] I’ll leave the
space Leos to you,
I’m heading after the shuttle!
[EXPLOSIONS]
Still no word from the shuttle.
So I’m gonna commence to
clean up the route!
[NICHOL:] What?
The shuttle just fired at a Leo!
[NICHOL:] There’s life
on the shuttle!
All suits, destroy the shuttle!
Fire!
Our forces alone don't
have the power
to retaliate against OZ right now.
But I'm sure that young
pilot is capable of doing it.
I certainly hope my
instincts prove to be right.
[EXPLOSION]
Come on everyone.
Together.
Let's protect outer space.
Your ride has arrived.
How did repairs on the
Tallgeese go, sir?
Thanks to your all your people's
help, everything's in order.
Thank you.
Captain!
[OZ SOLDIER:] The radar's
picking up objects
from point 0430 behind us!
[OZ CAPTAIN:] They're here.
Just in time!
Which means they're gonna
sink this ship.
I'm sorry.
Give it your best shot, sir.
I don't know what to think right
now,
but, Colonel: win this battle!
Thanks for your help.
Good‐bye.
Let's get going, huh Tallgeese?
[EXPLOSIONS]
Fifty Aries and twenty Cancers.
I'll just have to prove to them
that they seriously underestimated
the value of my life.
How many more?
Nice move!
But I'm not gonna die yet!
[ZECHS:] Treize, stop
following me around.
Or else I'll just want to
fulfill your radical hopes.
This friendship of the past
will only last until the
day my mask breaks.
And now, I cannot be your
friend any more.
[ZECHS:] Farewell, Treize.
[HEERO:] Earth.
The planet in the solar system
that miraculously
gave birth to
life.
In the year After Colony 195,
with the development of
the colonies,
people now live in new
surroundings.
Thanks to plentiful natural
resources
and cultivated technological
abilities.
However, this new world
is nothing but an imitation
of humankind's motherland,
the Earth.
But why were the colonies
made in the first place?
I hear the main purpose was
technological development
to improve the lives
of humankind on Earth.
Did humankind start
asking for too much
from this imitation world?
The self‐sustained way of life
is more stable than life on Earth,
especially since it lacks
the risk of natural disasters.
It appears that this
unlimited growth
was guaranteeing the eternal
existence of humankind.
Perhaps there was an age when
people
dreamed of the possibilities in
outer space,
where they could start
from scratch.
However, it's unthinkable
that the colonies
or that humankind will ever
forget the Earth.
What did technological development
in the colonies
bring to the
Earth?
The kind of technology the
Earth wants most: military power.
Destruction is a human nature
that can never be gotten rid of.
And now, the colonies are
developing
a militaristic
disposition.
The colonies cannot
forget the Earth.
The Earth has great beauty.
The animals known as humans
have acquired such strength
that they even think
about controlling this
planet for themselves.
From the point of view of
a planet’s life,
the life of a living thing lasts
no more than an instant.
But in the end, it is only
themselves
that humans can think
of.
Nothing changes.
The time spent by humans in outer
space has been a complete waste.
The ideal is just a dream.
This false pacifism.
This false living space.
Outer space is nothing but
a breeding ground
for even more battles
in the future.
Wars throughout history
have claimed many lives.
Although humankind hasn't
been able to forget the sorrow
that has been cause by the wars,
they have not stopped fighting.
The blood and tears they
shed are merely ceremonial.
One can't speak of history
without referring to the wars
in each era as important events.
I'm sure the pale pep talks of
fighting for peace
have been repeated
numerous times in the past.
The colonies say they need
armaments to maintain peace.
It's no different from on Earth.
The colonies think
they've joined the big boys.
I guess they believed the
bloodshed
would lead to higher morale—
Okay, that's enough Duo Maxwell.
Let's avoid that subject.
It's making your
classmates uncomfortable.
Personally, I don't feel it
was an appropriate subject
for your greeting speech.
Now, Duo, please take a
seat in the back.
[HEERO:] So why do
people fight anyway?
Perhaps meaning of human existence
lies within their will to fight.
People feel a sense of
accomplishment through battle.
And it's also a fact that
the ones actually fighting
are never perceived as
being tainted.
[ENDING MUSIC]
[NARRATOR:] There's no
glory or praise
for the Gundam pilots
returning to the colonies.
Only orders to destroy OZ.
The Gundam Deathscythe battles
the Tauruses in outer space.
But Duo is defeated
and taken prisoner by OZ.
In order to maintain
confidentiality,
Heero searches for
Duo to kill him.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 19
Assault on Barge