[OPENING THEME]
GUNDAM WING
[NARRATOR] Treize Khushrenada
assumes the position as the
World Nation's sovereign
and once again accumulates all
military armaments on land. In
space the White Fang
completes its gigantic space
battleship Libra. With his
desire to eliminate Earth
commander Milliardo Peacecraft
proceeds with his plans
to enter into a
fully fledged war with the
entire forces of the World
Nation led by Treize.
The Gundam pilots continue to
fight, not siding with anyone.
And right before
them the largest battle yet to
be experienced by humanity
is about to begin.
Make it fast. We're
expecting our enemy.
Our enemy? Who do you mean?
The most annoying and fearful
enemy in the universe:
The Gundams.
Go Forth Gundam Team
Go ahead Ms. Relena.
[ZECHS] The Earth only seems
beautiful because we
have the chance
to see it like this
from outer space.
Those on Earth can't possibly
appreciate its true beauty.
Are you suggesting all of
humanity should come up
to outer space?
Those who don't want to come
here certainly don't have to.
[ZECHS] I won't simply ignore
powers on Earth that are a
threat to peace here in space.
Surely that's no reason to
become the largest threat to
peace yourself though.
The time has come for Earth and
space to discard all
their weapons.
No. This isn't the time for your
world of total pacifism.
Therefore outer space must
direct all its force against the
people on the Earth.
Using the battleship Libra.
No! You're mistaken Milliardo.
How would you know?
I know that because I am
Relena Peacecraft.
My dear Relena...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
You've grown up strong Relena,
but your strength is no
longer needed.
I want you at least to
remain a kind woman.
In truth I don't even know
whether I'm being held in the
arms of Milliardo
the kind brother that
I once knew...
... or in the bloodstained hands
of Zechs Marquise.
If you want to return to the
Earth I'm not going to stop you.
If you want to stay in
space I'll find you a place to
live in a colony.
I'm staying right where I am.
Until you change your mind.
Do me a favor. Show Relena to
the officer's room Dorothy.
[DOROTHY] Right away.
Let's be on our way Ms. Relena.
It'd be wiser to continue
this discussion after
you've had some rest.
Perhaps you're right. Show
me the way then.
Sure.
Do you consider me a weak man,
Quinze?
[QUINZE] On the contrary if you
hadn't been looking out
for someone I
wouldn't have welcomed you as
the White Fang leader.
Thanks for saying so.
Now then how shall we proceed?
Destroy Libra. That simple.
But will that end
the war though?
No it won't. On Earth Treize is
getting ready to send a
military force to space.
The colonies will
retaliate against that.
But we can't just leave Libra. I
agree that we should destroy it.
Sure thing Duo. But can
we destroy it?
Are you saying we take on
Zechs as our enemy?
Are you saying that
guy's our ally?
I... well...
Heero! What's your opinion?
Zechs is our enemy. He feels the
same way about us.
[ALARM]
[MAN] Howard: Mobile suit
carriers approaching.
[MAN] It's a large fleet
from the White Fang.
There you have it. They've
beaten us to the punch.
[TROWA] Is Heavyarms ready?
‐Yeah it's all ready to go.
And Altron is too.
OK. Let's go!
Let's go Heero.
Sorry but Wing Zero won't be
joining this battle.
Huh? What's going on Heero?
Gotta take care of something.
Man just check out how
many there are.
It goes to show they're
afraid of us.
Hold on Wu Fei! There's a
separate unit!
[DUO] Above us! Leave the
other units to me.
There's another unit here as
well. I'll leave the
front ones to you.
Hang on. We're at a disadvantage
fighting this many separately.
Ugh! It's pointless trying to
tell these guys they always
fight alone. Huh?
[GUNFIRE]
Here goes! Ugh!
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
Strategic programs have been
loaded onto these mobile dolls.
[VULCAN GUNFIRE]
They're unlike anything
we've fought before.
[DUO YELLS]
[EXPLOSIONS]
The Gundams are struggling with
the enemy's tactics.
So the mobile dolls are
regarding the Gundams as
their main targets.
But we can't attack and
protect the Gundams.
Yeah I know that.
[HOWARD] Heero... what have you
got up your sleeve?
It's only natural that Zechs
would use his mobile
dolls strategically.
[GUNFIRE]
Miss Noin... can they control
the movements of the mobile
dolls this precisely?
No not usually. I can only
imagine that Zechs must have
developed some new system.
I won't be pushed around by you.
[VULCAN GUNFIRE]
[DUO] Trowa are you OK?
Yeah Duo. Almost there. One more
go. That should be enough.
[DUO] OK.
So tell me have you come up with
a good way to persuade Mr.
Milliardo.
I'm not persuading. I
must convince him.
It's impossible to convince him.
Because Mr. Milliardo is dead
serious about
destroying the Earth.
I just can't believe that my
brother's actually
thinking of initiating
another war though.
There will be another war. Just
as Mr. Treize predicted.
I won't let there be!
How will you stop it?
I'm not sure.
[DOROTHY] Use this!
It's the only way you'll be able
to stop Mr. Milliardo. You can
do it Ms. Relena.
If it means preventing a war
from starting...
No I could never do
something like that.
Because you can't shoot your own
brother? Or because it's against
your ideal of pacifism?
It must be because you're Relena
Peacecraft and you're unable
to take action being
constrained by your ideal world.
[RELENA] That isn't
true Dorothy.
I just don't believe that true
peace can be obtained
through assassination.
Oh. Then that leaves
me no choice.
[BEEP]
Dorothy?!
[RELENA] DOROTHY! OPEN THE DOOR!
Just stay in there until
everything is over Ms. Relena!
[RELENA] DOROTHY!
We've received information that
all mobile dolls sent
to Peacemillion
have been destroyed.
It makes no difference. I never
expected that we would
defeat them simply
by loading the
strategic program.
Then why did you send
out the units?
I have started a war of
attrition against them. Even the
Gundams and their pilots
have their limits do they not?
[ZECHS] But not the
mobile dolls.
You've got a point.
We will start the Libra as soon
as we are ready to go. We're
heading for the Earth.
Yes sir!
Damn! That was one
hard day of work.
[BREATHING]
Howard! Hey I'll need this
fueled up and repaired.
[HOWARD] Roger!
[GUNDAM ACTIVATING]
Yes I know that Zero. As it
stands we can't
possibly defeat Zechs.
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
Jeez they just kept coming after
us no matter how hard we
fought 'em off.
Fighting like that won't get us
anywhere. What we really
need now is a plan.
That's easier said than done.
Look we've already made it
really close to Libra
right? It's too late to
come up with a plan.
But surely there'll be a lot
more mobile dolls
guarding Libra.
They'll probably separate us
and then attack us.
[SALLY] You're right. And the
enemy will attack when
you're most worn out.
That just means we'll have to
crush Libra before
they get to us.
[QUATRE] No that won't work. We
don't stand a chance right now.
But what options do we have?
[HOWARD] No need to worry yet.
We have the people and
resources we need.
And the Gundams are
almost repaired.
Yeah, sure. Almost.
That's right. We're not
machines. If they keep
challenging us to these battles
we're eventually gonna fold.
Both the pilots and
the mechanics.
[HEERO] Could you install this?
But this is... no way!
Quatre can handle that.
I see. OK. I'll do it.
What do you think?
It's not bad at all. I'd like to
try it in real combat.
Do that. I'm going to have my
hands full fighting Wing
Zero with Epyon.
Commander Milliardo!
Peacemillion is heading
straight for us!
I'll face them now.
I've asked Howard to install the
Zero System in this
suit as well.
But how come?
It's a good system for leading
troops into battle. Try it out.
I can't Heero! I can't do it! I
just can't. No! Not the Zero!
I can't do it! I don't have what
it takes! Heero why don't you
lead us with Wing Zero?
Wing Zero will be fighting
Epyon. But someone has to lay
out a plan if we're
going to survive this.
[QUATRE] I know that.
Then you've gotta take command.
This is the way you can pay
back the people
[HEERO] ... in outer space. OK?
Heero...
The code's Zero. You have to
input the letters to
activate the Zero System.
Mobile dolls from Libra are
coming this way. You'd all
better head out.
But I... how will I?
Heero!
Epyon's coming. The
rest is up to you.
[DUO] We'll take good
care of 'em.
Hang on. From a strategic point
of view Heero has to
go fight Epyon.
But we need a strategic plan of
our own. [WU FEI] They're here!
Hey Wu Fei! Trowa!
[SOLDIER] The mobile doll troops
have encountered the enemy.
So this is how the mobile doll
command system taken from
Epyon operates.
Mr. Milliardo is a true genius.
This way even the soulless
mobile dolls are able to
fight with the mind of a human
being. Now my dear mobile
dolls let's see
a spectacular dance.
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
[EXPLOSIONS]
Heero...
[ZECHS] Let's get started.
I'm here.
[HEERO] I wanna know what you're
up to. Why are you
starting these battles?
[ZECHS] To end all battles.
[GUNFIRE]
Ugh!
Wu Fei! Move back here for now!
[DUO] Why should he? I'll go
and support him!
Duo!
[DUO] What?
Ugh!
[GUNFIRE]
We're not getting anywhere.
We've gotta get in some
kind of formation.
[DOROTHY] Now let's
change our plan.
We'll isolate each one of the
Gundams and destroy
them separately.
[ZECHS] I see you've
mastered the system.
And so have you!
[EXPLOSIONS]
Miss Noin!
[DUO] Miss Noin!
It's exactly the same. It's just
like the attack on the
Sanc Kingdom.
[QUATRE] This isn't working.
We're gonna get totaled.
[QUATRE] Wu Fei fly right
through the enemy troops.
The rest of us will direct fire
to where Wu Fei was.
Eh? Quatre?
[WU FEI YELLS]
What's this? They've come up
with a strategy!
The enemy's divided into a
number of units. Now's our
chance to defeat those
units one at a time. Trowa
attack the troops on the
upper right side.
Then destroy the front unit
Duo and Wu Fei.
[TROWA] Roger. [DUO] Gotcha.
[WU FEI] There's a good plan!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I can't let the
system control me.
There's no choice now but to
master the system.
[DOROTHY] I don't understand.
The Gundams are predicting
each of my moves!
How come? What's happening?
The movements of these mobile
dolls aren't just programmed.
Some one's changing their
tactics based on the actual
battle. Gotta predict them.
[DOROTHY] Who's doing this?
Who could it be?
Some one's controlling
these mobile dolls.
[DOROTHY] It must be...
Quatre Raberba Winner!!
[QUATRE] Dorothy Catalonia.
Use Libra's main cannon
and strike them!
What's going on? You've
gotta be kidding!
It's the only way to
stop the Gundams.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SOLDIER] What are they doing?
Please be careful! They're gonna
try and shoot down Peacemillion.
They're what?! [SALLY]
Move the ship!
This ship's massive it can't
move that quickly.
JUST DO IT!!
[SOLDIER] We can't avoid
its line of fire!
[SALLY] Increase the output of
engines 1 to 8 to their maximum!
But then we'd overload the
engines and they would explode!
That's better than
being shot down!
[HOWARD] We've got no options!
We're flying at a tremendous
speed and we don't
know how firing the cannons
will effect Libra!
Just fire. That's all we can do!
[ZECHS] What?! Dorothy!
Everyone get outta here!!
Libra's firing their
main weapon?!
[SOLDIER] Engine two on the
port side's exploded!
No!
[CANNON FIRING]
[SALLY PO] Did we dodge it?
[ALARM BEACON]
Main cannon system down.
[SOLDIER] Various damage to
spaceship structure.
This can't be happening. It
wasn't supposed to
happen like this.
Work on balance control. Each
section report damages.
[ZECHS] I must leave Heero.
[ZECHS] This was too much
responsibility for Dorothy.
Hey Zechs... according to Zero
you have no future.
Is Epyon telling you
differently?
[RELENA] I must put an end to
this meaningless battle...
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR] Hilde sneaks into
Libra and obtains valuable
data on the ship.
But mobile doll versions of the
Mercurius &amp; Vayeate chase after
Hilde as she escapes.
What's more the data on Heero &amp;
Trowa is programmed
into these dolls.
The White Fang prepares to
battle against Earth
while trying
to terminate the Gundams.
Next on Gundam Wing episode 45:
Signs of the Final Battle.