[OPENING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] Zero System. The
name given to a cockpit
system that quickly
calculates battle data and feeds
the large amounts of statistics
on estimated values directly
back to the pilot.
But, this system also drives a
pilot to his limits.
To the extent that he won't even
fear his own death.
Thus helping him gain
absolute victory.
The year is After Colony 195.
As the world constantly changes
in the chaotic era,
there are two mobile suits that
could turn humans into the
ultimate weapon.
The Wing Zero, and the Epyon.
Sanc Kingdom's Collapse
[REBEL:] Our enemy isn't Oz,
it's the Romefeller Foundation,
the ruling class on Earth.
But would you seriously consider
teaming up with the
Treize Faction?
Our first priority is to regain
control of outer space.
We'll need to take in soldiers
of the former alliance.
Absurd! There's no way we could
team up with them.
Unless those of us that consider
Romefeller an enemy all team up,
there's no way we can
break their control!
Maybe. What do you think, Duo?
Well, it's true that Romefeller
is an enemy to us,
the Treize Faction, and to
the former Alliance.
But still, it's just as
important to think about what
happens once we defeat him.
Talk to me again once you
figure that out.
Hey there! Duo!
[DUO:] Until then, I'll continue
fighting alone to
defeat Romefeller.
Hey! How did it go?
That meeting wasn't
going anywhere.
[LAUGHING CHILDREN]
Yeah, I wonder what true peace
really means anyway.
Huh?
I‐uh nothing. Just delete that!
Whoa, was that totally out of
character or what!?
Hey Duo, let's go somewhere
that's really fun!
Somewhere fun?
Yeah, let's go! Hurry, let's go!
[NOIN:] Oz's mobile doll troops
have moved to the boundaries
of the Sanc Kingdom.
and forces have been gathering
in the surrounding
military bases.
[NOIN:] It's unmistakable. Oz
is‐ no, Romefeller is planning
to destroy the Sanc Kingdom.
It's only a matter of time
before they attack.
Very well then. I want to
talk to Duke Dermail.
No wait, Romefeller now regards
the Sanc Kingdom as an enemy.
We have no choice but to fight
to save the Kingdom!
The Sanc Kingdom under the
Peacecraft rule has always
practiced the idea of pacifism.
We should advocate for
disarmament and aim for a
peaceful world where no
battles are fought. Therefore
we mustn't fight.
Sure, but you have to understand
the Sanc Kingdom is about
to be annihilated.
But still. I am going to do
everything I can to avoid a war.
[NOIN:] I can understand Miss
Relena's ideals however,
Romefeller's military is trying
to invade the country
Relena's too caught up in her
ideal world. ‐What's that
supposed to mean?
With things the way they are
around the world, it'd be
impossible to achieve
total pacifism.
So, you're disputing Miss
Relena's ideals? ‐I'm not.
Total pacifism is what people
are hoping for, and people can't
live without hope.
Tell me Heero, do you have any
hopes of your own?
I only want to fight against
those who try to conquer.
I wonder how Quatre's doing.
I hope he's able to come back
here as soon as possible.
[DISTANT EXPLOSION]
That sound means!!
Don't let up! Show them what the
Maguanac Corp is made of!
Dammit! Things sure look bad!
Auda! Take the third unit and
head to the left wing!
[AUDA:] Roger!
[GUNFIRE]
What's that??
[AUDA:] Master Quatre??
It's Quatre!!
He's finally returned!
Hey!
You came back! We have
something for you Master!
Yes, I know that! I came
back here to get it!
Alright, let's move in and
destroy them all at once men.
[SOLDIER:] Captain! The enemy is
starting to fight back sir.
Hey! Where'd that white
suit come from AHH‐
What happened!?
[SOLDIER:] Gundam 04??
Sandrock, let's do it!
[EXPLOSION]
I'm so glad you're safe
and sound Master.
Rashid, all of you, sorry I've
been such a pain, and thank you.
What exactly are you saying
Master? We'd like to thank you
for saving our lives.
So Master Quatre, are you in
need of the Gundam again now?
Yeah, something's come up that I
have to take care of soon.
[CIRCUS MUSIC]
Amazing! See, isn't this fun?
‐You said it!
[RINGMASTER:] Next, a
performance with the lion,
the
king of the animals, and
a young clown!
[LION ROARS]
Ah, watch out!
Excellent! I could fall for that
clown. ‐ Sure, whatever.
Huh?
It's him, Trowa!
[CATHERINE:] Great show Trowa!
[TROWA:] How did I do? ‐Great!
The crowd sure did love you.
That's good.
Hey Trowa, it is you! Trowa!
Hey! [CATHERINE:] ‐Hey,
excuse me!
So you were here! Where are the
others, how's Heero?
Isn't he with you??
Uh...
Trowa?
[CATHERINE:] Get out! ‐Huh?!
You must be an old acquaintance
from his past, but Trowa's not
going to be doing any
more fighting!
Trowa! What's gotten
into you anyway??
Get out of here! Just leave us.
Trowa...
[NARRATOR:] Meanwhile, Colonel
Tubarov was executing his plans
to construct a gigantic space
battleship, as ordered by the
Romefeller Foundation.
This project, commandeering the
manpower and resources
of outer space,
was becoming a significant
burden on the citizens
of the colonies.
We're progressing at an
aggressive pace, but given the
enormous size of the battleship,
it's still going to
take some time.
No excuses! We need this new
symbol of our strength completed
as soon as possible.
[DERMAIL:] Symbol sir?
Oz currently lacks an individual
that can fill Treize's place!
So it's crucial that Oz has a
symbol of strength to bring the
soldiers together.
And we must also eliminate the
existence of any country that
disrupts such unity!
You're talking about the Sanc
Kingdom of course.
The Sanc Kingdom most certainly
had a role to play in
proving Oz's support for
peace policies.
But now they're nothing more
than a hindrance to us!
So you're saying...
[DERMAIL:] We can no longer
afford to have any nations
that won't obey the
Romefeller Foundation
[SOLDIER:] Captain! The
surrounding mobile doll unit has
started to advance
from the country's
mountain border!
Right. Our main unit will
proceed to attack
from the shores.
We must siege the capital
of Sanc Kingdom.
[CAPTAIN:] Newport City.
[NOIN:] Miss Relena?
I've just been told our
surveillance system
at the border
has detected an invasion of
mobile doll troops.
Duke Dermail contacted me just
a little while ago.
He says Oz plans to attack us
for our unrestricted acceptance
of Oz deserters and
armed guerrillas.
I didn't expect Romefeller
to be this dirty!
Miss Relena, the Sanc Kingdom
stands as a hope for
peace in today's
violent world, just please don't
be too hard on those who
fight to protect it.
[RELENA:] Miss Noin!
Pagan, please evacuate all the
students from the institution.
Right.
No, stop it. Don't go doing
that. Stop it Epyon!
All units, attack!
[EXPLOSION]
There are just way too
many of them!
[PILOT:] Alright units, release
your Virgo troops!
[EXPLOSION]
All units, retreat to the
defense line now!
What, even more troops!?
I'm sure glad I'm not too
late Miss Noin!
Quatre!? Thank god.
[DISTANT EXPLOSIONS]
[DOROTHY:] Even the Sanc
Kingdom, with its total
pacifism and all,
has finally gotten dragged into
this storm of firepower.
Didn't you follow Pagan's
instructions Dorothy?
You have to leave at once.
Who, me? My stay at
the Sanc Kingdom
would be all but meaningless if
I couldn't witness
this situation.
[DOROTHY:] What do you plan
to do Miss Relena?
Will you keep resisting? Or will
you get military resistance
from your allies?
That method is not an option
in the Sanc Kingdom.
But what other methods are
there Miss Relena?
If the Sanc Kingdom were to
collapse now, then the ideal of
total pacifism would vanish!
As if it were a dream. [RELENA:]
‐That's not true at all Dorothy,
What all the people are wishing
for is true peace.
And those same people are
fighting beautifully to
protect that peace too.
Isn't it grand?
Heero! You're straying too far
off. Don't leave the city!
[HEERO:] If I start going out
of control again,
no one's going to be
able to stop me.
I haven't got the time to listen
to you and your war
hobbies right now.
That's not fair Miss Relena!
‐Not fair?
You can assemble people with
your sweet talk about peace,
but when
an emergency arises you
don't even do a thing!
[RELENA:] Now that's
not exactly true!
Oh no? You can't do anything?
That's because you're chasing
the impossible dream of
total pacifism.
How can you say that?
My teacher told me something
once; that man is a
fighting animal
and that whoever wins after
continuously fighting
should rule.
Isn't that the way to bring
about proper order?
Order could never bring about
peace in such a situation,
that's nothing but domination!
But one can start to establish
order merely by thinking
this way, right?
What can one accomplish
with total pacifism
when actual battles are being
fought as we speak?
[DOROTHY:] What you have is
nothing but a dream!
[GUNSHOTS]
We're the last line! We can't
let them get through.
Backup troops??
Don't let up, it's
far from over!
Miss Noin!
No! They've already
entered the city!
Miss Relena!
[DOROTHY:] There's no place in
the world today for
powerless total
pacifism. You'll ony fall prey
to those fighting animals.
This is the time to stand up and
fight Miss Relena!
[RELENA:] Just because humans
are fighting animals,
that doesn't make this
situation right!
I believe that people can find a
way to establish peace
without finding it
necessary to fight!
You're so beautiful when you
start talking of your ideas!
If you ask for their assistance
I'm sure the Treize
Faction and other
soldiers with grudges against Oz
will come to you at the
drop of a coin!
[EXPLOSION]
If the Sanc Kingdom and my own
existence are going to cause the
devastation of war
then I'll do my best to take a
new step toward total pacifism.
Yes it's very important that you
act now Miss Relena.
The city is being attacked!
[HEERO:] Relena!
Here Miss Relena! As requested,
you are now connected to
outer space and all
private lines of the
Foundation executives.
But is there anyone within the
Foundation now that can be of
help to you Miss Relena?
[RELENA:] My name is Relena
Peacecraft. Chief Representative
of the Sanc Kingdom.
Miss Relena!?
Our country is presently under
attack following Oz's
declaration of war against us.
How shrewd. Is she asking for
help from other countries?
[RELENA:] Armed combat counters
the Peacecraft philosophy and
the beliefs of the of the Sanc
Kingdom and our pacifism.
However, if our nation becomes a
target for Oz to conduct
their battles,
I shall renounce this country's
sovereignty, and
dissolve this nation.
[ZECHS:] How could she!? I
hope I'm not too late!
[RELENA:] Total pacifism should
not be the cause of battle,
under any circumstances.
[RELENA:] I am therefore
surrendering myself to Oz.
Miss Relena...
[RELENA:] This is to further
my ideal of peace.
An incredibly bold move.
I wonder if we could use that
power as a unifying force
for Romefeller.
Stop the fighting at once.
You no longer have a reason to
fight this battle.
Well done, wow! How much better
can you get Miss Relena?
I'm not in the mood for your
flattery right now Dorothy!
[DOROTHY:] I'm serious, I'm an
even bigger fan now!
Miss Relena, let's go to the
Romefeller Foundation!
I'd be more than happy
to escort you!
[RELENA:] My dear people.
Please forgive me.
This is the only
path I can take.
[RASHID:] Master Quatre,
let's go after it!
[QUATRE:] No! That would spoil
the move just taken
by Miss Relena.
Quatre! Will you please
come with me.
Where to?
Outer space.
I'd be glad to.
[DOROTHY:] I will personally
guarantee your safety
Miss Relena,
however I don't know how the
Foundation will want
to treat you.
[RELENA:] I'm lost. How in the
world am I going to make my
ideal a reality now?
We'll take in the Virgos, then
commence takeover with
manned suits.
Sir, there's still a mobile suit
continuing to retaliate
in the mountains.
What's that!?
[EXPLOSION]
[HEERO:] Where... where
is my enemy??
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] The dream of an
ideal world of peace
was easily overrun by the
overwhelming force.
But the Romefeller
Foundation hands the
heartbroken Relena yet
another cruel option.
Meanwhile, two Gundam pilots,
Heero and Zechs,
start a battle at the now
demolished Sanc Kingdom.
But, the battle is
now unnecessary.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 37:
Zero vs. Epyon