[THEME MUSIC]
[NARRATOR:] The attacks by 5
Gundams from the space colonies
reflected their
retaliatory intentions.
The Gundams’ target is OZ,
who'd masked its identity in the
troops of the Alliance military.
The Gundams had a number
of missions to attack OZ.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken
center stage.
With an army of elite
soldiers at his command,
Treize Khushrenada carries
out his plans to...
destroy the Alliance military.
The battle between the mobile
suits sent to Earth and OZ...
causes the Earth to
shudder violently.
Yeah, and I think it’ll be
a big hit with the soldiers.
Wow. Trowa’s usually so quiet
so it must be a good idea.
There’s nothing wrong with
acting on your emotions.
At least, that’s what
I was taught.
Yeah.
It’ll be my last
grandstand show.
[NARRATOR:] Catherine’s Tears
Prepare to drop Tallgeese.
Col. Zechs,
there’s turbulence in the area
where we’re to make the drop‐in.
Please be careful!
Everything’s ready.
Gage is in order
and prepared for drop.
Exit in 7 seconds.
Starting countdown...
5... 4... 3... 2... 1... exit!
[COMPUTER NOISES]
Col. Zechs, you can be
picked up on the Radar now.
Go ahead and speed up.
Col. Zechs?
Col. Zechs, are you all right?!
Y‐yes. I can hear you.
I’m ready to commence the tests.
[STRAINED GRUNTS]
Col. Zechs, anti‐aircraft
missiles are ready.
We’ve locked them
on to the Tallgeese.
Roger! Fire them!
Are you sure about this?
That’s what this mobile
suit is demanding!
The Tallgeese is
increasing its speed!
Alright, fire
anti‐aircraft missles!
Sir!
[EXPLOSIONS]
[Overlapping confusion]
Col. Zechs has conquered
that Tallgeese monster.
You’ve completely
mastered this thing!
The super vernier engine...
is different
from what’s on the blueprint.
If we went by the blueprint, its
operations would be affected.
Hmm. Doesn’t matter.
It’s up to the pilot to overcome
such operating difficulties.
Yes sir.
Fire fighters! Rescue
the injured! On the double!
This is Red Cancer,
I’ve crossed the defense line.
Proceeding to attack
frontline base.
Blue Angel here, roger.
Watch your back at
all times, huh Alex?
Hah, you won’t see me
letting my guard down!
Our advance guard
has been destroyed!
How many in the enemy troops?
Model signal confirmed!
One OZ Cancer and one OZ Aries.
Argh, you’re kidding!
Only two of them?!
[SCREAMS]
Our mobile troops
have been wiped out!
Enemy mobile suits are unharmed!
I guess the guards that we
gathered from elsewhere...
are no match for
these mobile suits!
We’re disarming our frontline
base as we speak.
We’re preparing to surrender,
so everyone take the
appropriate actions.
Surrendering? I think you’re
misunderstanding something.
Huh?
This is called an execution!
[SCREAMS]
What do you think you’re doing?
Don’t fire on us!
You poor relics from
the ancient past,
let this new age
baptize you all!
Stop! This isn’t even a war
you guys are starting!
It’s a massacre!
We already said this
is an execution!
[LAUGHTER]
A little too much
laughing, Mueller.
Lake Victoria.
Now this brings back memories.
I wonder how
Instructor Noin’s doing?
We’ll never be anything
but children in her eyes.
The least we could
do is show her...
how much our skills
have improved.
Lieutenant Alex!
Hmm?
We’ve got the
Victoria Base on the line!
Good! This is Alex of the
No. 33 Ind. Troops of NE Africa,
Somalia front.
What? Isn’t Lt. Noin there?
Lieutenant Colonel Noin is
on a mission to Moscow.
Moscow, huh? Now, would
she be there with Col. Une?
No, the Lieutenant’s
trip is unrelated.
In any case, we’re
planning to attack...
the former Alliance’s
Mogadishu fortress.
We need to drop by to
pick up some supplies.
We’re coming in to land.
What do you mean, you have no
soldiers with combat experience?
Since when has this base been a
maintenance facility
for old mobile suits?
It was approved by Lt. Noin.
Are you sure? Didn’t Col. Zechs
twist her arm or something?
I heard Noin’s trip to Moscow
had to do with Col. Zechs too.
That is true, but Lt. Noin
planned this trip on her own.
Think she’d do anything
for a killer of his own men?
Everyone here would do anything
they could for Col. Zechs.
You fool! We only follow the
orders of Treize Kushrenada.
Lt. Noin taught us to make His
Excellency’s ideals a reality!
That’s enough. Meuller.
We can’t make them
change their minds.
But, Alex...
We can still request
more of their soldiers, pal.
I just explained,
we don’t have any experienced
soldiers stationed here.
You do have one.
An elite soldier by the
name of Col. Zechs Marquise.
We can determine the combat
skills of the pilot...
by matching this data...
to the basic capacities
of the 01,
as we can judge
from its remains.
What do the remains tell you?
It’s completely destroyed.
01’s self‐detonation device
couldn’t have worked any better.
Could the Gundam pilot
have survived?
Doubt it.
This can’t be!
What is it?
It says this pilot wasn’t human.
I must’ve input
something incorrectly.
What do the results say exactly?
Response speed was unusual.
Same with strength and endurance
to gravitational force.
I heard that the pilot
was still a boy.
These figures are unthinkable!
Not surprising.
I’m sure he must’ve gone through
special training courses
in outer space.
But these results have
completely undermined
any psychological
advantages I had.
I thought our differences
lay only in of our mobile suits.
That pilot might even be
able to bring out
the full capacity of
this Tallgeese.
An impressive piece of work.
I had no idea you had a taste
for antiques, Colonel.
You’re not really expecting to
use this in combat, are you?
In fact, I’ve already
used this suit.
I heard a nasty rumor that 01
self‐detonated in Siberia.
It was also used to
attack the Sanc Kingdom
in Northern Europe, wasn’t it?
I bet that guy who lost his
life piloting this thing...
would’ve preferred something
a little less antiquated,
don’t you think, Col. Zechs?
What are you getting at?
We’re planning to attack
the Mogadishu Fortress
of the former Alliance tomorrow.
But our mobile suit troops alone
couldn’t possibly conquer it.
We wanted to get some help
from soldiers at this base.
Fine.
Huh?
I’ll go on this Tallgeese.
As your subordinate.
As our subordinate, Colonel?
What’s your problem?
You’re in charge of front line
battles of Somalia, are you not?
Then here are your first
orders, Col. Zechs.
Prepare to leave at 0400 hours
tomorrow on the Tallgeese.
This is Red Cancer, taking off.
Don’t let them see us.
It’ll give them an excuse to
fire the Noventa cannon,
the pride of the Alliance.
Yes sir!
All Aries troops, prepare
yourselves for takeoff.
Lieutenant Meuller!
What is it?
Will you need to use some
debris against the radar?
No.
But the enemy will detect us!
Don’t worry.
They’ll detect Zech’s mobile
suit long before they find us.
Are you using Col. Zechs
as a decoy?
This plan will get the enemy to
point their
Noventa cannon inland.
Yes sir, I understand.
Let’s get see the Lightning
Count’s true abilities, huh?
We’re at our drop‐off point.
Roger, drop the Tallgeese
Col. Zechs!
What is it?
I have a message
from Red Cancer,
he says “Good luck
on your mission.”
I won’t need any luck.
Releasing the Tallgeese!
Enemy machine
detected in the sky!
It’s headed straight this
way, from the inland.
OZ has come all the way
out to these remote regions.
Use the Noventa cannon and
don’t let them get any closer!
Target detected!
Height and angle confirmed!
On standby to fire!
Fire the Noventa cannon!
[EXPLOSIONS]
High pressure explosives strike
confirmed, enemy’s been hit!
What?!
A body of energy is
headed this way!
It’s headed straight
for the Leo troops!
The enemy hasn't been shot down!
Let's try out the modified
super vernier engine.
Why aren't you firing
the Noventa cannon?!
The enemy's mobile suit is
so fast, we can't lock onto it!
More enemies!
They're attacking from the sea!
I never realized this
fortress was so fragile!
Enemy mobile suit is calling!
I’ll connect him!
I’m from the No. 33
Independent Troops,
and my name is Col. Zechs.
You have lost your
defensive advantage,
and any further battle would
be completely meaningless.
We demand that you disarm
your weapons at once.
I’m sure that’s what
His Excellency,
the peace‐oriented late
Noventa would want.
All our mobile suits
have been defeated
and the No. 5 block
has been annihilated!
All right, we surrender.
[EXPLOSIONS]
Alex! Meuller! What are
you doing?! Stop your assault!
They've already acknowledged
their surrender!
Why, Colonel Zechs.
You're overstepping your
bounds of authority.
You can leave everything
to Meuller and I
from here on in, Zechs.
Including the execution of
these ex‐Alliance members.
Execution?!
These fools who
are stupid enough...
to constantly oppose
the changing era.
It's up to us to
correct this stagnation.
So, it's an official discipline.
Hah, here comes your discipline!
Damn you, OZ! No one
stands a chance against
your cruel and immoral
methods of assault!
I’ve hit the command tower!
I’m going in for a 2nd attack!
Stop this! How dare you
call yourselves OZ soldiers!
You should be ashamed
of yourselves!
The extent of your conceit
is appalling and even vulgar!
Lieutenant Meuller! Col. Zechs
says to stop the attack!
OZ villains, go to hell!
Zechs! How dare you
kill a fellow comrade!
It's your fault!
He died because of you!
[EXPLOSIONS]
Die!
[SCREAMING]
Damn you, Zechs!
[MUFFLED EXPLOSIONS]
Looks like you
underestimated my suit.
My next shot will finish
you off for certain, Colonel!
Say your prayers!
I can’t see him anymore,
where did he go?!
Your skills are
quite impressive.
But for one of Noin's students,
you’re certainly lacking
in intelligence.
You scum! How dare you talk
to me about Instructor Noin!
Has this era made him insane?
You act way too calm
for your own good!
These men have no right
to be given any power!
Fools!
[MUFFLED EXPLOSION]
The vernier engine is
working beautifully.
Thanks, I’m glad to hear it.
What's this about?
It’s a report regarding
Alex and Meuller.
I’d like you to send it to
Lieutenant Noin for me.
Why’s that, Colonel?
Tell her what a mistake it is...
to teach nothing more
than mere techniques.
But Colonel Zechs, sir!
Wars are heartless.
Wars truly are heartless indeed.
But I'm recreating a mobile suit
from the remains
of an enemy suit,
so as a soldier, that makes
me no better than them.
That carrier's transporting
enough fuel for 20 shuttles.
Meaning OZ has started to
position their space army
in preparation for conquest.
Ladies and Gentlemen, allow me
to present our next performance,
shown here for the
first time ever!
Introducing the rising star of
our circus, Trowa Barton!
A mobile suit?
Trowa?
[CROWD REACTS POSITIVELY]
What’s Trowa doing?
What on earth has
he got planned?
This is gonna be the best!
A performance like this
would bring the house down
no matter where we took it to!
Now for my self‐detonation show.
[CROWD REACTS NEGATIVELY]
Trowa...
[CHAOS]
Next'll destroy the
storage tank.
This’ll be my last battle.
Don’t need to worry about
running out of bullets.
[EXPLOSIONS]
Trowa, what's going on?
What's gotten into you?
You're planning to die!
This is the end.
Trowa! What are
you doing? Trowa!
Catherine, stay away from here!
I am going to self‐detonate
along with him.
What do you mean, Trowa?
Come down here and let’s talk
things out! Come on, hurry!
Catherine!
Stay away, Catherine. I’ve got
to go through with this!
Trowa? Trowa!
Don't you think your life is a
little too valuable, Trowa?
Self‐detonate?!
What are you thinking?
What would your
mother and father
think of such a hasty
and selfish decision?
Did you give a thought to the
people you'd leave behind?
You're the most pathetic
person I ever met!
You didn't think about us!
The people you'd leave behind!
We'd have to keep on
living in sorrow.
You're the one that
brainwashed...
my Trowa with your
strange ideas.
I won't let you off so
easy next time.
That girl’s tears stopped me.
If you were in my shoes you
still would've done it, right?
Now you should know why
I admire your strength.
I’ve said this before.
The only way to live a good life
is to act on your emotions.
Let's get going.
Yeah.
I’m sorry to see him
that boy leave.
He really was pretty good.
With training, he could've
been the best in the business.
What're you talking about?
You gotta let go of your kids
if you want them to grow up.
We helped raised Trowa
in this circus,
so I’m sure he'll
come back one day.
He'll come back for sure.
[ENDING MUSIC]
Heero tries to make up
for his mistake of killing
the honorable leader Noventa,
pacifist of the former Alliance.
Within the war zones
created by OZ,
Heero confronts Sylvia,
the granddaughter of Noventa.
How can he compensate
for his wrongdoing?
Just about then,
Zechs is handed an order from
the Romefeller Foundation.
Next on Gundam Wing, Episode 14:
The Order to Destroy 01