[OPENING THEME]
GUNDAM WING
[ZECHS] Certain conditions must
be met for total peace.
[ZECHS] First all weapons must
be eliminated. And second
the desire to fight must be
erased from people's mind.
Libra plunging to Earth. It's
the only way to achieve
total pacifism!
The people who have lost Earth
will hate you and the colonies
will rely on you.
The same mistakes will be
repeated as long as you live.
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
[NOIN] Zechs considers this
place his grave. And it's not
because he wishes to die
a brave man in a battle. He
intends to pay for the sin of
purging humanity all by himself.
I'm sure Heero's figured that
out by now. He should
have anyway.
[NARRATOR] The Final Victor
[LADY UN] How's the troop
evacuation coming along?
[SOLDIER] 80% of our soldiers
have returned safely but there's
substantial damage to
our mobile suit force. It
appears that 67% of them
have been destroyed.
Then destroy our remaining
mobile suits as soon as
they are retrieved.
[SOLDIER] What?! It's important
that we rid ourselves
of all weapons left on the
Earth. Those are his
excellency's orders.
I understand now. So Treize
Khushrenada's objective was
total pacifism as well huh?
Who are you!? What?
I welcome you your majesty.
I really wish you wouldn't refer
to me that way any longer.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[DUO] Alright we made it.
[SCIENTIST] Thanks for
your help Duo.
Now it's up to you. I'll do my
thing with the guys outside.
[SCIENTIST] Hey don't get too
rowdy! We need to concentrate.
Tell that to the enemy will ya?
I am like a body that has lost
its soul. Now's your chance
to take revenge
for your father's death.
Let's put an end to all this.
The revenge and the battles.
Yes.
Now what can we do about Libra
and Peacemillion?
We have already estimated the
location of the
impact and issued
an evacuation warning.
Evacuation? You're not serious.
If those two battleships hit
ground the entire world
will be effected.
[HOWARD] If those battleships
enter the Earth's atmosphere &amp;
explode on ground
the initial explosion might be
limited to a radius of a few
hundred kilometers.
But the enormous amount of dust
spreading across the skies
would block solar rays,
resulting in a dramatic decrease
in temperatures
around the world.
[RELENA] That's terrible.
[SALLY] And people won't be able
to live on the Earth any longer.
The only way to avoid this is to
change their orbit or blow
them up in space.
Both are next to impossible.
[LADY UN] No we still have hope.
There's a Gundam close to
Peacemillion's power supply.
[RELENA] Is it Heero? [LADY UN]
No I think it's 02.
Duo? Then they're likely with
them. Well then we
still have hope.
But where are the other Gundams?
There's too many mobile dolls
moving about to know for sure.
[DUO] I've continually fought
and with each battle I've been
killing my own heart.
And my heart has been completely
void of feeling for quite
a long time now.
Maybe my life doesn't have value
anymore. But I have to
keep on living.
Why's that?
I've got a home to go back to.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Well unlike you I don't have any
place left at all to go back to.
Can you stand up Quatre?
Listen to me Trowa. You've gotta
do me a favor. Look after her
and forget about me.
Don't worry about it. I'm sure
she's strong enough to take
care of herself.
Yeah. I guess you're right.
You had better get going.
[QUATRE] Make it
through this somehow.
[DOROTHY SOBS]
Hey they've stopped moving.
Yo Trowa!
I'll come and join you. I've
completed my mission here.
Roger that. Where's Quatre?
[QUATRE] I'm right here.
[DUO] OK when we're done here
we'll celebrate with some
expensive champagne.
That sounds great as long as
it's non‐alcoholic.
[SOLDIER] Lt. Noin. Lt. Noin
this is MO‐2 calling come in.
Lt. Noin!
How come you're trying to
reach Lt. Noin?
You'll know soon enough. The
real question is whether the
times have changed even
more than I expected. [SOLDIER]
Colonel we've got her!
It's good to see you're
well Colonel.
Noin are you monitoring the
battle between Zechs and Heero?
[NOIN] Yes. Relay those images
to our line right away.
I'm not with OZ any longer. I
won't take your orders.
This isn't an order. It's a
favor as a fellow
believer of peace.
Very well then.
Heero...
Send this image at once to all
of Earth and space.
Yes ma'am.
[CONFUSED QUESTIONS]
[LADY UN] The battle you are
witnessing has no significance
to either Earth or the
colonies. But it's necessary
just the same because in reality
it's a battle to save the
colonies. This year in After
Colony 195 the history of battle
is about to come to an end.
Unless these two continue to
fight peace will never be
achieved. Can you feel it?
Can you feel the misery of this
combat? And can you see the
peace that awaits us?
This battle is making each one
of us look for a solution
to secure peace.
[MAN] Representative Un?
So she's alive!
[SCIENTIST] The regular booster
alone won't be enough to
change its course.
[TECH] We've got to take out the
pressure limit controller &amp;
the power cylinder.
We are stopping this disturbance
by causing another disturbance.
[TECH] Seems to be our
specialty doesn't it?
[QUINZE] Freeze! Don't
move a muscle.
Hey Quinze long time no
se‐ [GUNSHOT]
[QUINZE] I told you not to move!
Go ahead and kill us!
We're all done here.
You people have caused me
nothing but headaches! How
many times do you have
to interfere with
Operation Meteor?
The Gundams were more than
enough to take revenge
for Heero Yuy.
That last time and this
time as well.
[QUINZE] If it weren't for you
people changing the orders
to Gundam pilots
mankind would have come to its
senses a lot sooner than this.
Probably but we rate mankind &amp;
Earth a lot higher than
you ever did.
[QUINZE] Enough! We're going to
interfere just one more time.
[GUNSHOT]
[EXPLOSION]
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
You're the same as Treize
claiming to fight for justice
to protect the weak.
[HEERO] But in fact you're
actually not helping to
protect the weak at all.
It's the stronger who create the
weaker. It was the strong
Earth that created the
weak colonies and almost drove
them to destruction!
[ZECHS] Now victory
will be mine!
[HEERO] I can't stand the weak.
They're always nervous
about when they might be
next attacked.
They can't trust anybody and
they never have an
opinion of their own.
[HEERO] I can't stand such
people. [ZECHS] Strong people
make 'em that way.
[HEERO] Zechs none of humanity
is strong all of
humanity is weak.
And that includes us as well.
[SOLDIER] Peacemillion and Libra
are moving away from Earth.
Wait a sec! A section of Libra
is falling towards Earth.
What?
[SOLDIER] The colony
delegation's making an
official statement.
[VOICE] In accordance with the
declaration of defeat
given by the
World Nation, we the colony
delegation have an announcement
from all colonies.
We wish to pursue the withdrawal
of the White Fang's demands
and hereby announce
our desire to coexist with the
World Nation. We further declare
our rejection of any
combat regardless of the reason
&amp; strongly hope that the World
Nation will follow suit.
We would also like to apologize
for the suffering endured by
many people as a
result of our unclear stance.
[DUO] Damn we're not fast
enough! ‐We'll have to ruin
as much of it as
possible to reduce damages to
Earth. [TROWA] Wu Fei!
[HEERO] You're finished Zechs.
[ZECHS] Not yet.
[ZECHS] I still haven't
acknowledged that I'm one of the
weak people in the world.
[HOWARD] That's a problem.
[SALLY] Does it have a
power system?
[HOWARD] Yes naturally. That
block alone would cause a
never‐ending winter on Earth.
Gundam 02, 03, 04, and 05 have
caught up with block A.
Wait a second isn't that where
my brother and Heero are?
They're not going to quit until
it's all over. [RELENA] No
stop you two. NO!!!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
The colonies have started
heading toward total pacifism
all on their own.
What you're doing is
meaningless.
My destiny is smeared with blood
and I won't be talked out of
this transgression.
[ZECHS] I'm gonna
settle this Heero!
Why don't you kill me?
Relena would be sad.
[QUATRE] Heero!
What Quatre?
Good you're OK. The block is
still descending quickly
toward the Earth.
Gotcha. I'm gonna destroy this
ship's power system.
We'll smash it to smithereens
before it falls on Earth!
One should never give up till
the end. That's what
Heavyarms has taught me.
Chance of success is almost nil.
But this is better than
sitting back and not
doing anything.
[SOLDIER] Are you OK
Master Quatre?
[QUATRE] What are you all doing
here? It's too dangerous!
What are you trying to tell us?
‐Let us help you out master.
We've come this far &amp; we're
going all the way. ‐Let us join
you Master Quatre.
Thanks you guys. Really.
Here it is.
[HEERO] My only choice is the
self‐detonation device.
[SOLDIER] 200 seconds before
Libra's Block A enters the
atmosphere. We're outta time.
[HEERO] Farewell Relena...
There's only one more thing
required to attain total peace:
A strong heart that can
empathize with people.
Like yours.
[ZECHS] You're too pure &amp; too
kind, but I guess that's what
gives you the right to live.
Just watch me I'm gonna live
right to the bitter end!
[HEERO] Zechs!
[ZECHS] I'll live the hard
life of a warrior!
[HEERO] Zechs stop it! [ZECHS]
Till we meet again Heero...
[SOLDIER] Detonation of power
system confirmed! Huh? One part
of the block is still
falling it's not disintegrating!
It's going to hit Earth for
sure. Tell the
Gundams to retreat!
[SOLDIER] Wait!
Zero please guide me
through this.
[WU FEI] You forgot this.
Take it!
Mission accepted.
[SOLDIER] Master Quatre we've
done all we could. We
must escape.
[QUATRE] You guys go first. I'm
fighting a bit longer.
[SOLDIER 2] But we've done
enough already! [SOLDIER 3]
Dying now would be meaningless.
[WU FEI] I've given Heero his
Buster Rifle. [CHEERS]
Master Quatre did you hear that?
Sure did. We'd better get out of
here because we don't wanna
get in Heero's way.
[DUO] OK!
Roger that retreating now.
[SOLDIER] It has entered
the atmosphere.
[SOLDIER 2] Something's
flying ahead of it.
[SOLDIER 2] Look it's Wing Zero!
[RELENA] Heero?
[HOWARD] He's not gonna make it.
[SALLY] No He'll make it. I
think he'll be OK.
But he's gotta get through the
Earth's high temperatures!
From what I have seen the
Gundams can overcome
any difficulties.
That's true. I know we can
believe in him.
Because Heero's the kind of
person who can give
everybody hope.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[GRUNTS]
I will... I will... I will!
I will survive!
[RIFLE DISCHARGES]
[SOLDIER] We did it!
[SOLDIER 2] The remains have
burnt up. [CHEERS]
Heero...
He made it!
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
You've done it Heero!
Yeah. Naturally!
He is quite the guy.
Now I get it. It's Heero who is
the heart of outer space.
Mission complete.
[NARRATOR] The year is After
Colony 195. On this day the
formation of the new
Earth Sphere United Nation is
passed at a conference
between Earth
and the colonies.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
So you're here again Dorothy.
That's right. But this is the
last time. I'm so tired of
living in the past.
I see.
[DOROTHY] Why is it that you
never pay respects to Mr.
Milliardo's grave Ms. Noin?
[NOIN] Because I don't need to.
I know that he's still alive
somewhere out there.
[MAN] Excuse me Vice Foreign
Minister Darlian? I'm wondering
are you off to Earth
again?
Yes. It's important that I get
the Earth Sphere
delegates to review
this terraformation
project ASAP.
Oh dear that's really a shame
because we were planning on
having your birthday
party here at our colony today.
[RELENA] I'm terribly sorry.
[MAN] Excuse me.
That's fine.
What? Huh?
Heero!
Next time hand it to
me in person.
[BREEZY MUSIC]
[THE END]
[ENDING THEME]