THEME MUSIC
To facilitate it's reign over the
world,
Romefeller foundation promoted a
new Oz.
With it's main power consisting of
unmanned units
called mobile
dolls.
Certain changes within the
Foundation
followed Treize Khushenrada's
retaliation,
including his being
stripped of all power.
At the same time,
the Foundation was rapidly
expanding its area of rule,
thanks to the highly skilled
mobile dolls.
The year is After Colony 195.
After the space colonies
accepted the Foundation,
execution orders were released for
the now isolated Gundam pilots.
For them it looked like the future
would take a turn for the worse.
Armed suits that shouldn't
be found in a pacifist nation.
Does the princess know
about these units?
People think about fighting
because
they possess weapons such as
these.
In order to cling to peace which
is really as fragile as glass.
Dorothy!
Miss Relena! Come on, hurry!
Let's get going, or else we're
gonna miss the fight!
[EXPLOSION]
Can't be!
A GUNDAM!
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
The God of Death Meets Zero
[PILOT:] Route Ritter! Route
Ritter!
This is Cracker Escort.
[RITTER:] Okay, I'm checking it.
We're entering the area in
question.
Any readings?
No. But I'd sure hate to be
involved in
an accident in an isolated place
like this.
Huh? What is that?
[RITTER:] Is it a mine?
[PILOT:] I'll check it out.
[RITTER:] Be careful!
‐[PILOT:] Roger!
It's the spacecraft from the
accident!
The pieces are scattered all over.
It must have exploded. Hmm?
What's the matter, did you
find something?
[PILOT:] ECMs, and they’re
powerful!
[RITTER:] What?!
[PILOT:] What’s this??
[PILOT:] Aaaahhh!!!
[PILOT:] A GUNDAM!!
[EXPLOSION]
[PILOT 2:] The Leo up ahead was
obliterated, prepare to attack!!
The God of Death is
back from hell!!
Damn it all, 02 is here!
I can’t contact fortress Barge!
[EXPLOSION]
So about 80%.
But the remaining modifications
shouldn't be too difficult.
Hmm? Time I made my getaway!
[NARRATOR:] Operation Nova.
Built with the plentiful
resources on the moon,
the Virgo mobile dolls were
directed at Earth,
to suppress rebel
forces.
The plan appeared to be
progressing smoothly.
But recently,
frequent disturbances
had hindered output on
the Virgo production line.
They´re disappeared? But
what about the escort troops!?
They have vanished, with
the carrier fleet.
Last located at D244 in‐
[TUBAROV:] ‐Idiot!
They couldn't have had an
accident!
They've been destroyed!
[TUBAROV:] Probably by a Gundam.
[SOLDIER:] Lieutenant Trant has
assembled a unit
and is headed to the
location sir.
Ten Tauruses, fifty space mines,
one support carrier...
What’s this?
Trant is the only soldier?
Contact Trant!
But sir he's out on a search,
so we shouldn't contact him
[TUBAROV:] I don't care! Get him
on the line! Sir!
[TRANT:] Good. It's stable now.
[TRANT:] Trant Clark logging in.
Following my examination of the
new Gundam's cockpit system,
I must conclude that it's unlike
anything I've ever encountered.
[TRANT:] This cockpit exposes the
vulnerabilities of all
soldiers in outer space.
[TRANT:] The cockpit is equipped
with a system that
increases the combative
abilities of the pilot!
[TRANT:] It can fully match the
reaction time of the mobile dolls.
But as soon as brainwave levels
are increased during combat,
a problem
arises.
[EXPLOSION]
[TRANT:] Here it comes!
[TRANT:] My arms! I can't move!
[EXPLOSION]
[TRANT:] Yahhh!!
[TRANT:] Terminate
combat simulation!
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[TRANT:] Why did I start
to hallucinate?
[EXPLOSION NOISE]
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
[TRANT:] Did they get out of
control
because they were hallucinating
too?
[TRANT:] If I could get data
on actual battles,
rather than simulations,
I'd be able to figure out
something.
[TRANT:] The two Gundam pilots
that escaped
from the lunar base are still in
outer space.
[SOLDIER:] Lieutenant
Trant come in!
This is the lunar base, come in!
Orders from Colonel Tubarov!
Huh. Either pilot will do.
I'll find
one of them and get my data.
Once I've done that
I'm sure I'll be able to
persuade Colonel Tubarov.
[TUBAROV:] Can't you find him
yet?? Where is Trant!
Uh... Well, sir.
I see. Get in touch with Fortress
barge,
then we'll immediately dispatch
some troops to locate Trant.
His actions are a definite
violation of military procedures.
[SOLDIER:] Yes sir!
I hope I'm overreacting.
You're the guy who needed vernier
fuel for mobile suits aren't you?
Yeah, sorry to bother you!
Here's your payment!
Genuine Oz products.
The stuff is in the trailer out
front so just help yourself.
Here, sign this form.
[DUO:] Just a sec! Don't you
want to see what's inside?
We'll never make ends meet if
those guys completely take over.
Until then I'm counting on you to
do what you can kiddo.
I'm trusting in you lad.
Just let me know if you need
bullets, contact me anytime.
Hmm? The old guy drove off
without even taking my payment.
[HILDE:] Duo!
[HILDE:] Is there anything
I can help with?
Nope! It's all under control.
Wait for me at the trailer out
front, I'll be right there.
Sure thing. Later!
[TRANT:] I'll go to the area where
a number of the carriers have
disappeared
and give it a thorough search.
[HILDE:] Duo!
[DUO:] Any success?
Uh‐huh! No luck.
I couldn't get any information
on the new transport plan!
[DUO:] Oz isn't that ignorant!
They're just being more
cautious than before.
I'd love to destroy barge right
now.
But I'll have to put it off for a
while.
Are you gonna keep on
fighting alone Duo?
[DUO:] What choice do I have?
I have no idea where
the others are.
So I'll just have
to go it alone.
Let me know if there's any way I
can be of help Duo.
I'll do anything!
Okay! I wouldn't mind having
a juicy steak for dinner!
Come off it! I'm totally serious!
[DUO:] I know I know. You're
doing more than enough already!
[BOTH:] Huh??
[HILDE:] What is that??
Wait a sec!
[DUO:] It's a Gundam!
[TRANT:] Freeze.
[TRANT:] Duo Maxwell, I demand
that you come with me.
Do it or you're
dead.
Hey, do what you got to do,
but remember the power of
that beam cannon.
You could completely
demolish this colony.
[TRANT:] I don't care.
I have no interest
in what happens to this place kid.
I've got no intention of remaining
an insignificant technical
officer.
Once I figure out this Gundam's
system,
Colonel Tuberov's mobile dolls
will
be a useless tool of the past.
What the new Oz needs is a
completely new system.
I'll do whatever is required
to make that happen.
Now come here Gundam pilot,
you're the only one I want.
What's with all this junk you've
attached?
Alright, what do you want me to
do?
I want you to fight the mobile
dolls with the Wing Zero here.
With real firearms
of course.
That's fine with me but I just
might escape during your tests.
[TRANT:] No you won't. I've set it
so the Wing's functions
can be stopped from
outside.
And besides, I've programmed the
mobile dolls
to switch their target to
that colony
in case you decide to try
something funny.
[TRANT:] Right! Commence!
[DUO:] If I use the rifle from
this position
it would harm the colony.
So I'll use this instead!
[TRANT:] That's good, that's the
way to fight.
Show me exactly what you see
before you.
Huh?? What's this?
What? No way!
[TRANT:] So you saw it?
You must tell me,
just what is the Wing Zero
trying to show the pilot?
How should I know what it means??
I see, that's my enemy.
Ahhhh!
[TRANT:] What now??
[EXPLOSION]
[HILDE:] AHHHHH!!
[DUO:] What am I doing?
What in the hell have I been
doing?
[EXPLOSION]
No. No way. Huh?
It couldn't be. There's no way.
How could a person do this?
[TRANT:] It's possible.
Believe me it is.
[TRANT:] We can do anything with
this outstanding system.
It's capable
of altering
human consciousness.
Anything is possible with this.
[SOLDIER:] Lieutenant Trant.
Can you hear me?
Hand over the Wing Zero and
surrender yourself.
Orders from Colonel
Tubarov.
[SOLDIER:] I repeat, hand over the
Wing Zero and surrender.
Huh, They're here.
I'll do it. I'm gonna go for it.
You better leave it alone.
Just forget that system.
Duo!
Its the Wing Zero! It's headed
straight for us!
Colonel Tubarov, shall we capture
him?
[TUBAROV:] Destroy him!
[SOLDIER:] Roger!
He's a dead man.
Just a little more, I can't
see everything yet.
[TRANT:] Come on, give me
all you've got!
[HILDE:] Don't do it! You cannot
fight in the state you're in Duo!
Don't worry Hilde! Remember,
I'm a Gundam pilot!
[DUO:] That system is more than a
human can handle.
I gotta stop
him.
It's expanding, my consciousness
is expanding!
I can almost see
everything!
I'm almost there!
I want more! I haven't had enough!
[TRANT:] I haven't had enough yet!
[DUO:] Stop it!
Damn! It's incredibly fast!
I can see! I can clearly see your
moves!
I can even see you during your
death!
[DUO:] In your dreams!
He’s even more powerful than me!
You're dead!
[GROANING]
[TRANT:] You fool! Haven't you
realized yet
that you don't stand a chance
against me?
[TRANT:] This will do it!
You'll die right now and the
glory will be mine!
[DUO:] You sure about that?
What??
It might just be a tie!
[TRANT:] Get away from me!
I won't be defeated and certainly
not by a young punk like you!
If you were to lose it wouldn't be
to me!
You'd be losing to the Wing Zero!
[TRANT:] There's no way I
can be defeated!
[DUO:] You still don't get it,
do you!?
[TRANT:] AAHHHHH!!!
I won't lose! I can't possibly
lose!
I can handle
a system like this no prob‐AGHH!!
It's just too much for a
human being to handle.
[DUO:] If anyone were capable of
it,
he'd be superior to
the entire human race.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] Zechs Marquise
once again dons his mask and
proceeds to crush
Propeller's mobile dolls.
Dermail is resentful and calls
Relena
to ask whether or not Zechs
is in fact Milliardo Peacecraft.
Realizing that the
Foundation plans to wipe out the
Treize Faction, Heero heads alone
for the battlefield that has
the highest risk of death.
Next on Gundam Wing Episode 33:
The Lonely Battlefield.