[OPENING THEME]
To facilitate it's reign over
the world, Romefeller Foundation
promoted a new OZ.
With it's main power consisting
of unmanned units
called mobile dolls.
Certain changes within the
Foundation followed Treize
Khushenrada's retaliation,
including his being
stripped of all power.
At the same time, the Foundation
was rapidly expanding
its area of rule,
thanks to the highly
skilled mobile dolls.
After the space colonies
accepted the Foundation,
execution orders were released
for the now isolated
Gundam pilots.
For them, it looked like the
future would take a turn
for the worse.
The Sanc Kingdom...
This is nuts, but
it's the only way
I knew it would be!
How very kind of you, but just
call me Dorothy Miss Relena.
And you are welcome to call me
Relena
‐ I couldn't!
You're the heroine of our times
Miss Relena! I myself feel a
great admiration for you.
The Reunion with Relena
[SOLDIER:] First unit, proceed.
Second unit, standby for orders.
[SOLDIER 2:] No signs of
movement, the field has
been secured.
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
We're surrounded! Hurry!
Is it Red‐One?
[QUATRE:] This is absurd Heero!
It's totally absurd!
[QUATRE:] It's a dispute within
their organization.
Participating in their fight
only makes you another target!
[HEERO:] A target?
That's fine with me.
Execution orders have been
issued for us Gundam pilots,
this way I can let Romefeller
know that I'm still alive.
It's my way of retaliating.
[SOLDIER:] After the enemy!
We'll show them what stray
dogs are made of.
[QUATRE:] Is this
really okay Heero?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[DOROTHY:] I finally got the
pictures. There's something so
wild about him...
Nice to meet you, Heero Yuy, and
Quatre Roberba Winner.
[DOROTHY:] Welcome to Earth.
Welcome to a warrior's paradise.
What did you say!?
[OLD MAN:] No‐ no oh no!
[SOLDIER:] Repeat what
you just said!
You're mistaken! I
haven't said anything!
Liar! You think that the two OZ
factions should just
crush each other!
Listen fellas, I just want
to live in peace!
Quiet you!
[SOLDIER:] The Treize Faction is
ready to attack this area,
all physically fit men are to
join our backup forces!
Get your boss out here and
round up the people!
[OZ GENERAL:] Total pacifism?
That's right! We refuse
to participate in
military operations in order
to attain peace.
The Treize Faction here are
former OZ members that defended
your land in the past.
But now... They're
resisting us as rebels.
That dispute concerns the OZ
organization. It has
nothing to do with us!
A very convenient
notion of pacifism.
Once the occupying army becomes
a nuisance, you suddenly declare
yourselves pacifists.
The duty of the military is to
protect the citizens.
But now the troops are unwanted.
I'm beginning to feel a little
bit sorry for the
Treize Faction.
In either case, the
battle will commence.
We should continue our
discussion after
peace is attained.
It's absurd to even speak of
pacifism in the flames of war.
Are you alright? I'm sorry I
couldn't come to help you.
Ah, thank you lad.
It happens all the time.
Fighting back against them would
only make things a lot
worse for me.
[MAN:] Are you a traveler?
‐[QUATRE:] Yes.
[MAN:] You couldn't have come
at a worse possible time.
This would be a beautiful place
if it weren't for
this situation.
They're starting to move in.
They're close this time.
I'll go check it out!
OZ's Aries suits...
Lure the enemies over this way.
Don't forget to
disperse the debris!
That's right, do everything to
defeat them!
‐ [SOLDIER:] Yes sir!
Shouldn't we be advising the
civilians to evacuate now?
Don't underestimate
our abilities!
We'll defeat the Treize Faction
rebels well before they come
close to the town!
[GENERAL:] Let's go
over our plans:
We'll trick the enemy's advance
guard by having our main
troops attack first.
Meanwhile, our mobile forces
will come in from the side,
enter the town, and attack
enemy headquarters.
The mobile forces will join our
main troops, expel the enemy
troops, and take over the town.
The leader of the mobile forces
will be... Red‐One.
You're in charge. Can
you handle it?
Of course I can. I am a Gundam
pilot, after all.
[OZ GENERAL:] What!? New forces?
Sir! Their abilities outweigh
the strength of our forces!
Send troops from our front line.
Wipe them out now!
Good, their firepower is
decreased. Smash through them!!
[EXPLOSION]
[QUATRE:] Wars are self serving.
I feel sorry for the civilians.
Heero, please stop!
Getting involved in this kind of
battle will end up
destroying us.
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
We'll finish them off before
their backup troops arrive. Hmm?
[SOUNDS OF CIVILIANS]
Didn't they tell the
civilians to evacuate?
[GENERAL:] Red‐One, what's your
present situation,
have you destroyed the
Headquarters yet? Red‐One!
[HEERO:] I'm altering the
mission, I'm defending
this position.
[GENERAL:] What!? What
are you saying??
This is the Gundam
pilot calling,
[HEERO:] I will proceed to
destroy enemy mobile troops.
[OZ SOLDIER:] Intercepted enemy
message What's this!? Gundam??
[SOLDIER ON RADIO:] What's the
matter? What is it??
[OZ SOLDIER:] The Leo up
ahead on the right!
[OZ SOLDIER 2:] It's piloted
by a Gundam pilot!
[GENERAL:] What are you doing
Red‐One, respond! Red‐One,
Red‐One!?
Evacuation of
civilians confirmed.
Red‐One calling blue.
[GENERAL:] Blue here. What's
wrong Red‐One? Why weren't
you responding?
Our mission here has completely
failed, too many casualties.
We'll retreat for now.
[GENERAL:] What do you mean,
what's happened Red‐One?
What's wrong?
What's going on there, come in
Red‐One, Red‐One,
what happened!?
Red‐One!
[RELENA:] There is no need for
armaments in pacifism.
But unless the whole world
starts thinking in these terms,
I'm positive that the Sanc
Kingdom will never be a
safe country.
[RELENA:] Under these
circumstances, I'm
delighted to have
the opportunity to attend
classes with you.
You who are poised to take on
the responsibilities
of your respective nations.
I really hope that together we
can think of a way
to eliminate wars from this
world in the near future.
Quite admirable.
[RELENA:] Any comments Dorothy?
I think it's wonderful.
If everyone in this world
were Miss Relena,
wars would be immediately
denounced as foolish.
And would disappear from
this world forever.
But if everybody were
Miss Relena,
nobody would realize just how
wonderful you are!
Dorothy. I'm aware that my views
may appear to be a little
naive to some people,
but I wonder why people battle
if everyone agrees that it's
foolish to do so.
I don't think that we're too
far from the answer.
Miss Relena, I think I
understand why there is never
an end to battles.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
People love to fight each other.
And fighting satisfies
their instincts, you know.
But many lives are lost
as a result of fighting.
Miss Relena, I'm not
interested in results.
You can leave things alone and
still get results.
Beauty lies in taking action.
The action of fighting is the
most fascinating human aspect!
Throughout history, people have
fought each other over
and over again,
As if battles are the purpose
of human existence.
That's why I started thinking in
this way. It's not true that
we shouldn't fight.
As humans, I think
we must fight.
I'm afraid I don't
share your opinion.
I'm positive that we're
capable of not repeating
the tragedies of the past in
the times ahead.
Your wise opinions are also
necessary in a war.
History changes radically
when the lives of
people with similar opinions
are sought after.
Miss Relena, I truly believe the
Sanc Kingdom is going to be the
center stage of these times.
[MUTTERING]
Watch me Dorothy. As long as I
live I will continue to
promote total pacifism.
Even if I end up getting killed,
I'm sure these policies
will bear fruit.
That's good to hear Miss Relena.
You mustn't fear death.
Because death is merely an end
result given to you
at your birth.
But don't be worried
Miss Relena.
Brave knights are about to
arrive before you who will be
very helpful for your future.
They will be able to
protect you.
So one of the enemies is
a Gundam pilot.
[SOLDIER:] I suspect he'll cause
a great deal of
damage to the area.
The mayor stressed total
pacifism right up til
the very end.
We'd have to destroy this
nation anyway.
Position yourselves for battle!
‐[SOLDIER:] Sir!
[QUATRE:] Mister!
Oh, so you made it out okay,
I was getting worried about you!
What's this?
‐ A war's going to break out.
I'm getting ready to move out
for a long spell.
What the!? New mobile dolls?
Look at them, all lined up.
Those guys just love to fight.
But we think that total
peace suits us just fine.
Our country took a courageous
position. We decided to follow
the Sanc Kingdom.
The Sanc Kingdom?
[PAGAN:] Miss Relena!
Are you alright?
What do you mean Pagan?
I mean that recently,
there's been a great increase in
the number of nations
relying on the total pacifism
of the Sanc Kingdom.
And all of these nations are
relying on the Sanc Kingdom
for leadership.
There's a lot of pressure to
meet these responsibilities.
Even you could get very
exhausted by all this pressure,
Miss Relena.
Thanks for caring Pagan, but
this is what I am
living for now.
I have to do my best, or being
leader of the Sanc Kingdom
would be in vain.
But there's also a certain
classmate of yours that
has me worried.
You can't let down your guard
with her around. ‐You
mean Dorothy?
Pagan please, you mustn't
speak badly of her.
I wonder what sort of education
she had at Romefeller...
Dorothy is a very
intelligent friend.
I'm sure she's thinking about
these war times even more
seriously than I am.
I'm sure that one day she'll
come to understand our views.
Miss Noin instructed me to keep
this a secret from you but...
Keep what a secret?
I'll tell you, since I believe
you'd do better to have as many
allies as possible right now.
Well, what is it? Pagan?
We've been able to locate the
Gundam pilot Heero Yuy.
Heero Yuy!?
[PAGAN:] Miss Noin is on her way
to meet with him as we speak.
He's here? So Heero has
returned to Earth?
He seems to be very
exhausted as well.
Miss Noin says she's planning to
bring him here to the
Sanc Kingdom.
Then he's really... come back.
[GUNFIRE]
The new models. It'll be
tough with this Leo.
[GUNFIRE]
[OZ SOLDIER:] The enemies are
battling at the defense line.
[OZ SOLDIER 2:] Hasn't
headquarters been evacuated yet?
Hurry!
Only the soldiers seem to be
panicked. Everyone
else is relaxed.
We're just tired of having
anything to do with war.
You're tired of it.
‐Everybody is!
It is possible to avoid fighting
and live in peace!
We've just chosen to do
what seemed natural!
These days many people and
indeed countries are beginning
to demand total pacifism.
Although their strength is
still insignificant,
once the number of people
who seek peace
outweighs that of the soldiers,
I'm certain the world is
bound to change.
I heard that the Romefeller
Foundation thinks of the Sanc
Kingdom as a problem.
Because many countries have
started supporting them.
Eventually Romefeller will be
left without any supporters.
[QUATRE:] So the Romefeller
Foundation considers the
Sanc Kingdom a threat because
they're afraid of them!
That opens up a chance for total
pacifism to be
realized worldwide!
What's wrong young lad?
[QUATRE:] Thanks for
everything Mister!
I'm going to go there, to
the Sanc Kingdom.
[SOLDIER YELLING]
I'll fight through this... It's
my way of retaliating.
I'm fighting through this
longer than anyone.
[HEERO:] Longer than
anyone on Earth.
[HEERO:] Longer than Relena,
of the Sanc Kingdom.
Heero!!
[QUATRE:] Heero! Are you
alright? Heero, we
can't die yet!
Listen to me! We have to
protect the Sanc Kingdom.
What, the Sanc Kingdom? Who, us?
That's right! That's the job we
must do here on Earth!
What the‐
Hey that's... the beam gatling
from your Gundam!
You're Gundam pilots so I'm sure
you know how to use that.
I'll back you up while you
get out of there.
Heero!
[NOIN:] So you told
Relena about it?
I'm terribly sorry.
I realize that this will
increase the odds of her finding
out about the Gundams.
We'll handle it if it comes up.
Pagan, don't worry.
I'm sure that smile of hers will
obliterate the suffering we're
about to experience.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] Heero and Quatre
decide to stay in the
Sanc Kingdom,
where Relena promotes pacifism.
But the kingdom is anything
but a place for rest.
The Romefeller Foundation,
angered by more and more nations
declaring pacifism,
attacks the Sanc Kingdom.
Heero, Quatre, and Noin, head to
battle in order to
protect Relena.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 31:
The Glass Kingdom.