[THEME MUSIC]
[NARRATOR:] In the year
After Colony 175,
the leader of the colonies
was assassinated.
Five Gundams were supposed to have
been sent to Earth
to take
revenge.
However, since OZ's
activities in space
took the form of cooperation,
rather than control,
the colonies decided to accept OZ.
In the year After Colony 195,
As OZ moves to take over
both the Earth and outer space,
the Gundams are labeled as rebels
and are isolated from society.
With no place to return,
the Gundams and their pilots are
forced to fight for
a reason to exist
in the ever‐changing world.
What’s going on?
They missed it!
Was that intentional?
Milliardo, there's one other
person who understands me.
Her feelings toward me have caused
her to have split personalities.
The actions you took were
right on the mark.
But then again, what I'm about
to do is also on the mark!
[NARRATOR:] Duo, God of
Death Once Again
[MILITIA SOLDIER:] We're
adjusting the ballast.
Proceed slowly. Easy does it.
[SALLY PO:] Wait.
Get some light on these rocks!
There it is!
It's hardly even damaged,
considering
the battle it's been through.
[MILITIA SOLDIER:] Major Sally.
Some vessels are approaching us,
Sally.
This was just Heero's trick,
discarding his Gundam into the sea
while he heads into space alone.
A mobile suit submarine carrier!
It’s natural that OZ
would come here too.
It's a dangerous job.
Don't concern yourself
about us militia men.
We’ve got our expertise as the
former Alliance's deep‐sea unit!
Prepare to send out
the Pisces now!
Something showing on screen!
Perhaps 01.
Right, send out the Cancers!
[OZ SOLDIERS:] Yes, sir!
All units, open fire!
Propeller sound confirmed!
Enemy mobiles!
They’re what?
Cancer! Cancer! Come in!
[EXPLOSIONS]
What on Earth could he
have been thinking?
Discarding his Gundam like that.
[SALLY] Heero.
The foundation of our future will
be built by these mobile suits.
[TUBAROV:] These are for
mass production.
But don't concern yourself
with cost performance.
Resources in space are unlimited!
What? He’s treating the
Space Colonies
as if they were true colonies
to be taken advantage of!
Let him be.
We'll give him
something to remember.
I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me.
Where do you think you’re
taking that to?
It's the Gundam you took apart
to try and steal our technology.
We're honored.
I’m surprised you’re still
interested
in it even after
reducing it to scrap.
How dare you!
I’ve got no need for it!
Hurry up and get rid of it!
[PROFESSOR G:] As you wish, Mr.
Chief Engineer.
Well now, shall I go on with
making a
mobile suit superior to the
Gundams?
[TUBAROV] Get to work!
[DOCTOR J:] Calm down now!
Quit rushing me!
I've got a whole bunch of things
to take care of right now.
Sorry to keep you.
Yes, there is no point in
just rebuilding them.
[MILLARDO:] You didn't use
to have any problems
with your principles
against war in space.
So why is there a need
for armaments now?
A century has passed
since the times
when the colonies were merely
experimental establishments.
We’ve determined there's no choice
but to avoid battle by arming
ourselves.
[DELEGATE:] This is Sally Po,
formerly a
Major with the Alliance Military.
As an active member of a rebel
organization member opposing OZ,
she has supported and led a
number of their maneuvers.
She may also have the
Gundam 01 and 04.
The Romefeller Foundation
that controls OZ
is the most powerful
entity on the Earth.
I'd say there are problems
with that organization.
However, we wanted to
protect the colonies.
And that's why we've accepted OZ.
We had to decide on the choice
that would
give us the most
safety.
Armed struggle will
continue on Earth.
That struggle has lead us to
choose
this method to protect ourselves.
Those on Earth opposing OZ
think that OZ themselves,
who are keeping the Gundam
engineers captive,
are the only ones who are changing
this world
into a dangerous place to
live.
We've received word those
engineers
have already been executed.
We cannot maintain our
dignity as a nation
unless we augment our strength
and eliminate the possibility of
encountering even more rebels.
Our decision is not
going to change.
Listen, Ambassador Peacecraft.
Please try to understand
our reasoning.
[MILLARDO:] The engineers
have been executed?
That's impossible.
It's this kind of unmitigated
rumor
that we must fear the most.
[NEWSCASTER:] In addition, natural
resources
and parts have been
transported
from the respective plant colonies
as we prepare for mass production
of the latest mobile suits
on the Lunar Plant,
together with support from OZ.
We no longer fear the
possibility of an invasion.
With the help of Commander‐
in‐Chief Treize and Colonel Une,
this will surely prove to
be the beginning
of a new era for outer space.
What BS.
It was them who planted the fear
of war in you in the first place.
[HILDE:] That's not true.
The colonies have suffered a
history of humiliation up til now.
We aren't afraid of any battles
that will allow
the colonies to pick themselves
up.
[DUO:] Who are you?
[HILDE:] My name is
Hilde Schbeiker.
I've volunteered my
services from this colony.
[DUO:] Oh, I get it,
you're an OZ soldier.
It’s easy for anyone to criticize.
The work of the colony's
students speaks for itself.
[HILDE:] Our volunteer work
at the Lunar Plant
best reflects our faith in OZ.
Keep that in mind!
Wow. Is that so?
Then maybe I should apply as well.
The next military exam
is in one week.
Hey, why don't you give it a
try if you like?
Count on it, baby, I'll be there.
[WUFEI:] We're headed to
the Lunar Base.
Are they using us as test
pilots for the new models?
Maybe a target for them.
Even OZ admits we're
pretty lively.
[TROWA:] I’m certain the
objective of OZ
and its mother organization,
the Romefeller Foundation,
was to destroy the
United Earth Sphere Alliance
and take control of the Earth.
Why don't they simply take
over the colonies?
Taking over the defenseless
colonies
should be no more difficult to OZ
than twisting a baby's arm.
Maybe Zechs would be able
to understand.
[WUFEI:] Treize is getting
hungry for mortal combat.
And the overconfident
colonies will soon realize
just how much stronger
Treize really is.
[OZ INTERCOM:] All soldiers
prepare to
board ship on the double!
All soldiers prepare to
We’ll confirm the boosters
and the checklist, and then...
[DUO:] Here you go, sir.
Okay.
Have a nice day.
[HILDE:] Hey you!
Stop right there!
I know you!
What is it? Did you
want something?
I told you that new volunteers
are to apply next week.
I want you to let me look at
that application!
Oh, this?
It's all filled out.
But it's a fake!
You scum!
[DUO:] Comin’ in!
[OZ SOLDIER:] He's taken the Leo!
After him!
Everyone stay calm!
I don't want to start firing this
thing inside the colony!
You won't get away!
My ultimate goal is to
destroy the Lunar Plant
but it's just too far
away from here.
[HILDE:] Stop right there!
It’s her again!
[HILDE:] If you choose to
retaliate,
I'll have to kill you!
Warning shots are meaningless from
those who’ve never even battled!
This one's for the peace
of the colony!
Hang on a second here, I’m
fighting for
the peace of the colony as well!
Got him!
[OZ SOLDIER:] We’ll move in
until it's in target range!
Good, fire!
Sir!
Hey!
We're both fighting for the
colonies, right?
Then how is it we’ve
become enemies?
[HILDE:] Pleading for your life?
I'm telling you! You and I
aren't enemies!
I volunteered and
pledged my loyalty.
I'm prepared to die any time!
You're so intense it
makes me sick!
[DUO:] Get outta here!
[HILDE:] Duo Maxwell.
Who would've thought you
were a Gundam pilot?
Why did you save me?
What are you talking about?
I'm prepared to sacrifice my life.
I don't need sympathy
from my enemies.
Hilde, that’s your name?
What enemies do you mean?
[DUO:] Since when is the colony
an organization fighting a war?
When the Alliance came from
Earth to attack the colonies,
the smiles disappeared from
people's faces.
I've been fighting to help give
back those smiles they lost.
[DUO:] But then I come back to
the colony, and guess what?
The people don't want
their smiles back.
Tell me something.
When did the colonies
become so twisted?
Outer space is affected
by war on Earth.
We can't just sit back
and be taken over.
This is outer space's decision.
Your bravery's commendable.
So where are you gonna take me?
To the Lunar Base.
[HILDE:] You'll be
questioned on the Gundam,
among other things.
[DUO:] That saves me a trip.
You know that I'm planning to
destroy the Lunar Base.
You don't stand a chance.
Why don't you think of
me as an enemy?
I’d never let you destroy
the Lunar Base.
Hate to say this, but you don't
have the skills to be my enemy.
So it's foolish for
someone like you
to even bother risking your
life against me.
But you know, you remind me
of just how reckless I was
when I went down to the
Earth to fight all on my own.
Don't patronize me!
[DUO:] In fact, we're
both foolish.
A soldier can get
killed at any time.
We'll see lots of friends in
the colony lose their lives.
Let's live out our lives believing
in the paths we've chosen.
You've got to be at least that
foolish to make it as a soldier.
Did he tell you anything?
Not a word.
I see.
Hey chief?
When we were fighting just now,
couldn't we have simply
fired a warning shot?
We have orders to kill
rebels when it’s necessary.
That's what wars are about.
Even if it means sacrificing
your own people?
Officer Hilde.
I feel bad about it.
But soldiers always have
to be prepared
to die in order to fulfill
their missions.
[INTERCOM:] Unit Chief, we're
about to arrive at the Lunar Base.
Good.
We'll take the shuttle to OZ's
military establishment.
We need to hand over the prisoner.
[EXPLOSION]
What happened?
[INTERCOM:] The third engine
has caught fire!
It looks like someone on
board was responsible.
Could it be Duo?
And now, the getaway.
Duo!
Hey, that was quick.
You've got good instincts.
I’m about to blow up the hatch.
So step back if you don't
wanna get hurt.
You're gonna do what, Duo?
Stop it, Duo! Duo!
[EXPLOSION]
[CHIEF:] What was that explosion?
What's the matter?
Give me a report!
The mass balance device is busted!
This’ll get me seasick.
Mobile dolls!
Don't you move!
Talk about irony! I made
it to the moon.
I finally made it.
Not too bad a job, if I
do say so myself.
Now hurry up and finish me off!
Though I do hate the idea of
being killed by a machine!
What’s going on?
You fool!
Give your code to prove
you're an ally!
You'll get killed!
I can't do that.
There's no telling who my
allies are anymore.
Duo!
Hurry up and go and do what
you want to accomplish!
Hilde, do you mean that?
I decided to live out my life,
believing in the path I’ve chosen!
Sorry, Hilde.
But this time I'm not gonna
be bailing you out!
I told you, I'm already
prepared to die!
Oh yeah, I remember.
But Hilde...
If you’re gonna do it, just
don't die in vain.
Oh, Duo. I won’t.
[CHIEF:] Hilde! What
are you doing?
Drop your gun at once.
I've got a serious problem
with your conduct!
It's underground, interesting.
I'll get to the plant
directly through this duct.
Hey, there he is!
Hey! Don't lose him!
[OZ SOLDIER:] We believe the
enemy has entered Area B6!
We're in pursuit!
[OZ SOLDIER #2:] Captain!
What is it?
[OZ SOLDIER #2:] We have
word from a colony Unit Chief.
The enemy is trying to destroy
the mobile suit plant!
What?
Get security underground to
stop him from entering!
What the heck? What is this?
[PROFESSOR G:] Who's there?
The God of Death.
[PROFESSOR G:] That
makes four of them.
[DOCTOR J:] Are you here
to kill us, too?
[PROFESSOR G:] Long time no see,
Duo.
So it was you guys!
Then those are...
[PROFESSOR G:] That's right.
They're new models.
Duo, how would you like
to operate one?
[DUO:] When will it be finished?
[PROFESSOR G:] In one month.
You just make sure you
stay alive until it’s finished.
If you do, you'll certainly have
your chance in the spotlight.
[OZ SOLDIERS:] He came in here!
Hurry!
You have got to make up
your mind quickly,
we can not have them
discovering this location.
Gotcha.
Okay, we'll do things
your way then!
[DUO:] Hurry up and get started!
Master O, could you do the honors?
As much as I hate to.
[PUNCHING]
It wouldn't hurt as much if you
screamed out loud, you know.
Yeah.
But Momma told me real men
never scream out loud.
You traitor, coming in here
and trying to kill us.
Is that any way to repay me
for all I’ve done?
We’re not going to let anyone
interfere with our research.
[HEERO:] Botched your mission?
You couldn't destroy the base and
you didn't kill Dr. J and the
others.
How about a little sympathy?
In any case, I’m still glad
I decided to come here.
I’ve got good news.
Your Gundam and mine are being
rebuilt as we speak, you know.
I can hardly wait until
they’re done.
Looks like OZ will be
keeping us alive for a while.
It's a good chance, so
don't die yet.
Don't worry about me, pal.
I have no intention of
dying that easily.
There's the colonies to fight for.
[DUO:] Just watch me.
I’ll become the God of
Death once again!
But right now...I need some sleep.
[TROWA:] I’ve just
completed my mission
to escort Ambassador
Peacecraft on his return.
[UNE:] Thank you.
I'm sure the Ambassador realizes
by now
how firm outer space’s decision
is.
How about from the eyes of
Zechs Merquise?
[UNE:] He has opinions about
this era as well.
The day will surely come
when we’ll battle again.
We'll hear his decision then.
I really don't think anyone
can stop the future.
Not even Mr. Treize.
What I can do, though, is try and
direct the future
towards Mr. Treize’s
ideal.
I can sacrifice my life
for that purpose.
I will fight and try to win..
For Mr. Treize's future.
And also for my own future, yes.
[ENDING MUSIC]
[NARRATOR:] Is destruction the
only path left
for an outer space gone
insane?
Time and time again,
a mobile suit resembling a Gundam
attacks
the colonies that are arming
themselves.
Trowa and Heero head out to face
this powerful new mobile suit.
The pilot is Quatre, cold with
anger and full of deep sorrow.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 24
The Gundam They Called Zero.