[THEME MUSIC]
“Those who have
laid eyes on a Gundam
shall not live to
tell about it.”
Those are the
orders I was given.
There’s a Gundam down here!
Hey, are you all right?
I need a favor of you.
Reload the explosives
for Heero Yui.
Forget that.
Stop worrying about
that right now!
You should start thinking about
what your next move is, kid.
[NARRATOR:] The Sorrowful Battle
[OZ SOLDIER:] We're
currently above
the Filchner Ice Shelf
of Weddell Sea.
We should be at the Barclay
Base in five minutes.
Any signs of enemies
in the area?
[OZ SOLDIER:] Nothing on either
the radar or heat sensors.
[NOIN:] I see.
I guess we’d better expect
Acht's search party
to regroup before
staging an assault
rather than assume they've
given up pursuing us.
That's a wise decision.
So OZ does have
one elite officer.
Hello Colonel Zechs.
I've brought Heero Yuy and Trowa
Barton to you, as requested.
Thank you.
You can call me Zechs Merquise.
Are we supposed
to shake hands now?
No. It's fine.
Heero Yuy, is it?
That’s the same
name as the leader
that kept the space
colonies together.
Is that what your real name is?
Is that your real name
you’re using?
Forgive me.
I guess there's no sense in us
using names from this point on.
We've done our best
to prepare a hospitable
reception for you.
So I hope you’ll try to make
yourselves comfortable.
My mobile suit!
[ZECHS:] Do you like it?
[MEISER:] Colonel Zechs!
The repairs to 01
have been completed.
The only things left
are the operational adjustments.
I'll introduce you.
This is Meiser, who’s in charge
of restoring your Gundam.
How are ya?
All that's left is adjusting
the cockpit to suit yourself.
Meiser's young, but
his skills are top class.
When can we start?
How does tomorrow
morning sound?
That's fine.
Heero Yuy!
Isn’t there something
you’re forgetting
to say to Colonel Zechs?
I will thank him,
but in my own way.
I'll kill Zechs.
That's how I'll
show my gratitude.
[ZECHS:] That'd be fine.
To the soldiers fighting
to protect the colonies,
this battle is no more
than a temporary obstacle.
And I'm a mere stepping stone.
I've never shaken hands
with anyone before.
[NOIN:] I have a feeling that I
must not let either of them die.
Of course not Zechs,
but not Heero either.
[OZ SOLDIER:] I’ve already told
you a number of times.
We've destroyed Gundam 01.
There isn't a single
stabilizer left here.
[RELENA:] I’ll wait
until after I meet
with Colonel Zechs to determine
whether or not that's true.
[OZ SOLDIER:]
The Colonel isn't here.
Then you should let me
meet with Lieutenant Noin,
who was in charge.
I’m sure she’ll meet with me
if you tell her that
I'm Relena Peacecraft.
[OZ SOLDIER:] But as I said...
[HIGH‐PITCHED ALERT NOISE]
[BUTLER:] Forgive me a moment.
Hello. What?
Good, well done!
Relena.
[WHISPERS]
Okay, that's fine.
[NOIN:] Relena's
on her way here?
[OZ SOLDIER:] Yes.
[NOIN:] Even the Peacecrafts
have caught on.
I expect the Romefeller
Foundation’s found out by now.
[OZ SOLDIER:] Please be
very cautious, Lieutenant.
[NOIN:] Thank you, I will.
From now on,
there will likely be
all kinds of people
trying to fly
to the Romefeller Foundation.
Defeating Zechs, who's seen as
the defender of the Gundams,
would be the perfect way to
show loyalty to the Foundation.
The search party's manhunt
could be intense.
But Zechs is
practically OZ's hero,
so why would they
even be after him?
Is the path Zechs is
about to take not wrong?
[GASP]
[ZECHS:] I’m sorry.
I wasn’t listening
in on purpose.
I might have at least a
partial answer to your question.
Over the many years
I spent with OZ,
I started to develop an
aesthetic sense in a war.
A sense that fighters could have
as the only nature they would
acknowledge in each other,
though separated as
enemies and allies.
But those Gundam
pilots are desperate.
They'll battle even if it
means forfieting their lives.
They live the true
lives of soldiers.
I am much too weak.
[NOIN:] That’s because they know
they're fighting for
the colonies!
Zechs, you have
someone to protect too!
[ZECHS:] I don't have any right
being given someone to protect.
But they would probably say
that very thought itself
makes me weak.
There's no need to try
to make battles look good.
If that’s the only type of
battle I’m capable of,
I'll simply be defeated here
and now by the Gundam.
What this is, is war.
Some lessons can only be
learned by risking one's life.
But, Zechs...
Noin.
This battle will take time.
I hope we can fight
without interruptions.
[NOIN:] Leave it to me.
I'll do everything to
prevent the search party
from getting in the way.
Actually, I’m more concerned
about the dignitary
of the Peacecraft.
My dear Imperial Guard.
Zechs.
The most important
person to you is Relena.
You'll fight your best
knowing you have
to protect that girl.
[MEISER:] He doesn't
trust me, does he?
[TROWA:]
It's not that.
He just doesn't want anyone
touching his mobile suit.
That's all.
Yeah, but still.
The self‐detonation
device isn't connected.
[MEISER:] Colonel Zechs
says you won't be needing it.
Zechs had regrets
after their last showdown.
So this time he
wanted to make sure
the fight lasts longer.
[TROWA:] Aren't
you gonna fight
in your own mobile suit?
[HEERO:] I think I’ll use
yours after all.
[TROWA:] How come?
[HEERO:] All of this generosity
is blurring the
focus on fighting.
[TROWA:] I can’t see that
being an issue with you.
No, I'm talking about him.
You're strong.
You really are.
[ZECHS:] I see.
So he'll fight with the 03
rather than the 01.
[MEISER:] But what in the world
could they be thinking
of, Colonel Zechs?
He sees our gifts
as some kind of charity.
But my feelings have
remained unchanged.
Colonel.
Does that mean we should
restore the left arm
of the Tallgeese?
[CHIEF ENGINEER:]
There's still time
to take the supply parts off 01.
[ZECHS:] No, just
leave it as it is.
[CHIEF ENGINEER:] But sir!
This is a continuation
of our last battle.
Tallgeese had its left arm
damaged in Siberia.
So this will be
a valid handicap.
Hey Jim.
I guess that's the difference
between Chief
Engineers and Pilots.
I suppose so.
It’s that kind of pride
that we backstage crew
don’t experience.
No.
I just don’t want
an unfair advantage.
[HEERO:] What time is it?
[TROWA:] 2:32 a. m.
Let me take over.
Appreciate it.
This weight is gonna be tough
for his left arm to handle.
[EXPLOSIONS]
[FIGHTING]
Has it begun?
Yeah, just started.
Has my radar broken down?
[ZECHS:] He's right below!
He's using snow clouds
to cover the heat source.
There!
We’re not gonna die in a
fight of this low caliber.
[MEISER:] We’re nearing
three hours
since the start of the battle!
That's a long time
for a meaningless battle.
[NOIN:] Meaningless?
What do you mean, meaningless?
Am I wrong?
I dunno the details,
but OZ is after you people.
What's the point of two sides
with a mutual enemy
fighting each other out here?
You think it's the pilots' fate?
That's stupid.
You might have a good point.
But they've been out
to kill each other until now.
So naturally they feel
it is some kind of fate.
This battle will go on
until they both realize
it is meaningless.
Are people trying to stop time
in order to find themselves?
Enemies are necessary.
That's the soldier's fate.
[NOIN:] No.
A soldier will be rejuvenated
when he finds
someone to protect.
Sometimes that takes time.
Right now we've lost sight of
how to protect the colonies.
We really can't afford
to be wasting time here.
I'll make sure there
aren’t any interruptions,
so they can get this over.
You mean the search party?
But Trowa, how are you
gonna fight them?
[TROWA:] I’ll just have
Heero return my favor.
[MORE FIGHTING]
[TROWA:] When you
run out of bullets,
click that switch.
It'll make the
left arm lighter.
So you're right out
of fire power now!
A beam saber!
Trowa really went out of
his way for me this time.
Now that's more like it!
[LASER SWORD NOISES]
[MRS. NOVENTA:]
I have no regrets.
That's what happens in war.
A wrong turn in the past
can be painful for everyone.
But you people are still young!
I hope you'll think about
building a new future.
Our family is honored
to have had the opportunity
to meet with you.
[BUTLER:] Relena!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Civilian
aircraft, land at once!
This is a strategic air zone!
Hurry, Pagan!
We mustn't stop!
[BUTLER:] But these
are surveillance suits
from the search party
after Zechs Merquise.
We don't know what
they might do to us!
They won't follow us
to the Barclay Base!
Escape!
I'll try my best, Relena.
[OZ SOLDIER:] The civilian
aircraft is accelerating!
Shoot it down at once!
[OZ SOLDIER #2:]
What the heck?
It’s a mobile suit!
It's a Gundam!
Heero?
[TROWA:] He's
fighting just up ahead.
What are you doing here?
I’m gonna make him stop
fighting with Zechs.
There’s no meaning
to this battle.
I understand.
Then you'd better hurry.
The search party's
becoming more aggressive.
Not working too well,
that left arm.
He's caught on.
You’re being way too kind!
You left that weak
point on purpose!
It’s these showy appearances
that I want to discard
in this battle!
This'll finish you off!
Heero!
Is that Relena?
Heero, I’m here to
deliver a letter to you!
[HEERO:] You're in
the way! Get lost!
[RELENA:] No, I'm staying!
This letter says how you should
live your life from here on in!
It’s your obligation to read it!
[ZECHS:] Princess!
Are you Zechs Merquise?
Princess. Please leave at once.
I must take revenge
for the death of my men.
I hereby order you
under the name of the
Peacecraft family!
Stop this battle immediately!
You've become strong, Relena.
That’s more fitting
for a Peacecraft daughter.
Just see for yourself how
dirty battles really are!
No!
If you're a true warrior
and true knight of Peacecraft,
you couldn't possibly
use such foul play!
[BUTLER:] Relena, there’s a
call from Lieutenant Noin!
[RELENA:] Miss Noin!
I completely misunderstood you.
I thought you were sincere.
How can you just sit by
and watch this fight?
This is neither a
duel nor a match.
They're trying to
kill each other.
Precisely.
I deserve your contempt,
but I can't help it.
Because I believe
in Colonel Zechs.
I'm not about to go interrupt
anything he plans on doing.
Heero! Defeat that man!
Anyone associated
with a foul group like OZ
is an embarrassment
to the Sanc Kingdom!
Go ahead! Kill him!
Stop it! Relena!
[NOIN:] Please stop.
It's a fact that he's
associated with OZ.
And I don't deny that some
mistakes were made, either.
I’m not gonna try
and explain it away
with his love for the
Sanc Kingdom, though.
But listen Relena,
no matter what destiny
awaits you,
you mustn’t do anything
as deplorable
as wishing for the death
of your own brother!
Brother? He's my brother?
[NOIN:] Ever since the
Peacecraft Monarchy
fell to the Alliance. he's had
his heart set on revenge.
Given the difficulties of
assembling power
from within the ruined
Sanc Kingdom,
he chose to join OZ to get
closer to the Alliance
and waited,
donning a disguise
he called Zechs Merquise.
[ZECHS:] My hands
have been stained
with too much blood.
Relena is the appropriate person
to revive the Sanc Kingdom.
[NOIN:] Once OZ brought a
new wave of chaos to the world,
Zechs must've lost the
sense of purpose in his life.
Now he can only find
the soldier in himself
when he fights the Gundams.
That's what this
battle is all about.
Heero lives by his own rules.
And Zechs searching for
the spirit to battle him
on a level playing field.
So once again he’ll be able
to embrace the Sanc Kingdom
and the Peacecraft name.
He's even prepared
to lose his life for this.
I'll keep believing in him.
I want to stay by his side.
No matter what he does
or what he searches for.
You're fond of my brother,
aren’t you Noin?
Yes. I do love him.
[RELENA:] Please watch
over my brother forever.
I don't know if I’m able to.
Colonel Zechs can be
reckless at times.
It must be in the
Peacecraft blood.
A number of attack carriers
are approaching us
rapidly from 3 o'clock!
[OZ SOLDIER:] I believe
they’re from the search party!
How many?
[OZ SOLDIER:]
I’ve confirmed over thirty,
but that's only a
portion of their fleet.
Get all the mobile suits ready!
Prepare to attack them!
They're here!
[TROWA:] Can you hear me,
Heero and Zechs?
There are about
thirty suits in flight.
A hundred if they
unload all Aries suits
from the carriers.
We should be able to handle
thirty each, pretty easily.
[ZECHS:] No, wait!
I'll attract them all myself!
Glory to all the colonies!
No, Zechs!
[ZECHS:] Heero!
We'll meet again to
continue our battle!
[TROWA:] He'll be
one tough guy to fight
from now on.
Yeah, you’re right.
Colonel Zechs.
Our Aries troops are all
prepared to go into battle.
Then take Relena with you
and make your escape.
[NOIN:] Zechs!
Once I know you've
gotten away safely,
I'll surrender myself.
[NOIN:] Then I'm
gonna fight too!
Noin!
Please let me protect
the promising leader
of the Sanc Kingdom!
Allow me to protect her!
I understand, Colonel.
Colonel, take care.
I don't care how it happened.
I'm just glad that
battle's finally over.
The war zone expands
into outer space.
As OZ moves to destroy the
remnants of the Alliance
Military,
it also makes plans
to reconcile the colonies.
Quatre and Duo decide
to head for outer space
to warn the colonies
of OZ's conspiracy.
But the colonies that
had been once their home
declare the Gundams
their enemies.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 17
Betrayed by Home, Far Away