[THEME MUSIC]
[LASER SWORD NOISES]
Heero! Defeat that man!
Go ahead! Kill him!
Stop it! Relena!
Brother? He's my brother?
Glory to all the colonies!
[NARRATOR:] Betrayed
by Home, Far Away
[SOLDIER #1:] I’m getting
nothing from the command tower!
[SOLDIER #2:] We'd better
get out of here too!
Hurry!
[SOLDIER #1:] Yes, sir!
[SOLDIER #2:] Enemy approaching!
Fire!!
[EXPLOSION]
The United Earth Sphere Alliance
had posted their own space
forces to the colonies
and strictly controlled the
freedom of the colony citizens.
After the collapse
of the Alliance,
the Space Forces had
remained in outer space
to further control the colonies.
However, the forces
were overpowered
by the mobility of OZ's space
mobile suits, the Tauruses,
which had been sent
up from Siberia,
and their powers of their space
forces were quickly diminishing.
[LADY UNE:] Soldiers of the
Alliance,
stop this futile resistance.
OZ has come here to bring
peace to outer space.
Now, let us together
welcome a new age.
Taurus Mobile Doll
troops all fine.
Or rather, everything's
in perfect form.
Is that right?
Then return the unmanned
Tauruses back to Barge.
[OZ SOLDIER:]
What about security?
[LADY UNE:] The colonists
consider mobile suits enemies.
I'll have a private meeting
with them later on today.
Over.
Cancel battle orders for
mobile dolls, return to Barge.
Mobile dolls and unmanned
battle weapons, I see.
It looks like OZ is
starting a war
for nothing more
the sheer fun of it.
[LADY UNE:] Today, in the
year After Colony 195,
the citizens of outer space
deserve to live freely.
However, to date,
the United Earth Sphere Alliance
has oppressed you.
The days of the Alliance
are now over.
A new order is being
built on Earth.
And it shall be the
same here in space.
You people are free.
And OZ supports you all.
And that concludes the message
we've received from OZ Military.
Or rather the OZ peace
support organization.
I would like to discuss this
at our next scheduled meeting.
OZ says they're in no
hurry to get our response.
[SPEAKER:] And on that note,
I hereby adjourn this
Colony Conference of Area D.
[SPEAKER:] Thank you very much.
Oh, not at all.
I'm thanking you on
my own right now.
But in the future, the whole
colony will be thanking OZ.
My, you're very young
for a leader.
Couldn't you interpret
youth as potential?
Unlike our ancestors,
we third generation
colonists know OZ
is different from
the Alliance military.
But OZ was part of the
Alliance at one point.
It’s naturally going
to take some time
before the people
can understand.
Troops from the
former Alliance military
are still scattered here and
there throughout the colonies.
[LADY UNE:] Excuse me,
I must be leaving to
liberate the next colony.
[SPEAKER:] Pardon me,
but I didn't catch your name.
Oh yes, that's right.
I am responsible for OZ's
outer space supervision.
And you can call me Lady Une.
One after another,
forces of the former
Alliance Military
unjustly stationed
in the colonies
have been forced to surrender.
With the new and
powerful OZ organization,
operations have commenced
for removal of space mines.
This should result in
the reestablishment
of communication
between the colonies.
I thought that OZ wanted
to take over the colonies
no matter what it took
for them to do it.
[QUATRE:] They do.
And they're using the
dirtiest method of all.
If OZ used force,
then the colonies
would get ready to retaliate.
But they'd be accepted if they
used the guise of assistance.
Most people in outer
space take things easy.
I doubt if anyone will
question OZ's plans.
I think it's time for us
to return to space.
With our Gundams.
[QUATRE:] The Gundams were
built
for the people of the colonies.
We’re the only ones that can
save people from OZ's evil plot.
[DUO:] You're right.
But how do we get into space?
It's important that we
don't get noticed.
[QUATRE:] We’ll do just
the opposite and get noticed!
If OZ is falsely promoting peace
while setting their sights
on taking over the colonies,
they can no longer threaten
the colonies to get to us.
[DUO:] But what if OZ
gives up their facade?
[QUATRE:] That would mean
revealing their true identity
to the people of the colonies.
The present OZ wouldn't see
that as a wise thing to do.
Which means we can
still fight them!
Let's return to space!
I'm extremely impressed with OZ.
All Alliance Military troops in
this area have surrendered.
Are they trying to atone
for Heero Yuy's assassination?
That remark's unfair.
There’s no ground to the rumors
that OZ was even
behind that assassination.
That's what OZ would
have us think!
Honorary Advisor!
Why are you here?
I came because I heard
you were about ready
to accept OZ's agreement!
These days OZ is
hoping for peace.
They're not an organization
to be trusted,
not in the past nor now.
Well, at the very least,
we do know Colonel Une
is trustworthy.
I hear she's executed a number
of aggressive and bloody
plans in the past.
Those are rumors!
She's been overlooking
the situation
and taking on the dangerous task
of removing space mines!
You don’t think it’s
because they
hope to conquer outer space?
It’s a fact that they’re
currently working for
the well‐being of the colonies.
In any case, sir,
OZ is reaching out to us
and it’s all in the
name of peace.
It's not in our best
interest to reject them.
Our policies focus on
our friendship with Earth.
I think we should welcome OZ.
This is truly most annoying.
[OZ SOLDIER:] We’re
entering the space mine area.
I'm sending the
mobile dolls ahead.
Approaching space mines.
This is Nichol.
We're finished with Area P03‐4
Cleaning up outer space
has gotten so much easier.
[SCI‐FI PHONE RINGING]
[OZ SOLDIER:] Colonel Une!
We’ve located a place
thought to be
a Gundam manufacturing factory
in 1307 of Colony D and
have arrested an engineer!
[LADY UNE:] Well done.
I'm returning to
the command tower.
Is this the engineer?
So, I finally get to meet
the commander.
He was trying to
destroy the outer block
of an underground military
equipment factory
where mobile suits
are manufactured.
Destroying evidence?
Unfortunately he’d already
destroyed all the data.
Were you the one who
built the Gundams?
What a stupid way
to ask a question.
Just answer my question!
I think you’ve got a lot to
do with those five Gundams!
Nope.
Not with the other four.
What do you mean?
I designed the best
Gundam I possibly could.
Why in the world would I go and
make four other
variations of it?
Are you saying you only
made one of those Gundams?
Yes.
A masterpiece I called the
Gundam Deathscythe.
The others are a fluke.
The Alliance prohibited
travel and communication
between the colonies, right?
I made only one and only one.
You only made one?
It’s a coincidence
that the others
were made at the same time?
Excuse me, I have a transmission
from Earth, Colonel Une!
They say Gundams 02 and 04
are presently attacking the
Singapore Space Port Base!
[LADY UNE:] What?
Well, so they’re coming
home as expected.
This newest OZ base isn't
anything like their others!
I can't get any
closer at this rate!
Let's go for the HLV equip
for mobile suit delivery!
Quatre!
Don't overdo it, Quatre!
[QUATRE:] It's okay.
We have to fight
so the other Gundam
pilots will figure it out!
Huh?
They'll see us
battling like this
and realize that they need
to go to outer space as well.
That outer space
is waiting for us!
[EXPLOSIONS]
To outer space! Every one of us!
So those are the Gundams, huh?
They are attacking
OZ's base on Earth.
It’s true Alliance Military
oppressed the colonies
and OZ was once
part of the Alliance.
I can understand a
certain colony's feelings
wanting to retaliate
against the Earth.
Yes, but even as we speak,
our peaceful ways are finally
changing opinions
within the OZ organization.
We can't continue to run
around with weapons.
Those Gundams are fighting
because they truly believe
they’re protecting the
colonies by doing so.
So?
They're a nuisance
to the colonies.
We must make our
intentions clear to OZ
before the Gundams
make them uneasy.
The Gundams love the colonies.
The Gundams have chosen to fight
because they love the colonies
more than anyone else.
[HONORARY ADVISOR:] Those
Gundams, they’re desperate.
They're facing their
enemies with limited power.
So why can't we
support these Gundams?
Let's see.
Good.
We made it into the
news all over the world!
Hmm? What's this?
[SPEAKER:] We wish to
publicly announce
a decision made by
Space Colony Area D.
Mobile suits known as Gundams
are currently going around
destroying OZ's facilities.
These Gundams have nothing
to do with Colony Area D.
We hereby declare that if the
Gundams consider OZ an enemy
then we will consider
the Gundams ours!
OZ has been fair to us.
Didn’t take long for OZ and us
to work out our misunder‐
standings toward each other.
We hope that the Gundams
are defeated in this battle.
We further hope that
the other colonies
will follow the example we’ve
set with this declaration.
I expected this.
But even so, it's still
hard to swallow!
[QUATRE:] It's all right, Duo.
We came down to Earth all alone.
It's okay if the colonies
don't understand right away.
I'm just happy knowing
there are others
fighting with the same
kind of feelings that I have.
That's more than enough.
Argh!
[DUO:] Quatre!
Come on, Sandrock, stand up!
It's way too early
to be defeated yet!
[DUO:] Damn it!
At this rate, we're not
gonna make it.
But I still think what we're
doing is probably a good thing.
So why is it we have
to die in a place like this?!
[WUFEI:] That’s because
we are doing the right thing!
We are right. We are!
It's that guy!
The ones who are right
have to be strong!
If this is all you guys can do,
then so be it.
The rest of us will take
over from here.
[DUO:] The rest of you
will take over?
That's more like it!
You'd have a hard time
explaining it to your comrades
if you were defeated here.
[DUO:] They figured out
we need help!
[QUATRE:] They got it! They
all understood our message.
My mission is to wipe OZ out.
If they're headed for
outer space, then I'll follow.
[TROWA:] It's gonna be
a difficult battle.
But right now I’m sensing
peace in our 5 hearts.
[OZ SOLDIER:] Is that the colony
where the fifth engineer
is holding out?
[LADY UNE:] The other four
hardly put up a fight.
But it appears there's
a stubborn one
who’ll try to resist.
[OZ SOLDIER #2:] Colonel.
There's a factory in a block
outside the colony but access
has been completely shut off.
[LADY UNE:] You've advised
him to surrender, have you?
He has ignored
all communication.
Then there's only one answer.
Open fire on him!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Colonel!
We’ve got heat detected
from the colony!
Front‐line troops,
spread out now!
[SCREAMING, EXPLOSIONS]
Two manned suits
have been defeated!
[OZ SOLDIER:] The mobile dolls
are unharmed because
of their quicker reaction time!
[LADY UNE:] Taurus
mobile doll unit,
prepare to fire
special beam cannons!
[OZ SOLDIER:] Colonel, the
beam cannons are too strong!
They'd cause a lot of damage
if they hit the colony directly!
Nichol, since when has OZ
tiptoed its way
through a battle?
We're not trying to
establish diplomatic relations.
We are trying to win a war here!
[LADY UNE:] Damage to the
colony wouldn't be our fault.
It'd be the fault of the rebel
holding out against us.
[DR. J:] Haha, I’m delighted
to hear that OZ
is as mean spirited
as it always was.
In that case, I'll happily
surrender to you.
[LADY UNE:] Good,
I accept your surrender.
Come out at once!
I'm certain that one
day the colonies
will come to recognize
the dark side of OZ.
[DR. J:] But I won't let the
Gundams' battle go to waste!
Hurry up, Quatre!
[OZ SOLDIER:]
A Gundam's operating
the mobile suit delivery
HLV spacecraft!
Surround it!
Those suits will try to shoot us
down when we start to lift off.
Quatre, hurry up!
Don't worry about me.
I'll back you two up
until you lift off!
Have you lost your
mind or something?
We all have to
make it up to space!
[QUATRE:] I know, but that's
why I have to back you up.
To make sure that at least
you two make it into space!
[DUO:] Quatre!
[QUATRE:] Please!
I can't take this much longer!
[WUFEI:] I'm grateful.
The only way to
show my appreciation
is to make it into space safely.
You fool!
And now...
the last choice open to
me is to self‐detonate.
[QUATRE:] What's this?
Are... are you telling
me to get off?
Thank you Sandrock!
I thank you, my dear Sandrock.
[OZ SOLDIER:] Get in there!
Hi!
What took you?
Why didn't you guys
put up more of a fight?
There were just too
many other things to do.
But anyway.
It's been fifteen years.
I'm amazed that all five
of us were successful
in completing our Gundams.
[OZ SOLDIER:] Shall we
have a public trial on this?
[LADY UNE:] No, there are
other ways we can use them.
After all, they are
the engineers
that built those Gundams.
Excuse me Colonel!
Five shuttles with Gundam pilots
have lifted off and are
heading for space!
Prepare to fire low‐orbit
satellite missiles! Right now!
Problems located in the
electric power generator.
[OZ SOLDIER:]
The system’s jammed!
Radio’s down,
and the radar's offline!
What in the world could be
causing all of this to happen?
Hey OZ.
You're going to seriously regret
that you kept us alive.
Not to mention the pilots.
[ENDING MUSIC]
[NARRATOR:] The battle between
the Tallgeese and Gundam
concluded one
chapter of the war.
However, a cruel destiny
still awaited the pilots.
In a mortally wounded state,
Quatre calls
on the other pilots.
Zechs refuses to fight
as a knight of the
Romefeller Foundation.
But Treize then demands
that Zechs die a hero.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 18:
Tallgeese Destroyed