[THEME MUSIC]
[NARRATOR:] The attacks by
the five Gundams
sent out by the space colonies
reflected their
retaliatory intentions.
The Gundams’ target is OZ,
who had masked its
identity within
the mobile suit troops
of the alliance military.
The Gundams had a number
of missions to attack OZ.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken
center stage.
With an army of elite
soldiers at his command,
Treize Khushrenada
carries out his plans
to destroy the
Alliance military.
The battle between the mobile
suits sent to Earth and OZ,
causes the Earth to
shudder violently.
[HOLLERING]
Don't you think your life
is a little too valuable, Trowa?
Self‐detonate?!
What are you thinking?
What would your
mother and father think?!
I’ve said this before.
The only way to live a good life
is to act on your emotions.
[NARRATOR:]
The Order to Destroy 01
[GRUNTS]
[TROWA:] Take better care.
[HEERO:] Huh?
Of your body, I mean.
Here!
That's Sylvia Noventa.
She's in Marseilles.
Are you sure that’s
where you wanna begin?
Yeah.
[NOIN:] Looks like
we're gonna make it.
What's the matter?
The display of Leos, huh?
They've been the main force
of the Alliance and OZ.
[RELENA:] Why was
the Romefeller Foundation
so set on using
mobile suits anyway?
Because people have a tendency
to fear large machinery.
But at the same time they
have a strong admiration for it.
[NOIN:] And mobile suits walk
on two feet .
The Foundation must've
preferred something
resembling a human battle
rather than one played out
with buttons and switches.
There's no formality
when it comes to killing men.
If there were, it would be
in the form of a game
in which people’s lives
were toyed with.
[RELENA:] In war, a frenzied
death is the most honest way.
[NARRATOR:] Only a few know
that the chaos caused by OZ
is all according to the plans
of the Romefeller Foundation.
An assembly of the
Romefeller Foundation
along with many invited guests
was being held on
the outskirts of Bremen.
The Romefeller Foundation was
formed from European royalty.
With their enormous
financial power
and personal connections
the aristocrats poured
their energy
into the development
of weaponry.
They soon provided mobile suits
to the United Earth
Sphere Alliance
while continuing to
increase their own force,
until they staged and succeeded
in the latest coup d'etat.
What's the matter, Lieutenant?
[NOIN:] You'll have
to forgive me.
I guess I can’t really
blame you,
considering what I did last time
I was out in a crowd.
On the other side of that door
are people responsible
for the deaths of
Mr. Darlian and
the Sanc Kingdom.
But today, Relena,
you mustn't do anything.
I understand.
I’ll act in the manner that
will be entirely appropriate
for a sovereign of the
peace‐oriented Sanc Kingdom.
[DERMAIL:] In the past, the
United Earth Sphere Alliance
has requested considerable funds
and assistance for world peace.
And we had no reservations
cooperating with them
to achieve world peace.
[DERMAIL:] However, the
Alliance started seeking
peace through dialogue alone.
Earth has too many disputes that
cannot be settled
through dialogue.
Isn't a system of control what
humanity truly needs?
And that is precisely how
control will be exercised now.
This is the way that peace
can be maintained.
The Alliance lacked the
necessary talent.
Many responsibilities
are required to rule.
But they attempted to run away
from those responsibilities.
The people here have traditions
with which to rule an era.
The world was corrupted
by such imperfect ideas
as equality and freedom.
And now the time has arrived
where we must once
again take control.
[CROWD APPROVES]
I can't believe that OZ is using
these methods
to take over the world.
The Romefeller Foundation
kept such ideas as these
behind closed doors while
hiding its presence
and true agendas
within the Alliance.
OZ took advantage of
the situation, saying
“If the Alliance is unable
to achieve world peace,
then we will.”
So the war will
continue, will it?
OZ has to keep winning
if they’re gonna make a
case for their policy to rule.
The rewards of victory and
OZ's success go hand in hand.
The collapse of the past
system was a revolution
against the kind of bad rule
that created poverty.
So, in order to continue
its rule,
OZ must continue to
win its battles.
And that’s why OZ must
have the strongest
mobile suit troops
in order to exist.
But the Gundams can defeat OZ.
OZ sees the Gundams as nothing
more than a simple menace.
By threatening to directly
attack the colonies.
OZ was successful in completely
silenced the Gundams.
The Romefeller Foundation is
trying to destroy the Gundams
as soon as they're able.
They'll sacrifice lives in
order to gain rule.
But Heero was willing to
sacrifice his own life
to save others.
They'd never understand.
[DERMAIL:] I would like now
to introduce you
to the conqueror
of the Alliance.
This fine gentleman
is nothing less
than a brave knight
fighting for us
in his quest to attain
world peace.
[DERMAIL:] A member of
our Romefeller Foundation
and chief commander of OZ!
Treize Kushrenada!
[KHUSHRENADA:] One may think
OZ's military power rooted
in its mobile suit forces
may result in excess rule.
The word “rule'' is
commonly associated
with oppression and
arrogant actions.
I look at it as
a way of governing
to keep people’s unnecessary
ambitions under control.
God let people run free.
People needs to be ruled,
and that can only be done
if there’s a system of rule
and control that
surpasses God’s.
Since God lets them
do what they want.
I'm sure God would understand
the steps we're taking.
[CROWD APPROVES]
Let's leave.
There isn’t any point
in our staying here.
These people see wars
through rose‐colored glasses.
And nothing we say
will change that.
Relena? Relena?
All of you are very mistaken.
And the Gundams will soon come
to rectify your mistakes.
As ambassadors to those
stifled by this whitewash!
Relena, that’s enough!
No, I'm not finished yet!
Please, I’m begging you, Relena.
Talking to them will
achieve nothing!
Thank you,
Lieutenant Lucrezia Noin.
[NOIN:] My apologies,
Your Excellency.
You’ll have to forgive me;
she's the younger sister
of a friend I invited.
What on Earth was
she trying to get at?
She must've sensed ou
anxiety toward the Gundams.
She's saying “be confident.”
[DERMAIL:] Speaking
of the Gundams,
I want to talk to you
about Zechs Merquise.
I think you're giving him
too much freedom.
Meaning what?
I heard a rumor
that he's reconstructing the
self‐detonated Gundam.
[OTHER GUY:] It's
insane to be fixing
a mobile suit that we’ve always
thought of as such a menace!
[OTHER GUY #2:] That Gundam
should be completely destroyed
to serve as a warning
to all the colonies!
I understand what you're saying,
and if thats what the
Foundation agrees on,
I'll contact Colonel Zechs
and tell him
to destroy the Gundam at once.
[ZECHS:] I’m surprised that
rumors about the Gundam
were so widespread.
[NOIN:] It just shows the
significance of the damage
they've rendered to OZ.
His Excellency didn't seem in
favor of the decision, though.
Can't help it, if they're
orders from above.
[NOIN:] Tell me, Zechs, will
you follow their orders
to destroy the Gundam?
[ZECHS:] How's Relena doing?
[NOIN:] She's a ball of energy.
It's not easy to escort her.
[ZECHS:] How much does she know?
[NOIN:] It seems that Mr.
Darlian, her foster father.
told her quite a lot
before he passed away.
I’ve told her you're a respect‐
able and trustworthy soldier
who was brought up in
the Sanc Kingdom.
I also mentioned to her
that you were the
only one present
when Gundam 01 self‐detonated.
And that you're reconstructing
that Gundam.
Which has lead
Relena to believe that
the pilot of the Gundam,
Heero Yuy,
must've somehow made
it out of there alive.
Heero Yuy... so that's
the name of that pilot.
[NOIN:] Relena appears to
have a connection with him,
much like yourself.
I understand.
Thanks for keeping
me informed, Noin.
[NOIN:] You’re not going to tell
her about yourself, Zechs?
Over and out.
How could I do that?
After all, I’m Zechs Merquise,
part of the organization
responsible for this blood bath.
[HEAVY RAIN]
I could set fire to this castle
and burn it down this minute.
But God would never forgive me
if I did such a thing, though.
[KHUSHRENADA:] Perhaps I'll
be punished as a criminal
for my profanity toward God.
In which case, an appropriate
punishment must be planned.
God's merely an imaginary figure
created by humans.
[NARRATOR:] Marshal Noventa
of the Earth Sphere Alliance
announced his objection
to the expansion of armaments,
which were supposed to be
only a deterrent to rebellions.
He passed a request for arms
reduction and disarmament.
The request was never realized,
because of his untimely death.
However, OZ chose that day
as the dawn of a new era
and lured the Gundams into
shooting down
a shuttle that carried Noventa.
[NOVENTA:] I won't let it
obstruct our peace proposal.
[SCARED SOLDIER:] M...Marshal!
Now, young man...
don’t be foolish!
As a result of this tragedy
the road to peace in the world
may have been lost forever.
[CAPTAIN:] Sylvia! You must
escape from the city at once!
[SYLVIA:] I appreciate your
concern about me, Captain.
[CAPTAIN:] Many soldiers from
the United Earth Sphere Alliance
are still stationed
here in Marseilles.
OZ is likely to follow
through with their plans
to attack those of us
who are still here.
[CAPTAIN:] Up until now,
I thought that the city
could be protected
because the Alliance
has a base here.
But now the base poses the
greatest threat to the city.
It'll be a battleground.
[SYLVIA:] Yes, I know.
It’s just that it’s taken me
longer than I thought
to leave behind memories
of my life here
with my grandfather.
Marshal Noventa
was a very fine person.
He always thinking
about how he could help
to achieve true world peace.
My grandfather's no longer here,
but his heart
will always remain.
I'll live my life remembering
that he's here in our hearts.
Oh, Sylvia.
I'm sorry.
[WARNING CALL]
[SOLDIER:] Captain,
we're under enemy attack!
Is it OZ?
[SOLDIER:] Yes!
We’ve confirmed ten Aries suits!
So they think they can
capture this place
with ten mobile suits
alone, do they?
What’ll we do now?
Don't worry, Sylvia.
We won't give up that easily.
Now get yourself to
a safe place.
Keep the Aries from residential
areas, and commence attack!
Leos, return Aries fire!
[GUNFIRE AND EXPLOSIONS]
Ha, this is like
a guerrilla attack!
We'll destroy every last one
of those Leos! After them!
[GUNFIRE AND EXPLOSIONS]
Now what have I done?
[OZ SOLDIER #1:]
The Alliance's Leos
are retreating to the
underground channels!
[OZ SOLDIER #2:] That’s probably
where the main forces are.
[OZ SOLDIER #1:]
Aries, assemble at once!
The underground channels, huh?
That’s a pretty
obvious decision.
Don't worry about me.
I'd get in your way
with this arm.
We have to make sure that
OZ doesn’t discover
we have a Gundam in town.
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #1:]
There's just a few of us left!
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #2:]
Is this the end for us?
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #1:] Head for
point 211 of the channels!
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #3:] Yes, sir!
[GUNFIRE AND EXPLOSIONS]
[SYLVIA SCREAMS]
Sylvia Noventa!
Who are you?
Aries suits have entered
the channels, sir!
There’s no choice but
to surrender.
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #1:]
Commander!
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #2:]
What's this?
It's a Gundam.
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #3:]
What's it doing here?
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #1:] The
Aries are only a block away now!
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #2:]
We'll stop retreating
and shoot as they come!
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #3:]
Commander??
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #2:] I don’t
know how much time we can buy,
but we have to hold them off
until this pilot returns!
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #1:]
Are we protecting the Gundam?
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #2:] Yeah,
‘cause it'll be our backup!
[GUNFIRE AND EXPLOSIONS]
[ALLIANCE SOLDIER #2:]
Continue fire! Don't ease up!
He's here.
The rest is up to
you now, Gundam.
[OZ SOLDIER #1:] All Leos in the
channels have been destroyed!
We're heading out!
[OZ SOLDIER #1:] It's a Gundam!
[OZ SOLDIER #2:]
What’s it doing here?!
[TROWA:] I’ll get rid of you
guys before the others catch on.
I have no intention
of getting involved
in a battle between
the Alliance and OZ.
However, I just can't afford to
have anyone see my Gundam suit.
[ALLIANCE CAPTAIN:] Five Aries
suits have been wiped out!
Is this a miracle?
Who could this
unidentified mobile suit be?
Whoever it is,
I'm extremely grateful to them.
[SYLVIA:] Heero?
You said your name
was Heero Yuy?
Heero Yuy, huh.
This is my grandfather's
grave, right here.
You said you wanted
to talk to me?
[GASPS]
I was the one who
killed Marshal Noventa.
Huh?
I made a critical mistake and
accidentally shot down
the shuttle that
Marshal Noventa was on.
Killing him and other people
who'd also been
advocating peace.
How could you? What happened?
This is the only thing I can do
for
you right now, Sylvia Noventa.
I can't undo my mistake.
I hope the anger felt by the
Marshal's loved ones and
the regrets of the
Marshal's soul
can be somewhat eased
if you pull that trigger.
You're such a coward!
It’s obvious that you wanna take
the easy way out of this!
This is the only answer
I can offer you right now.
[SYLVIA:] You coward!
You coward!
Try to understand,
I didn't come here to make you
suffer any more than you have.
I'm leaving now to go pay a
visit to your grandmother.
I heard she's living
over in Sicily.
What?
[TROWA:] This is
where it starts.
He goes from one
family member to the next,
seeking their verdict.
Everything this guy does
is completely thorough
and well thought out.
Everything Heero Yuy does.
Wars are nothing
but repulsive killings!
So how is it you can be
so clear‐cut about it all?
It's the only way
I know how to live.
Do it.
[EXPLOSIONS]
Gundam 01 has been destroyed
as per the orders,
Inspector Acht.
[ACHT:] I did see the explosion.
But would you have any objection
to my collecting the remains?
You're not satisfied with the
docs we submitted, Inspector?
I'd rather confirm the remains
with my own two eyes.
And I’ll have to prepare
a document of my own
to satisfy the hard‐liners of
the Romefeller Foundation.
Feel free.
I don't imagine we'll find
anything out of the ordinary.
That man isn't likely to be
careless with details,
Zechs Merquise.
There weren't any
Gundam parts left
at the Lake Victoria base,
Inspector.
That man is fond of
the mobile suits.
I can't see him bending his ways
because of a request
from the likes of us.
What will he gain by opposing
the Romefeller Foundation?
I haven’t got a clue to
what he's thinking.
But Romefeller's is starting
to take over this era.
All we have to do now to
move into the top ranks
is prove that Zechs betrayed
his official orders.
[MISER:] The Inspector is just
trying to find faults with you
so he can score some points
with the Romefeller Foundation.
He's not gonna find
anything that differs
from what the documents
show, though.
I’m sorry I had to involve you
in this performance of mine.
I figured it'd be a real waste
to just destroy the Gundam 01
at this point in the game.
But the bad news is
that we've destroyed
most of the spare parts
to the Tallgeese, Colonel.
In that case I'll just have to
be more careful with it.
No pilot is capable of
harming either the Tallgeese
or yourself, Colonel Zechs.
Not true: there is
at least one man.
[CLOSING MUSIC]
[NARRATOR:] A war is
supposed to be heartless.
But Heero places his own destiny
in the hands of Mrs. Noventa.
Meanwhile, Zechs longs for
a decisive battle as a warrior.
Noin invites Heero to
Antarctica where Zechs awaits.
Inspector Acht pursues them
with his own forces.
The revival of the Gundam
is about to ignite
a new blaze of its own.
Next, on Gundam Wing
Episode 15: To the
Battleground, Antarctica.