[OPENING THEME]
GUNDAM WING
[DOROTHY] I want to be with you
Mr. Milliardo. I want to imprint
this war on my memory.
After all this is going to be
the final battle.
Zero showed me something quite
amusing. [HEERO] Is that so?
I've decided I'm going to join
you. It seems like it would
be the best way
for me to defeat both Zechs and
Treize. [SALLY PO] Wu Fei...
Alright then. Escort Ms.
Dorothy in.
[RELENA] I'm the only one
capable of stopping my brother.
Milliardo...
Target: Earth
An object's approaching us from
behind. [NOIN] What?
[SOLDIER] It appears to
be a shuttle.
An enemy?
No. An enemy would have started
attacking us long ago.
This is Peacemillion here. I
demand the approaching
shuttle respond.
I figured you'd be
there Miss Noin.
Sally Po!
I've brought a couple of strong
allies. How about letting us
come aboard your ship?
[QUATRE] Heero! Wu Fei!
So you made it without
getting shot to pieces.
[WU FEI] Hey do you mind if
we stay for awhile?
No stay for as long as you like.
I'm just glad to have you guys
here visiting with us.
This will be one tough
battle huh Noin?
All battles are tough by their
nature. I'm sure you
already know that.
Sally I feel so powerless. I may
need to depend on you quite
a bit this time.
It won't be me you'll be
depending on. Those kids have
left their doubts behind.
They've found their missions in
life. If you stay on their side
you won't go astray.
Guess you're right.
[DUO] So you brought that
troublesome suit with ya?
You'd have to be insane to pilot
a thing like that.
I never said you had to
pilot it. ‐ Huh?!
You piloted it though!
In that case...
I can handle that suit. I have
experience from piloting Epyon.
Which has the same system on it.
Epyon? You mean the one Zechs
was on? What were you doing
piloting that thing?
I almost forgot what you're
like. You're just about as far
from normal as they come.
Hey we're dividing our
technicians into two groups!
I'll give out the orders
[HOWARD] ... for the Altron
repairs. ‐ That's my Gundam.
Trowa we'll modify your suit for
space compatibility in no time!
[TROWA] Appreciate it!
Even once it gets modified
you're nothing but a sitting
duck to the enemy.
You'd be better off not
returning to the battlefield.
You're probably right.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Good girl. You guys must miss
Trowa since he's not
here anymore.
Hey Catherine! [CATHERINE] Yes?
[MANAGER] You know for our
next performance...
[ANIMALS REACTING]
What's going on? Ah!
[PILOT] Stay where you are! The
OZ space force has taken
over this colony.
What in the world?
[NARRATOR] The surrender of the
space fortress Barge and the
lunar base was a
blow to the OZ space force. OZ ‐
which had reigned as the leader
‐ now had no place to
hide from White Fang and the
antipathy of the
colony citizens.
It stood isolated from
all other forces.
[PILOT] This is a declaration to
the White Fang. We the OZ
space force have taken
over the colony C421. We demand
that you turn over the space
battleship Libra that
you seized from us. Should you
choose to ignore our demand
we cannot guarantee
the safety of this colony or its
citizens. [DUO] Those
OZ guys in ...
... space have really
lost it now.
That's because the White Fang
has pushed them to the edge.
The White Fang didn't
leave them a place to run. And
this is what the result is.
Those weakling guys depend too
much on their mobile dolls. What
else do you expect?
I wonder how the White
Fang will react.
[HEERO] The White Fang's a bunch
of weaklings too. However
Zechs will never
go for OZ's demands. The colony
citizens will be sacrificed.
They'll lose their lives so
Zechs can win. Man can this
seriously even be called a war?
Oh Zechs...
Blasted OZ. Are they really
going to stop at nothing?
We can't just let the colony
citizens die sir!
But sir we can't just hand this
battleship over to them either.
[DOROTHY] Hahaha. Well gentlemen
it looks like this brings
us one step closer
to our ultimate victory.
Doesn't it Mr. Milliardo?
What is that supposed to
mean Ms. Dorothy?
I mean that OZ has made the
foolish choice to take the
colony citizens as hostages.
Now the people's anger will be
directed at OZ and no
one but them.
But we can't just let them die.
Direct the Libra toward colony
C421. We'll fire the main cannon
as we change direction.
[ZECHS] Notify everyone who
should be informed.
[SOLDIER] Roger that sir! ‐Cmdr.
Milliardo! If we use
the main cannon
we' d kill OZ along
with the colony!
This is a war we're fighting
here Mr. Quinze. If we're going
to win we must be prepared
to make any sacrifices
that are necessary.
But I...
The death of the people will be
recorded in the history of
the colonies as
an honorable sacrifice necessary
to achieve our ideals. Oh
it'll be beautiful!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SALLY] Libra has changed
direction. They're heading for
the colony taken over by OZ.
And destroy the whole colony.
That guy's unreal.
[NOIN] Impossible! Zechs would
never do such a thing.
I can understand how you'd wanna
believe that. But right now
he's the leader of
the White Fang.
I know.
Huh?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Leave the vernier adjustments
for later. Let's get a move on &amp;
overhaul the power pack.
Hmm?
It's not ready.
[HOWARD] Hey Trowa what's the
matter? Hey Trowa what do you
think you're doing?
Wait Trowa!
[MOBILE SUIT POWERS UP]
He's really gone overboard.
Let's follow him. Wing Zero is
too dangerous in his state.
[DUO] Right.
You look calm. Aren't you at
least a little bit worried about
your comrade Wu Fei?
Well there is no point in my
interfering this time.
Besides I'm powerless until
Nataku is all repaired.
Calm down. Zero will wipe out OZ
and its mobile dolls.
That'll be easy.
But what can we do about
Libra's main cannon?
We aren't the ones who can
stop that cannon.
[SALLY] What?
Huh Heero? You mean...
Oh Milliardo...
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
I have good news your
excellency. I am quite
certain we'll be able to
retrieve the Libra. We'll have
supremacy in space.
[SERVANT] Are you sure you don't
want to hear him out
your excellency?
[TREIZE] OZ has changed
considerably during the short
time I was absent.
Sir?
From now on I refuse to allow
them to bear the name of OZ.
Give them that message for me.
[MAN] What?! We've been
discharged? How could that be?
We're doing this for
his excellency!
But why? Why doesn't his
excellency approve of our
operations? We cannot allow the
White Fang to claim
supremacy in space.
We have a problem. It's a
Gundam. A Gundam's headed here!
Huh?!
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
[EXPLOSIONS]
[BREATHING]
I really hope you're
alright Cathy.
[CHATTER]
[SOLDIER] Everybody shut up
and form a line!
[MAN 1] What's going on outside?
[MAN 2] I hear a Gundam got
past our defense line.
What? ‐ What's gotten into them?
I don't know but I wish they'd
just leave us alone.
All we wanna do is live our
lives in peace!
[MAN 1] Hey what are you two
talking about? You were
told to keep quiet.
You can't scare us with your
bluffs. That's what we
were talking about.
Manager!
What'd you do that for?
Stop it Catherine. Just be quiet
and do what they say.
But manager...
There's something so
wrong about this.
They're trying to control
everyone with force.
I know. It isn't right.
Everybody's aware of that but no
one will do anything about it
because no one wants to risk
their life. But Trowa's
different. He continually
risks his life as he keeps
searching for the
correct path to lead.
Otherwise he couldn't take on a
dangerous task like being
a Gundam pilot.
[PILOT] Why has a Gundam come
here? Have they joined forces
with the White Fang?
[PILOT] If that's the case then
they've given up on this colony.
You'll regret this.
This is payback for what you
Gundams have done!
[PILOT] What?!
[SCREAMS]
I... I've gotta save Catherine!
[CATHERINE] Trowa!
No!! No!!
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
[BREATHING] [TARGET
SYSTEM BEEPING]
Don't do it Trowa!
[QUATRE] Open your eyes Trowa!
The person you have to
protect lives there!
You were the one that corrected
the mistake that I made.
I can't let you make
that same mistake.
Don't let the Zero control you.
You're too strong to
let that happen!
[PAINFUL GROANS]
[TROWA] The... the person... I
wanna protect... lives there...
[BREATHING]
[QUATRE] Trowa! Trowa
are you alright?
TROWA!
[TROWA] You're right Quatre.
Yeah. We have people we both
wanna protect. Just as you said.
Trowa! Your memory! It's back!
[TROWA] Let's go.
Catherine's waiting for us.
[SOLDIER] What's that? Our
Taurus unit has been destroyed?
Well we'll just have to take the
hostages with us. Have the
Taurus inside the colony
increase security on
the exit hatches!
[CRASH]
What was that?!
[CRASHES]
It's a Gundam! How on Earth?
[DUO] Surprise ya? Sneakin' in
unnoticed is one of
my specialties!
Surrender. I won't allow you to
harm the colony any more than
you already have.
[MAN 1] Main cannon energy
already charged.
[MAN 2] Ready to fire any time!
[MAN 3] Wait a second! A
civilian shuttle's approaching
from one o'clock.
[QUINZE] What?!
Milliardo. It's me Relena.
[DOROTHY] I knew you'd be coming
Ms. Relena. But you've come too
late to make a difference.
Listen Milliardo. I'm convinced
that you're making a
huge mistake.
[ZECHS] Stay away Relena.
[RELENA] I'll do no such
thing Milliardo.
When Libra's main cannon is
fired your shuttle will be
destroyed. You'll simply be
wasting your life.
I don't care if my life is
wasted. But at least let me say
this much to you please.
We both bear the Peacecraft
name. As such aren't you
embarrassed? Brandishing huge
military power and controlling
people as you are.
Is that all that you
have to say to me?
Wait Milliardo! ‐ Fire the
cannon. Start the countdown
now. [SOLDIER] Yes sir!
[DUO] We've saved the colony!
Tell White Fang to
cancel their attack!
There won't be any need. What
you guys just did was
meaningless.
[DUO] What?
The target of Libra's main
cannon was never really that
colony in the first place.
What? Then where were they...
no... you mean?
[MAN] 10 seconds to fire off
the main cannon.
Milliardo! Is there no way to
stop you from attacking the
colony? God will never
forgive you for something like
this Milliardo. I beg you.
Try and come to your senses.
I have come to my senses.
[SOLDIER] 3... 2... 1 ... zero!
Milliardo!
Fire the main cannon.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
He missed!?
Was he just bluffing?
No. He's on target.
Libra's target is the Earth.
[EXPLOSIONS]
[DUO] There's no
turning back now.
Maybe we are
powerless against him.
[TROWA] Perhaps...
[CATHERINE] I believe in you.
And I'm sure you people
understand. Please don't allow
these miserable wars to exist.
Please build a peaceful
world for all of us.
That was splendid! After that
attack the people will shudder
at the mere thought
of our tremendous power. The
test of the main cannon was
a great success.
That was no test. It was an
official challenge to
Treize and the Earth.
Yes of course it was.
[QUINZE] We've got an overload
in the main cannon
control circuits.
[QUINZE] They're checking it
over now. ‐ Make it fast. We're
expecting our enemy.
Our enemy? Who do you mean?
The most annoying and fearful
enemy in the universe:
The Gundams.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR] A battle program is
developed based on the
Epyon system.
The mobile dolls loaded with
this system prove to be more
than the attacking
Gundam pilots can handle. Heero
tells Quatre to repay the
people in the colonies
by conquering the Zero system.
Allowing Quatre to successfully
execute their plans.
Next on Gundam Wing episode 44:
Go Forth Gundam Team.