[OPENING THEME]
GUNDAM WING
[NARRATOR] Space fortress Barge
‐ a symbol of OZ's domination ‐
surrenders into the hands
of the White Fang.
As a result the map of power in
space is drastically rewritten
with Milliardo Peacecraft now
the leader of outer space in
both name and reality.
Meanwhile on Earth – With Queen
Relena at the helm the
Romefeller Foundation is
on its way to forming an
unarmed World Nation
which has realized
total pacifism.
But with Treize Khushrenada's
return Relena is relieved
of her duties.
Battleship Libra
[NARRATOR] The year is
After Colony 195.
The delicate situation between
Earth and space causes
tensions to increase.
Lt. Nichole. Glad you're OK,
sir.
Hardly "OK." There were
only 18 survivors.
Unfortunately that's all I was
able to bring back from Barge.
What's that, Lieutenant?
We survived in dishonor just so
we could bring her back
here to the Earth.
[NICHOLE] Please, you must take
her to his excellency Treize.
[NURSE] Her bullet wounds have
completely healed but she's
still in a coma.
My dear Lady. I'm glad you
made it back home.
I can't tell you how good it is
to be able to see you again.
You never left my heart
for a moment.
But Lady... I want you to see
how I handle things now.
A fantastic battle is about to
commence between
space and Earth.
And it's sure to end the
pathetic history
mankind has created.
A star role in this final scene
would be too much of a burden
for Relena Peacecraft.
I must take on the role as the
leader of the
Romefeller Foundation.
That's right.
She can take on the role of
establishing the new history
we're about to lay out
for her. Relena Peacecraft shall
be the new hope for the
people of the Earth.
[TREIZE] I'm hereby making an
announcement to the
leaders of the world.
What's the purpose of our World
Nation's existence?
The previous sovereign, Queen
Relena, said it was
“true peace,”
but were the people able
to live in peace?
The answer to that is no. People
continue to live in uncertainty
and feel threatened.
And why is that?
Because an armed organization
calling themselves White Fang
is challenging us to a war. We
mustn't allow this
tyrannical behavior
they've exhibited towards us.
I say to the leaders of the
world. No, I say this to all
the citizens of the
World Nation: Now's the time to
unite as one force and fight
against this threat
from outer space. And then our
victory over them
shall earn unity
and peace for the Earth. Is that
not our mission in this life?
[THUNDEROUS APPLAUSE]
[TREIZE] Don't laugh at this
Lady. I have no choice but
to do some acting
if I'm going to help the people.
[SPACESHIP SOUNDS]
[RELENA] This is the third time
I've seen the Earth from space.
Father: You never stopped hoping
for peace between the
colonies and Earth.
I don't know if I can follow
in your footsteps.
[SOLDIER] How are you
feeling Ms. Relena?
Very well thanks.
We've got a little while yet
before we reach the
Libra battleship.
Try to get yourself some rest.
I'll do that. Sorry to
trouble you like this.
No problem.
[RELENA] Relena you have to have
courage if you're going to save
the beautiful Earth.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[PILOT] Those damned
White Fang troops.
It doesn't look like they're
about to let us get away.
[PILOT 2] They have no lunar
base and Barge is gone.
They've got no place to go but
they still choose to betray us!
[PILOT 3] They used to be part
of the Treize faction.
Once Treize becomes
the leader of the World Nation
it would be too awkward
to stay with us.
[PILOT 2] Soldiers shouldn't
worry about principles
and opinions.
[PILOT 3] It's a pity they
fail to realize that.
[PILOT] If we can just take out
one of them we'll be
reducing their force.
This will show my loyalty
to his excellency.
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
[GUNFIRE]
This is it!
That's Gundam 05!
It's coming here! ‐ What?
[SCREAMS]
[EXPLOSIONS]
[PILOT] Send out all the Virgos!
Set target to Gundam 05!
I'll check and see whether or
not your actions are justified.
If you guys are justified then
you'll defeat me!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Is that it?! Don't expect that
to defeat me. And you won't even
come close to Treize!
So that's it. So that's how the
Gundams fight their battles.
That's the ideal his
excellency spoke of.
[GUNFIRE]
Come on! Now is your chance if
you wanna get me!
Don't underestimate
your battles!
[SHIP] Lunar base! This is the
pursuit unit. We're fighting the
Gundam at point 09!
Send reinforcements!
Thanks Gundam. I've learned a
lot watching you.
I have seen the truth in your
fighting. I thank you.
What is he doing!?
Gundam: You're correct. White
Fang and OZ are mistaken.
My only regret is not being able
to tell that to the others.
[EXPLOSIONS]
[WU FEI] Irregularities in the
drive system. Left arm immobile.
Operational abilities down
in every segment.
Nataku we cannot afford to bite
the dust at this stage.
There are still too many fools
here in outer space.
[ELECTRICAL SOUNDS]
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[NARRATOR The nearly complete
battleship Libra is a
major threat
to the people on Earth. While
anxiety increases among the
people the new leader
Treize Khushrenada fully
utilizes his leadership
abilities to either do away
with or take over all
retaliatory forces.
In order to dispel their fears
against space the people
unite under Treize.
But their fears become so strong
that it hastens their
preparations
for battle against
the White Fang.
[ALARM BEEPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[QUINZE] Commander Milliardo our
Libra is finally complete.
Good. Assemble the entire crew
in the main hangar.
I want everyone to hear my final
announcement to Earth. ‐
Very well then sir.
[ZECHS] What we're doing really
doesn't reflect our
personalities...
... does it Treize?
Hmm...
It's been awhile.
You've been fighting
all this time?
My exact words to you.
[WU FEI] I saw the suit Zechs
Marquise piloted. Are
you using it now?
[HEERO] Yeah. [WU FEI] How
about the other one?
[HEERO] That's Trowa's. But it
won't be of much use until it's
upgraded for battle in space.
I see. And where are you headed?
Libra's in the
opposite direction.
[SALLY PO] We're headed for
Peacemillion* where Noin's
waiting for us.
She's already there with the
three other Gundam pilots.
Don't tell me you wanna get out?
We're running out of fuel fast.
Aren't you afraid I might take
over this shuttle and fly it
straight to Libra?
Good point. I never even
thought of that.
But on Peacemillion there are
supplies as well as
engineers who can
repair your Gundam. You can go
and attack Libra any
time after that.
So you guys want me to join you?
You can use Peacemillion any way
you wish to be true to your
sense of integrity.
I thought I was giving you an
offer you couldn't
possibly refuse.
[SALLY PO] Wu Fei... ?
Thanks for your kindness but I'm
not making any deals.
[SALLY PO] Wu Fei...
Just drop it. He does
things his own way.
[SALLY PO] It certainly
looks that way.
[ALARM BEEPING]
[SALLY PO] The White Fang's
mobile doll carriers?!
Looks like their
reinforcements have arrived.
Yeah and they've already
surrounded us! ‐ I see.
How many?
[SALLY PO] Judging from those
carriers? They've probably got
ten Virgos on each.
So 40 mobile dolls?
Shouldn't be a problem.
It is me they've come
looking for.
You're not using your head.
You'd be committing suicide
with your Gundam.
[WU FEI] I don't care.
‐ Take Zero.
What?! [SALLY PO] Heero...
[WU FEI] Take Wing Zero?
[HEERO] Yeah but don't get
disillusioned by the
cockpit system.
[WU FEI] Tell me Heero why
are you doing this?
[HEERO] While you're piloting
the Zero it'll tell you who
your true enemies are.
Well let's give it a try.
Are you sure about
lending him the Zero?
All the Gundams were built based
on the Zero suit. He has the
right to pilot it.
Come on Zero show me what you
got! Let's see just
what you can do...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Ah!
The road I'm taking is the
correct choice.
If you're telling me that I'm
wrong
then use all the power
you've got and try
and stop me...
Ugh... Ah...
Ugh! Oh no!
I can fight on my own! I'll keep
on fighting alone until
the day I die!
Is that Treize?
[WU FEI] Zechs?
[EXPLOSION]
[SCREAMS]
[ZECHS] The Earth's World Nation
is claiming that unity
will achieve peace.
I never dreamed that I'd hear
such rubbish from Treize. I'm
sure that none of you have
forgotten about an organization
that existed on Earth called
the Allied Forces
of the United Earth Sphere
Alliance. Now did that
ridiculous organization
eliminate wars and make world
peace a reality? Of
course it didn't.
Under the guise of peace and
justice the alliance came
to the colonies
with its overwhelming military
force. If we truly want to
eradicate wars it cannot
be achieved by simply uniting
nations. It's a problem that
requires an end to
earthlings. Because as we all
know earthlings have
fought since ancient
times when our ancestors first
stood upright. Battles
between human races
eventually became battles
between countries and over
thousands of years
since the dawn of time we have
continued to write our
bloodstained history.
There's no reason for this other
than the simple fact
that fighting
is a part of human nature.
[TREIZE] Milliardo....
you're not mistaken.
Then we have no choice but to
give up? No that's far
from the truth.
That's because there are some
human beings that
possess the power to
overcome their own base
instincts. [RELENA] Milliardo...
No way! I wanna keep fighting!
[ZECHS] I'm sure you've noticed
by now. The citizens of
the colonies are a
new breed of humans. With the
ability to gain true peace by
controlling their instincts to
battle. The colony citizens
have lived their
lives in space where earthlings
aren't welcome. And the
people of space know
through experience just how
meaningless these
tragic battles are.
[WU FEI] Is that my future?
With them?
So my path will become the
same as theirs?
[ZECHS] Understand that the
colony citizens are
preoccupied with just living
in outer space and they don't
have the ability to fight. Then
why did we stand up
on their behalf? Because the old
breed of mankind who
loves to battle
remains on their comfortable
Earth &amp; tries to conquer the
defenseless colonies.
It has been 200 years now since
our people started living in
space. Isn't it about time
that we put an end to this
history filled with disputes? To
accomplish that we have
to eliminate the hotbed of all
these battles: The place
we call Earth.
My enemies are Milliardo
Peacecraft and Treize
Khushrenada. I will defeat them.
That's what I must do.
Of course we don't intend to
kill needlessly.
We have no choice but to fight
him. At the very least we can
say we rate humanity
a little higher than he does.
With this in mind I once again
announce to Treize Khushrenada,
sovereign of the World Nation,
that we demand the Earth
be eliminated from the universe.
If you cannot abide
by this demand
we'll have no choice but to
start a war to end all wars.
[HEERO] You're back early. Zero
showed me something
quite amusing.
[HEERO] Is that so?
I've decided I'm going to join
you. It seems like it would
be the best way
for me to defeat both Zechs and
Treize. ‐ Wu Fei...
Now get the Libra started.
‐ Roger!
[BEEP] Huh?
What? [SOLDIER] It's an
unidentified shuttle.
How should we handle it?
[DOROTHY] This is Dorothy
Catalonia. Hello
Milliardo Peacecraft.
It's such a pleasure to see you
again. I hope you
remember how you and I
played with Mr. Treize back when
we were just children.
Fire. [SOLDIER] Huh?
[ZECHS] That shuttle belongs to
Romefeller. Shoot it down.
[SOLIDER] Roger.
Once upon a time there was a
person with two names. That
person was the direct heir
of a pacifist nation but he wore
a mask and changed his name
to take revenge
against those responsible for
the nation's collapse. He
soon became the
legendary hero of an army. Today
that person says he will
punish foolish
earthlings. What has made
him go this far?
And can one call this an act of
pacifism? Or are these the
instincts of a hero?
[SOLDIER] We're locked
onto the target.
It's possible that this person
actually dislikes pacifism. Or
maybe he dislikes
his sister who keeps believing
in their father's pacifist ways.
I guess nobody
really knows what his true
intentions are. I want to be
with you Mr. Milliardo.
I want to imprint this war on my
memory. After all this is going
to be the final battle.
Alright then. Escort Ms. Dorothy
in. [SOLDIER] Huh?!
[DOROTHY] Thank you very much
Mr. Milliardo. I promise to
never leave your side
under any circumstances.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[RELENA] I'm the only one
capable of stopping my brother.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR] Zechs joined the
White Fang to put an end to
the warring history
of mankind. But very few know
his real intentions.
Noin, Relena, Heero, and the
other Gundam pilots
watch in horror
his one last act of faith which
can only be regarded as
a foolish act.
Next on Gundam Wing episode 43:
Target: Earth.