[OPENING THEME]
[CHIRPING BIRDS]
[SOLDIER:] I'm terribly
sorry your excellency,
this country road will continue
for some distance.
No, I'm actually perfectly
satisfied with this beautiful
display of nature.
[TREIZE:] And there's no need to
worry yourself about me,
I'm a defeated man
and no longer your leader.
Sir.
Does all this area belong to the
Romefeller Foundation as well?
[SOLDIER:] Mm‐hmm
[TREIZE:] Initially, the
Romefeller Foundation used it's
financial power to protect
this environment.
[TREIZE:] My support for that
attitude is precisely
why I built the
"Specials" unit within the
United Earthsphere Alliance.
But then those young
warriors with
rebellious wings placed
themselves before us.
Passing Destinies
[TREIZE:] Gundams. The mobile
suits made from Gundanium alloy,
and sent from the colonies.
The high level pilots of these
Gundams soon challenged me.
My name is Wu Fei.
I'm Treize Khushrenada.
The duel is mine.
Kill me.
[TREIZE:] That strength and
bravery was exceptional.
I was moved by every action they
took, and could not
remain still.
[TREIZE:] I'm sure it was the
same with you Zechs Marquise.
However you too should be
fighting with a pure heart to
achieve your goal.
[GUNSHOT]
Set the Sanc Kingdom free from
the grasp of the Alliance!
[NOIN:] All mobile suits have
left the carriers!
[ZECHS:] Then I'll
leave as well.
I'll be backing you up!
Concentrate only on achieving
your mission Lieutenant Zechs.
I'm totally focused.
[SOLDIER:] The new type of
mobile suit is approaching fast!
[TECHNICIAN:] Direct all laser
cannons at that suit!
[EXPLOSION]
[ZECHS:] It took me 13 years to
return to these grounds.
Father, forgive your son.
[ZECHS:] There's been much
bloodshed along the way,
and I've only been able to live
a lifestyle that counters
your teachings
based on the principles of
total pacifism.
My hands, they are too
stained with blood.
I'm completely unfit to lead the
Peacecraft monarchy.
[ZECHS:] But I'm sure that she'd
be able to lead the country in
the manner you'd intended.
I will fight to make
that happen.
I have failed you.
Please forgive me.
[TREIZE:] By appearing on the
center stage of history,
we steered the times in the
right direction.
The remaining frontier
is outer space.
[TREIZE:] Lady Une, I'm leaving
outer space in your hands.
Explain our love to the
people of the colonies.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
I'm sure they'll be able to
understand us, if you greet them
with your affection.
[UNE:] In the year After Colony
195, the United Earthsphere
Alliance collapsed.
However, the Alliance's forces
remained in space.
Being in charge of outer space,
my mission was to subjugate
these forces, free the colonies,
and allow them to
become independent.
[UNE:] Once this was
accomplished,
we should have achieved Mr.
Treize's ideals and our
ideals for OZ.
Which would have been the case
if it there had been no
conflicting opinions between Mr.
Treize and Duke Dermail.
[UNE:] The Gundam pilots became
witnesses to the
changes in history.
[SOLDIER:] Excuse me, I have a
transmission from Earth,
Colonel Une.
They say Gundams 02 and 04 are
presently attacking the
Singapore Space Port Base!
I'm returning to the
command tower.
Hurry up Quatre!
Don't worry about me! I'll back
you two up until you lift off!
Have you lost your mind or
something? We all have to
make it up to space!
[QUATRE:] I know! That's why I
have to back you up,
to make sure at least you two
will make it into space.
Quatre!!
And now, the last choice open to
me is to self‐detonate.
What's this? Are you telling me
to get off? Thank you Sandrock!
I thank you, my dear Sandrock.
[UNE:] But there was neither
glory, nor praise to greet them
when they returned to
outer space.
All they received was isolation,
and a cruel destiny as
rebellious figures.
[EXPLOSION]
I'm afraid we're probably
going to have to
considerably restrict your
activities here, sir.
For defeated men like myself,
restrictions become the
foundation for a new strength
But in my case I feel much
freer being restricted.
Perhaps up until now I wasn't
able to experience freedom.
[TREIZE:] Perhaps this latest
action of mine has allowed me a
chance to step back,
and re‐evaluate myself.
[TREIZE:] Just like you overcome
the ordeal I put you through
Zechs, to earn your freedom.
[ZECHS:] Treize, stop
following me around.
[EXPLOSION]
And now, I cannot be your
friend anymore.
[ZECHS:] Farewell Treize.
[TREIZE:] After you left, with
Chief Engineer
Tubarov at the helm,
the Romefeller Foundation
completed those mobile dolls,
that are incapable of feeling
the beauty or sorrow
of a battle.
[TREIZE:] Romefeller used them
in their attempt to rule the
Earth from outer space.
As one who looks for meaning
in human battles,
I couldn't accept the
Foundation's way of thinking.
[TREIZE:] Zechs... Without you,
OZ ends up allowing worthless
actions, by worthless people.
[DERMAIL:] Very nicely done
Treize Khushrenada!
Outer space is now close
to accepting OZ.
[TREIZE:] So it seems.
And Colonel Une's achievements
have been impressive.
She succeeded in forming
friendly relations with one
colony after another.
The sense of independence built
by forming a nation will trigger
the mindset to develop
productivity and defense.
This leads to the nation
becoming militaristic
which means that every country
on the Earth will jump
into OZ's arms
practically begging to be
governed by us.
It's beautiful Treize. You've
made outer space a member of the
Romefeller Foundation.
[TREIZE:]The living environment
of the colonies is bogus, as
is their pacifism.
They may only be a hotbed,
giving rise to
countless battles.
[TREIZE:] Zechs, or rather,
Milliardo. Had you
already realized that?
The new system, since OZ and the
colonies became united, has
had a considerable
influence on Earth.
On behalf of my nation, I've
come here so I might find out
more about this situation.
Your nation?
Yes, my nation. I've come here
from the Sanc Kingdom, my name
is Milliardo Peacecraft.
Oh, his excellency has had ties
to the Sanc Kingdom
since his youth,
but I'd heard your nation was
recovering from it's strife that
was caused by the wars.
As an individual I think I
understand the
implications of war.
So I thought I could give advice
to the space colonies desiring
their own military power.
There are quite a few ways in
which to obtain peace
for oneself.
I'm sure that between what each
of us has learned, we'll find
the best direction to take.
You might very well be on the
right track to peace,
Representative.
[TREIZE:] My beloved Lady. You
were right all along.
[TREIZE:] As long as mankind
exists in this world, there will
always be battles.
And denouncing battles will
never lead to peace.
It's natural for this world to
continue fighting.
Oh Mr. Treize.
[TREIZE:] Zechs and the Gundam
pilots are making an effort
to construct a new
future as we speak.
Those that fight have a
sense of satisfaction.
[TREIZE:] And those in actual
combat are not perceived
as being tainted.
A life is too precious to
be replaceable.
It's because one faces an enemy
and risks their own
precious life,
that amid all the sorrow, a
warrior's soul will shine
with nobility.
Tag along, on my
journey into hell!!
[TREIZE:] Pure and genuine
Gundam pilot, having repeatedly
seen the way you've fought,
I couldn't help but feel
inspired. You changed
something inside me.
Even altered my destiny.
Nataku, you and I have to become
a whole lot stronger.
[TREIZE:] The foolish Romefeller
Foundation removed the human
aspect from battles.
I might've suddenly found myself
in a position where I must
personally bury OZ.
However the times have entrusted
the pilots with destiny itself.
[TREIZE:] Young warriors, what
do you see beyond this dark
mass of confusion?
[UNE:] They continue to fight.
The youngsters who will
change the times.
[EXPLOSION]
Treize is hoping that we will
both put up a good fight!
There's no choice left
but to battle.
Without fighting, nothing
can be created.
[ZECHS:] What's this?
[ZECHS:] Treize.
[TREIZE:] Zechs Marquise, or
rather, my eternal friend,
Milliardo Peacecraft,
OZ is changing and I have found
that I am sorely
lacking in power.
Romefeller's way, or rather the
path that mankind is taking,
is just too selfish.
[TREIZE:] I never expected
their increased power
would result in them abandoning
the true heart of humans.
Milliardo there's one other
person who understands me.
[TREIZE:] Her feelings toward me
have caused her to have
split personalities.
Please save this
unfortunate Lady for me.
Ahh!
I'm going to fight for Treize,
to help realize his ideal!
[ZECHS:] Treize, I've
got no power.
In the confusion of all these
battles, I'm still only able to
walk the path of a soldier.
Take me to the Fortress Barge,
now.
[UNE:] That's when I started
realizing that the
purpose of battles
isn't limited to making
ideals into reality.
I know this is what Mr. Treize
was trying to make
me understand.
[HEERO:] Botched your mission?
You couldn't destroy the base
and you didn't kill Doctor
J and the others.
How about a little sympathy. In
any case I'm still glad I
decided to come here.
I've got good news.
Your Gundam and mine are being
rebuilt as we speak, you know.
I can hardly wait until
they're done.
[DUO:] Just watch me. I'll
become the God of
Death once again.
But right now, I
need some sleep.
[TREIZE:] Even if the space
colonies no longer have a
reason to retaliate.
And even if the pilots are
captured and stripped
of their suits,
those Gundam pilots will
continue to fight.
[TROWA:] Hey! Quatre!
What's going on here?
[QUATRE:] Trowa... Outer space
has gone crazy. I'm gonna use
this Gundam to destroy it all!
Tell the other for me... tell
them to stay away from me!
[QUATRE:] I'm telling you not
to get any closer!!
[TREIZE:] What strong will.
And what purity.
Yes, we must fight
against each other.
[TREIZE:] But our desire to
fight is the same.
[QUATRE:] That's it then.
Goodbye Heero.
[HEERO:] Trowa, the Vayeate's
about to explode, get out now!
[QUATRE:] Trowa!
[QUATRE:] Trowa!!
[TROWA:] We have to
acknowledge the facts.
The five of us have become
nothing more than redundant
soldiers, Quatre.
[EXPLOSION]
Trowa!!!
[APPLAUSE]
Duke Dermail, I am sorry but I
cannot support the
Romefeller Foundation in the
path it's taking.
What?
[TREIZE:] What's important for
mankind is not absolute victory,
but his attitude
toward fighting.
An era constructed by soulless
weapons known as mobile dolls,
will become an embarrassment to
future generations.
[TREIZE:] The traditions you
value so highly,
would appear blurred
alongside those five
genuine warriors.
‐[QUATRE:] Heero?
[QUATRE:] Heero!
[DERMAIL:] So you're saying that
you want the Romefeller
Foundation headquarters
to take OZ out of your control?
[DERMAIL:] I hereby confine you
to the Romefeller
Foundation headquarters.
[UNE:] I've come to a decision.
I'll look over those young men
who shine in the battlefield.
And I'll love them.
[GUN COCKS]
I fail to understand just what
you are getting at.
And that is exactly why you and
I will be enemies.
Shall we escape?
Afer we pay them back, eh?
[GUNSHOT]
[TREIZE:] Lady Une, my love.
Rest in peace.
[TREIZE:] Between the far
distances of the shining stars,
I continue to pass by
numerous destinies.
Time has passed at a tremendous
pace. From a period I remember,
long ago.
[TREIZE:] Operation Nova. I
can't imagine the Romefeller
Foundation allowing
the rebellious actions of the
soldiers that continue
to support me.
And now they've sent Virgos,
mass produced mobile dolls,
to Earth, in their quest for
complete control of the Earth.
But right now, I have no right
to express my opinions on this.
Am I right? Heero! Let's
go to the Earth.
[PO:] There it is!
What on Earth could he have been
thinking, discarding his
Gundam like that?
[PO:] Heero, the foundation of
our future will be built by
these mobile suits.
[TREIZE:] And now, the casting
for the actors is almost
complete,
as we begin
the third act.
All that's left, is to wait for
the curtain to rise.
[UNE:] Everything is proceeding
just as you planned Mr. Treize.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] Outer space rushes
aimlessly into a
period of battles.
Heero and Quatre arrive on Earth
and become targets of
Romefeller's plan to execute
the Gundam pilots.
Without any time for rest, Heero
heads to gather information
for his next battle.
when he hears of Sanc Kingdom,
Relena's home country.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 29:
The Heroine of the Battlefield.