[OPENING THEME]
GUNDAM WING
[QUATRE] This is no time to be
fighting! It's too dangerous to
stay on this battleship.
Quatre Raberba Winner.
I thought so.
You're by far the most misguided
one out of all the
Gundam pilots.
[NARRATOR] Takeoff
Into Confusion
[BATTLE SOUNDS]
Move it!
[GUNFIRE]
That's him.
Gotta do better. I'm over here.
Silence you!
There was a time when battles
could be won and lost with the
mere push of a button.
and these mobile dolls are the
absolute root of that
detestable &amp; hateful spirit.
And their extension is that
Libra ship over there.
[TREIZE] When wars are
dehumanized both victory and
defeat become miserable.
And God no longer lends
a helping hand.
Enough with the fancy speeches!
Too many people have died
for nothing because
of you and the battles
you've fought!
If you're gonna fight anyone
then fight me and no one else.
[TREIZE] You're
absolutely right.
[WU FEI] Are you prepared for
the worst Treize?
Of course I am but this time I
won't go easy on you.
Enough talk!
[GUNFIRE]
It seems that I've defied death
a number of times up until now.
This time will be no different.
[DUO] So what've you got
up your sleeves?
Well the first thing we want you
to do is to take us over
to Peacemillion.
[DUO] To Peacemillion?
Zechs will certainly have his
way unless we do
something to stop him.
We want to change Libra's orbit
but in order to do so we have to
board Peacemillion.
When you say “Zechs' way” you
mean he's really...
That's right. He's targeting
Earth to the very end. We'll be
able to atone for our sins
the moment we can put a stop to
his maniacal schemes
and evil plans.
Alright then. Follow me.
Have you finished calculating
the wave course yet?
[PILOT] Yes. We can enter
Earth's atmosphere if we
continue on the present course.
There's a 69% chance that we'll
collide on land in the
northern hemisphere.
The energy that'll be released
is estimated at about
6000 megatons.
Did you hear that information
Commander Milliardo?
[ZECHS] That'll be
plenty Quinze.
If the Peacemillion and Libra
both crashed on that
green planet
seasons would cease to exist &amp;
then they'd be plagued with an
everlasting winter.
However commander this
calculation is based on the
assumption that
Peacemillion's drive system
remains turned off.
Peacemillion used to be a ship
of mine. I know it'll
understand my intentions.
[QUINZE] Yes sir.
Can you say that about the
Gundam pilots Zechs?
Of course. No doubt they will do
everything they can to
try and stop me.
So you're waiting for them huh?
[ZECHS] Those pilots don't act
in a way that's inevitable
or predestined.
That's what makes them
professionals in combat like me,
Zechs Marquise!
[NOIN] Yes.
[RELENA] Wait! Heero tell me why
it's necessary for
you to go too.
Libra is going down. There isn't
any reason left to
keep on fighting.
My brother Milliardo Peacecraft
and the White Fang have
been defeated.
I'll make you a bet. Zechs
doesn't think that he's lost.
What's more I doubt
him or Treize
are ever going to allow
this battle to end.
[RELENA] What?
That's why I've got to go
and fight them.
Do you really think if you go
that the war's going to
come to an end?
I'll defeat Zechs, and I'll go
get Treize. Then the
war will be over.
Afterward if you make it out of
here, there'll finally be peace.
This is the only thing I
can do for you.
[RELENA] Heero...
[HEERO] I promised that I would
protect you. But in order to
protect you and the
Earth sphere Relena I have no
choice but to fight.
[RELENA] No.
Please let me fight.
I won't. No way. Heero, you're
planning to die aren't you?
Believe in me...
[SAD MUSIC]
[RELENA] Heero!
I do believe in you. Yes I do.
Goodbye Relena.
Heero!
[QUATRE] What is this?
The mobile doll control room.
No way! I'm positive this is
the Zero System.
You got it. We have connected
the mobile doll control system
to the Zero System.
So now you know. My desire to
fight activates all
mobile dolls.
What's the idea?!
Quatre Winner: I challenge you
to a duel. I lost the battle
when each of us used
the Zero System. But I wonder
what'll happen this time around.
So you've decided
you can fight without the
Zero System right?
I wouldn't fight if I could help
it. But unless I keep on
fighting you people won't
surrender and the war
will never end!
That's absolutely right. Now
let's determine for ourselves
which is more advanced:
The Zero System or the bare
human conscience. [QUATRE]
And if I refuse?
[SWORDS CLASHING]
How come you're so attached to
war?! Why must we go
through this?!
You're so kind aren't you
Quatre? And what reasons do
you have to fight?
I fight for my family. I have to
fight if I'm going to ward off
my family's sorrow.
My father did that. He fought so
that I wouldn't feel any sorrow
and he died for it.
That's why I'm going to die
fighting a beautiful
battle as well.
Then you actually hate
war too don't you?
No war is not to blame for
destruction and massacre. The
enemies we must defeat
are in our respective hearts!
I believe in peace because it
surpasses war. I believe in the
heart that hopes for peace.
Then I'll ask you this: You say
that you fought for everyone
but what has everyone done
for you in return?
I'm not fighting to receive any
kind of compensation.
That's why you'll always
be an amateur!
Please stop this Dorothy.
[DOROTHY LAUGHS]
The colonies betrayed the
Gundams. The colony citizens
killed your father. And
finally the armed colonies
declared independence from
Earth before truly
understanding what was going on.
All of your battles up until
now have been a true
waste of time. Your sympathy
toward others, too much
sympathy toward others,
has resulted in this
worst case scenario.
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
Everyone on board?
[VOICE] Yes sir!
Alright we'll proceed
straight for MO‐2.
Heero! Can you read me?
Come in Heero.
We'd only be disturbing them if
we contacted them now.
But Heero's on a
suicide mission.
[RELENA] Heero! Come in.
I'm begging you!
Forget about me Relena. Life is
something that's cheap.
Especially my life.
I'm coming Quatre!
You made it Trowa! Sorry pal but
I gotta get going.
[DUO] So I'm afraid you're
on your own here.
[TROWA] that's fine. I'll be OK.
[DUO] You sure?
[DUO] Don't go getting
yourself killed.
[TROWA] Take care Duo.
[DUO] There's no
turning back now.
Just as long as one of us can
make it to Peacemillion
then we will be able
to carry out our mission. So
don't mind if someone
gets thrown off.
Gotcha I won't worry. Besides I
got enough to think about.
Hang on we're coming.
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
No one in their right mind would
try to fly through this.
Now I regret that I ever found
them. Watch out y'all!
The God of Death and the Gods
of Plague are here!
Hey what's this?
Just leave these guys up to us.
[DUO] Thanks I'll do just that.
We weren't nearly strong enough
to have any luck unifying
outer space. But Earth
is becoming unified. Is that
girl behind it... or was it?
Fellow comrades: No one's
permitted to die until we
see master Quatre.
[VOICES] Right!
[DOROTHY] Why are you holding
back? Or can't you go for it?
Well you can sure bet
that I will!
That purity! That softness! That
kindness! No wonder you Gundam
pilots get defeated!
Maybe you're right. This is the
only way I really know
how to fight.
But it's because we take on
losing battles that we've
been able to keep the
colonists from the
horrors of war.
[DOROTHY] You'll never change
anything that way.
[QUATRE] Then what do you
suggest I should have done?
You should have become the
leader of the colonies and
staged a magnificent war
[DOROTHY] Just like Mr.
Milliardo's doing.
Dorothy you're mistak‐
And you should have staged this
war in front of all of mankind.
A miserable war that they'll
never ever want to see again!
[QUATRE] Are you saying that's
the significance of this war?
That's right. You can't do away
with wars Quatre by just taking
weapons from people.
You first have to change the
hearts of all of mankind. If you
don't do that humanity
will... it will perish just
like my father did.
You are a very kind person.
Kinder than me. [DOROTHY] That
doesn't make me the least
bit happy. Kindness just gets in
your way when you're
trying to survive.
It's more appropriate for
mankind to put all their efforts
into just surviving!
Dorothy you're just the same way
I used to be. You can't stand
your own kindness
and your own hatred of war. You
should never try to fight your
kindness. Trowa taught
me that. You have to try and
accept every‐ thing around you
because humanity needs
that kindness. Without kindness
mankind has no reason to exist.
You agree don't you? Humans that
only think of their
survival are life forms
that are lower than animals!
They can't even feel
for others...
[TREIZE] What's wrong? How come
you don't use your dragon?
Because I want to fight you fair
and square Treize.
That's how come.
[TREIZE] That's not like you.
Why the hesitation?
[WU FEI] Look who's talking! Why
didn't you kill me back there?
Well I just couldn't kill one of
the few people that
understood me. That's all.
[WU FEI] You loser!
I can't stand the sight of you!
Then come and get me now.
You're only capable of looking
down on people like this.
You're only fighting
to satisfy your ego. How many
people have died for you?
[TREIZE] Do you really want to
know? As of yesterday
99,822 people.
[WU FEI] What?
[TREIZE] Lady how many
have died today?
So far we have received
confirmation of the deaths of 82
White Fang soldiers
and 105 of our own soldiers. ‐ I
see. Give me their names
later on today.
[LADY UN] Yes sir. I will.
Damn you!
I remember everyone who has
sacrificed their lives in
Battle. How could I
forget them? Noventa. Septem.
Ventei. Darlian. Walker. Otto.
Bunt.
Their names are all
etched into my heart.
How could you be such a ‐
[TREIZE] I could only grieve
over the lives lost by those
who fought. But...
at least try to understand this:
Not one of those people
have died in vain.
[ELECTRICITY SIZZLING]
That was beautiful Wu Fei.
No Treize! How could you?!
Bye Wu Fei. My eternal friend.
I'm honored I could fight
with you pilots.
This can't be true! No way! I
won't let this happen!
[TREIZE] Milliardo. I'll be
waiting on the other side.
[EXPLOSION]
Damn it!! I didn't
think I'd win.
[SOLDIER] Colonel Un?
Your orders?
You must get in touch with the
White Fang. Tell them as
of this moment
the World Nation
declares its defeat.
Huh Colonel?
This is humiliating don't make
me repeat myself send
them the message!
[SOLDIER] Yes ma'am! Mr.
Treize... you were splendid.
This is the right way.
This is good.
So there you are Ms. Dorothy.
The Earth delegates have
just contacted
us and they have
announced their defeat.
What? The Earth has declared its
surrender? [QUINZE] Also the
combat observation
unit has just informed us that
Treize Khushrenada has
died in battle.
No! That Just can't be! [QUINZE]
The victory belongs to us.
But that
doesn't change our plans to ram
this ship into Earth. Those are
Commander Milliardo's orders.
We'll start the final boost.
Evacuate the ship
at your own discretion. Good
luck. Keep safe.
[TROWA] Things didn't go as
planned did they? In a way
what you people
were trying to do was probably
the right thing. But it still
won't bring true peace.
I was only...
[TROWA] That's sad. A
woman who can't cry.
The Earth has declared defeat?!
I don't believe it!
Things are not over yet people.
The White Fang plans to
direct Libra and
Peacemillion to ram into Earth.
[RELENA] Let's turn around.
If we go now
we should still be able to stop
them. [HOWARD] That would
be impossible.
We can't say for sure until we
try. [SALLY] There's one
person who could
make the impossible possible.
[RELENA] Heero?!
You bet. But there's absolutely
no way we could tell him
that right now.
[RELENA] Quickly let's go to
Heero. We can't. The shuttle's
used up the propulsion
energy for the initial boost.
[SALLY] Relena!
[RELENA] In that case I'll go
alone. [SOLDIER] No stop!
Let me go! Heero I'm on my way!
He's finally here.
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR] Battles are started
by people. And people realize
peace through battle.
But how many lives must be lost
as a result? And what's the
meaning of plowing
Peacemillion and Libra into
Earth? In the final stages of
battle the two Gundams
predict the dawn of a new age.
Next on the final episode
of Gundam Wing:
The Final Victor.