[OPENING THEME]
GUNDAM WING
[NARRATOR] Treize Khushrenada
assumes the position as the
World Nation's sovereign
and once again accumulates all
military armaments on land. In
space the White Fang
completes its gigantic space
battleship Libra. With his
desire to eliminate Earth
commander Milliardo Peacecraft
proceeds with his plans
to enter into a
fully fledged war with the
entire forces of the World
Nation led by Treize.
The Gundam pilots continue to
fight, not siding with anyone.
And right before
them the largest battle yet to
be experienced by humanity
is about to begin.
Everyone get outta here!
Libra's firing their
main weapon?
No!
[CANNON FIRING]
Main cannon system down.
[SOLDIER] Various damage to
spaceship structure.
This can't be happening. It
wasn't supposed to
happen like this.
[ZECHS] This was too much
responsibility for Dorothy.
Hey Zechs... according to Zero
you have no future.
Is Epyon telling you
differently?
Signs of the Final Battle
OK it's all finished. You never
know when we'll have to
fight next right?
Counting on you buddy.
Huh?
Quatre... what are you doing?
I can still fight without it.
[DUO] Heero be careful yourself.
I know you can control it now
but that doesn't change the fact
that it's a dangerous system.
You're right.
I can't believe he agreed...
Hey you guys! I thought that I
told you to leave the repairs
to the mechanics.
[HOWARD] Don't forget it's your
duty as pilots to rest
when you can.
We know. Hey man I'm famished
let's grab something to eat.
Sounds good to me.
[SALLY] That's the natural
resource satellite MO‐2.
They're done mining it so it's
been left circling
Earth's orbit.
It would be perfect for a
frontline base.
Look at all of those mobile
suits. The World
Nation's been bringing
all the weapons from Earth to
this one location.
[SALLY] Sure looks that way.
Still it's astonishing that they
could assemble this many suits.
Does Treize Kushrenada honestly
expect that he's gonna
be able to settle this
war in space?
I really don't know. But they
have never done anything like
this before now though.
What in the world could those
guys be thinking?
I wonder.
[SIREN]
[ROCKET LAUNCH]
The sixth launch was
very successful.
Now most of our military force
has been transferred.
[TREIZE] How are things at M‐02?
Shuttles from all around the
world are starting to
arrive there.
[SOLDIER] Our defense line
should be ready in time for
Libra's approach.
The time's finally come to put
an end to this prolonged fight.
By eliminating
the White Fang who is using
military force to disrupt our
peace we will bring calm
to Earth and space. My fellow
soldiers I do hope that
you'll fight your best
to achieve peace and
order for us all.
[SOLDIERS] Yes sir!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[HILDE] This is transport
carrier 781. Please give me
boarding directions.
[HILDE] Duo I know you're gonna
be mad at me but I'm gonna
fight my own way.
The repairs to Libra are
almost completely done.
There's still time before the
World Nation's military
forces at M‐02
start making moves.
Switch to our emergency shift
and have everybody who is not on
duty get some rest.
[QUINZE] Will this be
the final battle?
It's gonna have to be. I'm gonna
rest too. Take over things here.
Commander Milliardo. What are we
going to do about the Gundams?
Leave them alone.
[QUINZE] Commander?!
The Peacemillion was hit pretty
hard. They'll be quiet
for the moment.
But sir we can't just simply
leave them out there
because Epyon alone
is our Gundam symbol. Anything
else that might get in the
way of our ideal
must be destroyed immediately.
Can we do that?
I've already sent mobile dolls
over there. I will defeat them.
You're in charge now so do
whatever you want.
Hmmm...
More to the right!
How do you like this place Ms.
Relena? Don't you find
it invigorating?
[DOROTHY] There's a tension in
the air as people
prepare for war...
Are you worried about Mr.
Milliardo? I'm sure you must be
considering that his next
opponent is Mr. Treize.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Why would my brother start a war
with a former friend
of his rather than
talking things over?
Because that is what they both
want to do. [RELENA] Huh?
It's just that you can't
understand how the two of
them must feel.
But that doesn't really
matter too much though.
What do you mean?
Look at those Ms. Relena.
What are they?
Mercurius and Vayeate. They're
mobile suits built by the
same engineers who
made the Gundams. Their test
pilots were Heero Yuy
and Trowa Barton.
What?
[DOROTHY] They've been
reconstructed into mobile dolls
with the combat data
of a Gundam pilot installed
right in the systems.
Even Heero's?
A Gundam pilot versus a program
doll. I wonder which of them
will end up winning?
Heero won't lose.
Right. He's just so
strong isn't he?
Well if you'll please excuse me
I've got some work to
take care of.
You can feel free to look
around Ms. Relena.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Heero...
Excuse me. Can I ask if you know
one of the Gundam pilots?
[QUINZE] Did you get it?
Yes sir we've found our target.
The Peacemillion assault
force is almost there.
We'll get them this time.
[DOROTHY] Are you
attacking Peacemillion?
Yes Ms. Dorothy.
It's no use. You just can't
defeat the Gundams with
mobile dolls.
We won't know until we try. I'm
sure that we'll defeat them.
It's very important that we do
so for the sake of our future.
OK fine. Then go right ahead.
I just hope we don't waste a
valuable military force
before the big battle.
Continue as planned!
I see. So you know one of the
Gundam pilots too.
Yes but I'm not nearly as strong
as they are. And I can't
fight with them.
But I'm sure there's something I
can do to help them.
You seem strong enough to me. I
on the other hand probably can't
do anything at all to
help them out.
Anyway it's too dangerous to
stay here. You'd better
make your getaway.
Right. I will go. I really have
to deliver this data I
got on Libra.
[HILDE] Why not come with me?
You wanna see that Gundam pilot
that you know don't you?
I can't. I have to stay. There's
still some things I have
to take care off.
Then I'd better be on my way.
Wait what was your name?
My name's Relena Peacecraft.
Well take care.
You too.
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
[ALARM] Huh? What is going on?
[SOLDIER] The hatch of the
number five hangar has
been destroyed!
[SOLDIER] A Taurus
cruiser's getting away!
Someone's trying to escape?
[DOROTHY] I notice that
the Taurus cruiser
is making a beeline straight
for Peacemillion.
Send out the Virgos and go
after it at once!
Virgos won't do it. You should
send out the Mercurius
and the Vayeate. I'm sure that
would attract the Gundams here.
I'll give the orders around
here. How about clamming up?
This isn't a kids game you know?
How true. This is a
war isn't it?
They're after me. And I just
cannot afford to get
caught here.
[QUATRE] The repairs to the
engine are almost done.
Oh yeah?
That Howard sure is quick when
it comes to getting his
work done huh?
I'll make my move quickly too.
I wonder if it'll make up
for our delays.
Now what move should
I be making?
An excellent play.
Offense is the best defense. If
you're only defensive you
limit yourself.
Thanks a lot for the good tip Wu
Fei. Heero wanna play?
[DUO] Huh? [QUATRE] Huh?
What's the matter Heero?
Is something bothering you?
[ALARM]
Guess they've beaten us
to the punch.
[QUATRE] Let's go! [DUO] Right!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[HEERO] Enemy mobile dolls.
Virgo troops confirmed.
Proceeding with mission.
The engine's just been fixed so
don't go and wreck it.
I understand.
[WU FEI YELLS]
They are coming in
from the right.
[WU FEI] I'll get 'em. [TROWA]
OK I'll back you up.
Good luck.
[SOLDIER] The Peacemillion
assault force has entered
combat with the Gundams.
[QUINZE] And what about the
Mercurius &amp; Vayeate?
Where are they?
[SOLDIER] They've almost got the
target within firing range.
Alright! We have to shoot down
the Taurus cruiser
before it reaches
the Gundam.
[EXPLOSION]
Ah! Ugh...
[HILDE] Only a bit further to
go. There's no way I'll let
you defeat me now!
It's those suits!
[HILDE SCREAMS]
There's just no end to them.
[HILDE] Peacemillion!
Peacemillion do you read me?!
Hey... that sounds like...
[HILDE] Please answer me...
Duo... Ugh!
Hilde!
[QUATRE] Duo go find her! [DUO]
And leave you guys?!
Hurry! We will take care of
everything here.
[DUO] Alright. Thanks!
[GUNFIRE]
Ugh. Watch! I'l make it!
Ugh! [GROANS]
Hey! It's not over yet. I'll get
this data to Duo and the others.
Just watch me. I'm
not going down!
[TARGETING BEEP]
Ah!!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Hilde... you still alive?
Yeah... somehow or other.
[DUO] Stay back. I'll take
care of these guys.
Duo! Be careful!!
What?
[DUO] Ugh!
What in the heck's going on?
They're way too strong to be
just mobile dolls.
[HILDE] Duo!
Those... those mobile
dolls aren't normal.
They are programmed with data
taken from you Gundam pilots.
Are you sure?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Heero... and Trowa...
[GUNFIRE]
You've gotta be kidding me. So
this is like fighting the two of
them at once isn't it?
Ugh...
Even so...
... they're pretty good copies!
But they're still
just dolls to me.
You don't seriously expect a
Gundam pilot to lose to dolls?!
[DUO] You've met your match!!
Next time you'd be better off
programming in MY data.
[DUO] Hilde. Hey Hilde say
something! Hey!
Hilde...
Du‐Duo... I'm glad... you're
safe huh... Duo.
Yeah but you're in terrible
shape. What did you come all the
way out here for Hilde?
[GROANS]
I brought you guys this data on
Libra. Please use it.
But... how come? Why'd you
risk your life?
Because I just... I wanted to,
Duo.
Geez... YOU'RE A STUPID FOOL!!
I figured you'd say
something like that.
[SOLDIER] The Peacemillion
assault troops have been
completely wiped out.
Oh that's such a shame. Funny
it's exactly what I
predicted would
happen to all of them. Well
maybe there's some
conciliation in the fact we at
least got to see the Gundams
fighting so hard. [LAUGHTER]
We can't let the data that she
brought us be put to waste.
No...
[DUO] Heero...
Relena Peacecraft is on Libra...
[HEERO] She is?
[DUO] Yeah. Hilde says
she met her there.
[HEERO] Relena...
[INTENSE MUSIC]
[RELENA] Heero...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR] Heero sneaks onto
Libra and goes with
Relena to see Zechs.
Treize leads a force of
thousands of armored mobile
suits. Treize desires one
chivalrous duel to settle the
battle. But as Milliardo,
commander of the White Fang,
Zechs refuses
Treize's challenge.
Next on Gundam Wing episode 46:
Milliardo's Decision.