[OPENING THEME]
We aren't needed in
outer space Heero!!
We mustn't fight each other,
it isn't right.
Relena...
The Locus of Victory and Defeat.
[RELENA:] That's right, I still
don't know where Heero has gone.
Please don't laugh father.
Because I can still hear Heero's
voice, even to this day.
Trust me father, I believe that
he'll one day arrive at
the Sanc Kingdom.
I wonder how long it's been? How
much time has passed
since we met.
[RELENA:] It was during my
shuttle flight with father, on
our way back to Earth.
Father, what is that?
[RELENA:] That was when I first
came across that
shooting star that
went by the name of Heero Yuy.
And was full of the
colony's hopes
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
[LAUGHING]
[HEERO:] One more to go...
[HEERO:] This is where
everything started.
My codename? Heero Yuy.
I was given one mission:
to destroy OZ.
He's still just a young boy.
[HEERO:] Did you see!?
See what?
They're down there!
‐Hurry!
Hey, who are you?
What?
[RELENA:] My name is... my name
is Relena Dorlian.
[RELENA:] What's yours?
[RELENA:] Until then, I
enjoyed a world of happiness,
not knowing what was going on in
the world, and not giving
anything back to society,
But meeting him greatly
changed my destiny.
Hey, that's him!
My name is Heero Yuy.
It's a pleasure.
[RELENA:] I'm sure that's him.
[RELENA:] Here you go.
It's an invitation to my
birthday tomorrow.
[RELENA:] I hope you'll be able
to make it to the party.
[GASPS]
But... but why?
I'll kill you.
[HEERO:] I wasn't the only
Gundam pilot that was part of
Operation Meteor.
There was also Trowa Barton,
pilot of the Gundam Heavyarms.
Quatre Roberba Winner, pilot of
the Gundam Sandrock.
This isn't right.
It's not.
You and I shouldn't be
fighting each other!
Put your hands down, I was the
first one to surrender and
come out, remember?
[EXPLOSIONS]
[SCREAMING]
[NOIN:] Stop! Stop
or I'll shoot!
[NOIN:] A kid did all that
damage to the base by himself?
Hmm? A woman? Now it
makes sense.
[HEERO:] Wu Fei Chang, pilot of
the Shenlong Gundam.
[PILOT:] Where's this
light coming from‐
[PILOT 2:] It's the enemy,
the enemy's here!
[HEERO:] And Duo Maxwell, pilot
of the Gundam Deathscythe.
Heero, what are you doing? Tell
me, just who are you anyway?
Those are torpedoes, aren't
they? I can tell. I want to
know who you are!
Talk to me Heero!
Relena...
Heero.
[GUN COCKING]
You're in over your head.
[GASPING NOISE]
[GUNSHOT NOISE]
It's pretty obvious to anyone
that you're the bad guy here.
Are you all right lady?
Heero, are you okay?
[GUNSHOT]
Don't overdo it! Remember,
you're injured.
Stop it! What do you
wanna shoot him for?
What in the world is that?
[DUO:] Don't look lady!
Now I'm sure you've got your
reasons for being here, but you
better just walk away,
save yourself a lot of grief.
You haven't had enough?
[GUNSHOTS]
[HEERO:] I don't consider the
other Gundam pilots my comrades,
I've never had any
comrades from the start.
Just like Relena, this
guy who calls himself Duo
is no more than an obstacle
to completing my mission.
Finally, everything is finished.
Mission complete...
[RELENA:] Father, that was
when you strongly wished
for peace between Earth
and the colonies.
We've heard everything
you've had to say.
I'd like you to leave the room
now, Vice Foreign Minister!
Isn't it about time you people
realized the ones posing
the most threat
are none other than yourselves?
[RELENA:] And father, you flew
with me to space once more.
That turned out to be your
last gift of kindness.
To show me just how
beautiful the Earth was.
[EXPLOSION]
Oh God, father!!
[RELENA:] What are you going
to do with my father, huh!?
[DARLIAN:] Relena
Father...
I have a confession to make,
Relena.
I'm not your biological father.
[GASPS]
You've got to believe what
I'm telling you.
Your real name is
Relena Peacecraft.
You're the daughter of the
Peacecraft family that
was so well known,
for it's total
commitment to pacifism.
Father that's not possible!!
Relena, watch out for the
OZ organization!
Don't die on me! No father!
Nooo!!
[HEERO:] Delete files on Heero
Yuy at the St.
Gabriel Institute.
Transfer procedures complete.
[RELENA:] Are you off
to fight again?
Where's your next mission Heero?
[RELENA:] I'd come across too
many of his secrets.
But the fact that Heero was a
Gundam pilot, sent
from the colonies
might have had a greater
influence than my own
personal situation
in regards as to how I was going
to live out the rest of my life.
Heero, I know too much about
you. Are you still
going to kill me?
Yeah.
I didn't want to die with no
answers but now it's different.
Now I know how you feel
when you fight.
Huh?
And that's because I'm on
your side now.
Huh? On my side?
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
What in the heck am I thinking?
I'd be better off if she died,
wouldn't I?
What's wrong with me!?
Heero!
Please Heero, don't run
away from me.
[RELENA:] Marshall Noventa,
Chief Commander of the United
Earthsphere Alliance,
was pushing for peace with the
colonies, and was planning
a significant reduction
in armaments.
However, the Commander‐in‐Chief
of OZ, Treize Khushrenada,
used shrewd tactics in his
release of information,
to lure the Gundams to the
New Edwards Base.
And tricked them into killing
the leaders of the
Alliance Military.
Now young man, don't be foolish!
[EXPLOSION]
The second act has just begun.
We'll be busy.
[RELENA:] Operation Daybreak...
This well planned coup
d'etat allowed OZ,
with it's soldiers posted at
Alliance Military bases,
under the guise of
Specials soldiers,
to overthrow the
Alliance in one day.
Just see for yourself.
It's a revolution.
The era of the
Alliance has ended.
[ZECHS:] Our OZ organization
must give birth to a true
alliance on it's own.
[SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOT]
[HEERO:] In addition, Colonel
Une proposed a plan to transfer
the Taurus space mobile suits
to the Siberia Base.
However this was also a
deceptive operation,
aimed at annihilating the
Gundams all at once.
Do you think that the other
Gundams will come?
We can't win by ourselves.
But I'm positive the
others will come.
You wish!
He's fast!
[ZECHS:] We'll fight for
recognition of superiority!
You ARE a Gundam pilot. I'm
sure that'll suit you!
Who would've guessed Gundams
had this much power?
[UNE:] Get Space Fortress
Barge on line!
[UNE:] Calling all
Gundam pilots.
We are now positioned to stage
an all out missile attack
on the colonies.
I demand all pilots to surrender
at once and hand over
your Gundams.
They've targeted the colonies!
And hand over our Gundams!?
Sounds like Oz's tricks.
You guys could fight!
Well can't you!?
Attention OZ.
I never would have imagined that
you people could be so
incredibly foolish!
In your eyes, inhumane moves
such as attacking the
colonies are just,
if that's what it takes for you
to come out victorious, right?
I surrender, but I will not
hand over the Gundams.
[DOCTOR J:] I repeat. I
surrender, but I will NOT hand
over the Gundams.
Mission accepted.
[RELENA:] Off to
fight again Heero?
[RELENA:]The Romefeller
Foundation sought to maintain
peace through it's conquests.
That may be possible as long as
they keep winning battles.
[RELENA:] However, as Relena
Peacecraft, the present leader
of the Sanc Kingdom,
I cannot allow them to reign at
the cost of many people's lives.
[HEERO:] I was defeated. My
hands were tied since the
colonies were being
used as a shield.
However, Zechs repaired my
Gundam in hopes that
we could end our unfinished
battle in Siberia.
[HEERO:] The battle took
place in Antarctica.
I refused to accept
charity from Zechs,
and challenged him in Trowa's
Gundam Heavyarms.
But this battle, a battle
between a man looking for
something to protect,
and a man who has lost all means
by which to protect,
had no meaning to it.
[RELENA:] Mistakes of the past
are difficult for
anyone to swallow.
But we're still young. We should
be thinking of
building the future.
I wanted to put an end to this
meaningless fight, Heero.
[EXPLOSION]
Has it begun?
[GUNFIRE]
Now that's more like it!
This will finish you off!
Heero!
Stop this battle immediately!
[ZECHS:] Just see for yourself
how dirty and foul
battles really are!
No! If you're a true warrior and
a true knight of Peacecraft,
you couldn't possibly use
such foul play!
[PAGAN:] Relena! There's a call
from Lieutenant Noin!
[RELENA:] Miss Noin.
I completely misunderstood you.
I thought you were sincere!
Precisely. I deserve your
contempt but I can't help it.
Because I believe in
Colonel Zechs.
I'm not about to go interrupt
anything he plans on doing.
Heero, defeat that man!
Stop it! Relena!
[NOIN:] No matter what
destiny awaits you,
you mustn't do anything as
deplorable as wishing for the
death of your own brother!
Brother? He's my brother?
[RELENA:] I learned then, for
the first time that Zechs was my
own brother, Milliardo.
A number of attack carriers are
approaching us from 3 o'clock!
They're here!
[TROWA:] Can you hear me
Heero and Zechs?
There are about thirty
suits in flight!
One hundred if they unload all
Aries suits from the carriers.
I'll attract them all myself!
Glory to all the colonies!
[ZECHS:] Heero! We'll meet again
to continue our fight
‐ No Zechs!!
[HEERO:] Next time I fight him,
will I be fighting against Zechs
Marquise or
Milliardo Peacecraft?
Whichever it may be, I'll defeat
him if he's going to
stand in my way.
If he's an enemy, I'll kill him.
[RELENA:] I haven't seen Heero,
or my brother since then.
Now, with OZ splitting
into two factions,
and continuing with their
foolish battle,
the world is proceeding along
the path to chaos.
[RELENA:] But I'm confident that
you will appear before me Heero,
to end this war.
Heero!!! I'm waiting for you to
come back to me Heero!!
[ENDING THEME]
[NARRATOR:] As long as mankind
exists in this world, there will
always be battles.
and denouncing battles will
never lead to peace.
Treize Khushrenada has
disappeared from the center
stage of history, however
while destinies slip past one
another, Treize begins to
proceed with new plans.
Next, on Gundam Wing Episode 28:
Passing Destinies