[♪♪]
Narrator: With high
expectations,
human beings leave earth...
...to begin a new life in
space colonies.
However, the United Earth
Sphere Alliance...
...gains great
military powers...
... and soon seizes control of
one colony after another...
...in the name of
justice and peace.
The year is after colony 195.
Operation Meteor.
In a move to counter the
Alliance's ternary,
rebel citizens of
certain colonies...
... scheme to bring new
arsenals to the earth...
... disguising them as
shooting stars.
However, the Alliance
headquarters catches on to
this operation.
Father!!
Where are you, Father?!!
Relena...
Father talk to me!
You've got to believe what
I'm telling you.
Your real name is
Relena Peacecraft.
Wha‐I don't know what
you're saying.
Party Night
[reporters clamoring]
Reporter: Are the colonies
starting a war against us?!
Guard 1: Clear the way!
Guard 2: Don't push step back!
Reporter: Well,
what's the scoop?
Relena!!
How could they ask those things?
None of them have any idea why
father was actually
assassinated.
[knocking]
I'm finally home, Mother.
Relena...
I'm so sorry.
I wasn't able to save Father.
Relena.
I'm just glad that you
weren't injured.
I knew something like this
would happen one day.
Relena...
You've got to believe what
I'm telling you.
Your real name is
Relena Peacecraft.
You're the daughter of the
Peacecraft family...
...that was so well known
for it's total...
...commitment to Pacifism.
Did he say anything before
he passed away?
No, he didn't really
say anything.
I have something to tell you,
Relena.
Mother!
Relena?!
You're my real mother!
You'll always be my mother!
Relena...
Lady Une: Now that Vice Foreign
Minister Darlian is dead...
...there are no longer any
diplomats acting as a bridge...
...between Earth and the
space colonies.
Treize: Right.
He was quite the individual.
Just the type of person who is
sacrificed to a new era.
Oh, by the way Lady Une.
You're not planning on
returning here yet?
No, I still have something
to take care of.
I need you to give me a
little more time.
You mean Darlian's daughter.
It's unlike you to make
mistakes lady Une.
I'd like your permission to head
to the J. A. P. point...
... with some mobile suits.
Take five mobile suits with you.
That many sir?
A dark shadow seems to follow
us wherever we go.
You mean the Gundams.
The Gundams have only been
attacking our facilities...
... and the new type
of mobile suit.
Think of it as a precaution.
However, if a Gundam
should attack us...
...five suits might
not be enough.
[cacophony]
We're gonna be late
for the party!
Wait for me!
Delete files on Heero Yuy at the
Saint Gabriel Institute.
Transfer procedures complete.
Girl: Hurry, hurry!
I'm not involved.
[♪♪]
Girl 1: Look, it's Relena!
Girl 2: Is it true that her
father was assassinated...
...by terrorists in
the colonies?
Boy: yeah, the press
is all over it!
Relena!
I'm so sorry to hear
about your father.
I wish I were anywhere
but at a party.
Seeing all this festivity
just makes me sadder.
That's very kind of you both.
But I can't be sad forever.
Let's try to be stronger.
Father wouldn't want me
feeling sorry for myself.
we'll be strong Relena...
Boy 1: What?!
Heero's moving to
another school?!
Boy 2: But he hasn't even been
here for a month yet!
Relena: Are you off to
fight again?!
Where's your next mission Heero?
I met Dr. J.
So even you can be surprised.
Ever since I met you,
it's been me who keeps getting
surprised by you.
If you killed me now it would
cause quite a commotion.
I don't think thats what
you really want.
The school's holding a
party right now.
Might as well stay and enjoy it.
At least until the
dance is over.
[boat horn]
Troop 1: They finally made it.
Troop 2: This fog would
slow anyone down.
We'll be moving the mobile suits
to the hangar at once.
Right!
What just exploded?!
Look at that!
[♪♪]
It's a Gundam!!
You let the enemy penetrate a
little too easily.
You can only blame yourselves,
poor security.
[carnival music]
[applause]
Where is that dimwit?!
He's up next!
He's right over there.
You're late kid!
Why can't you just stay here and
wait like everyone else?!
I made it here on time.
That's good enough.
You punk!
We're up next, the
audience is waiting!
get going.
Just leave it to me.
All you have to do is
stand very still.
Ladies and Gentlemen!
Our next performance is by
Catherine Bloom...
...the knife‐throwing
star of the circus!
[guys swooning]
[drum line]
Stand still Trowa.
C'mon, look a little scared.
Otherwise how will I have any
fun, my little doll.
[suspenseful music]
What is it?
Unreal, he's not
afraid of anything!
It's death...
He's begging for his death.
I don't understand!
You wanna die, Trowa?
No!
Trowa...
Trowa!
Why didn't you dodge the knife?!
I'm not paid to dodge.
Boy, You looked just
like a wild beast.
Your eyes are just
like that lion's.
[growling]
Oops, I guess that
was an insult.
You'd look better out there if
you smiled a bit.
You're good looking, and I'm
not just saying that!
Oh my god, I haven't even
apologized to you yet!
Trowa! I'm really
sorry I hit you.
I told you katherine,
this is my job.
Trowa! How about that smile?!
[♪♪]
Look! Relena and Heero.
She must be feeling better.
But it's a shame her dress
wasn't ready for the party.
Just have to use your
imagination.
She's wearing her
dress right now.
Heero, I know too
much about you.
Are you still gonna kill me?
Yeah.
I didn't want to die
with no answers.
But now it's different.
Now I know how you feel
when you fight.
Huh?
And thats because, I'm on
your side now.
Huh, on my side...?
What's that?
Oh no.
That's an OZ suit carrier!
They've caught on to this place!
Heero!
Don't stop at anything.
It'll be reported by the
press as another...
... terrorist attack
against the Alliance.
I don't feel too
great about this.
Attacking a defenseless
civilian facility.
Then stay behind!
I'll have someone else
lead the attack.
But why?!
With that attitude, you're
risking your life as
well as others'!
I can't have that in a leader!
Forgive my insubordination!
I'll carry out our
mission at once.
Very well. Get on with it.
Roger!
We'll descend immediately!
Stay calm, don't get angry.
‐Right, let's go!
‐Roger!
Mobile suit 1: Hey
what was that?!
Mobile suit 2: Watch out!
It's the enemy!
[♪♪]Gundam Wing
[panic &amp; hysteria]
Oh no, those are the
Militaries mobile suits.
Why would they be coming
here to fight?
Relena!
Leo, Aries both confirmed
as standard suits.
I'll get em.
Why is the enemy out here?
Here he comes!
Mobile suit: We're fighting off
an enemy mobile suit.
What kind of suit is it?
I have no idea!
I've never seen this
type before!
Just as Colonel
Treize predicted.
So it's probably them.
But why did it show up here?
Capture that unconfirmed suit!
Dispatch the
remaining Aries suits!
[siren]
[♪♪]
Just as I thought.
Others are attacking OZ
facilities besides just me.
I know one of them's
Trowa but...
Does this mean there
are others too?
Are there more Gundam
pilots like me?
Wish I could meet them.
All of them.
Mate 1: This is good stuff!
Nothing like a good cup of joe
after a long days hall.
Mate 2: You got that right!
Mechanic: Hey Duo! Duo!!
What's up Duo?
Whatcha doin there?
Nothin. Just thinking how
beautiful the moon
looks from Earth.
You bet it does; it's
a real beauty.
From the colony the moon
just too close.
It almost looks like
a graveyard.
Yeah... A graveyard.
Wonder how long I'll be able to
see the moon like this.
I doubt if that guy even
looks at the moon.
He should try enjoying life,
rather than spending his time
trying to outsmart me.
While he's alive, that is.
I know what you're saying, but
it's not that simple.
It's just human nature.
What's that guy doing? I wonder.
[machine gun fire]
[♪♪]
Aaaargh!!
I don't believe it.
His suit is far more mobile than
ours suits could
ever hope to be!
Mobile suit: It's a
flight model! Ascend!
It's too heavy fool!
[whimpering]
Everything will be okay!
Stop crying and run!
‐Okay!
It'll be all right! Just hurry!
‐We will!
Relena...
Heero...?
What in the heck am I thinking?!
I'd be better off if she
died wouldn't I?
What's going on? He stopped!
What?!
Do you mean the Gundam's
protecting Darlian's daughter?!
Yes! No mistake.
It's the girl we're after;
Relena Darlian!
Could it be, that the girl
somehow knows the
Gundam's pilot?
[♪♪]
Heero...is that you?
What's wrong?
Can't do it...
What's wrong with me?!
[screaming]
Troop: All of our suits
have been destroyed!
Then I'll go!
Colonel Treize is on the line!
What?!
Lady Une.
Cancel your mission.
Return to base immediately.
But Colonel Treize!
I've decided to let
Darlian's daughter live.
But Colonel! The
mission was to...
Lady...
We were met by an
unexpected enemy.
Don't think of it as a failure.
Return immediately.
Right. I understand.
Nion: Thank you very much,
Colonel Treize.
I'm sure Lieutenant Zechs
will be pleased.
Zechs has always gone out of his
way to help me out.
Saving Relena is the very least
I can do to thank him
for his efforts.
Please give my regards to
Lieutenant Zechs.
Yes, sir!
So the rumors were true.
He still has a living
blood relative.
He could've said something.
I see.
You'd rather stay here,
would you?
Heero, that's you, isn't it?!
Answer me! Heero!
Tell me why you rescued me?!
I don't know.
why did I save her? She
knows too much!
You didn't kill me! You said
you were gonna?!
Answer me, Heero!
Heero...
How come I can't kill her?!
Heero!!
Please, Heero.
Don't run away form me.
To be continued
Next Episode
As the leaders of the Alliance
Military gather...
...at the New Edwards Base to
discuss armament
reduction issue...
...Treize Khushrenada, head of
the OZ organization...
...skillfully lays a trap to
attract the Gundam pilots.
The liquadation of the
peace loving...
...Alliance is carried out
by the Gundams.
Treize's trap opens the gates to
a new era of bloodshed.
Next, on Gundam Wing, episode 7
Scenario for Bloodshed