[DAGGER]
Ladies and gentlemen of BRR.
Once again, this is
a declaration of war.
[ROSIA]
Man! I'm starving!
[CYAN]
Rosia.
What's going on? Why do
you all look so worried?
[DAGGER]
Hello, Rosia. Long time no see.
[gasps]
[DAGGER]
Don't worry.
I'm not concerned with
you girls anymore.
[gasps]
[DAGGER] I'm here to
inform you my colleagues
from BVL wish to
challenge Plasmagica
to a battle of the bands.
Will you stand tall
and accept it?
Or run away and hide like
a bunch of scared cats?
The countdown to
the glorious day
of your misfortune has begun.
Struggle all you want.
[DAGGER cackles]
[MAPLE]
He finally came, huh?
That bastard!
You know, for someone
as tiny as he is now,
he's sure got a big mouth!
What are you gonna do, Prez?
[MAPLE]
Hm. What do ya think?
You girls up for it?
Of course! We accept
his challenge!
You betcha, pyuru!
And with Cyan,
there's no way
Plasmagica can lose!
Sure.
[ROSIA whimpers]
[DAGGER] You're worthless.
Complete trash!
--And trash gets dumped!
--[GIRLS scream]
[DAGGER] Goodnight, goodbye,
and good riddance!
[screaming]
[HOLMY]
Rosia?
[gasps]
Is everything all right?
Uh, sure.
[CYAN] Don't worry,
Rosia. It'll be fine.
We won't let something
scary like what went down
before happen again, okay?
Cyan, you're the best.
So that band is called BVL, huh?
No matter how much I search,
I can't find out
anything about them.
I don't like going in blind.
[CHUCHU]
Me, either.
Still, no matter what kind of
music they come up with
for Midi City--scratch that!
For Sound Planet,
we've just gotta win!
Everyone's depending on us!
For the sake of
Pyuru Land, too, pyuru!
[BOTH]
Yeah!
♪
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Pumping Jumping! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CYAN] ♪ Dontcha come at me
with your monotone ♪
♪ Feelin' somethin'
more harmonious ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Waiting, to take a breath ♪
♪ I look, listen,
oh so carefully ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Oh baby,
can you hear the chords ♪
♪ Soundin' sweet the more
we rock the pop ♪
[MOA] ♪ Let's mix and
match our swing now ♪
♪ To make the music that we've
all been feelin' inside ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ (Passhuwa!
Pappasshuwa! Pashuwa, yes!) ♪
[CYAN]
♪ 'Cause even in my dreams ♪
♪ I hear the sound
of your voice ♪
[CHUCHU] ♪ In you I finally see
There is no other choice ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ I know I can
keep pushing ahead ♪
♪ And that I can really change ♪
[MOA] ♪ All I need is
to find melodies ♪
♪ I haven't
discovered just yet ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ Everybody Rock!
Rock! Give it your all! ♪
♪ Just sing and be yourself! ♪
♪ Keep on keepin' on
and on and on and on ♪
♪ and cramming emotions
into your music ♪
♪ Everybody Rock! Rock!
With all your heart! ♪
♪ And soon you'll
hear new melodies ♪
♪ Hear the pulsing beat ♪
♪ The power of the rhythm ♪
♪ The magic never stops ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ All you need is
harmony (words don't matter) ♪
♪ Honesty
(With your feelings) ♪
♪ Keep on strumming! Keep on
going! Keep on and on! ♪
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[school bell rings]
[ROSIA]
That girl.
I wonder if she's
here again today.
[sighs]
[ROSIA gasps]
What do you think you're doing?
You're not peeping
again, are you?
[ROSIA whimpers]
[PEIPAIN]
Either you hurry up and answer
Master Ailane's question,
or I'll make you regret it.
My business is with that
little shorty, not you two!
So just back off!
[PEIPAIN] How can you
speak to us so rudely?
You dare insult Master Ailane?
I will not forgive
those who harm my master.
And I have no patience
for brats like you.
[ROSIA]
I-It's you guys, isn't it?
You're the ones who
teamed up with Dagger
and are taking on Plasmagica
in a battle of the bands!
Could be. And what would
you plan on doing
about it if that's true?
Maybe... Look, I don't
know what your deal is,
but if you're gonna
do something weird
to Plasmagica's
Melodisians, then--!
[AILANE]
Then what?
[gasps]
I'd think long and hard
about what you're gonna
say to me, if I were you.
[AILANE]
Hmph.
[ROSIA]
Plasmagica would never lose
to the likes of you people!
You hear me? Never!
[CHUCHU] Looks like the
time's finally come, y'all!
Pyuru! We'll fight
with Cyan's new song!
[RETOREE]
Let's lay it on 'em hardcore!
Yeah!
I was wonderin'.
Is there anything the rest
of us can do to help you out?
[CYAN]
Huh?
How do you wanna do this, pyuru?
Well... First, I'll try
making a demo of my ideas!
Sounds good! I can't
wait to hear them!
Cool!
Well, that's what I said
about it at the time, anyway,
but I can't think of anything!
[sighs]
I have to write something
that's not only super catchy,
but surprising, too.
[CYAN]
Hey, Mr. Berry.
I'm not getting any ideas here!
This is no time to whine, Cyan!
Everyone's counting on you,
so get it together!
All right! I'll do my best!
[gasps] I overslept!
Practice already started and
I still don't have anything!
I have to hurry!
[CHUCHU]
If we're gonna beat them,
then we should focus
on something positive.
We need that kind of energy
to smash their darkness.
Like Cyan did that
time before, pyuru.
[CHUCHU]
That's right.
We also need to work extra hard
to further evolve
our Melodisians!
I'm sure that Cyan will write
an amazing song for us!
And we need to do our best
to bring that song to life!
We don't wanna let Cyan down!
--[MOA] Pyuru!
--[RETOREE] Yeah, let's do it!
[CHUCHU]
Speaking of which.
Where is she?
Cyan's never this late.
[CYAN]
Can we really do this?
Can we win with a new
song written by me?
[door opens]
[MOA]
Hey! There you are!
We were worried, pyuru!
Yeah, you're really late.
We were about to go find you.
Oh! Sorry!
Guess I got caught up
in the writing!
Whoa, you look tired.
Feelin' okay?
Have you slept?
You weren't awake all
night writing, were you?
[nervously giggles]
[CHUCHU] You need to take
better care of yourself!
Not only for your well-being,
but they say wonderful songs
come from healthy bodies!
And healthy bodies
are made of yummy,
delicious food, pyuru!
[CHUCHU]
I've got an idea!
There's supposed to be
a new burger place
that just opened up around
here. Let's check it out!
[MOA] Oh, yeah! I read
about it in a magazine!
Hamburgers for sure
qualify as yummy!
Is this the one?
[CHUCHU]
Yes! That's Retoree for you!
[RETOREE]
Awesome.
I say we end practice for today
and go pay 'em a little visit!
[MOA]
Sounds good to me!
But, don't we...?
You've gotta relax and take
it easy once in a while.
We still have plenty
of time, pyuru.
Totally.
Oh. Okay.
[CHUCHU]
Rushing won't do you any good.
Yeah. I guess you're right.
[CROW]
Yo! What's up?
Man, this place never
changes, does it.
Huh. I almost forgot.
You used to work here
part-time as well, didn't you.
[CROW]
Yep!
And thanks to the
money I made here,
I was able to get my hands
on my beloved Red Tomahawk.
But, enough memory lane.
So what was it you wanted
to talk to me about?
Not now.
I wanted to discuss it with you
later tonight. It's serious.
For real?
Why didn't we just talk
about this at the studio?
Could've saved me
the trouble of coming
all the way down here.
Anyway, is it just me?
For now.
But Aion will be
joining us shortly.
As a protector of the Holy Land,
this store is like
the underworld to him.
Hence, he requires
resolve and courage
just to be able to walk into
an establishment such as this.
You knave!
You're late, Aion. As expected.
Gah!
[AION] F-For a god to descend
upon a place like this is--
[CROW] What are you,
some old, creepy witch?
Seriously, what's up with
the weird wizard outfit?
It's kind of embarrassing, dude.
[AION] Any opinion concerning
my holy black clothes
from a small, ant-like
rodent such as you
means very little
to a god like me.
Say what?
[YAIBA]
We are all here now.
Hence, we should speak.
But where's Rom?
[YAIBA]
This actually concerns Rom.
A CD?
[CROW]
What's with this thing?
I was helping the
president the other day--
organizing, filing,
things of that nature--
when I came across this.
So what is it? A band demo?
[YAIBA]
Indeed.
[CROW]
Hm.
What's this?
[AION]
Interesting.
Who is this Black Swan
spreading his dark wings?
These guys look super lame.
Whoa, wait a sec!
[AION]
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but isn't this the force of
light that shines brightly
in the hearts of girls
everywhere with his sweet,
dulcet tones, better known
as Trichronika's vocalist?
[CROW] Yeah, the same guy
whose clothes flutter
like butterflies,
and who calls his fans
"Dream Galaxy Tourists,"
also known as
Trichronika's vocalist!
[YAIBA] Indeed, it is the man
who uses his frivolous smile
as a weapon, appearing
in his old form,
Trichronika's vocalist!
And?
So it's that annoying guy--
why does it matter?
[YAIBA gasps]
What the heck?! No way!
[AION]
What a revelation!
This could be called
a shocking truth
that overcomes a taboo domain!
Right now, turmoil is
shaking the very universe
within this god!
Indeed, I admit,
when I first saw this
troubling photo, I also
received a Legend of Shock
like I had been hit on the head.
Does this mean Rom
and that flaky Shuzo.
used to play together
in the same band?
Yeah, And they called
themselves "Amatelast."
[AION, CROW gasp]
--What kind of pretentious
--[AION] The name has
--crap is that?
--a sweet ring to it.
And hence, that means
Rom and Shuzo--no,
likely just "Shu"--
once polished their
musical souls together.
[CROW, AION gasp]
Thinking back now...
Blow that off for now.
Let's think of something
cool that'll blow Shuzo's
lame saying right out of the--
[ROM]
Shut up!
Don't say that moron's
name around me!
It's not just about
being popular!
What do you want now, Shu?
Ah, the lovely nostalgia.
You're the only one who
calls me that these days.
[YAIBA] I think we can safely
assume from this demo
and picture that there
is a Legend of Destiny
between Rom and Shuzo.
[CROW]
Yeah.
So... Did you listen to it yet?
[AION]
I'll take that as a "No."
Those who are brave do
such things, and hence.
No, I get it.
It'd be hard to
listen to this alone.
♪
[AMATELAST]
♪ Emotions high ♪
♪ The feelings I ♪
♪ Hold in my hands ♪
♪ Make my rusted heart ♪
♪ Grow even tighter
than before ♪
♪ The pouring rain ♪
♪ It's pounding down ♪
♪ On the broken pavement ♪
♪ And I can't make
the words out ♪
♪ On this hazy night ♪
[AMATELAST] ♪ Fading in
and then disappearing ♪
♪ Offering no clarity ♪
♪ Memories of you and I
are never-ending ♪
♪ Memories too bright
for reality ♪
♪ They were just
illusions, you see ♪
♪ Years have caused these cracks
within our foundation ♪
♪ (Take me away) ♪
♪ I'll say goodbye
to illusions ♪
♪ That give rise to confusion ♪
♪ (My Heart) ♪
♪ Melting away the
future promises made ♪
♪ They melt away into eternity ♪
♪ And fade into the sky ♪
♪ Emotions high ♪
♪ The feelings I ♪
♪ Hold in my hands ♪
♪ Make my rusted heart ♪
♪ Grow even tighter
than before ♪
♪ The pouring rain ♪
♪ It's pounding down ♪
♪ On the broken pavement ♪
♪ And I can't make
the words out ♪
♪ On this hazy night ♪
♪
Ah.
[RIKU] Let's not do it right
now after all, brother.
If we did, we'd be interrupting
Shuzo's civilized time.
But Shuzo doesn't have any
time that isn't civilized!
We'd be putting it off forever!
That may be true, but--
Come on. Let's go, Riku.
Hold on a second!
[SHUZO]
Hey, twins!
[BOTH gasp]
Come over here and have a seat.
Enjoy some nice
milk tea with me.
Sure.
Okay.
[SHUZO]
Well?
Well what?
I believe there was something
you wanted to talk
to me about, yes?
Ah-- Uh, yes.
[gasps] We, uh, wanted
to ask about this.
Huh?
[SHUZO] "From Judas, the
agency of the supernova band
Trichronika, this band stands
at the top of Midi City
right after their debut."
Hm, I see. Nice article.
And what would be
the problem here, twins?
Are you saying a newer
band that happens to hail
from our agency shouldn't
get their shot at stardom?
This should be a happy
occasion for all of us!
Actually, I agree
with you there.
Except...
What we're bothered by
is something else.
The article below that one.
Huh?
[SHUZO]
"ARCAREAFACT beat
BRR'S SHINGANCRIMSONZ
by a huge margin
at the recent battle
of the bands.
But there are
rumors of cheating."
The members of ARCAREA
all happen to be pretty wealthy.
There are stories
circling around that they
relied on the power
of money to win.
[SHUZO]
Kai, Riku.
You two really do have
the kindest of hearts,
almost to a fault.
Listen, you mustn't be
swayed by the rumors
in these gossip papers.
Haven't I always told you?
Our job is to make joy.
To bring extraordinary music
to all the fans out there
and make them happy.
To fill hearts with pleasure
and delight and enrich lives!
The hearts of those
who truly love music
cannot be bought with
money in any amount!
Yeah, you're right!
Thanks, Shuzo!
I'm glad we talked
to you about this.
I feel so much better now!
[chuckles] That's good to hear.
[YAIBA]
Listen, we can't ask Rom
about this directly, understood?
[AION] Even a god such
as myself must agree
with those words.
For real? What's wrong?
You two are like the
biggest 'fraidy-chickens
I've ever seen!
[laughs] That settles it, then.
Looks like I, the great Crow,
will take care of business!
Listen up, Rom!
I got a question for ya!
You guys are late as hell!
Are we? Oh, sorry
about that, dude.
[CYAN whines] If I don't
come up with something soon,
it'll be too late! I'm
running out of time here.
I'm sure they're
all looking forward
to hearing this new song.
And I still don't have anything.
Even if I finally
get the song done,
that won't be the end of it.
We'll need to rehearse it,
and I'm taking away
from our precious practice time!
But knowing that's
not making me
come up with the
song any faster!
I should've just said
"Let's write it together"
from the very start!
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid!
I give up.
I'll just talk to the
others and-- No, I can't!
How am I supposed to
tell them that even after
all this time that I still
don't have anything?
--I'm doomed!
--[knocking]
Um. Yes?
Hey, sweetie.
May I come in for a moment?
So, Cyan. How are you?
How're things going?
Great! Really great!
Couldn't be better!
[CYAN]
Not great at all.
That's good to hear!
Anyway, I don't mean to take up
too much of your time, but...
I got you something!
It's an herb candle.
The fragrance is
supposed to relax you
and refresh your mood.
Thank you so much!
[CHUCHU]
Well, see you tomorrow, then!
[CYAN] Yeah. Sorry for
making you worry, meow.
Remember, we're counting on you.
Yeah! Right.
[CYAN]
Stupid Cyan!
You were supposed to tell her
that you don't
have anything yet!
Something just doesn't
feel right about this.
[knocking]
Yes, who is it?
Pyuru!
Cyan, are you all right, pyuru?
Yeah! I'm totally fine.
[CYAN] No, that's a lie!
I'm not fine at all!
So are you maybe feeling hungry?
[CYAN]
Uh... Well, I...
[MOA]
Here! Donuts, pyuru!
Oh, wow! They look delicious!
[MOA]
Well, I'll leave you to it.
[CYAN]
Thanks, Moa. I appreciate it!
I'm looking forward to
hearing the new song, pyuru!
Right! Sure!
[CYAN]
Ugh, I'm in so much trouble!
It's... no use.
[knocking]
Y-Yes?
Hey there. You got a minute?
Tell me. How's the
song writing going?
Smoothly?
For sure! Smooth as silk!
It's almost done, in fact!
Everything okay?
Did I come at a bad time?
[CYAN]
N-No, really!
You know,
if you need a change of
pace from all this work.
Like, if you wanna play
a game, or surf around
on the internet or something,
you can do it in my room.
It's always open to you.
Stop by whenever, okay?
Sure! That's very sweet of you.
I'll keep that
in mind. Thank you!
Cyan, are you sure
you're all right?
Uh-huh.
Night, then.
Don't work too hard!
Okay.
[door closes]
[CYAN]
What am I doing?
What's wrong with me?
No one's rushing me to finish.
Instead, they're all
worried about me.
So, what now? What should I do?
[MOA]
What?! Cyan ran away, pyuru?
"Please don't look for me.
I'll be fine."
What does this mean?
[MOA]
I don't get it!
What was she so
worried about, pyuru?
I'm just guessing here,
but what if she got
stuck trying to write
the new song for us?
Maybe, but...
[RETOREE]
Cyan, why?
[CYAN]
"Sorry for leaving so suddenly,
and I must apologize
for being selfish.
Is there any way you can give
me just a little more time?
Please, just a little more."
Hello, Mr. Berry!
Yo! Hey, Cyan!
Long time no see!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Chuchu! ♪
[CHUCHU]
Okay, sugars. Let's do this!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Cyan! ♪
[CYAN] It's time for everyone
to hear our music!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Retoree! ♪
[RETOREE]
We're so perfectly in tune.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Moa! ♪
[MOA]
Pyuru, pyuru, pyuru...!
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Tell me
Why I'm so happy with you? ♪
♪ Tell me
How we have so much fun ♪
I know I'm ready for it ♪
♪ Let's (Fine!) go! (Fine!) ♪
♪ Sing for the show!
(Let's go) ♪
♪ CHU-CHU-CHU
CHU-CHU CHU CHU-LU-LU ♪
♪ CHU-LU-LU-LU ♪
[CYAN] ♪ I feel like the
thumping of my heart ♪
♪ is speeding up the rhythm ♪
♪ What can I do?
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My spirit is so electrified ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want to
(Que sera sera sera) ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Our memories
are piling up like photos ♪
♪ In a picture album of
melodies (Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[MOA] ♪ When I need recharging
all I have to do ♪
♪ Is play the album
of my memories (Yay!) ♪
[CYAN] ♪ We'll keep writing
all these new songs ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ Our imagination won't stop ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU]
♪ Almost done! ♪
[RETOREE, MOA]
♪ (Precious number one music) ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Now put it
all together! Yay! ♪
♪ Tell me
How you inspire music ♪
♪ In me?
My singing is all for you ♪
♪ Tell me
Why I never noticed until now? ♪
♪ (My song is you!!) ♪
♪ I know, it's all
in my subconcious ♪
♪ I know, you're with me
through everything ♪
♪ I know, you're
in my heart forever ♪
♪ Always (Fine! Fine!) ♪
♪ I love you (Once more) ♪
♪ Singing with you! (Yay!) ♪
[ROM] It's been a while
since our last training camp!
[CROW] Rom, there's
something I wanted--
[MAPLE]
You should deepen your bonds
even more this time!
Another word for
"bonds" is "ties."
That's in the title of an
old tv show, I believe.
♪ What would we do, baby... ♪
[CROW] Prez, will you
please just go home!
[MAPLE]
Wait, are you talkin' to me?