[OPERATOR A]
Victorious, ma'am.
Preparations to attack the
target are now complete.
[VICTORIOUS]
Excellent.
[sighs] What a lovely
place it was.
Sound Planet.
I heard its sound energy
increased exponentially
after "a certain
point in time"--
very fortunate.
It was wonderful
and vibrant power.
Completely worthy
of my little plan.
Now, let me hear the
Black Hole Canon sing.
[OPERATORS]
Yes, ma'am!
[OPERATOR B]
Time alignment, check.
[OPERATOR C]
Power, check.
[OPERATOR A]
Begin gun barrel deployment.
[VICTORIOUS laughing]
[OPERATOR A]
Deployment completed.
Gun barrel, fixed.
Begin charging.
[OPERATOR B]
Compressor at critical.
[OPERATOR C]
Calculations, check.
[OPERATOR A]
Release the safety.
Target, Sound Planet.
[VICTORIOUS cackles]
Fire!
[CROWD cheering]
Love me up..."Eternity"
Die Otherwise...
"Falling in Hell"
I'll be looking down on you
Einsamkeit...
Luge... Zweifel...
...Zuchtigen
Platonic fairy tale, so
overwhelmed by darkness I find
That your beauty is
burned into my memory
My love for you is so
intense it drives me crazy!
-- I just want to die
--[VICTORIOUS cackles]
Follow me to hell,
and we can waltz together
into the abyss of dependence
Fall onto your knees,
look with me,
in the shards of broken dreams
And gaze into reflections
of our masochistic love
Deep within your eyes, I can
see, your desire to serve me
You've let me love
all parts of you
so now I'll break
your heart in two
Dominieren
Fall onto your knees,
look with me...
[ARASHI]
Oh, no. Disaster.
At this rate, Midi City will
be destroyed in moments.
We're in danger of losing
all the music to her darkness!
Then we must do
what only we can do.
[OBORO]
We must foil the Queen's plot
before she succeeds.
Then our only choice
is to return to the past!
Kamui, the rest is up to you.
Ninja Art: Lightning Shuriken!
[RIN, OBORO]
Aye, sir!
Love me up..."Eternity"
Die Otherwise...
"Falling in Hell"
[MAPLE]
Hey, listen up!
I've got some
scuttlebutt for you!
Guess what, you guys?
A brand new theme park
was just completed
in our own Midi City!
It's called Pyu-roo Land,
isn't that the cutest?
And if that's not exciting
enough news for ya.
There's gonna be
a big ol' concert
to commemorate
the grand openin'!
[GROUP]
Huh?
[MAPLE]
However!
It is not just anyone
who'll get to play
in this special
concert, you know.
They must be able pass
through a narrow gate,
squeezing themselves down.
All the while, wondering if
they can get through or not,
the suspense is killing them.
Almost there. Almost there.
[ANGELICA]
President.
[whip lashing]
Ah!
[MAPLE] So, ladies,
in order to earn your place
in the concert's lineup,
we're gonna have to get you
back on stage and
playing your hearts out
again from now on.
An inaugural
concert's a big deal!
We definitely wanna win a
spot in that show, don't we?
It'll get us all moving
forward again, for sure.
And I really like the
name "Pyu-roo Land."
It sounds awfully
familiar to me, pyuru!
[door chimes]
[ROSIA]
President, Angelica,
and while I'm at it,
my sweet Big Sisters.
Good morning to all of you!
[MAPLE] Oh, Rosia!
I'm so happy you're here!
Yay!
[growls]
[HOLMY]
Good morning, everyone!
[JACKLYN]
Yo, what's happening, guys!
It's lovely to see you all!
Yeah, Pyuru!
So, about that
theme park concert.
We've been asked
to perform in it,
but it looks like
you haven't? So weird!
Uh, sorry?
Well, we have a lot of big hits.
So many, in fact, that from
the very beginning, see,
we were guaranteed a spot in it!
[giggles]
Oh! But if you really wanna
be there, I know a producer--
Well, bless your heart, honey.
I see you're concerned,
but we'll be fine.
Rosia, watch what you're saying.
[JACKLYN] Yeah, we don't
know anything yet!
[laughs nervously]
Are you gonna eat that?
[MAPLE] With Criticrista
on the roster now,
Banded Rocking Records
will be an even bigger
force to be reckoned with!
Now let's all be friends
so your performances
can live up to that--
[CROW]
Hold it right there!
[ALL gasp]
[CROW] ♪ Born in a
moment too resolute ♪
♪ Crimson and scarlet adorning
the crown of the head ♪
♪ to the feet ♪
Crow has arrived!
[AION] ♪ Shaken by darkness,
and hiding in darkness ♪
♪ and covered in darkness
and forbidden waves of black ♪
Black monster, Aion.
[YAIBA] ♪ Searching all
throughout the land ♪
♪ to find a way to rule over ♪
♪ every savage living
thing on Earth ♪
♪ That's the mind
of the dragon fox ♪
Hence, Yaiba appears
bearing his legendary
dragon sword.
ROM]
♪ Secrets of men ♪
♪ Secrecy is what gives
grown men spice ♪
♪ That is the truth,
I tell you no lie ♪
♪ For my name is Rom! ♪
[CROW, AION, YAIBA, ROM]
♪ Sing on your knees, ♪
♪ all of you cattle ♪
♪ Be baptized in our crimson ♪
♪ Through your reverie,
fate will be changed ♪
♪ SHINGANCRIMSONZ ♪
Yo, Prez! What's the big idea?
You forgot all
about us, didn't you?
That's not cool!
[MAPLE]
Eh, what was that?
Ah! Don't you play
dumb with me, egg man!
We, SHINGANCRIMSONZ,
the agency's fiery,
passionate stars, will carry
the coming Apocalypse
with scarlet wings
burning crimson!
That's nice to hear.
Keep up the good work, kid.
President, you've really
changed a lot, man.
We true soldiers create
our music from the soul.
Day and night, scattering
our crimson sparks
all over those who seek 'em.
Did you forget us, for real?
The Legend of Shame
parades around
with a foolish and
lewd countenance
as though it's something
to be proud of.
Hence, the act of foolishness
deserves certain death!
[AION]
Was it a lie when we swore
that we would stand
at the top together?
The sin of causing offense
with the power of words
is deeper than even
the depths of hell.
This is inarguable.
Enjoy melting into Hades!
[MAPLE]
Ha, ha!
[screams]
All this talk about
big concerts reminds me
of when we played the
Grateful Rock Festival.
[MAPLE]
Ah! Not the face!
I wonder.
How's everyone doing now?
Ah!
[MAPLE] Oh ya, there wathum
other big newsth to thare!
It so happens, there's
also a major concert
this weekend sponsored by BRR.
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
You wait to tell us
this till now?
[EMCEE]
Hey, superfans!
Welcome to Banded
Rocking Records'
Futures Live Concert!
--[PIG MOUSSE] Plasmagica!
--[PIG MACARON] SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
[EMCEE] To kick things off,
up first, of course,
are BRR's shock troops,
SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
[CROW] We gaze at you,
with our burning crimson eyes,
and continue to love you,
as we always will.
[CROW, AION, ROM, YAIBA]
SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
Now let's party, all you cattle!
[snorting]
[CROWD cheering]
♪
[CHUCHU] You jazzed about
our first concert in ages?
I know that when Cyan went home,
it left a huge hole
in our hearts and the band
that's hard to fill,
but as usual,
let's still do the best we can!
Yeah, you're right, Chuchu.
She's not actually here,
but no matter what,
she's always with us in spirit.
No question!
I bet wherever she is, she'll
be able to hear us playing
and she'll be rocking out, too!
Yes, I'm sure of it.
[knocking]
Hello, my big sisters!
Rosia and, her super miracle
pretty band, Cri-Cri,
will make sure to
totally kill it tonight
as the closing act of the show.
So don't you worry
about a thing, 'kay?
Oh, pyuru.
Middle school brat.
[SHINGANCRIMSONZ]
♪ Flowers drenched with ♪
♪ the blunders of society ♪
♪ I gather them,
with my own hands. ♪
♪ They vanish in the darkness ♪
♪ I seek what I can
from my periphery ♪
♪ As I descend, to my
own end, I search ♪
♪ For the destiny unknown,
so out of reach, ♪
♪ Thus is the mortal coil ♪
[CROWD cheers]
[HOLMY]
Hey, I noticed something.
The girls from Plasmagica
seem really lost
without Cyan in
the band, don't they?
Well, like, they did
start out as a trio.
So, to me, they're just like
the OG Plasmagica now.
Yeah.
A strawberry shortcake should
always have sponge cake,
strawberries, and whipped cream,
but I think it's better
to have custard cream, too.
'Cause that makes
it extra special!
[ROSIA]
Hm.
[EMCEE]
They're minus one member now,
but fear not--their music
is still alive and kickin'!
Give it up for
Plasmagica!
♪
[CHUCHU]
Now, let's do it.
With our ultra-best performance.
To make the ultra-best smiles!
[CHUCHU, MOA, RETOREE]
Ready, go!
[gasps]
[DAGGER chuckles]
[DAGGER cackles]
[CROWD gasping]
[yells]
[ALL grunting]
Hang on, girls!
What's happening?
[MAPLE]
Wait. Don't tell me...
Who is she?
[MAPLE]
Look there's Dagger!
Oh, come on!
Why is he here?
[MOA]
Pyuru!
[DAGGER chuckles]
[DAGGER cackles]
Oh, no. He came back.
No way!
Hey! What the hell, Aion?
The yakiniku bento is mine!
Get your stinkin'
paws off of it!
[AION muffled] I'm merely
following the strict orders...
Ugh!
Stop talking with your
mouth full, it's so gross!
Ah, gimme my lunch
before it's gone!
[ROM]
Crow, shut your pie hole!
[DAGGER] Hello again, ladies
and gentlemen of Midi City.
You remember me, don't you?
I suppose I will introduce
myself, just in case.
My name is Dagger Morse.
Thanks to these girls,
I am fortuitously
making a comeback.
Tonight, we celebrate
my resurrection.
But first, It would be
impolite not to show
some gratitude to those
who have consigned me
to my current state of being.
[gasps]
[screams]
[RETOREE, MOA screaming]
[DAGGER cackles]
[DAGGER]
Huh?
I'm sorry, but, who are you?
Don't worry. You're
going to be all right.
So, you must be
the Queen of Darkness.
I see.
You are in an evil
alliance with Dagger.
This is the end of
your diabolical scheme!
Prepare for destruction!
[DAGGER] Hm. It appears
a nuisance has arrived.
We'll excuse
ourselves for today.
Get back here, Dagger!
Damn it all. They got
away from us!
What? Great.
[OBORO]
I have blundered.
Prez! Are you okay?
What happened?
What about the concert?
[MAPLE]
You mean...
You didn't see that?
[CROW]
Hm?
What?! Seriously?
That slippery jellyfish bastard!
Please forgive me.
My name is Arashi
of Ninjin Riot.
I am Rin, from the same group.
[OBORO]
As am I. Call me Oboro.
[ARASHI] We have come
from the future to stop
the schemes of the leader
of Planet Victorian,
also known as
the Queen of Darkness,
who is trying to take
over Sound Galaxy.
[PLASMAGICA gasps]
The future, pyuru?
You traveled through
space and time?
[ARASHI]
We did.
How cool! It sounds like
the plot of a science fiction
B-movie, doesn't it?
Young lady, this is
anything but fiction.
Something terrible is
about to happen here.
What do you mean by "terrible"?
In the near future,
Midi City will be decimated!
[ALL gasp]
Decimated? You mean
destroyed, right?
That would be awful!
C'mon, give us all the details!
The Queen of Darkness'
goal is to drain
all Melodisian stones
of their power.
And use that energy to take
over Sound Galaxy for herself.
Her intention: to silence
the music in this world.
[ALL gasp]
[OBORO] We suspect the
lead vocalist of the band
you saw earlier,
the one with Dagger,
is the Queen of Darkness,
but in disguise.
[PLASMAGICA gasps]
Wait, did we miss
something before?
[CHUCHU]
Uh-huh!
We will continue investigating.
Will you help us?
We'll expose her true identity,
and then defeat her,
along with her
hideous ally, Dagger.
How? The power of music.
Oh, yeah!
Nobody trashes our city
and gets away with it--
not while we're around!
Don't worry about it,
man! We got this!
[YAIBA]
Hence.
We will stop her by
any means necessary.
[AION] This dark sun
god proudly supports
and condones the
above declarations.
Damn it!
I don't know who this
Queen of Darkness is,
but she'll know me
when I pay her a visit
with my Third Generation
Crimson Knuckle!
Taste the crimson!
Well, that sounds
very effective.
We'll also do what
we can to help
our beloved Midi City.
Pyuru!
[OBORO]
Then, we leave it to you.
Ninja Art: Lightning Shuriken!
[RIN, OBORO]
Aye, sir!
They just took off?
Sure looks that way.
[ROSIA]
How did Dagger find us again?
Why? No more, I can't take it!
[piano music playing]
[CHUCHU] Because of Cyan
having come here,
peace finally returned
to this city.
I thought that meant
I could simply enjoy
music again forever after.
I guess not.
Can we do this without her?
I'm not so sure.
[sighs]
[MOA] Yum, strawberry.
It takes me back, pyuru.
[keyboard tapping]
[RETOREE sighs]
I can't seem to
concentrate on anything.
[RETOREE]
Cyan, I miss you.
[CYAN]
Mm.. This sounds all wrong.
And it won't work, either.
Ugh.
[CYAN]
Oh, no. I'm running out of time.
And to make matters even worse,
it's our band's very
first performance.
Oh! Why'd I have to tell
them I'd write the song?
"Hey, Cyan, wanna
write a new song
for the school festival?"
"Oh, yeah! That sounds
great, I'd love to!"
Sure, I meant it,
but so far, I've only
got a big donut!
"Oh hey, Cyan, is it done?"
"Uh, I, um, yeah, totally! Sure!
Ready in a jiffy!"
Now what?
I can't exactly tell
them I haven't even
written one note yet.
I'm so dead!
[CYAN]
You guys. I miss you!
♪ Counting every star I see, ♪
♪ observing quietly, ♪
♪ trying hard to hide
the sadness I feel. ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Have you noticed it at all? ♪
♪ When I think about
what could have been, ♪
♪ my heart starts
slowly breaking. ♪
♪ I get so restless, ♪
♪ my nights are sleepless ♪
♪ I'm waiting here for you, ♪
♪ hoping you'll make
my wish come true ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Falling through
the sky, star of dreams ♪
♪ Shining brightly
in the night ♪
♪ I wanna be with you
and we could watch ♪
♪ Just you and I ♪
♪ No matter how
far away we may be ♪
♪ From each other now ♪
♪ I know someday ♪
♪ That our hearts
will beat as one. ♪
A shooting star!
Huh?
Or is it?
[gasps]
[yelps]
[screams]
Ow.
What on earth was that thing?
[gasps, screams]
[KAMUI]
Cyan Hijirikawa, yes?
Uh--
[KAMUI]
Come with me. Right now.
[gasps]
I don't believe this. Not again!
[screams]
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Chuchu! ♪
[CHUCHU]
Okay, sugars. Let's do this!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Cyan! ♪
[CYAN] It's time for everyone
to hear our music!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Retoree! ♪
[RETOREE]
We're so perfectly in tune.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Moa! ♪
[MOA]
Pyuru, pyuru, pyuru...!
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Tell me
Why I'm so happy with you? ♪
♪ Tell me
How we have so much fun ♪
I know I'm ready for it ♪
♪ Let's (Fine!) go! (Fine!) ♪
♪ Sing for the show!
(Let's go) ♪
♪ CHU-CHU-CHU
CHU-CHU CHU CHU-LU-LU ♪
♪ CHU-LU-LU-LU ♪
[CYAN] ♪ I feel like the
thumping of my heart ♪
♪ is speeding up the rhythm ♪
♪ What can I do?
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My spirit is so electrified ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want to
(Que sera sera sera) ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Our memories
are piling up like photos ♪
♪ In a picture album of
melodies (Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[MOA] ♪ When I need recharging
all I have to do ♪
♪ Is play the album
of my memories (Yay!) ♪
[CYAN] ♪ We'll keep writing
all these new songs ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ Our imagination won't stop ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU]
♪ Almost done! ♪
[RETOREE, MOA]
♪ (Precious number one music) ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Now put it
all together! Yay! ♪
♪ Tell me
How you inspire music ♪
♪ In me?
My singing is all for you ♪
♪ Tell me
Why I never noticed until now? ♪
♪ (My song is you!!) ♪
♪ I know, it's all
in my subconcious ♪
♪ I know, you're with me
through everything ♪
♪ I know, you're
in my heart forever ♪
♪ Always (Fine! Fine!) ♪
♪ I love you (Once more) ♪
♪ Singing with you! (Yay!) ♪
[MAPLE]
Oh, no!
The universe will be destroyed
by its accelerating expansion!
I mean, by an attack by
Sound Planet's greatest enemy,
the Queen of Darkness!
[MOA]
I'm starving!
What should I eat for
dinner tonight, pyuru?
[MAPLE] Moa, you're
just so. You're so Moa.