[CROW laughs]
[CROW] I did it! I wrote
another amazing song!
Am I awesome or am I awesome?
[MAPLE] Training camp went
well then, I take it?
Hell yeah it did!
This masterpiece is as sharp
as the blade of a knife.
And it'll cut through
the darkness
of Midi City like butter!
It's the jam, I tell ya!
As usual, yours truly
was in charge
of writing the lyrics,
but this time,
to shake things up a bit,
I joined forces
with Yaiba and Aion
to hash out our collective
apocalyptic feelings
into this magnum opus!
That's what
SHINGANCRIMSONZ is all--
[ROM]
You're taking too long!
Slow your roll, Rom!
We finished the song ourselves!
The least you could--!
Enough! Look!
The president's so bored,
he's sleeping!
You bastard, Wake up!
What kind of manager decides
to take a nap during
one of his artists giving
a passionate speech
about the making of a new song?
No, no, I wasn't sleeping,
I was flabbergasted!
Your new song is so amazing,
it left me breathless
and I passed out!
Makes perfect sense, right?
Ha, ha! It blew your mind!
Why don't you call that
"Arcade Ray of Fart"
or whatever the hell
they're called and--
Get it right. It's
ARCAREAFACT, so hence.
Yeah, what he said.
Call those rich boys up
for a battle of the bands
vengeance match!
[MAPLE]
You got it! Just leave it to me!
Wait a minute, President.
Is a rematch battle really
the best idea right now?
[MAPLE] You mean because of
the rumors going around?
Yes.
[MAPLE] I have an idea how
to fix that situation.
[ANGELICA]
Huh?
♪
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Pumping Jumping! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CYAN] ♪ Dontcha come at me
with your monotone ♪
♪ Feelin' somethin'
more harmonious ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Waiting, to take a breath ♪
♪ I look, listen,
oh so carefully ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Oh baby,
can you hear the chords ♪
♪ Soundin' sweet the more
we rock the pop ♪
[MOA] ♪ Let's mix and
match our swing now ♪
♪ To make the music that we've
all been feelin' inside ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ (Passhuwa!
Pappasshuwa! Pashuwa, yes!) ♪
[CYAN]
♪ 'Cause even in my dreams ♪
♪ I hear the sound
of your voice ♪
[CHUCHU] ♪ In you I finally see
There is no other choice ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ I know I can
keep pushing ahead ♪
♪ And that I can really change ♪
[MOA] ♪ All I need is
to find melodies ♪
♪ I haven't
discovered just yet ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ Everybody Rock!
Rock! Give it your all! ♪
♪ Just sing and be yourself! ♪
♪ Keep on keepin' on
and on and on and on ♪
♪ and cramming emotions
into your music ♪
♪ Everybody Rock! Rock!
With all your heart! ♪
♪ And soon you'll
hear new melodies ♪
♪ Hear the pulsing beat ♪
♪ The power of the rhythm ♪
♪ The magic never stops ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ All you need is
harmony (words don't matter) ♪
♪ Honesty
(With your feelings) ♪
♪ Keep on strumming! Keep on
going! Keep on and on! ♪
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
Eh, heh! Well, what do ya know?
Right when they happened
to cross my mind,
because they'd dropped
right off the map,
it seems Tsurezure
are on an expedition.
How funny! Ha, ha!
A-ha! Maybe they're contestants
on a reality TV show!
Enough about that.
Anyone heard from Titan?
[ARGON]
Shyaa?
[SELEN] Huh. Now that you
mention it, I haven't.
I wonder where he is.
[phone rings]
[GRAMPS]
Yes?
One moment, I'll ask.
Young Master, a
representative from BRR
is calling to say
that SHINGANCRIMSONZ
have requested a battle
of the bands rematch.
What should I tell them?
Huh. What good does it do
us to beat them again?
Refuse.
[GRAMPS]
Very well, sir.
I'd reconsider that.
What do you mean? What for?
[VICTORIOUS] You should
accept this challenge.
But, why?
[VICTORIOUS] It would appear
that their first defeat
wasn't enough.
You should crush them again.
So thoroughly, they would
never even consider
challenging you a third time.
Make Midi City shout
from the rooftops
even more about how
wonderful your music is.
You're right. Put
them in their place.
Gramps. Tell them we accept.
Very well, Young Master.
Thank you for waiting.
They accept your challenge.
[NICKEL]
Wow! Looks yummy!
Here you go. Some for you!
Ha! Yay! Let's eat!
[BALT]
Wait! Not yet!
We'll eat together as a family
once big brother gets back.
Just wait till then.
[TITAN]
I'm home!
Sorry I'm so late, you two.
[BALT, NICKEL]
Welcome home, big brother!
We missed you!
And here. Brought you something.
[NICKEL]
Sweets!
You've returned
later than usual.
[TITAN] Yes, someone took
the day off suddenly,
so we didn't have enough people.
Oh, wow! That looks really good!
Let me get you some.
Sorry, I've got practice today.
But I'll have some later.
Okay. Sounds good.
Have a good practice!
Hope it's fun!
[NICKEL]
And come home soon, okay?
I will.
[ROSIA]
I'll find out their weakness.
For Plasmagica's sake
and ours, too.
Today's the day!
Not here again, huh?
Lame.
[ROSIA] That's what she
wants me to think!
Rosia?
Oh, Holmy. What's up, girl?
What are you doing over here
in this part of the building?
This is a high school
classroom, you know.
Nothing, really.
Listen. Are you...
...maybe trying to hide
something from the rest of us?
[ROSIA gasps]
Tsukino and Jacklyn.
We're all worried about you.
And what would you plan on
doing about it if that's true?
I'd think long and hard
about what you're gonna
say to me, if I were you.
[HOLMY]
Rosia?
Huh?
Hiding something?
A number one idol like me
has hundreds of things
to hide at any given time!
A girl's gotta have
her secrets, ya know?
Come on, you know
that's not what I mean.
Like everything is sups fine.
There's no problem at all.
Okay, bye!
Hold on, come back!
[ROSIA]
No.
I can't get everyone
else involved.
[VICTORIOUS]
Yes, that's right.
You boys must keep winning
by whatever means necessary.
First, we raise your popularity.
Once that happens,
the world will be our oyster.
With your current
abilities and wealth,
it's only a matter of
time before ARACREFACT
will stand at the very top.
Your position in the music world
will become immovable.
Sounds good to me.
You're a smart cookie.
Shyaa.
[VICTORIOUS chuckles]
[door opens]
Hey, guys. Sorry I'm late.
[TITAN]
Did something happen?
N-No, of course not!
Well, there's some
business I must attend to.
If you'll excuse me.
[ORION] You're late, Titan.
That's happened a lot lately.
You're not having any trouble
putting the new song
together, I hope.
No, I...
Anyway. So, what were you
all just talking about?
Oh, nothing important.
Just our strategy for
the upcoming rematch
against SHINGANCRIMSONZ.
What do you mean, "strategy"?
You aren't hiding something
from me, are you?
[ORION]
Funny you should ask.
I was curious if you
were keeping any secrets
from your band mates.
[gasps]
He's got a point, Titan.
You've been late more
and more often lately
and you never give us
a reason. Why is that?
Well, because...
[ARGON]
Aw, c'mon, guys.
Let's stop talking about
all this boring stuff.
It's practice time. Let's rock!
The more we sit around here,
the more my muscles slowly
turn into fat. Shyaa?
[ORION]
Yes, you're right.
[SELEN]
Agreed!
[RETOREE] Before,
everyone in SHINGAN seemed
really positive, so I
didn't wanna say anything.
But it's a completely
different story
if they're doing another
battle of the bands.
I won't let those guys
cheat 'em again!
Neither will I.
[RETOREE]
In order to stop them,
we need to get some
irrefutable proof!
[CYAN]
Yeah!
[RETOREE]
Oh, by the way.
if you wanna make a dent
in the snacks over there,
help yourself.
[CYAN]
Really? Yay! Thank you!
[CHUCHU]
I understand the situation.
But, first, I wanna thank y'all.
[GROUP gasps]
For coming to talk to us!
It really means a lot!
I agree, pyuru!
No, really.
Thanks for listening.
It sounds like
she's worried that
if she talked to you
about whatever it is
that's bothering her,
all it would end up doing
is causing trouble
for the rest of y'all.
She's keeping things
to herself to protect us?
Rosia, that's totes whack.
She should be able to
talk to us about anything.
I know how you feel, pyuru.
[chuckles] How about
this. Try asking her
if everything's okay
one more time.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[CHUCHU] I'm sure she has
a reason for acting this way,
but with just a little push.
and asking her just
the right way,
you might find you
can resolve this.
I mean it.
We've learned that from
first-hand experience.
Just let her know how
you really feel, okay?
See, Rosia...
...doesn't like to lose and
hardly ever shows any weakness.
So, sometimes, I guess
we take advantage
of her mad determination.
Oh, Rosia. Just tell us
what's bothering you.
Right, we'll do it.
We'll try talking
to her one more time.
Good call!
Do your best, pyuru!
--[JACKLYN] Okay!
--[HOLMY, TSUKINO] 'Kay!
[door opens]
Huh? Holmy!
Hey, Rosia.
Would you mind coming
with me for a bit?
[ROSIA]
Oh, this is where...
What the--?
[BOTH giggle]
[ROSIA]
Hey, girls?
Man, this place takes
you back, doesn't it?
While Tsukino and I were
saving this exact table
for the rest of the band.
students from another
school came to pick a fight.
Yeah, 'member?
They said this table had
been reserved for them,
so they made us
get up and leave.
I was so surprised.
I accidentally dropped the
ice cream cone I was holding.
But then, you saw
what has happening
and stepped up to face them,
head on, without fear.
[ROSIA]
Listen up!
I'm not buying this
"reserved" crap!
I think you just made
that up to get your way!
But, more importantly,
you made my friend cry,
and I won't stand for that.
You better apologize or
I'll beat one out of you!
We came to depend
on your confidence
and strength, and your
ability to lead us
through whatever may happen.
You're way strong, yo,
but don't you think
it's all right for you to
come to us for help sometimes?
If we approach
problems together,
we'll have four times
the courage to face them.
Ten thousand times the courage!
[gasps]
And remember, we're not
just your band mates,
we're your friends, too.
And what else are
friends for, right?
Holmy...
[ROSIA] Aw, man, look
what you made me do.
[HOLMY, TSUKINO, JACKLYN giggle]
[ROSIA] Fine then.
I'll tell you everything.
Thank you. All of you.
[EMCEE 8A]
Yeah!
Today's battle is
a rematch between
SHINGANCRIMSONZ, who suffered
a staggering defeat
in the last round,
and ARCAREAFACT, the newcomers
on their way to becoming
the top act of Midi City!
It's like a super Battle
of the Bands mega match
to end all matches!
You do not want to miss this!
[FANS cheering]
The time is finally at hand.
[YAIBA]
We have returned after strenuous
and diligent training.
Now we simply must do
what we came here to do.
And hence.
[AION] There is one omnipotent
dark god who will bring
cursed blessings on
tonight's concert.
I am he.
Right! Listen up, guys!
Take all that is
SHINGANCRIMSONZ,
and burn it into
their souls for real!
[YAIBA, CROW, AION]
Hell, yeah!
[car horn blares]
[FANS cheer]
SHINGANCRIMSONZ.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I can't believe you dared
to challenge us again
after being defeated
so soundly before.
Sorry to be the one to tell you,
but no matter what kind
of music you perform,
there's no way you're
going to beat us today.
Huh?
Because the outcome was
decided from the start.
What do you mean by that?
What's this "decided" crap?
[MAPLE]
Wait just a minute!
This go around, we expect you
to fight fair and square!
No cheating allowed--
you got that?
[ANGELICA]
Last time and today, too,
you tried to use your
wealth to buy votes.
You should be
ashamed of yourselves.
What did say? Cheating?
What's this about?
Honestly, I don't have a clue.
Don't pretend like
you're innocent.
This security guard
told us everything.
You paid off all the staff
at the concert hall.
Once you had them
under your thumb,
you somehow managed to
break into the main server
and manipulate the votes.
The evidence for your
cheating operation
is all here, plain as day!
Don't deny it!
The least y'all could
do is fess up to it!
[MOA]
Yeah, pyuru!
No way. You can't be serious.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
Cat's outta the bag, I guess.
No point in denying it.
Aw, man.
I wish we could've at least
finished this concert
before you confronted
us about it.
Shyaa. Caught us red-handed.
[hisses]
You'll pay for this.
[ORION] If you really wanna
get your music out there,
and become popular
as quickly as possible,
then money is the answer
to all of your problems.
What about you hobos
and that rinky-dink
little agency you're with?
Don't pretend like you're
really satisfied there!
We're wealthy!
Guilty as charged!
And since we have that wealth,
what's wrong with using it
to help us get to the top?
[ROM]
Bastard!
[gasps]
What the hell?
Get outta my way, Shu!
I'm not moving.
Whatever quarrel you have with
them doesn't matter to me.
They're my juniors.
[SHUZO]
Rom, You shouldn't be trying
to settle this with violence.
Let the music do the
fighting for you!
Let's go.
Uh, okay.
[ROM]
I may be pissed, but he's right.
Tonight, we'll fight with our
souls and the music they bare!
If you think you can win
everything with money,
you're dead wrong.
Tonight's match is
going to teach you
an important lesson.
You'll figure out
what matters the most.
[GROUP gasps]
Well then!
Good luck! Ta-ta!
Damn it.
Enough!
What were they talking about?
What kind of deceptive crap
were you doing behind my back?
Titan!
Take it easy!
[TITAN]
Listen up, you guys.
I don't know what
really happened,
but with our musical talent
and a lot of hard work,
we can make it to the top
without cheating to get there!
We're artists, remember?
Don't deny the souls of music
inside every one of you!
Titan...
[ARCAREAFACT]
♪ Just awake ♪
♪ We'll play to the beat ♪
♪ Our souls ring out ♪
♪ Bringing light
into the moments ♪
♪ that were hidden
away in the dark ♪
♪ Take our pride... ♪
Listen to them!
They're so amazingly talented!
They didn't even need to
cheat in the first place!
Yeah, you're right, brother.
They should've just fought
fair from the very beginning.
Inside them, there's
something happening
and I'm worried it's
not something good.
♪
[gasps]
[SHINGANCRIMSONZ]
♪ We all go about our lives ♪
♪ Everyone has their own pride ♪
♪ Clashing one on one
then moving on ♪
♪ To the world that's
next in line ♪
♪ Souls unshakeable are
flames that bind us ♪
♪ Together we all hold
the light inside ♪
♪ Entrusting all we have ♪
♪ And all we know
into this song ♪
♪
♪ Flickering through illusions
of a summer day ♪
♪ Covered head to toe in sweat ♪
♪ So much so we take
our shirts off ♪
♪ Since then we've
all been walking ♪
♪ Forward day by day ♪
♪ Straight up the hill ♪
♪ Just hoping we will find ♪
♪ The answer ♪
♪ Struggling for what we want ♪
♪ We're fighting to go on ♪
♪ Changing ♪
♪ Through the honesty
of our emotions ♪
♪ Once again ♪
♪ Ah, One rising
after the other ♪
♪ Just like the sun
and the moon ♪
♪ With light inside each one ♪
♪ The same one we all share ♪
♪ Even as the blowing wind ♪
♪ Changes direction onto me ♪
♪ I still feel a warmth
from deep within ♪
♪ It's a warmth I can't forget ♪
♪ Though I walk a path
full of misery ♪
♪ Where shadow lives... ♪
Okay. Shall we go, twins?
[RIKU]
Huh?
[KAI]
You've seen enough already?
Indeed.
[BOTH gasp]
[SHUZO]
Kai, Riku.
Every single moment
I'm with you two,
you always make me shine!
Thank you, my friends.
[BOTH]
Sure!
Now, shall we be going?
[FANS cheer]
[EMCEE 8A] All right, everyone!
It's on for real today!
You all know what to do, right?
[EMCEE 8A]
Tonight's winner is...
...the band who played
their latest song
and performed with
burning crimson,
SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
Yeah!
"Performed with
burning crimson."
True.
[laughs] We did it, guys!
Good job. You were
amazing, Crow.
I grabbed the cattle by
the ears and took them
on a first-class
trip to paradise!
[laughs]
[BALT, NICKEL]
Big brother!
Hey, you two!
Nice work!
You guys may have lost,
but you were great!
That song was so amazing!
ARCAREAFACT's the best ever!
Think so?
Titan, I'm sorry.
Your beautiful song was
sullied by our cheating.
Orion, there's something
that I've been hiding
from the band, as well.
You see, I've been acting
like the rest of you,
like nothing happened,
but the truth is,
my father's business went under
and I couldn't bring myself
to tell you, so I hid it.
[GROUP gasps]
Are you serious?
Shyaa?
[ORION] No matter what
may happen, you're still you.
It's not like the songs you
write have changed or anything.
[TITAN]
Thanks.
Shyaa! Let's go back
and have a pity party!
Hey, you two.
If there's anything you want
to eat, just let us know.
[NICKEL]
Really? Yay!
What kind of food
should we ask for?
Manager!
What is she doing,
anyway? Where'd she go?
You know something?
I don't recall seeing
her for some time now.
[phone ringing]
[ORION]
Gramps, what's the matter?
[ORION gasps]
Where are you?
[ORION]
Gramps! What happened?
That manager girl--
she took everything.
Everything! All your
belongings, I'm so sorry!
[ARGON]
Shyaa?
My 22-karat gold workout
machines are all gone!
What kind of a monster
is she? Seriously?
As I thought.
She wiped out the
bank account, too.
Oh, wow. She really
had us fooled.
What's going on here?
Young Master.
My sincere apologies.
I was here, but I
couldn't stop her.
Don't worry about it.
It's fine as long
as you're okay.
You're too kind, Master!
Shyaa. Well, anyway,
what do we do now?
You can come stay with us.
If you wanna.
[ALL but KIDS gasp]
It's okay! Right, Big Brother?
Uh, yeah, sure!
I wonder how we're
all gonna fit, though.
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Tell me
Why I'm so happy with you? ♪
♪ Tell me
How we have so much fun ♪
I know I'm ready for it ♪
♪ Let's (Fine!) go! (Fine!) ♪
♪ Sing for the show!
(Let's go) ♪
♪ CHU-CHU-CHU
CHU-CHU CHU CHU-LU-LU ♪
♪ CHU-LU-LU-LU ♪
[CYAN] ♪ I feel like the
thumping of my heart ♪
♪ is speeding up the rhythm ♪
♪ What can I do?
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My spirit is so electrified ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want to
(Que sera sera sera) ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Our memories
are piling up like photos ♪
♪ In a picture album of
melodies (Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[MOA] ♪ When I need recharging
all I have to do ♪
♪ Is play the album
of my memories (Yay!) ♪
[CYAN] ♪ We'll keep writing
all these new songs ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ Our imagination won't stop ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU]
♪ Almost done! ♪
[RETOREE, MOA]
♪ (Precious number one music) ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Now put it
all together! Yay! ♪
♪ Tell me
How you inspire music ♪
♪ In me?
My singing is all for you ♪
♪ Tell me
Why I never noticed until now? ♪
♪ (My song is you!!) ♪
♪ I know, it's all
in my subconcious ♪
♪ I know, you're with me
through everything ♪
♪ I know, you're
in my heart forever ♪
♪ Always (Fine! Fine!) ♪
♪ I love you (Once more) ♪
♪ Singing with you! (Yay!) ♪
[TSUKINO] The baked sweet
potato came out great!
[HOLMY] Let's all split
it and eat it together!
[JACKLYN]
It's steaming hot!
[ROSIA] This was baked
by yours truly, ya know.
Open wide!