[KAMUI] We have arrived
at our destination.
What is going on here?
[yells]
[KAMUI]
Hm?
Hello.
And jus-just who might
you be pyuru?
[CHUCHU]
Moa! What's going on out here?
[RETOREE gasps]
A robot?
[GIRLS grunts]
What's happening?
Spinning, spinning,
spinning, meowing...
--[RETOREE, CHUCHU] Cyan!
--[MOA] Cyan, pyuru!
[gasps]
♪
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Pumping Jumping! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CYAN] ♪ Dontcha come at me
with your monotone ♪
♪ Feelin' somethin'
more harmonious ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Waiting, to take a breath ♪
♪ I look, listen,
oh so carefully ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Oh baby,
can you hear the chords ♪
♪ Soundin' sweet the more
we rock the pop ♪
[MOA] ♪ Let's mix and
match our swing now ♪
♪ To make the music that we've
all been feelin' inside ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ (Passhuwa!
Pappasshuwa! Pashuwa, yes!) ♪
[CYAN]
♪ 'Cause even in my dreams ♪
♪ I hear the sound
of your voice ♪
[CHUCHU] ♪ In you I finally see
There is no other choice ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ I know I can
keep pushing ahead ♪
♪ And that I can really change ♪
[MOA] ♪ All I need is
to find melodies ♪
♪ I haven't
discovered just yet ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ Everybody Rock!
Rock! Give it your all! ♪
♪ Just sing and be yourself! ♪
♪ Keep on keepin' on
and on and on and on ♪
♪ and cramming emotions
into your music ♪
♪ Everybody Rock! Rock!
With all your heart! ♪
♪ And soon you'll
hear new melodies ♪
♪ Hear the pulsing beat ♪
♪ The power of the rhythm ♪
♪ The magic never stops ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ All you need is
harmony (words don't matter) ♪
♪ Honesty
(With your feelings) ♪
♪ Keep on strumming! Keep on
going! Keep on and on! ♪
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[giggles]
Easy, Moa.
You're gonna rub
her shoulder off!
I could say the same
for you, pyuru!
[ANGELICA] Here. This
should warm you right up.
Aw, thank you so much!
It's been a while, huh, Cyan?
Sure has!
Here, pyuru!
Strawberry! Moa!
Cyan, I gotta say,
I really missed you a lot.
And I missed you, too, Retoree!
By the way, Cyan.
Why're you back in Midi City?
Well, I was thinking
about everybody
and looking up at
the stars, and...
I, uh, well...
[CHUCHU]
Oh, I see.
That has been bothering
me for a while now.
Yeah, pyuru.
Who's that?
[KAMUI]
I am a member of Ninjinriot,
the steel wings that
soar across the sky.
I am called Kamui!
That girl's power
is needed to face
Midi City's greatest crisis.
I undertook the mission
to bring her here.
You're from Ninjinriot?
So, that's the story, pyuru.
Makes as much sense
as anything else.
I heard about everything
that's going on here
from that big guy.
So, it sounds like we have
to find the Queen of Darkness,
who's trying to take
over Sound Galaxy,
and come up with a way to
foil her diabolical plan.
Yes, pyuru.
But, to be honest,
I've been really worried
about facing her.
Well, by ourselves, anyway.
Same here.
But now that Cyan is
by our side once again,
I know we can!
The four of us together
can do anything!
[giggles]
[KAMUI] I have successfully
completed my mission.
I will now return.
[MAPLE]
Hold it right there.
[KAMUI]
Hm?
[MAPLE laughs]
President?
Hey, Mister Robot-
From-The-Future.
I think you've forgotten
something very important.
Luckily, I happen to
have it right here!
[KAMUI]
Is that... a bill?
It's the cost of the repairs
on the building you destroyed.
You're paying this in full
before you go anywhere.
[KAMUI]
The cost of repairs?
[MAPLE]
That's right!
Now cough up the coin,
you giant hunk of tin!
Do it!
[KAMUI]
Sorry!
Bye-bye then...
Another disappearance.
[sputters]
[CYAN]
Wow!
My room looks exactly the same!
Just like I left it!
That's how we wanted it.
We asked the president
to keep it ready for you.
Retoree took time to clean it
every once in a while, pyuru.
Uh...
Yeah. Well, y'know.
Thank you. All of you!
But it's not like we can just
hang out here and relax, huh.
Unfortunately, no.
There's so much more
we need to know.
Who is this Queen
of Darkness, really?
What does she want?
What is she doing?
We ran into her recently.
She actually made
a surprise appearance
at our concert the other day.
[CYAN]
What?
[RETOREE]
And if that wasn't bad enough,
Dagger was with her.
Dagger, too?
Yeah, and it seems that
he's started working
with a band of really
scary-looking girls.
Dagger...
What in the world could
he be planning this time?
Whatever it is,
the best way to
fight back is clear.
We polish up our
skills as a band.
[ALL] ...and defeat them
with the power of music.
Pyuru!
[phone chimes]
Who could this be?
Pyuru!
Moa?
Is there something wrong?
[MOA]
Th-Th-This is bad, pyuru.
Who's it from?
It's my home planet.
I've been-I've been ordered
to return home, pyuru!
[CYAN, CHUCHU, REOTREE]
You what?
What for? What's the reason?
[MOA] The Planet Pyuru
Investigation Committee
is angry because they
haven't been receiving
my scheduled reports.
Is that because you
didn't actually write any?
[MOA]
Pyuru.
Ah, I see.
So does it specify
when they expect you?
Today, pyuru.
[ALL]
Huh?
That light...
What in the world is it?
Who is that?
An investigator
from Planet Pyuru.
[INVESTIGATOR]
Pyuru, rurururu!
Pee-ru.
Pyuru-ruru! Pyururu!
[gasps]
Pyuru-ru-ru-ru!
Pyuru-ru-ru-ru-ru-ru-ru-ru!
[INVESTIGATOR]
Pyuru-ru-ru-ru-ru-ru-ru.
Pyuru! Pyuru-ru-ru-ru.
Pyuru pyuru.
Pyuru-ru!
Moa, would you mind
letting us know
what you're talking about?
I couldn't understand a word.
Could fill us in on
the details, sugar?
[MOA]
Pyuru...
Well, uh...
You see, I... I guess that
"today" means "right now"!
I've been ordered to
leave this very moment
to return to
Planet Pyuru, pyuru!
[ALL]
No way!
[RETOREE]
You're kidding, right?
Pyuru...
[MOA] Everyone,
I'm really sorry, pyuru.
This wouldn't have happened
if I hadn't been slacking off.
And with Cyan back,
I felt like we were about to
really get things
going again, pyuru.
Moa.
[CYAN]
What a mess.
Will it work out somehow?
[CHUCHU]
Wait a second!
Huh?
Nothing says she
has to go alone!
What if we go with her?
[RETOREE, CYAN, MOA]
Huh?!
We can't let something
like this stop us--
there's way too much at stake!
Let's join her and let her
people hear our music.
That should convince
them to let her stay!
[CYAN]
I agree! Great idea, Chuchu!
[RETOREE]
Totally!
And besides, I'm dying
to see Moa's planet!
You guys... Thank you
so much, pyuru!
[MAPLE] Now that
everything's been decided.
Let's be on our way!
[ALL but MAPLE]
Uh...
[MOA]
Pyuru, rururururu!
A group trip!
This is gonna be fun, pyuru!
This ship is amazing!
Yeah, now that I think about it,
this is our first time
riding in it, Moa.
How does it work?
Is it difficult to pilot?
Pyuru-ru, pyuru-ru-ru-ru-ru-ru!
Pyururururu!
[groaning]
[MOA] We've made it safely
out into Sound Galaxy, pyuru!
Okay! Everyone can relax now!
[RETOREE]
What? Already?
[MOA]
Pyuru!
[MOA] In the past, Pyuruians
all lived peacefully
on this happy
little planet, pyuru.
Time marched on.
And even though they never
had any Melodisians,
the people prospered and
the economy grew like "whoa"!
[MOA] In no time,
Pyuruians found themselves
in an energy shortage!
So, in order to look
in to the energy use
and resources of other worlds,
they sent investigators
like yours truly
to different planets
across Sound Galaxy!
Wow.
That's a pretty important
mission, wouldn't you say?
So, since you were slacking
off on that mission,
they ordered you to return.
Pyuru.
[INVESTIGATOR]
Pyurururu--
pyruru.
[MOA] Look! That's
Planet Pyuru, pyuru!
[CYAN]
It's so cute!
Ah!
[CROWD cheers]
[CHUCHU]
Whoa.
[RETOREE] That's uh...
That's a pretty grand welcome.
Meow.
I wonder what all
the hoopla is about?
[MAPLE clears throat]
I am pleasantly surprised that
Banded Rocking Records
have become so famous
in this part of the galaxy.
That it wa--
[laughs]
[MOA]
Papa! Mama!
[MOA'S DAD]
Welcome back, pyuru!
Good to see you, Moa! Pyuru!
Uh, and you are?
[MOA'S DAD]
I am the king of Planet Pyuru,
Hapi the 17th, pyuru.
And this wonderful
woman beside me
is my queen, Meri, pyuru.
Did he say "king"?
"Papa" and "Mama"?
So that means...
Royal Planet Investigator
Crown Princess Moa
of the Pyuru Royal Family
has returned home
as ordered, pyuru!
Did you say "Crown Princess"?
Cat's out of the bag!
I am indeed the princess
of Planet Pyuru.
Surprise?
[CYAN, CHUCHU, RETOREE]
A princess?!
Your Majesties, Mama and Papa.
By your command, I have
returned home, pyuru.
I'm so happy you're here, Moa.
[MOA'S DAD] Ehem. "Good work,
pyuru!" is what I'd like to say,
but you have been
ordered to appear
before the Royal Investigation
Committee first, pyuru.
There, you will
explain the reason
why you did not
turn in your reports
as per the assignment, pyuru.
Understood, pyuru.
Now, now, dear. Please.
Moa's only just arrived.
[MOA'S DAD]
Pyuru?
She's returned safely
after a long journey.
[MOA'S DAD]
But, pyuru!
Moa, are these people
accompanying you today
the same ones who have
been taking care of you
on Sound Planet, pyuru?
[MOA]
Yes, Pyuru.
Let's worry about the
details tomorrow, pyuru.
Tonight, we'll have
a banquet to welcome
our honored guests, pyuru!
--[MOA gasps]
--[RETOREE, CYAN, CHUCHU sigh]
Thanks!
[CHUCHU] Moa, if you're
the princess here,
why'd you come to Midi City
as an investigator?
I specifically requested
the assignment
because I was born in this
castle and I'd never left it.
I wanted to know firsthand
what life was like
in the outside world, pyuru.
[MAPLE]
Very admirable.
I'm worried.
What if I'm not able
to convince them?
I mean, I was
neglectful of my duties.
[COYOTE howls]
[MOA'S DAD laughs]
I feel like we've known
each other forever, pyuru!
Agreed! We've bonded
like brothers, pyuru!
[BOTH]
You're drinking too much.
Pyuru.
Oh, my.
Is this some kind of
delicacy, or...?
I'm not eating that.
[WAITRESS 2A]
Pyuru!
[whimpers]
[WAITRESS 2A]
Pyuru! Pyururu!
Delicious, meow!
You're right! Yummy!
I've never eaten
anything this amazing
in my whole life!
[MOA]
Thanks for waiting, everyone!
[giggles] Pyuru.
Moa, you look so lovely!
Like a porcelain doll!
[camera shutter clicking]
[drumming]
[DRUMMER singing]
[BAND MEMBER 2B]
♪ Uh peeru, peeru mm ah ♪
What the--?
Is that some kind of ritual?
Moa, what's going on?
They're playing the song
of my people, pyuru.
Oh, yeah? It's very...
"Unique" is a good word.
Agreed.
[BAND singing]
[gavel banging]
[COMMITTEE HEAD]
Your Highness--I mean,
Royal Planet Investigator Moa.
First of all, thanks
for your hard work.
[MOA]
Thank you, ma'am.
Do you understand why you
were ordered to return home?
Yes, ma'am.
It's probably because of...
...all the late reports?
They weren't simply "late."
Most of them didn't
arrive at all!
Oh, that's because...
...I was planning to
submit them all at once.
[COMMITTEE HEAD]
So, that's what happened.
Well, because those
reports never came,
we were worried something
had happened to you.
[MOA]
I'm terribly sorry.
While we're thankful
you are safe,
due to this neglect,
we have concluded
that you did not fulfill your
duties as an investigator.
As such,
we have no choice
but to strip you
of your investigator title--
Wait a minute, please!
Pyuru-rurururu.
Looks like they're
arguing about something.
Guess so.
I hope everything's okay.
Yes, it's my fault!
I take full responsibility for
not submitting those reports!
But mere words in
reports can't even begin
to express everything
about my band
and my dear friends, pyuru!
Band, pyuru?
[MOA]
Pyurururu!
Yes, pyuru! I couldn't
express it alone.
So, my band mates came
with me to show you!
A nice gesture, Princess Moa.
But can this "band" of yours
solve our energy
problems, pyuru?
Uh, well I-I don't...
Moa!
Listen.
I want everyone on Planet
Pyuru to know, pyuru.
I ask for permission for
Plasmagica to perform!
Ugh. That's quite
enough, pyuru.
How will listening to some
performance show us anything?
[MOA'S MOM] I think that's
an excellent idea, pyuru.
Mama!
We want to hear this music
you think is so wonderful.
[MOA'S DAD] We can decide what
to do after we hear it, pyuru.
So then. What do ya say, pyuru?
[COMMITTEE grumbles]
Well, if your majesties
feel that way, then so be it.
Papa, Mama! Thank you, pyuru!
Yes!
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU, RETOREE]
♪ Distance between us  ♪
♪ can never break our bond  ♪
♪ Our hearts are
harmonizing in full ♪
♪ The power of our song
breaks barriers ♪
♪ Nothing could go wrong ♪
♪ We sing all knowing ♪
♪ It's through the music
all of us will ♪
♪ finally connect ♪
♪ So I hope our sound
reaches you, ♪
♪ Voices shining through ♪
♪
[MOA] This might not
work after all, pyuru.
[CYAN]
Moa, you're too worried!
You've gotta have more fun!
Then they'll understand!
[gasps]
[CHUCHU, RETOREE, CYAN]
♪ We're running quickly ♪
♪ towards the promise
of our future  ♪
♪ Let's keep holding on to the
bond we've been fighting for ♪
♪ I want what I feel inside
to be cranked to the max ♪
♪ And everything I've
ever wanted to say ♪
♪ will be understood
through our musical notes ♪
[CHUCHU, RETOREE, CYAN]
♪ Distance between us ♪
♪ can never break our bond ♪
♪ Our hearts are
harmonizing in full ♪
♪ The power of our song
breaks barriers ♪
♪ Nothing could go wrong ♪
[MAPLE]
No matter how much they argue
about those reports,
the mind is no match
for this melody, is it?
Not at all. Well said.
[CHUCHU, RETOREE, CYAN]
♪ Voices shining through ♪
♪
[TOWNSPEOPLE cheer]
Thank you! Thank you,
everybody, pyuru!
[MOA'S DAD]
Thank you all so very much
for letting us listen to your
wonderful performance, pyuru!
The power of that energy
far exceeded anything
we could have possibly
imagined, pyuru.
As a result, we feel
we must also recognize
Moa's work as an
investigator, pyuru.
Therefore, Moa is to
officially continue her work
as a Royal Investigator
on Sound Planet, pyuru.
[CHUCHU, CYAN, RETOREE]
Moa!
[MOA'S DAD]
By the way, Maple,
I have a favor to
ask of you, pyuru.
[MAPLE]
Oh? What is it?
[MOA'S DAD] I have no idea
how the ins-and-outs
of this request would work,
but could you supply music
from your planet to
Planet Pyuru, pyuru?
We've heard a large
music theme park
is being built and will
soon open in Midi City.
There's to be a
celebratory concert
to commemorate
its opening, pyuru.
[MOA'S DAD] If arrangements
can be made for that concert
to be simulcast here
on our planet,
then we would like to
offer to pay the cost
of construction
in return, pyuru.
[ALL gasp]
Seriously, Your Majesty?
I'll contact the person
in charge right away!
[ANGELICA] Hello? Are you
the person in charge?
Uh-huh.
Yes, I'm afraid His
Majesty insists on it.
Really, you don't say?
Yes, understood.
Thank you so much.
I've just contacted
the person in charge.
They say it's a
very welcome offer
and that it's been accepted.
[MOA'S DAD, MOA'S MOM]
Ah! Pyuru!
That's Angelica for you!
She works fast and gets it done!
[MAPLE grumbles]
Moa, this is all thanks to you.
After watching you
have so much fun
performing with your
wonderful friends,
any worries I may have had
are now put to rest, pyuru.
[MOA'S DAD]
Moa, do your best, pyuru!
And do those reports, pyuru!
[gasps] You got it, pyuru!
[MOA'S MOM] Moa, dear, I've
also put your favorite food
in the cargo hold.
[MOA]
Really, pyuru?
[MAPLE]
Come on!
Let's get this show
on the road already!
Papa, Mama, thank you so
much for everything, pyuru.
[MOA'S DAD]
Ah! Take care, pyuru.
Stop by and visit us
from time to time,
if you happen to be
in the galax--
[MOA cries]
[MOA'S MOM]
Oh, there, there, Moa.
Papa, Mama, I love you so much!
Thank you, pyuru!
[CHUCHU] Well, I guess
that's all settled then.
[RETOREE] I honestly wasn't
sure what would happen
for a while there.
[CYAN] I'm really glad
everything worked out!
Uh-- What's wrong, Moa?
[MOA] The nagonago
fassagua my mom gave me
escaped, pyuru.
[MAPLE yells]
[screaming]
[CHUCHU yelps]
What is that freaky thing?
[RETOREE]
And why is it still alive?
[CYAN]
Moa, do something!
[MOA]
I can't, pyuru!
[ANGELICA]
President!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Chuchu! ♪
[CHUCHU]
Okay, sugars. Let's do this!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Cyan! ♪
[CYAN] It's time for everyone
to hear our music!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Retoree! ♪
[RETOREE]
We're so perfectly in tune.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Moa! ♪
[MOA]
Pyuru, pyuru, pyuru...!
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Tell me
Why I'm so happy with you? ♪
♪ Tell me
How we have so much fun ♪
I know I'm ready for it ♪
♪ Let's (Fine!) go! (Fine!) ♪
♪ Sing for the show!
(Let's go) ♪
♪ CHU-CHU-CHU
CHU-CHU CHU CHU-LU-LU ♪
♪ CHU-LU-LU-LU ♪
[CYAN] ♪ I feel like the
thumping of my heart ♪
♪ is speeding up the rhythm ♪
♪ What can I do?
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My spirit is so electrified ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want to
(Que sera sera sera) ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Our memories
are piling up like photos ♪
♪ In a picture album of
melodies (Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[MOA] ♪ When I need recharging
all I have to do ♪
♪ Is play the album
of my memories (Yay!) ♪
[CYAN] ♪ We'll keep writing
all these new songs ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ Our imagination won't stop ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU]
♪ Almost done! ♪
[RETOREE, MOA]
♪ (Precious number one music) ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Now put it
all together! Yay! ♪
♪ Tell me
How you inspire music ♪
♪ In me?
My singing is all for you ♪
♪ Tell me
Why I never noticed until now? ♪
♪ (My song is you!!) ♪
♪ I know, it's all
in my subconcious ♪
♪ I know, you're with me
through everything ♪
♪ I know, you're
in my heart forever ♪
♪ Always (Fine! Fine!) ♪
♪ I love you (Once more) ♪
♪ Singing with you! (Yay!) ♪
[MAPLE] Next time, there'll
be a sweets festival!
What confectionary delights
will you girls make, Chuchu?
[CHUCHU] I'd tell you,
but that's a secret! Sorry!
[MAPLE groans] Spill the
beans! Spill the beans!
Spill the beans!
--[fart sound]
--Oh, spilt it!