Ah!
[DARUDAYU]
You never change, do you?
Huh?
[GRATEFUL KING]
Well, if it isn't Darudayu!
[DARUDAYU] After peace continues
for hundreds of years,
something will surely come,
wanting only to
destroy it in kind.
That is just how
the world works.
In times past,
whenever Midi City--
no, whenever Sound Planet
faced an unprecedented crisis,
the one who always provided
our salvation was...
The legendary
Melodisian Almaz, correct?
Aye.
So you are familiar with
the tale, I take it?
Yeah.
The sound energy hidden
in every substance,
as well as all living
things in this world,
is derived from
the Melodisian Stone.
The phantom Melodisian Almaz
is said to be its source.
[DARUDAYU]
Aye.
A Melodisian Stone
of the highest purity,
believed to have
never been violated.
I came by to tell you
my disciples and I
are about to embark
on a journey to find it.
With that in mind,
I also had a favor I
wanted to ask of you.
I see. Your visit has an agenda.
You want me to take
care of Midi City
while you're gone, right?
Well deduced, King.
I should have expected
no less from you.
But as you can see,
I'm pretty busy
with my retirement.
I don't know if
I'll be much help.
[drum beats]
Uh... All right, I get it!
Jeez. Talk about an offer
you can't refuse.
[DARUDAYU chuckles]
[DARUDAYU]
Well then, I leave it to you.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Yeah. Sure.
Take care.
[DARUDAYU]
Oh, and one more thing.
You know of the girl that has
returned to us, don't you?
Cyan? Indeed, I do.
♪
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Pumping Jumping! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CYAN] ♪ Dontcha come at me
with your monotone ♪
♪ Feelin' somethin'
more harmonious ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Waiting, to take a breath ♪
♪ I look, listen,
oh so carefully ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Oh baby,
can you hear the chords ♪
♪ Soundin' sweet the more
we rock the pop ♪
[MOA] ♪ Let's mix and
match our swing now ♪
♪ To make the music that we've
all been feelin' inside ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ (Passhuwa!
Pappasshuwa! Pashuwa, yes!) ♪
[CYAN]
♪ 'Cause even in my dreams ♪
♪ I hear the sound
of your voice ♪
[CHUCHU] ♪ In you I finally see
There is no other choice ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ I know I can
keep pushing ahead ♪
♪ And that I can really change ♪
[MOA] ♪ All I need is
to find melodies ♪
♪ I haven't
discovered just yet ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ Everybody Rock!
Rock! Give it your all! ♪
♪ Just sing and be yourself! ♪
♪ Keep on keepin' on
and on and on and on ♪
♪ and cramming emotions
into your music ♪
♪ Everybody Rock! Rock!
With all your heart! ♪
♪ And soon you'll
hear new melodies ♪
♪ Hear the pulsing beat ♪
♪ The power of the rhythm ♪
♪ The magic never stops ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ All you need is
harmony (words don't matter) ♪
♪ Honesty
(With your feelings) ♪
♪ Keep on strumming! Keep on
going! Keep on and on! ♪
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[ROSIA panting]
[ROSIA]
Oh, shoot! I'm gonna be late!
[piano playing]
[gasps]
Who's out there?
[ROSIA pants]
I hate peepers.
Every one of them should
go straight to hell.
[ROSIA] That uniform.
Is it from our high school?
I don't know... And what's
with this feeling?
Why am I suddenly so tense?
[CHUCHU] The time has
finally arrived, everyone!
This weekend,
the Sparkling Midicians
Long Beach
Water Sports Meet Full
of Girls! Tee-hee!
Awesome, right?
[CHUCHU]
Ah...
With that in mind.
I wanted to have
a discussion about
what bathing suits
we're going to wear.
We should choose
something that reflects
everyone's personalities
while simultaneously
keeping the image
of Plasmagica consistent
as a whole.
Like having the same design.
but different
colors for everyone?
Or the opposite--
having the same color
but different designs, pyuru.
Since this is a sports meet,
there'll be events with
lots of movement.
Should we choose a design
that won't slow us down?
Nope! That's not the
goal here, at all!
You mean, we should...?
Yup!
We should totally choose
something way fetch
to show off the sup's fresh
energy of middle school girls.
We cannot shy away!
It's not that I'm
shying away, it's just--
Fresh energy.
Freshly-baked taiyaki
give me lots of energy
and tastes yummy!
But anyway.
I'm really looking forward
to the tournament!
With my skills in the water,
the race might be the one
thing no one can beat me at!
[ROSIA]
Jacklyn.
Wear this during
the swimming race!
It keeps water resistance
down to a minimum.
It's lile a way
high-tech design!
[JACKLYN]
Huh?
Listen up!
We're definitely
not going to lose!
[EMCEE 4A]
All right!
How ya doin' out
there, Midi City?
Know what time it is? Do ya?
That's right!
It's time for the
Sparkling Midicians
Long Beach Water Sports Meet
Full of Girls, Tee-Hee!
An exciting event where young,
cute girls represent Midi City
competing in various games
and competitions,
vying for the top honor!
Let's give it up for
our contestants!
[AUDIENCE cheering]
'Kay, it looks like we're
part of the White Team.
[gasps] Shizuku Secret Mind
is on the White Team, too!
[RETOREE]
Really? Ugh.
So is Cri-Cri.
Yeah, because we're all
from the same agency.
Bein' on the same team
as that middle schooler...
It's total lame sauce.
Do you not like Rosia, pyuru?
That little brat,
always trying to get some
cuddle time with Cyan.
What?
Come on!
She probably just really
likes Cyan, pyuru!
That's something the
two of you have in common!
[RETOREE] Uh! That's not
what I'm talking about!
[CHUCHU]
The events we'll be competing in
are the water relay,
water rodeo, water sumo,
water ball-toss,
and then finally,
the water chicken fight.
It's gonna be a pretty
difficult schedule, actually.
I wonder if I'll
last till the end.
Just try to stay strong.
Sure thing.
[ANGELICA]
Ladies!
The chicken fight teams
will be determined
by drawing lots,
so please take one.
[CHUCHU, CYAN, MOA, RETOREE]
Okay!
[CHUCHU]
So...
It looks like I'm on
the same team as Cyan,
Tsukino, and
Shabobon. Yay, Cyan!
[ROSIA]
Retoree! Isn't it great?
We're on the same team together!
This is gonna be major fun!
[ROSIA] The chicken fight
is my place to shine!
You better not hold me back!
[RETOREE] Of all people,
why'd I have to end up
with this annoying little brat?
[MAPLE]
Water! Water!
All this water means
that it's the swimsuit--
I mean, swim meet
I've been waiting for!
You're getting a little
too excited, President.
If not now, then when
should I be excited?
Oh, it's bathing
suit time! Can't wait!
[EMCEE 4A] And now, a special
live broadcast from today's
super guests, performing
a new song for us!
Please welcome Trichronika!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
It's great to be here!
To everyone at the event,
as well as those watching
the broadcast across Sound
Galaxy, funny-funny hello!
[KAI, RIKU]
Hi, everyone!
[AUDIENCE]
Hi, guys!
Thanks, everybody.
We are currently in the middle
of our Rainbow Galaxy Tour.
But in our hearts,
we are there with you,
and to prove it.
we've written you
a beautiful message!
We hope you enjoy
our gift of music.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
Shuzo!
Oh! It's been a while
since I've seen
Shuzo and the gang.
These galaxy live broadcasts
certainly make that easier.
True!
And it appears they're
working hard, as usual.
Know what, twins?
Since we started our
Dream Galaxy Tour,
we've visited a lot
of planets, haven't we?
[KAI, RIKU]
Yep!
[SHUZO] Each planet had
its own kind of charm,
and every day we awoke to
an exciting new adventure!
[RIKU]
True!
Even playing the same
song on another planet
got a different reaction
from the audience,
all across Dream Galaxy.
And that made the concerts
feel new every time!
Oh, I agree.
There were many wonderful
and beautiful discoveries
made along the way.
And, you know,
that got me thinking.
When this tour is over and
we go back to Sound Planet,
how will they--specifically,
how will the people of
Midi City receive us?
[DIRECTOR]
Trichronika, please stand by!
Now then, you two,
let's do our best!
[BOTH]
Right! You got it!
Wow! Look who it is!
Corriente! Wendy! Hello!
Cyan! You came back, I see!
Sure did. It's a long story.
Now I get to tell you
how cool you were
against that monster!
For sure! You were
like a superhero!
Oh?
Oh! Sorry!
You two haven't met, have you?
Hi, I'm from
Shizuku Secret Mind.
Shabobon's the name.
Nice to meet you!
I look forward
to working together!
Well.
I'm sure you already
know about this stuff,
but feel free to have
some water, if you like!
You're too kind!
Thank you, as always!
But we only get two
bottles free, right, pyuru?
[CORRIENTE]
You know the drill!
[RETOREE]
Meh.
I don't really
like crowds, anyway.
[CYAN]
Retoree! Here! Have one!
Uh-- Thanks a lot.
Is something the matter?
[RETOREE]
Mm-mm. Nah, nothin' at all.
Okay. Guess that's good to hear.
As for me, I'm actually
a little down.
[RETOREE]
Hm?
I'm not what you would
call a "strong swimmer,"
or even very good at
sports in general.
So I'm kinda worried
that I'll end up
causing trouble for everyone.
But you know what they say,
"You're a meanie if you
don't participate," right?
I believe it's
"There's meaning
in participation."
[gasps]
[CYAN] But I think it's good
to challenge yourself.
You shouldn't run away
from things just because
you're not the best at them.
It's okay to mess up!
That's the best way to
learn how to get better!
Let's have fun!
Sounds good.
You two are so
inspirational, pyuru!
Now don't forget.
Getting a cramp can
really slow you down.
So make sure to
warm up carefully
and do your best!
[RETOREE]
I'm fine as long as
I'm with everyone from Plasma.
That's enough for me.
[EMCEE 4A]
Okay!
Are all our contestants
warmed up and ready to go?
It's time to start the games
you've all been waiting for!
♪
[SHUZO] ♪ I'm running through
a boiling highway ♪
♪ Between the ocean waves ♪
♪ It's reflection seems
so close to me ♪
♪ It's lights up in the
night like Star Shine ♪
♪ I always felt like
I could reach out ♪
♪ And I could touch
the "Sky so high!" ♪
I'm getting the hang of this!
[yelps]
[EMCEE 4A]
Oh!
Contestant Chuchu has
fallen into the water!
I did it!
[EMCEE 4A] Contestant Candy
Lapin reaches the goal!
[CHUCHU]
Oh, now I've gone and done it!
[whistle blows]
Here I go, pyuru!
One... Two...
Pyuru!
[yelps] P-P-Pyuru!
Looks like I win!
[EMCEE 4A]
Up next is the water rodeo!
Whoever can stand the water
coming from all directions
the longest wins!
All right.
[EMCEE 4A]
Ready?
Huh? Meow?
[EMCEE 4A laughs]
Contestant Cyan has fallen off!
The event hasn't
even started yet!
I can't get them in at all!
Like, oh, my gosh!
You're amazing, Rosia!
Ah... This is just
the beginning!
I will never give up!
[CHUCHU, CYAN, MOA cheering]
You're so close! You can
do it! Come on! Come on!
[RETOREE]
A chicken fight with teammates
I don't really know.
And the one I do know
is that lame Rosia.
I wish I could've been
on the same team
as Cyan and the others.
[STAFF 4A]
On your right! Coming through!
Excuse us, please!
[STAFF 4B]
Excuse us!
[STAFF 4C]
[STAFF 4A] Aw, man!
It won't fit through the door!
[STAFF 4B]
What if we flip it upright?
Maybe I'll just sit it out.
[ROSIA]
Hm...
All right! Scoot, scoot, scoot!
Left, right!
[sighs]
[gasps]
Hey, Retoree! Whoa,
you surprised me!
Why are you hanging out
in a place like this?
[RETOREE]
N-No reason. I was just leaving.
What did you come here for?
I, uh, you know just came
to look for something I forgot!
Oh, my! I wonder
where it could be!
Maybe here? Or over here?
--Under here?
--[RETOREE] Well, I'm out.
--See ya.
[door rattles]
[RETOREE]
Huh?
Ugh. What are you
doing over there?
The door. It won't open!
What?
--[ROSIA] Sure.
--[RETOREE] See?
You're kidding, right?
[ROSIA]
What the--?
No way! Why won't it open?
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention all contestants!
Everyone in the chicken fight:
please gather by the
pool in 15 minutes!
We have to hurry!
[ROSIA grunting] Come on,
please! Open, open, open...
[RETOREE] Oh, well.
Maybe it's for the best.
If we're stuck in here,
then I won't have to be
in the chicken fight.
[EMCEE 4A]
Now!
It's time for the second
heat of the freestyle race!
Keep a close eye on contestants
Corriente and Jacklyn!
They're both
exceptional swimmers!
We're expecting an event record!
Good luck, girl.
You're gonna need it.
[EMCEE 4A]
On your mark.
That's what you think.
[JACKLYN]
Almost!
Yeah! I did it!
[EMCEE 4A] There it is!
The fastest time in history!
That's how it's done! Boo-yah!
[EMCEE 4A]
Results for the second heat
of the freestyle race are:
1st place, Contestant Jacklyn.
2nd place, Contestant Corriente.
These two have broken
the event record!
Congratulations to them both!
Hey, Retoree.
It's real talk time.
You look super uncomfortable
when I get close to Cyan.
That's just... It's whatever.
Well, there's no need
to worry, either way.
I mean, it's not like
I like-like her
or anything like that.
I'm fascinated by her talent!
Her talent?
Because she's the
first person I've met
that I didn't wanna lose to.
[ROSIA]
Until she came along,
I was able to get the results
I wanted by working hard.
I had never lost
to anyone before.
It was my first time
to ever feel that way.
That's why I'm
interested in Cyan.
Listen, you might not
think winning or losing
really matters all that much.
But to me, it does!
Working hard and doing
all that I can help
make my music be
the best it can be!
[HOLMY]
Jacklyn, that was incredible!
It was really close, though!
I bet This swimsuit Rosia gave
me probably helped me win!
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Where is Rosia, anyway?
Retoree's missing, too.
[CHUCHU, CYAN]
What?
I wonder what happened to them.
[ROSIA]
There you have it.
That's why I wanna win.
That's what interests
me about Cyan.
[RETOREE] She's not really the
person I imagined her to be.
Up until now, I didn't
really like her.
It's okay to mess up!
That's the best way to
learn how to get better!
Let's have fun!
Listen.
I think I might've
had the wrong idea.
[ROSIA]
Huh?
About the swim meet
today, for one thing.
Because of all the crowds,
I decided from the start
that I wasn't gonna
have any fun.
Also...
Don't we have a chicken fight?
We sure do!
But if we're gonna make it,
we've totes gotta get
out of this place.
[EMCEE 4A] It's time for the
last event: the chicken fight!
The red team has an
advantage, but the team
who wins the chicken
fight will receive
a rockin' 690,000 points!
What about all the points we got
from everything up until now?
Not much point in competing.
Seems like this always happens.
[RETOREE]
I-It's not open yet? Seriously?
[ROSIA] I know, right?
The window's stuck!
I'm lighter than you, so just
keep holding me up, okay?
[RETOREE] She always says
just a little too much.
[gasps, yelps]
[BOTH yelping]
[BOTH groaning]
[CHUCHU] Retoree! Rosia!
You're here, too?
Thank goodness!
We looked for you everywhere!
We were worried, pyuru!
Sorry.
Rosia!
I'm so glad we found you!
What were you doing?
Yeah. You missed the race.
[ROSIA]
Sorry that I worried you.
but we don't have any time
to just stand around.
The white team, led by Rosia,
will definitely not lose! Right?
[ROSIA]
Gooo!
[gunshot]
[yelps]
All right!
Look out. This one is all ours!
Oh, no you don't!
That's not gonna work on me!
So not fair
Now it's my turn!
[gasps] Counterattack!
Okay!
[yells]
I've been bested!
We did it!
That was a cool move, Retoree!
Great idea!
Yeah, it was!
[EMCEE 4A]
That's it!
The last team remaining
is Holmy, Wendy,
Retoree and Rosia!
Yay! We won!
[EMCEE 4A] And that gives
the white team 690,000,
bringing their total to 690,180!
The white team wins!
Yes! Retoree!
[ROSIA, RETROEE]
Hmph.
[CYAN]
Retoree!
[yelps]
[CHUCHU, CYAN, MOA, TSUKINO,
HOLMY, JACKLYN] We did it!
Retoree, you were
absolutely amazing!
You and Rosia worked
great together, pyuru!
It's all thanks to Cyan.
Huh? To me?
Did I do something?
[RETOREE chuckles]
[TSUKINO, ROSIA, JACKLYN, HOLMY
laughing, chattering]
Oh?
[SHIBARIN] Y'all! We're
never gonna make it!
[KITTSUN] That old guy hates
it when we're late, too!
[POKOE]
We have to hurry!
[HAKKUN]
I hope he's not there yet.
[SHIBARIN]
That's wishful thinkin'.
[KITTSUN]
Right?
Like he's got
anything better to do.
[POKOE]
Let's step on it!
[HAKKUN] Yeah, he's scary
when he gets mad!
[OGASAWARA] Those high
schoolers are late again.
Whatever! I'm just
gonna start singin'!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Chuchu! ♪
[CHUCHU]
Okay, sugars. Let's do this!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Cyan! ♪
[CYAN] It's time for everyone
to hear our music!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Retoree! ♪
[RETOREE]
We're so perfectly in tune.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Moa! ♪
[MOA]
Pyuru, pyuru, pyuru...!
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Tell me
Why I'm so happy with you? ♪
♪ Tell me
How we have so much fun ♪
I know I'm ready for it ♪
♪ Let's (Fine!) go! (Fine!) ♪
♪ Sing for the show!
(Let's go) ♪
♪ CHU-CHU-CHU
CHU-CHU CHU CHU-LU-LU ♪
♪ CHU-LU-LU-LU ♪
[CYAN] ♪ I feel like the
thumping of my heart ♪
♪ is speeding up the rhythm ♪
♪ What can I do?
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My spirit is so electrified ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want to
(Que sera sera sera) ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Our memories
are piling up like photos ♪
♪ In a picture album of
melodies (Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[MOA] ♪ When I need recharging
all I have to do ♪
♪ Is play the album
of my memories (Yay!) ♪
[CYAN] ♪ We'll keep writing
all these new songs ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ Our imagination won't stop ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU]
♪ Almost done! ♪
[RETOREE, MOA]
♪ (Precious number one music) ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Now put it
all together! Yay! ♪
♪ Tell me
How you inspire music ♪
♪ In me?
My singing is all for you ♪
♪ Tell me
Why I never noticed until now? ♪
♪ (My song is you!!) ♪
♪ I know, it's all
in my subconcious ♪
♪ I know, you're with me
through everything ♪
♪ I know, you're
in my heart forever ♪
♪ Always (Fine! Fine!) ♪
♪ I love you (Once more) ♪
♪ Singing with you! (Yay!) ♪
[TITAN] We are not idols--
we are artists!
[ORION] Your golden
melodious is constantly
provoking all five
of my senses, Titan!
[SELEN chuckles]
[ARGON]
Shyaa!
[MAPLE]
Who the heck are you people?