[CROW] ♪ This is the Eden
of all things iniquitous ♪
♪ breaking away from the
cretinous herd, falling down ♪
Ha, ha! Crow has arrived!
[AION] ♪ Dying the darkness
to crimson through power ♪
♪ only given to us from the
magical sword, of Thanatos ♪
Stomach crusher, Aion!
[YAIBA] ♪ His prey scatters,
but it doesn't matter ♪
♪ because he's
already penetrated ♪
♪ their internal organs ♪
♪ Legend of Amino Acids ♪
Hence, Yaiba appears bearing
his legendary dragon sword.
[ROM]
♪ Needs of grown men ♪
♪ Men need persistence
and guts ♪
♪ We must pursue
justice for all ♪
♪ For my name is Rom! ♪
[SHINGANCRIMSONZ] ♪ Now take
your spoon and let it drown in ♪
♪ This mouthwatering ocean ♪
♪ Surrender your soul
to the taste ♪
♪ Curry with all the things ♪
[MAPLE]
Get out!
♪
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Pumping Jumping! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CYAN] ♪ Dontcha come at me
with your monotone ♪
♪ Feelin' somethin'
more harmonious ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Waiting, to take a breath ♪
♪ I look, listen,
oh so carefully ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Oh baby,
can you hear the chords ♪
♪ Soundin' sweet the more
we rock the pop ♪
[MOA] ♪ Let's mix and
match our swing now ♪
♪ To make the music that we've
all been feelin' inside ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ (Passhuwa!
Pappasshuwa! Pashuwa, yes!) ♪
[CYAN]
♪ 'Cause even in my dreams ♪
♪ I hear the sound
of your voice ♪
[CHUCHU] ♪ In you I finally see
There is no other choice ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ I know I can
keep pushing ahead ♪
♪ And that I can really change ♪
[MOA] ♪ All I need is
to find melodies ♪
♪ I haven't
discovered just yet ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ Everybody Rock!
Rock! Give it your all! ♪
♪ Just sing and be yourself! ♪
♪ Keep on keepin' on
and on and on and on ♪
♪ and cramming emotions
into your music ♪
♪ Everybody Rock! Rock!
With all your heart! ♪
♪ And soon you'll
hear new melodies ♪
♪ Hear the pulsing beat ♪
♪ The power of the rhythm ♪
♪ The magic never stops ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ All you need is
harmony (words don't matter) ♪
♪ Honesty
(With your feelings) ♪
♪ Keep on strumming! Keep on
going! Keep on and on! ♪
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CROW]
Ah! I ate so much!
Oh, hey, Rom,
you rock for treating us all
to dinner again, man.
I'll definitely pay
you back someday.
It's cool. Don't worry about it.
What you can do...
...is give me your most
passionate performances!
[sputters] Oh, Rom, I can't
believe how much
you can still ignite that
little spark inside my heart.
[YAIBA]
The ultimate Legend of Leader!
[AION]
That meal tonight will be carved
in the Dark Apocalypse
as the Night
of the Cursed Full Stomach
and be spoken of for eternity.
[CROW] I'm fired up like the
red hot flame of a gas burner
when you're making fried rice!
[yells]
[EMCEE 5A]
Hey, kids!
It's time to meet this
week's featured band!
From Judas, the same
world-famous idol label
as Trichronika.
The fastest to debut
in the label's history.
The new stars
and golden artists.
It's ARCAREAFACT!
Arca-what?
They're on the Judas label?
[ORION]
Checkmate.
I am the golden noblesse oblige
that shines supreme Orion!
Shyaa! Ooh!
Shyaa! Ah! Ah-shyaa!
This is no six-pack!
No way, this is my eight-pack
of revolution abs!
Argon!
[SELEN] A little pick-me-up,
and a fresh fairy fortissimo!
Selen!
[TITAN]
With my dulcet piano,
I will spin the world
into purest gold.
Titan!
I don't know why but
I hate them so much!
[EMCEE 5A] This week,
they take the top spot
from Trichronika, who are
on their Dream Galaxy Tour.
Tough luck!
You're kidding!
Hence, my friends.
There goes Trichronika's
Legend of Monopoly.
It is just a weekly ranking,
but these newcomers have
stollen the spotlight.
You'd better get back here, Shu.
Wait. What the...?
[CROW]
Is that money?!
Yeah! It's freakin' money!
Hey, hobos.
You're SHINGANCRIMSONZ, right?
Huh?!
You got some reason to be here?
[ORION]
Today's a very special day
for us in ARCAREAFACT.
We thought we'd come see
what you paupers look like,
since we're partying anyway.
What was that, punk?
We're going to start a
revolution in this city.
Yes. You'll be hearing
so much love for us,
you'll wanna cut your ears off.
For now, you'll have to polish
your instuments and wait.
No way! You gonna make me?
[yelps]
Hey! Get back here!
Au revoir.
What the hell did you even
come here for, you idiots?
[CHUCHU] Mm, I think
it's starting to sound
a whole lot better!
Me, too.
It sounds fantastic, pyuru!
But there's still
room for improvement!
We should get out
of our comfort zone
and try something totally
new and different.
[ALL]
Huh?
[CHUCHU] So I wanted
to talk to you girls.
I believe the time has come
for us to attempt something
we've never done
before, my sugars.
On that note, do y'all
have any good ideas?
Something completely new, pyuru?
We'll need to do more
this time than just
change our appearances,
won't we?
Chuchu, I have an idea
that could maybe work.
It would be pretty cool
to try writing a song
that's in a style different
from the ones we usually do.
In fact, we could all
use the challenge!
What do ya think?
Like we're exploring new ground?
Oh, I hear you and I like it!
Me, too! That's a
really great idea!
Yeah? Think so?
Thank you!
[phone rings]
Huh, who's calling?
Hi?
[GRATEFUL KING]
Yo, Cyan.
Mr. Berry! I mean,
Mr. Grateful King.
[GRATEFUL KING]
It's been a while.
How are ya doin'?
[CYAN]
Good!
Um, I ended up back
here in Sound World.
Oh, yeah, I already heard.
Seems like there's some
trouble brewin' again, huh?
[CYAN]
Yeah. And it's worse this time.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Looks like our buddy Dagger's
been layin' pretty
low these days.
That said, you gotta
get a whole lot better
before he comes back.
[CYAN]
We will, I swear!
[GRATEFUL KING]
No matter what, move forward
believing in your own power.
[CHUCHU, CYAN, RETOREE]
Got it!
Bye, kid.
[MOA]
So nice!
King called because he was
worried about Plasmagica.
Yes, sure sounds like it.
Uh, Cyan?
[CYAN] So, you guys, what we
were just talking about.
I think I'm...
I'm going to try writing
us a brand new song!
What?
Do you really mean that, pyuru?
Great! I say go for it, honey!
A song with a new style.
Can't wait to hear it!
[MAPLE]
Everyone! I've got big news!
[laughs]
A-ha!
[CROW]
Hey, President!
That last job you set us up
for was like a bad joke, man!
Calm down.
A request just came in today
for a battle of the
bands with you boys.
Lemme see!
[MAPLE] It's some hot new
band that just got signed
to the Judas label.
Ugh! Those Arcareafools!
[MAPLE]
What, you know them?
They were a sheer
disgrace to all warriors
and were extremely rude
as well, and hence--
Ha. I know what their game is.
"New stars,"
"golden boys," whatever.
We're gonna shut 'em up for good
with our raging
crimson performance!
Yeah, you know it!
President, you go
tell them we accept!
[BUD VIRGIN LOGIC]
♪ Fall onto your knees, ♪
♪ look with me,
in the shards of broken dreams ♪
♪ And gaze into reflections... ♪
[DAGGER chuckles]
Excellent, Ailane.
Keep this up, and we will dye
all the Melodisians
in Midi City in blind,
painful darkness with
the music of BVL.
And then, I will have my revenge
on those hateful wretches.
Your power is essential
to achieve that, Ailane.
I won't disappoint you.
[DAGGER]
My true resurrection will occur
upon the opening
of PuruLand. Just wait.
[HUNDREKO]
Master! Oh, there you are.
We've been looking
all over for you.
Well, I had to
speak with Dagger.
Master Ailane, this is rather
difficult for me to ask,
but, are we absolutely
certain we can trust
this Dagger character?
I feel uneasy about it.
[HUNDREKO]
So you know, Master,
I would bury that monster
for you in a heartbeat
if you asked.
Peipain, Hundreko,
please do not worry yourselves.
Hopes and dreams
don't mean anything.
I say everyone should just
go straight to hell.
[EMCEE 5A]
The wait's almost over!
Today, we have the
band from Judas
that burned in like
a comet, ARCAREAFACT.
facing off against BRR's
fiery guys SHINGANCRIMSONZ!
Let 'em hear it!
Now, the battle of the
bands is about to start!
Get ready for awesome!
[FANS cheering]
Did you get a good look at
the merch those guys have?
Everything was all
shiny and sparkly.
I hate it!
Whatever, that stuff
is just gravy!
All we gotta do
is wrap the stage
with raging crimson flames,
like every other time
we're up there!
And, hence!
[AION] We shall perform
a new piece smeared
with oozing blood
from a dark melody.
Oh, yeah! Let's get
going, all you cattle!
♪
They're sounding good so far!
Agreed, Pyuru
Will they be okay? I don't know.
[SHINGANCRIMSONZ]
♪ Ah, embraced by illusions ♪
♪ underneath the moon ♪
♪ What choice have I
in this crimson roulette? ♪
♪ The judgement bestowed,
its consequence unknown  ♪
♪ Will our amusement cause
the world to fall ruin? ♪
♪ Spoiled are the fruits. ♪
♪ Gone is the faith. ♪
♪ Countless are those
who've been driven insane ♪
[SHINGANCRIMSONZ]
♪ ...of reach, ♪
♪ Thus is the mortal coil ♪
[FANS cheer]
[TITAN] People! We are not
idols! We are artists!
[ORION] And not just any
artists. We are golden artists!
♪
[ARCAREAFACT] ♪ The chill
of the pouring rain ♪
♪ Falls through
transparent skies ♪
♪ It leaves its warmth behind ♪
♪ Cold and wet is how
it's left us this time ♪
♪ So now our imagination
wants to take the lead ♪
♪ Be our compass and our guide ♪
♪ As we run, to worlds
still yet unknown ♪
♪ To once again be
anywhere that isn't here ♪
♪ On our own ♪
♪ Let's ring the bell
and start the race ♪
♪ I want to fly ♪
♪ Another day ♪
♪ I hear the journey's call ♪
♪ And so I will heed ♪
♪ Let's stir it up to ♪
♪ Just awake ♪
♪ We'll play to the beat ♪
♪ Our souls ring out ♪
♪ Bringing light
into the moments ♪
♪ that were hidden
away in the dark ♪
♪ Take our pride and
throw it all away ♪
♪ Who needs it now? ♪
♪ Why dooon't we all... ♪
Hey, what's that?
[ARCAREAFACT]
♪ Then we will walk ♪
♪ With humble hearts ♪
Money...
Again.
♪
[FANS cheer]
[EMCEE 5A]
Time to cast your votes!
Those here in the audience...
...and those watching
the live broadcast!
Keep your votes coming!
Who's gonna be the
big winner tonight?
The suspense is killing me!
What's the verdict?
[EMCEE 5A]
The winners are ARCAREAFACT!
This is an unprecedented
landslide! Amazing!
Well, obviously.
[MAPLE]
What did he say?
Hard to believe they
won by so much.
Something's rotten here, pyuru!
I have some doubts.
What the...
[CROW]
What the hell?!
No way the great me
gets beat down!
How'd this happen?
I cannot comprehend
such a huge disparity.
And hence--
[AION] Perhaps there
was darkness writhing
beneath the surface that not
even this god can understand.
[CROW]
What?
So you're saying
those guys might've used
the power of money
behind the scenes?
[YAIBA] And hence,
how can we think otherwise
after seeing that result?
Aren't you gonna
say something, Rom?
Don't just take this
lying down! Hey!
[ROM grunts]
--[thud]
--[CROW groans]
[CROW]
Ow! What the hell was that for?
Shut your face hole!
A loss is a loss!
Even if they did
something shady,
it wouldn't have mattered,
'cause we would have won if
our performance was up to par!
Am I wrong?
No, you're right.
What you say is true and valid.
[AION] As ever, I must submit
to your strong, holy words.
[CROW]
All right!
We start from scratch tomorrow!
Now that that's decided--
let's get some dinner!
Yakiniku , boys!
[CROW, YAIBA, AION]
Yakiniku !
[CROW, YAIBA, AION chattering]
Shyaa!
Hey, did ya see?
At the show there were
some regular jewelry girls.
Couldn't take their eyes off
my eight-pack abs, man.
Would ya blame 'em?
[SELEN chuckles] Yeah, I'm
pretty sure what I heard from
the audience tonight was
the word "muscle head."
Whoa, Selen, you're
so harsh, bro!
But I know you're
just hidin' the love
when you say those things.
Yeah, sure. You keep dreaming.
Very strange.
We gave them such
a sound, severe beating.
And yet, they don't appear
to have learned their lesson.
How annoying would it be
if they tried to get revenge?
[ARGON]
Well, no matter how many times
they try to crawl up,
we just have to
smack them down again, right?
Your thoughts, Titan?
Uh-- Yeah, sure. I agree, too.
[ORION]
What's wrong?
You're rather quiet
this evening.
Oh. I'm fine.
Ah-shyaa!
Man, you gotta
lighten up a little!
I know!
Let's crack open some champagne!
We deserve a reward
for tonight's win!
Oh, yeah!
[ARGON]
Right?
Sorry, can't.
I'm heading home now.
But why?
We were just about to
celebrate our victory.
Are you feeling ill?
[ARGON]
Shyaa, no!
Aw, Titan, way to
bring down the room.
I really need to work on
arranging our new song.
Won't you get more
good ideas by doing that
here when you're talking to us?
No, I need alone time tonight.
Gotta go.
[SELEN] Titan's a real
workaholic, isn't he?
[ARGON] Shyaa, and he never
wants to join the party.
[RETOREE]
I knew it.
[MOA]
What are they up to?
Cheating, and right
behind our backs.
We've got 'em now.
Good evening,
Big Brother, welcome home.
Thank you for working
so hard for us!
[TITAN]
It's good to see you, Balt.
Oh, hey, where is
your brother Nickel?
He's sulking, right over there.
He says he wants a new toy.
[NICKEL]
No fair.
Everyone else has one.
I'm the only one who doesn't.
Oh, quit your whining!
Father lost his business,
so they took everything away.
Including the mansion,
the furniture,
all Mother's fancy dresses,
and even her jewelry!
You know we can't buy toys!
[NICKEL]
But, b-but--
[BALT]
Crying won't get you anything.
Don't be so selfish!
[NICKEL crying]
[TITAN]
Nickel, I brought you something.
[NICKEL]
Oh, you have sweets!
Uh-huh!
Now, stop your fighting
and share them.
--[NICKEL] 'Kay!
--[BALT] Yay!
[NICKEL, BALT]
Thank you, Big Brother!
[NICKEL]
Yummy!
[BALT]
Yeah, they're so good!
I'm glad. My pleasure.
You two, be patient
just a little longer.
'Cause, soon, I'm going to
be number one in Midi City,
and I'll make sure you get all
the treats you could ever want.
Mean it.
I'm sorry I acted so selfish.
Uh, hey, Big Brother?
Can you play the piano for me?
When I hear your music,
I like it,
'cause it makes me feel
all better inside.
Yes! Please play, Big Brother!
[piano playing]
[CROW]
Katsu ! Katsu ! Katsu !
Boys, didn't you already
eat yakiniku after the show?
Yeah, you'd think it
was their last meal.
Idiot, yakiniku
and chicken katsu
go in different stomachs, duh!
I did not know that.
[CHUCHU]
Hey, you guys!
We've got news about
the battle of the bands,
earlier, uh...
[ROM] I will wrap this
soul in crimson flame!
It will burn passionately
on stage, for real!
Yeah! All you can eat, Aion!
C'mon!
[AION] This dark sun
god's internal organs
are already full to bursting.
The next time we
see those guys,
they're as good as dead.
[CROW]
Nah--total waste of time!
Well, seems like the
guys've pretty much
gotten over it by now.
Maybe we don't even
need to tell them.
So positive, pyuru.
Yeah, we could learn from them!
--[ALL gasp]
--[electronic static]
[CHUCHU]
What is this horrible noise?
My ears are bleeding!
[DAGGER]
Ladies and gentlemen of BRR.
Dagger!
[MAPLE] Hm. So he's finally
on the move again?
Good to know.
Sneaky bastard.
[DAGGER] This is an
official declaration of war
against Plasmagica.
This time, I will unquestionably
bury you in darkness.
[DAGGER cackles]
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Chuchu! ♪
[CHUCHU]
Okay, sugars. Let's do this!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Cyan! ♪
[CYAN] It's time for everyone
to hear our music!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Retoree! ♪
[RETOREE]
We're so perfectly in tune.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Moa! ♪
[MOA]
Pyuru, pyuru, pyuru...!
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Tell me
Why I'm so happy with you? ♪
♪ Tell me
How we have so much fun ♪
I know I'm ready for it ♪
♪ Let's (Fine!) go! (Fine!) ♪
♪ Sing for the show!
(Let's go) ♪
♪ CHU-CHU-CHU
CHU-CHU CHU CHU-LU-LU ♪
♪ CHU-LU-LU-LU ♪
[CYAN] ♪ I feel like the
thumping of my heart ♪
♪ is speeding up the rhythm ♪
♪ What can I do?
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My spirit is so electrified ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want to
(Que sera sera sera) ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Our memories
are piling up like photos ♪
♪ In a picture album of
melodies (Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[MOA] ♪ When I need recharging
all I have to do ♪
♪ Is play the album
of my memories (Yay!) ♪
[CYAN] ♪ We'll keep writing
all these new songs ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ Our imagination won't stop ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU]
♪ Almost done! ♪
[RETOREE, MOA]
♪ (Precious number one music) ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Now put it
all together! Yay! ♪
♪ Tell me
How you inspire music ♪
♪ In me?
My singing is all for you ♪
♪ Tell me
Why I never noticed until now? ♪
♪ (My song is you!!) ♪
♪ I know, it's all
in my subconcious ♪
♪ I know, you're with me
through everything ♪
♪ I know, you're
in my heart forever ♪
♪ Always (Fine! Fine!) ♪
♪ I love you (Once more) ♪
♪ Singing with you! (Yay!) ♪
[MAPLE]
Cyan, ya seem a little down!
[CYAN]
Really, meow?
[MAPLE]
At times like that,
you just need to
cut loose and yell!
Like "phew" and "boom" and "aha"
and "whoo" and "yay" and
"shabalogadingdong"
and "wah-ha-ha"!