[FANS cheering]
Grateful King,
you're actually here!
I missed you so much!
Your worries are over, kid.
I wouldn't leave ya hangin'.
I promise, we're all gonna get
through this thing together!
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
[GRATEFUL KING]
But, listen--
there's something we
gotta take care of first.
--[gasping]
--[door bell jingles]
[GRATEFUL KING chuckles]
Hello, everyone!
Oh, wow! You, too, Shuzo?
Wait, Shu?
What're you doing here?
[SHUZO chuckles]
You're all gonna co-write
a new battle song.
It'll be so awesome, Victorious
won't know what hit her!
[gasping]
So? You ready?
[ALL gasping]
♪
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Pumping Jumping! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CYAN] ♪ Dontcha come at me
with your monotone ♪
♪ Feelin' somethin'
more harmonious ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Waiting, to take a breath ♪
♪ I look, listen,
oh so carefully ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Oh baby,
can you hear the chords ♪
♪ Soundin' sweet the more
we rock the pop ♪
[MOA] ♪ Let's mix and
match our swing now ♪
♪ To make the music that we've
all been feelin' inside ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ (Passhuwa!
Pappasshuwa! Pashuwa, yes!) ♪
[CYAN]
♪ 'Cause even in my dreams ♪
♪ I hear the sound
of your voice ♪
[CHUCHU] ♪ In you I finally see
There is no other choice ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ I know I can
keep pushing ahead ♪
♪ And that I can really change ♪
[MOA] ♪ All I need is
to find melodies ♪
♪ I haven't
discovered just yet ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ Everybody Rock!
Rock! Give it your all! ♪
♪ Just sing and be yourself! ♪
♪ Keep on keepin' on
and on and on and on ♪
♪ and cramming emotions
into your music ♪
♪ Everybody Rock! Rock!
With all your heart! ♪
♪ And soon you'll
hear new melodies ♪
♪ Hear the pulsing beat ♪
♪ The power of the rhythm ♪
♪ The magic never stops ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ All you need is
harmony (words don't matter) ♪
♪ Honesty
(With your feelings) ♪
♪ Keep on strumming! Keep on
going! Keep on and on! ♪
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[NARRATOR] The Queen
of Darkness, Victorious.
A woman whose
insatiable thirst for power,
has inevitably led
to her ruthless quest
to take over the world.
[NARRATOR]
Planet Ordinis.
A planet of people who
mandate efficiency and success.
In addition, a harsh
world where gifted
children receive advanced
education from very early on.
And those lacking
power or natural ability
are quickly sifted out,
with only the elite remaining.
[VICTORIOUS]
Hmph.
[gasps, growls]
--I'm gonna get you.
--Shh!
[BOTH giggle]
♪ No greater power
than justice ♪
[BOTH]
♪ Must carry it out ♪
♪ Give all I have
to its purpose ♪
♪ Learn through sacrifice
Grow powerful in service ♪
♪ No greater power
than justice ♪
[BOTH laugh]
[laughing]
[VICTORIOUS]
Hey, so, Astreal...
...once we finish tomorrow's
exam, what d'you wanna do?
Huh? What do you mean?
We still have to get
ready for another exam.
Except... it's a writing test
and I'm no good at that.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Huh?
Lemme explain.
I decided that every
time I achieve a goal,
that I would give myself
a reward to celebrate it.
Yeah, but how?
With something I was
never able to do until now.
To make things right,
me and all my surroundings,
too, each day!
[ASTREAL]
Hmm.
And then, when I
pass the very last
test that we take,
I want to make this planet
positively flood with justice.
[ASTREAL sighs]
Victorious, you're an idealist.
No, actually I'd
call you a dreamer.
You can't achieve
anything without dreams!
If the two of us work super hard
together, it'll come true!
Let's get through
these trials and then,
we'll make this planet overflow
with love and justice!
You really think we can do that?
I don't think, I know!
We are best friends,
aren't we?
[gasps]
Yeah, we, are!
[screams]
[grunting]
[groans, pants]
Hey, Victorious? I don't
think I can go any further...
You stop talking
like that right now.
Come on!
[ASTREAL] But I still
can't see the top...
How much longer do we
have to keep climbing?
It's so far...
It's better if
you don't look up.
Just focus on your handholds.
And take it slowly,
one little step at a time.
[ASTREAL]
Hmm.
♪ Gotta keep climbing up
It's all that we can do ♪
♪ But I don't think I can
I don't think I can go on ♪
♪ Just a bit further and
we'll overcome this awful path ♪
♪ Oh, but all I see is
the terror in front of me ♪
♪ Follow me ♪
♪ I'm too afraid ♪
[VICTORIOUS]
♪ Just take my hand ♪
♪ and we'll face
all your fears... ♪
♪ Together! ♪
[BOTH]
♪ When we're together we're-- ♪
[gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
[panting]
[gasps]
Look! We're almost to the top!
Yeah, you're right!
Okay. Now.
♪ I know that we can overcome ♪
♪ Just a little further ♪
[ASTREAL] ♪ We've gotta push
just a little bit harder ♪
[VICTORIOUS] ♪ Justice is
the greater power! ♪
[BOTH]
♪ We must do what's right ♪
♪ To get the power
that we're seeking ♪
♪ We can't give up
on this fight ♪
♪ We must go on! ♪
[gasps]
Victorious, no!
[VICTORIOUS whimpers]
As... Astreal, help me...
[whimpers]
I'm gonna fall...
[ASTREAL grunts]
But you're so far down...
Help me, please...!
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[thud]
[VICTORIOUS whimpers]
[gasps, wails]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[ASTREAL]
I finally made it to the top!
It's right there.
I did it, all by myself.
I did it.
[gasps]
Astreal...?
Why did you betray me
and leave me to die...?
[ASTREAL whimpers]
Tell me...
Just tell me!
[gasps, shrieks]
[VICTORIOUS] All of a sudden
there's this strange feeling
coming over me...
[VICTORIOUS]
And I like it...
I get it now...
This is the power of darkness
born from the seed of hatred.
It gives me strength
I've never known before.
Darkness itself is power...
...and I'm filled with darkness!
[laughs]
[NARRATOR] The malice,
jealousy, and rage festering
in her heart had become
unspeakable power.
She now felt like pure darkness
was the one true power,
and tirelessly sought
only that henceforth.
It consumed her.
Keep going.
It's still not enough!
I intend to be the
only being who stands
at the top of this planet.
So I must have all existing
energy in my hands!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, ma'am!
[VICTORIOUS]
Sound Planet.
A world that enriches
Melodizians with music, you say?
[NARRATOR]
Victorious developed a dangerous
obsession with Sound Planet,
as it pulsed and evolved
with music's constant energy.
[VICTORIOUS chuckles]
Delightful.
I think I'll have
a little fun with them.
Uh, so... I solemnly swear
I'll be the very best
manager you ever had,
and I look forward
to working with you boys!
[VICTORIOUS]
I will take as much advantage
of these blind fools as I can.
Not just of their music,
but all they hold dear.
We've always written
our own songs,
so how are we gonna
share the work?
It never crossed
my mind once, pyuru.
It's gonna be tricky for sure.
Yeah.
With an outlook like that,
we're dead in the water.
[GIRLS sigh]
A new song and
all of us are writing it...
We're gonna rise
to the challenge, though!
[GIRLS gasp]
Yeah, there's no
backin' out now!
It's a done deal!
So now's the time!
I guess I'll just have
to use my burning,
passionate, crimson--
I'll show you how it's done.
With our unwavering
spirits shining,
let's write an extraordinary...
...sparklingly brilliant,
fantastic song!
Yeah! Shuzo's right!
Aw, but I don't wanna
write it with those twerps!
Cyan, you've got this
down pat now, don'tcha?
Uh?
[gasps]
Yeah!
[CYAN]
I do. I know how to do this now.
As a group for the first time,
we'll write an amazing
song that shows
the strength of the love
we have for our bands,
our friends, and most
importantly, our music!
[CYAN giggles]
What's the best way to start?
[CYAN] I've always loved
music and that love of music
led me to the
friends I have now.
So what d'ya got?
Hey! No looking, pyuru!
Heh! You're not even close.
[growls]
--[MOA gasps]
--I'll give you some pointers
on writing passionate lyrics--
[grunts]
[CYAN] Our love of music
gives us the ability
to understand each other
without saying a word.
Hello!
[CYAN] Even people who
seem standoffish at first,
are much easier to understand
through the language of music.
[CYAN] And that is the tie
that binds us all together
more than anything.
It's unbreakable.
Heh.
[CYAN]
We might have arguments
or misunderstandings sometimes,
but when we make music together,
all of that just goes away.
[CYAN] Even if there are
times we actually get mad
at each other and don't speak,
as long as we have music,
we know for sure...
[CYAN] ...that it's just
something we'll look back
on and laugh about.
That's right. Music.
It's something no one
can change, ruin,
or ever take away from us.
It's what gives life to us all.
[GRATEFUL KING]
Did you wrap up that tune?
--Yes!
--Pyuru!
[GRATEFUL KING] Good job
knocking it out in record time!
All right,
The concert is tomorrow.
Let's all join rockin' forces,
and save the world, ya dig?
Can I count on ya?
[EVERYONE]
Yes!
[EMCEE 11A]
Yo!
Today's the day you've
all been waiting for!
Puru Land's finally finished,
and it's time to raise the
curtain on the opening concert!
Come on, everybody--
let's get fired up!
[FANS cheering]
[CHUCHU gasps]
It's so cute!
It's too bright.
I can't wait to try
the pink sheep ride, pyuru!
I can see why!
[CYAN squeals]
[CYAN]
Look! Fireworks!
[gasps] Y'know, these fireworks
are from Planet Pyuru.
Papa--uh, the king--
gave 'em to us as a gift
to celebrate tonight, pyuru!
[laughs]
Well, that's a great present!
[ROSIA gasps]
[CROW chuckles] Sounds like
everyone's totally stoked!
[MAPLE]
Angelica, if anything happens,
the safety of the Myumon
audience is our first priority.
I'm already on it.
The plan is in place.
And the other matter?
What do you want to do?
[MAPLE] Hmm... We'll only
use that as a last resort.
[FANS cheering]
[EMCEE 11A]
The wait's almost over, kids!
We'll kick off the show here in
a few, but first things first--
We're gonna hear
a few words of welcome
from his majesty, the king
of Planet Pyuru-du!
He generously contributed
funding and materials
for the building
of Puru Land!
Yes, Mama...
Right there, pyuru...
That's good... Oh, yes...
Oh, you hit the spot--
Oh, you like that,
don't you, pyuru?
[EMCEE 11A]
Oh... Ahem!
[BOTH gasp]
[MOA'S DAD
Oops, pyuru! [chuckles]
[MOA whimpers]
Papa, pyuru...
[MOA'S DAD]
Ahem, pyuru.
Up to this point,
we of Planet Pyuru
knew little of music or bands.
But thanks to Sound Planet,
we have learned
how joyful it is,
and it has become very dear
and important to us,
enriching our hearts very much.
We always want it in
our lives, pyuru!
Music is a wonderful,
magical entity
that will not only
save our planet,
but all other worlds,
and in fact, all life, pyuru!
Music will never die, pyuru!
We must make sure we keep it
alive and well forever, pyuru!
[MOA'S DAD] Today's concert
will also be shown
live on our planet.
And the entire population
is looking forward to it
with all ears and hearts, pyuru.
Now, everyone, come together,
right now, pyuru!
[FANS cheering]
[EMCEE 11A] Fine words
to live by, Your Majesty!
And we all say "thank you"!
[EMCEE 11A]
And last, but not least,
there's one more
announcement we gotta make
before we rock your socks off!
[FANS murmuring]
Good evening.
You may not be aware
of this just yet,
but the notorious
Queen of Darkness
is targeting this very concert.
[FANS murmuring]
It isn't likely, but should
there be any incident,
please follow our instructions
and evacuate as
quickly as possible.
That is all.
[EMCEE 11A]
Suh-weet!
Now that we've gotten the
important stuff out of the way.
C'mon, everybody! Rock 'n' roll!
[FANS cheering]
[laughs]
[GRATEFUL KING gasps]
[VICTORIOUS laughs]
That was a riveting
speech indeed.
Now, time to get
to the good part!
[FANS screaming]
[GRATEFUL KING gasps]
[CYAN]
Mister King!
All right, girls!
It's now or never!
Yeah!
[FANS yelling]
[screaming]
No, she's here!
[VICTORIOUS laughs]
How wonderful...
All your panic, fear,
and negative emotions
are making me stronger
by the moment.
So, by all means,
please keep it coming.
[moans]
This power feels like
the source of life itself!
[CROW growls]
Whoa, Shuzo, look!
Her strength is terrifying!
Cyan, help!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Let's go, you guys!
[gasps]
[VICTORIOUS cackles]
[CYAN whimpers]
[CROW grunting]
[grunting]
[VICTORIOUS laughs]
What's wrong?
Do battle with me if
you dare. Too bad, though.
Whatever absurd music
you try to play,
I won't hear a
single note of it.
[CYAN]
I can't move...
[VICTORIOUS laughs]
[MAPLE growls]
It's worse than I thought!
Now what?
If they can't play
their instruments,
then we're toast, man!
[GRATEFUL KING]
Cyan... ya gotta bust out, kid!
[VICTORIOUS] First, all you
nuisances will be swallowed
by darkness.
Then, I'll alter Sound Planet
into a desolate orb
of purest gloom.
To make it the
next stepping stone
in my conquest of Sound Cosmos!
Oh, no, you won't!
[VICTORIOUS gasps]
Now what?
Well, it's about time!
[GRATEFUL KING]
What?!
[MAPLE] Maple Wonderful Robot,
ready for takeoff!
Here's the deal:
King Pyuru and I
worked on this mecha
project in secret.
With high-quality Melodisians,
we made an instant
battlefield transporter,
And because that wasn't enough,
we also made this ultra,
hyper, super-cool, invincible,
mega-giant Maple
Wonderful Robot!
[MAPLE bellows]
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Chuchu! ♪
[CHUCHU]
Okay, sugars. Let's do this!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Cyan! ♪
[CYAN] It's time for everyone
to hear our music!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Retoree! ♪
[RETOREE]
We're so perfectly in tune.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Moa! ♪
[MOA]
Pyuru, pyuru, pyuru...!
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Tell me
Why I'm so happy with you? ♪
♪ Tell me
How we have so much fun ♪
I know I'm ready for it ♪
♪ Let's (Fine!) go! (Fine!) ♪
♪ Sing for the show!
(Let's go) ♪
♪ CHU-CHU-CHU
CHU-CHU CHU CHU-LU-LU ♪
♪ CHU-LU-LU-LU ♪
[CYAN] ♪ I feel like the
thumping of my heart ♪
♪ is speeding up the rhythm ♪
♪ What can I do?
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My spirit is so electrified ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want to
(Que sera sera sera) ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Our memories
are piling up like photos ♪
♪ In a picture album of
melodies (Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[MOA] ♪ When I need recharging
all I have to do ♪
♪ Is play the album
of my memories (Yay!) ♪
[CYAN] ♪ We'll keep writing
all these new songs ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ Our imagination won't stop ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU]
♪ Almost done! ♪
[RETOREE, MOA]
♪ (Precious number one music) ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Now put it
all together! Yay! ♪
♪ Tell me
How you inspire music ♪
♪ In me?
My singing is all for you ♪
♪ Tell me
Why I never noticed until now? ♪
♪ (My song is you!!) ♪
♪ I know, it's all
in my subconcious ♪
♪ I know, you're with me
through everything ♪
♪ I know, you're
in my heart forever ♪
♪ Always (Fine! Fine!) ♪
♪ I love you (Once more) ♪
♪ Singing with you! (Yay!) ♪
[MAPLE]
It's finally time to square off
with the Queen of
Darkness, Victorious!
[SHUZO giggles]
I'll dispatch her with a sparkle
from my extraordinary
Rainbow Smile Shining Star!
[MAPLE]
Shuzo, you're the best!
[high-pitched voice]
I love your sparkle!
[DAGGER]
"I love your sparkle"?