[CHUCHU]
So, you're saying you believe
that the vocalist for BVL,
is the Queen of Darkness?
Yeah.
But I still don't have any real,
hard evidence of it yet.
Where did you get
that information from?
I looked around.
Those girls were in the high
school building of our school.
[ROSIA] When I heard
her playing that music,
I felt a deep, painful
darkness wash over me.
The other thing is,
if they're working with Dagger,
they're also probably...
Brainwashed.
[ROSIA]
And that's not all!
This girl.
It really seems like
she hates music.
And it also felt like
those dark feelings
gave her some terrifying power.
If they perform like
that, I don't think
that even you guys will
be able to get through it
without being burned.
So, that's why.
You have to cancel.
Leave the battle!
But we can't do it.
Not this late in the game.
Yes, you don't have
to worry about us, so...
That's right, pyuru!
We wrote an amazing song for it,
so we should be more than fine.
Yeah, but--
You don't get it. She's crazy!
[CYAN]
Rosia.
We appreciate it.
But, see, we all agreed.
We have to go through with this.
[gasps]
Plasmagica works as a team.
And we swore that we'd give it
everything we've got, together!
You understand, right?
Trust us, it'll be okay.
Don't worry about it, Rosia.
Cyan and the girls
have it covered.
Yeah, it's like totes fine!
All good!
Whoa, Tsukino, that
was totally Rosia!
All right, then.
But, hey.
If anything shady should
happen to you guys at all,
we, your friends in Criticrista,
will not stand by!
Pyuru!
[gasps]
♪
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Pumping Jumping! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CYAN] ♪ Dontcha come at me
with your monotone ♪
♪ Feelin' somethin'
more harmonious ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Waiting, to take a breath ♪
♪ I look, listen,
oh so carefully ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Oh baby,
can you hear the chords ♪
♪ Soundin' sweet the more
we rock the pop ♪
[MOA] ♪ Let's mix and
match our swing now ♪
♪ To make the music that we've
all been feelin' inside ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ (Passhuwa!
Pappasshuwa! Pashuwa, yes!) ♪
[CYAN]
♪ 'Cause even in my dreams ♪
♪ I hear the sound
of your voice ♪
[CHUCHU] ♪ In you I finally see
There is no other choice ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ I know I can
keep pushing ahead ♪
♪ And that I can really change ♪
[MOA] ♪ All I need is
to find melodies ♪
♪ I haven't
discovered just yet ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ Everybody Rock!
Rock! Give it your all! ♪
♪ Just sing and be yourself! ♪
♪ Keep on keepin' on
and on and on and on ♪
♪ and cramming emotions
into your music ♪
♪ Everybody Rock! Rock!
With all your heart! ♪
♪ And soon you'll
hear new melodies ♪
♪ Hear the pulsing beat ♪
♪ The power of the rhythm ♪
♪ The magic never stops ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ All you need is
harmony (words don't matter) ♪
♪ Honesty
(With your feelings) ♪
♪ Keep on strumming! Keep on
going! Keep on and on! ♪
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CYAN]
How can anyone hate music?
I can't believe there are
people like that in the world!
[CHUCHU] Yes, I was
surprised to hear that, too.
Yeah, but, why would she
go and join a band, then?
So weird, pyuru.
Even if he hexed her,
can that possibly be
the only thing that makes
her hate music so much?
I hate him. That
slippery jellyfish!
Then the only way to fix
this is with our music!
We have power, too, so we're
gonna use it for good!
[DAGGER] Finally, the day
of the battle of the bands.
Ladies, are you
ready for victory?
Don't you worry about it.
We've prepared
everything we need to--
we've been ready from the start.
[DAGGER chuckles]
Very well.
[AILANE]
But first, a word--
I recall you promised
us we would enjoy
a crushing defeat at
the fight the other day.
Pretty big talk
for a little loser.
[DAGGER]
Let go! Stop!
Please, put me down!
I get it! I get it, okay?
Good.
We understand each other.
[DAGGER] First, we get
revenge on Plasmagica.
From there, we will conquer
Midi City--no, Sound Planet--
And even all the Sound Cosmos.
This battle of the bands is
merely a stepping stone to that.
Honestly, It doesn't matter
who we're up against.
The light of Midi City
will soon fade out and die.
All will be
drenched in darkness.
[DAGGER] O-Oh, what
reassuring confidence.
But tell me, why do you
detest music so much?
Don't even think it has
anything to do with you.
[DAGGER]
Hm. Well, it hardly matters.
I don't care, as long as
you carry out your mission.
Master Ailane's music
has always been strong,
and her performances,
awe-inspiring.
We admire and respect
her and, until now,
she's always kept both
of us right by her side.
However, now with
this upcoming battle,
Plasmagica, and
everything will be dyed
in permanent darkness
by our performance.
It's different from
what happened last time.
Hundreko, we need to
have a serious talk
with her before she--
Ugh.
[HUNDREKO] Independent
Myumoroid, biako System,
model number: WT sm
00110, activate.
Code Hundreko.
Cancel sleep mode.
Good morning. What did you need?
We can't continue like this.
Like what?
Master Ailane took us in.
She's the one who
looked after us both.
Until today, we three have
always been inseparable.
The Ailane I once knew
could never in her life
be a person who hated
music, even a little bit.
However, I'm just
her lowly maid.
My opinion is meaningless.
What should I do?
There is truth to
what you are saying.
For all she has done for us,
we owe her absolute obedience.
But I, too, miss the
person she used to be
and I want her back!
She may well reprimand me.
But if we can return
her to that time,
then I will cooperate
with you, maid!
[PEIPAIN]
Good. Let's plan.
[BOTH panting]
Dear girls, let us
take a brief respite
from our journey here.
But, look, Master, the summit
is before our very eyes.
Shouldn't we wait to rest
until we have reached the top?
[DARUDAYU] It is true,
the mountain's pinnacle
is only a short distance away.
However, I have
absolutely no idea
what awaits us beyond that.
I suspect we must be
prepared for anything.
Therefore, I believe
it would be best
to regain our strength here,
and take some time
to enjoy the scenery.
[A, UN gasp]
I am an utter failure.
I should have considered
what may lie ahead.
The failure falls on me as well.
After all this time we've
traveled, it escaped me.
[stomach growls]
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Thank you, Master!
[DARYDAYU chuckles]
[DARUDAYU]
We are so close.
our sojourn to this place has
been both long and difficult.
Our planet has also overcome
many trials and tribulations.
[DARUDAYU] How beautiful Sound
Planet is and fragile, too.
Along this journey,
we've met powerful foes.
It is our moral imperative
to guard this planet.
Which means, we find a way
to work in harmony
with everyone.
[DARUDAYU]
I've said my piece.
Now, girls, shall we continue?
[A, UN]
Yes!
[phone rings]
Yes?
Ah! King, lovely
to hear from you.
Oh.
Plasmagica is playing in
a battle of the bands?
I see. Who are their opponents?
Oh, no.
Aye, I understand.
A, Un! Let's go!
We must hasten forward!
[BOTH]
Yes!
[EMCEE 9A]
Okay!
Now, it's finally time
for the super-hyped battle
of the girl bands!
All right, let's get
ready to rumble!
[MAPLE]
Moment of truth! Go get 'em!
Y'all know how much this
place means to us.
Now let's rock it!
[RETOREE, CYAN, MOA]
Mm!
[DAGGER cackles]
[HOLMY]
Rosia, where are you going?
I'm still kinda
worried about Cyan
and the other girls,
so I thought I'd just
check in on them real quick.
But they're about
to go on stage,
don't bother them!
Aw, but I wanted to wish
them all good luck!
[HOLMY, TSUKINO, JACKLYN gasp]
Owie! What'd you
stop so short for?
Rosia?
What's your damage?
[ROSIA]
It's them.
[sighs] I want to
tell her how we feel,
but I know I'll lose my
nerve when I see her.
[AILANE]
Listen, you two.
We're going to send
everyone into hell!
You're right.
Disobedience will
get us punished.
[PEIPAIN]
Yes, but,
this is for Master
Ailane's sake, also.
We have to find a way to
be strong and push through.
That's right. You can't
leave things like this.
[PEIPAIN, HUNDREKO gasp]
Oh, it's you!
Why're you here?
I'll tell you why.
Because of Ailane's dark music,
Midi City won't have any
hope for the future,
and that's not okay!
Quiet, little girl!
You don't know a single
thing about our Master!
You're right, I don't!
But what I do know:
I love our city, and I don't
wanna see it destroyed.
It, or its music!
--[HOLMY] Exactly!
--[TSUKINO] You tell 'em!
[BOTH gasp]
Please tell me.
Why does your master
hate music so much?
We can't say.
Because even we don't
know the answer to that.
Isn't there some way
you can just come out
and ask her the reason?
[HUNDREKO]
That is impossible.
But how come?
[PEIPAIN]
The truth is, Hundreko and I
are only servants
to Master Ailane.
[HUNDREKO]
We cannot defy her wishes.
Yeah, but that
still isn't right!
If she's up to something bad,
you have to be brave and
tell her to stop doing it!
Yeah, she ain't lyin'.
There was a time she was
much easier to talk to.
Yes.
However, ever since she
started getting involved
with that guy Dagger,
she hates music even more.
And if that weren't bad
enough to deal with,
she doesn't even
seem to hear us.
It's almost as though we
barely exist to her anymore.
What the hell are you doing?
[CHRITICHRISTA gasps]
Ugh.
Hey, Pinky. I've already
warned you once.
Why can't you stop
peeping around
where you don't belong?
Tell me. You live
in a city of music.
Why would you do that
if you hate music so much?
Again, if I tell you the answer,
what do you plan
on doing about it?
Those without power should just
shut their mouths and
watch what happens.
[gasps]
Please, it's wrong.
If you perform with
anger in your heart,
then Midi City will
drown in darkness,
and be destroyed forever!
Master, her words are valid.
Please, do not do--
Enough!
[BOTH gasp]
[AILANE] Tonight my
desires will be fulfilled,
no matter what you say!
If you really think
you can get in my way,
then go ahead. I dare
you to try and stop me
with that irritating noise
you call "wholesome music."
At least that way, you might
go down with some dignity.
[AILANE]
We're leaving.
[BOTH]
Yes.
[FANS cheering]
[EMCEE 9A]
Tonight, they'll make
their first official appearance!
What kind of performance
can we expect to see?
Please welcome
to the stage, BVL!
[BUD VIRGIN LOGIC]
♪ Let the curtain rise ♪
♪ on this song of our demise ♪
♪ A foolish story all about
the unending search ♪
♪ For happiness ♪
♪
[BUD VIRGIN LOGIC]♪ The second
hand ticks and tocks away ♪
♪ As everything turns to dust ♪
♪ With good and evil above me ♪
♪ Descend to the end I must ♪
♪ Ah, faith has now become
so misshapen and grotesque ♪
♪ Such a wicked form ♪
♪ Just destroy the world ♪
♪ Annihilate everything
in your path ♪
♪ Let the music
be the soundtrack ♪
♪ Of this global ruin ♪
♪ Affection, kindness,
compassion, ♪
♪ all things that show love ♪
♪ Are no more ♪
♪ No they're not
needed anymore ♪
♪ Continue, to purge
all from you ♪
♪ Don't take it,
you have to refuse ♪
♪ Let solitude of judgment
be your guide ♪
♪ Falling falling
petals of roses... ♪
[DAGGER]
Yes, this is wonderful!
As long as I have this power,
I will return to
my original form.
[DAGGER]
Wha-What happened?
What can possibly be missing?
[DAGGER]
Curses!
Now, believe in yourself.
And also believe in us,
We'll believe in the music, too.
This is the fight of our lives!
♪
[CHUCHU]
Now, my sugars, let's do it!
With our ultra
best performance.
[RETOREE, CYAN, MOA]
To make the ultra best smiles!
[PLASMAGICA]
Ready, go!
All right!
♪
[CYAN]
♪ No matter where ♪
♪ I go I always
hear the sound ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Your singing voice ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ The melody ♪
♪ So sincere ♪
You two!
Why did you not play
the music of darkness?
Answer me!
Master Ailane, would
you listen, please?
We have dutifully served you,
and played this kind of music
up until now, because it's
everything you believe in.
Then explain yourself.
You have changed!
And not for the better!
[gasps]
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Although it
might hurt to keep going on ♪
♪ We're facing forward and
marching the path we're on ♪
♪ I know one day... ♪
Before you met Dagger,
you were very different.
Your passion for concerts and
all music was unbreakable!
That's why... now it's
hard for us to believe
you could hate music so much,
you'd want to annihilate it!
I may only be a Myumoroid,
but I still have a Melodizian.
Whenever the three of us
played songs together,
my Melodisian glowed
brighter than any other time.
Because of you, Master.
We understand there was a thorn
that pierced your heart.
Yet we have no idea
where it came from!
Master!
You don't have to bear this
horrible pain by yourself!
Oh, Peipain! Hundreko!
[sobs]
[HUNDREKO]
Master!
[PEIPAIN]
Is that really you?
[FANS cheering]
[EMCEE 9A]
Thank you, Plasmagica!
As usual, you bring the happy
back to the people
like nobody else can!
All right, kids, keep
those votes comin' in!
Now, it's time to
see the results!
Who's our next big winner?
Sit tight!
[DAGGER]
Who cares about the results?
[ALL gasp]
[DAGGER]
You're utterly useless!
[AILANE screams]
[CYAN gasps]
[RETOREE gasps]
[roars]
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Chuchu! ♪
[CHUCHU]
Okay, sugars. Let's do this!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Cyan! ♪
[CYAN] It's time for everyone
to hear our music!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Retoree! ♪
[RETOREE]
We're so perfectly in tune.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Moa! ♪
[MOA]
Pyuru, pyuru, pyuru...!
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Tell me
Why I'm so happy with you? ♪
♪ Tell me
How we have so much fun ♪
I know I'm ready for it ♪
♪ Let's (Fine!) go! (Fine!) ♪
♪ Sing for the show!
(Let's go) ♪
♪ CHU-CHU-CHU
CHU-CHU CHU CHU-LU-LU ♪
♪ CHU-LU-LU-LU ♪
[CYAN] ♪ I feel like the
thumping of my heart ♪
♪ is speeding up the rhythm ♪
♪ What can I do?
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My spirit is so electrified ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want to
(Que sera sera sera) ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Our memories
are piling up like photos ♪
♪ In a picture album of
melodies (Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[MOA] ♪ When I need recharging
all I have to do ♪
♪ Is play the album
of my memories (Yay!) ♪
[CYAN] ♪ We'll keep writing
all these new songs ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ Our imagination won't stop ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU]
♪ Almost done! ♪
[RETOREE, MOA]
♪ (Precious number one music) ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Now put it
all together! Yay! ♪
♪ Tell me
How you inspire music ♪
♪ In me?
My singing is all for you ♪
♪ Tell me
Why I never noticed until now? ♪
♪ (My song is you!!) ♪
♪ I know, it's all
in my subconcious ♪
♪ I know, you're with me
through everything ♪
♪ I know, you're
in my heart forever ♪
♪ Always (Fine! Fine!) ♪
♪ I love you (Once more) ♪
♪ Singing with you! (Yay!) ♪
[OGASAWARA yelling]
[OGASAWARA]
Listen, teenage noobs.
Today, just for you guys,
I'm offerin' somethin' special.
I, the amazing
producer Ogasawara,
(as if you didn't know),
will tell you the
secrets of success.
[STUDENTS]
Ooh!
[OGASAWARA]
First secret: Respond!
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
[OGASAWARA]
That's right.
When somebody speaks to you,
you must respond immediately.
That's the "A" of the ABC's.
[STUDENTS]
Ooh...
[OGASAWARA] That's why
you should respond now!
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
[SHIBARIN] It's like an
interjection in a folk song.
[HAKKUN] Or the kneadin'
part of makin' mochi?
[KITTSUN]
Pretty good, Hakkun!
[POKOE] Can I ask, why does
everyone in this business
always greet each other
by sayin', "Good mornin'"?
[OGASAWARA]
Huh? Th-That's, well, you know.
"Yo" isn't enough, is it?
And neither is "Hey," and
"Shyaa" is weird, too, right?
[HAKKUN]
What?
[SHIBARIN]
I don't get it.
[OGASAWARA] But "yo"
is the worst one, though.
[KITTSUN]
The old guy seems "off."
[POKOE]
Oh, I see.
So, then, what's the
"B" of the ABCs?
[OGASAWARA] Okay, high
schooler you've got me.
[AILANE]
My name is Ailane!
I will drive this
world into darkness!
[MAPLE]
You will? But how?
You're so small and adorable!
I'm delighted to meet you!
[PEIPAIN]
Keep your lechy eyes
away from Master
Ailane, you pig!
[HUNDREKO] Master, I want
to slice him up! May I?
[MAPLE]
Yeah, do it baby.