[DAGGER]
Who cares about the results?
[ALL gasp]
[DAGGER]
You're utterly useless!
[CYAN screams]
[roars]
Be careful, Cyan.
Oh, no. President!
Do you think that's
the Queen of Darkness?
[MAPLE]
Hmm.
[roars]
[CYAN]
Chuchu, we've gotta do it again!
[CHUCHU]
Right!
[VICTORIOUS]
I made it.
[MAPLE] Hey. Aren't
you ARCAREA'S manager?
♪
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Pumping Jumping! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[CYAN] ♪ Dontcha come at me
with your monotone ♪
♪ Feelin' somethin'
more harmonious ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ Waiting, to take a breath ♪
♪ I look, listen,
oh so carefully ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Oh baby,
can you hear the chords ♪
♪ Soundin' sweet the more
we rock the pop ♪
[MOA] ♪ Let's mix and
match our swing now ♪
♪ To make the music that we've
all been feelin' inside ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ (Passhuwa!
Pappasshuwa! Pashuwa, yes!) ♪
[CYAN]
♪ 'Cause even in my dreams ♪
♪ I hear the sound
of your voice ♪
[CHUCHU] ♪ In you I finally see
There is no other choice ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ I know I can
keep pushing ahead ♪
♪ And that I can really change ♪
[MOA] ♪ All I need is
to find melodies ♪
♪ I haven't
discovered just yet ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU] ♪ Everybody Rock!
Rock! Give it your all! ♪
♪ Just sing and be yourself! ♪
♪ Keep on keepin' on
and on and on and on ♪
♪ and cramming emotions
into your music ♪
♪ Everybody Rock! Rock!
With all your heart! ♪
♪ And soon you'll
hear new melodies ♪
♪ Hear the pulsing beat ♪
♪ The power of the rhythm ♪
♪ The magic never stops ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ All you need is
harmony (words don't matter) ♪
♪ Honesty
(With your feelings) ♪
♪ Keep on strumming! Keep on
going! Keep on and on! ♪
♪ Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ Jump to the beat! Hey! ♪
[laughs]
[laughing]
[VICTORIOUS laughing]
[roars]
[ALL gasp]
[CYAN]
Is that?
[VICTORIOUS laughing]
[screams]
[roars]
[MAPLE]
Everyone okay?
Master Ailane!
[BOTH gasp]
[DAGGER]
Ugh. Damn it.
[VICTORIOUS laughs]
[DAGGER]
Who are you?
Greetings, I'm Victorious.
To most, I'm known
by another title.
They call me the
Queen of Darkness.
[ALL gasp]
Oh, no. It's her!
[MAPLE]
Let me get this straight.
That's the real
Queen of Darkness?
No way! Don't tell
me that she was--
[TITAN]
Take a look.
What we're seeing now
is her true form.
[NICKEL] Big Brother,
who's the spirally lady
all dressed in black?
[laughs]
I admit, I've had quite a
bit of fun playing with you.
But now, I'm afraid
playtime is over.
On the day of the upcoming
Puru-Land Puru-Puru Rock Fest,
Sound Planet will be destroyed.
And then, music will die out!
Your days are numbered,
but I hope you'll enjoy
the ones you have left.
[laughing]
The Puru Land concert, huh?
What the hell?
So the singer from
that chick trio band
isn't the Queen of Darkness?
[ROM]
What in the world's goin' on?
[CROW]
Uh.
Aion?
What's the matter?
It looks like you just
saw a ghost. Hence.
[AION]
Ailane.
Who?
You know her or something?
Whoa! Take it easy!
[AION]
She's my little sister.
[ALL]
You're kidding!
Hence, whoa.
[CYAN]
Excuse me.
Are you all right?
Master Ailane! Wait!
[MAPLE]
Hey, are you okay?
[DAGGER] You think I
look hideous, don't you?
Go ahead and laugh.
[MAPLE]
Let's call a temporary truce.
In order to protect our world
in times like these,
I think it's best we
all fight together.
[DAGGER]
Tch.
Fine, but never forget,
I have no intention of becoming
friends with any of you.
[MAPLE chuckles]
[MAPLE]
Come on, buddy. That's my line.
What did you say?
That little girl is
really Aion's sister?
Yup.
[MAPLE] Where did Aion
go after he told you this?
He left without saying anything.
[MAPLE]
Hmm...
[bell chimes]
How dare you! You got somethin'
you wanna say to us?
Actually, we do.
[ROSIA] Wait, what was
that? Ailane's gone?
[AILANE]
I knew that I'd find you here.
Ailane.
Hundreko, what's the matter?
[HUNDREKO]
The master is nearby.
She must be in this building.
Huh? How would you know that?
My sensors make me
aware of such things.
That's kinda weird.
Knowing Aion, I'm pretty
certain he's on this roof.
Aion?
Aion is Ailane's older brother.
[PEIPAIN, HUNDREKO gasp]
[AILANE] Seems your habit of
hiding away in a high place
when things get rough hasn't
changed at all, has it?
Yeah.
[AION]
Ailane, what are you doing here?
Why are you in
a band in Midi City?
Do you even have
permission to be here?
I know that man has a lot
of expectations for you.
I can't imagine he'd allow this
to interrupt your studies.
The fact that you're
in a band like this,
out and performing,
it's just shocking.
Why in the world--?
You mean you don't know?!
[gasps]
It's you. This is
all your fault.
The music...
You took that music
you loved so much
and pushed all your
passion for it on me!
Because of that, I-I...
--Master Ailane!
--There she is!
I knew that coming to see
you would be a mistake.
Ailane, wait!
Please, come back! Master!
Cyan, we should go, too.
Yeah, 'kay.
[CROW]
Hey!
[yelps]
I didn't... I didn't
understand anything.
[ROM]
Wanna grab somethin' to eat?
[PEIPAIN]
Master Ailane!
Please, why won't
you talk to us?
Just tell us what's going on!
[AILANE]
I'm sorry.
All right fine, I'll tell you.
I'll tell you everything.
[AILANE]
I suppose you've figured it out,
but I have an older brother.
He was wise and noble,
and all of our relatives
had high hopes for his future.
I wanted to be just like him.
To me, and to others,
he could do no wrong.
What'cha think?
It's beautiful, Brother.
[AILANE]
As our father's successor,
he was made to study
how to be a good emperor,
and was expected to be
perfect in everything he did.
However, in time,
he was crushed by the
expectations and pressure.
Before long, music
became the only thing
that made him feel peaceful.
[knocking]
Hey...
[AILANE]
Then Father and our relatives
tried to take even that bit
of solace away from him.
They said he was a failure
as a successor.
[FATHER] This isn't how the next
head of the family should act!
What are you doing up here in
your room by yourself every day?
Playing music.
[FATHER]
What?
That's what I wanna
do with my life!
Don't be ridiculous!
You don't understand
the position you're in?
Darling, take it easy,
that's enough.
[AILANE] Father couldn't
bear the disappointment.
He kicked my brother
out of the house.
[AILANE]
Big Brother.
Are you really
going to leave home?
[AION]
Yeah.
Why won't you just beg
Father for forgiveness?
[AION]
Listen.
I can't do anything
other than music.
I can't live up to
his expectations.
Music really means
that much to you?
More than your family?
Is it more important
to you than me?
I'm sorry.
Just do whatever you want then!
Ailane.
[AILANE]
In time,
Father decided to make me
the successor to the family.
My name is Peipain.
Master Ailane, it's very
nice to meet you.
Model number: WT-sm
Zero-One-Zero-Zero.
Designation: Hundreko.
Well, I am called Ailane.
I control the darkness
of this world.
And I think everyone
should just go to hell.
In the end, that course of anger
just led me to be
used by Dagger.
It's pathetic.
[CYAN] But that doesn't mean
you hate music, does it?
What does it matter?
Well, I-I mean, after
hearing you play earlier,
I just couldn't imagine it.
Huh.
[CYAN]
Ailane.
Keep making music.
Not just for yourself, but for
your bandmates and the world.
Music brings joy to everyone.
I don't know.
[CYAN]
Here, take this.
[AILANE]
Is that what I--?
[gasps]
It's yours.
[MAPLE]
Something special for you.
[AION] But-But I didn't
order any gyoza .
[MAPLE]
I know. It's on the house.
Family chats require energy.
Are you her big brother or not?
Go talk to her, dude!
You know, they say blood
is thicker than water.
And hence--
Don't sweat the small stuff.
Just tell her how you feel,
and say it from the heart!
[sighs]
[DAGGER] Victorious.
We cannot underestimate her.
[MAPLE]
You're right about that.
[DAGGER] I will not stand by
and let her do as she pleases.
After all, this city is mine.
[MAPLE chuckles]
[MAPLE]
Whatever you say.
Oh, and on a side note, Dagger,
stop brainwashing
innocent girls already.
[DAGGER grunts]
Now, Master Ailane.
Yeah.
[AION]
Ailane!
Hey, uh, listen,
we're going to go on ahead.
We have preparations to make.
[AILANE]
All right, so what do you want?
[AION]
Look, I was unhappy.
I was so focused on finding
what I wanted out of life
that I ended up forcing all
the family matters onto you.
That was wrong.
I feel awful about
what I did to you.
Yeah, you're right. All of
this mess is your fault.
How I came to love music
so much that it hurts...
Learning how much fun
being in a band is...
All these things are your fault!
[AILANE] SHINGANCRIMSONZ's
performance wasn't bad.
I actually enjoyed it.
I will keep playing
music in a band.
Just wanted you to know.
[gasps]
Ailane!
[AILANE]
I'm heading home now.
It's high time I discuss this
properly with Father and Mother.
Is that so?
[ringing]
Ailane!
Wait, Big Brother!
Good luck, Ailane!
Thank you, Aion!
I'll always love you!
We've finally arrived
at our destination.
Oh, wow.
There it is. The great
Melodisian Almaz.
It's so beautiful.
[DARUDAYU]
A! Un! We need to hurry!
[A, UN]
Yes, Master!
[MAPLE] In light of this
terrible situation,
I have some fantastic news
to share with all of you!
That'd be nice for a change.
Tell us about it,
President, with passion!
[MAPLE] You got it! All three
bands under the BRR banner...
...will be appearing
as part of the lineup
for the Puru Land
Pyuru-Pyuru Rock Festival!
[GUYS]
Yes!
[ALL]
All right!
Meh.
We were set to appear from
the beginning, but whatevs.
I'm totes stoked for
you guys, though!
For sure!
She just had to say something.
[MAPLE] However, in her
declaration of war,
Victorious stated that she
will target this concert.
So if you're unable to
demonstrate your strength here,
there will be no future for us.
[gasps]
[GRATEFUL KING]
I won't let that happen!
[gasps]
[gasping]
[CROW]
Grateful King!
That's right, baby.
It's finally my turn.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Chuchu! ♪
[CHUCHU]
Okay, sugars. Let's do this!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Cyan! ♪
[CYAN] It's time for everyone
to hear our music!
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Retoree! ♪
[RETOREE]
We're so perfectly in tune.
[PLASMAGICA]
♪ Moa! ♪
[MOA]
Pyuru, pyuru, pyuru...!
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Tell me
Why I'm so happy with you? ♪
♪ Tell me
How we have so much fun ♪
I know I'm ready for it ♪
♪ Let's (Fine!) go! (Fine!) ♪
♪ Sing for the show!
(Let's go) ♪
♪ CHU-CHU-CHU
CHU-CHU CHU CHU-LU-LU ♪
♪ CHU-LU-LU-LU ♪
[CYAN] ♪ I feel like the
thumping of my heart ♪
♪ is speeding up the rhythm ♪
♪ What can I do?
(Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[CHUCHU]
♪ My spirit is so electrified ♪
♪ I go anywhere I want to
(Que sera sera sera) ♪
[RETOREE] ♪ Our memories
are piling up like photos ♪
♪ In a picture album of
melodies (Yeah, yeah, yeah!) ♪
[MOA] ♪ When I need recharging
all I have to do ♪
♪ Is play the album
of my memories (Yay!) ♪
[CYAN] ♪ We'll keep writing
all these new songs ♪
[RETOREE]
♪ Our imagination won't stop ♪
[CYAN, CHUCHU]
♪ Almost done! ♪
[RETOREE, MOA]
♪ (Precious number one music) ♪
[PLASMAGICA] ♪ Now put it
all together! Yay! ♪
♪ Tell me
How you inspire music ♪
♪ In me?
My singing is all for you ♪
♪ Tell me
Why I never noticed until now? ♪
♪ (My song is you!!) ♪
♪ I know, it's all
in my subconcious ♪
♪ I know, you're with me
through everything ♪
♪ I know, you're
in my heart forever ♪
♪ Always (Fine! Fine!) ♪
♪ I love you (Once more) ♪
♪ Singing with you! (Yay!) ♪
[OGASAWARA]
Good morning!
[HAKKUN]
Crazy.
[KITTSUN] Seriously, what
do you think? Isn't this bad?
[OGASAWARA]
Uhh...
[SHIBARIN] What's gonna
happen to Midi City?
[POKOE] Things have gotten
pretty violent there.
[OGASAWARA]
Hey.
[KITTSUN] "The bands for
the concert to commemorate
the opening of Puru Land
have been decided.
Representin' the artists
appearin' at the event,
Shuzo from Trichronika said
"With the power of
everyone's music,
we'll defeat the Queen of
Darkness known as Victorious."
They're doin' it, ya'll!
[HAKKUN]
Crazy!
[SHIBARIN] Should we help, or we
gonna sit back and do nothin'?
[OGASAWARA]
Yo!
[POKOE] I wonder if there's
anything we can do.
[KITTSUN]
There's one thing for sure.
We can go to Midi City
the day of the concert!
[POKOE]
Yeah!
[SHIBARIN]
It's decided!
[OGASAWARA]
Shyaa!
[HAKKUN]
Midi City. Here we come!
[KITTSUN]
The old guy's pretty late, huh?
[POKOE] He's strict with others,
but pretty easy on himself.
Kinda hypocritical,
if you ask me.
[SHIBARIN] Look at him,
sleepin' on the job.
[HAKKUN]
Crazy.
[MAPLE] Darudayu,
what in the world is this
"Melodisian Almaz"
you're talking about?
[DARUDAYU] To be truly
enlightened about that subject,
one must first undergo
a purification ceremony
and remove all worldly desires.
[MAPLE]
That's impossible.
[GRATEFUL KING]
For you maybe.