How many seconds has it been
since you wrote down the first name?
Well, Near, look like I win.
40.
We're still alive.
It's been over a minute and we haven't died.
Didn't I already tell you all
that no one was going to die?
But... But... But why?
Why won't they die?
God, I did everything you told me.
Rester, Gevanni, take him now.
Gevanni, the notebook please.
If you didn't believe me earlier, then see for yourselves.
I can confirm that the first four names are
definitely the real names of the SPK members.
The second four are the names of your team.
The only name that hasn't been written down
is Light Yagami.
If that weren't enough, Mikami also addressed you as God,
and said he did what you asked him to.
It's settled.
It's a trap!
This whole thing is a set up!
This is all part of Near's plan to frame me.
Isn't it a little odd that no one died
after having their name written in the notebook?
This proves it's a trap.
I believe I already told you that no one
would die because I modified the notebook.
No, you... that... that can't be.
This is a set up.
I don't know this guy.
Light, it's too late to deny it.
You know Near has won.
Just a moment ago, you were saying, "it looks like I win."
How much more of a confession do we need?
Light.
Why?
Stop it.
Light Yagami.
L. Kira.
It's over. You've lost the game.
Just a moment ago, you proclaimed
your victory, expecting us all to die.
And to tell the truth, you might have actually won,
and I would've lost.
We ended up doing exactly what you expected us to,
and altered the fake notebook in Mikuni's possession.
However, when I said before
that we had modified the notebook,
I was, in fact, referring to the
real notebook as well as the fake.
We only switched part of the fake notebook.
But as for the real one, we replaced the entire thing.
This notebook here is actually the real one.
No.
Impossible!
We used the same kind of pen that Mikami
used, copied his handwriting perfectly,
and made both the inside and the outside
of our fake look exactly like the original.
Gevanni was able to do it in a single night.
Of course, since I had touched
the real notebook before coming,
I've been able to see the Shinigami as well.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Mr. Shinigami.
I'm Near.
Nice to meet you too.
My name is Ryuk.
He can talk to Ryuk.
He can see him, so that means it.. it must be true.
Some of the edges of this notebook's pages are torn.
Tell me, if someone's name was written on a
ripped off piece of paper, would they still die?
Oh yeah, of course they would.
I thought so.
I bet you were able to use that to your advantage.
I wonder how many times you deceived us with this,
and how many people you killed.
Light Yagami, you are Kira.
Thi... this has got to be a trick.
Or could it be that Mikami's betrayed me somehow.
You're mistaken.
This was all thanks to Mello.
I believe if I explain this
much, you'll begin to understand.
What? Mello?
Please take a look at this page of the notebook.
Takada's name is in the notebook.
I was the one who killed her, but her
death was written there just one minute later.
Did that mean Mikami did the same thing I did?
God, you told me you couldn't move freely.
I had to make sure Takada was taken care of.
Wasn't that my duty to you?
You idiot!
I gave you strict orders not to make
any unnecessary movements until today.
It's all true.
On the 26th, right after Takada's kidnapping
was broadcast on the news, Mikami went to the bank.
I'd been trailing him.
I knew he went to the bank every month on the 25th.
So it was bizarre
for someone so methodical to
go to the bank twice in two days.
I followed Mikami to the bank as
he headed for the safe deposit boxes.
It was only at this time that he seemed
concerned whether someone was following him or not.
I got into his safe deposit box.
Inside was the real notebook.
Sure enough, Takada's name had
already been written inside it.
Do you understand now, Light Yagami?
You didn't realize that Mikami made a move on
his own and wrote Takada's name in his notebook,
because you had already killed her
using a notebook clipping yourself.
This was the event that made me consider
the possibility of a fake notebook.
We were able to stop you thanks
to the efforts of one person
it was Mello who did it all.
Mello probably knew what was going to happen all along.
It can be resolved by having
a name written in the notebook?
That's right.
Well then, if I don't do it...
I bet Mello knew in his heart that working by ourselves,
neither of us would be able to attain our goal
and surpass our mentor L.
But together... together, we can stand with L.
Together, we can surpass L.
And now, acting as one, we face the Kira who defeated L.
And with solid evidence, beat him at his own game.
Let's see you try and talk your way out of this one,
if you can.
That's right.
I am Kira.
That's right. I am Kira.
And what can you do?
Kill me right here?
Hear this.
I'm not only Kira, but I am also...
God of the New World.
Kira has become law in the world we now live.
He's the one who's maintaining order.
I have become justice, the only hope for mankind.
Kill me?
Is that really the right thing to do?
Since Kira's appearance six years ago, wars have stopped,
and global crime rates have been reduced by over 70%.
But it's not enough.
This world is still rotten with too many rotten people.
Somebody has to do this.
And when I first got that notebook all those years ago,
I knew I had to do it.
No.
I was the only one who could.
I understood that killing people was a crime.
There was no other way.
The world had to be fixed.
A purpose given to me.
Only I could do it.
Who else could have done it and come this far?
Would they have kept going?
The only one...
who can create a new world...
is me.
No.
You're just a murderer, Light Yagami.
And this notebook is the deadliest weapon
of mass murder in the history of mankind.
You yielded to the power of
the Shinigami and the notebook.
And you have confused yourself with a god.
In the end, you're nothing
more than a crazy serial killer.
That's all you are.
Nothing more and nothing less.
Useless fools.
As if they could ever understand.
Near, here's some food for thought.
That notebook you have and the one that.
Aizawa brought from the Japanese task force headquarters
are they both real?
What is he up to?
Is he bluffing?
At the moment, only I know where the real notebook is.
If you truly want to defeat Kira,
as well as test the notebook that Aizawa was carrying,
I guess you're going to have to
write down either my name or Mikami's.
It's the only way to see if it's real,
or fake.
He's hidden a piece of the notebook.
Matsuda.
Matsuda! You idiot!
Who the hell do you think you're shooting at?
Don't screw with me!
What was it all for then?
What about your dad?
What the hell did he die for?
My dad?
You mean Soichiro Yagami?
That's right, Matsuda, in this world,
all those earnest people like him
who fight for justice they always lose.
You want a world where people
like that are made to be fools?
I know you understand, so kill the others.
Shoot them!
You led your own father to his death.
And now that he's gone, you call him a fool?
His blood!
I'll kill him.
He has to die!
Matsuda!
Damn you.
What the hell is this?
Mikami, what are you waiting for?
Write down their names!
Write them down!
Kill them now!
It's finally over, isn't it, Near?
Yes.
Where are you, Misa?
Where's Takada?
Someone.
What do I do now?
What the... Mikami!
Quick, stop the bleeding.
It's already too late.
He'll be dead in a few seconds.
Wait, Light!
He's getting away.
Light!
Mr. Aizawa.
It's unlikely he has anymore pieces of the notebook.
And with those wounds, he's not going to go far.
He'll stop running soon, even if we leave him alone.
Hmph.
Near, I'm not gonna follow your orders.
Very well then.
I'll leave it up to you.
Well, Light, it looks like you've lost.
Remember how, in the beginning when we first met,
I told you that I'd be the one
writing your name in my notebook.
That is part of the agreement between a
Shinigami who brings a notebook to the human world
and the first human who picks it up.
If they put you in prison, who knows when you'd die.
And I don't want to lie around waiting.
So it's all over.
You'll die here.
It was good while it lasted.
We eased each other's boredom for quite a while.
Well, Light, it's been interesting.