I'm going to announce my engagement to Light
at the Pop Music Festival.
I used to really like Kira too, but I know for sure
that Light is gonna catch him soon.
And as for you, you'll probably be executed.
You are to send me a fan latter that
I'll be able to recognize as yours.
You will also enclose something else in the envelope.
Five blank pages from the notebook.
Carry on with your judgments and killings as
usual until I received the letter and the pages.
And how after you receive them?
Make a notebook that looks as
close to the original as possible,
and act as if you're killing people by using this decoy.
Aw, come on now, lady.
I mean, wearing a short skirt like that in the winter.
Please, someone.
Delete.
He's getting off the train.
A man who was on the same train as Mikami just collapsed.
He was harrassing a young woman
and suddenly fell to the floor.
It all happened about a half a minute
after he wrote something in the notebook.
That's gotta be it.
Well, now we know for sure.
Yes.
Our next order of business is to
get as close as possible to Mikami.
But before we rush in blindly, there's
something we need to be careful of,
and that is the being known as the Shinigami.
The Shinigami will be loyal to Mikami,
and it will warn him if it discovers we're following him.
But the Shinigami can only be seen by
those people who have touched the notebook.
It's going to be pretty difficult to be
careful of something we can't even see.
We're going to try, no matter how difficult.
Right. Understood, sir.
Light's having another one of his
meetings with Takada this evening.
Right after they started having these encounters,
Takada got a phone call from Kira,
and all the surveillance cameras had to be removed.
The first thing that came to my mind
was that they'd be able to
communicate secretly by writing messages.
Everything checks out in here.
I've gone over the entire room, and there's nothing in it.
There's only the wiretap on me.
Uh, right.
Then all that's left is the bathroom.
Why does Light care so much about
checking for cameras and wiretaps?
Never mind that, why is Kira allowing
these meetings in the first place?
Something just doesn't add up.
If they really are writing notes to each other,
there's only one way to prove it.
Light. I thought you should know.
I had a private chat with Ms. Misa Amane yesterday.
About what?
Whoa. Oh boy, Light's in trouble now.
Matsuda.
Is there some reason you're so happy about this?
She told me that she's planning to announce her engagement
to you during her appearance at the Pop Music Festival.
Whoa. He's busted.
Light's in the dog house!
Shut up, Matsuda!
No.
She thinks we're together because I
haven't been able to break it to her yet,
but she means nothing to me.
Misa, you idiot.
Why pull a stunt like that?
No. Takada. you're just as bad.
Why are women like this?
Nothing, you say?
Why should I believe you?
She was in charge of killing before T.
Somehow she gained the same power as I had
and found out that I was Kira.
In the end, I had no choice but to take her as my partner.
It's the only reason I would
ever choose such an impulsive girl.
So, Misa was doing Kira's killings.
But right now, I'm the one doing it for him.
Light had no choice with Misa,
but he chose me specially to help him.
Believe me. She's nothing.
You're the only one for me.
You're the only one for me?
Is that supposed to be serious?
I expected better from you, Light.
She does have a point.
I mean, that's a really cheesy line, especially for Light.
So which one do you think he'll pick?
Amane or Takada?
Well, he could keep two timing them.
Are you serious?
You don't see any problem with that?
Hey, I'm not the one who...
Will you two shut up?
You're going to have to prove yourself from now on, Light,
but I will trust you.
Of course, if I find out that you're lying,
you'll pay dearly.
In fact, I'll tell Kira about it.
Kira, huh?
You know, I understand that the
world really needs Kira right now,
but I just can't help but wonder.
Will the day ever come when you and I can be together?
I can't help but hate Kira for choosing you
as a spokesperson, because it keeps us apart.
I don't mind if he kills criminals,
but we've done nothing wrong.
We have the right to lead happy lives, don't we?
Yes. I want to be happy together with you.
But that could only happen if Kira wasn't around.
You're right.
If only Kira wasn't around.
Kira should be arrested.
It's true.
If you and I are ever going to
have a chance at being happy together,
Kira needs to be caught.
W... Wait a minute, Kiyomi.
Do you seriously mean that?
Yes.
All right, but if I'm going to
arrest him, I'll need your help.
You'll be putting yourself in danger.
After all, I'll be defying the police, and you'll
be going against Kira and the entire world as well.
Are you sure... that's OK?
That's a long pause.
All right.
If cooperating with you means that we can be together,
then I'm prepared to make that sacrifice, Light.
What a turn around.
Just like you'd expect from our guy!
He was able to move the conversation from
cheating on Misa Misa to getting Taki to help him.
Mikami's talking to himself.
What's going on?
He was too far away for me to pick up his
voice, but I recorded video of his lips moving.
I'm sending you the footage I was able to get.
It's of Mikami during his lunch break.
This is it right here. He's saying something.
Show it to us one more time in slow motion.
Is that you, Shinigami, is what he said.
He seems to have reacted to
the scrap of paper at his feet.
He just gave a small sigh.
At this point, he talks to himself a little more.
I'm gonna zoom in on his lips.
That Shinigami.
Ever since he...
handed me the notebook,
he hasn't reappeared.
That Shinigami.
Ever since he handed me the notebook,
he hasn't reappeared.
Mikami was given the notebook by one of the Shinigami,
but it seems that Shinigami hasn't been following him.
So that's how it is.
I guess that's all for today.
See you next time.
Of course.
It's finally over.
Man, things got pretty intense today, don't you think?
It's tough to do this for hours on end.
Yeah. You really look like you're suffering.
All right. I'm gonna wrap things up at the hotel.
OK, thanks for all your hard work.
You know, I feel kind of bad that Aizawa is stuck
with booking the hotel and checking out every time.
It's gone.
The mark I left is gone.
I left four marks.
Two of them are gone.
The room's been left just as it was.
Housekeeping hasn't come in yet.
Then how and why would anyone
switch these two notepads for new ones?
That settles it.
They're writing notes.
Yes?
What's that?
You want to meet and talk with Near in person?
Mr. Aizawa.
It's been a while.
And it's a pleasure to meet you.
That's very nice of you,
but kind of hard to accept while I'm blindfolded.
He doesn't have any weapons or cameras on him.
In that case, you're free to take off your blindfold.
Huh?
Near, I believe what you said earlier.
L was been meeting Takada almost every single night.
I know.
Well, then what about this?
They are passing notes to each other.
I confirmed it.
Mr. Aizawa, please don't take
any unnecessary actions on your own.
Unnecessary actions?
Yes This is not the point where we bring up
evidence against Kira and openly confront him.
I must corner him in a dead end with
a plan that would guarantee his defeat.
This is what it will take to stop him for good.
Mr. Aizawa, I'm going to be blunt with you.
You and the rest of the task
force are already out of the picture.
However, if you still want to help capture Kira, you can.
All I want you to do is keep an
eye on him, as you've been doing.
That's it? Keep an eye on him?
Yes.
Of course, there certainly is
a purpose in watching over L.
In fact, I've already taken it
into account as part of my plan.
That's why I'm hoping you can help me in that respect.
I want you to watch him, in order to win against Kira.
And after that, I want you to be a witness...
to the end of Kira.
This has been a year of breathroughs for
me, and I'm sure for many others as well.
And what better way to bring this year to an
exciting close than with the EastWest Pop Music Festival?
I'm your host for this evening, Kiyomi Takada.
We hope you all enjoy the show.
All right, the Pop Music Festival's about to begin!
Matsuda, shouldn't you be checking
over the reports on Kira's killings?
Yeah. In a minute.
But after Misa Misa performs.
She's the opening act this year.
We got to cheer her on. Yeah!
Can we help you?
Hm?
Pardon me.
We're from the SPK.
We'll need you to come with us.
Before we continue,
I'm afraid I must apologize on behalf of the staff of NHN.
It's very unfortunate,
but it seems that this year's opening act, Ms.
Misa Amane, has not entered the concert hall yet.
Huh?
What?
Of course, many unexpected things can...
What's going on?
Mogi didn't tell us anything about this.
Take me back to NHN right now!
What is this?
Are you trying to ruin my reputation?
Misa Misa, you've got to try and stay calm.
Motchi, why should I?
We need to do this in order to catch Kira.
But that has nothing to do with me.
You should know that I was going to
take you at gunpoint as a last resort.
But you didn't resist.
That was a great help.
Thank you, Mr. Mogi.
I probably would have resisted if I
hadn't listen to what Aizawa told me. But...
after hearing about the notepads,
there's no doubt in my mind.
What's going on?
Near.
Yes? What is it, L?
We have a problem.
Mogi and Misa Amane have gone missing.
I'm already aware of that.
I was the one who took them into custody.
He what?
For what reason?
Oh, just in case.
Near, kidnapping is a blatant criminal act.
You have to stop this now.
Actually, Mr. Mogi and Amane both came here willingly.
You can even ask them yourself.
I'll put them on the line now.
Here they are.
Mogi. Misa. This is L speaking.
Light!
I'm told that Near is detaining you.
He said that you both agreed to it. Is that true?
It is.
Mogi.
A... Actually, I was against the whole thing.
But Motchi said it would be
best if I just went along quietly.
He told me we would have both been killed if I didn't.
All right.
It's fine, as long as you both consented to this.
So now I've removed Misa Amane,
the one who might be the second Kira from the equation.
Light Yagami, I'm sure the significance
of this move isn't lost on you.
Hey, no way!
You're planning to end this without Misa Misa performing?
God, what a rip-off!
It looks like Lidner and the others were successful.
It's past 9:00.
All right. It's my turn.
Mikami leaves work at almost the same
time every day, with only slight variations.
He leads a completely scheduled life, for the most part.
So, he always goes to that particular gym
every Monday and Thursday at around 9:00.
Is that correct?
Yes.
He's kept that routine for the
past four years, ever since he joined.
He didn't even skip New Year's Day.
I became a member and made a
few inquiries to confirm it myself.
Good.
So then we can assume...
that he'll be there on Monday the 31st as well?
Yes.
If he's the type of man who would go on
holidays, then he'll certainly go on New Year's Eve.
Giovanni, would it be possible for you to
touch the notebook on the 31st at the gym?
Huh?
Yes.
I've already done a thorough
check of the hotel's security.
The locker room is definitely
free of any kind of surveillance.
Then I'll leave it to you.
Sir, if there is a Shinigami with him,
there's a distinct possibility
that I will die, isn't there?
Yes.
Part of the reason you're doing
this is to test that theory.
Even if you don't see any Shinigami
after first touching the notebook,
I want you to continue watching Mikami for a while longer
before we conclude whether or
not he has one following him.
I can have Rester do it if you're too scared.
No. I understand. I'll do it.
Hm?
If there's a Shinigami around.
No. If there was one, I'd be dead.
It's too late to turn back now.
I have to touch it.
Sir, I've succeeded in touching the notebook.
I can't confirm the existence
of any Shinigami at this time.
Commander Rester, please connect
me with Mr. Mogi for a moment.
Hm?
Mr. Mogi, according to your
investigation and the rules of the notebook,
how long can a person be controlled before their death?
Based on the data we got from
Yotsuba's experiments, it's 23 days.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'd say that the killings done by
Yotsuba were more than enough to prove it.
Thank you for your assistance.
We have to consider the possibility
that Giovanni is already being controlled.
In that case, they could be making
him say that there is no Shinigami.
That means I need to confront L in exactly 24 days,
if Giovanni is still alive until then.
Kiyomi.
I saw you had some trouble at the Pop Music Festival.
Yes.
I never imagined that Ms. Amane would missing.
Give T an order to contact you
and let you know as soon as he's confirmed everything.
Once you hear from him,
I want you to send me a text message
or call me with the following message.
I want to see you as soon as possible.
Photographs?
Yes.
I want to see exactly what he wrote in the notebook.
I want to see the pattern in how Mikami writes,
if there are any habits, and what kind of notebook it is.
I want to see it all.
Everything in detail with my own eyes.
What do you think, Near?
Perfect.
Giovanni has done an excellent job.
The handwriting matches that of the
records Mikami keeps as prosecutor.
There's absolutely no doubt.
This is his handwriting.
I agree.
With this, we can do it.
The escort team has been attacked.
Ms. Takada, are you all right?
Is this Near's work again?
No. This isn't his style.
It's more like Mello!