Well, then, let's begin tonight's meeting.
There's supposed to be eight of
them, but only seven are present.
That must mean that...
They probably killed one of their members.
Hmm.
In order to further the growth of the Yotsuba
Group and best serve its financial interests,
who should we kill next?
You see? It's just like I told you last week.
This is not good. At this rate...
But before we get to that, there are
several topics that we need to discuss.
First, there is the issue of Hatori's death.
That was unavoidable.
To be honest, in a certain sense,
I'm relieved that Hatori is dead.
Kira has demonstrated that we
must be committed to these meetings.
We now know what will happen if we try to leave.
Hmm.
I think we all understand what
Hatori's death means for the rest of us.
Let's not take it lightly.
Now, moving on, our next topic is Eraldo Coil's report.
One of their members just died,
and that's all they're going to say?
So did we really pay $5 million for this report?
I mean, come on. Look at this.
He hasn't found out anything important
about L, like his name or his face.
Is this Coil guy seriously going to be of any use to us?
Hold on a second.
There is something very interesting
in the last part of this report.
Coil's warning us that we can't
afford to take L's existence too lightly.
In particular, it says, the concentration of killings
that are beneficial to Yotsuba will likely be noticed by L
if they continue on Fridays and Saturdays.
Sounds like this Eraldo Coil has
figured out what we've been up to.
I admit, it's quite impressive.
At any rate, I personally think we
should stop killing every weekend.
This is unbelievable.
It's like they're trying to confess to everything.
Hmm.
As long as we have this video as evidence,
we could probably arrest all seven of them.
This is not good.
Kira hasn't been flexible up till now, has he?
It would be nice if he could spread
out his killings over the whole week.
The fact that Coil noticed what we've been up to makes
it too dangerous to continue killing at our usual pace.
From now on, we have to be even more careful
and make sure that nobody else happens
to notice a trend in these deaths.
Now, onto the main topic.
Who should we kill?
Hmm.
I think we should focus on ELF Insurance.
If they expand into the Japanese market,
Yotsuba and many other companies
will lose valuable clients to them.
Agreed.
All right.
Any objections to killing these
people from ELF with accidental deaths?
No objections.
Oh.
Is this for real?
How can they do this so easily?
Another potential candidate is Santero
Zenzai, a member of the Kugisawa Group.
He's been protesting Yotsuba's resort development plans.
Zenzai's known to have high blood pressure,
so we can designate a time for him to
suffer a stroke, resulting in natural death.
Any objections?
No objections.
Kira? Deaths by accident, by disease?
Designated times of death?
It's all just as we suspected.
We were right.
Now, unfortunately,
we can only be completely sure after
those people they've named are dead.
Ah.
We will continue to monitor these meetings
and take note of what they say, how they act,
and, most importantly, whether
the people they choose actually die.
If we can confirm the connection
between their plans and the deaths,
then we'll definitely be able to catch Kira.
Ryuzaki!
Ah, mm... what is it?
There's no need to yell in unison.
I can't carry on knowing these people will die.
That's just immoral.
Right.
Here it comes.
I know you're planning to catch Kira by letting
these guys actually carry out these murders,
but we can't let that happen.
That's right.
It's obvious that these seven men are behind the killings.
With Matsuda's testimony and this footage we've recorded,
we have all the evidence.
You're making this difficult.
If we were to take action now,
everything we've done will go to waste.
So what do you say we take care of the ELF in three weeks.
And as for Zenzai, we'll ask
Kira to kill him this weekend.
No objections.
If that's what they're going to
do, then there's not much time left.
Light, we already know the phone
numbers of these board members, don't we?
Yeah.
I don't care who we call.
I need to reach one of these men
and have them stop these murders.
Please, hold on.
That will cause suspicion.
It would mean the investigation
caught up to them three days
after they were contacted by Aiber.
Also, it would make it far more unlikely
that we would be able to
discover who the real Kira might be.
We can't afford such a huge
setback, seeing how far we've come.
In order to catch Kira,
we are going to need some solid proof.
Ryuzaki, if one of these seven men is in fact Kira,
would it be safe to say that if I try calling one of them,
the odds of that person actually
being Kira is going to be one in seven?
I'm thinking there could be more than one Kira among them,
a probability of two in seven at most.
If we're prepared to let them know that
the investigation is catching up to them,
let's place our bets on these odds.
Ryuzaki, I'm going to pose as L.
Judging from their conversation so far,
the one least likely to be Kira
but with the most influence is...
Ooi!
Namikawa.
Uh...
If you're going to make a call, please use this phone.
It's set up so it can't be traced or tapped.
You know, this would all go a lot faster
if we'd kill off the execs of our
rival companies and be done with it.
That would be going a little too far.
Why?
We can kill them and split their holdings.
Is this Reiji Namikawa, head of the
Yotsuba Group's marketing department?
Hmm.
Yes. And who is this?
Listen carefully, but don't draw attention to yourself.
I am L.
I've placed cameras and wiretaps
throughout that meeting room.
Even as I speak, I'm recording
footage of your entire meeting.
The first thing you discussed was Hatori's death.
Now you're debating who to kill next.
Am I correct?
He's been watching everything.
If you're not Kira,
or if you are not someone who can contact Kira directly,
let's make a deal.
A deal?
I need you to delay the deaths of ELF's
president and Mr. Zenzai by one month.
I doubt it will be difficult for someone
of your standing to accomplish that.
Yes. Yes, I see.
Right. Uh, go on.
If you complete your end of the deal and
cooperate with our requests from now on,
then your crimes... no, not just yours,
but everyone's crimes, with the
exception of Kira's will be pardoned,
based on the premised that Kira blackmailed
you into participating in these meetings.
I see. OK.
My only option is to join L.
No, I'll be dead if Kira manages to find out.
What should I do?
If you tell the others about this call, they will panic.
It would be of no advantage to you.
Everyone would be arrested immediately.
But that's not my intention.
I'm planning to go one on one against Kira.
Listen.
If I win against Kira, you
will be acquitted of all charges.
If Kira wins, then you'll be free to
carry on with your comfortable life.
Just play along with both parties.
Staying on the sidelines would be best.
You're not in a position to lose
anything, regardless of who wins in the end.
You would only be at a loss if I
decided to arrest you right here and now.
Damn it.
He already knew what answer I would have given.
That's all for now.
Right. I'll see you Monday then.
What's going on, Namikawa? Who was that?
Oh, one of my men screwed up
again. I'll have to fix it on Monday.
Anyway, sorry for the interruption.
Let's get back on topic.
We were discussing when we should
kill Zenzai and the men from ELF.
Here's what I'm thinking.
We'll give Coil one month to reveal L's identity.
If he still hasn't uncovered the information we
need, then we can go ahead and kill the targets randomly.
Then we'll give him another month
to investigate and repeat the process.
Once we get rid of L permanently, we can go
back to killing two or three people a week.
In other words, our top priority
should be the elimination of L.
I see.
Once we kill L, there won't
be anything standing in our way.
But until then, we need to be careful.
Right.
Sounds like a reasonable plan to me.
We need to be extremely careful
if we don't want to get caught.
Then we're in agreement.
We'll give Coil one month.
Agreed.
L, this should satisfy you for now.
We will still be meeting on a weekly basis.
That is all.
That went well.
Yeah.
You really are quite amazing, Light.
Not only did you manage to delay the killings,
but you also set up Namikawa as a potential mole for us.
It sounded exactly like the sort of thing I
would do, and you thought of it quicker than I did.
At this rate,
if I end up dying somehow,
it's quite possible that you
would be capable of succeeding me.
What? Why are you being so morbid?
There isn't time for that.
We only have a month to figure out Kira's
identity and gather evidence against him to prove it.
This is only the beginning.
Yes, but you were the one who first noticed
the connection between Yotsuba and Kira.
You actually might be more capable than I am.
I honestly believe you could take this on.
Tell me, If I should die,
would you take over for me as L?
If I should die, would you take over for me as L?
If he is Kira and just playing
innocent, he's sure to say yes.
What are you talking about?
As long as we're joined by
these, we would die together anyway.
I see.
Ryuzaki, I'm sorry,
but I'm going to have to tell everyone
what you're really thinking right now.
He thinks that if I am Kira,
then there are two possibilities.
Either I'm just pretending I'm not
him and putting on an act or Kira's power
has passed on from me to someone else,
and I have no memory that I
was ever Kira in the first place.
He's trying to determine which, if either, is the truth.
The first theory... if I am putting on an act,
he will never remove these handcuffs.
No, even if I wasn't pretending to be innocent,
I'm sure he still wouldn't take them off.
Ryuzaki still believes that I'm Kira.
Even if that power had been passed to someone else,
he thinks that I would have planned to have
it return to my once I'm safe from suspicion.
In other words, I wasn't being controlled at all.
He thinks it was a plan...
to pass on the power and arrange for it
to come back to me once I've been cleared.
Impressive.
He figured out exactly what
I'd been thinking all this time.
Ryuzaki's theory is that once I steal L's title,
I will become Kira again.
Correct.
Taking on the identity of L,
having the power to control the police in every country
while being Kira in secret... it's ideal.
And you're thinking I could do it.
No, that I would do it.
That's what you're saying, isn't it?
Yes.
But what about now?
I told you, I don't want your title.
That should prove even to you that
I'm not putting on an act, shouldn't it?
If this is all an act, and you
are trying to steal my identity,
there's no chance you would be foolish
enough to reveal your plan in front of everyone.
Wouldn't you agree?
Hmm.
Ryuzaki.
Huh?
Do you think that I'm actually
capable of becoming a murderer?
Kira?
Even after I help you catch him?
Do I seem like that kind of person to you?
Yes, you do.
I've always thought so.
Hmm.
Gah, not again.
OK, break it up! Once is enough.
It was a draw, so let's just
leave it as an even match, OK?
Yeah, you're right.
Anyway, let's focus on catching the
Kira that's in front of us right now.
As long as I have the handcuffs
on, you shouldn't have any complaints.
I suppose so.
We only have a month, so
there's no time to get distracted.
Ryuzaki.
Yes?
We have plenty of footage from this meeting.
Can we use that as evidence against those seven
men and prevent the murders of other criminals?
Here we go again.
Unfortunately, no.
But why?
At the moment, we're not certain
if Kira is among those seven men.
If all they have is a tenuous connection with him,
then Kira will kill them as soon as they're arrested.
We have to be absolutely sure that Kira is among
them, so there's no point in detaining them now.
And even if it does turn out to be one of them,
it will still be quite difficult
to determine who the culprit is.
Mm, I believe it's still far
too early for us to make our move.
Hold on.
At the same time, we can't say that
he's definitely not among the seven.
That means there's a chance the killings will stop
if we take this opportunity to arrest them.
I think Dad's right. There is a chance.
We have to act on it.
Excuse me, but...
I think from now on, I should go after Kira by myself.
Huh?
You can use these headquarters as you wish.
I'll also be here, but we will be working independently.
You can conduct your investigation
under your own direction.
Feel free to arrest those men if you like.
I will be carrying on my own investigation.
We'll only get into arguments if we don't
split up and act separately at this point.
This is for the best.
Are you saying you're going to figure
out who Kira is by any means necessary?
Yes.
This case will never be solved
unless we capture Kira himself.
Don't get me wrong.
I wouldn't say that preventing more deaths is pointless.
But if we don't uncover the entire truth once and for all,
Kira will only appear again, and the
number of victims will continue to increase.
That's why I believe it's more
important to find out who Kira really is.
As I've been saying, I'm opposed
to arresting those seven men.
If you want to do so, then you will
have to take responsibility for them.
I will pursue Kira on my own.
We only have one month.
I wonder who will succeed?
R... Ryuzaki. Where are you going?
To Amane's room.
Sorry, I know you're on your father's side in all this,
but I can't remove these handcuffs.
I'm afraid you're going to have to come along with me.
Light! I didn't know we were supposed to have a date.
Oh, right, I should have known.
Misa Amane...
Tell me, do you love Light from the bottom of your heart?
Huh?
Uh, yeah.
Of course I do.
But you also worship Kira, don't you?
Well, yeah.
So then, if you had to choose between Light and Kira,
who would you pick?
What?
That's obvious. Of course it's gonna be Light.
I'm really grateful to Kira and want to meet
him someday in person, but that's not true love.
I'd definitely choose Light.
But your precious Light is planning to catch Kira.
Isn't that right?
Well, yes, of course I am.
He says he wants to catch Kira.
Now what will you do?
Well, if that's what Light says, then
I'm gonna support him no matter what.
I see.
So if you were given the opportunity
to work with Light on this investigation,
would you take the offer?
What? Ryuzaki...
Yeah, of course I would.
I'd do anything I could to help Light.
Wait, hold on a second. Where are you going with this?
I'm planning to have Aiber pose as Eraldo Coil again.
He'll tell the Yotsuba members
that while he was investigating L,
he discovered that Misa Amane might know who he is.
He'll also tell them that L brought her in for questioning
on suspicion that she was the second Kira.
That part is true.
If the Yotsuba Group believe that
Misa could be their lead to finding L,
then they'll say that they want to meet
her to discuss their advertising campagin.
They'll use that opportunity to question her.
Thanks to Matsuda's screw-up,
they may already be considering Misa as
their new spokesperson, so this could work.
Yeah, right.
We can't do that.
Why not?
This plan is too risky.
Who knows what could happen to you?
Oh, wow! Does that mean you're worried about me?
Yay!
But don't worry.
I won't mind doing something
like this if it's for you, Light.
Listen, Misa.
If they suspect that you might know who L really is,
we don't know how far they'll be
willing to go to get that information.
No problemo.
I promise I won't say anything, even if they torture me.
I can attest to that.
But Kira can control his
victims' actions before their death.
There's a good chance he might try to
manipulate her into revealing
what she knows and then kill her.
Also, if he does manage to kill
L, he won't have any use for Misa.
He'd kill her to keep her silent.
Uh, I don't like the sound of that.
Light.
Hmm?
You forget that if we win against Kira, Misa won't die.
Besides, as long as we're handcuffed
together, you and I share the same fate.
If I die, so will you.
If that happens, Misa is the
one who would grieve most of all.
Either we lose and both die together,
or we successfully catch Kira.
Which is it?
We catch Kira!
I would never dream about living in a world without Light.
Yes, that would be dark.
Cut it out! This is just crazy.
We're running out of time, and
I'm starting to get desperate.
As for Misa Amane,
I've turned to her because I know her
bravery and love for you is boundless.
Do you really mean it?
Oh no, I think I've totally
misunderstood you all this time.
I even called you a pervert.
But you actually do understand how I feel, don't you?
Yes.
Misa is indisputably the most
perfect and worthy woman for Light.
Yay!
You're such a sweetie. Thank you, Ryuzaki.
I could actually fall for you.
Let's not go that far.
But you could maybe be a friend of mine.
Would that be OK?
Yes.
So now I've gained yet another friend.
Yeah. Of course, any friend of
Light is a friend of mine as well.
Let's all be friends together.
Yay, fun, huh.
And of course, I would never
think of betraying any of my friends.
With our powers combined, we'll arrest Kira.
Unfortunately, Light's taking a
different investigative approach from us
and will be working with his father and the others.
Hmm?
I'm afraid it will just be you and I.
Huh? What's up with that?
Come on, L. Now you're just playing dirty.
You're leaving me with no other choice but to join your...
No, that's quite all right.
What are you talking about? Of course he'll be joining us.
That's not it either.
I've been opposed to this
investigation since the beginning.
It's too dangerous for her!
Oh, Light. You're so sweet.
Thank you for worrying about me.
But please let me do this.
I want to be useful to you somehow.
If I can be useful, then maybe you'll love me even more.
And besides, I would gladly die if it were for you, Light.
Figuring out the logistics of arresting
seven people is going to be challenging.
I don't suppose you two have any ideas. Mogi? Matsuda?
Well, I am an actress.
Director Nishinaka, Light, and
the others, and now even Shinigami.
They're all asking me to act.
This is a lot of work.
I might land a commercial gig, too. I'm so popular.