Delete.
Delete!
The average Japanese adult would say that.
Teru Mikami was a child with a strong sense of justice.
He was able to distinguish right from wrong
better than any of his peers.
And compared to the average Japanese person,
Teru had been through and seen far worse miseries,
and even witnessed death.
His hat.
Get it.
In this world, there is only good and evil.
That was one of the first universal truths I grasped
from observing the world around me when I was a child.
Every human being, without exception, ends
up falling into one category or the other.
Even those in innocent years of elementary school,
one could not escape that fact.
As class president, I strived to achieve
great things for my fellow students,
but there were always enemies.
Good against evil.
No! Stop! Let go of me, please!
Evil has to be confronted.
What do you want, nerd?
There were times when it seemed
evil would triumph over good.
But no matter what happened to me,
I felt happy for one reason.
Thank you, Teru.
Hearing those words of gratitude from the victims
made me want to save them again and again.
For that reason, I never spared any effort.
And in the end,
I was able to stand up for my sense of justice.
Does this bug you?
But that was only true in the world of children.
Middle school was another matter entirely.
The more I confronted evil,
the more enemies I had to face.
Victims would become participants,
and even the people watching would be influenced by evil
and become enemies themselves.
But for justice to triumph, it requires action.
So I realized, to serve justice, I had to delete evil.
The only person who understood
my hopes and remained my ally
was the woman who raised me on her own.
My mother.
No.
Rather, it used to be my mother.
Teru, not everything in the world is
going to work the way you want it to.
You have to stop doing this.
There's no reason for you to
suffer so much for your beliefs.
What do you think you're proving getting hurt like this?
This is plain foolishness.
You have to realize that somethings never change...
My mother was wrong.
She didn't side with justice.
She was one of those who deserved to be deleted.
That was when the miracle happened.
Four of the worst delinquents from my school
lost control of their car while they were joyriding.
They died instantly.
One bystander was killed as well.
That bystander was my mother.
In one fell swoop, all the
people I resented had been deleted.
At first, I was terrified.
I couldn't stop shivering.
But then it hit me.
With these people out of the picture,
how many others would benefit as a result?
Clearly their victims were relieved.
But beyond that.
Wouldn't everyone in my class be
happier now that they were gone?
And sure enough, I was right.
Our classroom became a peaceful, joyful place.
There will always the consequences for evil deeds.
That is the way the world is.
The way it should be.
Evil must be deleted.
Now then, let's see.
Are there any more problems with these records?
No, they're fine.
With every passing year,
my commitment to justice only grew stronger.
I saw that there will always be
those who have no reason to exist.
Those whose very existence is a threat to society.
And the closer they grew to adulthood,
the less likely was that they would ever reform.
They could only be deleted.
Mysteriously, every time I judged someone as evil,
they would soon be taken care of.
Was it coincidence?
Was I special somehow?
In the end, it didn't matter.
Divine judgment must be brought up evil.
And if it isn't, then someone must
take it upon themselves to punish evil.
That's why I became a prosecutor.
It is the role of the prosecutor to
see that evil is brought to justice.
It was an ideal job for me.
And then...
God came before me.
Everything that had been happening around me
wasn't coincidence.
It was divine justice.
God had been watching me.
God had seen how I did not surrender to evil.
He reached out his hand and
punished the evil people for me.
Once I realized that, I started to frequent
places where God was bound to be watching.
And then it happened.
God recognized me as I had always hoped!
Not only that, but he found me worthy
of sharing his power to eliminate evil!
With this, it doesn't matter if I can't hear his voice.
I shall figure out what Kira wants and carry out his will.
Delete.
Mikami made the choice to kill Demegawa himself.
I never requested it.
An understandable move, but now there's no spokesperson.
Kira needs a voice.
At the moment, I can't make any moves myself.
What will he do?
Kira isn't saying anything.
He must be in a situation where he can't move freely.
But this is an important time for him.
We need a spokesperson to spread his word to the people.
Then I will take the initiative.
Extra, extra!
There's a new development in the Kira case.
He's chosen a new spokesperson to take Demegawa's place.
Take a look.
That woman.
Kiyomi Takada.
Good evening.
This is Kiyomi Takada from News 6.
Starting today, it will be my
duty to spread the word of Kira
accurately and quickly.
From now on, NHN will fairly...
So he picked NHN's star newscaster, huh?
Kira's got good taste.
Choosing Taki was a good idea.
There's no mistaking it.
That's the girl that Light dated in university.
...but also his liaison with the people of the world.
You've moved quickly, Mikami.
However, it won't take them long to find the
connection between us, which could be a problem.
No. On second thought, she's not a bad choice.
It's one I never would have
considered, since I already knew her.
But this could actually make things easier.
I can definitely use her,
but I'll have to find a way to contact her soon.
Kiyomi Takada.
I had a chance to meet her when I was
part of a debate program she was hosting.
She was a shrewd and fair host for the most part,
but her attitude changed suddenly
when Kira's name was mentioned.
She had a uniquely rigid sense of
justice that I could identify with.
She hates crimes and social evils with a passion.
I talked with her privately several times after that.
She clearly supports Kira.
But it's more than that.
She thinks like Kira.
That makes her the broadcaster most
worthy of being the new voice of Kira.
Kiyomi Takada.
It'd to be too suspicious for Kira to
choose an ex-girlfriend as his representative.
And there's been no sign of
Light sending her any messages.
Maybe I'm thinking about this too much.
Everyone, I just had an idea.
I was thinking we could make use of Kiyomi Takada.
To be honest, I know her.
Back in university, she and I were
actually dating for a little while.
Whoa.
So he admits it.
He has no intention to hide the connection.
If she's acting as his spokesperson,
she must be receiving orders from him.
She's in contact with Kira somehow.
I think our best bet is to use that
connection to find a way to Kira through her.
But Taki's probably doing it
because Kira's threatening her, right?
She might be too scared to help
us out with her investigation.
That's a good point.
I'm not too worried about that.
I know her current cell phone number. I'm pretty sure
that I'll be able to convince her once we get talking.
She'll meet with me if I ask her to.
Ha ha. Wow.
Listen to this guy.
You're the man, Light.
Talking to her will be easy, but the real challenge
will be to get her to help us find and arrest Kira.
We used to talk about a lot of different topics
while we were in college, and one thing was clear.
She worships Kira.
But we might be able to use that to our advantage.
The police claim they support Kira,
but aren't doing anything one way or the other.
So I'll reveal that I've joined the police,
and ask her what we can do to help Kira further.
To her, it'll sound like a good idea.
We can convince her to assist us as
long as we pretend it's for Kira's benefit.
Do you think that'll go over well?
I'm not entirely sure. But it's worth a try, at least.
I agree.
It'd be foolish for us to pass up a lead like this.
In that case, I'll call her tonight.
Light.
If you don't mind, I'd like to listen
in on your conversation with Ms. Takada.
Of course.
That's fine with me.
Actually, it's better if you do.
If she lets slip something about Kira, it
would be best if more than one of us was listening.
Uh, yeah.
Yes, Hello?
Kiyomi? This is Light Yagami.
Light?
Hi. It's been a while. What's going on?
Kiyomi, I have something important to tell you.
Could we meet somewhere?
I have a favor to ask you.
A favor?
Yeah.
I know my timing is pretty bad, I mean,
you're the woman the whole world is watching right now,
so it might not be possible.
Don't play innocent and humble with me, Light.
You wouldn't have called if you
didn't think it was possible to see me.
You're right.
Ever since we graduated,
I wanted to talk to you again, but I never had the chance.
And now it looks like our jobs have brought us together.
After so much time, our paths are about to cross again.
Call me crazy, but I feel like this is fate.
What do you mean, our jobs?
I'm working with the police now.
That was part of what I wanted to talk to you about.
In person.
The police aren't doing anything
to defy Kira at this point.
All right.
I may be able to help you,
depending on what you're asking for.
I appreciate it.
At the very least, I just want
you to hear what I have to say.
Anywhere.
Just us two.
Well, OK then.
After tonight's broadcast is finished.
That sounds perfect.
I'll book a hotel room for us.
A hotel room?
Are you sure?
The last I heard, you were still living with Miss Amane.
Are things not going to well on the home front?
Well, to be honest,
Misa's just not intelligent enough to be my partner.
Motchi.
Yes?
Your cooking is really good.
And I appreciate that you're doing everything for me,
but it's been five days now.
Right.
Light doesn't know about you
hanging around all the time, does he?
I'm beginning to get a really
bad feeling about this whole thing.
Uhhuh.
I mean, I know that Light trusts me totally,
but don't you think most people
would start saying I'm cheating on him?
Oh, he'd be so jealous.
Near and the others told me that this
woman is supposed to be the second Kira.
But it could really be this unbelievably stupid girl?
It seems that Kira still hasn't tried to contact me yet.
If he's in a situation where he's
unable to contact me even if he wants to,
then the next best thing would be
for him to contact Takada instead.
Good evening, this is the 9:00 news.
First, I have an announcement
that comes directly from Kira.
His words are to become the new law of the world.
Kira will never forgive those people
whose existence is a threat to justice.
But he will also not forgive those who live
wastefully, and refuse to use their abilities
to contribute to the betterment of society.
What?
So Kira's going to kill lazy people now?
You're kidding me.
You're taking this too far, Mikami.
It's too early to be making those kinds of statements.
I've got to get a hold of him soon.
Matsuda, how is it?
Good.
Audio and video online, no blind spots.
Until next time...
The 9:00 news is just saying.
Everything's in order. I'll head back to HQ.
OK.
I missed you.
Huh?
Um, I'm sorry. It's just anyway, please, sit down.
To be honest,
it doesn't seem like that long
since we last saw each other.
What the hell is Light doing?
He's not saying anything.
If he just stays silent, she'll get suspicious.
Come on.
Don't tell me you've never been in love before, Ide.
What?
How's it going?
The mood's perfect.
That's not what I meant.
Huh?
Please excuse me.
Kira.
Is it Mikami?
She just said it's Kira.
Kira's contacting her directly?
You should answer it.
Um, right.
Hello.
No, I'm with a friend right now.
Yes, we're alone.
If luck is on my side, I can get on the phone myself.
Well, Mikami, can you make it happen?
He wanted to meet me all of a sudden.
Someone who requests a private
meeting with Kira's spokesperson.
I'd like to speak with him, if I may.
He said the he wants to speak to you.
Perfect.
I was right to choose you, Mikami.
She's passed the phone to Light.
It could be dangerous if he's the real thing.
Yes? Hello?
Who am I speaking to?
Five pages on November 26th?
I don't get it. What do you mean?
You're God!
You're doing well, Mikami.
Let's just see how much you can figure out.
Got it. You're not free to speak right now.
Yes.
You're being watched at the moment.
But how can I trust you're the real Kira?
Is he asking me to judge someone right now?
Turn to Sakura TV!
What's that?
Sakura TV?
Quick. Let's check it out.
We'll invite Kira back to our program
no matter what it might take...
He died!
This is bad. He's the real thing.
Mikami. You're even better than I expected.
What? He's removing the bugs?
We don't have a choice.
I don't understand. What's going on?
Now I can talk without any constraints.
What?
Listen, Kiyomi.
I am the real Kira.
That's right. I'm Kira.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
Light is Kira?
Listen.
I won't allow you to ask Kiyomi who I am.
You don't need to know my identity.
Yes.
I'll leave the rest to you, God.
Do you understand?
I am Kira.
The man who was on the phone
is one of my followers who I've shared my power with.
I... I can't believe it's you.
You were the only man I ever really admired.
To be honest, the only man I ever felt a connection with.
And now to find you're Kira...
it's incredible.
Please, join me, Kiyomi,
and you will be the goddess of the New World.
Oh, Light.
Light, are you OK?
Yeah.
Kiyomi was able to work things out with Kira.
I've decided that from now on,
I'm going to pretend to be dating her.
We might be able to find Kira that way.
Delete.
Delete!
Come to think of it,
it's always been a one on one battle between myself and L.
It's been going on since the beginning.
Alright, Near.
Fine.
I'll come out if you come out.
I'll accept your challenge.