The current Kira is foolish and overconfident,
not to mention unusually cooperative with the task force.
In fact, I suspect he's working hand in hand with them.
You think so?
That would make the second L and Kira...
one in the same person.
To the members of the Japanese task force,
was there ever a point in the investigation
where the Second L was suspected to be Kira,
even if the suspicions were later dropped?
Near. I have to kill him.
This is really bad.
Turn on the TV. It's Demegawa!
This is Demegawa live!
My comrades and I have finally pinpointed
the hideout of the evil organization
bent on trying to catch our beloved god Kira.
We now have the building completely surrounded!
Hello, Kira supporters.
I urge you, do not rush the building all at once.
The traitors may attempt to
blend in with the crowd to escape.
I am Kira's loyal servant and spokesman.
You must listen to me!
Find them, pull them from the building,
and bring them in front of the cameras.
They'll be a sacrifice for Kira!
You can't hide from me. I'll find you.
Near. You've got no choice. You'd better evacuate.
You've got some nerve to say that, being Kira.
What? Are you still going on about that nonsense?
Think about it.
With all the anti-Kira groups around,
why is it we're being targeted, and
right after I start suspecting you?
Pretty convenient, if you ask me.
Near, with all due respect, you're wrong.
You're jumping to conclusions.
Members of the task force, please listen to me.
Kira is likely amongst you.
Even as we speak, he is in that room.
I'm simply asking you to think about this carefully.
Light is Kira.
This is all sounding way too familiar.
The original L also thought that Light had to be Kira.
The first wave of 20 people
will break the door and get inside.
Second wave, stand by!
Wait!
We're the first wave!
What? Like hell. We're going first!
Near, we have to evacuate immediately.
Really, what pathetic people.
I'm not surprised that there are ordinary
people who support what Kira's trying to do.
I'm talking about honest citizens who believe
in their hearts that, by punishing evildoers,
Kira will actually make this world a better place to live.
But, as for this crowd outside,
they're a completely different breed.
They are truly despicable and stupid.
This is just a diversion for them.
They're all selfish.
I... I know that, but it still
leaves us with the immediate problem.
We'll use L's legacy and the
anti-Kira protesters we hired.
Yes, but we only have one shot with that plan.
I'm aware of that, but I can't
imagine a better time to do it.
Besides, it should be interesting.
What?
It's... It's money!
Money?
There's so much!
What?
That's a lot.
Amazing!
Man, I wish I were over there right now.
Matsuda.
Heh.
Humans are so interesting.
Of course, you can use money to get
apples, so I can kind of understand.
I got these first, you bastard!
Out of the way!
Dammit!
He's planning to use all this
chaos to escape into the crowd.
Even so, he can't escape from Demegawa's cameras.
Over there, pilot!
Go to the floor where all the money's coming from!
Geez! What are you doing, Demegawa?
Don't you know that you can't
buy love and peace with money?
A literal downpour of money is
causing mayhem in lower Manhattan.
The police have arrived.
Police?
They're a welcome sight in the midst of
what can only be called a full scale riot.
This is bad.
At this rate...
Let's go.
This is our window of opportunity.
We can leave via the front exit.
It makes sense that the police would
have to mobilize for a riot like this.
Damn! Near was prepared for this situation.
He's planning to come out along with the rest of them,
and if I tell Aizawa and the
others to keep an eye on the police,
it will only make me look that much more suspicious.
The police are coming out of the building.
They've secured the area.
Where is he?
He's got to be in there somewhere!
Where?
Dammit.
How much money do you think was there?
Bet it was a lot.
Matsuda! Knock it off.
It bet it was around $10 million or something.
Ooh. What's that in apples?
Near.
Already?
This is Near.
We've re-established a secure connection,
so I thought I should give you a call to let you know.
You're safe. That's a relief.
To all of you on the task force,
I'm sure that by now some of you are
starting to suspect that Kira may be one of you.
Given the timing of today's attack on our headquarters,
I don't think anyone could blame you for having doubts.
If you don't suspect the second L of being Kira by now,
you're in the wrong line of work.
The number I gave you the day before has been reconnected.
Please feel free to call any time you like.
Well then, I'll be waiting for your call.
Those were some strong words.
This guy's pretty sure of himself.
I've been thinking,
and if any of you want to cooperate with Near,
please go ahead.
I'm not particularly satisfied
with the way things are going either.
Ideally, we should cooperate with the SPK.
Maybe this will clear the air a little.
Still, it kinda feels like Near's against us, doesn't it?
When I think about Deputy Director Yagami
I don't want to suspect Light even a little bit, but...
Dad?
Welcome back.
I didn't know you were gonna be home tonight.
Oh, yeah. What are you still doing awake?
I've a couple of exams coming up.
I see.
Well, don't push yourself too hard, OK?
Kay. You too, dad.
I wouldn't be surprised if one
of the others contacted Near.
It's inevitable.
The problem is what comes after that.
If I'm too late to act,
something might happen that I won't be able to take back.
I've got no choice but to do it.
Oh! An emergency order from Light! Yay!
Hm. File number three.
Huh?
No way.
Yes? This is Near.
I'm with the Japanese task force.
My name is Aizawa.
So, the time has finally come.
If I do this my safety is guaranteed,
and I can finally just to be a normal wife.
This is what Light wants for me.
He wants me to be happy, just as a woman should be.
Thank you, Light.
I see. That's very interesting.
You're saying there were two
suspects in the Kira investigation
that the previous L detained for more than 50 days,
and they were cleared based on the 13 day rule. Correct?
Yes. But of course, that alone
doesn't come prove they were Kira.
And L was willing to release them because of that?
No.
L had Deputy Director Yagami, the chief
detective at the time, put on an act.
He was instructed to tell the suspects that they had
both been found guilty of being Kira and the second Kira,
and that they were going to be executed.
Then on the way, the deputy director
pulled over and pointed a gun at the suspects.
He said that he would first kill Kira, then himself.
The idea was that if he were Kira, the suspect
would have killed the chief right then and there.
Kira is quite impressive.
He must have used his detainment
to demonstrate his innocence.
Well done.
Out of curiosity, did the suspect volunteer
to be detained as part of the investigation?
Hm.
Come to think of it, Light did volunteer to be imprisoned.
If he did, then I'd say that settles the matter.
Wouldn't you?
So, who was it?
Who were those two suspects?
I can't tell you that much.
I'm willing to cooperate, but I'm still a
member of the Japanese task force working under L.
I understand.
Thank you very much.
You information's been quite valuable,
especially the part about Shinigami's eyes
that enable you to see other peoples' names.
It was very helpful.
Goodbye.
Hm.
Will that be enough, Near?
Shouldn't you have pressed for a little more information?
I think that all things considered,
his level of cooperation is fine for now.
And besides, I discovered something very important.
The person suspected of being
Kira is Deputy Director Yagami's son.
It's the only possible explanation.
Why else would the deputy director
say he would kill Kira, and then himself?
Therefore, tha tmeans the second L,
and the person I think is Kira, can only be one man.
Light Yagami.
Light.
Yes?
There's something you should know.
I phoned Near and talked to him.
Don't worry about it.
After all, I was the one who recommended it.
So, what did the two of you end up discussing?
No, on second thought, I probably shouldn't ask.
I guess it's not appropriate for me to ask
those kinds of questions if I'm a suspect.
Hm.
Don't get me wrong.
I want to believe that you aren't Kira,
but I've got to be certain.
I'm sorry to have to do this again,
but I want to put you under
surveillance until we catch Kira.
I'm afraid that goes for Misa Amane as well.
I'm going to search your place right now.
There's a possibility that Amane might have a notebook.
Hang on a second, Aizawa!
No.
Go right ahead. Look at this way.
At least you can prove to everyone
that I'm not sneaking around and
contacting Misa in private, right?
Huh?
Mogi?
I'm coming with you.
I want to make sure, too.
It would be best for everyone if Light wasn't Kira.
But if Amane has any evidence on her
that connects her with Kira, then...
Huh?
Motchi, Monchichi, long time no see, you two!
Light hasn't been home at all
lately, so I've been super bored.
Uh...
Well, there's no way she's got the
notebook hidden under a dress like that.
We were just investigating a tip that
there were explosives planted in L's house.
We think it's a prank, but we'd
like to check the rooms, just in case.
What? How about Light? Is he OK?
I have to call him.
No. You can't call him right now.
How come?
Don't worry.
Light's safe, but he's really busy right now.
He has some other things he has to do,
so he's handed the investigation
over to us for the time being.
Oh, I get it.
Light loves me like crazy,
so he doesn't want me to call him,
'cause that'll only make him worry about me.
Search as much as you like, Aizawa.
You won't find the notebook.
I wouldn't like all the suspicion
to ruin the atmosphere around here.
This isn't a social club.
I think Aizawa and Mogi should do as they see fit.
It's time for Kira's Kingdom.
Greetings to all my fellow Kira worshippers.
I am Demegawa, the voice of our god, Kira.
Behold!
This is the new Kira's Kingdom,
which shares its name with this program.
Its construction is going smoothly,
but will depend on the generous
support of our loyal viewers.
Once it has been completed, let us welcome our god here!
Whoa. Talk about bad taste.
Hey, so is everything OK?
Oh, yeah. Seems like it was just a prank.
Oh.
But just in case, one of us is going to stay
and keep watch over you for the next few days.
Really? Oh, that would be great.
Mogi, why don't you go back to headquarters?
I'll say on guard here.
Huh? I'm with Monchichi instead of Motchi?
What's wrong? Don't you trust me?
No. You're just not Monchichi without your old haircut.
You're not cute anymore.
Mogi!
Yes, sir. My apologies.
All right. You stay.
We are now accepting donations,
starting at the million yen mark
towards the completion of Kira's Kingdom.
So, if you truly...
This sounds like a con.
Yep. Just another scam at this point.
It doesn't even seem like Kira's style.
Demegawa.
He's just acting on his own now.
If he keeps doing this, he'll end
up pushing people away from Kira.
I don't need him anymore.
But I can't do much at the moment.
Hey. Welcome back, Aizawa.
We didn't find a notebook in Light's or Misa's room.
But still...
I understand.
You're more than welcome to keep watch
over Misa and I until you're satisfied.
Next on the program, it's time for me to introduce
the new leaders I have chosen for Kira's Kingdom.
The first gentleman is...
Delete.
We will unite with Kira, and work with him.
Delete!
Save me.
And delete.
Wha... What the hell is this?
Why would Kira kill his own supporters?
Do you think it's because
they're going overboard with this?
That might be a possibility.
But this is horrible.
What's going on?
There was no chance for either Misa Amane
or Light to use the notebook to kill Demegawa.
Mikami.
I can definitely use him.
It seems I was right to choose him for this.
He understands Kira's beliefs and ideals perfectly,
and he knows what Kira wants and doesn't want.
Thanks to that, he takes action without needing my orders.
I had Misa relinquish ownership of the Death Note.
Before she lost all her memories of
the notebook, she sent it to someone else,
along with some special instructions.
Now she won't be able to answer any questions about it.
She's just an ordinary woman.
The main problem was selecting the next owner.
I saw him trying to speak to Kira
through the television broadcasts.
It was clear he worshiped Kira
from the bottom of this heart.
He would understand that he was chosen
simply by receiving and accepting the notebook.
There was no mistake in my selection.
Teru Mikami.
He's more than worthy of becoming the hand of Kira.
Shinigami.
Thank you for coming to me.
Now I'll be able to punish evildoers with death.
God.
You're a woman who the entire world pays attention to.
It must be fate for us to cross paths again like this.
Please, just listen to what I
have to say first, all right?
Let's meet somewhere.
Alone.