Huh?
What is this?
Everyone, the Shiniga...
Now, try to kill me.
Although this was announced as a worldwide broadcast,
the truth is we are only broadcasting
in the Kanto region of Japan.
In actuality, the fist of your
victims was a suspect in Shinjuku.
Furthermore, his crime was
only ever reported inside Japan.
I used that information to deduce this much.
You are in Japan, and your first
victim was little more than an experiment,
which means that you haven't been killing for very long.
Kira has found a way to obtain
information from the Task Force Headquarters.
There are 141 people in the police force
who have acces to classified
information regarding the investigation.
I am sure that somewhere in this list of police officers,
and the people closest to them,
we will find our suspect.
On December 14th, 12 FBI investigators entered Japan.
Here are are on December 19th.
Using prison inmates, Kira conducts experiments
manipulating his victim's actions before they die.
He needed to know how much control he had over his
victims before he could use it against the 12 agents.
I suspect Kira had to be one
of the people being investigated
by the FBI between the 14th and the 19th of December.
In fact, I have no doubt.
Raye Penber's fiance?
Naomi Misora.
So it's her.
She was working under me.
I guess she must have come to Japan with her fiance.
I heard she was seen with Penber.
It's possible that she may have found a lead.
If that's the case, did Kira manage to get to her first?
Everyone, at this point I'd
like to focus our investigation
on only those people who Raye Penber was tailing.
There are two groups.
Deputy Director Kitamura,
as well as Detective Superintendent
Yagami and their families.
At this stage I'd like to place wiretaps
and surveillance cameras in both households.
That's my son you're talking about.
Are you honestly telling me that you suspect him?
I do suspect him.
I want to you, I'm L.
Relax, Light.
While it's try that Kira hates losing,
it's also true that most people
would rather win than lose.
It's human nature.
Look at that.
He's going for the win.
I suspect that you, Light Yagami, are in fact Kira.
You think I'm Kira?
Ryuga, what would it take to get
you to believe that I'm not Kira?
Please, isn't there something?
If you are not Kira, that truth will be revealed.
Just let things run their course.
Four days ago...
Our audience rating should go up 60%
no, more like 70% percent after this.
...contained a prediction of two
deaths, proving that he is Kira.
We understand that the second tape
contains a message to all people of the world.
I am Kira.
The news anchor, Mr. Kazuhiko Hibima,
will die of a heart attack at exactly 6:00.
Stop this broadcast!
We can't let him finish!
You idiots!
You told us that Kira couldn't kill without a name!
But from what we've just seen,
I'd say it's not entirely impossible
that Kira can kill with only a face.
This is the police.
Stop this broadcast now!
There's a strong possibility that this Kira's a fake.
No, we should think of him more as a second Kira.
Mr. Yagami, I'd like your permission to ask
your son to cooperate with us on this investigation.
At the very least, I'd say this
isn't the Kira we're familiar with.
That's almost exactly how L, I mean, Ryuzaki said it.
When we meet, we can confirm our identities
by showing our Shinigami to each other.
If there's a message here written in some code
that only people who have this
Shinigami power can understand,
there'd no way for me to decipher it.
Still, it would only make sense
for us to look into all of the places
that were mentioned in the journal.
When you two are working together,
I want you to keep a close eye on Light the entire time.
It's only a slim chance, but if Light is Kira,
then there's still a possibility that the
second Kira may try to contact him somehow.
Also, Mr Yagami, please ask
Mr. Mogi to start following Light,
so he can keep tabs on what he's doing.
Light, there you are.
Hi there. I'm Light's girlfriend, Misa Amane.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hideki Ryuga.
Huh? Hideki Ryuga?
I'm not exactly sure how you'll take this,
but regarding Misa Amane,
there's something you should know.
We've taken her into custody under
suspicion of her being the second Kira.
We gathered physical evidence from
the envelope sent by the second Kira,
and particular hairs and fibers caught
in the masking tape used to seal them.
They matched what we found in Misa's room.
Ryuzaki, what's the meaning of this?
Now hurry up and kill me!
If you wanted to, you could
kill me right now, couldn't you?
Does this mean you admit to being the second Kira?
Is this the reason you wish to die?
No.
I don't know anything about the second Kira.
Ryuzaki, like I said over the phone, I could be Kira.
Why come here to announce that you could be Kira?
It's an act.
There's no could be about it.
You are Kira.
Light, are you feeling OK?
Yeah.
I know I must look pretty bad in here, but
this useless pride I suppose I'll have to...
get rid of it.
Ryuzaki, I realize that I was
the one pushing for confinement,
and that I asked you put me in here,
but this whole thing's completely pointless.
I'm not Kira. You have to get me out of here!
I just heard.
Two weeks' worth of criminals
were just murdered all at once.
It happened yesterday.
I don't understand what's going on here.
I'm not sure how much more of
this the three of them can take.
Ryuzaki, you have no reason
to keep Light locked up anymore.
It's already been 50 days.
I'm going to kill you here, and then kill myself.
What?
What are you talking about, Dad?
You can't, that's crazy!
How can you even say that?
It's too late.
Please, don't, Dad! I'm not Kira!
Light, my son... from one murderer to another...
No, Dad!
I'll see you in hell.
No! Stop it!
It was a convincing performance.
As we discussed, I will end their confinement immediately.
As for your part in this agreement, Light,
you and I will be together 24/7,
and that's how it will remain
until we've brought Kira to justice.
Their deaths have all worked in Yotsuba's favor.
Looking back, there have been 13
similar deaths in the past three months.
Is Kira someone from Yotsuba?
Or is Kira simply using Yotsuba?
I haven't figured that out yet,
but we'll proceed under the
assumption that this is Kira's doing.
We will focus on Yotsuba.
Please be sure not to act
impulsively, out of panic or haste.
And don't take matters into your own hands.
I'm an agent with Yoshida Productions.
Would you be interested in using
Misa Amane as your new spokesperson?
Ryuzaki, are you watching this?
The eight men who came here were having a
meeting to decide who they get Kira to kill for them.
If Matsuda dies, our suspicions about
the Yotsuba Group would be confirmed.
Do you think there's anything I can do to save myself?
Matsuda, you idiot.
Good luck, Misa Misa!
I'll be here ready to celebrate
when they decide to hire you!
It's always been my dream to become Kira's wife.
I know he'll need me by his side.
And you know why?
Because I'm the second Kira.
Well, since I happen to be Kira,
does that mean you'll marry me, Misa?
So, based on what he said, Higuchi is Kira.
So, what are you gonna do?
I'm going to trick Higuchi using Sakura TV.
Like a hidden camera show!
Higuchi, we've got a problem.
Turn on the television.
Huh?
So you're saying one of those people is Kira, right?
Yes. I've got a lot of evidence to prove it, too.
It's... it's him!
Why is he still alive?
I see Higuchi. I'm in pursuit.
We're heading after him.
You in the red car!
Pull over to the side of the road. Now!
Rem. Let's make the deal.
A deal?
You were speeding. License, please?
Yeah. No problem.
Hey!
Higuchi ditched the cop. He's driving away.
This is Traffic Control...
Everyone!
It's too dangerous to allow further action by Higuchi.
Let's bring him in.
I believe he has the same powers as the second Kira.
He is able to kill just by looking at someone's face.
Please keep this in mind when you move in to arrest him.
Stop right there.
Stay back!
Stay back or I'll shoot, I swear!
Ah!
Higuchi, how were you able to kill people?
You probably won't believe me,
but I've got a special notebook.
If I write someone's name in it while
thinking of their face, that person dies.
It was in one of the compartments of Higuchi's bag.
What is it, Mr. Yagami?
It's a monster!
A Shinigami.
There have to be two notebooks.
Possibly more.
This isn't over yet.
How to use it.
It says the human whose name is written in this notebook
shall die.
And then there's this last rule.
According to this, if the person using the note
fails to consecutively write names of people to be killed
within 13 day Of each other, then the user will die.
Light Yagami and Misa Amane are both still alive.
13 days.
That's the only problem.
The following is the record which contains everything
I have investigated on the Kira incident.
That fact that now you are reading this
message means I am no longer alive at this moment.
I hereby leave this record as my firm achievement.
That is all.
It's been 10 days since Ryuzaki's funeral.
Look like we're not gonna die after all.
We know Watari's true identity now,
but we never found out anything
about who Ryuzaki really was.
Yeah, that's true.
Who could have guessed that Watari
was actually a famous inventor?
The paper says he founded orphanages around the
world using the fortune he inherited from his patents.
He was a fine man.
A hero.
But it doesn't help us now.
We can't continue investigating using
this place as our base with L and Watari gone.
This is tough.
Light, how's it going?
I should be able to transfer the system and
most of the information out of here by tonight.
It's weird, though.
I almost feel as if I'm stealing.
I've created a voice filter identical
to the one reason Ryuzaki used.
We can use it to make the police think he's still
alive, and give them orders like we've been doing so far.
But who is going to take the place of L?
Where will he work from,
and what will we do with the notebook?
Come on. What are you talking about, Light?
You're the only one who can take on the role of L.
Huh?
I don't know.
Ryuzaki was killed by Kira because he challenged him.
That's not something I'm eager to do.
Besides, I would be fooling the people of the world.
I can understand how you feel, but you're
really the only one of us who can do this.
That's right.
Even Ryuzaki said so himself.
You would be capable of succeeding L.
Just as I thought.
It's too simple.
It's no fun without Ryuzaki here.
I understand.
All right, I'll do it.
But I won't be like Ryuzaki.
I won't take big risks like
challenging Kira directly to gather clues.
it's just not me.
Yeah. It's probably better if we play it safe.
Ryuzaki may have been a little too confrontational.
In that case, I'll be able to do the same
sort of work using both this computer and my own.
In fact, it'll be possible for me to
act as L in the comfort of my own room.
I can be Watari, as well.
But it'll be difficult to pull
off with Mom and Sayu around.
Things would be easier if I
could rent a one bedroom apartment.
Well, considering your age,
it certainly wouldn't look odd to
anyone if I let you move out on your own.
Hey, yeah.
And then we'll be able to use Light's new
apartment as our Task Force Headquarters.
That's a great idea.
All that's left to figure out
now is what to do with the notebook.
It's really not that difficult.
There's five of us here.
And we know none of us will ever use the notebook.
We'll just have one of us take it and hide it
somewhere where no one else could ever get to it.
Please, Chief. It's got to be you.
Uh, yeah, Chief. We can count on you.
You're a pillar of justice, after all.
You want me to... all right.
We'll avenge Ryuzaki together.
Yeah. Kira is still out there somewhere.
We'll catch him. That's a promise.
Well then, why don't we have a little
party to celebrate Light becoming L number two?
Quit fooling around.
Now's not the time for stuff like that.
Let's take it easy.
Light.
This is our first date in forever.
Can't you enjoy yourself a little more?
Misa, let's move in together.
Do you mean it?
Yeah. I've already rented a place.
Yay! Victory is mine!
Misa wins!
Victory?
Over Kiyomi, and Mari, and Yuri.
But it's all right now. Don't worry.
I knew you were just using those other girls to trick L.
You don't have any reason to see them anymore, right?
Right.
Hey.
Now that L's dead, does that mean
you've finally settled the score with him?
Yeah.
So in that case, I guess things are
gonna get pretty boring from now on.
That's not true, Ryuk.
Huh?
From this moment on,
I'll show you the creation of the new world.
Ah!
Daddy!
Daddy?
Hm?
This will be the rebirth of Yotsuba.
Yeah. It's a new start.
Huh?
Hey, Namikawa! What's wrong?
That's impossible.
In April 2012, Light Yagami, age 23,
joined Japan's National Police Agency.
In the summer of 2012,
Kira's killings increased at an unprecedented rate.
Numerous people around the world were terrified of Kira,
and yet, there were just as many cheering him on.
Gradually their private thoughts became public opinion,
and soon, certain nations
began to accept Kira's judgement.
The world was heading into a dark age
in which Kira's will was the only law.
What is it, Roger?
It's L. He's dead.
L's death?
Where'd they hear it from?
Who told them?
Who is this guy?
Is he joking?
What's with this strange feeling?