What was that?
Roger?
What did you just say?
I'm afraid L is dead.
He's dead?
But... But how?
Was it Kira? Did Kira kill him?
Come on, Roger. You've got to tell me!
Probably.
But he promised me he'd find Kira and execute
him, and now you're telling me that he's been killed.
Mello!
If you can't win the game, if you can't solve the puzzle,
then you're just a loser.
So, which of us did L pick? Me or Near?
He hadn't chosen yet.
And now that he's gone, I'm afraid he won't be able to.
Mello.
Listen.
You two Near.
Can't the two of you work together?
All right.
Sounds good.
It'll never work, Roger.
We can't do this together.
You know I don't get along with the Near.
We've always competed against each other.
Always.
You know what?
It's fine.
Near should be the one to succeed L.
He's not like me. He never gets emotional.
He just uses his head, like it's a game or a puzzle.
And as for me, I'm leaving this institution.
Wait, Mello!
Don't waste your breath.
I'm almost 15 years old.
It's time I started living my own life.
A police officer who happened to
be nearby during Higuchi's arrest
overhead him talking about a notebook.
If you write a person's name in it with
their face in mind, that person will die.
So that's what you're saying
this notebook of death actually is.
That's right.
At this point, the Japanese police
should have it in their possession.
Mr. President, the current L is a fake.
He was created by the Japanese police
to avoid confusion and panic amongst
the various international police agencies.
The reak L is dead.
Uh, Director Mason.
This boy, who is he?
Sir.
Near is Well, in a sense you could
call him the true successor to L.
But still, it's impossible for us
to censor everything on the internet.
And we haven't had any new leads in a while.
But posting names and faces online?
I'm sorry, but if you ask me, it's
the people doing that who deserve to die.
But I guess that's never gonna happen.
Kira gets a lot of his information from the internet,
so he's not gonna kill those people.
Matsu, you silly. You've got it all backwards.
Still.
I can imagine how some people must feel.
To them, the world's become a good place
for people who don't commit any crimes,
or rather, it's a good place for
innocent people who lead good lives.
Look who's talking.
It's more than that.
Soon, everyone in the world will think that way.
Are you all still talking about that Kira business?
Please, give it a rest for one afternoon, dear.
Light, you too.
I'm home.
Hey, how's it going?
We were just having tea.
Oh Light, Misa.
Seems like it's been forever, you two.
Missed you guys.
Aw, we missed you too!
And you must be Mr. Matsuda, right?
That's me.
Wow, it's been a long time.
Thank you for always taking such good care of my father.
Gee, Sayu.
You're all grown up.
And pretty.
Last time I saw you, you were this big.
Matsu! Your face is going bright red!
It is?
I mean, no way!
Well, you can forget it.
I'll never let Sayu marry a cop.
Huh?
Yes. That's right.
I'd never want that for my daughter.
Really?
Aw man.
I never got the chance to
propose or even tell her I like her.
You're too cruel to me, mom and dad.
Mom?
Anyway.
I think you'd be a good catch, Mr. Matsuda.
What?
You... You really think so, Sayu?
Yep!
In fact, I was thinking if you were a little younger,
I might've considered going out with you some time.
Guess my little sister's all grown up, isn't she?
No kidding.
She's already way more mature than Matsu.
But of course, Light hasn't changed one bit.
You're just as wonderful and
handsome as when I first met you!
You've already got a career and everything.
Make it official.
You should stop living together
secretly and just get married already.
I think that's a great idea.
A heart-warming scene from the
most unfortunate family in the world.
Hm?
Yes? What is it, Aizawa?
Yes.
Right.
OK.
We have to go.
Matsuda, Light. Come with me.
A kidnapping?
Involving who?
They got Director Takimura of the NPA.
I'm not sure who's behind it.
Ah, damn it.
As if we don't have enough on our
plate already with the Kira case.
Are you sure about this?
Unfortunately, yeah.
We got the call at 6:12.
That was about 45 minutes ago.
In the meantime, we were able to confirm that
the call originated from the director's cell phone.
Did the kidnappers make any demands in terms of ransom?
They did.
They want a trade.
The director for the notebook.
Who's behind this?
And for what reason?
Do you think it's Kira?
Maybe not.
If the existence of the notebook has been
leaked, there could be any number of people
who'd want it for themselves.
But hang on.
Dad, did you say anything to
the director about the notebook?
We all agreed to keep the
information between the six of us.
So, he didn't know it, did he?
I never told the director, so he
couldn't tell the kidnappers anything.
Someone knows about the Death Note.
And beyond that, they know
that the Japanese police have it.
And now they've come to claim it for themselves.
Notify every bureau in the police
department, but only about the kidnapping itself.
Got it.
Has there been a call from the suspects?
No.
There's a visitor here who wants
to meet with Director Takimura.
What?
My name is John McEnroe.
I'm an agent with the FBI.
Of course, this is just an alias.
As my assignment involves Kira,
it's a necessary precaution.
Kira?
Due to unforseen circumstances,
the director is unavailable.
If it's acceptable, you could speak with me instead.
Very well. That's fine.
Pardon me, I'll get straight to the point.
The Japanese police have proven
themselves to be unreliable.
So in order to solve the Kira case,
we want you to hand over the notebook to us.
So the FBI was behind it!
Where did you take the director?
What are you talking about?
Don't act like you don't know.
This is a serious criminal offense.
What would the FBI gain by capturing
the director of the Japanese NPA?
Then how do you know about the notebook?
What the hell is going on?
By the sound of things, it seems that the director of
the Japanese police force has been kidnapped by someone.
Specifically, someone who wants the notebook.
All right, Commander Rester.
Pass on this message through our agent.
Suggest to the Japanese police that would
like to assist them in rescuing the director,
and apprehending the culprits.
We'll take the notebook once we have the opportunity.
Roger that.
Attention.
This is headquarters.
We have new orders for you.
Has he decided to say anything yet?
He told us the Japanese police
have begun to wimp out on Kira.
Looks like right now, the only ones who are
officially working for L are Suichiro Yagami,
Konzo Mogi, and Tota Matsuda.
Isn't that right?
Yeah.
There was also Kida, but he was killed by Kira.
Right.
And as top cop, somehow you didn't know that
this notebook even existed, or that you had it.
Japanese cops must be a joke.
Of all the investigators on the task force,
Deputy Director Yagami would
be the highest ranking, right?
Yeah.
My theory is that there are two notebooks out there.
One of them is in Kira's possession,
the other is with the NPA.
We're going to take both of them.
Huh?
Don't worry.
As long as we do what Mello says, there'll be no mistakes.
It's been a year and a half since
he joined us, and in that entire time,
he's never been wrong about everything.
Yeah, but that's what's so weird.
If he was able to bring us the head of a
mafia boss that even Kira himself couldn't kill,
why the hell would he even
need the notebook to begin with?
It's not just the nobebook I'm after.
I want to eliminate my competition.
I will be the best.
I don't care what it takes.
I'll beat Near by any means necessary.
Boss!
Shut up.
Can't you see that I'm busy?
I'm sorry.
But Eddie and I were talking for a minute, and it
looks like Takimura hung himself with his tie somehow.
What's wrong with you?
Just great.
What are we supposed to do with a dead hostage?
No. This will be just fine.
Huh?
If Kira is responsible for this,
we know he can't touch us since
he doesn't know our names or faces.
That's why he went after Takimura instead.
That means Kira is someone who knows about the kidnapping.
That should make things rather interesting.
So what are we gonna do, Mello?
I'll tell you what we're going to do.
We're going to kidnap Soichiro
Yagami's daughter, Sayu Yagami.
We still haven't been able to find any leads
on either Director Takimura or the kidnappers.
Things are getting pretty weird.
I mean, they should have contacted us by
now with further demands, but still nothing.
We know one thing.
I found out the real name of the FBI agent, John McEnroe.
According to his personnel file,
he's actually called Larry Connors.
Well, that's good to know.
He's also a genuine agent.
His background and credentials check out.
On top of that, the director of the FBI has
offered to help us rescue Director Takimura.
I'm pretty sure we'll be able to trust them.
But the director should already be dead by now.
Why haven't the kidnappers said anything?
Are they gonna give up on the deal
just because they lost their bargaining chip?
I didn't think our opponents would be such pushovers.
Remember, Dad, and the rest of you, too.
We're going to have to be extremely careful.
The director might not have known about the notebook,
but he does know who was originally working with L.
It's possible the kidnappers might come after us.
Hey, Light?
Huh?
I'll be a good girl and go to bed by myself, OK?
Uh...
Yeah. Goodnight.
Goodnight, everyone.
Guess I'll hang out around here.
It just occurred to me, we're
not the only ones in danger here.
Our families are at risk.
A call from the Director's cellphone.
It must be the kidnappers.
Quick, Aizawa.
Got it. Tracing.
This is Yagami.
Look.
About trading the director in exchange for the notebook?
The deal's been canceled.
Takimura is dead.
You bastards!
What did you do?
It's only canceled, though, regarding the director.
The new deal is this.
The notebook for Sayu Yagami.
Huh?
Seeing as you're the Deputy
Director of the Japanese police,
it would be stupid to ask you not to call the cops.
But you had better handle this
on your own, without backup.
If I see the police making any big
movements in the next little while,
I'll kill your daughter! That's right.
Just as easily as we killed the director.
I'll send you a photo of Takimura's
corpse, to prove I mean business.
Take a good look.
I'll contact you tomorrow.
Huh? Wait!
Damn, they got me.
They used the director's death
as an opportunity to get to Sayu.
Looks like things are getting interesting again.
Sir, I...
I... can't believe they'd go this far.
Damn them.
Yes, yes. Coming.
Darling?
You usually never call from your
work phone. Is something the matter?
Huh? Sayu?
I don't know.
Now that you mention it, she is late coming home.
Sayu.
Dad, are you OK?
I've just realized something.
I think it was Kira who killed the director.
Not the kidnappers.
Huh?
He probably did it because he doesn't want
the notebook to fall into the wrong hands.
Kira claims to be justice.
He wouldn't want the notebook used by someone evil.
If he killed the director, then it's reasonable
to assume he has ways of obtaining information
from within the police force.
That means we should be the ones who investigate this.
We leave the police out of it.
Otherwise...
Kira will find out about it,
and probably kill the hostage.
Right. And we can't take that chance.
Near.
We've just received a report that the director
of the Japanese Police Agency has been killed.
I see. By whom?
By whom?
Uh, the kidnappers, of course. Who else?
It'd be interesting if it turned out to be Kira.
Hm?
That's a very good point.
The police won't be trading their notebook if
the hostage is dead, so it protect Kira's interests.
And if it is in fact Kira, that can
narrow down our list of suspects significantly.
Hm?
By the way, Commander Rester,
have you been able to determine his whereabouts yet?
Not yet.
We were able to confirm that he
left the institution four years ago,
but nothing beyond that.
Very well, that clinches it.
What?
Mello, you never change.
You always overlook the most important things
because you let your emotions get the better of you.
Or perhaps you're not even involved in this case.
How could you leave your photo behind at the orphanage?
This is Yagami.
Your daughter has finally arrived.
It's about time.
What do you mean?
You already have a pretty good
idea of where we are, don't you?
Hm.
We'll make the exchange here.
Come to LA, by yourself, in two days.
And of course, bring the notebook with you.
I won't make the trade unless I'm sure my daughter's safe.
I want to talk to her right now.
How about this?
I'll send you another photo.
That should satisfy you.
Sayu.
Hey Chief, we've narrowed the
call down to 5th Street in LA.
I just checked out the show
that was playing in the background,
and it's being broadcast right now on a local LA station.
They must have shown us that
so we know the photo's recent.
Thank goodness.
At least we know she's still alive.
That's reassuring.
I'm taking the notebook to Los Angeles.
It's my decision, both as Deputy Director of the
Japanese Police Force, and as Sayu Yagami's father.
I'll take full responsibility for the consequences.
That's my final word.
Wait, Dad.
Before we do anything, we have to come up with a plan.
He's right, Chief. We can't rush in.
But I have to be in LA in two days.
We don't have time.
So what you're telling me is that
Kira killed Takimura, not the kidnappers?
I'm simply putting it forward as a possibility.
If it does turn out to be true, then it means Kira
must be getting his information from the Japanese police.
Hm.
Hm?
Yes?
This is L.
Hm?
I don't believe it.
It's L.
I've already heard what investigator John McEnroe,
or rather, Larry Connors has had to say to Deputy Director.
Yagami in regards to the notebook and the Kira case.
Will you help us with the investigation
into NPA Director Takimura's murder?
I see. Well...
Pass me the phone.
Huh?
I'm pleased to meet you at last, L number two.
Number two?
What do you mean by that?
Who is this?
There's really no point in trying to hide it.
We are a new organization known as
the SPK, or Special Provision for Kira.
It was established to find and
capture Kira without the help of L.
Furthermore, seven of our top
members already know of L's death.
They do?
Where'd they hear that? Who the hell told them?
As for myself, I am at the center of the SPK.
You can address me as N.
N?
Who is this guy? Is he joking?
But, this strange feeling.
What is it?
Damn. What's going on?
I've already checked today's flight crews.
No one on board was suspicious.
I can still make it.
But at this rate, is my only option to kill Sayu?