Near, it's all taken care of.
I did exactly as you asked.
Good.
T, that is all I have to tell you today.
We'll talk soon.
Very well, I understand.
I also have a message for you.
Yes? What is it?
I've confirmed it.
Hm? You got a text?
Oh, it says she wants to see you.
Man, I'm so jealous. Huh?
I've done it.
That's the sign of confirmation from Mikami.
Now all I have to do is wait for
Near to request a meeting face to face.
Game over, Near. I win.
I knew what your move would be from the very beginning.
Sir, this is Giovanni.
I've been checking the Notebook regularly as you ordered.
For the past three days, he's continued filling out
one page every night, after midnight, as he usually does.
The victims still match up, and there's
been no change in Mikami's behavior otherwise.
I understand.
Well, then let's begin.
Oh! It's Near.
He called.
L?
Yes, this is L. What is it, Near?
I want to meet you.
What?
There's something I must show
you pertaining to the Kira case.
But don't you suspect me of being Kira?
Do you really think it's wise to reveal your face to me?
That's true.
I cannot show you unless I reveal my face.
Furthermore, the very act of
showing my face will prove something.
And that will bring this case to a close.
All right, fine.
As far as I'm concerned, the sooner you
realize you're wrong about me, the better.
The time has finally come for
Near to prove that Light is Kira.
But on the other hand, if that's true,
this will be a chance for Light to kill Near.
It all comes down to this.
I'd like to lay out some ground rules for the meeting.
We're willing to go along with whatever you want.
First, I want to have all the
investigators from both teams be present.
In other words, everyone who is chasing after Kira
should be gathered together to take part in the meeting.
I understand. That's not a problem.
As I mentioned before, there are
a total of four members in the SPK.
That's including myself. All of us will be there.
Besides our team, we'll also bring along
Mr. Mogi, who is currently staying with us.
As for Misa Amane, she will be
released right before we meet.
She'll not be told where we're going.
You can come and meet us once you
confirm that she's been safely released.
Is that acceptable?
What do we do?
Hmm.
OK, Near. I understand.
I have a team of five investigators, including myself.
Of course, Mogi's with you at the moment.
So aside from me, they'll there'll be only three people.
Very well, that's fine.
Now, as for our meeting place...
Daikoku Wharf.
There's a warehouse on the outskirts of the southeast side
that's been abandoned for some time.
It's known as the Yellow Box.
I've already taken the liberty of purchasing it.
If this arrangement is fine with you, then we'll use it.
How about it, Light Yagami?
With a location like this, you
can do what you're planning to do.
One more thing,
this meeting cannot take place
unless I have your word that
someone will bring the Notebook.
Wait. Why the Notebook?
It's quite simple.
If your entire team leaves HQ to meet me,
there will be no one left behind to guard the Notebook.
I can promise you this I will
make no attempts to steal it.
In fact, I won't even try to touch it.
As long as Mr. Aizawa can confirm
that it's the genuine Notebook,
I'm willing to place my faith in you and accept his word.
Huh?
All right.
However, I do insist that
someone other than L hold onto it.
My reasons for making that request
should be fairly obvious to you.
Right, I understand.
But I'll be the one who decides who will hold onto it.
Does that sound fair?
Yes, of course.
Then all that's left to arrange is the time and date.
Right. The question is.
What time?
Mikami makes his judgments after midnight.
He most likely receives a notice in
the morning of which people to kill next.
If we take his movements into consideration,
say, three days from now on the 28th at 1 PM.
O'clock, huh?
That's the exact time I expected him to pick.
Near is obviously aware of Mikami's movements.
That's fine by me.
The time doesn't really concern us.
Well then, 1 o'clock, three days from now.
Sure.
Near.
Light Yagami.
I know exactly what your plan is,
and I am going to win.
Kiyomi, I'm sorry, but I'm a
little busier than usual today.
Oh, really?
Does that mean you can't stay until morning?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Police are going to have their
hands for the next two or three days.
That's a shame.
Hm?
I've already given orders to both
Mikami and Takada about what to do.
This will be the final order to kill Near.
Quick. This way.
Are you all right?
Yes.
They're getting away. After them.
We need to get inside NHN now.
Don't do it take a look around.
It's not safe for her here.
Not even inside.
Mello!
It's best if you get her away from here right now.
Miss Takada, get on.
Now.
It's OK, you'll be safe with him.
Please, you have to go.
Right.
Team A and Team B, stay on that bike's tail and
don't lose sight of them.
As for the rest of you, I need you to find that assailant.
All right, we've confirmed Miss Takada's safety.
Let's get her into Car number 7.
What the hell?
No, he's taking her.
Damn it.
Stop, you idiot.
You can't do that.
What if it ends up hitting her?
Wh... What are you doing?
One of the attackers was heavily armed.
As of this moment, both Miss Takada's escort team
and the police are hot on the tail of the suspects.
Oh, man. This is really bad.
Is it Near again?
Near.
You promised that we'd meet in three days time.
What's the meaning of making a move like this now?
It doesn't make sense.
No, this isn't Near's style.
It's more like...
It's Near.
So those cars got ahead of me, huh?
How many damn body guards does one woman need, anyway?
Hey, come on, give me a break.
Since when were the Japanese
allowed to carry around such big guns?
You got me.
I'm part of this whole kidnapping incident.
That means you'll have a lot of questions to ask.
You won't shoot...
What an idiot.
He probably wouldn't have told us anything, anyway.
And death is the only way to pay for crimes against Kira.
This man...
he's the person that Light warned
me to be extra careful of Mello,
Mihael Keehl.
Take off everything you're
wearing and put it all in that box.
Hurry up.
You can use this blanket.
L, I am not the one who kidnapped Takada.
Is that so?
Then it has to be Mello.
Yes, that's right.
And I have to be honest with you on this
we had one of our members escorting Takada,
and they confirmed it Mello was the one who abducted her.
I apologize for letting this happen
while one of us was guarding her.
Near, isn't there any way for you to contact Mello?
No, I'm afraid that would be impossible.
While I do have a method of getting in touch with
him, there's no way he'd respond in the current situation.
Bbefore I take off the rest,
could I please have the blanket
so I can wrap it around me?
Whatever you want.
Our latest report is that the escort team
was forced to shoot one of the perpetrators.
They are also still making efforts
to track Miss Takada's whereabouts.
Were you able to get a hold of her?
Not yet.
Takada's phone has been turned off.
Mello must have confiscated it.
Damn it.
I need to get in touch with Takada.
With no way of getting a hold
of her, all I can do is wait.
This is the only thing that can be done.
If I don't do it...
As for the suspect who was gunned down earlier,
we're still not able to identify him.
The police are tracking the remaining suspects...
Matt. I never thought you'd be killed.
I'm sorry.
Light's cell phone.
Could it be her?
Quiet, everyone.
Hello?
Light? I...
Miss Takada?
Listen to me. Are you all right?
The only reason she'd be able to
call me like this without getting caught
is if she had an opportunity to get away from Mello.
Or...
Light, Light, please save me.
It's all right.
Calm down and answer my questions, OK?
Oh, OK.
First, your location. Do you know where you are?
N... No.
No, I don't know where I am.
I was put into a truck that was locked from the outside.
But we were on the freeway,
and I caught a glimpse of the sign
that said we were heading to Nagano.
Right now, I think we're parked
inside of a building somewhere.
Miss Takada, you are Kira's spokesperson.
Do you remember the conversation we had
when I told you that there might be people
who would try to hurt you because of that?
Y... Yes, I remember.
We talked what you should do if
a situation like this ever arose.
Do you remember that?
Ah, I remember.
I did what you told me to, Light.
I did it.
Yes.
I didn't struggle, even when he stripped me naked.
I did exactly as you said.
I made survival my first priority, and...
...and, I did it.
Please, Light.
I did everything that you told me to.
Come quickly.
Save me.
Miss Takada, you remember what I
told you to do after that, don't you?
I have to do as many killings
as possible while I still can.
I... I know, but... but Light.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
Aizawa, Ide, let's get going.
Matsuda, you stay here and take care of headquarters.
You got it.
It's me.
Send me as many names of people to punish as you can.
Here's my email address.
Yes, right. I understand.
If Takada is calling me like this,
it must mean that she's been able to kill her kidnappers,
in which case, the only certainty is that
she's in a situation where she can't move.
Nakajima, I'm going to the
scene of the crime for this case.
OK.
All right, I got the location by tracing the call.
Head to Karuizawa by freeway.
Karuizawa, huh?
Damn. It'll take at least 30 minutes to get there.
Well, hurry. This is Mello we're talking about.
Who knows what he'll do?
Got it.
I don't believe this Aizawa and Ide are just too stupid.
They jumped the gun and got in the
front seats without even thinking.
This is just too easy.
Ah, no Mello.
What the hell is this?
Kiyomi Takada suicide.
January 26, 2013, 2:32 PM.
Burns to death by setting fire to everything around her
including everything she wrote on.
Looks like this is the end,
no, more like the beginning
the perfect world of Kira.
And those who know of the Notebook's existence
all of them will die.