And once you're fully convinced I'm
the real thing, you and I can get married.
And so, based on what he said, Higuchi is Kira!
If the killing of criminals stops now,
then there's no doubt that Higuchi
is the one with Kira's powers.
However, I know Amane would do almost anything for Light.
But to think that she would actually go this far?
If criminals do stop dying after this,
it will make it difficult to determine a critical element,
how Kira conducts his murders.
I have to think of a plan.
Misa.
How did you get Higuchi to confess?
Easy. That guy's totally in love with me.
All I had to do was tell him I'd
marry him if he was really Kira.
Plus, I managed to convince him that I'm the second Kira.
If I didn't say this now,
I'd probably end up contradicting my story later.
Misa. You idiot!
Didn't I tell you to deny all that?
But... But now we know Higuchi's Kira, right?
So what's the problem? Can't we just catch him?
I suppose this is what you would
call a victory, right Matsuda?
But right now, we still don't know
exactly how he kills his victims, do we?
Yes. That's what I was thinking.
Before we move to arrest Higuchi,
I want to find out how he kills people.
If the criminals stop dying, we
won't be able to figure it out,
unless we come up with another idea.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
At any rate, even if we do arrest Higuchi,
we're not going to do it until we're
certain that criminals have stopped dying.
Let me think about this for a moment.
Weddy.
Yeah.
An update on the current situation, please.
Everything's going smoothly.
We should be able to track 70% of their movements
using our cameras inside the office building.
What about outside the office?
That's not gonna be possible with just Watari and me.
What if you focus solely on Higuchi?
Higuchi?
I've only been able to enter the
houses of five of the men so far,
but Mido, Namikawa, and Higuchi all
have super high tech security systems,
especially Higuchi.
He recently constructed a dampening
room that shuts out any electronic waves.
It took me two days just to break into the place.
This guy sure does sound suspicious.
Hm.
All right. Then begin installing microphones,
trackers, and cameras, but not in the house.
Instead, just put them in every car.
What?
After getting this far?
Do you know how difficult it
is to break into someone's house?
Besides, do you have any idea
of how many cars this guy has?
He has six.
Fine then.
I just have to install them in all his cars, right?
Yes, thank you.
If Higuchi had been bugged earlier,
I would have been in big trouble.
Light.
I'm sorry to keep coming back to this topic.
I'll just get right to the point.
What is it?
Do you remember?
Killing anyone, I mean?
Huh?
Are you still going on about that?
Look, I'm not Kira!
How many times do I...
I just want you to answer the question.
Well, do you remember?
No, I don't.
Miso, what about you?
I don't remember.
How could I, 'cause I'm not Kira.
Look, Light.
Please listen to what I'm about to say.
I'd like you to thoroughly analyze my current theory.
This could determine the way
in which we end up catching Kira.
Light Yagami used to be Kira.
Kira's power has somehow passed onto another person.
Light Yagami now has no memory of ever being Kira.
I need your analysis based on these assumptions.
Do you think you can do that for me?
Yeah. I'll give it a try.
Light Yagami used to be Kira.
Kira's power has somehow passed onto another person.
Was that because Light Yagami wanted it to happen,
or was there someone else in control of Light,
lurking in the background, who gave him the power?
Was it that person who passed
Light's powers to someone else?
Given your premise, it would be my will.
Yes, of course.
If there is a third party with the
ability to bestow or transfer Kira's power
and they didn't want their method to be discovered,
it makes no sense that they would wait so
long to transfer it from you to the next Kira.
If we believe that this was the work
of some being watching us from above,
then we'd have to accept that
they are impossible to catch,
not to mention I'd already be dead.
Or at the very least, I'm being made to be a fool
by eternally dancing in the palm of someone's hand.
It's highly unlikely that such a being exists.
Even if Light Yagami was Kira,
Kira's power can be transferred by
the will of the person who possesses it.
Thank you, Light.
I can now say that I feel 99% better.
We'll create a situation where Higuchi won't
be able to pass off his power to anyone else.
We'll have him show us how he kills.
So, what are you gonna do?
I'm going to trick Higuchi using Sakura TV.
Like a hidden camera show!
What?
We'll use the Kira Special that Demegawa airs every week.
We'll book a three hour time slot.
It'll be announced that Kira's identity
will be revealed near the end of the special.
Would anyone actually buy that, though?
This is Sakura TV after all.
For all we know, Higuchi might
not even watch that program.
We'll get Namikawa to call him and say,
"This is bad. Turn on your TV."
That should be enough to get him watching.
Higuchi will buy it once he realizes
that the special guest on TV
is someone who knows his secret.
Oh, I get it.
So we'll be using Aiber, then.
He'll reveal that he was a spy all along!
No, I'm afraid you're incorrect.
We will not be using Aiber.
Whoever appears on the show...
has to be someone who Higuchi
believes he'll be able to kill.
In other words, it has to be someone...
whose name he can look up easily.
But we're never going to find a person like that, are we?
Hm.
You're the only one who can do it.
Matsu!
Matsu?
Higuchi probably thinks that you
were listening in on their meeting
and overheard their plan to kill people.
It would make sense that Misa's manager who he
thought was dead is the one revealing his secret.
That's right.
We'll have Sakura TV use a voice filter
and frosted glass to protect your identity.
Higuchi will probably realize from the announcement
and the silhouette that it's the manager, Taro Matsui.
And just to make sure, we'll have the studio mess up
and accidentally reveal your
face from behind the frosted glass.
Wow! That sounds exciting!
Until the show ends, the announcer will
keep saying they'll reveal the full name of H,
who's acting as Kira.
Higuchi would feel cornered.
He'd have no choice but to find out
the manager's name as soon as possible.
We can anticipate what actions he'll take.
We'll witness his killing method.
After that, we arrest him.
There is one potential problem with this plan.
If Higuchi can kill by simply looking at someone's face,
just like the second Kira, Matsuda will die.
But, considering the fact that you're still alive,
and how he's pursuing Misa, I doubt that's the case.
At any rate, we're only going to
do this once criminals stop dying.
We'll have to wait for two or three
days to see whether or not that happens.
In the meantime, Matsuda will have to
decide if he wants to go through with this plan.
I don't need two or three days to decide.
I want to do this.
Well, I'm here.
What's with this private meeting?
Namikawa.
Tell me, who do you think is Kira?
Ha. Why do you want to know what I think?
Besides, for all I know, it could be you, Shimura.
Or maybe even Mido.
Shimura can't be Kira.
He was the one who came crying to me about
how he can't go along with Kira's crimes anymore.
Really?
But if Mido had turned out to be
Kira, you would have been killed.
No.
You and Mido would have been successful on your own.
There's no way either of you would
need to hold those stupid meetings.
Let alone with seven others.
I can at least see that much.
We're all cooperating with these killings
because we're afraid of Kira turning on us.
I mean, it's only a matter of time
until the public finds out.
And this isn't going to stop until that happens.
So, Shimura, let me ask you, then,
who do you think Kira might be?
Takahasi or Higuchi.
No. Takahashi is just a decoy.
Kira would make sure there
are people less clever than him.
Well, then, it looks like we all know the truth already.
It's Higuchi, isn't it?
Yes.
He's the one who's the most
obsessed with money and success.
He might always act as if he's
not interested in those things,
but that just proves it all the more.
And he always insults everyone around
him, and can't use his people well.
I believe that's why he was demoted from
being head of the development department.
By the way, I meant to ask was
I the only one you invited here?
I also invited Ooi, but...
he said you can hold your stupid
private meetings by yourself.
Go figure.
Heh. Good old Ooi, always the blunt one.
We can also rule out Kida as a possible suspect,
as he was the one who provided the
account for funds in order to commission Coil.
Namikawa.
During that first meeting after Hatori died,
you got a call on your cell phone.
I was wondering who it was from.
You know, Shimura, you really are a sharp one.
Kira probably selected you
because he appreciates your caution.
Hm.
Namikawa speaking.
It's L. Before I go on, are you by yourself?
No.
Then just act like it's a normal call again.
I don't think there's any need for that.
One of the people here with me was just
expressing his suspicions about your last phone call.
Who is that on the line? Namikawa?
It's L.
L, Mido and Shimura are here as well.
I'm reasonable certain that neither of them are Kira.
In fact, they seem fed up with it at this point.
I'll speak for them and say they'll choose to
stand back and watch your face-off with Kira,
like I plan to.
That's fine.
Tonight, I'm gonna catch Kira.
But I'll need a favor from you.
Hm?
Then it's the end for Higuchi.
What? You know that it's him?
Ha!
So even the great L can be tricked.
Based on your reaction, I'm now
100% certain that Higuchi is Kira.
Namikawa's pretty smart, huh?
But then, I always thought he
was, from looking at his face.
I guess this proves it.
No.
That was just because Light messed up.
I'm baiting Higuchi with a staged TV special tonight.
Sakura TV.
A few minutes into the program,
I want you to contact Higuchi, tell him to tune in.
Do that for me, and I won't go
after you, or any of the other five.
As for the others, Kida, Takahasi, and Ooi,
if they try to do anything, make sure to stop them.
All right. I understand.
It seems it really was Higuchi.
He'll be captured tonight. Apparently.
It's been about three days
since I stopped killing criminals.
That should be good enough, shouldn't it?
Now, when I marry Misa Amane, the second Kira,
I'll have the Shinigami eyes.
With that power in my hands,
Yotsuba will be under my control.
Higuchi, we've got a problem. Turn on the television.
Check out Sakura TV.
Hm?
So you're saying one of those people is Kira, right?
Yes.
I've got a lot of evidence to prove it, too.
What the hell is this?
Come in, it's probably a hoax. This is Sakura TV.
No, it's more than that.
At the beginning of the show he
said that he overheard a meeting...
between eight people.
What? Someone who knows about the meetings?
Who is it? Did someone betray us?
Then one of them was killed by Kira,
and now there are only seven left.
The man who died was Mr. H.
Mr. H?
Hatori.
If he knows this much, he could be one of the other six.
No, maybe it's Coil.
Mr. H wanted to leave the meetings,
and was killed by Kira because of that.
No, it can't be any of the others.
There's no benefit for them to do this.
But no one else knows about the meetings, do they?
Dammit, who is it?
What? Wait.
Could it be...
Huh? Oh!
Ah!
It's... It's him!
Cover him up! Cover him up!
It's Misa's manager.
Matsui. That's his name.
Why is he still alive?
He explained earlier that he
thought he was going to be killed.
He pretended to fall out of the apartment
window and escaped to a balcony a few floors below.
But that can't be.
Just to be careful, I went home that
night and wrote his name in the notebook
like it was written on his business card.
Why is he still alive, then?
Could he be a former entertainer who
became a manager using his stage name?
Is that possible?
If that weren't bad enough,
he said that he continued to
investigate Yotsuba up until now,
and he's figured out which one of us is Kira.
I'm contacting everyone right now to let them now.
All right. We'll talk later.
Sir, we're terribly sorry for that accident.
Are you all right?
We can stop, if you want.
No. I knew I was gonna be in danger going into this.
This is for the sake of justice,
so I'll see it through to the
end, even if it means my death.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Listen, just be sure to hold off on the Kira
announcement until the last minute, all right?
I have to kill him!
Calm down.
Misa knows his face, so if she's the second
Kira, she should know what his real name is.
It's him.
Oh, what the hell?
To be honest, I've been debating for a long
time whether or not I should make this announcement.
But now that I'm here, I know I've
done the right thing in coming forward.
This is bad.
Who knows then he'll make the announcement?
...Kira's identity will be announced soon.
Cosme Misa, a devilish charm.
An angel's glitter.
Misa's new line of lipstick, just for you.
Mido, it's me.
Are you watching Sakura TV?
Why don't you call your father in the House of Counselors?
Have him pull some strings at the Ministry
of Internal Affairs to stop this broadcast.
I'm watching, but I don't think we could stop it.
No one believes this program, so we'd only
make ourselves look suspicious if we stop it.
Besides, there shouldn't be anything to worry about.
The guy revealed his face earlier.
Everyone knows it's really Taro Matsui.
Namikawa's already gone ahead
and told everyone to watch the show.
Since one of us seven has to be Kira, that
should mean Taro Matsui will soon be dead.
Right?
Of course.
I'm the only one who knows, or even
suspects that Taro Matsui isn't his real name.
That means if I say anything,
it'll reveal the fact that I'm Kira.
Yeah. It's true.
I'll talk to you later.
Stay tuned to Sakura TV.
Dammit!
Ryuzaki.
Mogi is in position in front of Yoshida Productions.
He's just received a call from Higuchi.
Yes, it's time for phase two.
Everything's as planned.
Moji, where's Misa?
Oh, Mr. Higuchi. Pleasure to hear from you.
I'm sorry, but Misa Misa's taking
a much needed vacation right now.
She should be back by, oh, tomorrow morning, though.
You can reach her then.
I'm asking you where she is now.
Well, that's private information.
She's requested that no one know where she is.
I'm very sorry.
I'll have her contact you tomorrow, first thing.
Damn! I know his face.
I could kill him at any time, if only I knew his name.
Do you know if Misa's former manager
was an entertainer at some point?
Come again?
I'm talking about Taro Matsui!
Oh.
I was only recently hired, so I don't know much about him.
If you need some information, I can
let you talk to someone from the office.
I just remembered.
Everyone's in Okinawa at the moment.
You could try calling the president, though.
This is going exactly as I planned.
It's almost scary.
You shouldn't be scared, Light.
You should be happy.
I'm patching you in to Higuchi's call
with the president of Yoshida Productions.
This is Higuchi from Yotsuba.
That manager's real name isn't Taro Matsui, is it?
He's not even pretending to hide
what he's asking about now, is he?
Stupid Higuchi.
If he's acting like that, it's
proof he's beginning to panic.
Then what was his real name?
I think it Yamada.
No. Wait.
Yamashida.
And his first name was, I'm sorry, I can't remember.
Don't screw with me!
Why the hell can't you remember
the names of the people you hire!?
All right.
No need for that kind of language.
I've got his personnel file back at the office.
Then go back there and get it.
You gotta be kidding me.
Give me a break.
We're on our first company vacation in two years!
If you wanna know that badly,
I'll give you the pin code for the office lock.
You can go in yourself and look it up. How's that?
The personnel files are in the
desk in the back to the left.
You'll find them filed in the bottom drawer.
They should all be sorted alphabetically.
But I'm pretty sure it was Yamashida.
If they're going to announce it at the end of the program,
that means I have two hours.
So what's he gonna do?
I see Higuchi.
He's only carrying a single bag.
I'm in pursuit.
Everything's still going according to plan.
Yes.
I'll kill him.
I'll kill him no matter what.
I've come this far. I won't let them stop me.
I'm not giving up until I have everything.
With these eyes, I'm invincible!
Higuchi has a gun on him!
The chief has been shot.
This isn't sounding very good.
Higuchi. Hold it right there.
With this show, I'm gonna have 100% ratings for sure!
I made it in time.