What?
I don't believe this.
Another 23 victims yesterday?
Are these confirmed?
As soon as we began to suspect
that Kira might be a student,
the pacing of the killings changed,
as if to contradict that theory.
This can only mean that Kira
has access to police information.
When L discovers that I'm somehow
getting confidential information,
he'll be obligated to start investigating
the police to find the source of the leak.
You're being followed by another human.
He's watching you right now.
That's a problem.
I'll have to get rid of him as soon as possible.
Because through a Shinigami's eyes, a
human's name can be seen above their head.
Not only that we see their lifespan as well.
However, if a Shinigami drops his
Death Note and a human picks it up,
he can grant that human the eyes of a Shinigami.
The price for having a Shinigami's eyes
is half of that person's remaining lifespan.
That's all it is.
So what'll it be, Light?
Is it a deal?
Has anyone seen Ryuk around lately?
Maybe he was serious about losing his Death Note.
It was probably picked up by some
human before he could get to it.
No way.
Then he'd be stuck there till the end of that
human's life or until the Death Note was destroyed.
That could take a while.
Yeah.
I can't picture Ryuk doing something so boring.
But do you know what?
I actually heard he was carrying two Death Notes.
Seriously?
Why would he need two?
Beats me.
I'll never understand that guy.
So the price for receiving the eyes of a Shinigami
is no more than half of my remaining lifespan?
That's it, right?
Yes.
Well then, do we have a deal or not?
Ryuk, this deal is...
out of the question.
Huh?
Let's get this straight.
My plan is to create an ideal new
world free from evil and all criminals,
and I intend to reign as a god
in that world for a very long time.
I might consider the deal if it lengthened my life,
but not if I'd die sooner.
I figured you of all people should
know I wouldn't take this deal.
Yeah.
I still felt I should tell you
that the deal existed, just in case.
Anyway, I've done my part.
I don't need you complaining I
didn't tell you this earlier on.
This is what you call telling me early on?
Don't you think you're a little late?
I don't see why you couldn't
have told me this when we met.
Or better yet, you could have simply included
it in the instructions for the Death Note.
Uh, good point.
He's not the slightest bit daunted
by the fact that I'm a Shinigami.
He doesn't suck up to me
and he seems to have no problem giving me a hard time.
Well?
You sure there's nothing else
you want to tell me ahead of time,
Shinigami?
No. Nothing else.
Probably.
Really?
That's too bad.
What do you mean?
You know, Ryuk, I might have seriously considered
the deal if you'd offered me wings instead of eyes.
Just the idea of flying round
freely in the sky sounds very godlike.
After all, it's been mankind's dream
since antiquity to be able to fly.
You'd stand out if you sprouted wings and flew around.
Not to mention, the police
would have no trouble finding you.
I was only joking.
Anyway, if I keep bargaining for eyes and
wings and whatever else, next thing you know,
I'm going to end up becoming a real Shinigami.
Though who knows? I bet that could be pretty interesting.
I wouldn't worry.
Even without the eyes and the wings,
you're already a worthy Shinigami.
The Shinigami Realm is slowly rotting.
We lead meaningless and empty lives.
And the only reason we still take human lives
is because we're afraid to die ourselves.
The truth of the matter is that
we no longer even know why we exist.
In fact, I doubt there's any
reason for our existence at all.
What I'm saying is compared to that,
you're becoming a much more impressive Shinigami.
I don't know about that. I
mean, from what you're telling me,
it sounds like I'm doing a lot more work than they are.
But...
I don't want to be compared to a Shinigami.
I'm a human using this Death Note to make
the world a better place for other humans.
But I wouldn't necessarily say that the
Shinigami Realm is meaningless to humans, either.
Huh?
Why do you say that?
Well, just think about it.
Whenever a Shinigami like you comes to the human
world, once every 100, no, more like every 1,000 years,
the human world changes dramatically.
The existence of the Shinigami
Realm is extremely significant.
Really?
You told me just now that the
Shinigami Realm is slowly rotting, right?
Well, when you return from this world,
why not use what you've learned here
to try and change it for the better?
Well, Light, I'm not sure why
I never noticed this until now,
but you're quite the positive thinker.
Yeah, of course I am.
That's why I'm using the Death
Note to create a better world.
You have to be a positive thinker
to even attempt something like this.
That's it.
I got it.
Got what?
What's this about?
I think I just figured out how find the
name the guy who was following me today.
How are you going to do that?
I'm going to use the rules of
the Death Note to my advantage.
I already know that if I write down a cause
of death, I've got 6 minutes and 40 seconds
to record the conditions and exact time of death.
First, I need to know exactly
how far I can go in terms of
specifying the details of death.
This should be interesting.
Yeah, it's me.
Another six inmates were found dead last night?
All were heart attacks?
It's him.
What?
Bizarre behavior before they died?
Could you be more specific?
What do you mean?
So they didn't just die from heart attacks.
No, what I'm saying is they all died of
heart attacks, but it wasn't quite that simple.
Before one of them died, he drew a pentagram
on the wall of this cell using his own blood.
Another left a letter, but it doesn't
seem to be a will or anything meaningful.
And as for the third victim, he escaped from his cell
and ran all the way to the staff bathrooms before he died.
What is it, Watari?
Three more heart attack victims.
But the circumstances of their deaths
are different from what we've seen thus far.
What do mean by different?
I'm sending you a copy of a letter,
as well as pictures taken at the scene.
OK.
It sounds like he was afraid
that Kira would find him.
It's believable that our victim might
have been genuinely afraid and wrote this,
but we know Kira can control the time of death.
What if he can also determine the
actions in the moments leading up to death?
In which case...
Chief.
Hm?
We can't release details of
these men's deaths to the media.
As far as they're concerned, these are just heart attacks.
Oh.
I have reason to believe that Kira was
performing some kind of test using these criminals.
And if that's the case,
we'd only be giving him the results of
this information if we took it public.
Right. I understand.
So now he's experimenting on his victims?
Horrible.
He's playing with people's lives,
as if all this was just a game.
It's unforgivable.
If Kira is really using criminals as test subjects,
what is he trying to achieve?
Look at this, Ryuk.
I think we're in luck.
The results of yesterday's little test have
already been downloaded onto my dad's computer.
And these results are just as I expected.
The Death Note will work for what I have in mind.
What do you mean by that?
One of them escaped and ran into the
bathroom I had specified in the Death Note.
Another one drew the same symbol
I had drawn in the Death Note before he died.
And finally, a third wrote the same letter I
had written in the Death Note word for word.
All three did exactly what I intended them to do.
For the other three inmates,
I purposely wrote conditions
that were virtually impossible.
Huh?
With the first one, I wrote that he would
die in front of the Eiffel Tower in one hour.
However, everyone knows that it's physically impossible
to go from a prison in Japan to
Paris, France in only one hour.
Since this couldn't happen, he
simply died of a heart attack in prison.
The next was supposed to draw an exact
picture of L's face on the prison wall.
This also didn't happen.
You can't draw someone you've never seen, right?
Makes sense.
With the last one, I tried something slightly different.
I specified that he would write a note that read,
"I know that L is suspicious of the Japanese police."
To be honest, I actually expected this
one to work, but it didn't end up happening
which means it's impossible to make
someone write what they don't already know.
Or at the very least, it has to be the kind of
thing that they could come up with on their own.
Basically, even the Death Note can't do the impossible.
But as long as it's within the realistic
limits of what that person might do,
I can control them as much as I want before they die.
That's very clever.
But what's all this leading to?
What's the point?
These latest victims will no
doubt keep L and the police guessing.
Even as we speak he's probably trying
to decipher all the clues I left for him,
especially that little note.
That absolutely meaningless dying message.
If Kira used those criminals to
conduct an experiment of some sort,
it means he's about to start something.
If he moves now, there's a good chance that
the FBI will notice someone acting suspiciously.
But perhaps he has a different goal in mind altogether.
Could the pentagram and this
letter be some kind of message?
Is this it?
All right, time for the real thing.
Real thing?
Yesterday on the news, they said this drug
addict tried to rob a bank but was unsuccessful.
He attacked a few people and then ran away emptyhanded.
I'll use him.
It's kind of last minute, but I'm sure I can find someone.
I got a few people in mind.
A few people?
For what?
You'll see.
Believe it or not, I'm actually
a rather popular guy, Ryuk.
Hello?
Huh? Light?
Oh, morning.
He's still following me.
Perfect.
This whole thing would just be a
waste of time if he wasn't tailing me.
Light!
A date?
Yeah.
It's a date no matter how you look at it.
And I'm sure even my stalker will see it that way.
But this isn't just a date, is it?
You said that you'd figured out
a way to find your stalker's name.
So tell me, what do you plan on doing?
Huh? Come on.
Didn't you see what I wrote in the Death Note?
I explained it in great detail.
No.
Doing that would take all the fun out of it.
In that case, just be patient and watch what happens.
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
No, not at all.
Anyway, I haven't been to Spaceland since junior high.
I'm so excited.
And the best part is I have you all to myself.
Uh, yeah.
During the week
he goes to school and crams school at night.
Dates on his day off.
A normal kid, just a hardworking senior in high school.
Chief Yagami's son, Light Yagami.
No cause for suspicion.
At any rate, I'll be done with my
surveillance today, and that'll be it.
I don't get it, Light.
Didn't you say you weren't going
out until entrance exams were over?
That was before I scored number
one on the national practice exams.
Ooh, you're such a nerd.
It's him. He's here.
Seven passengers excluding him.
No one's in the way.
Everything should go smoothly.
Aahh!
Stay in your seats unless you want to die!
A busjacking?
You gotta be kidding me.
Everybody shut up!
If anybody moves, I'm putting a bullet in their head.
All right, driver, you listen to me.
I know you've got the number
for Spaceland's office on you.
Call 'em!
OK.
This this is Sasaki calling from bus 174.
Tell 'em what's going on and no tricks, either.
My bus has been hijacked and
he's holding a gun to my head.
Give me that.
You heard what he said.
Now you listen up.
Have a female staff member bring
all of Spaceland's cash from yesterday.
I know it's there.
Have her meet us two bus stops from the park,
and don't make me wait.
If you mess with me at all or
try to get the police involved,
I swear I'll kill every one of these passengers.
Hunnh!
Yuri, don't be scared.
As soon as he turns around
I'm going to grab the gun out of his hand.
Don't be stupid. That's risky.
If it comes to that, I'll take care of it.
It's OK.
We don't have to pass notes back and forth.
As long as we keep it down, he won't be able
to hear our voices over the sound of the engine.
Do you have any proof that you're not his accomplice?
Why should we trust you?
Accomplice?
Yes, I've read about this before.
The first hijacker comes in like he's working alone.
Meanwhile, a second one pretends to
be a hostage and stays in the very back,
just in case something goes wrong.
What's the matter?
You you really think he is one?
I... I have no choice.
I'm sure Light Yagami isn't Kira.
If he was, he could just kill
this guy with a heart attack.
Here's my proof. Take a look.
FBI?
I see.
L needed an outsider so he got the FBI to
investigate anyone connected to the Japanese police.
His name is Raye Penber.
I trust you.
And I guess for the time being, I won't bother asking
what an FBI agent is doing on the bus in the first place.
Do you have a gun?
Yeah, I've got one.
So if it comes down to it, I can rely on you, right?
Yes.
Get the hell up, you old hag!
You want me to shoot you right now?
That's right, this guy.
His face was all over the local news just a few days ago.
Look at me when I'm talking to you!
Some junkie.
He tried to rob a bank and ended up
killing three people before he got away.
He's extremely dangerous.
We're safe. He won't shoot us.
In fact, he's not gonna do anything.
Aaah!
Don't move, you little punk!
What the hell is that?
Ah, smartass.
You guys were planning something back here, weren't you?
Damn it.
If he sees that note from before,
he'll find out that Light was planning
to jump him and take his gun away.
Plans for a date, huh?
Stupid kid.
Gotcha.
Huh?
Who... who the hell are you?
You in the very back, what do you think you're doing?
D-don't mess with me!
How long you been hiding back there?
What's this?
You're talking to me?
So you mean you can actually see me right now?
Ahhh! Stay there, you!
You keep away from me, you freak.
This isn't good. He's hallucinating.
Everyone get down!
Oh, I get it.
That little note that, like, accidentally dropped
was actually torn from the pages of the Death Note itself.
Since he tricked this guy into touching the paper,
he's the only other one in the bus who can see me.
That's so smart.
Get away!
Aaaghh!
Aaaaaagh!
Sorry, pal.
I'm a Shinigami, so I'm afraid
your bullets aren't gonna kill me.
Anyone who touches the Death Note can see me.
I have to stay till the death Note is
finished or I see you die, whichever comes first.
And the Shinigami can't die from being shot.
I've said all these things at one time or another.
Well, he is the top-ranked student in the country.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
He even used this hijacking as a way
to get the guy following him
to willingly give up his name.
Stop the bus.
Let me off!
11:45 on the dot.
Everything went just as I planned.
Kiichiro Osoreda.
Accidental death.
Boards the 11:31 Spaceland-bound bus
near the eastern entrance to the park
holding a loaded gun and attempts to hijack the bus.
Sees a horrific phantom and
empties his gun trying to kill it.
Terrified, he flees the bus.
Immediately afterwards, at 11:45,
he dies when struck by a car.
The Death Note never failes.
You will be next, Raye Penber.
It's just as I thought.
He doesn't suspect me at all.
The remaining investigators will all die of heart attacks.
Farewell, Raye Penber.