I can't believe my son is looking at those magazines.
Hey, Light!
Come on!
Dinner's ready.
I'll solve equations with my right
hand and write names with my left.
I'll take a potato chipand eat it!
And the witness to my alibi is L himself.
Are you sure about this? Ryuk.
Yeah, I'm sure nobody's following you, OK?
Now hurry up already, will you?
The symptoms are getting worse.
I really hope you're not saying what you
think I'd want to hear just to get some apples.
Whoa! Hold it right there.
I just flew out and checked a 100-meter
radius around you, and there was no one there.
So yeah, for the last time, I'm sure. OK?
All right.
But on the news, they said they were
dispatching 1,500 investigators to Japan.
They're bluffing.
You said so yourself.
If it were really happening, they
wouldn't announce their arrival.
Instead, they'd come and investigate secretly.
I suppose you're right.
Well, then, I'll buy you some apples.
Nice.
Here you are. Please come again.
Light, come on. Hurry up.
You know, you really haven't been that nice to me.
You have me looking all over for cameras,
telling me that I can't even
eat apples in the house anymore.
It's not right.
Make sure you eat the core as well.
You know, I might actually write your name
in my Death Note and kill you, just like that.
I wouldn't laugh if I were you.
Right.
That reminds me, I've got one finishing touch left to add.
Hmm. Hey, Ryuzaki.
Yes?
I've been thinking about the purse snatcher
and the embezzler's heart attacks two days ago.
It seems my family couldn't have had
any knowledge of them before they died.
Shouldn't that resolve any doubts you have?
You may be right.
Even though Kira can control the time of death,
I don't think there's any way he could have arranged
their deaths without having seen the broadcast first.
Hmm?
Your son has come home.
Huh.
Heh.
So you're going to keep quiet
and pretend to study again, huh?
I have a good grasp of where all the cameras are placed,
but I only managed to kill a purse snatcher and
an embezzler using that trick with the potato chips.
Both of them were guilty of much
lesser crimes than my previous victims.
Next, in local news...
Huh?
You're watching TV?
I made sure to kill criminals
whose names and faces were broadcast
when I didn't have access to TV or the internet.
But there's a chance I'll look even more suspicious
if only these lesser criminals end up
dying while I'm not receiving information.
In other words, if I kill other petty criminals
whose names and faces are broadcast as I watch TV,
I won't draw unnecessary attention to myself.
For this to work, all I really have to do
is remember the identities of the criminals
I either see on TV or while I'm online,
regardless of the severity of their crimes.
That way, whenever I go out,
I can use that piece of the Death Note I
keep in my wallet to kill them at random times.
Just like that.
It's the perfect way to deal with these hidden cameras.
In the past few days,
I've listened to all of our audio recordings
and reviewed the video footage we captured.
I've gone over them many times.
And I've come to a conclusion.
Our surveillance of the Kitamura
and Yagami households has revealed...
nothing.
We will remove the cameras and wiretaps.
All that, and we still don't have any suspects.
It's OK, Matsuda.
We'll have to pursue other leads, but we'll get him.
Please don't get the wrong idea.
Huh?
I only said that we were unable
to reveal anything suspicious
based on our surveillance.
What?
Even if Kira was among them,
I'm sure he wouldn't make it obvious.
No, in fact, it could mean he was able to continue
killing without doing anything outwardly suspicious.
Well, then you believe that Kira
is among one of those families.
As I've said, there's a 5% chance.
Kira never stopped killing people, even
while the surveillance cameras were in place.
I still have no idea how he's
been able to commit these murders,
but... let's say he could kill someone
simply by wishing death upon them.
You'd think that any human being
would have shown at least some emotion,
some sign that they were knowingly
committing an act of murder.
So the obvious conclusion is
that Kira couldn't be one of them.
However, what if he is one of
these people we've been watching?
If he is, we have to assume that his
psyche has reached godlike proportions,
punishing evildoers without the
slightest change of expression.
It almost makes me want to
believe that Kira doesn't exist,
that this is just the wrath of a vengeful god.
But that idea is completely absurd,
to think that God would need a
person's face and name to kill them.
No, these aren't acts of God,
but someone very childish and immature
who wants to pretend they're God.
That's what's going on here.
A mass murderer who calls himself Kira exists somewhere,
I'm sure of it. And I will catch him.
But I can't count on Kira making any mistakes.
It doesn't matter how long we watch him.
He's not going to expose himself to us.
So what should I do?
Ideally, I ought to get to know him well enough
that he'd admit to me that he
was Kira and show me how he kills.
Would that even be possible?
Hey, Light.
I just checked, and all the cameras have been removed.
All of them, every single one.
Hello?
Are you listening to me?
Hey, Light.
Oh, good point.
We still don't know if they've
removed all the wiretaps from the house.
I suppose this means I'm no longer a suspect.
Everything's going as planned.
But I'm sure L won't give up that easily.
If he's still working with the Japanese police,
chances are my father is working
with him, or under him, anyway.
If that's the case, I'll have to use my father to
find out L's true identity, and I"ll eliminate him.
Once I get rid of L, Kira will be one step
closer to becoming the god of the new world.
Light, hurry up.
You don't want to be late.
Do your best.
I know you don't need it, but good luck.
I really don't see why you two are
making such a big deal out of this.
I'm relieved.
We don't have to deal with wiretaps in the house anymore.
Well, it's nice to know that one cause
of stress was resolved before my exam.
And once I get into university,
I'll have a lot more room to act as Kira.
Then I can focus on finding out who L really is.
You there.
The exam will be starting in 10
minutes, so you better hurry up.
It's fine.
I planned to get here three minutes before the test.
I hate waiting.
I'm here too early.
Well, well. Confident.
And begin.
Hmm?
You there, student number 162.
Sit properly in your chair.
Hmm?
It seems like a lot of Shinigami
are observing the human world lately.
Uh, what's with that, anyway?
It turns out that Ryuk is being kept by a human.
Ha, what's he thinking?
Seriously.
He's a disgrace to the pride of the Shigiami.
No, I'm talking about the human who's keeping Ryuk.
Huh?
Who would want him as a pet?
Aren't pets supposed to be cute?
When you're right, you're right.
So what's the story on this human, anyway?
Is it a male or a female?
Who knows?
In that case, I think I'd better go take a closer look.
Oh boy.
You're a college student now.
That's kind of exciting.
I'm filled with joy.
Now for the freshman address,
freshman representative Light Yagami.
Yes.
Ooh. Wow.
And freshman representative Hideki Ryuga.
Oh, uh, here.
Is that Hideki Ryuga, the pop idol?
That guy?
There's no way he's got the brains
to get into a school like To-Oh.
Yeah, you're right.
He doesn't look anything like the real Hideki Ryuga.
I knew I'd be giving the address with one other student.
But I never expected this.
I remember him from the exam center.
He got into trouble for sitting oddly on his desk.
It seemed like he was off in his own world.
As all of us embark on this new chapter of our lives...
The student who scores highest on the
test is supposed to give the speech, right?
I guess both of them must have
had the high score this year.
I heard they both had perfect scores for all subjects.
Seriously?
It's hard to believe there are actually people like that.
I think I like the little one on the right.
What? You're so weird, Kyoko.
Look at how he's dressed.
Mmm.
Man, these two are total opposites.
Yeah.
This one looks like a sheltered genius
who's been groomed for success his whole life.
But the other one.
As we embark on this new chapter in our lives...
There's something not right about him.
He's just freaking weird.
This guy must be what they call a mad genius.
Coming to the To-Oh entrance ceremony dressed like that?
Unbelievable.
Either he's crazy, or he's just toying with us.
...your freshman representative, Hideki Ryuga.
Light.
Light Yagami?
Your father is Cheif Soichori Yagami of the NPA.
Your respect for your father is matched
only by your strong sense of justice.
Who the hell is this guy?
You're planning to join the
police agency when you graduate.
And you've already got experience, seeing as you've
helped the police solve a number of cases in the past.
Now you're showing an interest in the Kira case.
I'm impressed by your abilities and your sense of justice.
If you promise not to tell anyone about
this, I have important information concerning
the Kira investigation that I'd like to share with you.
Where's this coming from?
And who is he?
Is it safe to just ignore him?
But I wonder what this information actually is.
I won't tell anyone. What is it?
I want to tell you I'm L.
What?
There's no way!
What's he talking about?
If he really was L, he'd never admit to it.
I thought this guy was a bit
strange, but this is pretty extreme.
Stop.
This isn't good.
Don't act surprised.
On the off chance that he really is L,
I have to act how Soichiro Yagami's son,
Light Yagami, would act in this situation.
There'd be no reason for him to be afraid.
If you are who you say you are, then you
have nothing but my respect and admiration.
Thank you.
The reason I chose to reveal my identity to you
is because I think you could be of
some help to us on the Kira investigation.
Light Yagami.
The likelihood that you are Kira is just under 5%.
Even so, something tells me I'm not wrong to suspect you.
But you're just too perfect.
If you are Kira, I can't think of anything that
would put more pressure on you than this little scenario.
If this guy is really L like he
says, then consider be impressed.
Indeed.
If this guy really is L, no, even if he's not L.
I... I can't do anything to him.
Huh.
If what he's saying is true,
it probably means he's already
shown his face to my father.
What now?
If he were to die right after telling me who
he was, it would only confirm their suspicions.
Although it's obvious Hideki Ryuga
is nothing more than an absurd alias,
it still complicates things.
Even if I get lucky and it isn't an alias,
if I try to kill him by simply
writing his name in the Death Note,
I might accidentally picture
the face of Ryuga the pop star
and end up killing him instead.
And if this guy doesn't die,
he'll know for a fact that I'm Kira.
Is he really L?
Does he already suspect that I'm Kira?
It's hard to say how much he
knows, but I must be under suspicion.
What other reason could he have for
telling Soichiro Yagami's son that he's L?
Does this mean that he's still suspicious of the
people that Raye Penber was investigating before he died?
Even so, I still don't see why he
would reveal himself to me directly.
I can't let him see any signs of distress.
It's better if I just clear my mind.
Ha, I didn't think the ceremony would be so interesting.
Hey, Light.
You hear that?
I think it's your new friend.
Uh, nice meeting you.
No, the pleasure was mine.
What an amazing car.
A limousine?
Well, I'm sure I'll see you on campus.
Yeah, take care.
That kid must come from some serious money.
Plus he's at the top of the class?
Where's the justice?
Huh?
Hey, welcome home, Mr. To-Oh!
Hmm?
Damn it! He got me!
Uh, what do you mean?
Damn L!
I've never been so humiliated in my life.
Uh, hey, why don't you just
do the Shinigami eye deal thing?
Then you should have no problem killing him, right?
And what good will Shinigami
eyes do me if this is just a trap?
If I kill him, and it turns out he's not really L,
that would be like announcing
to the real L that I am Kira.
Uh, sorry.
Don't think that Shinigami killing people
and humans killing people are
the same thing, because they're not.
I want nothing more than to kill him.
But if I do, it's like asking to get caught.
Unfortunately, the Death Note can only
kill the person whose name is written in it,
so it's not like I can arrange
for someone else to kill him.
It's inconvenient.
That's the flaw with the Death Note.
Light is usually so calm, but he's snapped.
This must be getting to him.
At first, I thought once I found out his name,
I'd have him die in an accident or kill himself.
However, none of that will do me any good unless
I know with 100% certainty that this guy is L.
No, it's already too late to do anything about it
since he's approached me and introduced himself as L.
It doesn't matter how sure I am.
Regardless of the cause of death, if L
dies now, the police are going to suspect me.
I underestimated him.
I'd never even considered the possibility that
he would reveal his identity to me on purpose.
He could be telling all the suspects the same
thing. In fact, it doesn't even have to be him.
He could have sent a double instead.
For L, this strategy acts as a solid defense,
and it allows him to confront Kira directly.
He can defend and attack.
He got me.
It was a good move.
I'm sure I haven't seen the last of Ryuga.
He'll keep trying to move in on
me, playing the absentminded genius,
and we'll pretend like nothing's going on.
Huh?
This is perfect.
There's no reason for me to be worried.
After all, this is proof that
they don't have anything on me yet.
So this whole thing is nothing
more than a contest between L and me.
A match of wits.
On the surface, we'll be two friendly classmates.
But in reality, we'll actually
be investigating each other.
This is interesting, Ryuga.
If it's my friendship you want, I'll gladly accept it.
In time, I'll earn your trust.
And once you've told me what I want to know,
there'll be no point keeping you alive.
Then I'll kill you, with my hands if I have to.
Hmm.
I don't see any way that Ryuga, or L,
can profile me based on a tennis match.
So I have to assume he has some other goal in mind.
Either way, I'm not going to let him win.