Near, if you don't mind me asking,
what do you make of all this?
I'm interested to hear what
your thoughts are on this case.
The current Kira is foolish and overconfident.
Not to mention unusually cooperative with the task force.
So much so that I suspect he's
working hand in hand with them.
You think so?
That would make the second L and Kira...
one in the same person.
What?
That can't be.
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
Having said that, I'll admit that I'm only 7% certain.
Don't worry, Commander Rester.
Making assumptions is part of any investigation.
If we're wrong, all it'll cost is an apology.
There have been less crimes lately
in Japan, and around the world.
It's because of Kira.
My daddy told mee that, if you do something bad,
your name will be written on the
internet and Kira will kill you.
Come on. I don't have all day.
How am I supposed to file this report without your name?
Will you give me a break?
Please, not my name!
Leave me alone or I'll put your names on the internet.
I will proclaim this right here and
now, to all the people of the Earth.
Kira is true justice!
Good evening.
It is my honor to be appointed by Kira as his spokesman.
This is not a hoax. It's the absolute truth.
I realize that there will be many
people who might try to have me killed now.
But, I'm prepared to risk by life...
Kira's Kingdom, huh?
What a horrible title.
This is insanity.
...can hear Kira's voice.
Trying to capture Kira is an unforgivable crime.
If you happen to know...
If anybody deserves to be killed by Kira, it's this guy.
...a criminal, or a regular citizen.
Switch it back to the press conference.
The president's about to start.
I wonder what it's about.
All they said was that it was gonna be
some sort of international announcement.
You don't do anything but watch TV, do you?
Wha?
Good morning. I'm gonna try to keep this brief.
No way.
The United States will no longer oppose Kira.
Those cowards!
I've done it.
I've even been brought America to its knees.
W-What the hell is he talking about?
Have they been threatened or something?
Are you saying that Kira is justice?
Justice?
No, no, I never said that.
But because if Kira, war and
conflict have ceased to exist.
Criminal organizations are in a state of ruin,
not only in the United States, but in all free nations.
Anyone who defies Kira head on will be killed.
That is a fact.
We are not acknowledging Kira as a symbol of justice.
We are simply saying that, as a country,
we will not take any actions against him.
How is that any different?
You're saying that you accept Kira?
Explain yourself!
You call yourself a representative of our country?
I can't believe it.
This is America.
How can their government do
something so cowardly like this?
Uh. Do you guys mind if I ask a serious question?
Oh, boy. What is it this time?
Are you telling us you're not always serious?
Do you guys ever think that
maybe Kira isn't completely evil?
What?
What kind of question is that, Matsuda?
I've been thinking about it,
and part of me just doesn't believe that he is.
So now you think Kira is justice too?
I don't really know.
But I think that Kira's trying to fight
evil and change the world in his own way
and, well, the world's become a good place
for people who live honest lives, so maybe...
You're wrong, Matsuda!
People are only afraid of losing their own lives.
How can you think that's real peace?
I understand that.
Believe me, I know that as well as you.
It's just that I can also understand the other side.
I can see why all those people call Kira a savior.
I'm not like you.
When it comes down to it, I've
always been a really weak person.
But I'm also a detective.
I can't accept Kira.
I know it's my duty to catch him.
No, I want to catch him.
It's just that I can't completely hate him either.
I guess I must be crazy or something, huh?
No, you're not crazy. You're normal.
You too, Light?
What are you talking about?
I'm sure that, on some level,
Kira probably knows that what he's doing is evil,
but he'll try to change the world,
even as a martyr, at the cost of his soul.
That's his brand of justice.
I bet that's what's going through Kira's mind.
Anyway, we shouldn't be arguing about it.
Good or evil, it's not our call.
All we have to think about is catching him.
If Kira gets caught, then that makes him evil.
But if he wins and rules the
world, then I guess he's justice.
But from now on, the world will
start leaning in favor of Kira.
It's only a matter of time.
Kira will be justice.
What's going to happen to us now?
It looks like we've been disbanded,
thanks to that chicken of a president.
No. He's not even a chicken.
He's less than a maggot.
You've got to be kidding.
There's no way accepting Kira will lead to anything good.
Huh?
So you're alive.
Near.
Hm?
What should we do?
Let him in.
Mello, welcome.
Drop your weapon!
Everyone, please put away your guns.
Having a shoot out here would achieve nothing.
Sir, with all due respect.
Mello's the one who killed our partners.
Please don't make me say it again.
Remember that our primary
objective is still to catch Kira.
Killing Mello right now will do
nothing to benefit our investigation.
All right.
It seems like things have been
going just as you planned, Near.
Yes.
I take it you've already heard all
about the second L from Lidner by now.
I've pretty much figured out who Kira is, and
it's mostly thanks to everything you've done.
Shut up, Near!
I'm not just a tool for you to use in
order to solve your puzzles, you know.
Mello.
If you really want to shoot me, then go ahead and do it.
Stop.
If you shoot him, then the rest of us
will have no choice but to shoot you too.
What will it solve if both of you die?
That's just what Kira wants.
You have a good point.
Anyway, I'm only here for one thing.
I came to take back that photograph you have.
Of course.
I got it from the orphanage.
There was only one and no copies have been made.
I've already gone ahead and dealt
with everyone who knows your face,
both inside and outside Wammy's house.
they'll keep quiet.
I can't say 100% for certain, but it shouldn't
be possible for you to be killed by the notebook.
Is that the only business you had with me, Mello?
Near.
Let's get one thing straight.
I have no intention of working together with you on this.
Yes, I know.
At the same time, I can't just take my photo and leave.
That wouldn't be right. So I'll settle my debt.
The killer notebook.
It belongs to a Shinigami.
Whoever touches it is able to see a god of death.
That's crazy.
Who the hell would believe in something like that?
I would. I believe him completely.
What good would it do for him to
tell an outrageous lie like that?
Even if he had something to gain, he could
at least come up with a more believable story.
Therefore, these gods of death must exist.
The notebook I obtained had
previously belonged to another Shinigami,
perhaps even Kira himself.
Also, some of the rules written inside are actually fake.
That's all I can tell you for now.
Near.
Mello?
Which of us is going to reach Kira first, I wonder?
The race is on.
We're both headed towards the same destination.
I'll be waiting for you.
Right.
Fake rules.
There's no doubt that the notebook can cause
heart attacks and control its victims to a degree.
As for burning it or tearing it up,
the notebook still exists, and there's no
way to confirm the rule one way or the other.
That means...
the false rule must be the one that states a person
will die if he doesn't write a name within 13 days.
Giovanni.
Please set up a connection to L.
Yes, sir.
It's Near.
Yes?
L, I thought you should know that we caught Mello.
Huh?
But he escaped soon afterwards.
We were able to interrogate him for a while.
He didn't really escape, did he?
You let him get away. Am I right?
No.
We tried to restrain him, but he was too quick.
Anyway, Mello mentioned that there was some
sort of Shinigami attached to the notebook.
Have you been able to confirm
the existence of such a creature?
Yes.
I can tell you for a fact that Shinigami do exist.
I didn't share that information with you at the beginning
because I was certain you would never believe me.
I would like to ask the Shinigami a few questions.
Forget it. I'm not up for that.
The thing that's bothering me the most about this
is the issue of those rules written in the notebook.
I have reason to believe that one of them is fake.
Huh?
A fake rule?
Yes.
L, I'd be interested to hear your thoughts on this.
Out of all the rules, which do you think is the fake?
I'd like to know.
By process of elimination, the obvious choice
would be the one stating that
the owner of a notebook will die
if they don't write a new name in it every 13 days.
I don't believe that.
I thought you might say so.
I've reached the same conclusion.
Shinigami, you know the rules of the notebook well.
Tell us, are any of them false?
No. They are all real.
I see. You have a Shinigami there with you?
Yes.
Is that so?
I think I'm beginning to get the picture.
In other words, Kira is there in the room,
and he's making the Shinigami lie on his behalf.
Whoa, this guy's good.
He nailed it.
I don't get what he means.
So what if the Shinigami is lying, and the rule's fake?
It doesn't really change anything, does it?
Yes, it does.
It means that Light's incarceration would be meaningless.
The rule says you die if you don't continue writing names.
But if that's false, being alive after more than 13
days in confinement wouldn't really prove anything.
But even if that's true, it doesn't mean he's guilty.
Besides, there's no way that Light can be Kira.
Before he passed away, the deputy director himself
was able to confirm that he didn't have a notebook.
If there's a problem, I suggest
we verify the rule this way.
I will volunteer to write down
Mello's real name in the notebook.
Of course, that means he'll die.
If I also die 13 days later, well, then I guess Kira wins.
Either way, it's a gamble I'm quite willing to make.
What? So this is just a game to him?
Testing and confirming the 13 day rule
can only benefit the Kira investigation.
And other than my possible
death, there would be no drawbacks.
I'm willing to put my life on the
line if it will help us solve the case.
If I answer him based on my feelings alone,
it will only make me look worse to everyone.
Could you please wait for a moment?
We need to discuss your suggestion.
OK. What are your thoughts?
We can say that we must respect human life
and deny this request, but I can't suggest that.
I'm the one under suspicion.
It's a tough call.
Mello killed the deputy director.
If Near is willing, I wouldn't stop him.
I'm against the idea, myself.
I don't believe that Kira is hiding among us.
We can't use the notebook, no matter what happens.
We should respect the deputy director's wishes to the end.
I feel the same. I'm opposed to the test.
Hm.
Near, we've talked it over, and we can't
allow you to use the notebook like that.
I had a feeling you might say so. No matter.
Just one last question before I go.
To the members of the Japanese task force,
was there ever a point in the investigation
where the second L was suspected to be Kira,
even if the suspicions were later dropped?
If you've been listening to our conversation so far
and have any intention of helping
my investigation in taking down Kira,
then call the number I'm about to give you.
Day or not, I will answer.
The choice is up to you.
There's no way that Light could be Kira.
No, it's more like I don't want to believe he's Kira.
But if the 13 day rule is fake, then we
really can't say for sure that he's innocent.
This could change everything.
Near. I have to kill him.
Yes? Hello?
This is Kira.
Is this a joke?
If you want proof, I can read out a list
of people that I'm going to punish tomorrow.
That way you can check it and
make your final decision afterwards.
Mr. President, I am very grateful that you
and your country have sympathized with me,
but I'm afraid even that much isn't enough.
The SPK is still trying to catch
me, despite your recent announcement.
I want you to stop them
immediately, and formally disband them.
At the same time, I want you to use the American police,
the CIA, the FBI, and all other law
enforcement organizations at your disposal
to find out where the SPK members are currently hiding.
As soon as you've found their base of operations,
I want you to forward that information to a third party.
I will give you this contact shortly.
Mr. President, whether you live
a long life or not is up to you.
Don't forget that.
I understand.
Mr. Demegawa, please wait a moment.
Why are you going to New York?
We are going to crush an
organization that dares to defy Kira.
it will be on live TV.
This is a direct order from Kira,
and it came through the President
of the United States himself.
Huh?
I don't know what's going to happen when we get there.
Hell, I don't even know what I'm
saying anymore, and I don't really care.
Sakura TV's ratings are gonna rocket
to 100, no, 120% for this special.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Come on, everyone!
The new age of Kira is about to arrive!
The previous L was suspicious of Light.
But if Light is Kira, and I just come
out and say we should investigate again,
then I'll probably end up dead, just like L.
That won't solve anything.
The 13 day rule, huh?
Aizawa.
Huh?
We have a long history.
I can tell exactly what you're
thinking about, and what's bothering you.
Between you and me, you should go
ahead and do what you think is right.
I didn't trust L to begin with.
I never did, to be honest.
I didn't sign up to join the Kira
task force because Light was running it.
I joined because I wanted to work with you.
Ide.
All right.
I'll see if I can contact Near without letting Light know.
OK.
I'll make sure that no one knows what you're doing.
You can count on me.
Light, I really want to believe
that you're not Kira.
This is really bad.
Turn on the TV. It's Demegawa!
Huh?
This is Demegawa live.
My comrades and I have finally pinpointed
the hideout of the evil organization
bent on trying to catch our beloved god Kira.
We now have the building completely surrounded!
Come on out!
Break down the door!
Right now our enemies appear
to be hiding within the building,
but they won't be able to hide from us for long.
Behold the power of the people!
The power of justice!
As soon as Near escapes, I'm
gonna write his name in the notebook.
Don't worry, Light. I won't let you down.
At this rate, we'll be dragged
outside unless we stop them somehow.
L.
What's going on, Near?
Could it be that this is some sort
of plot by Mello to finish off the SPK?
No.
Surely it couldn't be that the SPK's security was so lax
that even a normal citizen could
find out where it was located.
Damn it.
He's lying through his teeth.
I win, Near.
I can definitely use this man.
He worships Kira from the bottom of his heart.
He understands that he was chosen the
moment he took possession of the notebook.
There was no mistake in my selection.