L. I want to meet you.
Daikoku Wharf, an abandoned
warehouse known as the Yellow Box.
How about three days from now, on the 28th at 1:00 PM?
That's fine by me.
Take off everything you're
wearing and put it all in that box.
You can use this blanket.
Ms. Takada, are you all right?
Light.
I did exactly what you told me to.
I made survival my first priority and... and I did it.
Come quickly.
Save me.
Kiyomi Takada.
Suicide.
January 26th, 2013. 2:32 PM.
Burns to death by setting fire to everything around her,
including everything she wrote on.
It is with great sorrow that I must announce
the passing of one of our very own colleagues.
The police have identified one of the bodies
found at the scene as NHN's Ms. Kiyomi Takada.
A two ton truck and a motorcycle were also
found in the ruins of the burned out church.
Investigators suspect gasoline was used to start the fire.
What I really want to know is who's
going to be Kira's next spokesperson.
Kira's message still needs to be
spread, and someone's gotta do it.
The death of newscaster Takada was a horrible tragedy,
but I can't help but think that if she was that careless,
she couldn't have taken her position
as Kira's spokesperson that seriously.
It needs to be said.
This is not a woman's job.
Kira.
Please make me your new representative.
No!
Give the honor to Sakura TV again!
Disgusting.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, they just announced her
death, and already it's started.
Every TV station airing its own
segment on who should replace her.
It's like she never existed.
Last night's judgments unfolded just as planned.
That means Takada and Mikumi have
had no problems contacting each other.
There's nothing to worry about.
It's near.
Hello L.
Yes?
I don't mean to keep bothering
you, but with regards to our meeting,
I wanted to confirm that we are still
set for the 28th at 1:00 PM, all right?
Yes.
It's just as I predicted.
He's sticking with the original time.
There's no doubt about it.
Very well.
The 28th. The day after tomorrow.
Right.
So, the day of tomorrow, huh?
Finally. Isn't it getting exciting?
Y... Yeah.
I can't help but wonder what Near wants to show us.
Matsuda, Ide.
When the day comes, there's a
good chance we might all be killed.
Don't you understand that?
Giovanni.
Yes?
Will you be able to make it in time?
Yes. I'll be there for sure.
Commander Rester, Lidner, Giovanni.
Let's put our best into this, shall we?
Good morning, everyone.
Uh, good morning.
First of all, in regards to Misa Amane,
we've already set her free.
You may call her to confirm it.
I don't know what's going on, but this
must be some sort of compensation or something!
They totally put me up in the
penthouse suite of the Teido Hotel.
Can you believe it?
Now, this is more like it!
I understand. All right, Misa.
Please stay there for a little
while longer until I call you.
OK!
All right, Near. I need you to connect me with Mogi.
We have the notebook locked away here,
and in order to open the safe it's kept in,
we'll need the pin number from each member of the team.
Understood.
I'll connect you to him immediately.
This is Mogi.
Number is 62-324.
All that's left is my number.
The killer notebook.
How to use it.
The human whose name is written
in this notebook shall die.
This note will not take effect unless the writer has
the person's face in their
mind when writing his or her name.
Therefore, people sharing the
same name will not be affected.
If the cause of death is written within 40 seconds
of writing the person's name, it will happen.
If the cause of death is not specified,
the person will simply die of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of death, details of the death
should be written in the next six minutes and 40 seconds.
Near, it's me.
We've discussed it, and it's been decided
that I'll be the one to carry the notebook.
L, are you sure it's all right
with you if Mr. Aizawa carries it?
Be honest.
Of course.
I chose Aizawa for the job
because we knew you'd prefer that.
I have no problems with it.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
Well then, we'll see you shortly.
Looks like this is the end.
No.
More like the beginning.
The perfect world of Kira.
And those who know of the notebook's existence,
all of them...
will die.
There's no mistake, Near's inside.
I checked it out.
All right. Let's do this.
Near.
You're far inferior to L.
You have no right to be wearing a mask of L.
It's them.
Those four are the SPK.
And the one wearing a mask is Near.
Hang on.
Am I the only one who sees something wrong?
He can go around accusing people of being Kira,
but the fact that he's wearing a mask
says he's only trying to protect himself.
Not anyone else.
It's just a precaution.
There's a good possibility that Kira has already seen
the faces of everyone in this warehouse, except for mine.
In fact, he may be writing down your names as we speak.
So I'd like to wait for one hour. No, make it 30 minutes.
That should give us more than enough time to
see if anyone is being controlled before they die.
Huh? What?
You're gonna wait and see if we die?
No. It's not impossible that Light really is Kira,
especially since the rest of
us are of no use to him anymore.
This is all just a front to buy some time, isn't it?
I never thought it would be this hard
to keep myself from laughing out loud.
Near must be waiting for him to come.
It's all just as I predicted.
Near!
It's already been over 30 minutes.
Nothing's happened yet.
Of course not.
That's because Kira's not here with us.
Very well.
Everyone seems to be safe.
I'll remove my mask now.
You're quiet, Near.
What's wrong?
Are you still waiting for something?
Waiting.
That's an excellent choice of words.
Yes, I am waiting, for the arrival of the
one who will solve everything once and for all.
Someone else is supposed to clear this up?
He'll be here soon.
It's only a matter of time.
There's only one entrance to this building,
and the only way to look inside is by opening that door.
That means he'll either walk through that door,
or at the very least, open it and peek through.
And just who is this person, anyway?
X Kira, the one who is currently using the
notebook and killing people on Kira's behalf.
He's bound to come here and bring the notebook with them.
And then he'll see me, and write down my real name.
Or rather, he'll write down the names of everyone
here knows about the notebook, and kill them.
Huh?
What?
What are you saying?
This doesn't make any sense.
What are you trying to tell us, Near?
That some other guy's going to drop by with
the notebook, poke his head in, and kill us all?
And you want us to sit back and let it happen?
Yes. That's correct.
Now, listen carefully.
If someone comes into the warehouse through that door,
just let him in without resisting.
If a door opens slightly,
simply act as if you don't notice anyone there.
But but that's just crazy!
He's already here.
God!
Delete!
Delete.
Delete. Delete. Delete. Delete. Delete.
Delete. Delete. Delete!
Delete. Delete. Delete. Delete!
Hold it! Don't do anything.
Everything is fine.
You won't die.
How can you be so sure, Near?
Because I modified the notebook.
Huh?
We took brief possession of the notebook
and replaced the pages.
The person behind the door has
been doing the killings for Kira.
He has also been using exactly one page every day.
Based on that, I was able to replace the page
he would use today, as well as all subsequent pages,
so that no one else would die.
Delete. Delete. Delete. Delete.
Delete.
Delete!
On the other side of that door is X Kira.
My guess is in roughly 40 seconds,
he'll look inside to see if we're dead.
That's when we'll restrain him and seize the notebook.
Whoever's name is not written down must be Kira.
It... It's true.
Kira would be the only one that guy wouldn't try to kill.
But still.
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it!
I knew all along you had tampered with the notebook.
Near, you've been completely defeated.
The notebook you altered was nothing
more than a forgery I had Mikami prepare.
On the other hand, the one Mikami is
writing their names in is the real notebook,
which had been kept hidden until now.
I had Mikami create a fake notebook for himself.
He also sent Takada several pages from the real one,
so in fact, it was Takada, not
Mikami, who was doing the killings.
As for Mikami, I had him write names in
public several times using the fake notebook.
That way he'd be noticed by anyone who was following him.
But Takada was the one behind the deaths.
Mikami simply sent the names and faces by cellphone.
This little performance was how I made the SPK
believe that the notebook Mikami used was the real one.
Mikami's daily behavior is so
methodical, it's almost obsessive.
He always fills exactly one page with names, every day.
And Near, you noticed this little habit and
though you could use it to tamper with the notebook.
All you had to do was count ahead to the
page he'd use on the day of this meeting.
Then you replaced all the pages from that day onwards.
You were confident you could prevent anyone from dying.
That was your big plan.
That's why you couldn't change
the date and time of our meeting.
But I was one step ahead of you, Near.
I always knew you were going
to try and alter the Death Note.
That's why I had Mikami check the
notebook every day for signs of tampering.
I've confirmed it.
I knew I'd won this game as soon as I got that message.
Mikami brought a different notebook today, the
real one, which had been kept hidden up until now.
But you know, Near, you did have a
chance to win, if only you'd taken it.
You were just too naive.
You're nothing compared to L.
L would have considered the possibility of a fake notebook
from the very beginning, and he would have tested it.
You had the chance, but you squandered it.
I've gotta say, I'm so disappointed in you.
This victory was no fun.
You tried too hard to win in a noble way.
Well, that's fine.
Everyone here dies today, thanks to you.
And as for me, I, Kira, will have my perfect victory.
You there, outside.
Huh?
Have you finished writing down the names in the notebook?
God.
Yes. I've written them.
No. I can't laugh yet.
I've got to hold it in.
They're all gonna die.
40 seconds after he wrote down their names.
35 seconds.
I'll claim my victory then.
Don't you think it's rather odd?
Hm?
Why would he answer you so quickly, calmly, and honestly
when you asked him if he had written down our names yet?
Who knows? Maybe he's just honest.
Or confident that he'll succeed or
perhaps he's seen through your brilliant plan.
Huh? In that case, we're in big trouble.
Teru Mikami.
If it's not too much trouble for you,
won't you please come in and join us?
I already know that you're the one who's
been judging and executing people for Kira.
If you've already written down our names,
then there shouldn't be anything to be afraid of.
You can come right on in.
Teru Mikami, is it?
He's correct.
There's no reason to hide from us. You can come in.
God.
You've done well, Mikami.
How many seconds has it been
since you wrote down the first name?
30 seconds.
31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39!
Well Near.
Looks like I win.
40!
That's right.
I am Kira.