I think we should do this every day.
The sun will do you good.
What in the world... am I supposed to do now?
Ah.
Mm.
Mmhm.
Hi, Ryuk.
Sidoh?
Wh... What are you doing here?
Hey. Quit following me.
I want my notebook.
Damn. Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
Too bad.
Things got a little complicated recently.
I have no idea where it is.
Why am I not surprised?
Look! I told you. Stop following me!
Then give me back my notebook.
I don't know where it is.
If you want it back, you're
gonna have to look for it yourself.
Moron.
Wammy's House isn't exactly a normal orphanage.
It's like a school for gifted children.
But here's the crazy part.
Its real purpose is to groom these kids
so that one of them could become the next L.
L's successor?
Apparently, the one most likely
to succeed L is this kid named Near.
Near. Is that N?
Also, we found some leads on Mello, the one N mentioned.
He's smart too, but he always came second to Near.
So Near was meant to be L's successor.
There's no mistake.
He has to be N. He's the one commanding the SPK.
As for Mello, he would've wanted to become L's successor,
but he probably lost out to Near.
That gives him a motive for wanting
to get his hands on the notebook first.
It all adds up perfectly.
This guy is definitely the
same Mello that N told us about.
These are sketches of both of them.
We couldn't find any photographs.
L's successors.
It looks like I'm still fighting L after all this time.
First thing's first.
I have to find out where Mello and his
mafia associates are hiding themselves.
I already had Misa check a list of known mafia syndicates
using her Shinigami eyes.
Look! I found him!
I can't see his lifespan.
He's number 105.
They have him listed as Jack Neylon,
but his real name is Kal Snydar.
He's got the notebook.
After that, it was a simple matter of using
the Death Note to make Snyder send a letter to me
with the location of the gang's hideout.
It should be arriving soon.
Hi Light!
Great news. The letter arrived.
He's in LA.
I did it.
I outmaneuvered both Near and Mello.
Guess it's no surprise.
As long as I have the notebook and Misa's eyes,
I'm unstoppable.
So, Light.
I guess this means I was helpful to you again, doesn't it?
Yeah.
I love you, Misa.
Los Ang... Ah... huh.
The next step is for me to figure out just
how much I can control people with this thing.
Aw. They're gonna have to be able to
see me before I can even talk to them.
What a drag.
Looks like Snyder's the owner right now.
Guess I'll have to make him touch the notebook first.
Oh well.
Tag, you're it.
The... uh, the notebook just flew.
Ha. It's a notebook that kills people.
Hell, nothing surprises me anymore.
Boss! Who is this?
The guy in the freaky costume? Who the hell is he?
Who brought him here?
I came here on my own. I'm actually a Shinigami.
A Shinigami?
If you don't want everyone to think you're crazy,
pass the notebook around, so they can see me too.
He says you can see him if you touch the notebook!
Please. Everyone touch it.
I swear I'm not crazy!
Fine, whatever.
Come on, guys.
Touch the notebook.
He wasn't there the last time I touched him!
Should I kill him?
Nice try.
You humans can't kill a Shinigami.
Jack's right.
That ain't no costume.
That's a real, live Shinigami.
So now what do we do?
Ryuk.
As of now, I'm going to forfeit
ownership of this notebook.
All I ask is that you agree to
follow whichever person I give it to.
What? You're giving up ownership again?
But wait.
Won't you lose all your memories if you do that?
Misa, lend me your notebook.
I'll keep it on me like this.
That way, even if I forfeit ownership
of my notebook, I won't lose my memory.
I'll give you as many pages as you need.
From this moment on, you're going to be Kira.
Can you do that?
Of course. But...
I don't get why you're doing this.
I'll explain everything to you right now.
I won't forgive any mistakes.
Chocolate is so good.
Hey. What about that stuff you told us? Is it true?
If the person using the note fails to
consecutively write names of people to be killed
within 13 days of each other, then the user will die.
If you make this note unusable
by tearing it up or burning it,
all the human who have touched
the note until then will die.
Are you saying those two rules are made up?
Oh yeah, those rules are definitely fake.
My guess is, some Shinigami wrote those down
as a joke before giving the notebook to a human.
As for the 13 day rule,
we can test that out by using one of our people.
But the real question is,
was this the notebook that was used by Kira?
And if so, was he aware that these two rules were false?
If he did know, he could've
used these rules to his advantage.
In particular, the 13 day rule would've
allowed him to prove his innocence in only 13 days.
Sidoh, go keep watch outside.
It'll be very convenient for us
that you can't be seen be humans.
Go outside and keep watch. Got it?
What's with this guy?
He's human, but he's scary.
Yagami speaking.
This is Kira.
What did he say? Kira?
I understand the notebook that was in your
possession has fallen into criminal hands.
Can... Can you prove that you are the real Kira?
Prove it?
Now that there are others using the notebook,
there's no point predicting
killings in order to identify myself.
They could just as easily kill the same targets.
But don't worry.
I've already taken this into account.
I've sent you something that will
clearly prove to you that I am Kira.
It's my own notebook.
Wha... What do you mean?
The notebook I've sent you gives me the power
to know a person's name by seeing only their face,
and you will be able to gain that same power.
Do you understand?
Please stay calm and listen carefully.
I've gathered information from the FBI and other sources.
On November 10 at exactly 11:59 PM,
arrangements have been so that all
known associates of the mafia will die.
It's already been written in my notebook,
so it's impossible for me to make any changes.
You will not be able to prevent these deaths.
I already know their location.
I will hand over that information
along with the notebook, so remember.
November 10th, 11:59 PM.
That's when it all happens.
That moment is your best and only
chance to get the notebook back.
It's up to you.
What should we do?
If the mafia members are going
to die on the day Kira specified,
it would be a chance to get the notebook back.
I don't like the idea of following
Kira's plan, but it's our best option.
Exactly.
But still, knowing the time of death for these
guys isn't going to be enough for us to make our move.
Ide, I think we both know what needs to be done.
We get the Shinigami to follow us in,
and... and then we do the deal for the
eyes, and make sure they're all dead. Right?
I will make the deal for the eyes.
No way, Chief. Let me be the one to do it.
I was responsible for handing
over the notebook in the first place.
Since that moment, I've been
unable to live with what I've done.
I've even thought of killing myself.
I'll use the notebook to kill
any criminals who try to stop this.
And then, after 13 days, I'll die as well.
If Dad writes a name in the notebook, then,
when the time comes...
Report.
Is everybody ready to move in?
Roger.
All right.
Deputy director, make the eye deal with the Shinigami.
All right, Ryuk. I'm ready.
Sure thing, boss.
Once you're finished,
I want you to take a look at the
photographs of the criminals I gave you.
Can you see their names and lifespans?
Yes. I can.
Their names should disappear soon.
That's your cue.
Everyone, move in!
So, Kira is involved after all.
I didn't think he'd go this far.
My plan was supposed to be perfect.
Damn! What the hell is Sidoh doing?
Relax, Sidoh. Just shut up and watch, all right?
All you have to do is sit here and do nothing.
If you can do that, you'll get your notebook back.
Roy, Skiier, the notebook's under Rod's body.
Bring it to the surveillance room upstairs.
Don't move!
L, we apprehended two of the criminals.
We've also been able to secure the notebook.
We'll begin withdrawing now.
Not yet. Keep going.
Huh? What?
We still haven't found anyone
who resembles our picture of Mello.
That means he must be hiding somewhere in the building.
We've come this far.
Let's finish this. Do a thorough search.
Ah!
What was that?
An explosion.
Don't move.
I've already blown up the two entrances to this place.
This will be your only warning.
The next explosion will take out the entire
building, as well as all your men inside.
So you'd better do as I say.
It's Mello.
Hm?
Yagami again, huh?
Maybe I should have killed you when I had the chance.
History repeats itself,
but I never dreamed in a million years
I'd be bargaining for the notebook with you again.
MIHAEL KEEHL.
Your real name.
It's Mihael Keehl.
What the hell? How did he...
I did it.
It's over, Mello.
It's time to turn yourself in.
If you give up, I won't kill you.
You have my word on that.
What are you doing?
Don't be stupid. Write his name down and kill him! Now!
You know how this works.
I write your name, and you will die.
Let go of that trigger and put your hands in the air.
Yagami...
Don't move!
I've written your first name, and it will
only take me a second to write your surname.
You idiot! Just write it!
Kill him!
I'm truly sorry.
For what it's worth, I give you my
word that I never wanted to kill you.
Hm?
But tell me, Yagami,
you've never killed someone before, have you?
Gunfire?
What was that?
Jose! The notebook!
Damn!
This guy he won't let go of the thing.
Son of a...
Hm?
Deputy Director!
It's all over, Mello!
Put your hands up and surrender!
Matsuda! Are you all right?
No. I don't think so.
I'm sure you'll live.
L, I don't see any sign of Mello.
Dammit. After all that, he got away?
That's why you should have just killed him.
Come on! Please, Dad!
You can't die on me like this.
Light.
Yeah, Dad?
Thank goodness.
You'll be fine. It's OK.
Light.
I still have them.
I still have the Shinigami eyes.
According to that Shinigami, Ryuk,
I can't see the lifespan of someone who owns a notebook.
But I can see the numbers above your head.
Light, you really aren't Kira.
I'm so glad, my son.
Don't tell me you're still worried about that, Chief.
Of course he's not Kira.
Come on.
You shouldn't talk so much, Dad.
That's important,
but I've got bigger things to deal with right now.
I've got to get him to write Mello's name in the notebook.
I... I'm so sorry, but in the end, I couldn't do it.
I couldn't bring myself to kill him.
I can't just come out and say, it's not too late.
No. Wait, maybe I can.
It all depends on how I do it.
No one will think it's weird if I get upset and panic.
Come on.
Dad, write his name.
You can't let him beat you like this.
Write his name down!
With your last bit of strength.
Do you want to die in vain?
D... Dad, no!
Light...
I'm sorry for your loss.
Dad.
Wake up!
Come on, damn it!
Don't you die on me, you idiot!
Dad!
You are the Shinigami who came here
to take back this notebook, aren't you?
Yes.
The notebook might be helpful to the Kira investigation,
but we really only need one of them.
I'll give this one back to you.
Humans who use the notebook are
cursed with fear, pain, and misery.
Of course, Soichiro didn't use the notebook.
He got to die believing that his son wasn't Kira.
I guess that means he was happy.
If Kira gets caught, then he is evil.
If Kira rules the world, then he is justice.
From now on, the world will
start leaning in favor of Kira.
Kira will be justice.