Light, there's another message from the second Kira.
It was sent to Sakura TV and we intercepted it.
I'm told it's a video and a journal this time.
Anyway, I figured I should tell you.
A journal?
What is that idiot up to now?
Why can't he just wait?
He wanted the journal shown on TV?
Yes. This is it.
Hmm.
2006?
These entries are from last year.
Please take a look at the entry he made on the 30th.
Hmm.
"Confirmed our shinigami at the Tokyo Dome."
This is probably supposed to mean
that he plans to do this on May 30th.
If this were aired on TV, his intentions
would be obvious to anyone who sees it.
Besides, he can't see my shinigami
unless he touches my Death Note.
How's he planning to do that?
Hey, Rem?
Hmm?
I forget.
Why can't I see my own lifespan
even though I have shinigami eyes?
Do you think you could tell me again?
Humans with shinigami eyes only need
to know the lifespan of their victims.
And just as we can't see the
lifespan of others of our kind,
humans who possess a Death Note cannot see
each other's lifespan, even with the eyes.
Hmm.
May 22nd.
My friend and I showed off our notebooks in Aoyama.
If by "notebooks" he's referring to our Death Notes,
that's something that could only be understood by me.
And as for the police, they'll be
distracted by the May 30th entry.
We confirmed our shinigami at
the baseball game in the Tokyo Dome.
It must've been intended for them.
I'm almost positive that the real message from this diary
is the one regarding Aoyama.
But if that's the case...
What do you think? Is it real?
I have to be careful not to say too much.
Better to wait and hear his opinion, first.
At this point in time,
all I can say for sure is, he must be stupid.
Yeah, I agree.
I mean it's completely obvious he
wants to meet Kira at the home game.
Doesn't he understand what would
happen if we aired this message?
It would create an immediate panic,
and the game would have to be canceled.
To be honest, it's so stupid,
I'm not even sure how to deal
with this whole situation anymore.
If we make the diary public,
then we'll be forced to make some kind of
televised announcement canceling the game on the 30th.
But if we don't broadcast it, we can be
sure the second Kira won't do anything.
Won't canceling the game make him angry?
There's no telling what he'll do.
Frankly, that's not a big concern.
From what we've witnessed, it's safe to
say the second Kira admires the real one.
He gave his word to the Kira we invented
that he'd refrain from killing aimlessly.
I'm inclined to believe that.
I say we make it public,
and we air an announcement canceling the game.
At the same time we'll announce that, on May 30th,
we're going to set up checkpoints on
all roads leading to the Tokyo Dome.
And finally, we'll send a response from our invented Kira.
Something like, I understand,
and I agree to meet you there.
Ryuzaki, you don't honestly expect him to go there
if we set up checkpoints around the dome, do you?
I don't think that Kira would even consider it.
But it's possible the other one might.
It all depends on how stupid he really is.
However, assuming he's not actually the idiot we think is,
there could be another message hidden
in this diary, one that's not so obvious.
If there's a message here written in some code
that only people who have this
shinigami power can understand,
there'd be no way for me to decipher it.
Still, it would only make sense for us to look
into all the places that were mentioned in the journal.
Uh, 22nd, he's meeting a friend in Aoyama.
24th, meeting another friend in Shibuya.
We have to be prepared for the possibility
that all of our efforts will be fruitless.
Let's keep an eye out for people with notebooks in Aoyama
and people in clothing stores in Shibuya.
It's as I thought.
If this phony Kira slips up and gets apprehended,
at the very least I have to obtain his notebook.
And in the worst case, I may end
up having to kill everyone there.
All we can do is place more
surveillance cameras in Aoyama and Shibuya
in the hopes that we might capture somebody.
We should also arrange to have undercover
officers in both locations on these dates.
I should probably go to Aoyama and Shibuya
since I blend in with the crowd there, ya know?
I'll go, too.
But, Light
I'll be all right. Don't worry.
Aoyama and Shibuya are places I'd go anyway.
Not to mention, out of all of us,
I'd probably look the most natural
hanging out with Matsui there.
Besides, the second Kira will be there
looking for Kira, not for the police.
OK, we'll talk more about our trips tomorrow.
Sounds good, Light. See you tomorrow.
Careful getting home.
Uh?
It never fails.
The second I'm out the door, my phone starts ringing.
Yes?
It's Ryuzaki.
When you two are working together,
I want you to keep a close eye on Light the entire time.
And please keep this between you and me.
Uh, sure.
Yeah, I understand.
I guess he still plans to investigate Light
until the probability that he's Kira reaches zero.
I'm home.
Hello, dear. You're back quite late today.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to keep the fact that I'm
helping with the Kira investigation a secret.
Uh, It's because I was hanging out my girlfriend.
Your?
What?
Light, you have a girlfriend, now?
What's her name?
It's not that surprising.
I'm 18 and I'm in university now.
Of course I have a girlfriend.
You should look for a boyfriend, Sayu.
Huh? A boyfriend? What's that supposed to mean?
Light, aren't you going to have any dinner?
Actually, I'm still full from room service at the hotel.
I can't believe you just said that to Mom.
So what's this about a hotel? Sounds pretty suspicious.
OK, Ryuk.
We need to have a little talk.
Ah, should've known.
And I'd appreciate an answer, if you could.
If two shinigami happen to meet in the human world,
are they allowed to speak to each other?
Hard to say.
As long as I'm attached to a human,
I'd say it's against the rules,
unless I had their permission, first.
But there's no laws against it either,
so I guess it's possible that
another shinigami might talk to me.
So does that mean that if this
fake Kira's shinigami were to see you,
there's a chance he might mention the fact
that you're with me and reveal that I'm Kira?
They probably wouldn't, but
it depends on their personality.
And if this kind of situation did arise,
I can assume that you'll act the way you normally do?
Yeah.
Even if I see another human with a shinigami,
I'm not going to tell you.
Well, I definitely think you've got the right approach.
Meh. Thanks.
Huh?
There's no way.
Did he really think this far ahead?
What is it?
Aoyama is a big area.
I was searching for possible meeting
places when I stumbled across this.
On the 22nd, there's a big event going on
at a club in Aoyama called the Note Blue.
"Aoyama" "blue mountain".
"Note" and "blue", it's a code.
Well, well. If you ask me, that's pretty elaborate.
He might be smarter than I thought.
Which means I'll have to be
that much more careful from now on.
In any case, this Note Blue place
is definitely worth checking out.
What's the point in going there if you
don't want him to find out that you're Kira?
You really think it's worth the risk?
Uh, excuse me, Light?
So what's going on here?
Oh. These are some of my friends from school.
Nice to meet you.
This is my cousin, Taro.
It's his first time ever in Tokyo,
and he wants to see Aoyama and Roppongi,
so I figured the least we
could do is show him a good time.
I'm counting on you guys.
Oh, yeah. He also told me he's looking for a girlfriend,
so does anyone want to volunteer?
Hey, I never said that.
I'm impressed, Light.
I doubt that anyone would ever suspect that there was
a police detective hanging around with these students.
With all of us walking together
like this, even if Ryuk is seen,
no one would be able to tell
which one of us he's following.
It's also a defense against L's surveillance cameras.
Not such a bad way to investigate, really.
I just have so stay relaxed
and keep an eye on the entrance
of the Note Blue when it opens.
Found you!
Moon Yagami, is it?
You're the only one whose lifespan I can't see.
He's Kira.
I can't believe it.
I never thought it would be this easy to find him.
All right, Rem. Time to go.
Huh.
You finally found him and now you just want to leave?
Well, I can't go up to him and say,
"Hi, Kira! Nice to meet you. I'm
the one who sent you the messages,"
with all these people around.
I know his name now, so I can
easily find out all about him.
After all, it's such a unique name.
Ohh, It's written as "Moon" but read as "Light."
Light Yagami.
He sure is amazing. Look at all this stuff.
He won the national tennis championship when he
was in his second and third years of junior high.
He gave an address as freshman representative at
this year's entrance ceremony at To-Oh University.
I can't find a picture of him, but there won't
be anyone else with a name like Light Yagami.
Who would've ever thought that
Kira would be so young and handsome?
Everything about him is better than I imagined.
I can't believe how easy it
was to purchase this information.
The world sure is a scary place.
I even know his home address now.
So we were there both days,
in Aoyama on the 22nd and Shibuya on the 24th,
and we observed nothing of
significance on either occasion.
That leaves us with only the Dome on the 30th.
I didn't notice anyone who
looked suspicious at the Note Blue.
Was he serious about the Dome?
Ryuzaki, apparently Sakura TV has just
received another message from the second Kira.
It was postmarked on the 23rd.
I'm happy to say that I have found Kira.
To all the people at the television
station and the police department,
I'd like to thank you very much.
Huh?
Im... Impossible!
Where, in Aoyama?
His shinigami.
It must have seen Ryuk and picked me out of the crowd.
No!
No, there's no way he could've
known who Ryuk was attached to.
I checked repeatedly that no one was following me.
If this is true, the only possible event
that would correspond with
this tape being mailed on the 23rd
is the entry regarding Aoyama on the 22nd.
The only ones from the task force who
went to Aoyama are Matsuda and Light Yagami.
Is Light really Kira after all?
Still, there's no proof it even happened in Aoyama.
This is a disaster if he found him.
Yeah.
It most likely means that the two
Kiras are now cooperating with each other.
At this point, I don't think we
should jump to any conclusions.
The second Kira is only saying
that he found him, nothing more.
He may not have made contact yet.
Now that it's come to this...
we have no choice but to communicate as
the police directly with the second Kira.
You want to send a message?
Yes.
The police need to reach out to
the copycat and offer him a deal.
We need to negotiate with him to
see if we can get Kira's real name.
That's the last thing you wanted to hear, right?
This isn't good.
I have no idea how the fake Kira will react to this.
But I have no means of stopping
the police from sending this message.
If Kira doesn't yet know your name,
it may not be too late for you,
provided you are willing to cooperate.
Whatever you do, you must not
approach Kira out of curiosity.
Make no mistake Kira will kill you if you contact him.
You'll be used and disposed of.
Consider your own life for a moment.
Yours, like every other life, has an intrinsic value.
Now is your chance to right past wrongs
by sharing what you know about Kira.
Only you can help us bring his reign of terror to an end.
Hmm.
Where are you going?
To introduce myself.
So this is what you meant.
Oh. Could that be your father?
Coming!
Welcome ho....
uh, hi.
Hello and good evening.
My name is Misa Amane.
I just came by to give Light an important
notebook he left at school earlier today.
Could you wait here for a second?
Light!
Notebook?
Could it be?
Um, pleased to meet you.
I'm Misa Amane.
I thought you might get worried
if you saw that message on TV.
I just couldn't take it anymore,
so I brought this notebook.
A Death Note.
A shinigami.
She's the fake Kira.
Please, come in.
Are you sure it's OK?
Thanks.
Mom, she came all this way to return my notebook.
Could you make us some tea?
Sure, I don't see why not.
Hmm?
I already told you about her.
Have a seat.
Oh. Um, thank you.
How did you find me?
I knew it.
You never made the shinigami eye deal.
When you have the shinigami eyes like I do,
you can see most people's name
and lifespan just by looking at them.
However, you can't see the lifespan of
any person who possesses a Death Note.
No kidding.
I have to admit, even I wasn't
aware of that little detail.
Well, now you've managed to find me.
But you were careless.
What if you were caught by the police?
Then they'd know everything about Kira.
It's all right.
Because the police didn't catch me,
and if I do as you say from now on,
they'll never be able to.
So we're safe.
After all, don't you need someone to see L's name?
If you want, I could be your eyes.
So
Yeah?
So what?
Would you please make me your girlfriend?
Girlfriend?
Yes.
If she finds out I'm manipulating her
and gets hurt, she'll probably kill me.
But still...
Impossible.
The day that you and I were in Aoyama,
there were three times the usual
number of surveillance cameras around.
Anyone who was in Aoyama on the 22nd would've
definitely been caught on camera that includes me.
If you and I were seen together,
it wouldn't look very good.
In fact, even being here together right now is a problem.
I wish you'd understand that.
But look these are pictures of
me when I went to Aoyama that day.
Well, I'm sure no one would recognize her from this.
And what about your fingerprints?
All those tapes you sent to the TV station.
They all had the same fingerprints on them.
Yeah, but those aren't my fingerprints.
It's not like I do these things
without thinking about them first.
Up until recently, I lived in the Kansai region,
and I had this friend who was into the occult.
I suggested that we distribute this fake poltergeist video
I had made to a bunch of different TV shows,
sort of as a prank.
And she agreed to help me with it.
I had her take care of all of the dubbing
so my fingerprints wouldn't be on the tapes.
Then I took them from her added the Kira graphic
and recorded the message with that voice effect.
And this friend you made the tapes with, where is she now?
Why are you doing this to me?
If you want me to kill her, just say so and I'll kill her!
If you really still can't trust me, then here.
I'll even let you hold onto my Death Note.
But you'd just be holding it.
So I'd still be the rightful owner of it
and that means I get to keep my shinigami eyes.
Isn't that right, Rem?
Yes, that's right.
Now there's no way I could possibly kill you.
And if I become a burden to
you, then you can just kill me, OK?
Why would she go this far?
But you might have removed
several pages from your Death Note.
You could be hiding them somewhere for all I know.
Why are you so suspicious of me?
I already told you, I don't
care even if all you do is use me.
Believe me.
How can you say that?
Exactly one year ago, my parents were killed in a robbery.
I was home with them at the time.
It happened right in front of me.
I wanted that man to pay for what he did.
But the trial dragged on forever.
Opinion started surfacing that
he was being falsely accused.
Then it happened.
Kira punished him for what he did to my parents.
And that's why Kira means everything.
Kira means everything to me.
All I... All I wanted was a chance to meet you one day,
so I could thank you for what you did.
So all these irrational moves, they
were just a means for her to meet Kira.
Still, she got around the surveillance cameras with ease
and managed not to leave her fingerprints on the evidence.
She's not as stupid as I thought.
And she has promised to obey me from now on.
I understand.
I can't be your boyfriend, but I can act like it.
The lengths you went to meet me, to be of help to me.
Those eyes of yours that you
sacrificed half your life to get
will become my weapon.
Thank you so much.
I'll try my hardest to make you love me, I promise.
That's good to know, Ryuzaki. I
also consider you a close friend.
It'd be a shame if you no longer came to university.
I was looking forward to playing
tennis against you one last time.
L will die. That's all it took.