The second L and the person I
think is Kira can only be one man.
Light Yagami.
This is Kiyomi Takada from News 6.
I have an announcement that comes directly from Kira.
His words are to become the new law of the world.
I just had an idea.
I think we can make use of Kiyomi Takada.
Please excuse me.
Kira!
He's removing the bugs?
We don't have a choice.
Listen, Kiyomi.
I am the real Kira.
Light is Kira?
All the pieces have fallen into place.
Now that things have come this far,
it's my turn to go to Japan.
Commander Rester.
Yes.
I'm afraid I need you to return to New York immediately.
Right now?
Yes. I'm intending to go to Japan.
All right.
So you would like me to stay
in New York while you're gone?
Not at all.
Then what's the point of me coming back there?
Truth is, I've never made travel arrangements
or boarded a flight on my own before.
That's why I need you to come back.
So you can escort me.
Understood.
We got him.
Both Yoshida Productions and
NHN are practically begging us now.
The great Misa Misa comeback plan is a huge success.
These days, it's nearly impossible for anyone
to get into NHN, but this will get us full access.
Yeah, that's right.
Mogi will be gaining entry as Misa's manager.
It'll definitely be to our advantage
to have someone who can go in and out freely.
In the meantime, I'll continue investigating Takada.
This is Near. I want to speak to L.
This is L. What is you want from us?
I'm following through with my goal to arrest Kira.
And that's why I'm Japan now.
He's in Japan?
Why tell me?
He's up to something.
L. I presume you've already contacted Takada
for the purposes of your own investigation.
That's right.
In fact, I'm investigating her myself at the moment.
I see.
For the time being, it's a given that, if
we want to get any closer to capturing Kira,
we'll have to keep an eye on
Kiyomi Takada and NHN in general.
I want you to pass on a message.
Inform her that, as of now, several SPK members
have entered Japan in order to catch and arrest Kira.
But why do that?
To lure Kira out of hiding.
I also want you to mention the following
to her so she'll relay it to Kira.
In total, there are only four active members of the SPK.
That includes myself.
Kira won't be able to resist such an opportunity.
Knowing him, he won't run.
Instead, he'll try to kill us before we get too close.
That's where I'll beat him at his own game.
Beat me at my own game, huh?
All right, Near.
If that's how you want it, I'll accept your challenge.
I am in Japan as we speak.
I am in Japan as well.
Then we'll be quite close to each other.
Who knows? We might even have
the chance to meet face to face.
I hope so.
Well, that'll be something to look forward to.
Yes.
When that time comes, we'll finish
this Kira matter once and for all.
Definitely.
It's all becoming clear to me.
From the very beginning, and even now,
it's been a one on one fight against L.
And even though he's dead,
the battle's just shifted to his heirs.
Very well, Near. Fine.
I'll come out to play if you will.
It's only fair, after all.
And when we meet, we'll find out which of us is
truly prepared to win, and whose wits will prevail.
When that happens, this long battle will end
and I can finally begin my reign at the top.
First, let's review what we know so far.
L is Light Yagami, and he's also Kira.
For now, we'll call him L Kira.
There's also another one.
Someone who has the notebook and is currently using it.
We'll call him X Kira.
Judging by the pattern of X Kira's killings,
he has definitely made the deal
and acquired the Shinigami eyes.
L Kira and X Kira can't communicate directly.
They must be planning to communicate
using Takada as a go between.
So, given the situation as it now stands,
there are two ways to win against Kira.
One, the simple way.
We arrange to kill both L Kira and X Kira
and confiscate the notebook.
However, no matter what might happen,
we will never resort to that.
Why not?
That's not the way we work, Commander.
We, sir?
Yes, that's right.
We kill those two and the murders stop.
Such ex post facto justification will not be tolerated.
That's not the way L and I do things,
because that would be an insult.
Don't forget, L entrusted this
case to those who came after him.
So, Kiyomi.
I heard on the news the other day that you
receive an enormous amount of fan mail every day.
Yes.
I'm told on average it's about 200 letters a day.
200 letters?
Wow, I'm a little jealous.
Man, this is kind of boring listening
to audio only without any video feed.
I think you should look through them,
even if they are just letters from fans.
You're right.
Keep calm as you read this note and the ones that follow.
Make sure not to let the people listening
to this conversation hear your reactions.
The SPK has started to make its move.
You have to start thinking about your safety.
Instead of accepting messages from Kira,
maybe you should consider
making a few demands of your own.
Light's getting down to business.
You shouldn't only be a spokesperson.
Your voice should be heard as well.
Reach out to Kira.
Tell him what you think he needs to know.
I have a different job for T.
In order to create the perfect
world that Kira has envisioned,
I want you to begin judging and punishing people as Kira.
It's all right, Kiyomi.
I have faith in you.
It's gonna be OK.
If you can do this,
I'm sure you'll be able to send Kira information
that you don't want the SPK to know about.
All right. I'll do it.
We nailed it.
That's our Light for you.
He's good.
Delete.
Kiyomi Takada.
Hm.
Yes?
I have an important message for you.
You are to send me a fan letter that
I'll be able to recognize as yours.
You will also enclose something else in the envelope.
Five blank pages from the notebook.
Carry on with your judgements and killings as
usual until I receive the letter and the pages.
And how about after you receive them?
You have to stop using the real notebook.
However, you must continue
entering names in a fake notebook.
A fake?
That's right.
Make a notebook that looks as
close to the original as possible,
and act as if you're killing people by using this decoy.
I understand.
God. What are you planning?
No. It's not my place to question God.
His will is absolute.
My job is to do what god wishes.
Huh? What's this?
It's a replacement for Kira's Kingdom.
God, what's wrong with these people?
Welcome to the show.
Today, Ms. Takada will introduce
her four new female bodyguards,
who were selected after a rigorous screening process.
The first is the winner of the
22nd World Karate Championships,
Miss Tatsumi Oyama.
The second is a former CIA agent, Ms. Halle Lidner.
If there is an SPK member among these
bodyguards, it would have to be Halle Lidner.
Looks like Near's conducting
his own investigation of Takada.
A phantom killer who stabbed six people in
Shinjuku's busy quarters was apprehended...
Who I chose to be X Kira?
Out of all the people in the world?
...educating our children about the existence of Kira
and the meaning of his teachings must be made mandatory.
Above all, we must teach our children that Kira is good.
Takada was chosen because
she's a strong supporter of Kira.
So, that means X Kira must be someone
who knew they Takada was a Kira worshipper.
Someone who had a close, intimate relationship with her
before her selection.
Also, Kira will not forgive
any crime, no matter how small.
From this point onwards,
you should assume that any
person alive is a viable target.
I'd like to hear Kira's voice.
I want to hear his thoughts once again.
We should follow his teachings, exactly as Kira ordered.
To me, it's obviously the
quickest path to lasting world peace.
Youth have a responsibility.
I think it is of the most importance that
young people do all they can to contribute.
It's our duty to improve our society.
If there are no words or orders from
Kira, then we have only one choice.
We need to think for ourselves.
We need to consider what Kira has taught us,
determine what he wants most, and
make our own decisions from there.
L Kira is Light Yagami.
Could X Kira be Teru Mikami?
Everything seems to fit into place.
That's what I've been asking.
So tell me why I'm not the headliner.
You said I was supposed to be the
highlight of the EastWest Pop Music Festival.
Well, it's true that you're the highlight,
but when it comes to the headliner,
it's a little harder to secure that spot.
Huh?
That's why we should be taking precautions.
Kiyomi Takada.
What an idiot.
She doesn't even realize that
Light's just using her for his investigation.
Don't say that.
You might end up dead if she hears you.
Duh, I know that.
That's why I whispered it quietly.
Hey!
She snickered at me!
I'm gonna go kick her!
Hang on!
What were you trying to do?
What was I doing? What about you?
Grr.
Lidner, that young lady is
actually a very good friend of mine.
Please, you shouldn't be so rough with her.
Hmph!
Of course, Miss Takada.
Please, excuse me.
Misa Misa, are you all right?
That was so frustrating!
L, this is Near.
I have a small request.
If Mr. Aizawa is there, would it be
possible for me to speak to him for a moment?
Near, this is Aizawa. What is it?
I have a question regarding
surveillance for L and Takada's meetings.
Are you recording both audio and
video feed to their conversations?
Uh, no. Only an audio feed right now.
I see. Only wiretaps at the moment.
How interesting. Thank you very much.
If they're only using wiretaps,
then it's safe to assume that L Kira and X Kira
have found a way to contact each other through Takada.
Seems like Lidner could be in more danger than we realize.
We knew the risks getting into this.
To be blunt, what's important is that
L starts focusing his attention on Lidner and Takada.
In the meantime, we'll use the
opportunity to investigate Mikami further.
Hm.
How are things, Giovanni?
Well, about Mikami.
It's strange.
It's ridiculously easy to trail him.
He's not trying to hide, or anything.
He's lived at the same place the past four years.
There's nothing unusual about him.
He also seems to be totally
dedicated to his career as a prosecutor.
I'm beginning to think he can't be X Kira.
No. There is a very high
probability that Mikami is X Kira.
Please be very careful.
Don't enter his room yet.
Just keep watch over him for now.
Gotcha.
Man, how many meetings do I need to
have with NHN, for crying out loud?
And seriously, how many times do these people
have to tell me, be careful about what you say?
What's with that?
Yes. Yes, of course. I'll ask her right now.
Uh, listen. Misa Misa,
Takada would like to have dinner with you this evening.
Just the two of you.
Huh?
That Kiyomi.
What's she up to?
Good idea.
The music festival's MC
should have dinner with the main performer at least once.
Tell her OK.
Hm.
Hello?
Miss Takada?
She's accepted.
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, and Lidner?
Please book a nice, private room for us.
And also, I'd like you to attend the dinner as well.
Huh? Yes.
Misa, I'm sorry to have to invite
you to dinner so late at night.
I'm afraid it had to wait until
after the 9:00 news was finished
No problem. I don't mind at all.
I'm a night owl, anyway.
Well, what is it?
I'm not really sure how to answer a question like that.
So, Light must be pretty busy.
How do you two manage?
Why, you! She knows that I can't see him that much,
while she can be with him all the time.
How dare she?
Things are great between us.
Light is way more affectionate
than he looks. At least with me.
In fact, he starts clinging to me as
soon as he gets in the door every night.
Ah. I see.
It sounds like you're doing well.
Thank goodness.
Yes.
Actually, I should probably
tell you, since you are the MC.
I'm going to announce my engagement
to Light at the Pop Music Festival.
Does he know about this?
Of course he does. It's an engagement.
It's not as if I can get engaged to myself.
He proposed to me more than a month ago.
It was so romantic.
Don't you think it'd be exciting to
announce it at the Pop Music Festival, Miss MC?
Why not?
If you're able to, that is.
What do you mean, if I'm able to?
What, are you not going to let me announce it?
Or maybe it's something else.
Maybe you're going to get Kira to kill me.
Of course not.
Only Kira can decide who he's going to punish.
I have nothing to do with his decisions.
Besides, I've always thought
of you as a good friend, Misa.
You shouldn't say such terrible things.
Anyway, I don't have any intention of killing
anyone, no matter how horrible they might be.
Well, whatever.
I used to really like Kira too, you know?
But I know for sure that Light's going to catch him soon.
Oh, yeah.
Once he gets caught, it'll be
nothing but bad news for him.
And as for you, you'll probably be executed.
Miss Takada? Are you all right?
Huh?
Listen, Kiyomi.
I am the real Kira.
Please, join me, Kiyomi,
and you will be the goddess of the new world.
Miss Amane?
Yes?
I find this unpleasant.
Hmph! Oh, yeah? I feel the same!
Obviously, this was a bad idea.
I should've waited until you grew up and learned
a few minutes before I invited you to dinner.
I suppose I'll know better next time.
Goodbye.
Oh?
I'm older than you, Kiyomi.
And anyways, you're being childish
for storming out in the middle of diner
over a silly little comment!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Hey, Motchi!
Thanks for waiting, Motchi!
How are you?
A...A... Are you OK?
Of course I am.
I won, after all.
Won?
Yeah. It was easy.
About tonight's meeting between Takada and Amane.
They just talked about Light Yagami.
If you read between the lines, they
were arguing over which one was his lover.
Your thoughts?
All I can determine is this.
Light Yagami is popular with the ladies,
and we know that Takada and Amane both adore him.
Near, please be serious about this.
It is serious if they're both truly in love with him.
They will not easily betray him.
In fact, they'll likely do whatever he asks.
Please stop.
Aw, come on now, lady.
I mean, wearing a short skirt like that in the winter?
It's an invitation.
Please. Someone!
Hm?
Cell phone?
Mikami's just taken out a notebook.
Delete.
He's writing something in it.
Could that be it?
He's getting off the train.
Mikami started talking to himself.
He seems to have reacted to
the scrap of paper at his feet.
He's gone into the gym.
I've entered the locker room.
I'm opening the lock on his briefcase.
I'm going to touch the notebook.