Ryuzaki.
Is something the matter? What is it?
Hm?
What's wrong?
Hm. Interesting.
The corner of the page of this notebook has been torn off.
Can you kill someone just by
writing their name on a piece?
Can't say.
I've never tried using it like that,
and I don't know of anyone who has.
Then let me ask you. Do gods of death love apples?
Not necessarily.
You see, our internal organs have already degraded.
We've evolved to a point where
we do not require sustenance.
Say, Light.
You're finally free to leave headquarters on
your own, but it seems like you never go out.
Even when Misa comes to visit, you only
chat with her for a few minutes outside.
You do realize you're free to
have a relationship with her now?
That can wait until we've managed to solve this case.
I'm not in the mood for love or anything else right now.
Anyway, are you suggesting that
I'll be a nuisance for staying here?
No.
Right now, I'm in no position
to continue punishing criminals.
That's why I need you to punish them for me.
Misa.
Let's create a new world together.
Careful what you do,
'cause God is watching your every move.
Hold my hand in the dark street.
For if you do, I know that I'll be safe.
Even if I'm far away and alone,
I can be sure that you'll find me there.
This I know.
You draw me close for a while. So quiet.
You tell me everything.
If I forget what you say, then you'd come to me
and tell me again.
Yes, you'd tell me once again.
But what happens when I know it all?
Then what should I do after that?
What then?
What's going on?
I heard criminals are being killed again.
There were 16 deaths just yesterday.
All of them were broadcast after Higuchi's death.
Immediately after, huh?
Do you think this could mean that
Higuchi wasn't necessarily Kira after all?
No.
It's safe to say that Higuchi was the one
killing criminals until we apprehended him.
Then this means we're dealing with yet another Kira.
Aw, man! Not again!
Damn. Damn you, Kira.
Another Kira's appeared? What's going on here?
I can't believe this.
It has to be Misa.
These killings began as soon
as Misa was free, didn't they?
Ryuzaki, are you still going on about that?
She has nothing to do with this.
Think about it.
This started as soon as Higuchi died.
I suppose you're right.
Oh, well.
If there is another notebook floating around out
there and someone is now using it to kill criminals,
I'll just have to bring that person to justice.
The Shinigami insisted that it didn't know,
but if someone were able to kill simply by
writing a name on a torn piece of the notebook.
It's not impossible, but there's that rule.
Whoever writes a name in this notebook
has to write another name within 13 days.
Otherwise, they die.
Light Yagami and Misa Amane are both still alive.
13 days.
That's the only problem.
Ryuzaki, I've been thinking,
even if we do manage to catch the person
who's been writing names in the notebook,
will we really be able to legally
convict and punish them for mass homicide?
What?
Of course we can convict them.
This guy's intentionally writing names in the
notebook, knowing that these people are going to die.
Even if we don't plan on publicly acknowledging the
notebook, the least we can do is execute the killer.
It's not a very humane way to do things,
but the higher-ups would probably
want to take measures like that.
If they admit to killing with the notebook, they'd
receive the death penalty, or life in prison, at least.
That's the best that they could hope for.
What are you thinking, Light Yagami,
making Misa kill again?
She'll be caught, and once that happens, you'll also be...
So that's what your plan is.
You're truly disgusting.
Light Yagami is certain that I will do
anything to help Misa and save her life.
And at this point, the only way for me to save
Misa is to write Ryuzaki's real name in my notebook.
And if I kill Ryuzaki,
it would mean that I deliberately lengthened Misa's life,
and I will die as well.
Light Yagami has planned everything
so that it will work out in his favor.
What are you gonna do, Rem?
You may be a Shinigami, but you can't
hide the fact that you care for Misa.
There's no way you would turn your back on her
now, after she's already halved her lifespan twice.
Come on.
Think about Misa's happiness.
What are you doing, standing out there by yourself?
What are you doing standing out there by yourself?
What are you doing, Ryuzaki?
Oh, I'm not doing anything in particular. It's just...
I hear the bell.
The bell?
Yes.
The sound of the bell is being unusually loud today.
Hm?
I don't hear anything.
Really? You can't hear it?
It's been ringing nonstop all day.
I find it very distracting.
I wonder if it's a church?
Maybe a wedding, or perhaps a...
What are you getting at, Ryuzaki?
Come on, cut it out. Let's get back inside.
I'm sorry.
Nothing I say makes any sense, anyway.
If I were you, I wouldn't believe any of it.
You know, you're totally right.
Honestly, most of the things you
say sound like complete nonsense.
There'd be no end to my troubles if I
actually took you seriously all the time.
I probably know that better than anyone.
Yes.
I would say that's a fair assessment.
But... I could say the same about you.
Hm?
What's that supposed to mean?
Tell me, Light, from the moment you were born,
has there ever been a point where
you've actually told the truth?
Where's this coming from, Ryuzaki?
I do admit, I stretch the truth here and there.
However, find me one person in this
world who's never had to tell a lie.
It wouldn't be easy.
Human beings just aren't made to be perfect like that.
Everybody lies from time to time.
Even so, I've always made a conscious effort to
be careful not to tell a lie that could hurt others.
That's my answer.
I had a feeling you'd say something like that.
Let's go back inside.
We're both drenched.
Yeah.
Well, that was certainly an unpleasant outing.
It's your own fault.
I mean, what did you expect?
You're right.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
I thought I might help you out.
You were busy wiping yourself off, anyway.
Look, it's fine. You don't have to do that.
I can give you a massage, as well.
It's the least I can do to atone for my sins.
I'm actually pretty good at this.
Fine. Do what you want.
All right.
Hey.
You'll get used to it.
Here. You're still soaked.
I'm sorry.
It'll be lonely, won't it?
Hm?
You and I will be parting ways soon.
Yes?
I understand.
I'm on my way.
Huh?
Come on. Let's go, Light.
It seems like it's all worked out.
Hm?
Ryuzaki. What's the meaning of all this?
You've somehow gotten approval from another
country to use the notebook for an execution?
Watari.
Excellent work. Thank you.
Not at all.
First things first.
Please make arrangements to
transport the notebook immediately.
Right.
Ryuzaki, what are you trying to do?
I'm going to try out the notebook for real.
We can't do that!
And there's no point in testing it now when
we already know the notebook's power is real.
And besides, who's gonna write the name?
If someone starts writing in the notebook,
they'll have to obey the 13 day rule,
and keep writing names forever.
It's already been worked out.
The person who will write in the book is a
criminal scheduled to be executed is just over 13 days.
If he's still alive 13 days after writing
the name, he'll be pardoned from execution.
But still, to sacrifice a life...
We're very close.
If we work this out, the entire case will be solved.
What is this?
A... A blackout?
Watari?
Watari!
Data deletion?
What the hell's going on?
I told Watari to make sure that
he should erase all information
in the event that something were to happen to him.
If something were to happen?
Could it be...
Where is the Shinigami?
Good question. I don't see it.
It disappeared?
What's going on?
Everyone, the Shiniga...
Ryuzaki! What's wrong?
Hey, Ryuzaki.
Come on.
Snap out of it!
What happened?
What's going on?
Calm down, Light.
We're gonna die!
Watari, Ryuzaki. It'll be us next!
Damn you!
Where are you, Shinigami? Come out!
Wait, Light.
You know something about this, don't you?
Come on out!
We'd better go and look, too.
Right.
Mogi. Take over for me.
OK.
There's something here!
What the hell is this stuff?
Sand?
What does this mean?
Whatever it might mean, whatever happens next,
I swear I'll avenge Ryuzaki's death.
We're going to solve this case in honor of him,
and for Watari, and all the other victims.
Oh, Light.
Let's do this. For them.
Yeah, but aren't we all gonna get killed?
Isn't that what all this really means?
Matsuda.
If you're afraid of dying, then leave the investigation.
We put our lives on the line when we chose to be here.
Yeah. That's true.
But it... it's weird hearing you say that.
You sound like Ryuzaki.
I've gotten rid of everything in my way.
I am the GOD of the New World.
Ryuzaki, Watari, Rem.
I've gotten rid of everything in my way.
I am the GOD of the New World.