Quiet, Matsuda.
This is not the time to be fooling around.
Knock it off.
Yes, sir.
This is the Kira investigation.
Stop messing around!
Sorry, Aizawa.
Matsuda, please don't, Matsuda.
After all, the last thing I want is to be dead weight.
Ryuzaki, is there anything I can
do to help with the investigation,
besides the manager thing?
Could you get me another cup of coffee?
I want to help, too.
I want to contribute to the case.
I love you.
So please, don't tell me you're going home now.
Instead, say you'll stay by my side.
Uh, Mr. Director, I can't do this.
I have a boyfriend. Can we cut the love scenes, please?
Uhh...
Wait.
Where'd this come from all of a sudden?
Can't we just fake kiss or something?
What?
You're kidding.
You can't expect us to make a movie like that.
If I say no, then it's no.
OK?
Come on!
Come on.
Get rid of her. Fire her.
The Yotsuba Group's main Tokyo office.
And today is Friday.
All the death that are beneficial for
Yotsuba are concentrated around the weekends.
Hmm.
The last thing I want to be is dead weight.
Mogi's been incredibly efficient from the start.
Quiet, Matsuda!
This is not the time to be fooling around.
Would you cut it out?
That is his specialty.
And could you get me another cup of coffee?
Matsuda!
Matsu!
Hello, Matsu, get over here.
I guess he had to run off somewhere.
Oh.
Hmm.
All right.
For the time being, I want you
to start going over this list here.
Yes, sir. Right away.
Would I punish evildoers and criminals if
I could kill by just seeing a name and face?
Is that what I'd do if I had that sort of power?
I mean, it's true that there are lots of people
around that the world could frankly do without,
but I don't think I'd become a
murderer just to change the world.
Surely I wouldn't do that.
No, I'm thinking too hard about this.
There's no way anyone could murder so
many people and not have any memory of it.
What's wrong?
You've been staring at me for the last two minutes.
Wait, let me guess.
You must be annoyed because I'm the
only one eating cake at the moment.
Am I right?
Uh, no, that's not it.
Here.
Really, don't worry about it.
Hmm?
Ryuzaki.
Yes, what is it?
Detective Eraldo Coil has just received a private
request to investigate and reveal the identity of L.
Isn't Eraldo Coil supposed to be the second
greatest detective in the world after L himself?
Who on earth would send such a request?
The man who sought out Coil's services is Masahiko Kida,
the head of the Rights and Planning Department
of the Yotsuba Group's headquarters in Tokyo.
So it is Yotsuba.
We know that Yotsuba must be linked to Kira.
If they're trying to find out L's identity,
it's probably because they want to kill
him and need that information to do it.
This isn't good.
We're already shorthanded enough as it
is, and now we have to worry about Coil, too.
Mm, mm. It's quite all right.
The detective known as Eraldo Coil is me.
Oh?
It's quite simple, really.
Three of the greatest detectives in the world,
L, Coil, and Deneuve, they're all actually me.
It's been my experience that people
who try to find me usually fall for this.
I'll give you this strawberry if you keep it a secret, OK?
Mm.
I'm impressed as always, Ryuzaki.
Maybe I should leave while I still have a chance.
No, then there would have been no point in coming here.
Or should I wait until everyone's
gone and search their offices?
I can't. I'd probably get caught doing that, and then...
maybe I should get out of here.
Not this again.
I'm too tired.
Look on the bright side. At least it falls on the weekend.
We never know how long these
confidential meetings will go on far.
Can you imagine if we did this on Mondays?
That would be the worst start to the week.
Confidential meetings?
All right!
The 19th floor.
I've made it this far.
I'm gonna see it through.
All right.
I just have to get close to him, right?
Leave it to me.
And you want me to make sure that
we're able to breach the security
and override the surveillance cameras
in the Yosuba Group's head office.
Is that all?
Yes.
At this point, it's safe to assume that Kira
and the Yotsuba Group are connected in some way.
We're going to investigate Yotsuba
to determine who holds Kira's power
and if there is more than one
person who possesses this ability.
We need a clear understanding, quickly.
We cannot let anyone from Yotsuba
figure out that we are investigating them.
Please realize that if they do notice,
it means we won't be able to catch Kira.
Damn it, I can't hear them clearly.
If only I could hear just one thing, something important.
Kill him.
I just heard someone say kill!
I'm sure Kira would approve.
Kira!
There it is. Kira, they said it!
What's that?
Let's have Kira get rid of him?
I heard it!
They really are working with him.
I did it! This is huge!
Who the hell are you?
Please be sure not to act
impulsively out of panic or haste.
And don't take matters into your own hands.
Ryuzaki.
Yes, what is it?
I have just received an emergency
signal from Matsuda's belt.
Oh, where is he?
It seems that it's coming from within
the head office of the Yotsuba Group.
Uh, sorry to barge in like this.
Um, my name is Taro Matsui.
I'm an agent with Yoshida Productions.
I just dropped by to ask if your company would
be interested in using our top multi-talented star,
Misa Amane, as your new spokesperson...
Hmm.
Disregard everything I just said.
We'll need to rethink our strategy.
Matsuda, you idiot.
Yoshida Productions, Taro Matsui.
He doesn't have anything suspicious on him.
I suppose that means he isn't a corporate spy.
Right.
Um, so please take Misa-Misa into consideration.
These two were only acting as guards.
The rest of them must be
discussing how they'll get rid of me.
Oh, there's no way out of this!
I'm going to killed for sure.
I wonder if the emergency signal got through.
For never mind that.
Even if it did, will Ryuzaki come and save me?
Oh no, what's gonna happen?
Go ahead.
You can answer it.
Don't say that you're here, though.
And hold it away from your ear.
Make sure we can listen in on the conversation.
OK.
Hello?
Yo, Matsui!
Ryuzaki.
Oh.
Uh, it's me, Asahi.
It's been a while, buddy.
Asahi! Yeah, it's been a long time.
Ha, it doesn't sound like you're out right now.
Don't tell me you're home already.
Yeah.
So, you by yourself?
Yeah, I'm by myself.
What's up?
He's not with Misa Amane right now.
Matsuda must be on his own.
Hmm.
So, do you want to, like, go out drinking tonight?
Huh? Right now?
Oh, sorry, I'll have to pass tonight.
Ah, what's the matter?
Don't tell me your wallet is in trouble again.
In trouble.
Yeah, that's right, big troubles with money.
You know me way too well.
Matsuda's saying he's in big trouble.
Oh, that's too bad.
Guess I'll drag you out some other time, all right?
See you, buddy.
Uh.
Aanyway, what do you think about contracting Misa-Misa?
I think she'd be great spokesperson for your company.
Hmm.
If you're going to promote one of your clients,
shouldn't you at least bring them with you?
Do you expect us to believe your this girl's manager?
Well, to be honest, at the
moment, she's filming a movie nearby.
Once she's finished, I'll call her and get her over here.
Then you can see why she'd make a great spokesperson.
I have to keep stalling them somehow.
Misa's cell phone is on voicemail right now.
I left her a message and told her
to get back to me as soon as she can.
What are you planning to do, Ryuzaki?
Well, we have to consider that if Matsuda dies, our
suspicions about the Yotsuba Group would be confirmed.
Hmm.
Let's just watch the situation for the time being.
What should we do?
The main question is whether he heard anything.
If it's a possibility, no matter how small,
we'll have to kill him.
I'm wondering if he really did
come here just to promote his client.
He could be an undercover cop.
No, that can't be it.
The Japanese police have completely
withdrawn support from the Kira case.
Look, it doesn't really matter who he is.
We have no choice but to kill him.
Hmm.
You know, now that I think about it,
it might be good to have her as the face of our company.
Hmm?
Ah, exactly.
Her shoot should be done soon, so please wait.
She'll convince you.
Mm, I'm beat.
I got a call from Light!
He really does worry about me when I'm late.
Misa?
Light! I'm sorry I've been working so much.
I'll be finished soon, 'kay?
Misa, you're not with Matsuda at the moment, are you?
Him? He's a total jerk.
He just ran off and left me here.
Oh.
Hang on. I'm getting a call on my work phone.
Oh hey, it's from Matsu.
Misa's just received a call from Matsuda.
Tell her to hold her phone so
that we can listen in as well.
Misa-Misa, when you're finished filming,
come over to the Yotsuba Group head office.
It's still tentative,
but there's a chance you may be able
to appear in Yotsuba's commercials.
We're working it out now.
What? Are you for real?
You're amazing, Matsu!
So that's what you've been up to all this time!
Don't worry. We're wrapping up soon.
Great. It's just a short trip by taxi.
Huh?
Listen to me, Light.
There is a chance that we may be able to save Matsuda,
but we won't be able to do it without Misa's help.
She'll listen to you and do anything you say, won't she?
Uh...
I'm Misa-Misa.
My only rule is I don't do nudes, but
swimsuits and lingerie are totally OK.
It's really nice to meet you.
Hmm.
I gotta admit, she is really cute in person.
That's not exactly the main issue now, wouldn't you agree?
By the way, Matsu, since Yotsuba's a big catch,
I got the OK from our office to have a special reception.
Hmm?
Reception?
Good evening.
We're very pleased to meet you.
Tonight, I'll be entertaining you as our
special guest, along with the girls from the agency.
Hey, is it just me, or is this getting weird?
Hmm. Well, it can't be helped.
Right now, we can't afford to leave
Misa's manager alone for a second.
Let's just go with it. I'm going to enjoy myself.
All right.
Hard to go wrong with this.
Hmm.
Ryuzaki and the others will be able to watch us from here.
This is my way out.
Here you are. Drink right up.
Man, we gotta do this more often.
Hmm.
Well, well.
Misa's pretty good at this sort of thing.
Excuse me, guys.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
Hmm.
Ryuzaki, are you watching this?
Yes.
L... Look, I'm really sorry that I...
That's not important right now.
OK.
Listen, the eight men who came here
were having a meeting to determine
who they'd get Kira to kill for them.
Oh?
I heard them say it clearly.
There's no doubt they're behind this.
Yes, that is probably true.
But if you did overhear them, and they caught you,
then they'll almost certainly be trying to kill you now.
I know.
Do you think there's anything I can do to save myself?
Well, luckily, you're still
alive, so we may be able to save you.
But for that to happen,
you will have to die before they can kill you.
What?
I want you to listen to me very carefully.
No way.
But that's... that's crazy.
And you know our company is expanding.
Hey!
What the hell?
Who's that?
Wow, I am so drunk.
Huh?
Oh, h... hi, everyone.
Everyone having fun? Good.
That's great.
Now, everyone, the moment you've all been waiting for,
the Taro Matsui show!
Hey, what are you doing?
Yay!
You can do it! Go Matsu!
All right, here we go.
Uh...
Hey, you're drunk. That's way too dangerous.
Don't worry. I'm just fine.
I do this all the time.
What the hell are you doing?
Get in here!
Stop!
Are you crazy, you idiot?
It's all right.  No prob.
He fell!
This can't be good.
Ah, no!
I heard a thud, so I came out.
This is just horrible.
Someone call an ambulance!
Geez. This sure is a crappy role.
Look, everyone, I think you should all just
leave this for us to take care of and go home.
What?
But...
Don't worry. We'll handle it.
Just don't forget about me for your next campaign, OK?
Let's go.
If the press sees us, we're in trouble.
Yeah.
What's going on?
Did someone jump?
Well, we're lucky that he ended up
dying right in front of us, at any rate.
Hey.
Huh?
Mm.
While I'm aware of the fact that we're shorthanded,
I'm not very pleased about having
to do this sort of thing myself.
Matsuda, you idiot.
"Misa Amane's manager dies in fall."
Hmm.
Yes.
You're Masahiko Kida,
VP of the Rights and Planning Department
at Yotsuba's Tokyo office, correct?
Yes, that's right. And who am I speaking to?
I go by the name Eraldo Coil.
I'm calling to discuss my terms with you.
What?
A $2 million advance and $8 million upon completion?
Is he out of his mind?
That's not all.
Even if we don't commission him, we have to
pay him $2 million just to keep him silent.
So he wants hush money, huh?
If he's saying something like that, we
should assume Coil knows quite a bit already.
This it's getting ridiculous.
I've had it. I want out of these meetings right now.
I don't know who Kira is, and I don't care.
I just don't want to get wrapped
up in this and end up in jail!
No.
Huh?
Hatori, I think you are going to end up dead tomorrow.
No, wait. I was only joking. It's not like that.
I'm in. I'll see this to the end.
So what are we going to do?
Coil is still willing to accept the
job, despite what he already knows.
Isn't it obvious?
He'll become partners with us, as long as we pay him.
His demand are exorbitant, but we need to
have someone as skilled as Coil on our side.
Good point. Pay him.
It doesn't matter how much.
Exactly. We'll just have to pay him.
Uh?
All right, we'll contract Coil.
Anyone have any objections?
No objections.
L, are you listening?
I am To disappointed.
I thought this would be a challenge.
Security level here is a joke.
They've left it all to a single contractor.
There weren't even any wiretap detectors.
It's been about a week since I first snuck into the place.
It looks like things have been
moving pretty smoothly since then, huh?
We've almost got them.
So one of these people...
mm... mm... is Kira.
Well, then.
Now that everyone's here, let's
commence our regular meeting.
But if there's supposed to be
eight, why are there only seven?
Ryuzaki, you think I'm capable of becoming a murderer?
Kira?
Even after I helped you catch him?
Do I seem like that kind of person to you?