(BOKUTO heavy breathing)
[BOKUTO]
Akaashi...
[BOKUTO] Don't send it
to me anymore today!
(ALL sigh)
[AKAASHI] All right.
[BOKUTO] Huh?
[AKAASHI]
But while I'm not
sending any sets to you,
please try and chill out.
[DAICHI]
This is our chance, guys. It
looks like their ace is off his
game! Let's keep after 'em!
[KURASUNO]
Yeah!
[SARUKUI] All right!
(whistle)
[AKAASHI]
Well done, man. Nice.
[SARUKUI]
Yeah!
[BOKUTO]
Oh.
(FUKURODANI cheers)
[TAKEDA]
It might just be me...
But Fukurodani's really...
got it together?
[KEISHIN]
Yeah.
[AKAASHI]
Chance ball!
[KOMI]
Here!
(internal) Right now,
Fukurodani's
front line attack
is two people.
[TOBIO]
Are they going for a quick
attack from the center,
or a back row attack, or will
No.4 finally make his move?
(TOBIO shock)
(whistle)
[UBUGAWA A]
A setter dump! Fukurodani turned
the game back around again!
[UBUGAWA B]
And their ace player hasn't
made a single shot yet!
[ERI]
Bokuto's such a goof.
He thinks he's the big
brother of the group,
[ERI] but in reality he's more
like the baby of the family.
[SARUKUI] Nice one, Akaashi.
[AKAASHI] Thank you very much.
[ERI] That being said, he is the
strongest player, though.
[AKAASHI]
Nice receive!
[KOMI, internal]
We're all used to
Bokuto's slumps.
[KONOHA, internal]
The most trivial things lift him
up or bring him down so easily.
[SARUKUI]
Left!
[SARUKUI, internal]
He's hopeless, really.
(whistle)
(FUKURODANI cheers)
[UBUGAWA A]
Match point for Fukurodani!
[YUKIE & KAORI]
Let's go! Whoo!
Fukurodani isn't a team
in which Bokuto leads...
[KEISHIN]
but rather they are a team...
where everyone else leads the
way for Bokuto.
[AKAASHI]
One touch!
[KEI, internal]
I understand now
that Fukurodani isn't
a one‐man team run by
Bokuto. Even so...
(whistle)
[KONOHA]
Oh man...
[KEI, internal]
Individually, there is nobody
scarier than him on their team.
[KOSHI, SHOYO, & TADASHI]
Good stuff guys!
[KOSHI]
Alright, one more point
and it's a deuce!
[KUROO]
Oh, good job there.
[ASAHI]
If I miss this serve,
then the game is over.
I have to make sure
to get it in!
(KEISHIN concerned)
[SARUKUI] Komi!
[KOMI] Hmph, yeah!
[AKAASHI]
Nice receive!
[AKAASHI, internal]
Karasuno should have realized
what kind of team we are by now.
In other words, they're not
paying attention to the ace.
[AKAASHI, internal]
And, this is about the time
when Bokuto starts getting all
fidgety, wanting the ball again!
(KEI alarmed)
[KOMI, WASHIO, & SARUKUI,
internal] We'll give all the
good sets to you!
[KONOHA, ONAGA, AKAASHI]
Sooo...
[FUKURODANI]
It's time to get back up, Ace!
(AKAASHI smirk)
(KEI annoyed)
(whistle) (long whistle)
(SHOYO, TADASHI, & KOSHI gawk)
(KEISHIN, TAKEDA, & HITOKA gawk)
(RYUNOSUKE frustrated)
(AKAASHI catching breath)
[AKAASHI, internal]
Help me out guys.
[KOMI, SARUKUI, & KONOHA,
internal] Leave it to us.
[SARUKUI]
Yo, Ace!
[KONOHA]
That was super awesome!
[KOMI]
In the end, it just
has to be the ace!
[YUKIE]
You look like your
hair exploded!
[KAORI]
Horned owl head!
(BOKUTO slowly cracking up)
[BOKUTO]
I am the best volleyball player
ever! Whoooo! Hey, hey, hey!
[KOMI, KONOHA, SARUKUI]
Hey, hey, hey!
[YUKIE]
As always, he sure manages to
recover quick.
[KAORI]
That's what happens when you
have a tiny brain.
[KEISHIN]
The weakness of their ace draws
out the strengths of the other
members.
[KEISHIN]
And at the same time, it becomes
the foundation that prevents
them from crumbling apart.
[KEISHIN]
Well well well. Strength comes
in many forms. Hmm?
[TAKEDA]
Honestly, I had thought that if
we could just stop Bokuto,
that would be enough
to care of these guys.
[TAKEDA]
But that was too simple, huh.
[KEISHIN]
For a team to allow a player to
be so arrogant...
and move around
wherever he wants...
[BOKUTO] I really am pretty
amazing aren't I?
[KEISHIN]
...it really all comes down to
[AKAASHI]
Yes yes of course you are,
Bokuto.
Right now, we've got
plenty of egos
to go around but not
enough of the trust.
[ASAHI]
(wailing) Sorry!
I'm sorry Coach, I chickened out
and hit a serve that was just
asking them to attack us!
[KEISHIN]
(surprised) Well, Man‐Bun has a
catharsis, now we're moving in
the right direction.
[ALL] Huh?
[KEISHIN] It's taking care of
the ball and doing what it takes
to stay on offense
[KEISHIN]
that determines whether or not
you finish on top.
[KEISHIN]
Nobody wants to end the game on
their own mistake.
[TOBIO] He's talking about you.
[SHOYO] Shut your face!
[KEISHIN]
But... nobody on the team is
ever going to blame you...
for hitting a serve that's
meant to take the win.
(TADASHI gasps)
[ASAHI] Yessir.
[KEISHIN]
Now that said. It's been a long,
hard, embarrassing,
humiliating losing streak.
But one thing is for certain:
(KEISHIN smirking)
[KEISHIN]
This offense will work.
And I'd take it against any of
the top teams in the country!
[TAKEDA]
At the moment, neither your
serves nor your combination
plays
are matching up against
other teams.
That is to be expected, because
you started way after them.
[TAKEDA]
But, you shouldn't stop there.
Don't think that your abilities
will only take you this far.
[TAKEDA]
Think of it this way; when you
mix colors, they get muddled and
lose what they once were.
[TAKEDA]
But, when they're all mixed
together, it turns to black. A
color that cannot be changed.
[TAKEDA]
And that's us. Black.
Like the crows we are!
(TOBIO & SHOYO confused)
[TAKEDA]
I'm sorry that metaphor
was a bit of a reach.
[DAICHI]
No! I think it was perfect!
[KURASUNO]
Thank you very much!
[DAICHI]
All right, our last penalty lap
of training camp!
[DAICHI]
One lap, floor flies!
[KURASUNO]
Right!
[YU] Asahi!
[ASAHI] Oh?
[YU]
We still have some time
before we get started.
Could you hit a few sets?
[ASAHI]
Oh sure.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Noya! Let me hit a few
of those, too!
[YU]
Yeah! Sure thing, Tanaka!
[KOSHI] Oh, me, too!
[YU, RYUNOSUKE, & ASAHI] Hm?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Oh, so you'll toss them
up for us, Suga?
Thanks, man!
Oh no, that's not it.
[YU, RYUNOSUKE, & ASAHI] Huh?
[KOSHI] I'm a hitter.
[TOBIO]
Ah, crap. If we could've nailed
more quick attacks,
we might have been able to
take a set from Fukurodani!
[SHOYO] But, with this,
we can fight.
[TOBIO] Hm?
[SHOYO]
Even if they predict our
strategies, or catch up to
us... we can fight! (giggle)
[TOBIO]
That depends on my set,
though...
[SHOYO]
Yeah well you're gonna get it
right, so it'll be okay.
[TOBIO]
Don't just assume stuff
about me on your own!
[SHOYO]
Then what, so you won't
be able to do it?
[TOBIO]
Of course I'll be able
to do it, moron!
[SHOYO]
See, that's what
I'm talking about!
[TOBIO]
We're gonna practice the
quick‐attack for a little bit!
[KEI]
[SHOYO]
All right!
(TADASHI cracking up)
[KOSHI]
(sigh) When we get back,
we're having the Spring
Nationals preliminaries
right away.
[DAICHI]
Yeah. Y'know I guess you're
right,
it will be just about
that time won't it?
Hopefully it'll be a
bit cooler by then.
(ASAHI jittery)
[KOSHI] But there will be some
lingering summer heat.
[DAICHI]
Why'd you say that, Suga?
[ASAHI]
If we can't get past the
prelims, we won't come
here ever again...
[KOSHI] What was that?!
Why are you being so negative.
[ASAHI] No wait...
[DAICHI]
Of course we're all going to be
coming back here, don't worry.
[ASAHI] Yeah you're
right. I'm sorry.
[KOSHI] Negativity, be gone!
[ASAHI]
(gut punch) Y'know... you uh,
you sounded kinda like Kageyama
just now.
[DAICHI]
Come on, Hinata, you dumbass!
[KOSHI] You're just like him!
[ASAHI] There it is again!
[SHOYO]
(shivers) S‐somehow I feel like
I'm being yelled at a
little more than usual.
(TOBIO confused)
[BOKUTO]
All right! Meat!
[YU]
I am going to eat everything!
[KIYOKO] Hey Yachi... Could
you take the plates over to
Miyanoshita please?
[HITOKA]
Sure!
[KAORI]
Peppers.
(ERI crying)
[KEI]
So I guess even Bokuto has
times where he's in a slump.
[AKAASHI]
Yeah... Well, he self‐destructs
whenever we're doing things we
don't quite understand.
[BOKUTO] Ribs, skirt steak,
tongue with salt, entrails...
[AKAASHI]
But even if our enemy is strong,
[BOKUTO] liver... sirloin...
tripe... intestines... so juicy.
[AKAASHI]
And if our guys are getting
In many ways, he's the most
reliable player on the team.
[SHOYO] Bokuto!
[BOKUTO] Huh?
Um. In an actual game,
we not gonna lose to you!
[BOKUTO]
Sure! (boastful laughing)
We'll take you on!
(BOKUTO's
stomach growling)
[BOKUTO]
(chuckle) Before the Spring
Nationals, first we have...
a competition for
the meat, Hinata!
[NEKOMATA]
(clears throat) Thank you all
for your hard work. It's been
a great training camp!
(stomachs growling)
[NEKOMATA] And now you can
fill your bellies as much
as you want.
Let your muscles repair
themselves to your heart's
content.
(SHOYO & TOBIO food lust)
[ALL]
"Time to eeeeat!"
(TOBIO choking)
[KUROO]
And then, poor Kenma
was all like...
[KUROO]
Ah! Hey! Oh hell no Bokuto!
You are not getting all the
meat you son of a bitch!
[KAORI]
Here have some rice balls!
[ASAHI]
Sure, I'll have a‐ Huh?
[YUKIE]
Don't mind if I do! (swallows)
(ALL disgusted)
[YU]
Do you understand? Tanaka?
[RYUNOSUKE] Yes
of course. Tiger head?
[YAMAMOTO] Yes, Master.
[YU]
There shall be no dudes...
Allowed to use this event
to hit on Kiyoko! Or there
will be hell!
[RYUNOSUKE & YAMAMOTO]
Your wish is our command!
(KONOHA & KOMI ogling trance)
[KONOHA] Go talk to her!
C'mon don't be a wuss.
[KOMI] No, you go!
(KOMI & KONOHA startled)
(YU intense growl)
(RYUNOSUKE intense growl)
(YAMAMOTO intense growl)
(KOMI & KONOHA fear
of god instilled)
[TADASHI]
So uh why is Nishinoya
the master?
[KEI]
Well apparently it's because he
is the chosen one,
the only person to have been
slapped in the face by Kiyoko.
[TADASHI] Aaah... (chuckles)
[DAICHI] Tsukishima!
[TADASHI & KEI] Hmm?
[DAICHI, mouthful]
You need to eat more food!
[KEI]
No... I've had enough thank you.
[KUROO] Come on,
eat vegetables, too!
(KENMA startled)
(TADASHI & KEI confused)
[KUROO] You too, Kenma,
I see you!
[DAICHI]
Here y'go have some rice!
(KENMA refusing)
[BOKUTO] Meat! You gotta eat
meat, Tsukki‐dude!
[BOKUTO] Or you won't be able
to grow up and be all big and
strong.
[KOSHI]
[BOKUTO] Don't you wanna be
big and strong like me?!
[YAKU]
Well he must think his relatives
[BOKUTO] I'm telling you.
It's no secret.
[KAI]
I'd say if they're
[BOKUTO] You gotta eat meat!
[KAI]
makes perfect sense.
[YAKU] Oh? You know, Suga?
[KOSHI] Huh?
[YAKU]
Blonde girl from your school...
she's acting suspicious. Is she
okay?
(KOSHI shocked)
(HITOKA spazzing out)
[HITOKA, internal]
Th‐this is just like...
[HITOKA]
a jungle of giants!
[HITOKA, internal]
(nervous) Oh man that smells
good... I gotta have some!
[WASHIO]
Oh, this one looks good.
[HITOKA, internal]
But if I plunge into that mess,
[ISAHARA] Hey, that's
the one I was about to eat!
[WASHIO] You snooze
you lose, nerd.
[GOURA]
Hm? Can you reach it?
Do you want one?
[HITOKA]
(startled) No!
I wouldn't taste good!
(GOURA confused)
[HITOKA]
Oh no, wait... I... I'm fine!
I'm not a crazy person. I think
I'll just go with this one right
here. (chokes it down)
(CHIGAYA & ASAHI mortified)
[HITOKA]
I‐it's delicious!
It tastes like meaty heaven...
(miserable)
[ASAHI]
Uuuh Yachi?
The one you just ate looked
like it was really burnt,
are you all right?
[WASHIO]
You need some tea?
[ONAGA]
We have some water too?
[OGANO]
Hey man...
are you like checking
out the scene over there?
[CHIGAYA]
Hmm? Yeah, if it was in the
middle of town,
someone might call the cops.
[CHIGAYA]
I wouldn't want to
be her right now.
[OGANO]
Oh! (dreamy sigh)
(ERI & KIYOKO soft giggling)
[KAORI] Ha!
(YUKIE munching)
[KAORI]
Where do you put all that?
[OGANO]
I think I'd like to be
[MAKO]
Y'know those third‐years from
Karasuno... They seem like they
have their act together.
[OGANO]
The managers of the
Fukurodani Group are at
a high aesthetic level.
But with Karasuno joining us...
Overall hotness levels
in the vicinity
have substantially increased.
What say you, sir?
[CHIGAYA]
I have no objections.
[KIYOKO]
Our ace is really
a big old softy.
[ERI]
Huh? Are you serious? But he
looks so big and scary.
[KAORI]
Though, I think that's
better than having such
a simple‐minded ace...
[SHOYO]
(amazed) The top five in the
entire nation...? That's so
cool!
[BOKUTO]
Isn't it? Isn't it though?!
(boastful laugh)
[KUROO]
Yeah well someone from your
region is up there, y'know.
That big fella Ushiwaka's
in the top three.
[SHOYO] Three?!
[BOKUTO] Hey! Hello I'm
right over here you know!
[HAIBA]
Okay so three means that...
there's like two more left
right?
[KUROO]
Hmm? Ushiwaka from
the Tohoku region,
[KUROO]
Kiryu from the Kyushu
region, and Sakusa from
the Kanto region.
[KUROO]
Those are the three strongest
aces at the national high
school level this year.
(SHOYO & HAIBA amazed)
(BOKUTO unimpressed)
[KEI]
Believe it or not, one of those
three aces is in Miyagi, of all
places...
[BOKUTO]
Hey, Tsukki‐poo! You practiced
a ton against my spikes!
I will not allow you to
be intimidated by Ushiwaka!
[KEI]
For the love of God can you
stop calling me that.
[KUROO]
Besides, just 'cause they're
called the "top three aces" ...
[KUROO]
doesn't mean their teams are
necessarily the top three teams.
[BOKUTO] Right on, right on!
[KUROO] Though, Sakusa's
team, Itachiyama,
is the heavy favorite to win
the nationals. Of course.
[SHOYO] Then...
[SHOYO & HAIBA] So if we
defeat them, will we be
the best in Japan?
[KUROO] Hm? Yeah, you bet!
But you guys suck.
(SHOYO & HAIBA shocked)
[HAIBA]
So what if Hinata is number one?
[SHOYO]
Well Kenma did say I was
better than you at serving
and receiving!
[HAIBA]
What? No way!
[TAKEDA] Coach Nekomata.
[NEKOMATA] Hmmm?
[TAKEDA]
I wanted to thank you again...
for inviting us down here.
[BOKUTO] But of course, you
weren't able stop my spikes,
were ya?!
[TAKEDA]
[SHOYO] So Lev, is it true you
caught that cat?
[NEKOMATA]
Oh no, it seems we've gotten
[HAIBA] Yeah well Kenma's arms
were too short, so he couldn't
reach it.
[NEKOMATA]
In six months time...
Not one team in the
tournament will be
the same as they are now.
Huh?
They will be new teams,
with completely different
playing styles.
[DAICHI] Oh I see. So Tokyo's
preliminaries are scheduled a
bit later then.
[NEKOMATA]
[KUROO] Well, we do have
a lot of schools.
[NEKOMATA]
But it is still my wish for
And the only way to do that is
to offer nothing but our very
best effort.
[TAKEDA]
Right.
(TOBIO yawning)
[SHOYO] I hate being the weakest
one on the team, but..
[TOBIO] Huh?
[SHOYO]
The fact that there are so many
people up above me...
[SHOYO]
is something that drives
me to get better!
[KEI, TADASHI, & TOBIO]
Huh?
[KUROO]
Well, see you again.
[DAICHI]
Yeah. Look forward to it.
[TAKEDA]
The summer break
training camp...
[TAKEDA]
It's finally come to an end.
If we win twice in
tomorrow's preliminaries,
[TAKEDA]
we will be able to advance to
the tournament in October,
which decides all the
area representatives.
[TAKEDA]
On top of the eight schools
that win the first round of
preliminaries,
[TAKEDA]
...eight more powerhouse schools
will join for the rest of the
tournament.
[SHOYO]
So we can only play two games
max in the first round of the
prelims.
[KOSHI]
Well since we made it into the
top 16 in the Inter High
preliminaries,
that means we us got a bye
for the first round.
[SHOYO]
(amazed) Yeah. We rock!
[DAICHI] All right,
let's start with stretches!
[HITOKA]
Finally, finally...
[KURASUNO] Yessir!
[HITOKA]
I‐I‐I'm starting to
get really nervous.
(KURASUNO stretch counting)
[KIYOKO]
Oh yeah, Yachi, this'll be your
first tournament won't it.
[HITOKA]
That's right...
[DAICHI]
1, 2, 3, 4!
[KIYOKO] For us..
This will be the last one.
[ALL] 5, 6, 7, 8!
[DAICHI] 1, 2, 3, 4!
(HITOKA tearing up)
[KIYOKO]
Oh! Sorry, sorry! I didn't
mean to make you cry!
[HITOKA]
I... I'm not! It's just that a
mosquito got into my eye...!
[KIYOKO]
A mosquito?
[YU]
Here goes!
(practice chatter)
[KOSHI]
Let's go!
[YU]
Bring it on!
[TADASHI, internal]
I won't serve to the libero.
I won't serve to the libero...
[TADASHI]
Why does it always go exactly
where I don't want it to?
[YU]
That was a nice serve Tadashi!
It was pretty tough for me to
reach!
[TADASHI]
Oh, okay...
[TADASHI, internal]
Well, he sure made it look
easy...
[TADASHI, internal]
One more!
[KEISHIN]
What are you reading
that's so interesting, Specs?
[TAKEDA]
Oh uh hey Coach...
Well, we know our
first‐years are amazing,
but I was thinking about the
other amazing first‐years out
there too...
[KEISHIN]
Oh... that guy. Yeah...
[YU]
Hey!
[KEI]
I'm home.
[AKITERU]
Man, just look how
much you've grown!
[AKITERU]
Of course, I guess you've been
taller than me for a while now.
[KEI]
(surprised) Hey bro.
[AKITERU]
S'been... a long time.
I don't even remember the last
time I've gotten to really talk
to you.
[KEI]
Oh really is that so?
[AKITERU]
Even whenever I come
back home to visit,
you're usually cooped
up in your room or whatever.
[KEI]
Is that so?
[AKITERU]
So uh... You seem a bit
different than before.
You went to that training
camp, right? How did it go?
[KEI]
Uh... it was normal...
[AKITERU]
I dunno, your face tells me
that it was pretty rough!
[KEI]
You still play volleyball
sometimes right?
[AKITERU]
Yeah, I'm on a team.
[KEI]
You have tournaments and stuff?
[AKITERU]
Yeah. Of course.
I guess you're probably
wondering
why I even bother
still playing, right?
(KEI uneasy)
[AKITERU] Well y'know... I just
never really wanted to stop.
(KEI surprised)
[AKITERU]
Listen, when I look back at how
everything went, I still get
frustrated.
It was never anything I wanted.
[AKITERU]
I mean, what you saw was such
a disgrace for me, too.
(KEI apathetic exhale)
High school wasn't what
I'd hoped. Didn't turn out
like I wanted.
I didn't get the uh... parts of
volleyball I love most.
But... I had already felt it...
[AKITERU]
I had felt how good it
feels to land a spike,
[AKITERU] and to hear the
crowd cheering you on.
(CROWD roaring cheer)
[BOKUTO]
It's all about having a badass
personal moment like that.
[AKITERU]
So I will keep playing...
Because I know it drives me to
be my best.
[KEI]
I see... So that's it...
[UKAI]
You boys have games starting
tomorrow, right? You should
probably wrap it up soon!
[SHOYO]
One more please! Just one more!
[TOBIO]
The next one is our
last, I promise!
[SHOYO & TOBIO]
One more! Pleeease!
[MACHIKO]
You know... I think this is
[UKAI] Okay. Just one.
[SHOYO & TOBIO] Thank you!
[COLLEGE GIRL]
They asked to borrow
[TOBIO] All right, Hinata!
Let's make sure to nail this!
[COLLEGE GIRL]
we start up because they
[SHOYO] Right on!
[COLLEGE GIRL] Apparently
he's the setter on Sho's team.
[MACHIKO]
Heh...
[OGASAWARA]
Here we go!
[COLLEGE GIRL]
I've been watching them play
since I got back,
and I gotta say, they're
really not very good.
(UKAI stunned)
(MACHIKO & COLLEGE GIRL stunned)
(OGASAWARA stunned)
(TOBIO & SHOYO impressed grins)
[FUTAKUCHI]
Oh man, Kamasaki, I see you
dropped by again?
[FUTAKUCHI]
You bored or something? Is your
job search going all right?
[FUTAKUCHI]
Maybe it's because your sleeves
are rolled up too tight.
[KAMASAKI]
Futakuchi you chode! Respect
your upperclassmen!
(KAMASAKI & FUTAKUCHI forcefully
separated)
[YUTARO]
Hey uh.... So... Was that story
that Oikawa told for real?
[AKIRA]
It's probably real, right?
I mean, he does pretty crazy
things...
(TORU frustrated)
[TERUSHIMA]
Huh? Karasa‐what?
[MISAKI]
It's "Karasuno."
[TERUSHIMA]
Where's that? Never heard of it.
If we're strong enough to defeat
Shiratorizawa...
We can win against any
team in the prefecture.
Heh... It's that simple.
[SHOYO]
I'm Shoyo Hinata, from the
Karasuno parking lot.
[SHOYO]
And I'm going to nationals.
After I kick your ass.
[USHIWAKA]
Gimme another one.
[TAKEDA]
August 11...
The Japanese National High
School Volleyball Championship
Tournament,
[TAKEDA]
Also known as the Spring High
School Volleyball Championships.
[TAKEDA]
The first round of the Miyagi
prefectural representative
deciding tournament...
starts today!
[AKITERU]
Having a super huge guy can be
the difference between victory
and defeat!
[KEI]
I'm not huge enough to be
called "super" huge.
[AKITERU]
Aw. You're so cute
when you a humble.
[KEI]
Don't expect a guy that is
almost 6'3" to be acting cute.
[KEI]
Next Haikyu!! "Match Begins!"