(HITOKA sighs)
[HITOKA, internal] Dear Mom,
[HITOKA]
They say Tokyo is a cool place,
but it still seems a lot hotter
than Tohoku.
[HITOKA]
We're on the third day of
training camp, which will last
the entire week.
[HITOKA]
So we're almost halfway there.
[DAICHI]
Go! (clap)
(uphill running)
[HITOKA, internal]
Everyone's getting pretty
exhausted.
[HITOKA]
Also, it's been roughly three
weeks since Hinata and Kageyama
got into their fight.
[KIYOKO] Good work.
[HITOKA] Here. It's all yours.
[KEI] Thanks.
[ASAHI] Oh, thank you. Aahh..
[HITOKA]
They're back to practicing
together now, but they still
won't talk.
(whistle)
[HITOKA] Woohoo!
Nice service‐ace!
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[KIYOKO]
As we've been going along...
everybody is making fewer
mistakes.
[KIYOKO]
And the point spread is
decreasing with each set, too.
[HITOKA, internal]
I am so impressed with how
much progress everyone's made.
I was a bit worried about how
down Tsukishima seems to be.
[HITOKA, internal] But maybe
that's just how he always is.
[RYUNOSUKE] One more Asahi,
Let's do it!
[HITOKA, internal] I mean,
he's certainly fatigued,
[KEI] So loud! (whistle)
[HITOKA, internal]
but still manages to be aloof
like usual. So, I guess he's
fine.
[TOBIO, internal]
Dammit! That was short again!
(whistle) (FUKURODANI cheers)
[DAICHI] Just shake it off!
We'll get the next one!
[SHOYO & TOBIO]
Sorry!
(whistle)
[HITOKA, internal]
Hinata and Kageyama's new
quick attack isn't going
very well.
[HITOKA]
During this training camp‐
(shriek) (jittery)
[BOKUTO]
Sorry about that!
[HITOKA, internal]
During this training camp,
I'd like to see it succeed,
even if only once.
[AKAASHI]
Thanks!
(practice game)
(ASAHI breath catch after
chugging)
(RYUNOSUKE & YU out of breath)
[KEISHIN, internal]
They're not used to a long
stretch of away games.
The temperature is
only getting hotter...
[KEISHIN, internal]
I'm guessing they'll eventually
start struggling.
(whistle)
[SHOYO]
Center!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hinata, get the last one!
(gasp) Sorry! Too close!
(SHOYO surprised)
[SHOYO] Ah.. Aaagh!
(NEKOMA celebrates)
[SHOYO, internal]
Everyone else is getting better.
[SHOYO]
Earlier, for just a moment,
there was even something
different about Tsukishima.
[SHOYO, internal]
(frustrated) I'm the
only one that's done
absolutely nothing...!
[KOSHI]
I've never seen Hinata
like this before...
He seems kinda agitated, y'know.
[TADASHI]
Yeah...
[RYUNOSUKE]
Chance ball!
[YU]
Got it!
[SHOYO, internal]
A chance for a quick‐attack!
It's mine!
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice cover! Nice cover!
[ASAHI]
Hinata is pretty clever‐
[SHOYO]
Hey! You just went easy on me!
(HITOKA & KIYOKO surprised)
(TAKEDA & KEISHIN confused)
[TOBIO]
Huh? Went easy? Me?
Really? You think so?
[TOBIO]
Try saying that again.
[DAICHI]
Take it easy, guys!
[TAKEDA]
I'm sorry,
we're gonna need a
time out please!
(long whistle)
[SHOYO]
That wasn't the falling
set just now!
(TOBIO shocked)
[TADASHI] (surprised)
What does he mean?
[KEI]
How should I know? It must be
an animal instinct or something.
[TAKEDA] Is he right, Coach?
[KEISHIN] Yeah, well...
If I had to call it one way
or the other, I'd say he's
absolutely right.
Up until this point...
His sets were falling down.
But, the last one looked like it
had more distinctive parabolic
curve on it...
[DAICHI] Kageyama please...
[KEISHIN] (gasp) In other words,
[DAICHI] you need to
calm down alright!
[KEISHIN]
it was like Kageyama wanted to
Recently, the Ginger....
hasn't landed any powerful
spikes.
[KEISHIN]
Which is a tremendous amount of
stress for a spiker.
[KEISHIN]
Kageyama may have unconsciously
been worried that Hinata would
start losing his rhythm.
[KEISHIN]
And he made an adjustment.
(TAKEDA impressed gasp)
[RYUNOSUKE] Calm your ass down!
[KEISHIN]
But Hinata... It's amazing that
you noticed,
[RYUNOSUKE] This isn't the place
for one of your little tickle
fights!
[KEISHIN]
At least you didn't screw up
again...
[TOBIO, internal]
Did I... just make a compromise
without realizing it? (exhale)
[SHOYO]
Keep trying, Kageyama!
[RYUNOSUKE]
I thought I told your scrawny
ass to chill!
[TORU]
Have you considered why're
you're having trouble responding
to Small Fry's request?
[TORU]
Or whether or not you even want
to put in the effort at all?
(SHOYO seething)
[SHOYO]
What are you doing, Kageyama?
[TOBIO] Okay starting tonight...
I'm not practicing with you.
(SHOYO & HITOKA shock)
[TOBIO] And I won't be using
our new quick‐attack during
games either.
[SHOYO] And why not?
[HITOKA, internal]
What? Their relationship's
gotten even worse?
[TOBIO]
"I have to keep trying"...
YOU told me that.
(SHOYO & HITOKA surprised)
[TOBIO]
As it stands now, it's useless
for us to practice together.
[HITOKA]
Um.. uh.. (shock)
[SHOYO]
Okay fine! Kenma!
Send me up a few!
[KENMA]
Eh.
[HITOKA]
Uh what?
[SHOYO, internal]
Kageyama started training
on his own again.
I cannot let him
get ahead of me.
There's one thing I need
to focus on right now!
[SHOYO]
I need to be able to battle
in the air by myself!
[BOKUTO]
Oh, Tsukki, you brought
a friend today?
[KEI]
What?
(SHOYO shock)
[KEI]
What happened to your favorite
partner?
[SHOYO]
Uh Kageyama is working
out by himself.
I got Kenma to serve for me, but
he crapped out after 5 balls.
[KUROO]
It's already amazing enough
that Kenma even stuck around
for that long.
[SHOYO]
Anyway...
[SHOYO & HAIBA]
Please let me join you! Hm?
[SHOYO] What? Lev?
[HAIBA] Oh, Hinata.
[KUROO]
Hey Lev... uh weren't you
practicing your receives
earlier with Yaku?
[HAIBA]
(shock) Yeah, I was doing really
well on my drills today so he
decided to let me go early!
[YAKU] Hey, have you guys seen
Lev anywhere?
[KUROO]
Really? You didn't run away from
[YAMAMOTO]
Probably squirtin' in the can.
[HAIBA]
No. Of course not!
[SHIBAYAMA]
Well he did just run saying that
he got the okay to go.
[YAKU]
(shock) But I never
told him he could go!
[KUROO]
Well, all right.... Okay...
Since we have the right
number of people...
Let's play a 3‐on‐3.
[HAIBA] Oh alright. Cool!
[SHOYO] (excited) Al‐right!
[AKAASHI]
Okay... I'm not so sure this
is a very balanced matchup.
[SHOYO, internal]
(amazed) I'm practicing with the
ace and setter of one of Tokyo's
powerhouse schools!
[SHOYO]
And, I'm playing against
Tsukishima!
[KUROO]
Nah, it's okay; might as
well do it while we can
get away with it.
(SHOYO & BOKUTO pumped yelling)
[KAORI]
And when I looked over, there
was a super huge rhino beetle,
and it like totally scared
the crap out of me!
[YUKIE] Oh yeah, come to think
of it, I think I like saw a
beetle too.
[KUROO] Lev!
[KUROO]
I told you to jump after seeing
the set! It's a read‐block!
[HAIBA]
Oh. Right.
[KUROO] Blockers...
try to avoid sideways jumps!
[SHOYO] Oh man! He picked
that one up!!
[KUROO]
If you can, make sure you stop
and jump straight up!
[KEI]
Okay!
[SHOYO]
Chance ball!
[KEI, internal]
Make sure you stop, and jump
straight up...
[SHOYO]
Awww! Man! Let's try it again!
[YUKIE] Um hey guys!
[ALL] Huh?
[YUKIE]
The cafeteria's gonna
be closing up soon...
So if you don't hurry up and
finish your practice you won't
be able to get any dinner.
(BOKUTO, SHOYO, & HAIBA panic)
[KUROO]
An army marches on its
stomach, gentlemen.
[BOKUTO]
Food!
(SHOYO conflicted)
[KUROO] Shorty.
[SHOYO] Oh?
[KUROO]
We'll pick this back up
tomorrow... 'kay?
[SHOYO]
(excited) Yessir!
(ASAHI snoring)
[YU] Hey... Wakey wakey!
[ASAHI]
Yeah. Get out of my face...
(KOSHI sleepy grumbling)
(RYUNOSUKE snoring)
(ASAHI & KOSHI
startled awake by sun)
[SHOYO, TOBIO, & HAIBA]
Time to eat!
[KEI]
You eat that much, but all that
nutrition isn't being used to
help you grow any taller.
[SHOYO, stuffing face]
Because I use it all for
volleyball, duh!
[KEI]
Nope... I didn't understand a
word of what you just said.
[ASHIYA]
You're up, Goura!
[KOSHI]
It wasn't clean! Kageyama,
follow that up!
[TOBIO]
Hinata!
[DAICHI]
Tanaka, you're open!
[RYUNOSUKE]
All right!
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Sorry bro! I think I might've
been aiming too hard!
(long whistle)
[EVERYONE]
Thank you very much!
[DAICHI] Let's go,
time for the hill!
[KURASUNO] Yessir!
[DAICHI]
Tanaka, you run double!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Aw, come on, man!
[ASHIYA]
Wow, that was really close...
[GOURA]
You know what...
[DAICHI]
Go!
(ALL running uphill)
[GOURA]
...I think they're
starting to get better.
[RYUNOSUKE] So hungry!
[KOSHI] I know!
[ASAHI]
I'm so hungry my stomach's
starting to eat itself.
[YU]
Yeah me, too.
[TADASHI]
This is crazy... How long is
he going to keep at it?
(HITOKA tossing ball up)
[TOBIO]
Agh. Dammit.
Send me up another one!
(TOBIO angry)
(HITOKA concerned)
[KEISHIN]
Kageyama... don't just think of
the plastic bottles as merely
targets.
[KEISHIN]
Now concentrate... Try to
imagine the bottle is the
spiker.
[TOBIO]
Huh... Imagine the... spiker...
[KUROO]
Oh, by the way... When
you're going one‐on‐one
against a spiker,
you don't want to stand
square in front of them...
Better to be standing right in
front of their dominant arm.
(HAIBA amazed)
[KEI] Hm? Okay ...
in the end... we're going
to be adversaries come
game time, aren't we?
So why are you giving
us so much advice?
[KUROO]
What's so weird about me being
nice? And helping my volleyball
brethren.
(KEI & SHOYO confused)
[KUROO]
You don't have to look
at me like that.
[KUROO]
(clears throat) The
"Trashcan Showdown"...
I want to make sure
it happens again.
(surprised)
[NEKOMATA]
All right, let's drink!
[TAKEDA] Sure!
[KUROO]
[NEKOMATA] Huh? Where
the hell is Keishin?
[KUROO]
And I think they deserve it.
[NAOI] Looks like he's
participating in some of the
students' personal training.
[KUROO]
[NEKOMATA] (growl) What tha?
Call his ass out here.[TAKEDA] Yes sir!
[KUROO]
Plus.. this ends up being some
good practice for me, too...
So don't get caught up
in the details too much.
[KUROO]
Come on, let's get to work.
[BOKUTO]
Akaashi, cover!
[AKAASHI]
Sorry about that, it was low!
Try to surround him and
spread out the surface
area of the block!
(KEI & HAIBA bracing themselves)
[BOKUTO]
Dammit, you're supposed
to be a first‐year!
Why are you so freakin' tall?!
[SHOYO, internal]
(gasp) He hit the block on
purpose?
[BOKUTO]
One more time! Akaashi, give me
a good one!
[BOKUTO]
Yeah! Hey, hey, hey!
[BOKUTO] Whoo! (snickering) Hmm?
[SHOYO] Holy crap Bokuto!
Uh‐that hit you just did..!
[SHOYO]
Did you glance it off the
blocker's hand on purpose?
[BOKUTO]
Yeah! It's a rebound!
[SHOYO]
(gasp) A rebound! Cool!
[BOKUTO]
(flattered) Oh yeah. It is,
isn't it?
(SHOYO enthusiastically nodding)
[KUROO, internal]
Shorty has a natural gift for
flattering people...
[BOKUTO]
Like, if your balance is off and
you feel like you're sure to be
blocked if you take the shot,
you hit the ball against the
blockers on purpose and have it
rebound back so you can set it
up again.
[BOKUTO]
Make sense?
(SHOYO amazed)
[BOKUTO]
But a lot of times
it doesn't work
and the ball ends up getting
slammed back in your face.
[AKAASHI]
Yeah that happens to
you a lot, Bokuto.
[BOKUTO]
That was your cue to say it
hasn't been happening to me as
much lately!
Spiking isn't all about slamming
it onto the floor y'know.
[BOKUTO]
If you just stay calm, you'll
have a clear head at the moment
of truth!
(SHOYO gasp)
[AKAASHI] Yeah, that has not
been happening to you a lot
lately.
[BOKUTO]
Watch it, Akaashi!
[HAIBA]
All right!
[BOKUTO]
Yeah nice one! Short‐stuff, get
the last hit!
[SHOYO] Sure!
(KUROO grins)
[BOKUTO]
Aw come on you guys! You don't
have to crowd the guy like that!
[AKAASHI]
This is more of
an umbrella than a wall.
There's no place to go. There's
nowhere to make a shot...
[BOKUTO]
If you stay calm...
...you'll have a clear head at
the moment of truth!
[AKAASHI & BOKUTO, internal]
He shot the ball upwards?!
[SHOYO]
Ouch! (groaning)
[KUROO]
Did you... aim that one?
That was an amazing block‐out.
[SHOYO] (surprised) Well I
guess I did aim at the tip
of Lev's hand...
[HAIBA] What?
But it was just coincidence that
it hit him. I can't really shoot
that accurately‐
[BOKUTO]
Oh... That was a triple‐block
with some giant 6'3" blockers,
you know?
And that was a really
nasty ball to hit!
Well done, shorty pants!
Gotta say I'm impressed!
(laughs)
[BOKUTO]
To the wee little fighter going
up against the 2‐meter wall, I
have something for you.
[AKAASHI] You're
over‐doing it again.
[KUROO] I think 6 foot 3 just
turned into 6 foot 7...
[BOKUTO]
I... am gonna teach you a
special attack, my man!
[SHOYO]
Really, a special attack?
[BOKUTO]
Yup!
[HITOKA]
Okay here comes the next one!
[TOBIO]
Slot 5...
(HITOKA impressed)
[TOBIO]
Let's do it again.
(HITOKA yawns)
[KIYOKO]
Yachi, I'm sure you must be
tired after all this... You
gonna make it?
[HITOKA]
Yes! I'll be okay.
[KIYOKO]
Today's the last day. Let's
finish it strong.
[HITOKA]
Yeah!
(surprised) Morning, Hinata.
[SHOYO]
Hey! Good morning, Yachi! I'm
pretty hungry, are you?
[HITOKA]
Yeah... I am. You practiced late
last night. Yet somehow you're
so full of energy this morning.
[SHOYO]
Mm‐hm, Yeah well I
just woke up so...
[HITOKA]
(acknowledgement) How's the
training coming along?
[SHOYO]
(grin) I'm working on something
really cool, can't wait for you
to see it!
[KEI]
(snicker) What a dork...
(TADASHI snoring)
[SHOYO] What's so funny?
[KEI]
Oh, nothing.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Somebody wake Tadashi up!
[NEKOMATA] And about
what I mentioned...
[DAICHI] Hmm?
[SHINZEN GM]
Yes, it's already been taken
care of as we planned. It should
be arriving around noon.
[NEKOMATA]
I see....
[DAICHI]
Oh my God...
(practice games)
(long whistle)
(YAKU sighs)
[YAKU] It's really hard
for anyone to win against
Fukurodani, isn't it?
[SENGOKU] It's all you, Goura!
[SHIBAYAMA] Hey Kuroo!
I did a quick summary
of the current scores!
[YU] Got it!
[KUROO] Thanks a lot!
[KAI] Amazing as always.
[RYUNOSUKE] Right!
[DAICHI] Left!
[YAKU] Just as I thought,
the strongest here is
Fukurodani...
[KOSHI] (groan) Sorry!
(UBUGAWA cheers)
(long whistle)
[ALL] Huh?
[YAKU]
Oh, the Ubugawa‐Karasuno
game ended.
[DAICHI]
Flying laps! Let's go!
[ALL]
You got it, Cap'n!
There's a strange dignity
about the way they go for
those penalty laps...
[KENMA]
If you include the previous
training camp...
they've done way more
penalty laps than anyone.
[KENMA] I could never do that.
[DAICHI] Well, time
for a flying lap!
[YAKU]
Whoa, Karasuno's Shorty
takes that pretty seriously
doesn't he?
[HAIBA]
Shorty, really? You're one to
talk, Yaku;
I'm mean c'mon you're not any
taller than Hinata, are you?
[YAKU] (anger) Lev! You sit
yourself down right over there!
[KUROO] I can't defend him
against that one.
[HAIBA] Hey. I'm not a dog.
What's the matter?
[YAMAMOTO] I told him not to
mention anything about Yaku's
[HAIBA] Can't you take a joke.
[YAMAMOTO]
no matter what... Dumbass...
[RYUNOSUKE]
(out of breath) Dammit!
We gonna keep losing
'til the very end?
(ALL catching breath)
[DAICHI]
Hang in there! We
have to survive this.
[ALL] Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE] Whaddya mean Daichi?
[DAICHI]
Listen guys... I accidentally
overheard something...
At first I thought I should
keep quiet, but...
[RYUNOSUKE]
Wh‐what is it?
[DAICHI]
When all of these practice
matches are over with...
[DAICHI]
...apparently the coaches
are treating us all to some
barbecue!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Bar...
[YU]
...be...
[SHOYO]
...cue?!
[BOKUTO]
Akaashi... who we got up next?
[AKAASHI]
Karasuno.
[KONOHA, SARUKUI, & KOMI]
Karasuno...
[BOKUTO]
What's wrong?
Ah nothing, they're just
kinduv a pain in the butt.
Yeah that's the truth, you can
never predict what kinda crazy
trick they'll try next.
But, it looks like
they are getting
pretty tired now...
[RYUNOSUKE]
Meat meat dinner, meaty‐meat
dinner!
[SHOYO]
Meat meat meat with
a side of meat!
[YU]
And meat for dessert!
[RYUNOSUKE, SHOYO, & YU]
M‐E‐A‐T! Now we got some energy!
[KONOHA]
Dude. They're freaks.
RYUNOSUKE, SHOYO, & YU]
You and me can eat the meat!
Eat the meat that can't be beat.
Hey Specs... You
didn't tell these guys
anything about the
barbecue, did you?
The only thing the schedule
said is we're having a meal...
Well, good thing
meat's on the menu.
[HITOKA]
Hinata, do your
best in the game.
[SHOYO]
Thank you!
[KEI]
Looking forward to your big
secret attack.
[SHOYO]
Just wait, you four‐eyed
butt‐wad!
[HITOKA]
And... I think I'd really like
to see the new quick‐attack
soon...
[SHOYO]
Mmm.... Well... Uh. yeah!
[HITOKA]
Huh!?
[SHOYO] Kageyama!
[TOBIO] Hm? Huh?
[SHOYO]
I really wanna try and hit that
set that drops down.
[HITOKA, internal]
He told you yesterday that
we won't be doing that
quick‐attack!
[TOBIO]
Don't get so anxious alright...
It's not gonna be
good practice for you
if I'm still messing
up the sets.
(HITOKA shocked)
[TOBIO]
I already told you, Hinata, this
isn't about how badly you want
to do it!
[TOBIO]
I'll set a ball that WON'T get
stopped by their blockers!
[HITOKA, internal]
That's how he used to sound, but
he's come quite a long way.
He actually showed
Hinata some respect.
[SHOYO]
I appreciate you being
thoughtful and all,
and you being considerate
is kinda freaking me
out a little...
[SHOYO]
But I really want us to try it
soon okay!
[TOBIO]
(annoyed) That's why I'm
practicing so hard, you moron!
(SHOYO shouting)
[HITOKA, internal]
And Hinata firmly believes that
Kageyama will definitely perfect
his sets...
[HITOKA, internal]
Oh! So that's why he got so mad
at him before!
(TOBIO heavy breathing)
[HITOKA, internal] Hinata
thought that it was something
that Kageyama could surely do,
but he showed a moment of doubt!
[SHOYO] Just how long are
you gonna make me wait?
[HITOKA, internal]
Hinata and Tsukishima always
[HITOKA]
But today, I think the crown is
on Hinata's head.
[SHOYO]
Thou shalt give me thy best set!
(laughter)
(RYUNOSUKE & DAICHI chuckle)
[KEISHIN]
Okay listen, I know you guys
have been working on some fancy
new tricks...
[KEISHIN] now go out there
and make one of 'em happen.
[ALL] Yessir!
[KEISHIN]
But just promise me one thing;
do not let Fukurodani's No.4
have a field day.
[ALL]
Right!
In the end... we spent most
of this camp running laps.
But I don't want you to think
it was all for nothing...
every single one of you
has improved along the way.
So you can chalk this one up
as a victory... and let's go
get some grub!
[KURASUNO]
All riiiight!
[RYUNOSUKE]
It's gotta be meat!
[YU]
And you can't have
meat without rice!
[SHOYO]
Mm, the perfect combo!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Yeah, and a meat‐salad
to top it off!
[DAICHI]
We're gonna win this
one and chow down!
[RYUNOSUKE, SHOYO, & YU]
Yeah!
[DAICHI]
Next Haikyu!!
"Gears".