[SHOYO]
Awesome! Leaving in the
middle of the night makes
my heart race!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Oh right, you guys got there
late last time.
[KEI]
It must be nice to be a
simpleton. You can fall asleep
anywhere.
[RYUNOSUKE & SHOYO]
What did you say?!
[TAKEDA]
Well, as you know,
we're scheduled to arrive
early in the morning again.
Coach and I will be
taking turns as the driver
to cut the drive time.
[KEISHIN]
(yawn) Sorry if I
fall asleep, guys.
[DAICHI] We're with you, sir!
[ALL] Sir!
[TAKEDA]
It's the middle of the
night, so keep it down.
[DAICHI]
Oh! Yeah sorry I forgot..
(DAICHI & ASAHI humbled laugh)
[TAKEDA] Everyone got
all your luggage?
[KOSHI, internal]
Hinata and Kageyama;
[TAKEDA] Check one
more time before we go.
[KOSHI]
They're barely speaking to
[YU] C'mon, Tanaka, let's show
'em that Miyagi pride!
[KEISHIN] Well, time to
get going.
[RYUNOSUKE] Ready
when you are, Noya!
[KEISHIN] Stop yelling.
(KEI sighs)
[KOSHI]
Just get on the bus, guys.
[SHOYO]
Hey, guys, where's
the Skytree?!
[KENMA]
Uh, the Skytree?
[SHOYO]
Wow! Isn't that Tokyo Tower
over there? (amazement)
[KENMA]
Um... that's just... a normal
radio tower... Sorry.
[KUROO]
What's the deal? You guys don't
have steel towers in Miyagi?
Is like this a real thing
I don't know about?
[DAICHI]
Oh well excuse us if
we simple country folks
don't know exactly what
the Tokyo Tower looks like!
[KOSHI]
Uh, this is Saitama.
We're not even IN Tokyo.
[TOBIO, internal]
So that's not Tokyo Tower...?
[SHOYO]
We're going to be at a different
high school than last time!
[KENMA]
All the summer training camps
are held at Shinzen. It's nice
and cool here.
[KENMA]
There's a ton of bugs though.
[HAIBA]
Hinata! Are you
any taller yet?! Huh?
[KENMA]
Hm? Shut up, Lev.
[SHOYO]
It's only been two weeks
since I last saw you...
Can't you think of
something else to say?!
[HAIBA]
Well, I grew a coupla
millimeters!
(SHOYO shocked)
[KEISHIN]
All right, we're going to be
swapping players constantly,
so be prepared for that. M'kay?
[ALL]
Right!
(long whistle)
[BOKUTO]
Our goal is... no penalties!
(HITOKA nervous)
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nishinoya!
[YU]
Got it!
[DAICHI]
Nice receive!
[TOBIO, internal]
Here's our chance!
[BOKUTO]
Okay here comes that wild
quick‐attack!
[TOBIO]
Leave it there... leave it
there... leave it there..!
(SHOYO gasp)
[TOBIO, internal]
It was too short!
[RYUNOSUKE]
What's up, Kageyama?
That wasn't like you, my man.
[TOBIO]
(mortified) I'm sorry.
[TOBIO, internal]
Dammit... it feels different
in an actual game.
(SHOYO concerned)
[BOKUTO] All right!
One more! Serve it up!
[KEISHIN, internal]
Surprised you, didn't it?
Don't worry, you'll
get used to it.
[KEISHIN, internal]
Kageyama's sets won't be
anything like what they
used to be.
(whistle)
[YU]
I've got it!
[TOBIO, internal]
(frustrated) This time,
it went out too far...!
[KOSHI, internal]
He saved it with his left
hand at the last second!
(whistle)
[TADASHI] Good one, Hinata!
[KOSHI]
But the timing was
weird... That used to
always throw Hinata off.
[YU]
That was nice! Good work!
[SHOYO, internal]
The set came falling
down again...!
[TOBIO, internal]
(heavy breath) This guy...
[SHOYO & TOBIO, internal]
He's different now.
(NEKOMATA chuckles)
[KONOHA] Shake it off!
[KOMI]
You couldn't have done
anything about that!
We'll get the next one!
(NEKOMATA chuckles)
[NAOI] Hmm?
[KEISHIN, internal]
Hinata and Kageyama...
They're not the only ones
who've changed things up.
(ASAHI exhales)
[KOMI]
It's going out, it's out!
[ASAHI] Tch.
(whistle)
[HITOKA, internal]
(chuckle) Asahi's so revved up
he can't control his strength.
[KEISHIN]
You're looking good!
Don't let up now!
[NEKOMATA]
Well.. isn't this just
delightful... It's
delightfully...
(KOSHI startled)
(RYUNOSUKE baffled)
(KURASUNO shocked) (whistle)
[NEKOMATA]
...not working at all. (chuckle)
[OGANO]
Hey, call me crazy but uh...
I think Karasuno just tried to
pull off a synchronized attack!
[KOSHI]
Cover that!
[YU]
Leave it to me!
(NEKOMATA surprised)
(NAOI surprised)
The libero came out
from the back zone
to attempt a jump set!
[YU, internal]
I overshot it.
[BOKUTO]
Hey, what's up with you guys
today? Are you all right?
[YU]
Shut up! (growling)
[NAOI]
What's going on with
Karasuno? They seem to
be having an off day.
[NEKOMATA]
(chuckle) I would say
it's quite the opposite.
[NAOI] Huh?
[NEKOMATA] This is exactly what
you'd expect from crows. They're
omnivores.
[NEKOMATA]
Whether it be deep in the
mountains... or in the
center of Kabukicho...
[NEKOMATA]
they eat whatever they can...
using the strengths of all those
around them.
[NEKOMATA]
They survive by
any means necessary.
[BOKUTO] Nice receive!
[DAICHI] Left, go left!
[NEKOMATA] I'd bet you anything
that those kids are
[ASAHI] Bokuto!
[NEKOMATA]
in the midst of an
amazing period of
[BOKUTO]
Take that!
(whistle)
[BOKUTO]
All right!
[NEKOMATA, internal]
With one exception, perhaps?
(KEI exhales)
(long whistle)
[EVERYONE]
Thanks for the game!
[DAICHI]
The penalty for this camp is
apparently something you see
only at Shinzen:
[DAICHI]
a refreshing uphill dash through
the forest behind the school!
[DAICHI]
Okay... ready...
(KURASUNO pumped up yelling)
(heavy pace running)
[HITOKA]
Here.
[TADASHI]
Oh... thanks a lot.
[HITOKA]
Here, Sugawara.
[KOSHI] Oh, thank you!
[GOURA] Serve's up!
Are Shinzen and Ubugawa still
playing their first set?
[SHOYO]
Mm‐hm.
Whoa! That serve
was freaking amazing!
[SHIMAFU]
Left side!
(UBUGAWA cheers)
[SHOYO] Wow! Shut right out!
[KEISHIN] A serve
and block. Yeah...
[SHOYO & TADASHI] Oh?
[KEISHIN]
Break up the
opponent with the serve,
and once their method of
attack is narrowed down,
you stuff 'em with a block.
That's the best attack
formation you could pull off,
besides a service ace.
[TADASHI]
Hm? Oh, so that's a
serve‐and‐block...
[OGANO]
Damn you, fish lips...
[GOURA]
Broccoli head...
[KUROO]
Don't say that...
It's an insult to healthy food.
[OGANO]
What was that?!
[KOSHI]
(sigh) Lost every match.
[DAICHI]
It does feel good to get out
and run a little though.
[RYUNOSUKE]
This is the first time I've had
to run so much since the other
Coach Ukai was around!
[DAICHI]
(sitting up) Come on you guys...
Let's go borrow Coach's tablet
and watch some videos of a few
synchronized attacks!
[KOSHI] Sounds good.
[RYUNOSUKE] I'm in!
[ASAHI]
I'll go hit up some serves.
I need the practice.
[TADASHI, internal]
Huh? Serves?
I should go, too!
[TADASHI]
Hey... uh... Tsukki...
I'm gonna go work on my serves
if you want to come along...
[KEI]
I'm going home and then
going straight to bed.
[TADASHI]
Oh.. Okay... but uh...
[KEI] What?
[TADASHI] Don't take
this the wrong way but...
but uh are you gonna do
anything to prepare at all?
[KEI]
We practice way
too much as it is.
(TADASHI surprised)
There is no use running
ourselves into the ground.
[TADASHI]
I... guess so...
Well... if that's
what you want...
[KUROO] Hey, you! Skinny!
With the glasses!
[KEI] Hmm?
[KUROO]
Can you maybe jump a few blocks
for us?
(BOKUTO stretching)
[KEI] Sorry, I'm all done
for the day... You have a
good night.
[KUROO & BOKUTO] What?!
[BOKUTO]
But there's no point in
practicing our spiking
if we don't have any
blockers! Come on!
[KEI]
Why does it have to be me?
What about your own guys?
[AKAASHI]
Nah, Bokuto's the worst...
His spiking practice goes on
forever, it's like he never
stops.
[KUROO]
And I've been too busy training
this bumbling idiot over here.
[HAIBA]
(exhausted moaning) I already
told you... I'll jump all those
blocks, I swear okay!
[KUROO]
Oh be quiet!
If you want to be part of
Nekoma's regular lineup,
you're gonna need to
improve your receiving!
(HAIBA defeated whine)
[KUROO]
He may not look it...
But this goofy fella is one of
the five
best spikers in
the entire nation.
[KUROO] He'll be some
awesome practice for ya.
(BOKUTO proud grin)
[AKAASHI]
Yeah I think he's still upset
he's not in the top 3 anymore
though.
[KUROO] There, there.
[BOKUTO] Why would you
say all that nice stuff
just to tear me down?!
[KUROO]
Anyway skinny jeans...
You are a middle‐blocker...
[KUROO]
Don't you think you ought to
practice your blocking once
in a while, pal?
(KEI pissed exhale)
(BOKUTO surprised)
(impressed snicker)
(KUROO snide grin)
[SHOYO, internal]
Today's quick‐attacks didn't
mesh at all... I gotta tighten
it up.
[TOBIO, internal]
I need to make sure this
actually works before next
month...
(SHOYO & TOBIO stubborn sigh)
[HITOKA] You guys want to
practice your quick attack?
Come on... I'll throw
some balls for you!
[SHOYO]
The way she's asking is kinda
pushy... and weird...
[SHOYO]
W‐we're ready!
[TOBIO]
Uh yeah, sure.
[BOKUTO]
Let's do one more!
One more!
[BOKUTO]
[KEI, internal]
Straight!
[BOKUTO, internal]
You're a pretty smart cookie...
But!
[BOKUTO] Yeah!
[AKAASHI] You are amazing,
you beat a single blocker...
[BOKUTO]
Shut up!
[KUROO]
Hey... how about we do a double?
[BOKUTO]
Double? Bring it on!
[KEI]
Is he dead?
[BOKUTO]
Here we go.
[KUROO]
Make sure you keep those
straights shut out, would
you, Skinny?
[KUROO]
Woohoo!
[BOKUTO]
Aaghh! Dammit!
(KEI low‐key surprised)
(BOKUTO frustrated groan)
[BOKUTO]
You're not all that bad,
buddy‐boy...
but you know, I gotta
be honest with ya...
[BOKUTO] Your blocks are
a little bit weak.
(KEI stunned, anger growing)
[BOKUTO]
Makes me think I might break
your arm or something.
You gotta rush in and
stop it, you know?!
[KEI]
Well, on the other hand,
I'm only in high school,
after all...
[KEI] I've still got a few more
years to grow and build up some
big ol' muscles.
(BOKUTO annoyed)
[KUROO]
You better stop dragging your
feet there, Skinny,
[KUROO]
or the carrot top's gonna take
all the glory for himself before
much longer.
[KUROO]
He's a middle blocker too.
[BOKUTO] Huh?
[KUROO] Hm?
[KEI]
Um yeah I don't think there's
much I can do about that...
I mean, let's be honest, there's
a big difference in potential
between Hinata and me.
(KUROO doubtful)
[INUOKA]
Oh hey! You guys practicing
spikes again? Want me to block
some? I'm happy to!
[YAKU]
Jeez, Lev, stop rolling around
on the floor and work on your
receives!
[HAIBA] Ugh! I'm tired!
[YAKU] Did you say you're
tired?!
[YAKU] Come on, get on your
feet! You've gotta perfect
that move!
[KEI]
[KUROO] What? Hey wait!
[HAIBA] No, I've already
perfected that...
[AKAASHI]
I think you might've
struck a little nerve
[AKAASHI]
just then, Kuroo... Nice move.
[KUROO] Eh?
[BOKUTO] You pissed him off!
[BOKUTO]
Come on, Kuroo...
I thought you had better
people skills than that.
[KUROO] Yeah well... I didn't
know he would be all like that.
[BOKUTO] Like what?
[KUROO]
Shorty over at Karasuno is
really something else, and face
it the kid is a serious threat.
[KUROO]
That said, he's still very
inexperienced... And well like I
said, he's short.
[KUROO]
Skinny is tall and brainy, and
yet he looks at Shorty not just
as an equal,
[KUROO]
but as someone that he
is no match against.
[KEI, internal]
Great, I forgot my
brace at the gym.
[KOSHI]
One more!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Wasn't the timing a little
bit too early there?
[KOSHI]
Oh, you think so? Then next one,
I'll delay it by one tempo.
[KIYOKO]
Here goes!
[DAICHI]
Sorry! One more!
[KEI]
It's nothing but a stupid game.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Bring it!
[KEI]
How can these guys get
into it so much.
I don't get it.
[KEI]
It'll just hurt you in the end.
[YU]
Tsukishima!
Eat up so you'll
have some energy!
[KEI] Look at you...
You are such a fat‐ass.
[YU] What'd you call me?
[YU] Oh I am going to
make you pay for that!
[ERI] Here you go.
[SHOYO] Ah! Th‐Thanks,
[KEI]
Hey, stop it... You're gonna
mess up my glasses!
[KOSHI]
Stop... You're gonna
make Daichi mad.
(whistle)
(long whistle)
[DAICHI]
Go!
(uphill running)
[DAICHI]
Go!
(uphill running)
(KEI panting)
(TADASHI glugging)
[KOSHI] Here, Hinata.
[SHOYO] Thanks!
[ERI]
Everyone! The Shinzen High
School club parents came! They
brought us watermelon!
(ALL impressed)
[SHOYO]
Whoa! That's really cool! Plgh!
(HAIBA chuckling)
[TOBIO]
Hey uh can I have another one?
[HITOKA] Sure!
[TOBIO] Hm.
Huh? Tsukishima, are you sure
you only wanted one piece?
[KEI]
Yeah. It was delicious.
[ASAHI]
When I was a kid, I ate so much
of this stuff I got sick.
[KUROO] Sorry, dude.
[DAICHI, ASAHI, RYUNOSUKE] Hmmm?
[DAICHI]
Uh, what for?
Yesterday... I kinda had
a little disagreement
with your big lanky blocker
with the glasses.
[DAICHI]
Huh?
(SHOYO frustrated)
[HAIBA] (laugh) You
really suck at that!
[DAICHI]
First of all, I can't believe
Anyway, what was the fuss about?
[KUROO]
I warned him that the short guy
on your team
[KUROO] would outdo him
soon, that's all.
(DAICHI surprised)
I guess it IS true that
Tsukishima feels
a little inferior
compared to Hinata...
[KEI]
It's Hinata's job to deal out
the real damage...
[KEI]
Think about it. From my
position,
all I'm supposed to be
responsible for is holding down
the fort the best I can.
[KEI]
It's no different than any
other game, really.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Uh, I dunno if this has
anything to do with
what we're talking about...
but my uh sister said...
[SAEKO] Say uh
you know something?
[RYUNOSUKE] Huh?
I heard a name while you
were playing at your little
training camp.
[SAEKO]
Do you guys have a player
on the team named Tsukishima?
[RYUNOSUKE]
(annoyed) Uh‐huh yeah, sure we
do...
[RYUNOSUKE]
The smartass with the glasses
who doesn't get along with
anybody else, what about him?
[SAEKO]
Does this Tsukishima guy have
like a... a brother?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh? How should I know? He's not
really the type of guy to talk
about himself.
[SAEKO]
Well uh when I was
back in high school...
You know back when our
volleyball team was at
their very best.
[RYUNOSUKE]
When the Tiny
Giant used to play?
[SAEKO]
Right... Back then, I think
there was
a really tall player with
the same last name on the
volleyball team.
[ASAHI] Huh?
[DAICHI] Hm? Tsukishima's
brother maybe?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Oh, well I don't
know about that.
I mean it could be a total
stranger that happened to
have the same last name.
[KOSHI]
Hey! We're getting ready to
start up again!
[DAICHI]
All right, let's go!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Oh! Cool, let's do it! (eating)
(long whistle)
[DAICHI]
Go!
(running uphill, grunting)
(KURASUNO out of breath)
[KOSHI] This is really tough...
[YU]
This is nothing! I could do this
at least ten more times!
[KOSHI]
How 'bout we just win one?
(TADASHI & KEI out of breath)
[ASAHI]
Hey Tadashi... your serves
are looking quite a bit better
these days.
[TADASHI]
Oh. Thanks a lot Asahi.
[ASAHI]
Yeah. I still have some
work to do on mine.
[KEI]
I bet you must really hate
what's going on, huh?
[ASAHI]
Hate what?
[KEI]
The feeling you're about to be
eclipsed by someone else.
[ASAHI]
(laugh) Well... I can't say it
doesn't bother me.
[KEI]
Hinata still wants to be the
ace... I dunno, if it were me,
I'd be uncomfortable.
[ASAHI]
Yeah I guess so.
But maybe that's why he
started saying that he
won't stop growing.
[ASAHI]
Either way, it seems to have lit
a fire underneath all of us,
hasn't it?
[KEI]
I saw what happened before;
if you're not careful,
he'll get too focused
and run you right off the court.
[ASAHI]
Huh?
Oh, you mean when I jumped
up to spike and we hit each
other.
[ASAHI]
Let's face it, Tsukishima...
given our positions, we
are the closest ones to
being his rivals.
[ASAHI]
So y'know... we feel how
Hinata is growing up
and stretching his wings a lot
more than anyone else does.
[ASAHI]
But whatever man... I'm not
letting him beat me.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Left, left!
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
All right!
[TOBIO]
Hey, stop slacking off!
Decoys still have to jump!
[KEI]
So observant of you...
Sorry, all right?
[DAICHI] Tsukishima,
you got next serve.
[KEI] Okay.
[KEISHIN] What do YOU think
[TAKEDA]
Huh? Well, I think he's working
diligently.
[RYUNOSUKE] Let's go!
[KEISHIN]
He passes the test, but never
aims for a perfect score.
[KEISHIN]
That's the feeling
I get from him.
[KOSHI] It's coming
from the left side!
[KEISHIN]
I don't need him
[TADASHI] You better keep
an eye on that Number 4!
[KEISHIN]
But if other players keep
[TADASHI, KOSHI, & CHIKARA]
Nice going guys!
[SHOYO] Center!
[KEISHIN] The ones I keep on the
[KEISHIN]
the ones I think give us
the best chance to win.
[KEISHIN]
But as the tallest player,
he is valuable.
(whistle) (KURASUNO celebrate)
[KEISHIN]
If Tsukishima can be the key
point for the blocks...
our defensive level will
go up significantly...
[TAKEDA]
You're right about that.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Cover! Cover!
[DAICHI] I got it!
[YU] I got it!
(DAICHI & YU collision)
(HITOKA & KIYOKO gasp)
[DAICHI & YU] Sorry!
[HITOKA]
They're all really into this,
aren't they?
[KIYOKO]
Yeah all the guys have been into
the game like they've never been
before...
[KIYOKO] And it can make it
a little scary sometimes.
(HITOKA concerned)
[KIYOKO]
Contact like last time can lead
to huge injuries.
[ASAHI]
Watch the left! Number 1!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Asahi! It's all you!
(KIYOKO & KEISHIN gasp)
[KIYOKO]
It's a bit short...!
(SHOYO stunned)
[ASAHI, internal]
This ball is mine!
(whistle)
(ALL amazed)
(UBUGAWA shocked)
[NEKOMATA, internal]
It's working well.
[NEKOMATA]
Even within one's own team,
the tension from acknowledging
[RYUNOSUKE] Now that's a kill,
Asahi! You crushed that thing!
[NEKOMATA]
you are rivals with one another
[ASAHI] Thanks.
[NEKOMATA]
However, if the team turns into
a group with no laws, they'll
[NEKOMATA]
Now this kid tightened things up
with just a single shot...
that's the ace for you!
[KIYOKO]
Hmm... Looks like I didn't need
to worry after all.
(ASAHI clench fist)
(KURASUNO uphill running)
(KEI panting)
[TADASHI]
You okay, Tsukki?
[KEI]
I'll be all right...
Go without me. (out of breath)
[TADASHI]
Uh okay... I...
I'll see ya then.
[SHOYO]
Practice time!
[KOSHI] Another day of
humiliating losses...
(RYUNOSUKE exhausted)
[ASAHI]
He's still the same as he's
always been.
[RYUNOSUKE] You mean Tsukishima?
[ASAHI] Yeah.
[RYUNOSUKE]
That guy... How do I
explain it... Ugh...
I feel like he could do
anything he wants to if
he'd just freakin' try.
[ASAHI]
What kind of things?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Like... Uh I don't know...
Like uh.... Agh, what
a waste of height!
[BOKUTO]
Hey, Skinny!
You wanna help us out with
our spikes again today?
[KEI]
I'm sorry... but I'm gonna pass.
[BOKUTO] What, really?
Hey Kuroo!
[KUROO] Shut up.
[BOKUTO]
I haven't said anything yet!
[SHOYO]
What?
So do you like have something
against the ace of Fukurodani?
[KEI] Course not.
[SHOYO] Then why say no?!
That seems like such a waste!
[KEI]
Would you please shut up?
Unlike you, I'm not a stupid
ball of energy.
[SHOYO]
Hey, not cool!
What's his problem?!
[SHOYO]
Fukurodani's ace player makes
the effort to invite him
to practice and he just says
no?! He is such a jerk!
[TADASHI] Hinata... listen...
[SHOYO] Hmm?
[TADASHI] Um what would you
say to Tsukki right now if
you could?
[SHOYO] Huh?
[TADASHI]
You know, like before... when
you talked to Kageyama and
Yachi.
[SHOYO] I wouldn't say anything.
(TADASHI startled)
[SHOYO]
How could I, when I don't even
know if Tsukishima likes
volleyball?
[SHOYO]
What's the point of saying
"Let's play" to somebody who
doesn't even want to?!
[SHOYO]
Argh! He doesn't know how lucky
he is to be that tall!
[SHOYO]
I mean if I had that kind of
ridiculous height.. I would be
unstoppable! It's not fair!
[TADASHI] Well...
(SHOYO surprised)
Look Tsukki doesn't hate
volleyball, Hinata...
Or else, he never
would've joined the club.
[SHOYO] What about you?
[TADASHI] Huh?
[SHOYO]
What would you say?
What would you tell him?
[SHOYO]
Lev! Teach me how to spit
watermelon seeds really far!
[HAIBA] First, curl your mouth
like a blowpipe!
[SHOYO] Okay!
[HAIBA] Spit at a
45 degree angle!
[SHOYO] Yeah?
[HAIBA]
Now bend your body
back like a whip...
[SHOYO]
(swallows) I swallowed 'em...
Next Haikyu!!
"Illusionary Hero".