[YU]
Whoa, is that...?!
[RYUNOSUKE]
I think it is!
[YU & RYUNOSUKE]
The Skytree!
[KAI]
Nah. That's just a regular old
steel tower.
(KUROO laughing)
[RYUNOSUKE & YU]
(excited yell) We're in Tokyo!
[ASAHI]
It doesn't seem that much
different from back home in
Miyagi...
[KOSHI]
Well, we ARE out in
the suburbs y'know.
(KEI yawn)
[YU]
Wake up already!
[KUROO]
Wait a second...
Aren't you missing a few guys?
[DAICHI]
Well, you see...
[YU]
Witness the true power...
[RYUNOSUKE]
...of the second‐years!
(RYUNOSUKE & YU powering up)
I wouldn't brag; the cutoff is
a 40 and you barely passed.
(RYUNOSUKE & YU realize)
[KOSHI]
Huh? Hinata failed English?
What happened?
[KEI]
Well right as the test ended...
he realized that all his answers
were off by one question number.
[ASAHI]
Oh... That's not good...
Ms. Ono's not the type of
teacher who'd let that
kind of thing slide.
[TADASHI]
Yachi didn't really take the
news too well, she was freakin'.
[HITOKA]
They're all correct...
every last one!
[DAICHI]
Kageyama failed Japanese?
[CHIKARA]
He said he didn't expect so
many reading comprehension
problems...
[CHIKARA]
He focused too hard on
memorization.
[ASAHI]
Oh wow! His kanji's perfect
though; that's crazy!
Well, no need to be too
upset... There'll be other
trips after this okay.
[TOBIO] How do we
get to Tokyo now?!
[KOSHI] Uh...
Let's walk there!
Or bike!
[KOSHI, internal]
What is wrong with these guys?!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey... Dork wads.
[TOBIO] Hm?
[SHOYO] Huh?
(RYUNOSUKE grin)
[KUROO]
So the dynamic duo had to stay
and take supplementary lessons?
[DAICHI]
Well uh... That's
not exactly uhm...
(YAMAMOTO excited yell)
[YAMAMOTO]
There's... TWO OF THEM!
One's the sexy kind and one's
the cute kind! I'M NOT WORTHY OF
SUCH A BLESSING! (wailing)
[HITOKA, internal]
A mohawk... Welcome to Tokyo!
[RYUNOSUKE] Take a
good look Tiger head.
(YAMAMOTO gasp)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Behold the glory of
going to Karasuno High.
[YAMAMOTO]
Agh! Hot n' shiny.
(RYUNOSUKE maniacal laughter)
[KIYOKO]
Let's go.
[HITOKA]
O‐okay...
[KUROO]
Well, you guys feel free
to head to the gym whenever
you're ready.
[KUROO]
The rest of our players are
already there, and we'll be
waiting for you.
[DAICHI]
Got it.
(after class chatter)
[ONO] Oh, wow! I can't believe
how serious you two are!
(SHOYO determined)
[RYUNOSUKE]
You both only failed one
subject, right?
[RYUNOSUKE]
If that's the case, you should
be able to finish all your
makeup work in the morning.
Once you've done that...
I'll send in the cavalry.
(school bell ringing)
(TOBIO & SHOYO serious running)
[ONO]
Good luck guys!
[SAEKO]
'Sup, Einsteins?
You ready?
(TOBIO & SHOYO nervous gulp)
[SHOYO]
Hey! You're Tanaka's
older sister!
[SAEKO]
Saeko, but you can
call me Big Sis.
Don't worry, I can get you two
geniuses to Tokyo in a flash.
[SHOYO & TOBIO]
Okay Big Sis!
[SAEKO]
Now let's hit the road!
[SHOYO]
Right!
(bing‐bong)
[RYUNOSUKE]
I CANNOT GUARANTEE it will be a
safe or comfortable ride.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Enter the vehicle at your own
risk. For love of God, please
buckle up!
(SHOYO & TOBIO screaming)
[SAEKO]
(giggling) Woohoo!
Yeahh!
[KEISHIN]
Coach Nekomata. It's
good to see you, sir.
[NEKOMATA]
Oh no, pleasure's all mine.
[TAKEDA]
It was really generous of
you to let us be a part
of the joint practice
session, sir.
[TAKEDA]
Thank you so much
for having us here.
Oh, don't think for a second
we're not benefitting
from this arrangement too...
It's a great opportunity for
both of us to see just where
you stand.
(KEISHIN & TAKEDA awkward)
[KURASUNO]
Ready!
(Practice drills )
[KENMA]
Hey... Shoyo's not here.
[YAMAMOTO]
He got stuck at school.
Yeah?
[KUROO]
After you and your teammates
finish warming up, you'll be
in this group.
[KUROO] Then everyone will
rotate teams every game.
[DAICHI] Sounds good.
[KUROO]
And after each set, all of the
losing teams have to do a flying
lap around the court.
(DAICHI acknowledges)
[HITOKA] What's a flying‐lap?
[KIYOKO]
It's similar to the motion
they do for a flying receive,
intercepting the ball in midair.
[KIYOKO]
For a flying lap, they slide
along the ground with their
hands close to their chests.
[KUROO]
The match list is over there if
you want to take a look at it.
[KOSHI]
[KUROO] I'm pretty sure your
first match will be against the
Shinzen team.
[KOSHI]
[ASAHI] Hmm? (startled)
[DAICHI] Great, thanks.
[ASAHI]
You mean the guy staring at us?
[KOSHI]
Yeah.
[ASAHI]
Nope. Never seen him before.
(TOBIO snoring)
(SHOYO uneasy)
[SAEKO]
Aw, don't stress yourself out,
kid. I understand you're in a
hurry.
[SHOYO]
Oh? (struggle)
But the way I see it, if
you never take a detour,
then you might never get
to see the flowers.
Yeah I have no idea what
that means, but I'll take
your word for it.
Oh my god... You should be
thankful you failed that exam;
or you wouldn't've taken this
little road trip with me!
(SAEKO catches herself)
(TOBIO bumps head, snorts)
You must really love
your volleyball to go
through all this, kid.
[SHOYO] Yup!
[SAEKO] So what got you into
it in the first place?
(surprised) In middle
school, I saw the Spring
Nationals on TV!
[SHOYO]
Karasuno happened
to be playing, so...
[SHOYO] I saw the Tiny Giant!
[SAEKO] You saw the Tiny Giant?
Guess you did.
(SHOYO shocked)
[SAEKO] What... did
that freak you out?
[SHOYO]
Wait a second you know
about the Tiny Giant too?!
[SAEKO]
I'm pretty certain we were in
the same grade! (soft laugh)
(SHOYO mindblown)
[SAEKO]
I never talked to him though.
If he'd been a troublemaker,
[SAEKO]
we probably would have
hung out all the time.
[SHOYO]
So you're one of those girls
who's attracted to like bad boys
and stuff?
[SAEKO]
(laugh) Is that a thing?!
(TOBIO grumbles sleepily)
[SAEKO]
Anyway...
(machine beep)
(gym chatter)
[SAEKO]
When I used to see him playing
in practice matches...
[SAEKO]
that kid was scarier to me than
any tough guy I'd ever met.
[SHOYO] Huh?
[SAEKO] Maybe intimidating's
a better word.
[SHOYO] So you mean
his spikes, or uh...?
[SAEKO] No...
[SAEKO]
There was one time they subbed
him out. I guess maybe he wasn't
feeling well.
(scared gasp)
(SHOYO question)
He was one of those
"ace players"
or whatever you guys call them.
[SAEKO]
I'm sure being the ace inspires
this crazy amount of pride and
confidence, right?
Well, that guy was
dripping with it.
[SAEKO]
I think I almost fell in love
with him! (laugh)
Besides... when the
ace is in play...
[SAEKO]
...all the other guys are on
their game.
That's 'cause nobody wants to be
a hundred percent dependent on
him, you know?
[TOBIO, groggily]
You really know a lot about the
Tiny Giant, don'tcha.
[SAEKO]
(startled) I‐I never said that!
I just saw a few of his stupid
games, that's all!
[SAEKO]
(chomp) When the hell did you
wake up?
[TOBIO]
Got hungry. (chewing)
[SAEKO]
You're a simple
creature, aren't you?
[TOBIO]
(belch) Yup.
It won't make you any better
and it certainly won't
make our team worse.
[SHOYO, internal]
A crazy amount of pride and
confidence.. that comes from
being the ace...
Well, it's just a little
further... Let's step on it!
Woooooo!
[DAICHI]
No. 7!
[ASAHI]
One blocker!
[CHIKARA]
Nice receive, Nishinoya!
[BOKUTO]
Okay... let's go left guys!
(whistle)
[ASAHI]
Man!
(long whistle)
[TAKEDA]
They're just as strong
as we expected.
[KEISHIN]
Yeah.
[DAICHI]
One flying lap!
[ALL]
Yessir!
[KEISHIN]
It's not that we're playing a
bad game or anything.
I mean these guys are
national‐level players.
(whistle)
[SENGOKU] Serve's up!
(KEISHIN surprised)
[OGANO]
Oooh, real nice, ponytail!
[HITOKA]
(skittish) That's powerful!
[KIYOKO]
Every member of that team has
an especially good serve.
[HITOKA]
Oh, right, Ubugawa's manager did
say they put a lot of effort
into serving.
[KIYOKO]
That's right. I guess ending
every practice with
a hundred serves must
really make a difference.
[SENGOKU]
Give us another one!
[KIYOKO]
At Ubugawa High School, serves
are their specialty.
(ASAHI tense breathing)
They're good, but if we
can hit that serve back
at 'em, just once...
[OGANO]
Bring it!
[HITOKA]
Whoa, all of them went after it
at the same time!
[OGANO]
Oh yeah gimme summa that!
(whistle)
[KIYOKO]
Y'see that combo?
[HITOKA]
Yikes... They're all popping up
out of nowhere,
so I can't tell which one of
them is going to hit the ball!
[OGANO]
(proud smirk) All riiiight!
[KIYOKO]
Shinzen High School:
Masters of Combo Moves.
(RYUNOSUKE uneasy)
[TAKEDA]
And of course...
there's our sworn rivals.
[YAMAMOTO]
Yaku!
[KEISHIN]
I see that receive is as
flawless as ever.
[TAKEDA]
No matter what, they always dig
in, connect, and strike back.
They're a solid team.
[YAKU]
Double block!
[KEISHIN] No joke.
[KONOHA] Sorry! Cover!
[BOKUTO]
Akaashi!
[TAKEDA] Just like
Shiratorizawa...
[AKAASHI] Bokuto!
[BOKUTO]
I got it!
[TAKEDA]
They've got one of the top five
aces in the nation.
(whistle)
[TADASHI]
Tsukki!
(KEI surprised)
Don't you run from it, Kenma!
[KENMA] It'll take
my arms off...
[NEKOMATA] It will not!
[TAKEDA]
I'm so glad we got to
be a part of this.
[BOKUTO]
Aw yeah, baby! You like that?
Whoooo's the greatest of all
time?!
[TAKEDA]
A powerhouse at the national
level with a legendary ace.
Fukurodani Academy!
[TAKEDA]
It's great we get to face
a team like them.
[KEISHIN] Pretty cool.
(KEI grunt)
[KEISHIN]
Still... This isn't the time to
be intimidated by their skill.
[KEISHIN]
We have to focus on going
toe‐to‐toe with these guys.
(long whistle)
[DAICHI]
Let's go! One flying lap, guys!
[ALL]
Yessir!
[SHINZEN A]
How many losses has
it been for them?
[SHINZEN B]
They're not really weak or
anything... it's more like...
normal.
[FUKURODANI A]
Which first‐year is the one
Nekoma had trouble with?
[FUKURODANI A]
Maybe Nekoma was too cocky.
(HITOKA offended grumble)
[KIYOKO]
It's okay, Yachi,
just ignore those guys.
Don't worry. If what Tanaka says
is true, then we'll be alright.
[SAEKO]
(out of breath) Oh, good,
they're still at it... We made
it just in the nick of time.
[YU] Big sis!
[ASAHI] I had no idea you
had a sister, Nishinoya.
[SAEKO] Heeey!
[YU]
No, that's Tanaka's sister!
[KOSHI]
Oh yeah, I see it.
[SAEKO]
What's up bro?
(panting) Glad you dummies
could make it out.
(TOBIO & SHOYO heavy panting)
(SAEKO grin)
[KUROO]
So the main characters show up
fashionably late, huh?
[KUROO]
Oh how tackyyy.
[BOKUTO]
Oh?
(AKAASHI exhale)
(TAKEDA, KEISHIN, KIYOKO,
& HITOKA excited)
(NEKOMATA satisfied smirk)
(TOBIO & SHOYO panting)
(whistle)
[OGANO]
Serve's up!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice receive!
(whistle)
[KONOHA]
Whoa, what's with that?
[ONAGA]
That was like stupid fast...
[KOMI]
I've never seen a
quick attack like that.
[OGANO]
We'll stop the next one!
[YOSHIKAWA & CHIGAYA]
Yeah!
(whistle)
[DAICHI]
Here we go!
[AKATANI]
Sorry! Cover!
[BOKUTO] Hot damn, that's
what I call a great serve!
[OGANO] Come on, Eikichi!
[CHIGAYA] Tch! (shock)
[KOSHI] Nice one, Hinata!
[OGANO]
You take care of
Number 10, Eikichi!
(whistle) (long whistle)
[CHIGAYA]
Dammit! I barely grazed
it! He's too fast!
[OGANO]
Those guys can't just bust in
here with a crazy quick‐attack
like that!
(TOBIO & SHOYO panting)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Turd‐nuggets who show up late
don't get to show off.
(TOBIO & SHOYO mortified)
[OGANO]
Flying laps. C'mon.
[SHINZEN]
Yessir!
[DAICHI]
It took 'til our ninth set,
but we finally won a match
so we dodged the flying lap.
[YU]
I'm starving!
(whistle)
[SENGOKU] Nice serve!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Looks like it's Ubugawa against
Nekoma playing over there.
[RYUNOSUKE]
It's late now... I bet that'll
be the last game today.
[YU]
Yeah.
[SHOYO, internal]
They managed to keep up with
our quick attack in the second
half.
(internal) Date Tech...
Seijoh... and that Inuoka guy...
(internal)
I guess I can't expect it to
work forever. Especially against
the faster opponents.
[INUOKA]
Yaku! Nice receive!
[SHOYO]
Wait a sec...
Inuoka swapped out?
[SHIBAYAMA]
Single blocker!
[INUOKA]
You got this, Lev!
(SHOYO gasp)
(whistle) (NEKOMA cheers)
[SHOYO]
That swing was just like a
whip... How'd he do that?
[ASAHI]
Amazing...
[KOSHI]
He's even taller than he looks.
You can't tell at first because
he hunches so much, but he's
pretty big.
[KOSHI]
I'd say he's at least 6'3".
[ASAHI]
Look how long his arms are.
[KOSHI]
Is he even human?
(whistle) (long whistle)
(NEKOMA cheers)
[OGANO]
What the hell is up with
these Karasuno guys?
That setter? And that
tiny middle‐blocker?!
[GOURA]
They did a number on you.
[OGANO]
Oh Shut up! You try facing down
one of those quick‐attacks!
[OGANO]
I'd like to see one of you
jerk‐holes handle it better!
[BOKUTO]
(amused laugh) Well this is
about to be an interesting year.
[KUROO]
Thank you for the games!
[EVERYONE]
[INUOKA]
Y'know. Your quick‐attacks were
just as great as always, Hinata!
[SHOYO]
Thanks but... we don't seem
to be improving very much.
[INUOKA]
Hm?
[SHOYO, internal]
We're just like before.
Hm... The whole point of coming
here was to get stronger.
[SHOYO]
Oh! That's right...
I was gonna ask you guys,
what's with that big tall
middle blocker?
[KENMA]
Oh... That's Lev Haiba,
first‐year.
He's half‐Russian,
half‐Japanese.
[SHOYO]
Half‐Russian?
No way! That's cool!
[SHOYO]
His name is... what now?
[KENMA]
His name's Lev...
It's Russian for...
I think it's like... "tiger"?
[INUOKA]
No, not tiger... it's Lion!
[SHOYO]
He's new, isn't he?
[KENMA]
Yeah... he just started playing
volleyball this school year.
[KENMA]
When we went to see you guys
during Golden Week, he was still
learning the ropes.
[KENMA]
We only took the players we
already had on the bench.
[SHOYO]
THAT GUY's new to volleyball?!
[KENMA]
Yeah... It was tough for me
because I kept getting paired
with him.
[KENMA]
I tried to adjust to him, but
our timing was always weird.
It's gotten better, though.
[SHOYO] Whoa...
[INUOKA] Yeah well... You didn't
seem too stressed out about it.
[SHOYO]
So even Kenma gets
caught off guard!
[KENMA]
Well, he's just kinduv
a strange person...
[KENMA]
He's mostly relying on his
instincts and physical ability
at the moment.
[KENMA]
Plus his height.
[SHOYO]
Heck yeah! He's way too tall,
it's not fair!
[INUOKA]
I cannot believe that
guy's luck! But he
still won't outdo me!
[KENMA]
Well, he's a good player, and
he's honest,
so I don't mind him. Though
sometimes he can be TOO honest.
[KENMA]
But... that said... he sucks at
passes and some basic stuff...
Even worse than you do.
[KENMA] His serves are way
worse than yours are, too.
[SHOYO] Wait, are you
saying I suck?!
[YAKU] I don't think I've never
known Kenma to be so outgoing as
he is now!
[KENMA] Well, you kinda do.
(KAI nods)
[SHOYO] Hey...
[SHOYO]
Lev Haiba... Huh?
He's even got one of those fancy
European names and everything!
(SHOYO panicking)
[SHOYO, internal]
Uh‐oh! I‐I should say hi! How do
you say hi in Russian?!
[HAIBA] Ah Karasuno's No.10...
[SHOYO] You don't speak
Russian?!
[HAIBA]
Yeah no sorry, I don't
speak a word of Russian.
Believe it or not, I was
actually born and raised
in Japan.
[SHOYO]
Huh, that's not what I was
expecting.
Anyway my name's Shoyo
Hinata, I'm a first‐year,
how tall are you?
[HAIBA]
Oh my name is Lev Haiba, and I'm
a first‐year too... And uh last
I checked I'm six‐foot‐four.
[SHOYO]
6'4"! I'm jealous!
[HAIBA]
Y'know...You look even tinier
from up close.
[SHOYO]
What was that, why don't you
come down here and say that to
my face! (growl)
[HAIBA]
Oh I'm sorry!
That came out wrong.
But I know that you can jump all
the way up to here if you want
to... I saw you do it during the
game.
[HAIBA]
(chuckle) Of course,
I can jump even higher.
[SHOYO]
(yowl of pain) Ouch!
(whimpering)
[SHOYO]
(shaking pain off) Fine...
I'll just have to get to the
top before you do.
[SHOYO]
Your spikes are great...
It's like it doesn't even
really matter to you
what's blocking your way.
[HAIBA]
Mm‐hm. Well that's because...
[HAIBA] I happen to
be the ace of Nekoma.
[SHOYO] Oh?
[HAIBA]
But Yamamoto gets really angry
whenever I mention that though.
[YAMAMOTO]
Whaaat?! How can you be Nekoma's
ace when you can't defend worth
a dried up crap?!
[SHOYO]
But Lev... You play middle
blocker position
so you're part of the
center line, just like I am.
[SHOYO]
I thought to be the ace,
you had to be a wing spiker,
like that mohawk
guy on your team.
[HAIBA]
What does it matter what the
name of the position is?
(SHOYO gasps)
[HAIBA]
To be the ace on the team... All
you have to do is score the most
points... That's all.
[HAIBA]
I'll see you tomorrow Hinata.
I look forward to being the
first person
to stop that special
quick attack of yours.
(SHOYO gasp)
[SHOYO]
The guy who scores the
most points is the ace...
That's all..
[SHOYO]
Is that really true?
(practice)
[SHOYO]
Bring it!
(whistle)
(KURASUNO cheers)
[NAOI]
Seems like Karasuno's more
stable than during Golden Week.
[NAOI]
And the quick‐attack from Number
10 is as sharp as always!
You're right about that;
I'd say they've really started
to gain their footing since we
last met them.
[NEKOMATA, internal]
But are you satisfied with
that, Karasuno?
[NEKOMATA, internal]
This amount of strength wasn't
enough for you to win last time.
[NEKOMATA]
And your reason for coming
here... ultimately was to
improve.
(long whistle)
Look! They haven't come up
with a countermeasure for
the crazy quick yet,
so try to use it as
much as you can!
[TOBIO]
Right!
[SHOYO]
Okay.
[HITOKA]
You need a towel?
[KEI]
Oh, thanks.
[YAMAMOTO]
Number 4!
[YAMAMOTO] It's up!
Cover for it, Kenma!
[KAI] Left, left!
[HAIBA]
Send it to me Kenma!
Over here now!
(whistle)
[HAIBA]
Yeah!
[YAMAMOTO]
Nice kill, Lev!
[HAIBA]
Sorry I got a little bossy with
you; I just got carried away.
[KENMA]
I've told you a million times,
I don't mind stuff like that...
[KENMA]
I'm just shocked you suddenly
asked me for a broad jump setup.
[HAIBA]
Oh, is that what that's
called? Interesting!
[TOBIO]
(surprised) So that broad jump
was just out of the blue?
[HAIBA]
But hey... we still pulled it
off, right?
[HAIBA]
Well that's because... I happen
to be the ace of Nekoma.
Center ace... Okay...
(long whistle)
[NAOI]
You're next up to serve, Kenma!
[NEKOMATA, internal]
We lost the Inter‐High
preliminaries...
What is it going to take for
us to keep moving forward now?
[NEKOMATA] I'm not sure
if it'll do the trick,
[HAIBA] You can do it, Kenma!
Give us a good serve okay!
[NEKOMATA]
but this new blood flowing
through Nekoma's veins ought
to change things up.
[NEKOMATA, internal]
And what will Karasuno
pursue in order to grow
stronger?
[NEKOMATA]
Stability...
or perhaps...
[NEKOMATA]
Evolution?
[KUROO]
Lev is getting pretty used
to everybody now.
[KENMA] Yeah, gradually.
[HAIBA] What? That's not true!
[KUROO]
Oh, you think you still
have a ways to go?
[HAIBA]
No! I'm the ace, so I'm ALREADY
in sync with the team!
[KUROO]
Only thing you're the ace
at is being a numbskull.
[KUROO]
Next Haikyu!! "Greed".