[BULLY A]
What's up, Tadashi?
You want some anchovies
for that Pizza face!
[BULLY B]
Man, you're such a
wimpy little dork!
[BULLY B]
If you don't like it, then you
better toughen up... Why don't
you carry our stuff?
(YOUNG TADASHI tearing
up into whimpering)
[BULLY B] Dude, he's crying!
[BULLY A]
This guy cries over everything!
[BULLY B]
(laughing) Cry baby!
(TADASHI sniffles) (surprised)
[BULLIES]
Huh?
[BULLY B]
What are you lookin' at?!
[BULLY A]
(nervous) I think he's
older than us!
[BULLY B]
Nah, he's in Class 3.
[YOUNG KEI]
(smirk) That's so lame.
[BULLIES & YOUNG TADASHI]
Uh?
[BULLY B]
What's so lame?!
Wait! I'm talkin' to you!
[KEI]
What?
[BULLY B]
(startled) (catches breath)
Well...
[BULLY B]
Your glasses are stupid! Get
outta here, Four Eyes!
(KEI cracks up)
[BULLY A]
H‐hey, wait for me! (scared)
[TADASHI]
To this day, I'm not exactly
sure if Tsukishima was calling
me lame too. Hmm. Anyway...
[TADASHI]
But what stood out to me was
that,
even though he was outnumbered,
he had the guts to say
that all by himself.
Seeing that really made
me envy him in a way.
[TADASHI]
I wanted to be brave
like that too.
What about you... what would you
say... What would you tell him?
[KEI]
Hey... I'm leaving.
[DAICHI] Alright.
[KOSHI] Good work!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey, Tsukishima!
We're gonna work on that
synced attack now...
You're not leaving yet.
(KEI slight annoyed)
[CHIKARA] I can stay
a while, too.
As long as you don't mind having
three wing spikers at once.
[CHIKARA]
I want to get that
timing locked in.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh?! Oh, I see!
You're after my spot!
Oh come on, you can't expect me
to be a benchwarmer forever.
[RYUNOSUKE]
(taken aback) All right,
that's it! You're goin'
down! Let's go, Daichi!
[DAICHI] Let me rest a
little first, would ya?
[KOSHI] See ya later!
[RYUNOSUKE]
But Captain! Some of us can't
afford to sit back and watch
like you can!
[KEI]
It's just a game.
[IZUMIDATE A]
Left, left!
[IZUMIDATE B]
Number 4!
(CROWD cheers)
[MOTHER A] My, that
Tsukishima's good!
[MOTHER B]
Well, he is the ace!
[AMEMARU 6]
Nice kill, bro!
[AMEMARU 5]
Good one!
(KEI proud grin)
[KEI]
Which high school
are you going to?
[AKITERU]
Karasuno... These days,
I think they'll even give
Shiratorizawa a run for their
money!
[AKITERU]
And I'll make sure we
go to nationals too!
(KEI proud)
[AKITERU]
(exhausted sigh) I'm back!
[KEI]
Hey, welcome home!
You stayed late again?
Everyone's so good, I have
to work really hard to catch up.
And Coach Ukai's a drill
sergeant... But still!
[AKITERU]
I gotta do whatever it
takes to make it happen.
[KEI]
There's a whole lot of guys on
the team... It'd be so cool if
you could do that!
[AKITERU]
I know, right?
[AKITERU] Hey mom!
[MOM] Welcome home!
[AKITERU]
Can I have three lunches
again tomorrow?
One for morning drills,
lunchtime, and team practice?
[KEI'S MOM]
Sure thing! High in protein and
low in fat, right, son?
[AKITERU]
Perfect! Thanks a lot!
[KEI]
Today, the lady at the
butcher shop said
"You're the little brother
of that great Karasuno
player, aren't you?"
[AKITERU]
Oh yeah?
[KEI]
You have a game tomorrow, right?
Can I come watch you?
[AKITERU]
(mulling it over) Sorry, I think
you'd throw me off.
[KEI]
(disappointed) Hey, what
position do you play now?
The same as in middle school?
[AKITERU]
Yeah, that's right.
[KEI]
Then, you're the ace!
[AKITERU]
Kinda.
(KEI grins, caught off guard)
[AKITERU]
You joined the boy scouts' team
the other day, right? What do
you do?
[KEI]
Receiving... It sucks.
[AKITERU]
In the beginning,
they don't quite
go the way you want
them to, right?
[AKITERU]
Stand over there for me.
[KEI]
Huh?
[AKITERU]
Ready?
(KEI sighs)
[AKITERU]
Look...
Don't try to push it up
with your arms.
[AKITERU]
First you gotta drop your waist
a little...
Then use your whole body to send
it out... Try tossing it to me.
[KEI]
Whoa!
[AKITERU]
It all starts with the receive.
And communication is
everything...
Are you friends with the other
kids on the team? At all?
[KEI]
(awkward) Yeah, duh.
[AKITERU]
Nice try!
You're not a very good
liar, kid.
[KEI]
Man...
(practice)
[KEI]
Hm?
Excuse me.
[TADASHI]
(shocked) Uhhh... wait!
Thank you for
the other day!
[KEI]
Hmm? (startled) Do I know you?
[TADASHI]
(shocked) Y‐Yeah...
Well, not really...
W‐we met at the park...!
[KEI]
Oh... Okay, what
are you doing here?
Uh... Well... I wanted to
play a sport too...
But baseball and soccer had
a lot of big scary guys so...
[TADASHI]
So I thought I'd be okay here.
Hey! Your shoes are really cool!
I always just use the ones
they give you in gym class.
[KEI]
They're my big brother's...
I'm just wearing them until I
get some new ones next week.
[TADASHI]
Oh your brother plays
volleyball?
[KEI]
He's playing at a powerhouse
called Karasuno High School...
And uh... he's... the ace.
[TADASHI]
(impressed) At a school like
that?!
Dude.. that's awesome!
(fascinated)
[KEI]
It... it's nothing...
It's not a big deal...
He's always been like that!
[TADASHI]
No way!
So he played in middle school?
Was he on this team?
Wow, I can't believe it!
(door sliding open)
[AKITERU]
I'm home.
(door closing)
So how was the
practice match today?
[AKITERU]
Oh yeah it was pretty great!
I landed a ton of spikes!
[KEI]
That's awesome!
Let's practice!
[AKITERU]
Um... uh after we eat.
[KEI]
Tadashi.
[BOY A] What was the
next class again?
[BOY B] Japanese.
[KEI]
Let's go watch Karasuno play
tomorrow... Cool?
[BOY A] Huh?
[KEI] My brother keeps saying
he'll get nervous if I go.
[KEI]
But he's a third‐year, so
this'll be the last chance
for me to see him play.
[TADASHI]
(excited) Sure! I still
haven't actually seen
one of the games yet!
[BOY A]
Your brother plays volleyball
for Karasuno High School? My
brother does too!
[BOY A]
What position is he?
[KEI]
He's a wing spiker.
[BOY A]
Yeah?! Same here!
But they've got way too many
people on the roster though.
[BOY A]
It would suck to go to a school
like that and never get to play,
don't you think?
[TADASHI]
(confused) Yeah but Tsukki's
brother DOES play.
[BOY A]
Wait... nuh‐uh! I just went to a
Karasuno game
and I didn't see a guy named
Tsukishima on the roster.
(KEI quiet shock)
[KEI]
You don't know what you're
talking about...
[KEI]
He's always telling me
about the games... You
don't know anything.
(BOY A caught off guard)
[BOY A]
Well, let's go to a game then
and see!
[KEI]
Yeah, we'll see alright.
(CROWD cheering)
(KEI panicked breathing)
[TEAMMATES A]
One more! Nice receive!
[TEAMMATES B]
Coming Left! Left!
(CROWD cheers)
(KEI snaps out of it)
[ALL]
Yeah!
[CLASSMATE A]
Wow! Check out the
ups on Number 10!
It's hard to believe
that guy's only 5'7"!
[CLASSMATE B]
Yeah, and he's only a
second‐year, too...
[BOY A]
You see?! That guy on the
left side is a third‐year
named Kawata,
and the ace player is a
second‐year that everybody
calls the Tiny Giant!
It's been that way
for over a year!
[TADASHI]
We get it already, okay!
Please just leave him alone.
[BOY A]
Yeah, well... My big
brother's a third year
and he hasn't gotten to
play a single game either.
[KEI, internal]
What is this?
[KEI]
It's like the feeling you get
when your favorite character in
a movie gets killed...
[KRI]
but for some reason, this...
this is even worse.
[KEI]
I don't see my big
brother anywhere.
[TEAMMATES]
One more! One more!
[AKITERU]
Go for it, guys!!
[KEI]
That's so lame.
It was nothing
but a stupid game.
[KEI]
But it seemed like it was
everything my brother stood for.
[KEI]
Enough for him to lie to me.
Then, you're the ace!
[AKITERU]
Kinda.
[KEI]
Maybe he was trying
to make himself
believe he could be the
ace if he tried hard enough.
[KEI]
But even if he could...
Was it really worth all that
desperation?
[TADASHI]
Tzukkiiiii! (catches breath)
[KEI]
What?
[TADASHI]
Tsukki, you've
always done everything
in a cool, smart way.
[TADASHI]
And... I was always jealous.
[KEI]
Yeah, and?
(TADASHI catches breath)
(determined)
[TADASHI]
But you've been acting really
lame lately okay!
(KEI caught off guard)
Hinata may very well become
the next Tiny Giant someday!
[TADASHI]
And if that's true, then
you just need to buck up
and beat him!
(KEI stunned)
[TADASHI] You have plenty of
skill! Use it to prove you're
a better player than he is!
[TADASHI]
You have the height, the brains,
and the reflexes,
so why do you always set
limits for yourself?! Why?
(TADASHI breathing heavily)
[KEI]
Fine... let's say I
tried really hard
and became the best player at
Karasuno. What comes after that?
[KEI]
On the off chance that we
get to go to the national
championships, what comes next?
[KEI]
There's always another
level to get to.
No matter how good you get,
you can never be number one.
[KEI]
Which means you'll eventually
lose! Everyone knows that!
[KEI]
What's the point?! What makes
you guys keep pushing?! Why does
it even matter?
(TADASHI seething)
[TADASHI]
(seething) Don't be an idiot...
It's our sense of pride! What
more do you need?! (panting)
(TADASHI heavy
frustrated breathing)
[KEI]
How 'bout that?
The day finally came.
(TADASHI confused)
(KEI laughs to himself)
(TADASHI baffled)
[KEI]
When the hell did you become
such a badass?
(TADASHI confused)
[KEI] Really... You're cool now.
[TADASHI]
(startled) T‐Tsukki? What's
wrong with you?
[KEI, internal]
At least, cooler than me
obsessing over it all...
[KEI]
But still...
I'm not convinced yet.
[TADASHI]
Huh?
[KEI]
I'll go ask them.
[TADASHI]
(confused) Tsukki?
[KOSHI] Uh hey, Daichi.
[DAICHI] Huh?
[KOSHI]
Shouldn't we maybe go
talk to Tsukishima?
[DAICHI]
If we force him to work on it,
it won't be personal training.
[KOSHI]
I guess you do have
a point there.
[DAICHI]
He's fine.
I've known that ever since
we had that very first 3‐on‐3.
[DAICHI]
Though, if Tsukishima starts
saying that he wants to quit...
I'll beg him to stay...
and I expect you to help me.
[DAICHI]
Look, I don't know what's going
on inside his head.
But we're all still going down
the path of development...
and none of us know the limits
of our own talents yet.
[DAICHI]
We still have a lot of
potential. And that
includes him.
[DAICHI]
And we all have to keep moving
forward to reach that potential.
[DAICHI]
Even if we don't understand why.
[KOSHI]
That's true.
[HITOKA]
Say uh, is Tadashi okay? I just
saw him run away making a really
weird noise...
[SHOYO]
Like what?
[HITOKA]
"TZUKIIIII!" yeah.
[SHOYO]
Oh... He's going to talk to
Tsukishima.
[HITOKA]
Did something happen?
[SHOYO]
Yeah. He seemed kinda worried
about him earlier.
[HITOKA]
Oh really?
You know how
Tsukishima never does
anything that isn't cool, right?
[SHOYO]
He always gets good grades,
and he does everything with like
a "SHIIIIING" or a "FWOOOOSH",
you know?
[HITOKA]
Umm... (internal)
I GUESS that makes sense...
[SHOYO]
Anyway, I think
he'll be alright.
[SHOYO]
Cause if he always does what's
coolest...
Then obviously he'll do what it
takes to be good at volleyball!
Cause volleyball's cool.
[AKAASHI]
Oya?
[BOKUTO]
Oya‐oya?
[KUROO]
Oya‐oya‐oya?
[KEI]
There's something I would like
to ask you... Do you mind?
[BOKUTO & KUROO]
Oh no!
[KEI]
(surprised) Okay then...
So uh here goes..
[KEI]
You're on a team that's known
for being pretty good, right?
(BOKUTO annoyed)
[KUROO] (annoyed) Well, yeah!
[KEI]
Even if you could get to
nationals, it's difficult
to win it all, right?
(KUROO annoyed)
[BOKUTO] It's not
impossible, jackass! (snarl)
[AKAASHI]
Oh don't get all bent out
of shape... Let's just
hear him out okay.
[KEI]
I'm asking a sincere question
here... What drives you guys
to work so hard?
[KEI]
Volleyball's only an
extracurricular activity.
[KEI]
Is there any benefit to it other
than being able to put it
on your college application
or something like that?
[BOKUTO]
Just an extracurricular?
(KEI startled)
[BOKUTO]
I have a mind to punch
you in the face.
[KUROO]
Dude. Maybe he's more
interested in his grades.
[KUROO]
Not that you would
know anything about that.
[BOKUTO]
What did you say? I've been
getting better.
I got a forty seven
on my Trig test. (whining)
[KUROO] Um. Congratulations?
[KEI] Should I say something,
or...?
[BOKUTO] Damn right. I'm
like a super genius over here!
[AKAASHI] Nah, this'll take a
minute.
[BOKUTO]
Hey! Tall dude with the glasses!
[KEI]
It's Tsukishima.
[BOKUTO]
Fine then, Tsuki‐blahala!
Is this game... fun to you?
[KEI]
(thinking) No... not really...
[BOKUTO] You think maybe
that's because you suck at it?
(KEI stunned)
[BOKUTO]
I'm a third‐year, and I've gone
to nationals, so I'm way better
than you... I'm like TWO of you!
[KEI]
I already know that.
[BOKUTO] But it wasn't until
only recently I felt like
volleyball was fun.
(KEI surprised)
[BOKUTO]
It started when line shots
became a viable option for me
during games.
[BOKUTO]
Blockers were starting to catch
onto my cross‐court shots and
making things difficult.
So I got ticked, and practiced
my line shots super hard.
[BOKUTO]
Then... at the next tournament,
against the same blockers,
[BOKUTO]
I shot right through and didn't
even let 'em touch the ball.
Made complete fools of 'em.
[BOKUTO]
That one shot alone felt like
YEAH, "My time has come!", know
what I'm sayin'? (laughs)
(KEI caught off guard)
[BOKUTO]
It's all about having a special,
badass personal moment like
that.
[BOKUTO]
Who cares about the future?
As long as you have a chance
at winning the next game...
Nothing else really
matters, does it?
You get hooked on the rush
of beating the guy in front
of you...
[BOKUTO]
and playing with a hundred and
twenty percent of your skill!
There's nothing better!
(KEI shocked)
[BOKUTO]
Well anyway, that's my story
and I'm sticking to it....
[BOKUTO]
Even though yeah I know it might
not really apply to everybody.
[BOKUTO]
So when you say volleyball's
only an extracurricular
activity,
[BOKUTO]
I literally do not understand
what you mean. That said...
I don't necessarily think
you're wrong either, pal.
[BOKUTO]
However... if that moment ever
does come to you...
that's the moment you'll fall
in love with volleyball.
[BOKUTO]
Okay! I answered your question,
so you owe me a few blocks.
[KEI] (startled) Wait, um...!
[KUROO] Yup, fair is fair after
all.
[HITOKA]
(surprised) Tadashi's back now.
[SHOYO] Tadashi! Where is he?
[DAICHI] One more!
[CHIKARA] Let's go!
[TADASHI]
It looks like he's practicing
with the two captains from
Nekoma and Fukurodani.
[SHOYO]
What? are you serious!
Maybe I should go over there...
[TADASHI]
Listen Hinata... Do you see
Tsukki as a rival?
[SHOYO]
Huh? Of course I do!
We both play the same position,
and he has everything that I
don't!
[SHOYO]
I've a lot to make up for.
Practice time! (pumped up yell)
Captain! I'm coming in!
[DAICHI] Sure.
[HITOKA] Hey, if Hinata and
Tsukishima are rivals... then
it's the Sun versus the Moon!
[TADASHI] Huh?
[HITOKA] Their names mean
"SUN shine" and "MOON island"!
[TADASHI]
(surprised) Oh yeah...
You're right!
[SHOYO]
Let's go!
[TADASHI]
I just hope it works out...
[HITOKA]
Oh?
(practice game)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Number 4!
(whistle)
(FUKURODANI cheers)
[HITOKA]
Oh wow. No.4 is really
intense again today.
[KEISHIN] Hey Specs.
[TAKEDA] Huh...
(long whistle)
(FUKURODANI celebrates)
[KEISHIN]
The spikes from No.4
don't need to be stopped.
Just make sure
they hit your hands!
[KURASUNO]
Right!
[HITOKA]
Oh, right...
Even if they can't stop it,
if it hits their hands,
the momentum becomes
a bit weaker.
[KIYOKO]
Yeah... Basically, there are
two different strategies when it
comes to blocking.
[KIYOKO]
The soft‐block makes it easier
to receive the ball by having it
hit the blocker's hand first.
[KIYOKO]
And the kill‐block completely
shuts the offense out.
Kill block... you mean,
kill as in murder?
Maybe...
(HITOKA panicked)
[KEI]
We don't have to stop him.
(KURASUNO shocked)
[KEISHIN]
That's right... if you guys can
slow him down, I won't ask for
anything else.
(TADASHI surprised)
(long whistle)
(whistle)
(FUKURODANI cheers)
[BOKUTO]
Nice receive! Send it over here!
[DAICHI]
Left! Get number 4!
[KUROO]
First, become conscious.
Insert power all the way up to
your fingertips, so that they'll
never get blown back.
[KUROO]
Oh yeah, and don't put your
hands straight up either...
Stretch 'em out...
[KUROO]
So you can teach this owl
with frosted tips a lesson.
[BOKUTO]
You wanna talk hair?! Huh?
[HITOKA, internal]
Let's see... a soft block
touches the ball to weaken
its momentum...
[HITOKA]
and to completely kill the
spike, it's a kill block.
[RYUNOSUKE]
It's a lob!
[YU]
Ggh, dammit!
(whistle)
[TAKEDA] Aagh! No way,
I totally thought he was about
to come in with a hard hit!
[TAKEDA]
Never expected that to
be some sorta feint.
[TAKEDA]
That's a national‐level
ace for ya.
[KEISHIN]
(amazed) Heh.
[RYUNOSUKE] Do you... think...?
[DAICHI] Mm‐hm.
[AKAASHI]
You're not supposed to run away
from it, you know?
[BOKUTO]
(stunned) I didn't run away!
I dodged it! Gracefully!
Big difference!
[WASHIO] You're a liar.
[BOKUTO] Washio! Alright,
fine, I'm sorry!
(KUROO snickers)
(BOKUTO sneers)
[NEKOMATA]
Hey... That's familiar.
(TADASHI gasp)
[NEKOMATA]
Looks like that grumpy
little fledgling's
about to come out of his shell.
(TADASHI relieved)
[HITOKA]
(surprised) The Sun
versus the Moon...
[BOKUTO]
Tsukki, jump me a few blocks!
[KEI]
For the last time,
stop calling me that.
[BOKUTO]
Okay... then how 'bout Skinny?
[KEI] Ugh!
[BOKUTO] All right! You ready to
get started, A‐Dog?!
[AKAASHI]
Is that supposed to be me?
[BOKUTO]
Well who else is it
supposed to be?
[AKAASHI]
Next Haikyu!!
"Versus Umbrella".