[Irihata]:
I'm sure you're tired
of hearing this,
but you need to be more
aggressive with those serves.
I know their Number 10 is giving
us a lot of problems so...
narrow his options.
Right!
Be on your toes.
You guys can do this.
Yessir!
[Keishin]:
Be alert, and don't let Oikawa's
serves intimidate you.
However high or hard he hits,
get under it, and dig it up!
Right!
Some of you consider this
long‐standing rivalry
a mighty burden to carry...
[Takeda]:
But in reality, it's
actually beneficial for us.
Honestly, we have
Aoba Johsai to thank.
They've motivated us
to sharpen our skills.
So let's show off
what we've learned!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yessir!
It's the final set! Just one big
push and we can overtake them!
With this team,
anything is possible!
[Daichi]:
Karasuno, fight!
Fiiight!
[Takinoue]:
Okay, here we go...
[Shimada]:
Yeah. This will decide exactly
where we stand against Seijoh.
You can do it!
You got this, Asahi!
[Yahaba]:
Oikawa, get us a point!
No matter what,
just get the ball up.
We've been trailing
behind them the whole game.
[Koshi]:
Come on, guys... we gotta
turn it around right here!
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Oooooooolé!
His serves are so fast...!
I see 'em coming, but I
feel like I'm reacting
in slow‐motion.
[Hajime]:
Mad Dog, take it!
All right, Mad Dog's engine
is still revved up.
Man, can you believe the arm
this guy? He just won't let up.
Come on... hang
in there guys!
Karasuno, let's fight!
[Hajime]:
Oikawa, get us one more!
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Oooooooolé!
All right!
Oh, it's up!
[Asahi]:
Cover!
YEEEAAAAAAH!
Finally stopped
their flow!
Nice one!
Good one, Bro!
[Ryunosuke]:
Would you calm down?!
All right, good
work, you guys!
[Daichi]:
Tsukishima! You're up!
Oh, right.
[Koshi]:
Go for it, Tsukishima!
Got it!
Mad Dog, yours!
Nice kill!
As always, when Mad Dog is
playing up on the front line,
you can just feel the energy
coming off of him.
[Matsukawa]:
Sure would be nice if
he could play like this
for the entire game.
[Keishin]:
Their ace has both
power and technique.
And Number 16 is both a
powerhouse and a decoy.
He's hard for us
to get a good read on...
Then of course there's Oikawa.
His serves are what
can really do us in.
We have to break
them down somewhere,
or they will break us!
[Irihata]:
It's clear both sides
are pretty equally matched.
When playing at this
high of a skill level,
it doesn't take much...
even the smallest misstep...
...Can turn into
a fatal blow.
...can turn into
[Keishin/Irihata]:
Sink your teeth in and hold on!
This final set is turning out
to be a nail‐biter, too.
Man, Karasuno hasn't been able
to take the lead once.
They have to be tenacious and
not fall even further behind.
[Koshi]:
Asahi! Serve
us up a point!
Yeah!
Whoa!
Wow! Nice shot!
We can't let that bother us
now, we'll get next one.
[Koshi]:
Asahi, get us another one!
It's up!
[Hajime]:
Nice receive!
Dammit.
[Keishin]:
There he goes again.
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Oooooooolé!
Yes! This is their chance
to shut down his serves!
Comin' your way!
[Toru]:
They're comin' with
a fast attack!
[Watari]:
Nice receive, Oikawa!
[Hanamaki]:
Take it Kyotani!
[Ryunosuke]:
Right, right!
Tanaka.
Huh?
Great stuff, you guys!
They did it!
Yes! They ended it!
Woah, did Tsukishima and Tanaka
switch places on that block?
Nice block, you guys!
Yeah! I wonder
if he predicted
[Shimada]:
that a line shot
would be coming?
I thought so...
Nice going, Tsukki!
Y'see that?
Tanaka has been going after
Number 16 pretty hard.
Hm? Y'mean like picking
a fight with the guy?
[Chikara]:
I noticed during the second set,
he had aimed for him and
forced them into a ricochet.
He also blatantly nailed a
narrow shot right next to him.
Even though there weren't any
blockers for a cross‐court shot.
[Yu]:
Seriously? I didn't
pick up on it!
[Chikara]:
You could tell Number 16 was
getting pissed and started
making more line shots
right back at Tanaka.
It seems Tsukishima
caught onto that as well.
[Ryunosuke]:
(hearty laughter)
Read that like
a book, Tsukishima!
I'm proud of ya!
[Kei]:
Uh... right.
[Keishin]:
All right, now we can get back
the momentum. Don't lose it!
I've got it!
Yeah, alright!
[Daichi]:
Number 16! 16!
[Toru]:
You're going to have to get
the point back yourself!
It's out.
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
[Keishin]:
Okay, here it is!
[Takeda]:
Yes! We flipped the lead!
Kill it, boys,
let's goooo!
Yeahhh!
Number 16 is pretty worked
up now. Just look at him.
Can it be... that Tanaka was
tilting him intentionally?
Not quite. While I have
no doubt he was provoking him...
I don't think
it was deliberate.
That's just how...
Tanaka normally is.
[Chikara]:
And I guess Tsukishima
used Tanaka's personality
to our advantage.
[Keishin]:
Seijoh seemed
solid as a rock,
but now we are starting
to see a crack!
This is our chance
to bring them down!
Let's keep the lead up!
All right!
(whistle)
[Gossiping Girl 1]:
Who's that? He
looks kinda, ugh.
[Gossiping Guy 1]:
I'm not sure. He said he
just wants to practice with us.
[Gossiping Guy 2]:
I saw him with a
different club on Saturday.
[Gossiping Girl 1]:
Well, if he's in high school,
what about his own team?
Uh long story short, he doesn't
really get along with them.
So... A
rebellious stage!
I'm surprised he's
playing a team sport.
Well, I assume... there must be
some kind of allure for him.
Oh... uh Kiyoshi... Hey.
Must be a big deal for him
to come all the way
here to practice.
Japan! Japan! Japan...!
Well... we're always short on
having enough guys to play...
Should be fine.
And he's better
than us, anyway.
[Gossiping Guy 1]:
Huh?! We are not
gonna lose, okay!
[Gossiping Girl 1]:
Aww, does that hurt
your little boy feelings?
[Gossiping Guy 1]:
Shut up!
[Daichi]:
Give it to 'em, Tsukishima!
Got it!
It's yours, Mad Dog!
[Team Karasuno]
(cheering)
[Spectator 1]:
Even with th time‐out,
he's no good.
[Spectator 2]:
Maybe it's impossible
for him to do more...
Since Seijoh's has
plenty of substitutes.
Maybe it's time they
pulled him back out.
It's fine. Relax.
Go scold Mad Dog!
(whistle)
If you want to get
back on the court, son...
you'll need to
check your attitude.
Get yourself
together already...
We've got our backs
to the wall now.
Yeah, whatever...
Who cares?
Yahaba, please... could you
just go a little easy on him.
Rather not... Sorry.
[Yahaba]:
Falling for the opponent's
taunt, getting worked up,
and self‐destructing?
That's lame.
What did you say?
The way you saunter
back onto the court...
with no regard to the kind
of crap you may have pulled...
Well, y'know not
everybody's gonna stand
for that kind of garbage...
I know I won't.
That said...
[Matsukawa]:
It's not like he
caused any real problems...
so if we're able to
use him during a game,
it should be
okay, right?
You sure he can keep up
with our practice though?
He's been on break.
Well, he's never on break
from being an asshole.
Well...
Those are not the moves of a guy
who hasn't been practicing.
I thought it was
a cold‐hearted move,
both against us
and against you.
[Yahaba]:
But that's not
the problem at all.
People we need most
become the regular members.
And you were chosen.
So I suggest you
earn your keep.
Man, he's gonna freak out and
pound Yahaba into a bloody pulp!
Could get ugly.
You should go try
and stop him..
Hell no!
But then, that's
all superficial.
Huh?
If you sling mud onto our
upperclassmen's big game...
then I will never,
ever forgive you!
Well now... Turns out you
actually do give a damn.
Well you at least
got that much right...
Each and every one of us should
respect their upperclassmen.
[Yahaba]:
Every point you gain or
lose goes for the whole team.
So please,
lend us your power.
[Hajime]:
Got it!
[Yutaro]:
Center!
Kunimi!
Kunimi's attack.
There's a chance...
...for a fakeout!
Tanaka!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
Kageyama... good eye
back there.
Thank you.
(whistle)
Huh? He's
already back in.
This guy again?
That was quick.
[Shimada]:
Though it must be
a gamble for Seijoh.
Out, it's out!
Sh‐shake it off...
[Player 1]:
He's kind of off today.
What should we do?
We don't have anyone else with
that much attack power, y'know?
Yeah but if his condition
gets any worse,
we're gonna be
in big trouble.
[Player 2]:
For now, let's pass it to
everyone else and just
keep our eyes on him.
[Chikara]:
Let's go, Tanaka!
It's mine!
[Toru]:
Nice receive!
Mad Dog, it's yours!
Oikawa's so sadistic.
They relentlessly depend
on him without question...
It's been a while since you came
here, lone wolf high school kid.
Huh?
So uh... I heard you're
going to Aoba‐Johsai...
They're a real powerhouse.
I couldn't get in there.
You're running away from your
team and practicing here
and there with no set home.
You sure picked
the easy way.
Huh?!
A team is reliable...
They're allies...
but then at the same time, they
can be a real pain in the ass...
That's for sure.
Until you learn how to
deal with that head‐on...
you can't really play
the game, y'know?
[Kiyoshi]:
You need to face the team,
and the team needs to face you.
If you can do that,
you can butt heads
and become stronger as a result.
Yeah!
[Kiyoshi]:
And, if you can do that,
remember that you're lucky.
Teams like that aren't
lying around everywhere.
They are such a good team.
Yeah!
[Kiyoshi]:
Keep it up, guys.
Sorry! Get it next time!
Yeah!
[Hajime]:
Mad Dog, it's you!
Good shot there.
Thanks.
Y'know if that Number 16
was a part of our team...
I can't help but wonder...
how we would all handle
the same situation.
[Koshi]:
Gotta admit... Oikawa really is
good at what he does, huh?
Let's get a point, guys!
[Team Seijoh]:
Yeah!
Up to this point... that 16
looked like an outlier...
but during that
last play we saw,
it's like the guy
is a perfect fit.
I don't like it...
In terms of total
team power...
we're not out of this thing yet,
Coach. Keep watching.
Right.
[Matsukawa]:
Kill it, Mad Dog!
[Yu]:
Tanaka!
[Tobio]:
Nice receive!
[Toru]:
Watacchi, nice!
[Ryunosuke]:
Counter!
[Toru]:
Great job, fellas!
Aw, man!
It's a tie!
Yeah, Seijoh
caught up!
[Yahaba]:
Kyotani, one more!
Yeah!
[Ryunosuke]:
Chance ball!
Slam it! Asahi!
Damn it!
Sorry, guys!
That's our ace for ya...
You smoked 'em!
That felt good!
You knocked the
crap outta that one!.
When it comes down to
Hinata's spikes...
If the window is narrowed
down or read correctly,
they can dig them up.
Yeah.
I have to use him
more effectively...
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
Man, not this again!
[Shimada]:
Every time it's
Oikawa's turn to serve,
I feel like my life
gets a bit shorter.
[Hitoka]:
Urgh... I think I might puke...
[Takinoue]:
Looks like everybody on the team
is feeling that way as well.
It's almost time for
the mid‐game to end.
If we lose a bunch of points
here, it'll kill us.
Let's end it with
just one serve!
[Yu]:
Bring it on!
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Oooooooolé!
[Yu]:
Daichi!
How does he dig up
something like that?
It's a chance ball!
Dammit! They're going
for the quick!
Kindaichi!
Dammit.
Shake it off!
If you have a request
for me, just say it!
Oikawa will fix things if I just
tell him. I gotta let him know.
Um... Oikawa...
I don't know what it was,
but the last one felt like
it was a little tough
to connect with.
Huh... okay, then.
[Toru]:
But, let's try it for
a little longer, okay?
Your point of impact is going
to be further out!
About one ball width.
Try it like that.
Yeah!
All Right!
A snappy broad jump.
Kindaichi's moving
differently than he did during
the Inter‐High prelims.
Shake it off!
You can end it right here!
C'mon! Concentrate!
It's a side‐out!
At the last second Seijoh was
able to turn this thing around!
This is rough...
It's becoming a tug‐o‐war
between the two teams now.
True... I guess... Oikawa raises
the standard of the entire team
by his own merit.
[Takeda]:
He really is something else.
I get why you'd say that.
[Keishin]:
But it's not even close to
the total strength of our team!
[Watari]:
Give 'em hell, Oikawa!
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Oooooooolé!
My bad! Tsukishima!
[Hajime]:
This one's yours,
Kindaichi!
Thanks a lot, pal!
It's all you, Hinata!
Okay!
[Hajime]:
Let's shut this down!
[Team Seijoh]:
Yeah!
The Great King really
is a special guy.
And how would
you know?
[Shoyo]:
I can just tell.
But still...!
With me around...
you can beat anyone!
Huh... Y'know, that
was kinda cool.
If you say so...
You're getting dug up
all over the place.
Yeah, well...!
Gettin' all ballsy
for no reason... Yeah, man!
[Shoyo]:
I‐I have a ballsy reason!
[Ryunosuke]:
I bet you do!
(laughs)
I got it!
Nice receive. Mad Dog!
Nice one‐touch!
I got it!
Bring it to me!
I jumped too far!
The net's too close!
The ball's too
close to the net!
[Koshi]:
It's right on top of it!
[Tobio]:
No one's there!
Slam it down!
To the front!
[Shoyo]:
It's the final set,
and the score is 17‐16.
We're coming to the end!
[Tobio]:
Yeah.
[Shoyo]:
We're gonna win!
Yeah.
Bring all the sets to me!
[Tobio]:
Next Haikyu!! ‐
"Switch for the Utmost Limit"
[Shoyo]:
You did hear that
last part, right?!
[Tobio]:
Huh?