[DAICHI]
Group up!
[KEISHIN]
Our first game today
is against Nekoma.
How'd we make out yesterday?
[KIYOKO]
Today will be the third set
we've played against Nekoma...
[KIYOKO]
Yesterday, we had two sets
against them and lost them both,
17‐25 and 19‐25.
[KEISHIN]
Eh... that just means we haven't
won a set off them yet.
[KEISHIN]
But if we calm down and give it
all we've got, we should be able
to give them a good challenge.
[KEISHIN]
Hey, this is the first Nekoma
game for you two in a long time,
right?
[KEISHIN]
Go out there and rough
'em up a little bit!
[TOBIO & SHOYO]
Right!
(long whistle)
[REFEREE]
Okay. Let's get going.
[YAKU]
Serve's up, Fukunaga!
[HAIBA]
I look forward to being
the first person...
to stop that special
quick attack of yours.
[SHOYO]
Bring it on!
(SAEKO snoring)
(SAEKO startled awake)
(hang over moan)
(SAEKO cackles)
[SAEKO] Shouldn't have gone
drinking with the faculty last
night...
[SAEKO, yawning]
What time is it?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice receive!
(whistle) (KURASUNO cheers)
[HAIBA] That guy is really
incredible!
[YAMAMOTO] Nice try, Lev, you
almost had it!
[HAIBA] Thanks!
[ASAHI] Give us another good
one, Tanaka!
[SHINZEN COACH] So Karasuno's
Number 10 does close his eyes
[KAI] Cover, cover!
[YAMAMOTO] Left!
[SHINZEN GM] So it looks like
the essence of that famous quick
[YAKU] Double block!
[SHINZEN GM] is in the setter's
fine‐tuned technique.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice receive, Captain!
[KENMA]
He jumped from A to C!
(HITOKA gasp)
(whistle) (YAMAMOTO amazed)
[HAIBA] All right!
[YAMAMOTO] Well done, my man!
[TAKEDA] Whoa! They stopped him!
[TAKEDA]
They just totally shut down that
quick attack!
[KEISHIN]
Nekoma has always been pretty
good at dealing with our famous
quick‐attack.
[KEISHIN]
On top of that, now they've got
a middle blocker who's as fast
as he is tall.
[YAMAMOTO]
Let's go, Kenma!
[TOBIO]
Hey... let's do some more normal
attacks now... you know the
floating ones.
[TOBIO]
Are you listening to me?!
[SHOYO]
Yeah.
[KENMA]
Lev.
I get the feeling that they're
going to start switching
things up with a few
normal quick attacks...
[KENMA]
So you should start
read‐blocking.
[HAIBA]
Okay, but what's
read‐blocking again?
[KENMA]
It's when you don't jump until
you see which way the ball is
headed.
[HAIBA]
Oh! Right!
(whistle)
[YAMAMOTO] Here we go!
[YU] Tanaka!
[RYUNOSUKE] Gotcha!
[KENMA]
It's when you don't jump until
you see which way the ball is
headed.
(ASAHI & SHOYO shocked)
[HAIBA]
Uh... it's a one touch!
[TADASHI]
I could have sworn
Hinata lured him in!
[KOSHI]
Even a step behind,
his block is so high!
[YAKU]
Chance ball!
[DAICHI, internal]
(frustrated) These guys...!
(NEKOMA cheers)
[TOBIO] Damn...
(long whistle)
[KEISHIN]
Big deal. So
they're starting off
with their guard up
against our quicks.
While we're playing Nekoma,
I want to focus on using Tanaka
and Asahi to attack left.
[TOBIO] Sure.
[ASAHI] Yessir!
[RYUNOSUKE] All right!
[TAKEDA] The good part is still
yet to come guys!
[KEISHIN, internal] I hope this
is the right way to go. Should I
[TADASHI] Let's all just calm
down and grab a point!
[HITOKA] Here you go.
[NEKOMATA, internal]
How do you expect to grow when
you focus primarily on defense?
[HITOKA] Here.
[TOBIO] Thank you. Oh?
[HITOKA]
Asahi.
[SHOYO, internal]
Where is this weird feeling
coming from?
[SHOYO, internal]
Nekoma... Lev... They're such...
powerful opponents.
[SHOYO, internal]
I have to get stronger...
Or I'll never beat them!
(long whistle)
[KAI]
Cover, cover!
[YAMAMOTO]
Left!
[YAKU]
Double block!
[YAMAMOTO]
Got it!
[RYUNOSUKE]
It's up! Nice work, buddy!
[YU]
Yeah nice cover!
[DAICHI]
Got it! Get the last hit!
[DAICHI] Sorry, that was short!
[KOSHI] Asahi!
[TADASHI]
Last touch!
[ASAHI]
Yeah!
(KOSHI gasps)
(ASAHI surprised)
(ASAHI gasps)
(SHOYO falls)
[ASAHI]
Ah! O‐Oh no,
I didn't mean to! Huh?
[SHOYO]
(panic) I'm sorry!
I was focused on the ball;
I wasn't paying attention!
[SHOYO]
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry! I'm
sorry! (groveling and crying)
[ASAHI] I'm perfectly fine.
[RYUNOSUKE] Hey, watch your
back, dude!
[YU]
You'd better be careful Hinata
or you're gonna get squashed.
[KEISHIN]
Make sure to look around you,
kid! That is why we call
everything out!
[SHOYO] Yeah.. Sorry...
[TOBIO] Hinata! Get it together!
[DAICHI] Now, now.
Take it easy, Kageyama.
[KEISHIN] Hinata probably
doesn't realize,
[KEISHIN]
but just now it seemed like he
was trying to take that ball,
which was intended for the ace.
[NEKOMATA, internal]
Is it time for the fledgling
crows to evolve?
[NEKOMATA, internal]
And will that be good or bad for
the team?
[NEKOMATA, internal]
Either way, evolution does not
come to those that do not seek
change.
[NEKOMATA, internal]
If you choose to seek it, no
matter if you are the star on
the court,
[NEKOMATA]
or the leader of the team, or
the ace who draws in the final
score...
[NEKOMATA]
You must be greedy, and declare
that you are the one to reach
the summit.
[SHOYO]
You know, Kageyama...
[TOBIO]
Yeah?
[SHOYO]
From now on, for those quick
attacks...
[SHOYO]
I'll keep my eyes... wide open.
I am done closing my eyes for
the freak quick attack.
(ASAHI & YU alarmed)
(DAICHI & RYUNOSUKE alarmed)
(KEISHIN & TAKEDA concerned)
[TOBIO]
Huh?
(SHOYO startled)
[SHOYO]
We can't keep doing this.
It obviously isn't working
anymore... so I‐
You learned to do the normal
quick attack... because it was
all you could handle.
[TOBIO]
I don't know what you're
thinking about right now,
but we can talk about
it after the game.
[TOBIO]
Because if you're saying
you're gonna do that during
this game...
[TOBIO]
I'm not gonna set to someone
I know will miss.
(SHOYO discouraged)
(whistle)
[YAMAMOTO]
Serve's up!
[YU]
Yours, Asahi!
[ASAHI]
Sorry, cover!
[HITOKA, internal]
That was an intense
conversation...
[HITOKA]
It seems like Hinata and
Kageyama just had an argument...
[HITOKA]
What do you think it was about?
You heard them right?
[KIYOKO]
Mm‐hm.
[HAIBA]
One‐touch! Chance ball!
[KIYOKO]
But it's not just
Hinata and Kageyama...
The moment after
Hinata ran into Asahi...
[KIYOKO]
They all started to get nervous.
[YAMAMOTO]
Get some!
(long whistle)
(NEKOMA celebrate)
[SHOYO]
We can't keep doing this.
[DAICHI, internal]
Hinata finally said what I've
been thinking for awhile now.
[ASAHI, internal]
Alright... We're gonna have
to come up with something
different.
[SHOYO]
All right, I'm going in!
[ASAHI, internal]
At this rate,
Hinata's continued
desire to improve...
[YU]
(laugh) Let me show you
how it's done!
(SHOYO laughing)
[ASAHI] ...could be deadly.
(KEISHIN tense)
(KEISHIN startled)
[NEKOMATA] Seems to me like your
players have had a change in
mindset. (chuckle)
[KEISHIN, internal] It's true
that this is a chance for them
to grow from adversity, but...
[DAICHI] Gather up!
[TAKEDA]
So it's safe to assume you guys
are the weakest of the teams
that are here right now, right?
(KEISHIN shocked)
[RYUNOSUKE, YU, ASAHI, & DAICHI,
internal] He's not wrong, but...
[TAKEDA]
All these other clubs would be
tough opponents if we fought
them in official matches.
[TAKEDA]
Do you see them as
merely enemies...
or do you see them as fellow
competitors from which you can
absorb new techniques?
The fact that you are as weak
as you are means that there is
potential for growth.
[TAKEDA]
And... nothing can be more
thrilling than that.
(ALL surprised gasp)
[DAICHI]
Thank you, sir!
[ALL]
Thanks!
[KEISHIN]
You almost sounded like a wise
old sage just now! Nice job,
Specs!
[TAKEDA]
Well, I am a teacher,
you know...
[KEISHIN]
Huh?
[KOSHI]
We can at least test
it out, right?
[KOSHI]
I mean the last time
we played Nekoma,
we managed to pull off the
normal quick attack without
really prepping for it.
But back then... we still
had the possibility of
doing the regular quick.
I felt like that was the only
way for us to get through them.
[SHOYO]
During the Seijoh match...
I realized it too late.
(KEISHIN, KOSHI, & TOBIO
surprised)
[SHOYO]
By the time I noticed
what was going on,
the ball was on the
floor behind me.
[TOBIO]
Sorry.
Oikawa read me like a book.
[SHOYO]
I was the one that lost, so I
don't want you to apologize to
me, Kageyama.
[SHOYO]
'Til the last second... I am
going to fight for myself in the
air!
[TOBIO]
Well during that match...
I understood how the setter
draws out 100% of the spikers'
skill...
at least to some extent.
(SHOYO heavy breath)
[TOBIO] That quick attack is
your most effective weapon.
[TOBIO]
For that move, missing the right
timing even by the tiniest bit
will kill you out there.
I hear you, I do... but
sorry it's not up to you.
[KOSHI, internal]
Kageyama isn't denying him with
some sort of emotional outburst.
He's just stating facts...
[KOSHI]
I'm sorry, Hinata. But from
listening to what Kageyama had
to say just now...
[KOSHI] I think he might
actually have the right idea
this time around y'know.
(SHOYO troubled)
[KOSHI]
That quick‐attack is amazing
enough already.
[KOSHI]
Perfecting the other attacks
with that at the core is
probably our best bet.
[KEISHIN] Yeah... gotta say I'm
with you, Sugawara.
[KOSHI] Oh hey Coach!
[KEISHIN]
Red. You say you want to fight
with your own will,
but that move depends on
a split‐second decision.
Trying to do something in
mid‐air in that brief of an
instant...
that just doesn't seem
very feasible to me.
[SHOYO]
But when I'm doing well,
everything looks like it's
in slow motion... just like
Tanaka said...
[RYUNOSUKE]
I just mean... sometimes I can
see the other team's block in
midair,
clear as day, like
it's in slo‐mo.
[RYUNOSUKE]
With a bright ray of light
shining through it.
[KEISHIN]
I guess... there ARE times when
you can see the opponent's block
more clearly.
[SHOYO]
The last point when we had
the practice match against
Seijoh...
[SHOYO]
The Great King, Oikawa...
I saw him. I saw his face.
[SHOYO]
I saw his eyes.
[KEISHIN, internal]
He saw... what?
[KEISHIN]
I get it... so you FELT
like you could see?
[SHOYO]
The first time I nailed the
quick attack in the 3‐on‐3... I
saw the other side.
[SHOYO]
I saw the view from the summit.
[KEISHIN]
Yeah, you're telling me it
SEEMED like you could see all
that stuff. (startled)
(KEISHIN concerned)
[DAICHI] Oh, there you
are! We're about to
start up you guys!
[KEISHIN] Whoa!
[SHOYO]
Okay, we'll be right there.
[KEISHIN] Narita.
[KAZUHITO] Yes?
[KEISHIN]
Next set, you're in for Ginger.
[SHOYO] Oh?
[KAZUHITO] Oh.. uh okay.
(TOBIO alarmed)
Alright I think I get what
you're after here kid,
but for now you need to keep
that red head of yours cool.
(SHOYO disappointed)
[KEISHIN]
It's not the right time for us
to start trying things like
that.
[KEISHIN]
And I can't risk anyone
getting hurt in a collision
like earlier.
(SHOYO guilty)
(long whistle)
[BOKUTO]
Aww yeah!
[TADASHI] Come on!
[SHOYO] Just shake it off, guys!
[KOSHI] Next, next!
[HAIBA] Bring it on!
[CHIKARA] Tighten it up!
(whistle)
[HAIBA] Right on!
[GOURA]
Shake it off!
[YAMAMOTO]
Nice kill, Lev!
[WASHIO]
Got it!
[AKAASHI]
Cover that!
[KOMI]
Serve's up!
[BOKUTO]
Get ready, Saru!
[DAICHI]
Thank you for the games!
[KURASUNO]
Thanks!
[NEKOMATA]
Next time is in two weeks...
It'll be during the
summer training camp.
[KEISHIN & TAKEDA]
We'll see you then, sir!
This is where the
real deal begins.
[NEKOMATA]
It'll be the only long‐term
training camp before the Spring
National preliminaries.
[TAKEDA] Yes.
[NEKOMATA] I'll have you little
young'uns out drinking with me
every night for the entire week.
[TAKEDA] Sure!
(KEISHIN defeated grumble)
[KUROO]
I know this is a bit late...
but I can't help but notice you
kept your third‐years too.
[DAICHI]
Yeah. You played last year's
champs on day 2
of the Inter‐High prelims,
right? Hinata told us.
[DAICHI]
That's some rotten luck.
[KUROO]
Yeah... lost the quarter finals.
[DAICHI]
Top 8 in Tokyo's nothing to
sneeze at though.
[KUROO]
Who cares if we
can't keep going.
[DAICHI]
(agreeing) True...
[SHOYO]
Oh?
[HAIBA]
See ya later, Hinata!
Can't wait to beat
you next time too.
[SHOYO]
Keep dreaming, pal!
I'll show you five‐three's
a million times better than
six‐four!
[HAIBA]
...Take it easy.
(vehicle starting)
[TAKEDA]
At the end of the day, I think
this camp was a success for us.
[TAKEDA]
Turns out there's a lot of
things we can work on, isn't
there?
[KEISHIN]
Well, one thing's for sure,
after all that's happened, we'll
have our work cut out for us.
[TAKEDA]
That's true... We can think
about all that out when we get
back home.
[KEISHIN] Back home, huh...
[TAKEDA] Uh... Coach?
[KEISHIN]
I just remembered I've got a
relative coming home soon that
can be quite a handful.
[TAKEDA]
Hmmm?
Thanks for all the hard work you
put in on the trip, guys.
[ALL]
Sir!
[TAKEDA]
And tomorrow, like I told you
before,
[TAKEDA]
there'll be an inspection going
on in the gym,
so we're not having practice.
So take it easy and get some
rest, since you guys haven't had
any downtime lately. (chuckle)
[SHOYO]
Kageyama.
[TOBIO]
Huh?
Hey... come set for me.
[HITOKA]
Oh, hey... You guys
aren't going home yet?
[SHOYO]
Actually, would you mind
throwing a few balls for us
before you go, Yachi?
[HITOKA]
(startled) I can do that?
[SHOYO]
Sure, all you have to do is
throw curveballs over Kageyama's
head.
[HITOKA]
O‐Oh... I'll try!
[SHOYO]
(exhale) I'm ready!
[HITOKA]
Okay.
[TOBIO, internal]
His attention is on the ball,
so this isn't his maximum
jump...!
[SHOYO]
Send me up another one!
(TOBIO annoyed)
(SHOYO missing the ball)
(SHOYO out of breath)
[SHOYO]
(grunt) One more!
[TOBIO]
(grunt) Instead of repeating
this attack that we may not be
able to do...
[TOBIO]
why can't we practice blocking
or serving or any of the other
ten thousand things
[TOBIO]
we need to get better
at right now?!
[SHOYO]
(out of breath) But...
if this quick attack
doesn't work out...
[SHOYO]
I have no reason to be standing
on the court! (heavy breathing)
[TOBIO]
I already told you, Hinata,
this isn't about how
badly you want to do it!
[TOBIO]
(annoyed) I'll set a ball that
won't get stopped by their
blockers!
[SHOYO]
You can, but how is that
supposed to make me any better?!
(HITOKA concerned)
[TOBIO] The first round of
prelims for Spring Nationals
is only a month away.
Now you tell me which
is more useful:
[TOBIO]
...you want a perfected
quick attack,
or a completely useless
quick attack?! HUH?! (seething)
[HITOKA]
Um Please take it
easy, you guys!
[HITOKA]
Let's just calm down and
take a step back, okay?
[TOBIO, internal]
Dammit! I know what
I'm saying is right...
[TOBIO, internal]
So why does he refuse to back
down?
[SHOYO]
(fuming) I told you... I want to
be able to fight on my own!
[TOBIO]
(seething) And I'm telling YOU
that your selfish attitude is
tearing this team apart!
[HITOKA]
(gasp) Come on, guys...
(SHOYO & TOBIO angry)
[HITOKA]
L‐Let's all get along... okay?
[TOBIO]
I'll set to whoever
I have to to win.
[TOBIO]
It's just... I highly doubt that
person is going to be you.
[TOBIO]
And that still hasn't
changed, you know.
[SHOYO]
(seething) KAAAGEEEYAAAAMAAAAAA!
(frustrated yelling)
(TOBIO shocked)
[TOBIO]
Dammit! Let me go!
Then throw me a damn set!
Do you hear me?! (struggles
to hold on) (tossed on floor)
(TOBIO shock) (snarling while
tossing Shoyo on floor)
[HITOKA] (gasp)
Someone! Tanaka...!
[TOBIO] Stoppit! (struggling)
[SHOYO]
They stopped the quick attack!
Today, and back during the
Seijoh match!
[TOBIO]
(struggling) Oh yeah?! What, are
you trying to say my set was bad
asshole?!
[SHOYO]
No! That's not what I mean! It
was perfect! It was spot‐on! But
they still stopped it!
[TOBIO]
(struggling) Well maybe that was
your fault, you ever think of
that?
[SHOYO]
If I stay the way I am,
I can't hold my ground
against the top teams!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey! Both of you guys!
Stop iiiiit!
Um my bus stop... It's right
over there, this'll be far
enough...
Um... thanks for walking me...
[SHOYO]
I'm really sorry about that.
[HITOKA]
No, it's not a problem at all!
It's alright...
No need to worry about me.
[HITOKA]
Hinata...
[SHOYO]
In my first and last tournament
back in middle school,
Kageyama kicked my butt.
[SHOYO]
I swore revenge. But instead,
when I entered high school, we
ended up on the same team.
[SHOYO]
He was a lot meaner than I
expected, so it was kinda hard
at first.
[SHOYO]
But come game time, I began
to know what he was thinking...
[SHOYO]
And for the first time, I felt
that instead of just a partner,
I had.. a friend.
(HITOKA tearing up)
[SHOYO]
See you later.
[HITOKA]
Yeah... (sniffling)
(school bell ringing)
[ASAHI]
So are you telling me that
Hinata and Kageyama actually
came to blows?
[KOSHI]
Things've been tense between
those two ever since the trip to
Tokyo. It's not good.
[RYUNOSUKE]
With the Spring National prelims
coming up, this is bad news for
all of us
[DAICHI]
Yeah but... those two bickering
with each other isn't exactly
outside of the norm.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Yeah and come to think of it...
they were at each other's
throats before they even,
joined us.
[ASAHI]
Wait, are you serious?
[KOSHI]
On the first day, they knocked
off the vice principal's toupee,
[KOSHI]
and then Daichi locked them out
of the gym. It wasn't pretty...
[RYUNOSUKE]
Well, those two knuckleheads
have come this far;
maybe it's just another hurdle
for them to get over.
Yeah... maybe so. But y'know
what... Let's not give up on
those two knuckleheads yet.
[KEISHIN]
Thank you. (sigh)
[KEISHIN, internal]
That freak quick was already
amazing.
[KEISHIN, internal]
It should be fundamentally
impossible to make it even
better.
[SHOYO]
I saw the other side.
I saw the view from the summit.
[KEISHIN]
Those eyes...
The amount of time you're at the
peak of your jump is only but an
instant.
[KEISHIN]
Even if you say you can see the
blockers, it's just a vague
recognition that they're there.
[KEISHIN]
But once in a blue moon, there's
a spiker who can actually see
blockers clearly,
[KEISHIN]
right down to their fingertips.
Even the positions of the
players behind them.
[KEISHIN, internal]
Could Hinata be one of those
spikers?
[KEISHIN]
A quick attack dished out from a
miraculous setup...
[KEISHIN]
If Hinata could dictate where it
goes with his own will from
mid‐air...
[KEISHIN, internal]
No, that's impossible!
Nobody would be able to pull
that off!
But wait... if it could be done,
then we would have a new ruler
of aerial combat, surpassing
even the Tiny Giant.
(door opening)
[KEISHIN]
Welcome to‐ oh... Sup, lil' Red?
Hey Coach... I want you to tell
me how I should be practicing.
[KOSHI]
Hinata and Kageyama are
fighting...
[ASAHI]
Ah, the struggles of youth.
[KOSHI]
You look out of place saying
that, Asahi.
[ASAHI]
Huh?! What's that
supposed to mean?!
[KOSHI] Well, you don't look
very youthful, that's for sure.
[ASAHI] Hey!
[KOSHI]
Next Haikyu!! ‐ "Tempo".