(pre‐game chatter)
[MAN] Can I have a program?
[GIRL] Sure.
[CHANTS]
Go, go, Dewa First! Push, push,
Dewa First! Go, go, Dewa First!
Push, push, Dewa First!
[PLAYER]
Serve it up!
[STUDENT A] That's them.
You know, Karasuno.
[STUDENT B] Karasuno?
[STUDENT A]
Back at the Inter‐High
prelims... That team went full
sets with Aoba‐Johsai...
[STUDENT A] These guys had
them down to the wire.
[STUDENT B] Oh, no joke?!
[STUDENT A]
Supposedly, they have that
guy from Kitagawa First,
[STUDENT A] "The King
of the Court".
[TOBIO] So do you know which ref
we'll have?
[STUDENT C] I hear they also
have Nishinoya from Chidori‐yama
Middle School.
[STUDENT B]
[STUDENT A]
Right. And other than him,
there was another guy
who received almost all the
serves directly from Oikawa.
I think he was their captain.
[STUDENT B]
Weird. Karasuno doesn't really
look all that big to me. I mean,
They're pretty small, right.
[STUDENT A]
I think there's a guy close to
6'3" on the team.
Though I don't think he did
all that much during the
preliminaries.
[STUDENT A]
Well, I know the two guys on
their left side are scary.
[STUDENT A]
They look like they could be
some power spikers.
But, the most important
thing about Karasuno...
[STUDENT A]
...their team manager
is a total fox!
[KIYOKO] Yachi, I'm sorry that
you have to cheer from all the
way up here.
[STUDENT B]
[STUDENT A]
And, of course, you know,
there's him.
[STUDENT A]
The little middle blocker who
lands all those ridiculous
quick‐attacks.
[STUDENT A]
Karasuno's No.10.
Ugh. Looks like he's
sick or something.
[HITOKA]
Uh... Hinata, are you
feeling alright?
[SHOYO]
Yeah I'm fine, I'm okay. I puked
on the way here, so I'm feeling
a little better now.
[KEI]
Eating tons of katsu bowls so
early in the morning is bound to
make you sick.
[SHOYO]
On match days, it's good luck
to eat katsu isn't it?
[KEI]
What the hell are you
talking about...?
[TOBIO]
You moron! Hinata,
you're a moron!
[DAICHI]
Kageyama. Your library of
insults could use some variety.
[TOBIO] (flustered) I‐I'll do my
best to increase my vocabulary!
[HITOKA] I have something that
might help your tummy!
[TADASHI] (queasy) Just thinking
about Hinata's puke makes me
want to puke myself...
[SHOYO] Oh, thanks!
[KEI]
Huh? Then go to
the bathroom then!
[ASAHI]
Me too, I've got a lot of
anxiety right now... (heaves)
[KOSHI]
I thought you were
concentrating,
but all you were doing was
holding back your puke?!
[YU]
Hinata. Is this really the
second time you've thrown up
on the bus?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Yeah but I'd like
to make the point
that this time around you didn't
blow chunks on anyone's crotch.
[RYUNOSUKE]
My little boy's
growing up so fast!
(YU & RYUNOSUKE cracking up)
[STUDENT B]
I don't know, I'm not sure.
Did these guys really
force Seijoh into a corner?
[SHOYO, singing]
Bath‐room, bath‐room,
I gotsta pee.
I'm gonna sprinkle all my
tinkle in the hoity‐
[SHOYO]
Oh, sorry about that‐
[TOWADA]
Watch where you're going,
pipsqueak?!
[SHOYO]
(frightened) I'm sorry,
I'm sorry!
[SHOYO]
Oh? Wait a second...
Ohgi Minami?
That's the team we're going up
against in our first match!
They won their first round!
[TOWADA] Wait? You must
be in middle school.
[SHOYO] Oh?
[TOWADA]
Ah, sorry if I scared you
there, little man.
[TOWADA]
Are you here to cheer for your
big brother or something?
[TOWADA]
Hm? My little brother's got a
t‐shirt just like that,
it's like his favorite shirt
in the whole world.
[SHOYO]
Gah! I‐I'm a first year at
Karasuno High School! I'm Shoyo
Hinata!
[SHOYO]
We're winning this tournament
and go to nationals! (heavy
panting)
[TOWADA] Huh? Karasuno?
(SHOYO scared)
[TOWADA]
Don't talk like getting to
nationals is so easy.
[SHOYO]
Huh? But I'm telling
you the truth.
[TOWADA]
Oh shut up, you little‐ (shock)
[SHOYO]
We're gonna beat everyone...
and go to Tokyo.
[TOWADA]
Heh! Look even if that were to
miraculously happen...
[TOWADA] You would only
end up being crushed by
Shiratorizawa anyway.
[SHOYO] Huh?
[TOWADA]
But we can at least have fun
until then, right?
(SHOYO question)
(long whistle)
[DAICHI]
The game before us is over.
Ready guys?!
[KURASUNO]
Let's goooo!
[TAZAWA]
Whatever, idiot.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh?
(RYUNOSUKE & SHOYO frightened)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Dude. Just look at these guys.
They must do their recruiting
at the local jail.
[KOSHI]
You of all people would say
that? And stop with that face.
(long whistle)
[TOBIO]
Nice kill!
[OYASU]
Shaved heads are seriously lame.
Dude, do you have
lice or something
[RYUNOSUKE]
I shall proceed. I offer
you my best regards.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Take that, goddammit!
[TOBIO]
Nice kill!
[RYUNOSUKE]
I apologize for that outburst.
[TOBIO]
Huh... Mmm...
(KURASUNO compliments
towards Hinata)
[STUDENT D]
Looks like everyone on Karasuno
has amazing attack power.
(TOWADA concerned)
(long whistle)
[HITOKA]
Spring Nationals volleyball.
For Karasuno High School, this
is just the beginning...
(whistle)
[EVERYONE]
Thank you for the game!
[HITOKA]
The beginning of their battles!
[CHANTS]
Go, go, let's go,
let's go, Kaji High!
[KEISHIN]
All right. I know their
third‐years have already
left the team,
but their backbone's always
been their second‐years.
They won the first round of this
tournament in straight sets as
well. So play smart.
[KEISHIN] And be careful
of No.1 on their left!
[KURASUNO] Yessir!
From the end of the
Inter‐High prelims until now,
you have tried things
you were not used to.
[TAKEDA]
They didn't always mesh,
and you lost roughly 70
of your matches
[TAKEDA] against the
Kanto powerhouses.
(ALL shamed)
[TAKEDA]
But, the new weapons that were
nothing but failures at first,
are now starting to take shape.
Now go out there and get a
victory... Balance out all
of those frustrations.
[KURASUNO]
Yessir!
[DAICHI] Karasuno, fight!
[KURASUNO] Fiiight!
[HITOKA] Fiiight!
[OHNO]
Oh, well well, look who's here.
Good to see you, Coach.
[UKAI] Yeah.
[OHNO] I suppose you're
here to see your grandson.
[UKAI]
No, that's not the only reason!
[HITOKA]
Uh wait? Grandson?
[OGASAWARA]
Hey uh, you're from
Karasuno, right?
Why aren't you down
by the court?
[HITOKA]
(annoyed) Only one team
manager is allowed
[HITOKA] to be on the bench!
So I'm watching here.
[AYA] Oh... Look, there's Sho!
[OGASAWARA] What? Where?
Oh yeah! I see him!
[OHNO]
This is the first time
[HITOKA] Sho? Oh, they're
talking about Hinata...
[OHNO]
They've got an amazing couple
Karasuno might actually go
pretty far this year.
[UKAI]
There is never a match that you
are destined to lose,
nor is there a match you
are certain to win either.
[UKAI]
The slightest difference
in condition, anxiety,
impatience...
[UKAI]
Even with the most powerful
team, the players are still
human.
[UKAI]
It doesn't take much. The most
trivial of disturbances can trip
anyone up.
I wonder... Will Karasuno
get tripped up today?
[YU]
Make it a good one, Asahi!
(ASAHI exhales) (whistle)
(whistle)
(YOKOTE & KARAMATSU stunned)
(TOWADA stunned)
(ball bouncing to a standstill)
(ALL amazed)
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[HITOKA] They did it!
That was incredible!
[OHNO] They're starting
off with a service ace!
[UKAI]
They're not too bad.
[KEISHIN]
All right... let's go!
(RYUNOSUKE battle cry)
(whistle)
[DAICHI, internal]
Wait. He switched over
to a feint...!
(TAZAWA shock)
[HITOKA] So fast! He
waited for it!
[RYUNOSUKE] Nice, Daichi!
[DAICHI, internal]
The motions of the spikers...
I feel like I can see them
better than before.
[YU]
Asahi!
[KEI, internal]
If their receives were
even the slightest bit off,
Ohgi never used fast‐attacks.
Not even in the first round.
[KEI, internal]
This'll go left.
[NATSUSE]
Tazawa!
(whistle) (KURASUNO celebrates)
[TAKEDA] So how do I put this...
[DAICHI] It's all you,
Tsukishima!
Everyone seems to have less
hesitation in their movements
compared to before.
[KEISHIN]
Yeah well it's not like we only
practiced nothing but new moves
during training camp.
[RYUNOSUKE] Coming your way!
[KEISHIN]
We crammed in consecutive
matches with powerhouses of a
[KEISHIN]
Serve strength, spike strength,
attack diversity, defense, all
sorts of stuff...
[KEISHIN]
compared to before, we saw
a much higher level in all of
it.
[KEISHIN]
And we've gotten used to it.
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[TOWADA]
Dammit!
(whistle)
[TOBIO] All right!
[HITOKA] Another service ace!
[YU] Nice, Kageyama!
[HITOKA] That makes...
set point!
[TOBIO] Thanks!
[TOWADA]
(sigh) You gotta be kidding.
We're up against another
strong team like this in
the first round.
(CROWD roaring cheer)
[CHANTING]
Shiratorizawa! (clapping)
(whistle)
[CHANTING]
Ushijima! Ushijima! (clapping)
(TOWADA, TAZAWA,
& YOKOTE run down)
[AKIMIYA]
Come on! We still got a lot of
chances left!
[AKIMIYA]
Let's go! Pick it up guys,
what happened to your usual
groove?
[TOWADA]
What!? Grrr...
[AKIMIYA] There ya go!
That's it!
[TOWADA]
I remember the Captain had
[AKIMIYA] That's the spirit,
let's get a point!
[TOWADA]
from trying to yell over
[AKIMIYA]
It's up! Towada!
[TOWADA]
Even if I chased it, I wouldn't
reach it.
[TOWADA]
Even if I reached it,
it wouldn't necessarily lead to
a score.
[TOWADA]
And even if it leads to a
score, it's still just a
small, meaningless point.
[TOWADA]
All it's doing is
delaying the inevitable.
(AKIMIYA sprint)
(AKIMIYA heavy breathing)
(whistle) (long whistle)
[AKIMIYA]
Hey guys come on, don't look so
depressed. It makes you look
even scarier.
I know people think
you're trouble.
But, if you guys weren't around,
there's no way we would have
been able to enter the
tournament. So thank you.
[AKIMIYA]
Remember, you guys have the
physique and an innate sense for
volleyball, so do your best.
(AKIMIYA quietly sobbing)
(TOWADA surprised)
(TOWADA frustrated)
(whistle)
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[HITOKA]
He did it!
[OGASAWARA]
Oh he's so cool!
He jumped sideways!
Incredible...
[SHOYO]
We're going to beat everyone,
and go to Tokyo.
[TOWADA, internal]
He wasn't bluffing. He really
intends to win this thing.
[SHOYO] Yeeeaahh!!
[TOWADA, internal]
With that tiny little body of
his, he's actually planning to
(long whistle)
[OHGI GM]
L‐let's just keep at it, guys!
It doesn't matter whether
you win or lose,
the most important this is
that you do the best you can.
[AKIMIYA]
Hey you dirty punks, don't get
all quiet on me now!
[TOWADA]
(gasp) Uh... Captain?!
[AKIMIYA]
Why is it that you
guys can pick fights,
but chicken out when
it comes to volleyball?
(MORITAKE & TAZAWA annoyed)
[TOWADA] We're not chickening
out!
[AKIMIYA]
(scared) Aww. Glare at me all
you want,
but I'm up on the second
floor so I'm not afraid of you!
(laughs)
[MORITAKE]
What the hell did he come here
anyway?
When your opponent gets going,
you just give up. That's what
I'm calling chickening out.
[AKIMIYA] This is your match, so
what you do is up to you. But,
I'll say one thing!
[TOWADA] Huh?
[AKIMIYA]
Being serious... being
desperate... and doing one's
best... Those are all okay.
(TOWADA shocked)
(SHOYO surprised)
(TOWADA starts cracking up)
[MORITAKE]
Dude? What's your deal?
[NATSUSE]
So uh are you like
losing it or something?
[TOWADA] Coach.
[OHGI GM] Yeah?
[TOWADA]
We are here on this court.
And we're here to
challenge these guys...
[TOWADA] We have no other
objective than to win and
move on.
(OHGI GM surprised)
[TOWADA]
Being content to settle for
our weaknesses and worrying
about how we look...
[TOWADA] It does nothing. It
just makes us look weak.
[MORITAKE] Uh, Towada...
[TOWADA] All right,
I'm gonna say it.
[MORITAKE] Say what?
(TOWADA inhales)
[TOWADA]
We are going to defeat Karasuno!
Qualify through the first round!
And defeat Shiratorizawa!
Alright!
[OYASU]
(laugh) You serious?
You actually said that!
[TAZAWA]
Heck yeah! Bring it on!
[KARAMATSU]
We're gonna defeat
Shiratorizawa, huh? Okay...
[YOKOTE]
Let's give it a go!
[TOWADA]
We are seriously going to win
this one, okay you guys!
[OHGI MINAMI]
Yeah!
[RYUNOSUKE]
We're going to end you!
(TOWADA, TAZAWA, & OYASU
annoyed)
(TOWADA grin)
(game in progress)
(KURASUNO celebrate)
[HITOKA] Wooohooo!!
[KOSHI] Nice, Hinata!
[OGASAWARA] You can't stop that!
[OHNO] That first‐year combo
is really something else.
[UKAI]
Yes. But I've noticed... the
second and third‐years have been
better than expected.
[UKAI]
At the moment, Karasuno is
showing signs of a return to
greatness.
[UKAI]
They have a passionate
counselor,
and their new players
are interested in leaving
their mark.
And well, the team is finally
able to do so because they
possess a rock solid foundation.
[OHNO]
What?
[UKAI]
Last year, just
for a short while,
I oversaw practices at Karasuno.
[UKAI]
Back then, they had the skill,
and they had the strength.
[UKAI]
But for some reason, I felt they
had a lack of confidence.
[UKAI]
It was as if they had
subconsciously become
accustomed to losing.
[OHNO]
Well they don't look
like that anymore?
[UKAI]
When the current third‐years
first came to play for the
Karasuno team...
[UKAI]
Karasuno was no longer
considered a powerhouse.
Their reputation was gone.
[UKAI]
The gap between what they had
once admired and what they saw
in reality was very apparent.
[UKAI]
Those players have been there
since the school was nothing.
[UKAI]
But, that may have made
all the difference.
Since they have been able
to come this far without
losing hope,
they have developed a resilience
that won't easily waver.
[YU]
Nice one, Daichi!
(whistle)
[HITOKA] Amazing! Amazing!
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[STUDENT A]
Man, they got a 10‐point lead.
[DAICHI] Let's keep
going! Don't stop!
[KURASUNO] Yessir!
[OHGI GM] Don't worry,
it's gonna be all right!
Just do your best!
(whistle)
[KOSHI] Kageyama, one more!
[KOSHI & CHIKARA] Alright! Yeah!
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[CHIKARA]
Kageyama's serves are spot on!
[KOSHI]
Right. Now it's match point!
[TOWADA, internal]
(out of breath) Every time,
after we're cornered in a
do‐or‐die situation,
we regret the lack
of practice...
[DAICHI]
Kageyama, one more!
Take it to 'em!
[STUDENT A]
The Karasuno and Ohgi
match is about to end.
This is probably a good chance
for us to find some pretty good
seats for the next one.
[STUDENT B]
Yeah. When there's a clear
difference in skill, the
games really are fast.
[AKIMIYA]
(concerned) It's not
over yet! Don't give up!
(whistle)
[TOWADA, internal]
Will I be able to reach it?
I seriously doubt it.
[TOWADA, internal]
Well, we're still second‐years,
so we'll still have another
chance next year... No big deal.
[TOWADA, internal]
That's exactly why we
stay weak! (panting)
(CROWD concerned gasps)
[TOWADA]
Last hit, send it ovaaaah!
(OHGI MINAMI shocked)
(YOKOTE battle charge)
[SHOYO]
Tanaka, your way!
[YOKOTE]
It's not over yet!
I'm open over here,
gimme the last hit!
(AKIMIYA hard swallow)
[TOWADA, internal]
(awed) At first, I looked
down on this kid...
[TOWADA]
I thought he was an idiot to
say he was going to Nationals.
I guess...
[TOWADA, internal]
...I was the idiot.
(whistle) (long whistle)
(KURASUNO cheering)
(CROWD clapping/cheering)
[HITOKA] Oh wow!
We did it! We won!
[OHNO] All right!
(AYA impressed)
[OGASAWARA] I don't believe it!
[KEISHIN]
All right!
[TAKEDA]
We got past the
first match Coach!
(long whistle)
[EVERYONE]
Thank you for the game!
[AKIMIYA]
Nice game! You held
that for a while there.
[TOWADA]
Hey.
[AKIMIYA]
It's natural to feel regret
right now.
(OHGI MINAMI surprised)
No matter how you played...
of course losing feels bad.
It's just part of it.
And it is the same for
everybody who plays.
Even for those who
don't even practice.
[AKIMIYA]
The feeling of "regret" is
natural. And it's a real
thing for anyone. But....
Those who do forget.
Those who lose their regret
are going to stay weak!
[AKIMIYA]
Three years of high school will
be gone in an instant if you're
not paying attention!
[AKIMIYA]
So hold on to that regret And
never forget it.
[AKIMIYA]
(surprised) Okay. I'll see ya
later guys. I'll come watch you
again next year.
[TOWADA]
Captain!
[AKIMIYA]
Oh?
[TOWADA]
Thank you. Thank you for all
you've done for us.
[OHGI MINAMI]
Thanks!
(AKIMIYA chuckles)
(game in progress)
(SHOYO & HITOKA nervous)
(RYUNOSUKE aggressively
eating a banana)
[KOMAKI] No.4, No.4!
[MINAMIDA]
Nice receive!
That dude, he gets my depth
perception screwed...
I tried standing next to
him in the hallway earlier.
I felt so tiny.
Well hell yeah he's huge!
He's like almost 6'7"!
(HITOKA & SHOYO panic)
[RYUNOSUKE, mouthful]
That's playing dirty!
[ASAHI]
It's a weapon... the
height is a weapon...
[KIYOKO, internal]
Tanaka, that banana suits you.
(whistle) (long whistle)
[EVERYONE]
Thank you very much!
[TOBIO, mouthful]
Looks like our next
opponent is set.
(SHOYO nervous)
[DAICHI]
If we win the next match,
we get past the first round
of the preliminaries
[DAICHI]
and advance to the deciding
tournament in October.
[DAICHI] Let's take
care of business guys!
[KURASUNO] Yessir!
[HITOKA, internal]
You lose just once
and you're out.
[HITOKA, internal]
And now... they're facing
someone over six and
a half feet tall...!
(SHOYO panicking)
[SHOYO] (jittery) Man...
6'7"... is freakin' huge...
[TADASHI]
So 6 foot 7" versus
5 foot 3", huh...
[SHOYO]
(annoyed) Hey I'm almost
5‐foot‐four, thank you very
much.
[KEI] That would be 6'7" versus
5'3"... a 16‐inch difference.
[SHOYO] Leave me alone!
[HITOKA]
Sixteen inches, well that's like
the same size as Hello Katey! So
that's not all that much!
[KEI]
Are you trying to
make him feel better?
[TADASHI]
Tekachu is 16 inches
tall too, I think.
[KEI] And the
black‐belly lantern.
[HITOKA] A black‐belly lantern?
[TADASHI]
What's that?
[KEI] It's a kind of shark.
[HITOKA] Oh.
[TADASHI]
Tsukki, you sure are smart!
[SHOYO] Wait... If I could stand
on a black‐belly lantern...
[TOBIO] Huh?
[SHOYO]
Then I could be up to
6 foot 7 inches tall, too.
[TOBIO]
Hey... are you wiggin'?
You're not...
gonna wuss out on us.
[SHOYO] Huh?
(whistle) (long whistle)
[DAICHI] Let's go!
[TOBIO] Hmm?
[SHOYO] Oh?
(KURASUNO hyping up)
[HITOKA]
Hinata has been talking about
a lot of crazy nonsense...
Do you think he's gonna
be alright, Kiyoko?
[KIYOKO]
Uh. Yeah... that doesn't seem to
be anything out of the ordinary.
[HITOKA]
Um okay I hope so.
[OHNO]
Well, kay, this is it!
Now they have to play this
enormous kid...
[OHNO]
No, no! The way they're playing
now, that won't matter! Isn't
that right, Coach Ukai?
[UKAI] Well... who really knows?
[OHNO] Wha‐
[UKAI]
High school boys aren't fully
grown, and how they play is
still a bit raw.
[UKAI]
So having a great ace, or
someone unconventionally tall,
can be the difference between
victory and defeat.
[KEISHIN] Ginger, get your
little red ass over here!
[OHNO] What, you don't mean
that...!
Pure height all by itself...
can be a huge advantage.
[UKAI]
How will Karasuno choose to
fight against it? That's the
real question.
[DAICHI]
Let's do it!
[KURASUNO]
Yeah!
[UKAI]
This will be something to see.
[TADASHI]
So a black‐belly lantern is
a type of shark and not a whale!
[KEI]
Lots of fish have misleading
names. The red bream isn't
technically a bream at all.
[TADASHI]
Tsukki, you really know
a lot about fish.
[KEI] Shut up.
[TADASHI] I'm sorry, Tsukki!
[TADASHI]
Next episode of Haikyu!!
"Simple,
Pure Strength".