(final whistle)
Excuse me, guys...
I need to go to the bathroom.
So... go on without me!
He sure takes going to the
bathroom pretty seriously.
Must have
to take a shit.
Oh, come on, man! You don't
have to say it like that!
I don't think he went
to the bathroom...
Shit.
Say "Poop."
It's "Poop."
Shit.
Say "Poopy."
[Tadashi]:
Um, Coach.
Hmm?
I apologize for wasting
the chance I had!
Taking care of the ball
and staying on offense...
determines whether or not
you're gonna finish on top.
I heard you point that out
at the Fukurodani match.
And Coach, I understand
why I was being put in.
[Tadashi]:
And I wanted to go in and do
my job. To keep us on offense.
But well... I wasn't able
to get it done.
Please Coach... Please give
me one more chance!
I know, Tadashi.
Just be patient.
Please... put me in!
[Hajime]:
Come on, Mad Dog!
Show 'em what you got!
Sorry! It's long!
[Toru]:
Mattsun!
Dammit, sorry guys!
[Takinoue]:
Oh man, this isn't good.
Number 16's in the game.
It's a five‐point gap.
You can do it Karasuno!
Let's step back, guys...
I don't think they'll
try to drop one up front.
Yeah.
Sounds good.
[Hajime]:
Go for it!
Bring it, bring it, bring it,
bring it, bring it, bring it...
Tanaka!
Y'like that?!
Aw, yeah!
[Saeko]:
Alright we're just
getting started baby!
[Yu]:
Send it over, Hinata!
Uh, Hey, look,
it's him!
Huh?
Excuse me, we're
making a substitution.
(whistle)
Oh... hey look! It's that
pinch‐server guy!
Ah, the guy that screwed up in
the WakuNan match earlier.
[Spectator 1]:
Of course, I can't blame him.
There's no way I'd want to serve
in the situation he was in.
He's the one who came in and
botched the serve before, right?
You think he's
gonna be okay?
Mm‐hmm...
Tadashi, go get
us ten points!
ERK! Yeah, well, that
would end the game...
It sure would.
(chuckles)
Now go ram the ball
up their fat noses!
Yeah. And uh...
Try to keep your cool.
Just get it over.
Over the net.
We all know
you can do it!
Right!
Ready... Now go out there
and get it dooone! Woo!
[Shimada]:
Eight seconds.
That's much time
you have to serve
after they blow the whistle,
you understand that, right?
Right.
From what I've seen before,
it's like the whistle
almost surprised you and you
just threw it up and served.
Don't get so flustered.
Okay.
So, then... did you
go talk to Coach?
And tell him what
you were thinking?
Uh... Yeah.
[Shimada]:
Well that's
a huge step.
And... you see there...
You're already
a completely different
player than you were before.
Now go out there and do
what you know how to do.
[Shimada]:
Just put the ball in play.
There's some
tension in the air.
I can't blame them after
what happened last time.
(heart pounding)
It's out!
(triumphant scream)
YEAHHHHHH!
He did it!
Kick ass!
Nice freakin' serve!
It's in!
Oh yeah, wait...
We were uh...
Cheering for Seijoh...
Yeah, I dunno... I think
they're overdoing it a bit.
It's still only
one point, right?
That's it! Get
another one!
Did my boy T‐bone just
get a service ace?!
Keep it going!
Catch up!
Sorry about that!
Shake it off!
Don't worry about it!
That was a really
nice serve, man.
Honestly, I thought
it was gonna go out.
This is exactly why I
can't stand jump floats.
Damn you, Tadashi you
really nailed that one!
Thanks.
It's really not something
to be all that surprised about.
Huh?
Now don't start being
a jerk about it!
[Kei]:
For the past five months he has
practiced serving more
than anyone else on the team.
You seaky little
supportive son of a bitch!
[Shoyo]:
Get another one Tadashi!
Give it all you got. Put the
ball right where you want it!
He's gonna be just fine.
When you run
from something...
It only tends to get
a lot harder.
I'm pretty sure Tadashi
understands that.
More than any
of us do.
Mm‐hm.
It only takes one great
ball... to break through.
Yeah. That's right.
[Keishin]:
And then we can start
our counter‐attack.
Let's cut it off!
You got it!
In this game, it's of the
utmost importance to connect
with your team... but the
serve is when you're out there
all alone.
Yeah...
[Keishin]:
And you could also say that
it's the only play in the game
where you can score with
nothing but your own skills.
Since volleyball first began,
I'd say that serves
have evolved the most
of any part of the sport.
And now, in modern‐day
volleyball, the serve
is the ultimate attack.
It can be used in
any number of tactics.
And is unaffected
by the block.
Yours, Mad Dog!
Son of a bitch!
You did it again
you beautiful bastaaard!
All right!
RIGHT OOOON!
Nice serve, man.
(cheering)
Way to goooo!
You freaking see that?!
That was so cool!
One more time!
Now, do it again!
Okay, guys, let's go!
All right, bring it on!
I got it!
Jump float... means
overhand receives!
[Toru]:
Nice Makki!
They got it! They're
going to attack!
[Tadashi]:
Oh, man. Now we've suddenly
gone from predator to prey...
[Hanamaki]:
Iwaizumi!
He received it with his body!
Ahh! Not yet, not yet! They're
not taking back the serve yet!
Cover iiiiit!
Thank you, Kageyama!
[Daichi]:
Tsukishima, last hit!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yeaaah! Tsukkiiii!
Did you just see that?!
He did a nice job
deflecting it off the block.
[Takinoue]:
They've gotten the last
three points in a row!
Do it again.
(whistle)
[Shimada]:
Oh... Seijoh's
taking a time‐out.
They're trying whatever they
can to stop our momentum.
All right!
Well done guys!
Way to go Tadashi,
you just made Seijoh
have to use one
of their time‐outs!
You rock Tadashi!
Thanks a lot, Suga!
That Number 12 is nuts.
You see that insane
receive he pulled off?
I'm pretty sure that was
nothing more than dumb luck!
Ow... That really hurt...!
[Saeko]:
That's it guys!
Kick their butts!
You've got this,
now keep it up, guys!
I can't do what
those other guys do.
I want to control my body...
I want to control the ball.
I want what it takes to
stand up to my opponents!
(whistle)
Tadashi! Get another one!
Watch the ball
all the way in!
Right!
[Shimada]:
Listen to me, Tadashi.
Don't give them the luxury of
being able to control the ball.
Use a direct trajectory...
Aim to go just barely over
the white belt of the net...
[Tadashi]:
...And let it fly!
I only have one weapon...
...my serve.
I get put into the game
for one reason.
And that's my one chance.
For one point at a time, it's
all on me. Everything is on me.
I have the power to change
the game's momentum.
Because that's my job.
(crowd cheering)
I'm the pinch server.
Nice net!
A little luck
never hurts!
No. It's more
than luck, Specs.
[Hitoka]:
OhmyGod... we're tied!
[Spectator 1]:
Karasuno totally caught 'em!
[Spectator 2]:
Now they're all tied up!
I... don't believe it...
Tadashi had a net ball
in the other match, too!
He is one lucky
little devil!
Mm‐hm! Mm‐hm!
They both may have
been net balls.
But the one during the WakuNan
match and the one just now
are different.
[Shimada]:
During the WakuNan match,
Tadashi was probably
more concerned about
whether or not the serve
would stay in bounds.
But right now...
he's thinking about exactly
where to land the ball.
The difference is... Now Tadashi
is serving on the offensive.
[Saeko]:
Tadashi is turning
into a stud!
Although I'm not sure it was
No matter what I do,
I keep throwing my serve tosses
really low...
Alrighty! Everybody calm down!
We're all calm, dude.
There's nothing we could
have done with that last one.
We'll get the
next one, okay?
Aw look at you guys! You're
all so poised and put‐together
it's making me kinda sad.
Heh!
Hmph.
There's a slow spin on it.
It won't shift around as much!
I got it!
Nice receive!
Coming back!
Great one‐touch!
Asahi!
Nice, Kageyama!
[Daichi]:
Triple block!
That's a pretty
high wall they've set up!
To the baaaack!
Aaaahh...
Yeaaaaah!
Whoa. Oh man Are you freakin'
serious? Is this happening?
[Spectator 1]:
Karasuno's at
match point!
One more point, guys!
Keep on it!
[Takeda]:
Good job Tadashi...
You're the hero of this match.
One more point.
Please boys, please
don't jack this up...!
Come on! Land this sucker!
Finish it off...!
Tadashi! Get us one more point!
[Shoyo]:
Bring it home!
That felt good.
This one's mine!
Damn, that guy's good.
Get the block!
Stop it, please!
Yeaaaah!
Nice job!
We finally stopped the bleeding.
But how many points did
he manage to take from us?
(whistle)
That was a fantastic
performance!
Good job!
Thanks you very
much, Coach.
All right!
Stay focused you guys!
Next time... I'll
get the ten points.
We are gonna win!
Tadashi has given us
new life. We have a chance!
Way to go!
[Daichi]:
We can't let it
go to waste!
YEAH!
Nice one, Man‐bun!
Here we go again!
We're back at
match point!
Do iiiit!
They got back in
the game so easily.
Even though they're cornered
they still managed to get off
a quick attack. And on top
of that it was right up front.
[Keishin]:
If it was up to me, I'd totally
be relying on the ace right now.
[Daichi]:
Nice receive!
[Hajime]:
It's a dump!
Hey, loosen up. You're
playing too stiff.
Yeah! Okay!
You got this.
We're right on the edge here.
I cannot let this be the last
match ever for our third‐years.
[Hajime]:
Get out of your head Kindaichi,
we need you in the game.
No matter what the situation...
we can handle it.
It's just us
and the ball.
Uh... Right!
Asahi! Crush it!
Make it count!
It's long! Get to it!
Aw... Yeah!
Nice kill!
Heck yeah!
Everything you'd
expect from Seijoh.
This next point.
It's huge. Here we go.
[Irihata]:
Now, in modern‐day volleyball,
the serve is one of the
most effective attacks.
It can be used in
any number of tactics.
And is unaffected by the block.
It is the ultimate attack.
That was basically a spike!
Yeah!
Nice oooone!
Well done!
Here we go Oikawa,
let's go get another point!
Now all of a sudden
Seijoh has set point!
Think they'll be able
to finish it off?
Damn it Noya!
Okay. We can't
do this alone.
Asahi. Listen up.
I'm counting on you!
Sure.
[Takeda]:
Asahi is going to help
with the serve‐receive?
If that's the call
from Daichi and Noya...
then it's probably for the best.
When Oikawa serves...
it's power... more so than
it's about his control.
We can't let his
serve go untouched.
We need to get
a hand on it.
[Keishin]:
We have to get
the ball into the air.
We've done it before.
We dug up a ton of serves
from Ubugawa and Fukurodani.
It'll be okay.
We can do this.
Bring it on!
Let's gooo!
[Yu]:
Daichi!
All right! Huh?
[Daichi]:
Nice Tanaka!
[Ryunosuke]:
Kageyama!
[Daichi/Yu]:
Asahi!
Way to go, nice receive!
(whistle)
Dude, they totally
took back the set!
I thought it really might
be Karasuno in straight sets.
Man! We had them
on the ropes!
Don't give up!
You can still
do it, guys!
Damn... this third set
is gonna be rough.
Just leave that behind us!
Yeah!
That serve really
is amazing. Isn't it?
Well yours is pretty
awesome, too!
You can tell he has a lot
more experience than I do.
[Tadashi]:
And I don't mean just because
he's a third‐year.
There's more to it than that.
[Shoyo]:
What do you mean?
[Tadashi]:
Jump serves have a lot of power
but they carry a lot of risk
in return. To put that
much power into it...
right in the middle of
pressure situation like that,
a lot of things can go wrong.
It's not even fair.
[Ryunosuke]:
Tadashi!
Some nasty
serves, my man.
Thank you. But, I still
have a ways to go.
Only about half of them...
are acutally any good.
[Ryunosuke]:
Well... then we'll have
to totally celebrate
the half that were good!
You'll have plenty of time
to pout and regret
the crappy
ones later.
So right now, grab ahold of
the good stuff by jumblies...
and make sure you
never forget 'em!
You killed it man!
And then, m'dude...
you can do again next time!
Yeah!
So it looks like we're
going into full sets. Hmph.
[Daichi]:
From the very first
practice match...
...and then the
Inter‐High prelims...
...until right now,
the semi‐finals...
We've always had the most
intense matches with these guys.
They're a challenging opponent.
[Toru]:
An aggravating opponent.
[Daichi]:
Until last year,
we didn't really know much
about each other.
[Toru]:
They were supposed
to be nothing to us.
[Toru/Daichi]:
But this is exactly how
it's supposed to play out.
[Toru]:
The final set...
[Daichi]:
...Our final battle.
[Hitoka]:
That was amazing,
Tadashi!
[Tadashi]:
Uh, thanks, Yachi.
[Hitoka]:
Just in case, I had an AED,
a stretcher, and a coffin
all at the ready. But we didn't
need any of it, did we?
[Tadashi]:
Did you just say
you broght a coffin?
Next episode of Haikyu!!
‐ "Team"