Slam it down!
Up front!
[Team Karasuno]:
All right!
Yeah! A side‐out!
Woo! How d'you
like that?!
We turned this
sucker back around!
Amazing! He hit it in front
of their attack line!
[Shimada]:
He's hitting with the
snap from his wrist,
so it's a pretty weak shot.
But as long as you can
shake the blockers off,
they can't dig it up
from there...
[Takinoue]:
So uh...
do you think Kageyama adjusted
it to Hinata intentionally?
Or did he just kinda mess up
in a good way?
That was so badass! It was like
you hit it straight down!
[Ryunosuke]:
Did you aim for that?!
Hinata was really close
to the net...
so I made the ball
close to him...
I'm just glad
it played out well.
[Toru]:
Ironically, the most
ingenius part of Kageyama...
...is not his technique,
but probably his stupidity.
[Toru]:
He plunges forward
without hesitation
when a normal person
would hesitate.
And he's going to keep doing it
for better or for worse.
When he's in the moment,
he can't see anything around him
and has no idea that nobody else
is keeping up with him.
But...
now a tiny little idiot
that goes even further
than him has appeared.
I only jumped up to where there
weren't any blockers around!
We gotta watch
Numbers 9 and 10.
Yeah. Those two morons
surprise me each and every time.
[Toru]:
However...
a cohesive team of six is
stronger than just two.
[Yutaro]:
Bring it on!
[Watari]:
Let's do it!
[Hanamaki]:
We're gonna
Glad you see it that way.
We are the ones
who are gonna win!
[Daichi]:
Do it, Tsukishima!
I got it!
That most recent attack...
it had to be a fluke.
Before they can figure it out,
I will crush them!
Oh yeah!
(excited cheering)
Yeah!
You can do it, Matsukawa!
You got this.
Yeah!
A pinch server, huh?
Guess they're trying
to bolster their defenses.
[Hajime]:
You're up, Yahaba!
At full strength...!
[Daichi]:
Asahi!
Sorry!
Cover, cover!
Tanaka!
[Yu]:
Double block!
[Toru]:
Yahaba!
Sure! Kyotani!
Damn!
Yeah, that way!
Yeah!
Did he hit with
his left hand?!
I thought that guy
was right‐handed!
Did he synchronize
on the fly?
Ambidextrous and able to
reposition himself in midair...
[Takinoue]:
A side‐out... If they
get to 20 points first,
it's gonna be tricky.
Please... please,
Don't let them pull away!
Right on!
Nice receive!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
That little brat!
(whistle)
Kyotani...
It's all you!
Yeah!
Excellent! We've caught up!
Yeah, what concentration.
[Keishin]:
These guys really
surprise me sometimes.
[Watari]:
Got it!
Watch out for
the right side!
Number 16!
Defend it!
Nice one‐touch!
Now you gotta
connect it!
Watch the left,
it's a spatch!
Pull back!
Whoa... Amazing...
[Matsukawa]:
Cover!
[Hanamaki]:
Left!
[Crowd]:
Whooooooaaaaaa!
Damn it!
All right!
[Toru]:
Okay, we don't
have far to go now!
Well, it looks like
they got there first.
[Daichi]:
Let's not panic!
It's just one point.
(whistle)
[Spectator 2]:
There he is! It's
that pinch server
who racked up five points
in a row during the second set!
Do it!
Here's your
shot, Tadashi!
Remember to
stay calm!
Give them
everything you got!
Right!
Come on!
Tadashi!
You can do it!
[Hitoka]:
Do it just like before!
Tadashi.
Now get us a point.
[Shimada]:
You can do it!
It's out.
No, wait...
The trajectory
changed this time.
All right!
Let's goooo!
Argh! You freakin'
kidding me?!
Last hit, it's you!
Mine!
[Ryunosuke]:
Chance ball!
[Team Karasuno]:
Synchronized attack!
Yeah!
Whoa! He is really
in the zone now!
Really nice one,
Iwaizumi!
Wow...
[Toru]:
Makki!
It's a feint!
Damn it!
All right! We cut Number 12
off at just one serve!
Nice kill!
Yeah!
When I first started
playing volleyball,
spikes were the only part
of the game that I liked.
But now...
I've learned the pleasure
of taking something my opponents
thought was a perfect shot
and sending it right back.
(whistle)
It's okay, dude!
But still,
I've gotta say...
he is hardly the
same guy I remember
from the Inter‐High
prelims...
That wasn't your fault...
They just made a play.
Just shake it off.
[Ryunosuke]:
All right!
Okay.
[Keishin]:
Tadashi.
It was a very
good serve, kid.
Every single point counts...
we can't let up!
Right...
[Keishin]:
The only way to win this
is to go after every ball
as if it's the most
important one in the game.
Neither side is
letting up at all...
So uh... If it's a deuce again,
do they playing until it's ,/
a two‐point ga‐
[Shimada]:
No... We can't settle,
we gotta to take it
Bring it on!
Aww... seriously?!
(cheering)
Whoa, what was that...?
A serve like that
at this point...
[Specatator 1]:
He must be some kind of monster!
One more time...!
[Scorekeeper 2]:
Seijoh's at match point.
You know what to do.
We gotta dig it up, Coach.
Sir!
Amazing mental strength...
They're under so much pressure.
Just make contact.
We're not gonna lose this one.
That's right!
(whistle)
Give it all you got!
Of course.
Okay... it's finally time, guys.
It's now or never!
[Seijoh Crowd]:
Oooooooolé!
Yeah!
Finally! Get him
outta there!
But even so... It's still
match point for Seijoh.
[Shimada]:
We've gotta be very careful.
Holy crap. It's
over for Karasuno
if they miss even
one more point.
[Scorekeeper 2]:
And they're about
to lose their libero.
Hey, Specs.
Got it.
Here goes!
(whistle)
[Keishin]:
It's the final battle.
Here goes.
(whistle)
[Keishin]:
It's the final battle.
Whoa! I bet they're totally
gonna use the tactical
one‐point two‐setter
now, guys!
If we can't get a side‐out
here, they're toast...
Good luck, guys.
Yeah!
[Takinoue]:
Oh man, all we can do it hope
for the best at this point.
Okay, Kageyama,
I've got an idea.
Let's go, Suga!
It's all you, man!
He always gets extremely focused
at the tail end of a game.
Where does that come from?
Dude! What're you doin'?!
Why are you picking a fight
with Hinata right now?
This is where
we're gonna end it!
Yeah!
Come on, Suga!
Eyes on the prize, dude!
If I make a mistake,
it's all over.
And if we can't survive
their attack, it's all over.
Okay!
In or out? Me or Iwaizumi?
They dug it up! But it
kept their ace in check!
Center!
YEAAAAH!
We stopped it!
Hinata!
Come on, I don't see
what the big deal is...
That is what the
middle blocker DOES.
Dude I'm SO sorry!
I'm surprised you lived
through that, Kageyama!
Karasuno caught up!
It's deuce...!
Sorry.
It's fine!
Just keep moving!
It wasn't like he went
in to shut them out,
but more like he just
sprung up to where the ball was.
Every single time, Shorty's
reaction speed astonishes me.
[Ryunosuke]:
Suga, serve up a winner!
Here!
[Toru]:
Front! Up front!
Whoa! That barely went
into their front side!
It broke 'em!
Now he's trying
to set Iwaizumi off?
He seems all
nice and pleasant,
but his serves aren't
pleasant at all!
[Asahi]:
Front, front!
Drop down!
I got it!
Yes, Suga!
There we go,
got the first touch.
[Toru]:
Now we won't see that same
attack pattern from last time!
Come on!
We just need to get
a finger on it!
Bring it to me!
No, no, no, no, no!
Yeah...
KAGEYAMA!
I won't do it.
I won't lose...
[Hitoka]:
Only one more point!
Man... even I thought
Kageyama wouldn't attack
after that last touch.
Gotta hand it to them, they're
really starting to get
into Seijoh's heads.
Yeah. That, and there's
the impression
[Shimada]:
that when Sugawara comes in,
he's up to something.
So even if just a little bit,
their attention
gets drawn to him.
That really pisses me off!
Nothing less from
Oikawa's protégé.
That confidence he has
when the chips are down...
that's all part of being
an amazing setter.
Yeah, you do
have a point.
[Yahaba]:
I want some
of that, too.
Are you saying you already know
the limitations of your power?
You think you know
all about your technique,
your body, your mind...
even though none of those
have been perfected?
If you believe that a person
was simply born with something
superior to you. That they
just possess a God‐given gift?
Then it is impossible
to overcome.
No matter your effort,
your creativity,
nor even
your teammates.
In fact, it's not
even really a problem.
It's not worth lamenting
because you see it
as a foregone conclusion.
[Ukai]:
It's a trap. You will only lock
yourself in a spiral of failure
and ineptitude. Don't
bother comparing your skills
to that of another.
Instead, you have only
yourself to improve upon.
Your path is yours
and yours alone.
"Today may be the day
you sieze the opportunity
to make your talent bloom.
Or maybe tomorrow, the day after
that, or even next year...
...or even maybe after
you turn 30.
[Toru]:
The time you choose to make
it happen is up to you.
But if you think
you don't have it,
then you probably won't have
it for your entire life."
Is it just me or... has
Oikawa changed recently?
Go, Sei‐Sei‐Sei‐Sei‐Seijoh!
Go, go, let's go, Karasuno!
Hey! Get with the program, man!
If they drop it as far forward
as they did earlier,
I'll get it...
You take the back.
Right!
Stay on your guard...
there's a chance they could
drop it on us again.
It's ours, we just
gotta take it.
Yeah!
Keep it near the
edge of the court!
Yeah, I know...
If I send up a weak serve,
they'll make us pay
for it immediately.
Okay, guys! We just gotta
get a hand on it!
Right!
We'll take it back!
Let's take this one!
Yeeeah!
[Ryunosuke]:
Make it count, Suga!
[Hanamaki]:
Up front!
[Yutaro]:
Iwaizumi!
Keep him in check!
TANAKAAAA!
Let's go!
[Koshi]:
Let's finish it off right here!
Argh! They got to it!
But look! A spatch!
[Hanamaki]:
Oikawa!
It's a chance ball!
He was outside the court!
[Keishin]:
How the hell did
he make that play?!
[Keishin]:
It's goin' to Number 4!
[Toru]:
Talent is something to nurture.
And wisdome is
something to hone!
This is it!
No! No!
Yeah!
The last hit!
A cohesive team of six is
stronger than just two.
Get to it!
Chance ball!
I don't think so...
He can't hit it from there!
Not on my watch!
Nice one, Mad Dog!
Slam it, Kageyama!
You kidding me...?!
Leave this one to MEEEEE!
Come at me, Tobio Kageyama.
Come at me with your
strongest weapon...
[Toru]:
Give it to me...!
No! Did they read in
to the switch...?!
All...
...RIIIIIGHT!
[Takinoue]:
We won! We won!
We woooonnnn!
[Takinoue]:
(howling in victory)
[Shimada]:
(sobbing)
Wha‐ Shimada...?! Don't
tell me you're crying!
[Shimada]:
N‐No, my contact
just fell out...
[Takinoue]:
Dude, you
wear glasses.
[Takinoue]:
Next Haikyu!!
‐ "Declaration of War"