[TAKEDA]
Wow Coach... to think we've
played more than 60 sets but
only won three of them so far...
[NEKOMATA] Come on, you need
another drink. Pronto!
[TAKEDA]
We've been walking on a thorny
[NAOI] No, if I drink any more
my liver might fall out.
[KEISHIN]
(laugh) Got that right.
[NEKOMATA] Oh you'll be fine.
Trust me!
[KEISHIN]
But, well, if we
[NAOI] I dunno. I've never
trusted you before.
[KEISHIN]
we were back during
[NAOI] And I'm not
about to start now.
[KEISHIN]
we might have won
[NEKOMATA] Now let me get
this straight mister,
[KEISHIN]
By centering on Hinata
[NEKOMATA] are you trying to
tell me that you're not gonna
drink my sake?
[KEISHIN]
[NAOI] Yeah... no....
Karasuno's attack style was
complete in its own way.
[NEKOMATA]
It's a joke, lighten up already!
[KEISHIN]
But using that strategy,
the limits became
quickly apparent.
And, Seijoh capitalized on it.
[KEISHIN]
So that's why we had to start
trying new things.
[TAKEDA] Yeah.
Understandably so.
[KEISHIN] Huh?
[TAKEDA]
The way I look at it, everybody
is their own cog in the machine.
[TAKEDA]
Every gear is its own piece.
And alone, there's no way we can
win against a powerhouse team
from the Kanto region.
[TAKEDA]
But, if all the cogs
fall into place...
(KEISHIN grin)
Hey! Don't think you can win
against Nekoma that easily!
[TAKEDA]
Easily? I never said
anything like that!
[TAKEDA]
But we still plan on winning.
[NEKOMATA]
Oh, you will huh?
Well look who's decided to
talk a little smack?! (laugh)
(TAKEDA laughs)
[DAICHI]
Okay, this is our final set. And
we've gotten our butts handed to
us the entire camp.
[DAICHI]
The least we can do before we go
home is take one from these
guys...
So let's show
Fukurodani who's boss!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[SHOYO]
I will prove that I learned
something from this trip!
(practice game)
[EVERYONE]
Thanks for the game!
[DAICHI] Yeah! Let's land one!
[YU, KEI, TOBIO, &
RYUNOSUKE] Yeah!
[BOKUTO]
All right! Bring
it on, Karasuno!
(whistle)
[YU]
Go for it, Asahi!
(ASAHI focused exhale)
[HITOKA]
Ah! There it goes!
[AKAASHI] Bokuto!
[BOKUTO] Yeah!
[DAICHI]
Left, No.4!
[KEI]
Tighten up for line shots...
He'll get through even
the smallest gap.
[BOKUTO]
Oh?
[KOMI]
It's out!
(whistle)
(FUKURODANI celebrates)
[KEISHIN] Blocked out, huh...
[TAKEDA] That was close!
[DAICHI] Shake it off,
Tsukishima! You almost got it!
[BOKUTO]
Maybe it's not the
[KEI]
Quiet.
[KONOHA]
Left, left!
[SHOYO]
Oh man, he picked that up!
[KOSHI]
But it's out of control!
(whistle)
[TAKEDA] From that situation to
a quick‐attack?!
(annoyed) Even if the
receive is out of control..
they can still do quick
attacks with confidence.
[KEISHIN] And their setter is
pretty damn good himself.
[AKAASHI] Nice serve!
[HISASHI]
Break it off at one point!
[CHIKARA]
(surprised) No.4 has moved
up to the front line!
[BOKUTO]
I can finally hit up front!
(whistle)
[KOMI] Serve's up!
[DAICHI]
Yours, Nishinoya!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice receive!
[BOKUTO]
Nice one, Saru!
Gimme the last one!
[KEISHIN]
Right now, we're at the point
where our wall is the highest on
the court.
[KEISHIN]
Go show them what you can do!
(whistle)
[KOSHI] Just how sharp of an
angle can that guy land those
cut shots?
[HITOKA] Oh?
[KIYOKO] A powerful hit that
cuts right in front of three
blockers...
It can be hard
to pull off.
And causes some physical strain
if you don't keep your
shoulders relaxed.
(HITOKA gasp)
[BOKUTO]
All right!
(boastful laugh) Did
you see that, Akaashi?!
I mean did you frickin'
see my super cut‐shot I
just did?! Huh?
[AKAASHI]
Yeah I saw it, it
was pretty incredible.
[BOKUTO]
Eh, it was a fluke! (laughing)
[KUROO]
Bokuto really needs
to shut up...
(KENMA yawns)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Cool... but a... fluke right?!
[ASAHI]
I wish I could do that.
You know that Bokuto from
Fukurodani. He's a different
player.
[BOKUTO] Hey, can I maybe try
making that shot one more time?
I wanna land another one!
[TAKEDA] I can't quite put my
[AKAASHI]
I think the other team will
completely see it coming,
Bokuto.
[BOKUTO] Oh! Yeah, I bet you're
right! Then, I guess I'll aim
for a line shot.
[TAKEDA]
Exactly...
[KEISHIN]
He might be the type of player
who boosts the morale
of his friends
and enemies alike.
[SHOYO & YU]
Boo‐yah!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Serve it up Tsukishima!
[SHOYO] A special attack?
[BOKUTO] You know it!
Okay.. About this attack...
What it does... is fool
the enemy with static and
dynamic movements.
(SHOYO interested)
[BOKUTO] Yeah
[AKAASHI]
There he goes exaggerating
again...
[KUROO]
So do you actually know what
he's talking about?
[AKAASHI]
Um I can only guess.
Now this attack isn't
something you use to
escape from the enemy.
[BOKUTO]
It's about perfect timing, a
perfect set, and a perfect
stance for spiking.
[BOKUTO]
You want everyone to think a
powerful spike is coming.
[BOKUTO]
Above all else... You even want
yourself to think you have
the perfect chance
to land the perfect kill!
[YU]
Leave it to me!
[SHOYO]
Nice receive!
[BOKUTO]
Make it look like you're gonna
smash 'em right in the nose!
(AKAASHI, RYUNOSUKE, & TOBIO
surprised)
(BOKUTO & TAKEDA shocked)
[KEISHIN]
Wait. D'you see that?!
Little Ginger tricked 'em!
[BOKUTO]
When the feint succeeds...
there's this glorious feeling
that's different from when
you land a spike.
[BOKUTO]
You know how several receivers
all jump in
trying to dig the ball and
it hits the floor right in
front of them?
[SHOYO] Yes.
[BOKUTO] You can look right into
their eyes the second they just
barely miss the ball,
[BOKUTO]
and then they land and look up
at you like little confused
puppy dog.
(KOMI, SARUKUI, & KONOHA
surprised)
[BOKUTO]
Oh man that is just the best.
(SHOYO astonished)
[BOKUTO]
He just faked us out!
[AKAASHI]
Bokuto, you were the one who
taught him that move.
(BOKUTO shocked)
(discouraged)
(KOMI, SARUKUI, & KONOHA angry)
Did you seriously just
use your stupid head?
Are you feeling okay!
[SHOYO]
Oh shut up, I use my
stupid head all the time!
Hmph! I say we don't let them
get another point the rest of
the way!
[AKAASHI]
I think it'll be impossible to
completely shut them out‐
[BOKUTO]
Can you just play along with me
once in a while?
[BOKUTO]
Damn that little Pipsquek!
I am not going to lose to him!
[ASAHI]
No.2!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Eat it!
[SHOYO]
Okay...!
[TAKEDA] Well one
thing is for sure.
[SHOYO] One‐touch!
[TAKEDA] Everyone seems
to be playing well.
[DAICHI] Got it!
Maybe that just some of
Bokuto's good influence.
[TAKEDA]
Oh, a setter dump, Coach!
(KURASUNO celebrates)
Kageyama's doing well, too!
I don't think I've seen him miss
a single jump‐serve today.
[KEISHIN]
Yeah... he's looking pretty
relaxed isn't he?
[KEISHIN]
Like the calm before a storm.
Or a leopard ready to pounce.
Kinda dangerous.
[DAICHI]
Tsukishima, let's get one more!
You can do it!
[TOBIO, internal]
I feel good. It's like my
stomach is completely empty.
But, I'm not hungry yet.
[TOBIO, internal]
I'm moving better than usual,
and I can see everyone else's
movements.
[TOBIO, internal]
My conditioning. It feels great.
[DAICHI] It's up!
[RYUNOSUKE] Nice, Daichi!
[TOBIO, internal]
And it looks like everyone
Does it have something to do
with the barbecue?
[TOBIO, internal]
Hinata's playing well,
too. He's not making any
unnecessary movements.
[TOBIO, internal]
Maybe now... we can use the new
quick‐attack. But I don't
know...
[RYUNOSUKE]
Asahi, nice receive!
(TOBIO gasps)
[TOBIO]
I know he wants to do it. But if
we miss now,
we might break the momentum
that the team has going.
[TOBIO]
The new quick‐attack can be
saved for when we have a higher
success rate‐
[SHOYO]
We doing this?
(TOBIO focused exhale)
[SHOYO]
The ball comes...
...and then... it stops.
(BOKUTO, WASHIO, & AKAASHI gawk)
(HITOKA & KIYOKO gawk)
(TAKEDA & KEISHIN gawk)
(whistle)
(SHOYO & TOBIO excited yelling)
[TOBIO]
Wait! What the hell was that?
You're supposed to give me a
heads up!
[SHOYO]
But you felt like we had it just
now, right? I mean didn't you
feel it?!
[TOBIO] I did, but this
is way too sudden!
[BOKUTO] What the hey? That
weird quick‐attack is back?
[TOBIO] I gotta get mentally
prepared and stuff!
[AKAASHI] No. That wasn't it...
[BOKUTO] Hmm?
[SHOYO] It's fine, we
were able to nail it!
[AKAASHI] Bokuto... What they
did was different
[TOBIO] It's not
all right! It's not!
[AKAASHI]
from what they've been
[SHOYO] Hey, let's do it again!
[TOBIO] Oh you think so, huh?
[TAKEDA]
Yes that's it...
[SHOYO]
The ball comes...
...and then... it stops.
(SHOYO & TOBIO power yelling)
[KEISHIN]
Oh yeah!
[TADASHI] Yeah!
[YU] What was that set you did
just now?! That was amazing!
[KOSHI]
Nice, Hinata, Kageyama!
[BOKUTO]
Hey Akaashi... was that freakin
awesome or what? Can we do that?
[AKAASHI]
I dunno... I think it's probably
more complicated than it looks.
[BOKUTO] Ohh...
[AKAASHI] Hinata is hitting it
naturally. Like it's nothing.
[AKAASHI]
But, that set looks like it's
really hard to hit unless you're
used to it. And besides...
[AKAASHI]
It would take a miracle
for me to just float
and stop the ball at the
point‐of‐impact like that.
[SHOYO]
We doing this?
[SHOYO] What? Why're you
looking at me like that?
You wanna fight?
[TOBIO, internal]
[SHOYO]
But that was incredible! It was
awesome! It totally stopped
right in front of my eyes!
Like, schwing! This time I felt
like it was totally gonna work
and stuff!
But to be honest, when it just
stops in front of me, it kinda
freaks me out!
You really are amazing,
Kageyama!
[TOBIO]
(disgust) You...
You're an idiot...
[SHOYO]
Amazing! Stupendous! (laughing)
[DAICHI]
You seeing this? Not
sure what to make of
Kageyama's expression.
[RYUNOSUKE] What's going on
with his face muscles?
[TOBIO] Shut up!
[ASAHI]
It's not very often that Hinata
gives Kageyama some straight‐up
praise.
[ASAHI] Good thing we had
faith and waited for them.
[DAICHI] Yeah.
[TOBIO] In any case,
next time, we need to‐
[HITOKA] You did it!
[HITOKA]
You did it! You did it! Nice
kill, you guys! That was
absolutely great! (happiness)
[HITOKA, internal]
Finally. It's been
a long three weeks.
[HITOKA]
Ever since their fight, Hinata
and Kageyama weren't on speaking
terms.
[HITOKA]
Nonetheless, the two of them
earnestly tackled the tasks
they each were assigned
to do. And now...
[HITOKA]
...the two of them
are back in business!
(HITOKA overwhelmed with
happiness, giggling)
[SHOYO]
(shaken breathing) One more
time!
[RYUNOSUKE]
I'm getting jealous!
Let me land something too!
[DAICHI]
We are not gonna lose.
[ASAHI]
No that'll be them.
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't get swallowed
up by them, guys!
[BOKUTO] Hey, hey, hey!
[SHOYO] All right! Let's keep
going!
[KENMA] That Shoyo...
[KUROO] Hmm?
[KENMA]
He's so full of surprises.
[KUROO]
Hm? I bet if the Shorty were
playing on our team...
Then perhaps you would
be a lot more motivated.
[KENMA]
I couldn't be on a team
with a guy like that.
[KUROO]
Huh? How come?
[KENMA]
I wouldn't be able to keep up
with him unless I was constantly
improving.
[KENMA]
No matter how smart I was about
ditching practice,
he'd notice the difference.
[KENMA]
Even that genius first‐year hit
a plateau for a second,
and Shoyo called him on it.
[KENMA]
That'd be exhausting.
[KUROO]
Hmmm.
Okay well, if Shorty was there
as a practice partner or
something...
THEN you think you'd
be more motivated?
[KENMA]
(refreshed) Wait, what?
[KUROO]
I'm just saying, when you watch
him play,
[KUROO]
you make a face like you just
bought a new game
and you're about to start
playing it, you know?
(KENMA shocked)
(long whistle)
[KENMA]
You're crazy. I'm not making a
face. What kinda face are you
talking about?
[KUROO]
A face of anticipation.
[KENMA]
Oh whatever. I don't
get you at all.
I don't look like that.
[KUROO] Do too.
[KENMA] Do not.
[KUROO] ...Do too. ...Do too.
[TAKEDA] Um...
lemme ask you coach.
[KEISHIN] Hmm?
[TAKEDA]
I have to admit, at first
glance...
I can't tell the difference
between this attack and the
old one from before.
[KEISHIN]
Ahh. The previous
quick attack used a set
that passed through Hinata's
impact point with a lot of
velocity.
[KEISHIN]
Meanwhile, the new quick attack
is lofted in order make it
[KEISHIN]
so that the spiker's highest
impact point equals the highest
point of the ball's trajectory.
[KEISHIN]
At the moment where the ball
begins to slow and starts to
fall downward,
[KEISHIN]
there is a brief moment to where
the ball just sits there instead
of blazing through.
[KEISHIN]
And that brief moment makes all
the difference.
It gives Hinata more
options before the hit.
(TAKEDA amazed)
(KEISHIN snickering)
I gotta bring the old man to the
Spring National preliminaries.
And show him our new trick...
live and in person!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice receive!
[TOBIO]
Kill the momentum of
the ball... Kill it...
[TOBIO, internal]
AAgh! It looked like it was the
same as earlier!
(KEISHIN & TAKEDA speechless)
(whistle)
(FUKURODANI celebration)
[TAKEDA]
That's too bad... I guess he
lost whatever
intense concentration
he had built up before.
[SHOYO]
Shake it off. Take it easy!
[TOBIO]
That pisses me off! (angry)
[SHOYO]
Oh chill out! What else
can you do at this point?
[ASAHI]
Well, it's not something that
will go all that perfectly in
the first place...
[DAICHI]
You know what time it is.
[RYUNOSUKE]
It's time for the upperclassmen!
[KONOHA]
Single block!
[SHOYO]
One‐touch!
[YU]
Got it!
(WASHIO & BOKUTO surprised)
(KOMI shock)
[KOSHI] It came off
the deflection!
And Nishinoya came from behind
the line! Which means, from the
libero's set...
[KOSHI]
The ace's attack is coming from
the back row!
[TAKEDA]
Gear number two. Nice job, guys!
(KOMI gasp)
(whistle)
[KOSHI] No it was out! Close!
(growl) (TADASHI disappointed)
[YU]
I'm sorry, the ball was too
freakin' low, dammit!
[ASAHI]
No no... I‐it was great! I think
that was more my mistake there.
[YU] Look if it's not good,
you gotta say that it's not
good, Asahi!
[ASAHI] Oh, sure...
[ASAHI] Uh it'd make me really
happy if it was a bit higher
next time.
[KOMI]
[YU]
Yes! I know! Thank you!
[KEISHIN]
That's great you guys!
Now don't let up!
(DAICHI agreeing nod)
[DAICHI, internal]
If we're too cautious, we won't
have the raw strength
to go toe‐to‐toe with
the powerhouse schools.
[KOMI] Got it!
[RYUNOSUKE] Left, left!
[DAICHI, internal]
In order for our team
to be successful...
[TADASHI] Chance ball!
[SHOYO] It's a free ball!
[DAICHI]
Even if we don't stack up
[YU]
It's mine!
[DAICHI]
We will need to hone and
perfect our new weapons!
[DAICHI]
This is it!
[DAICHI, internal]
Multiple spikers from
multiple directions
need to simultaneously
start their approach!
[DAICHI, internal]
A synchronized attack
at First Tempo!
[DAICHI, internal]
Do not allow their blockers
to narrow in on a target!
[DAICHI]
Everyone has to plunge‐in
believing that the ball will
come to them!
(RYUNOSUKE winding up)
(HITOKA & KIYOKO gasp)
(KEISHIN & TAKEDA gawk)
(BOKUTO shocked)
(whistle)
Right on!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Me do a good spike...
Me so happy feels...
[YU] All right! (laughing)
[KEI] He's crying...
[ASAHI] I think he
forgot how to talk...
[RYUNOSUKE]
I dunno, it's just been a while
since it felt this good to nail
one.
What the Hell, these guys're
attacking from all over the
place.
[DAICHI]
Well done Kageyama!
[TOBIO]
Thanks!
[TAKEDA]
Nice kill, Tanaka!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Thank you!
Always full of surprises...
Aren'tcha...
[YAKU]
Don't look away!
[TAKEDA]
Gear number three!
[TADASHI]
There was the synchronized
attack.
They were able to execute the
set and spike from First Tempo.
They totally nailed
it didn't they?!
[KOSHI]
As opposed to their
triple‐block,
our attack had four
people, including the
attack from the back.
[KOSHI]
They can't possibly keep their
eyes on everyone. Hmm...
[TADASHI]
Hm? Is there
something wrong, Suga?
[KOSHI]
Well...
I think there's something I
want us to try out now.
(whistle)
[BOKUTO]
Dammit!
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[ASHIYA]
Oh man, Karasuno is on a roll.
[YUKAWA]
Now they're starting
to land the attacks
that were sluggish during
the first day of training.
(long whistle)
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Finished off a set against
Fukurodani all tied up!
[YU]
Yeah!
But don't celebrate just yet.
Tough part's comin'.
[ALL]
Yessir!
Now you should never
let your guard down.
But... be aware that everything
you've been working on...
is starting to come together!
[TAKEDA]
So in the course of
battling out this set,
remember what you've got
and keep it going!
[ALL]
Yessir!
[KEISHIN]
And this time, just like we
planned,
[KEISHIN]
we haven't been letting their
ace player land spikes and boost
their morale.
[KEISHIN]
Well, aside from that one
ridiculous cut shot.
[KEISHIN]
That is all thanks to you
getting the one‐touches!
[KEI]
Oh... thanks.
If we keep No.4 under control,
we can take it home...
Now let's do this!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[AKAASHI]
I know things are looking
rough...
but look we need to stay calm
and not get distracted
by the wide variety of
Karasuno's offensive tactics.
[KOMI] Yeah!
[ONAGA] Yessir!
[AKAASHI]
Bokuto? Are you listening
to this or what?
[BOKUTO]
Yeah! Course I'm listening!
Come on, let's get this thing
started! I'm pissed
[YUKIE]
Something's going on there.
(AKAASHI sigh)
(practice games)
(whistle)
(FUKURODANI celebrates)
[YU]
Dammit, sorry about that!
That was our chance to turn
the tables!
[DAICHI]
Nah, don't sweat it!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice fightin', Noya!
All right, this serve is
gonna finish 'em off!
[SARUKUI]
You got this, Bokuto!
[AKAASHI]
Come on Bokuto... we need to
stay calm here.
[BOKUTO]
I AM calm!
Crap, Bokuto's starting
to get fired up...
All right, punks! Here ya go!
(KONOHA startled)
(whistle)
[BOKUTO]
Aw crap, that was so stupid!
Sorry guys I don't know what the
hell is wrong with me! (wailing)
[KOMI] Why don't
[UBUGAWA A]
Hey look at that now Karasuno's
caught back up again.
[UBUGAWA B]
Yeah... will there be a huge
upset at the very end here?
[DAICHI]
Their No.4 makes shots
from anywhere.
[DAICHI]
Let's aim for him and put him in
check for a little bit.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Yessir!
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE, internal]
Crap! I aimed for the corner a
bit too much!
[BOKUTO]
I got it.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Whoa, that was lucky! Heh.
[BOKUTO]
Give the ball to me! I'll stop
their run right here and now!
[AKAASHI, internal]
When I send the ball to
Bokuto... and he's a bit too
overzealous...
[AKAASHI, internal]
A: He lands it like normal.
[BOKUTO] All right!
[AKAASHI, internal]
Or B: He misses or gets stuffed.
And that increases the chance
for his spirits to get
completely crushed.
Then he's no good to us.
[AKAASHI, internal] Or C: He
doesn't get a set at all.
[BOKUTO] I don't care anymore!
[AKAASHI, internal]
Which means he'll get all pouty.
And that's pretty annoying.
[AKAASHI]
Here, Bokuto!
[SARUKUI]
Triple block!
[BOKUTO]
Bring it!
[KOMI]
Got it!
[BOKUTO]
One more time, Akaashi!
(annoyed) This one's all you!
[BOKUTO]
This one's is it!
This time, we'll make
sure to stop him guys!
[ASAHI] Now!
[DAICHI] Now...!
[SHOYO]
Oh?
(AKAASHI speechless)
(whistle)
[KURASUNO]
All right! Yeah!
[UBUGAWA A]
Now Karasuno's flipped
the game around!
And I'm pretty sure this the
first time Karasuno has been in
the lead all week long.
[UBUGAWA B]
Yeah, maybe so!
Um was that a block they
just did over there?
[KIYOKO]
Not quite...
It didn't clear the net...
Whenever that happens...
it's just called a missed spike.
(BOKUTO heavy breathing)
[KONOHA, internal]
Ugh... Oh no...
[SARUKUI, internal]
Oh, it's time for that?
[KOMI, internal]
You're kidding me, isn't it
early?
[ONAGA, internal]
Really, already?
[WASHIO, internal]
That was fast...
[AKAASHI, internal]
Oh, here it comes...
[BOKUTO]
Akaashi....
Don't send it to me anymore
today!
[SARUKUI, KOMI, WASHIO, &
KONOHA, internal] (sigh) Now
he's in sad mode...
[DAICHI]
Hmm? What's this?
[AKAASHI] (sigh) All right.
(BOKUTO whimper)
[AKAASHI]
But while I'm not sending any
sets to you... please try to
chill out.
[TAKEDA]
You think this could be
our chance, Coach?
[KEISHIN]
Yeah, we can take this set!
[DAICHI]
This is our chance guys.
It looks like their ace is off
his game, let's keep after 'em!
[KURASUNO]
Yeah!
[TOBIO]
Hinata...
we're gonna use that
quick‐attack again.
I'll give you the set you
want, so trust me. And fly!
[SHOYO]
Yeah! Heh.
[SHOYO, internal]
With this new weapon...
[SHOYO]
We can do it. We will win
against Fukurodani!
[SHOYO]
It looks like we can
finally beat Fukurodani!
[TOBIO]
Their ace was telling them
not to set for him anymore.
[SHOYO]
Wait, does the winner
get to eat more meat?
[SHOYO]
And if so, does the loser get
stuck with vegetables?!
[TOBIO]
We absolutely MUST
win this game!
[SHOYO]
Next Haikyu!! "Above".