[Daichi]:
It looks like
they chose to receive.
We'll be serving first.
Okay.
Time for the
deciding tournament.
They seem nervous...
A lot more nervous than
they usually are...
[Takeda]:
especially the
third‐years.
[Shoyo]:
Aw, yeah!
Tsukishima! Your new
glasses look so cool!
Uh, you know you've been
saying that every day lately.
When YOU say something
of mine is cool,
it makes me feel
a lot LESS cool.
That's not cool!
[Akiteru]:
Here ya go, Little Bro!
Huh?
It's a pair of
sports glasses...
I found some that are functional
AND pretty cool‐looking.
When you're wear
these, face‐blocking
won't be scary at all.
Uh, yeah, it will.
Ushiwaka's only human, you
know... You can beat him.
What's up with the first‐years
looking more confident
and reliable than us?
We don't have TIME
to be scared!
Yeah!
(whistle blows)
[Terushima]:
If we do end up going against
each other in the tournament.
I'm sure it's gonna
be a real good time.
(whistle blows)
[Team Karasuno/ Team Johzenji]:
Thank you for the game!
Johzenji! Johzenji!
This is it! The big
tournament starts today!
These guys are one of the best
four from Inter‐High prelims...
This should prove to be
a pretty interesting match.
Alright, Man‐bun. You give
that first shot all you got!
[Daichi]:
Karasuno, fight!
[Team Karasuno]:
Fight!
Woo!
[Ryunosuke]:
You got this, Asahi!
Get a nice,
solid receive!
Man... that's intense!
Nice cover!
Terushima, last hit!
Chance ball!
Woo... yes!
Way to fight
you guys!
You gotta hit that strong all
the way from the end line?
And he was hitting
it off‐balance, too!
Normally, you'd return
it with an underhand pass.
[Futamata]:
Serve's up!
Got it!
[Ryunosuke]:
Left side!
Let's go!
This is no good... It's like
being up against a superstar
baseball team during
gym class, or something...
Yeah, exactly...
They don't really fit
any sort of pattern,
and you don't have any idea
what they're gonna do next.
[Koshi]:
Yeah... and the worst part is,
none of that is a coincidence.
Uncertainties are
normal for Johzenji,
and that in itself
is their weapon...
[Terushima]:
Let's do it again!
Come on!
Hey!
Dork.
Sorry, guys!
[Johzenji Cheer Leader]:
Shake it off, shake it off!
Come on! Grab the
ball and give it back!
[Numajiri]:
Yeah!
You guys get carried
away too easily.
I hate to tell ya, but you're
the only third‐year left...
Having to deal with
all those lunatic kids,
you never
get a break.
[Daichi]:
Make it a good one, Tsukishima!
It's a quick!
Well, in case you didn't know,
they can attack normally, too.
Aw, sweet! A net‐ball!
I'm on it!
[Spectator 1]:
Nice reflexes!
[Spectator 2]:
But it might
not connect!
Nice Hinata!
Whoa, he's flying!
[Hitoka]:
Look out!
[Spectator 3]:
He's like a dang spider!
Back side!
Holy crap!
They returned it!
Guys who are super athletic
AND unpredictable.
Sounds familiar,
doesn't it?
BOO‐YAH!
Well... that was actually
rather surprising, wasn't it?
But... It should be noted that
Karasuno's ridiculous attack
hasn't been used yet.
Take it to 'em, Kageyama!
Aw, crap...
No matter how pretty the receive
is, as long as the ball gets up,
they can do
something with it.
[Anabara]:
All the boys know that, and they
have the skills to back it up.
Dammit!
[Terushima]:
One more shot!
Jiri, go direct!
Brutal... They're doing
nothing but defending.
[Ryunosuke]:
Daichi, nice receive!
There it is!
No.10's
super‐quick attack!
Hey, Kageyama! There's no way
we can lose to these guys!
(intense high‐five)
So that was the quick‐attack
we heard about.
[Shoyo]:
OUUUUCH!
[Tobio]:
Sorry, wuss.
It's hard to predict
the opponent's movements,
but the ball
isn't disappearing.
Let's calm down
and go at 'em.
[Shoyo]:
Right!
Nice, Captain...
[Futamata]:
Number 10!
Johzenji can be inaccurate in
all sorts of ways, can't they?
I mean... look at them,
their blockers are jumping
all over the place.
And they're quick to
fall for decoys, too.
But they're nothing
if not persistant.
And no matter how
you look at it,
they're pretty tough
to deal with.
Check this out, I have
a friend who plays on the
Johzenji basketball team...
Oh yeah?
I heard that their
volleyball team plays nothing
but 2‐on‐2 games for over
half of their practice time.
[Obara]:
Really? Just 2‐on‐2?
Well, that's dumb.
Well, if that's all they're
used to, then they play
without expecting anyone
to do anything for them.
And so, every single one of
their players is looking to
set up some attack
at all times.
[Anabara]:
You idiots!
Talk to each other!
And that's how things
like that happen.
Each and every one of them
is really annoying...
Yeah, well, all the
other schools in town
think we're pretty annoying
too, y'know...
What?!
Tanaka!
[Terushima]:
Nice one, Jiri, yeah!
[Kei]:
There are two attackers
in Johzenji's front line,
excluding their setter.
A back row attack, maybe?
That guy's the setter.
Who's gonna set it?
Someone from the back row?
Huh?
WHAAA!
Let's go! Let's go!
I gotta say...
they're tricky,
but they're pretty entertaining
team to watch in action,
aren't they?
Can't argue with that.
But...
[Takeda]:
when it comes to such
a freewheeling attack,
we can keep up with them.
So are you havin'
a good time yet?
They play hard...
and they're good...
Old coach Ukai
used to say...
"That to truly have fun, you
need to have strength as well."
That one is not necessarily
complete without the other.
I didn't understand what
he meant... when he said
fun was so
important...
[Terushima]:
All right!
[Tadashi]:
But now watching Johzenji,
I think I'm starting to see it.
So having fun...
IS their strength.
Maybe they're just trying
to build each other up...
but they sure do a lot
of clowning around.
Well, when they're
in the groove,
they do play
good volleyball.
[Futamata]:
Sorry, sorry!
But this happens whenever
you compliment them...
He's really tiny,
but he sure can jump!
[Team Karasuno]:
(cheering)
The setter looks like he's
kinda set in his ways...
But he still manages to come up
with some really crazy attacks,
doesn't he?
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice receive!
[Daichi]:
Asahi!
Who's it gonna be?
I see it! I don't think so!
Nice block, Kageyama!
Uh... that block
just now...
[Takinoue]:
...he took it with his face.
[Takeda]:
Time out!
Gah! Kageyama,
are you okay?!
He'll be fine,
little man.
Please, don't die!
Until you stop bleeding,
you have to sit.
Whatever, man!
I'm just fine!
[Daichi]:
No, you're not...
What's wrong with you?!
[Kiyoko]:
How are your eyes?
[Tobio]:
They're fine.
Did their enthusiasm
lure him in?
They can be
a bit infectious...
Well, this is a good opportunity
to cool your head off.
[Keishin]:
You not getin' back out
there out until
you stop bleeding anyway,
so go get yourself checked out.
[Takeda]:
I‐it's just in case!
Come on, let's go.
[Shoyo]:
Hey, Kageyama!
Don't worry!
I got this!
How about... You just leave it
up to your upperclassman.
[Koshi]:
Tsukishima, make it
a nice serve!
Wait, what are they doing?
[Obara]:
Why are they
taking out Number 10?
I mean, he doesn't seem like
he's doing all
that bad or anything.
[Futakuchi]:
Maybe they're going
to use this opportunity
to try something else out.
Besides... the other guys
seem to be a little better
at basic playing skills.
Oh, come on, man...
I'm telling the truth, right?
So tell us,
what do you think about your
little friend there, Aone?
[Obara]:
You seem to know
his game pretty well.
Is this all he's got or what?
[Aone]:
It may be like that for now.
Oh, my God... he...
...Spoke!
And Player 10 standing over
there... understands that.
Hey, Ginger.
You should
watch Kazuhito...
He's been practicing
combination plays
with Sugawara setting
for him, yeah?
So, I want you to just watch and
learn from your upperclassmen.
Yessir.
We're gonna cut 'em
short with one serve!
Kazuhito,
get a grip!
Could you please just calm down.
We know you wanna be in there.
I want to be in the game,
and practice, too.
There is still...
a lot to do!
[Tadashi]:
Nice kill!
Whew...
Keep at it,
keep at it!
Okay!
[Numajiri]:
Terushima,
serve it up!
Woo‐hoo‐hoo! That's what
I'm talkin' about baby!
That look as though he's just
scored three points in one shot
is really
pissin' me off!
Yeah, well, uh...
look who's talking, Tanaka.
What'd you
just say to me?!
Don't get distracted
by their excitement.
Just go after them,
and TAKE the set!
Shake it off,
shake it off!
C'mon guys,
let's do this!
[Tadashi]:
Oh, look at that...
Kageyama is going
to be just fine!
Yeah, it looks like it.
Nicely done.
[Takinoue]:
But I guess they're not
gonna swap guys in yet.
[Daichi]:
Nishinoya!
[Yu]:
Got it!
[Asahi]:
Nice receive!
So I seem to recall you saying
you've "got this"...
Oh, shut your face!
I'll be able to do so
real soon! You'll see!
Brutal!
Nice kill!
We won't lose...!
Ah, Chance ball!
Got it!
[Team Karasuno]:
Synchronized attack,
Sugawara version!
All right!
[Kiyoko]:
This is it.
Set point.
That thing where everyone
starts moving all at once...
That looks
pretty awesome!
Hey... listen up...
Oh my God...
please you guys...!
[Daichi]:
C'mon, Kazuhito! One more!
Johzenji is also doing
a synchronized attack?!
[Terushima]:
Oh, NOW it's on!
HUAAAAAAA... aaaaah...
All right, guys! That's what
I'm talkin' about! Good stuff!
Yeah, we used to do
that ALL the time.
That synchronized attack
from Johzenji just now...
They're playin' us
at our own game.
Copyin' what
they saw us do.
What? When they're behind? And
even trying it out on set point?
[Keishin]:
Could be, because we're still
in the first set.
It's absolutely frightening
how reckless they are.
Check out
their banner...
"Simple and Strong" doesn't
seem to mesh very well
[Takeda]:
with how the team
acts, does it?
They're pretty wild
and sporatic.
They should probably go
with something like:
"Crazy and a Little Confused."
I'm not so sure... up until
very recently, Johzenji has been
known as a pretty
simple yet strong team.
At least they were...
You guys should
really think about
when to try
something like that.
But I really thought we
could pull it off, coach.
They took a set
from you guys!
Just like all of you,
they can cause a lot of trouble
if you let 'em get going!
That Number 10 sure
jumps around a lot.
That is what
their banner says.
Yeah, and then
there's ours...
[Bobata]:
Our banner seems so cheesy.
We should probably
get ourselves a new one, huh?
Come on it's not that bad.
"Simple and Strong"
is timeless, right?
[Terushima]:
That's more a matter
of taste, but, uh...
it's not a good match
for our team.
At least not for our generation.
Or rather... the generation
that's coming after us.
I'll say...
[Anabara]:
My name is Anabara, and I'll be
your coach starting this year.
I will be recreating the team
from the foundation up.
First off, make 2‐on‐2
games actually happen.
[Student 1]:
I heard they have five
second‐years on their squad.
[Student 2]:
Seriously? Making it
to the semifinals
with a team
like that is amazing.
[Okudake]:
Hey, man.
Hmm?
They'll be a time...
when things aren't all
fun and games anymore.
What're you going to do
with yourself, then?
I dunno. I'll probably
have fun anyway.
[Terushima]:
Alright guys are you
ready to do this?!
[Team Johzenji]:
(cheering)
Aw man...
[Futamata]:
I'm guessing we're gonna
see that weird combo
of theirs again.
Hinata, Kageyama,
make sure to calm down!
[Shoyo/Tobio]:
(psyched yelling)
Dear God,
shut up!
[Terushima]:
I see you're back!
You're like a spider monkey!
It's boring out here without
you y'know. And your huge jumps!
"Boring"?
Yeah boring like
your captain!
He's good and all,
but he's kinda dull!
Huh? I have no idea
what you mean...
Well in any case... next set,
we're playing to win!
Y'know, one‐on‐one, I can't
really win against you, Dye‐job.
Hey! Don't give me
a nickname, Coppertop!
But with the rest of
my team, you can't win!
[Futamata]:
All right, send it up!
[Daichi]:
Nishinoya!
All right!
I TOLD YOU GUYS!
Amazing reflexes!
No... more like he knew
that it was coming.
Daichi, nice
ass‐wiping!
You REALLY need a
new way to say that...
Here!
Do these guys
even HAVE a plan?!
All right!
This time, we
finally nailed it!
Thanks!
Sorry about that!
Nice cover!
No matter how much we
told you to calm down,
I had a feeling you guys would
still botch the first shot.
[Daichi]:
You're too wound up!
I'm no good at super‐flashy
moves, but at the very least,
I can create a foundation.
Anyway, go play to
your heart's content.
[Shoyo/Tobio]:
Thank you!
[Keishin]:
Even if these guys ARE a bit
wild and undisciplined...
they aren't any better
or worse than we are.
Although...
[Keishin]:
We have somethin'
else goin' for us.
The lead just keeps
getting bigger.
[Terushima]:
Come on guys,
get into it!
[Bobata]:
It's up! Last hit!
Get back!
Yeah!
Tanaka, nice one!
All right!
A counterattack!
Yeah!
Dammit! There's no way we can
keep up with that Number 10!
Hinata, nice kill!
[Shoyo]:
Anytime!
[Daichi]:
Shake it off, shake it off!
[Shoyo]:
Sorry!
This set's all ours!
[Yu]:
It's out!
[Futamata]:
Shake it off, shake it off!
[Ryunosuke]:
Get some, Daichi!
Got it!
Sorry!
I got this!
He's just going
to send it over!
Oh, yeah,
take it to 'em!
Uh, sorry...
Look at that!
They're taking a time out!
It's good to be
on the offensive,
but Johzenji is
rushing themselves.
Come on guys we're so close!
We got this,
we can do it!
We can make
something of this!
Then, what do we do with that
quick attack from Number 10?
What should we do?
Uh... what
SHOULD we do?
[Terushima]:
Don't think too hard!
Just rush in and attack!
Just go for it! Do it!
[Okudake]:
So, Misaki, what are you
going to do from now on?
[Misaki]:
I still haven't
found a successor
to take my place on
the sidelines yet...
so I'll stick around
until Nationals.
I can't say I'm
disappointed about that.
Y'know, those guys are
actually really good
whenever they're
doing well,
but when they break down,
it goes downhill fast.
You gotta whip 'em
into shape.
I don't think they'd listen
to anything I have to say...
Aw, come on, now.
That's not true.
[Bobata]:
You're right! Let's just do it!
Just rush in!
[Futamata]:
Totally!
[Numajiri]:
Just rush in, guys!
[Misaki]:
What is the big, stupid hurry?!
You guys are always trying
to make it happen
with just enthusiasm.
But listen. There are times that
won't always be fun and games.
What're you gonna
do with yourself then?
I dunno, I'll probably
have fun anyway!
You seriously having fun
when you're getting crushed?
I don't know what kind
of player that is,
but he's certainly
not going to win.
Um... Misaki? Is
something wrong?
I'm fine but
they're not.
[Misaki]:
I don't think these goofballs
can face their weaknesses
unless somebody just comes out
and tells it to them straight.
Which brings me to this:
Uh, yeah?
Just so you know...
Okudake asked me to smack
their asses into gear.
"Asses"?
Wow, how lewd...
She just said "asses"!
Kay...
it's true that the current
situation isn't much fun.
[Terushima]:
And well, I hate to say it,
but those guys are playing
a lot more freely
than we are.
You know what Okudake
liked to say...
"To play, you first
need a playground."
Bear with the times
that are "not fun"...
and then you can keep playing
till the very end.
Did I just hear them all
over there talking about asses?
What's the matter?
[Ryunosuke]:
Kiyoko...
I don't really get it...
but I think it's a good idea
for us to be scolded, too.
We are prepared to
take your punishment.
No.
Here...
I'm not smacking
your butts.
Kiyoko sounds so sexy
when she talks like that!
We're halfway through
the second set...
[Keishin]:
This is where the fun
REALLY begins...
[Daichi]:
Those guys from Johzenji sure
play some magic volleyball.
[Shoyo]:
We gotta keep up!
[Yu]:
Rolling... Head‐butt!
[Shoyo]:
Noya, that's awesome!
[Daichi]:
That's NOT volleyball...
[Asahi]:
Next Haikyu!! "To the Next"