[Terushima]:
Aw, man!
If we had just won yesterday,
we'd be playing
in a game right now!
Well if Karasuno were to
win against Shiratorizawa...
we'd at least come out
looking a little cooler.
Nah.
We would've won if that stupid
Number 10 wasn't around.
Nah, it was the setter... That
guy caused a lot of trouble.
Not the captain?
Although Number 10 was pretty
fun to watch, wasn't he?
The captain, huh?
[Futamata]:
Well, maybe you're right...
He's their foundation
and that can
sometimes be overlooked.
[Tobio]:
Captain!
Hey, Daichi!
You okay?!
[Guy 1]:
Oh, my God.
[Guy 2]:
Something wrong?
[Guy 3]:
He collapsed!
Hm? What happened?
That... was a collision.
[Toru]:
On the last hit, right after
he returned the ball...
the captain collided with
that kid with the buzzcut.
It looked like he hit
his face pretty hard.
[Hajime]:
Whoa...
(groans)
Alright, what hurts?
M‐my face...
Daichi, where
are you right now?
Sendai City Gymnasium.
And what team are
we playing against?
W..Waku South, right?
I'm fine, I swear!
[Takeda]:
Look, you hit your
head pretty hard.
so for now, go to
the medical office.
[Keishin]:
He's right.
[Takeda]:
Please...
you need to confirm that
everything's alright, okay?
Now, do it!
That's the quickest way to
get you back into the game.
Okay...
You're bleeding
What?
You okay? You
feelin' nauseous?
I hope this isn't
a concussion...
Ah, I feel f‐
Too bad for him...
I guess that might be it for
Mr. Captain for this game...
But it's the coach's
decision, though.
[Hajime]:
A hit like that could
give you a serious concussion.
Hey Specs... you mind
if I leave this to you?
Um, Daichi...?
I'm really sorry!
[Daichi]:
No, I'm sorry, Tanaka.
I saw you coming in
to cover the loose ball...
but my body had a will of
its own and went for it.
But, hey,
look at that...
[Daichi]:
You got us a point back,
and now...
we're on our way
to TAKING this.
Karasuno's Number 5...
[Toru]:
He's pretty damn strong
mentally during a match...
But that's only when
he finds himself cornered
and has to make a play.
I wonder how he will hold up
now that he's the reason
the team's backbone has snapped?
If they lose this match now...
this will be the last game
the Captain'll ever play.
I'm sorry, Asahi.
I'll be right back.
But until I get here...
It's up to you.
Don't you worry...
We'll be fine.
[Hajime]:
His footing seems to be steady,
so he's probably okay, right?
[Toru]:
Yeah, but the problem
is this match.
Who can serve as a substitute
for their backbone?
It's a big role to fill.
Maybe they'll
use two setters?
Yeah I dunno, unless
they regularly practice
a double setup... or unless
they have a setter who happens
to be better at attacking and
defending, than a wing spiker
would be... doing that
on the fly is too risky.
A wing spiker who can
replace their captain...
I'm not sure if they have a
player like that or not.
We're counting on you!
Make it count!
Huh?
Ennoshita! You got this!
Hm... He's one of the ones who
played in the practice match.
What kind of kid was he?
I don't remember
too much...
[Hajime]:
But I think he was pretty steady
and accurate in his deliveries.
[Toru]:
Karasuno doesn't
have a very big squad.
Maybe they don't
have anyone else.
Just like the
practice matches...
Just like in practice...
Just like... practice...
Anyway... go play to
your heart's content.
It's not the same!
Watching form the sidelines,
and being on the court
are two completely
different things!
Oh... so I guess it is
you after all, Ennoshita.
Oh...!
Hey, Ennoshita,
you think I can send up some
quick attacks from the get‐go?
Uh... Mhm.
Ennoshita! Their Number 1
blows balls outta the court,
so keep that in mind!
You got that?!
Uh... yeah.
Ennoshita, be cool,
it's all you!
Make it happen,
you got this!
It's understandable that
Ennoshita would be uneasy.
But I have to say,
if anyone was ever needed
to take Daichi's place,
it'd be him.
Hey, Ennoshita... Sorry,
but... but we need you.
Why are you "sorry"
about that?
Or are you just
feeling bad
that you knocked Daichi
out of the game.
[Chikara]:
Either one of you
could have been the one
hurt by that impact.
Just so happens
that it was Daichi.
It could've
been you, instead.
You understand that, right?
But you know,
there's only one thing we're
all thinking about right now.
Alright, go ahead, Asahi.
We're just glad you didn't
get hurt too, Tanaka!
[Chikara]:
So c'mon! Buck up!
We need you to be focused!
Our ability's already down with
Daichi being out of commission.
Can't have you all mopey
on top of that.
Oh, I hope this all works out.
I mean Ennoshita can be a little
bit on the timid side, y'know.
He's a shy one.
Oh hell no!
[Saeko]:
Whenever they're at our place,
no matter how you look at it,
Ennoshita is totally the head
hancho of the second‐years.
Of the wing spikers,
Ennoshita is a good fit at this.
He works pretty
well with others.
And has a knack of keeping
our crazy second‐years
under control.
And plus, lately, he's been
spreading his influence
over to those knucklehead
first‐years, too...
Yeah, you're right...
[Koshi]:
All yours, Ennoshita
[Nakashima]:
Nail it!
[Naruko]:
Center!
[Team WakuNan]:
(cheering)
[Nakashima]:
Okay...
Time to get those points back!
Gah! Sorry!
I'll extend my defensive
range a bit more!
Sorry if I'm
making things harder.
[Kazuhito]:
Don't sweat it!
[Chikara]:
I can't match Daichi when
as I am the one
standing here,
making excuses and running
from responsibility
won't do us any good.
Besides...
Avoiding the conflict now,
will only make it worse
in the future.
That... I know.
Let's GOOOOO!
COME ON!
Not bad... substitute captain!
Until the Spring Nationals,
the third‐years will continue
to lead the team.
But make sure you second‐years
start thinking about
the next captain.
It's important, you guys.
[Chikara]:
That's what Coach said.
[Ryunosuke]:
The next captain, huh?
Wouldn't it be all right
for Ennoshita to do it?
Wh‐wh‐why me?!
Just a hunch,
that's why!
And you just ate that popsicle
in like two bites, didn't you?
According to the rules,
the libero can't become
the team captain, can he?
Yeah!
I think Tanaka would
be fit for it, too...
but looking at our line‐up
of all our first‐years...
[Hisashi]:
We'll have to deal with a
couple of idiots...
[Kazuhito]:
And a jerk.
Yeah... I do think we probably
need someone really calm
in the
captain spot...
I do agree that Ennoshita
would make a good captain,
but I'd like some more options.
In other words, you guys should
consider yourselves
as candidates!
No, no, no, no...
That would be
a terrible idea.
[Ryunosuke]:
Whatever...
don't be wussies.
Yeah, but... I ran away, so...
[Chikara]:
I could... I could never be
the leader of the team.
[Chikara]:
Don't you remember
last summer...
Not yet! Dig that ball up!
[Chikara]:
That next day, two of the
first‐years stopped showing up.
And several days later,
I ditched practice
for the first time since
starting in middle school.
I just... went home.
I faked an illness.
I did feel... a little guilty
about abandoning the guys.
But at least I wasn't
getting yelled at in practice.
Whew, air conditioning!
So I skipped the next day...
and the day after that, too.
I didn't have to run
in the blazing heat.
I didn't have anyone
screaming at me to "Do better."
Okay. Here goes nothing...
I'm... sorry for ditching!
Please let me join
practice again!
Ennoshita, I'm glad
that you came bac‐
Then don't show up in
your school uniform!
Captain...
I‐I'm sorry! I'll
change right away!
Relationships between
teammates are difficult...
but only being
nice does you no good.
Yessir.
Hey! If you're heading over,
yous hould probably change!
[Kiroki]:
All right, let's get started!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yeah!
[Kiroki]:
Let's get some laps!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yessir!
Uh, yeah...
[Kiroki]:
Karasuno, fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
[Chikara]:
There were five first‐years that
boycotted practice back then.
Of which, two resigned
from the volleyball team.
I saw them later...
they seemed happy enough.
Which is the better choice?
Well that probably
depends on the person.
For me, the time I spent
not playing volleyball
was the most painful,
so I went back.
But, all the doubt and
guilt from my leaving...
that'll probably
never go away.
[Ryunosuke]:
That may just be why.
It's all right because
you're back here with us, now!
Oh, my popsicle was a winner...!
I'm gonna go redeem it!
Okay, so not everyone on a
team's the same type of person,
y'know? Y'see, I like to jump
right into things while other
people out there are
pathetic little wimps!
But then, you!
You're the type of guy
who can work with everybody!
All I know is that I came back
and I'm glad I did.
Uh‐huh, of course
you are!
Me, too!
But either way,
someone who quits isn't
fit to lead the team.
Let's GOOOOO!
[Yu]:
It's up!
[Ryunosuke]:
Ennoshita, nice one!
Give it to me!
Asahi!
(cheering)
Ennoshita! Good job
getting that up!
Y‐yeah!
Even if did run away...
even if I'm no match for Daichi,
I am going to fight!
That's why I'm here!
That's why I came back!
[Hisashi]:
Asahi, serve it up!
Sorry about that.
Okay, okay,
next one!
[Shoyo]:
Serve it up!
We're not gonna let you keep
getting points, you know!
We're sending this one down!
Waku South is staying
pretty poised.
Shake it off, shake it off!
We can get 'em!
Uh... Tadashi...
Nice receive!
[Hisashi]:
It looks like Kiyoko's
calling for you.
[Tadashi]:
Oh!
Oooooh, yeah!
[Koshi]:
Nice kill, Tanaka !
(whistle)
Huh?
When Tsukki is up to serve,
you need to put in Tadashi
as the pinch server.
Under these conditions,
I want to avoid them
flipping the game
and winning the set.
We'll push it hard
and shake 'em off.
[Referee]:
Okay. You can go.
You're way too stiff.
It's not like last time when
the opponent was in the lead.
We're all just thinking
about how lucky we'll be
if we can get this.
Thanks, Tsukki!
Was he... trying
to encourage you?
Tsukishima sure has a crappy way
of saying nice things.
[Chikara]:
Tadashi...
are you gonna puke?
Uhh... N‐no, I
think I'll be okay.
Good, glad to hear it.
But I... think I might.
A‐are you
all right, man?
Yeah, that's an Ennoshita...
He know good and well that
seeing someone more nervous
than you can help you
calm yourself down.
Work your sorcery, my man.
I'm going to puke.
It's fine, it's just fine...
Just like Tsukki said,
we're in the lead...
I need to loosen up.
And I practiced
a lot for this.
(whistle)
[Tadashi]:
Crap! The serve toss
was a bit low!
[Ryunosuke]:
YEAAAH BUDDY!
It made
it over!
Yeah!
[Koshi]:
One more point!
Oh, my God...
Whoaaaahh!
Do it again,
Tadashi!
You got it!
Uh... 'kay.
You can do it,
Tadashi!
Alright, so... I got lucky
that last one went in.
But if I miss the next one,
then it'll...
just cancel it out.
So... remember what
you did in practice.
You can do it, land
the ball in the court!
What's up? He's not going to
hit it while jumping this time?
Got it!
Is it some tactic to stop
using the jump float?
It's just a hunch, but that
Number 12 really screwed up
the pinch serve back
in the Seijoh game.
And since that last serve
was pretty sketchy...
[Spectator 2]:
...maybe he chickened out?
Crap! The attack is coming!
Move it, Tadashi!
[Koshi]:
It's dropping! Go front,
the front, front, Tadashi!
[Tadashi]:
Please legs... move...!
It's up!
Nice one,
Ennoshita!
Asahi!
All right!
Asahi, that last
back‐row attack was nice!
Heh... thanks.
Um... Coach looks
a little upset...
Oh no, he looks
really pissed.
[Keishin]:
TA‐DA‐SHI...!
H‐he knows, Coach.
Probably... he probably
knows better than any of us.
What tha? Was there
a problem or something?
Even without a jump serve,
[Shimada]:
you can hit a ball
that doesn't spin.
But when you jump up and make
contact from a higher point
of impact, the ball can
travel with more force
and is more effective.
[Saeko]:
Okay, I see.
Don't get me wrong,
taking a defensive
approach during a match,
isn't always
a bad thing.
[Shimada]:
Now that said, in the end,
it ended up being
a point for Karasuno.
But...
for Tadashi and his level of
skill right now,
the only weapon he really has,
is his serve.
So if he moves away from that...
If he abandons his strength...
...he has nothing left.
Don't be an idiot...!
It's OUR sense of pride!
What more
do you need?!
[Tadashi]:
I'm not a very
confrontational guy...
but I still went off
on Tsukki the other day.
I don't even know
what I'm doing...
Uh, hey Coach,
how's Daichi doin'?
He'll be fine, there aren't
any signs of a concussion.
However...
The bleeding and pain in
his mouth are a bit severe.
[Keishin]:
I'm gonna to let him
rest a bit, just in case.
Okay, thanks, Coach!
Mm‐hm. Your job
is to win the game,
and prepare the next
stage for Daichi!
You guys don't need to think
about anything other than that!
You understand?
[Team Karasuno]:
Yessir!
[Chikara]:
Hands in, guys.
All right! Let's go!
Karasuno... fight!
[Team Karasuno]:
Fiiight!
(whistle blows)
Nice kill, Ushijima!
Ushijima! Ushijima!
Hey, Shiratorizawa
is five points
from winning the match
before us.
Time to head over.
Yeah.
[Seijoh Guy]:
And the Karasuno ‐
Waku South match
seems like it will
drag on a bit.
Oh, is that so?
How is Karasuno doing
without their team captain?
His impressive receives that
have always stood out...
Well they aren't the only
good ones that they have.
But it can't last. If the
balls that they're used
to going up stop doing so...
Their game will start to change.
[Toru]:
Things like that start working
on you slowly and quietly.
Maybe it's right about now...
that they really
start feeling it
[Tobio]:
Ennoshita would be the type
to make a good team captain.
[Shoyo]:
Then, who do you think
would be vice‐captain?
I doubt Tanaka and Noya
are up for it.
[Tobio]:
Why's that?
[Shoyo]:
Because they have
mental problems.
[Tobio]:
You're one to talk!
Next episode of Haikyu!!
"The Losers"