[TAKEDA]
It'll be tricky.
Exams are also next month...
You do know that, don't you?
(KEISHIN shocked)
[TAKEDA]
Don't you?
I'm sure you can guess what I'm
about to say.
(YU & RYUNOSUKE quivering)
(TOBIO quivering)
[TAKEDA] If you fail
even one subject...
(SHOYO quivering)
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
Extra lessons on weekends.
And possibly during
the summer as well...
So wouldn't that make your
little field trip impossible?
(ALL shouting)
[DAICHI]
Hey! This isn't something you
can just run away from!
Ennoshita, go get them!
[CHIKARA]
Hmhm.
Okay... So what's failing?
How bad can I do?
[KOSHI]
Are you serious?!
You guys, I think
Kageyama's dead!
[KOSHI]
Well, the pressure's
already high for us
third‐years to make good grades,
[KOSHI]
since we decided to
stay with the club.
[KEI] Yeah NONE of us
can afford to fail.
[CHIKARA] No kidding.
[SHOYO]
Wait! Maybe if we ask the vice
principal nicely, we can still
have a chance to...
[KEI]
Why don't you just focus all
that energy on actually passing
your classes?
Even if the school didn't
make you forgo the trip...
the tutoring sessions
could still cause a
scheduling conflict.
[SHOYO]
(devastated) Coach, help!
[KEISHIN]
Gah... Well, this is just a part
of being a high school student,
you know‐
[SHOYO] Yeah, but‐!
[KEISHIN] Chin up, Red!
Just try to stay positive!
[SHOYO]
Stay positive?! Fine... If
you say so, I'll do my best...
Could you tutor me?
[KEISHIN] Hinata...
You're not gonna like
what I'm about to say.
(SHOYO gasps)
[KEISHIN]
Do I really look to you like the
kind of guy who got good grades?
[SHOYO]
(mind blown gasp) No.
[KOSHI]
Hinata... You're overreacting;
I'm sure everything's gonna work
out just fine.
[SHOYO]
No... You don't get it; on a
hundred‐point scale,
I don't even score in
the double digits...
How am I ever gonna pass?
[KOSHI] Huh?
[SHOYO] What?
[KOSHI]
You're already saying your
prayers?! How bad IS this?!
(SHOYO, RYUNOSUKE, TOBIO, & YU
screaming, various as of
distress and sobbing)
[KEISHIN]
Takeda, get a grip!
[KEI]
Ha ha! They're so dead!
[DAICHI] Calm down!
[ALL] Huh?
[DAICHI]
You still have
time before exams.
You might be numbskulls...
but can Karasuno win games
without you?
[DAICHI]
I don't think so!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Uh, yeah thanks for the...
compliment, I guess?
[DAICHI]
We are doing this...
ALL of us...
Now let's go to Tokyo!
Listen, you four... From now on,
you have one rule. And it's very
simple.
[DAICHI] Never fall
asleep in class!
(ALL startled)
[ASAHI]
They have to be TOLD that?
[DAICHI]
Don't pull any all‐nighters...
They'll make you slow in class
AND on the court...
[DAICHI]
Get 8 hours of
sleep every night!
[YU & SHOYO]
(wounded) Okay...
[KEI]
See you guys later.
[ASAHI]
Cool. See ya.
It's gonna be all right...
I mean you passed your
entrance exams to get
in here, didn't you?
[RYUNOSUKE]
(whimper) Thanks, Suga!
But if you do fall asleep,
I'll make sure you
face the consequences.
[SHOYO]
(exertion) Kageyama...
[TOBIO] Hmm?
(SHOYO conspicuous
inaudible whispering)
[TOBIO]
What?! No!
[SHOYO]
Hey, don't be so selfish!
If we fail the test, we
don't get to go to Tokyo!
[SHOYO]
It's Nekoma! And some
other good Tokyo teams too!
[SHOYO]
You can't pass that up! Plus I
thought you told Ushiwaka you
were gonna be the best setter!
(TOBIO annoyed) (grunt)
[TADASHI]
So it turns out Kageyama gets
bad grades too...
[TADASHI]
You'd think he'd be a little
smarter than the rest of 'em...
Hinata doesn't really
surprise me though.
[KEI]
Yeah, his brain's just like a
volleyball; nothing but empty
space inside.
[SHOYO]
TSUKISHIMAAA!
[TADASHI & KEI]
Huh?
[SHOYO]
Sorry...
Can you help us
study?! Please?!
[KEI]
Me? No thank you.
[SHOYO]
(shattered) Just a couple
minutes a day!
Or at least maybe give me a
few pointers here and there!
[TADASHI]
Couldn't you maybe spare some
time before or after practice?
[KEI]
Don't you think it's kind of
unfair of you
to make the little guy do
all the groveling, Kageyama?
[KEI]
I want to hear it from you.
(TOBIO angry)
[SHOYO]
Let it go! You have to!
[TOBIO]
Please help us.
[KEI]
What's that?
[TOBIO]
Could you please help us study?
[KEI]
Sorry, could you
please speak up?
[TOBIO]
I'M ASKING YOU... WOULD YOU
PLEASE HELP US STUDY!
(ALL startled)
[KEISHIN]
What's all that racket?!
Keep it down!
[SHOYO, TOBIO, & TADASHI]
S‐Sorry, Coach...
[KEI]
I didn't do anything.
[STUDENTS]
Sorry.
[KIYOKO]
Oh no, that's alright.
[SHOYO] Kiyoko!
[KIYOKO] Huh?
[SHOYO]
I looked for people
in other classes
that haven't joined a club...
Here's what I found out.
[KIYOKO]
Hm? Oh thanks a lot.
[SHOYO]
Oh, it's uh...
[KIYOKO]
Hm? (soft laugh)
[SHOYO, internal]
What's so funny?
(shakes it off)
Uh, listen... it's gotta be
really hard for you
doing all the manager's work
by yourself, isn't it?
[SHOYO]
Let me know if I can do
anything.
(KIYOKO acknowledges)
[KIYOKO]
After the next tournament,
we third‐years will
be gone, y'know.
[KIYOKO]
And well, you've
all improved so much,
[KIYOKO]
I've been wondering what our
team's going to look like after
this year's over.
But of course, I'm
determined to do my share
of the work until then.
[SHOYO]
Uh... let me help you!
[KIYOKO]
(surprised) Thank you...
But final exams
should come first.
(SHOYO speechless)
[KIYOKO] And then
practice, of course.
(SHOYO surprised)
[KIYOKO] I mean, you
are the Greatest Decoy...
We're gonna need you.
[SHOYO]
Right!
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[KEI]
Okay, let's try the next one.
[KEI] Hinata, take
a look at number 6.
[KOSHI] That one
works out like this.
[YU]
Oh!
[PROBLEM GUY]
Problem Number 6.
Enter the appropriate
phrase in parentheses to
complete the proverb.
(SHOYO anxious)
[PROBLEM GUY]
The meaning is, "Even the
heartless can
sometimes shed tears of
compassion." Fill in the blank:
[PROBLEM GUY]
Even a demon can...
[SHOYO]
Die?!
Uarghhh!
[TADASHI]
Ah jeez! Poor demon!
(SHOYO confused)
[TOBIO]
What did that demon
ever do to you Hinata?
[KEI]
Demons are usually
seen swinging clubs...
I can see how you
might've gotten confused.
[SHOYO]
Gah, would you please
shut up! (seething under)
[KEI]
You just saw the word "demon"
and wrote down the first
thing you could think of.
You really are stupid.
[TOBIO]
Exactly. Why don't you
use your brain for once?
This is important.
[SHOYO]
Why do you guys always
have to pick on me, huh!?
[KEI]
You don't have any room
to talk though, Kageyama...
[KEI]
I mean aren't you doing even
worse than Hinata is?
[KEI]
You should at least start
practicing your English
vocabulary words.
[TOBIO]
I don't need to know no English!
[KEI]
Oh my God you guys are
completely hopeless
(TOBIO stunned)
[DAICHI] Kageyama.
[ALL]
Huh?
[TOBIO]
A B‐Quick.
(SHOYO surprised)
[TOBIO]
A... C... Time lag in front of
setter...
Left side back row attack. D,
Parallel, Semi, Time lag behind.
[TADASHI]
(nervous laugh) Of course.
Perfect... When'd
you learn those?
[TOBIO]
Hm? The first time
I saw them... I guess.
[DAICHI]
Then I don't want to hear
you say that memorizing
words is too hard.
(SHOYO, TADASHI, & TOBIO
dumbfounded)
[SHOYO]
Yikes...
I am gonna beat you!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey... let's meet at
my place on Saturday.
[YU] I'll be there!
(SHOYO eavesdropping)
[SHOYO]
(power‐up yell) You guys
won't beat me either!
[KEI]
Could you please calm down and
focus on studying then?
[CHIKARA]
Nishinoya... Can I see
that quiz from yesterday?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Snacky time!
[CHIKARA]
With literature, you can
usually find the answer
somewhere in the passage.
[CHIKARA]
You just have to read carefully.
[PROBLEM GUY]
Problem Number 3. Copy the
sentence from the passage
[PROBLEM GUY]
that most exemplifies the two
contradictory feelings Norio
has.
[YU]
You just have to step up
and be a man, Norio!
[CHIKARA]
How? It says you have to choose
a sentence from the passage!
You can't just tell Norio
whatever you want!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Norio was kinda bein' a wuss.
I thought you said you were good
at memorizing quotes and stuff.
[YU]
You bet I am! Like this!
[CHIKARA]
Uh I don't think your shirt's
gonna be on the test!
[YU] Damn...
[SAEKO] Are you
actually studying?
(YU excited)
(ALL curious)
[SAEKO]
Y'sick or somethin'?
[RYUNOSUKE]
What do you mean, "are we sick?"
[YU]
Saeko! Hey there!
[SAEKO]
What's up, Yu? Looks
like you're stayin' cool!
[YU]
Thanks, I try!
[HISASHI]
Sorry if we're uh...intruding.
[SAEKO]
Oh no you're fine.
So why didn't you think to ask
your big sister
to teach you, ya little punk?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Just forget it, sis...
You're just as stupid as
I am and we both know it.
[SAEKO]
Obviously not, since one of us
is a college student, jerkwad.
[RYUNOSUKE]
All you do is work and practice!
[SAEKO] Shut up! You don't
know what I do with my time!
[HISASHI] So that's his
sister... Makes sense.
[KAZUHITO]
Um yeah...
[SAEKO]
Don't come crying
to me when you fail!
[KAZUHITO]
What does your sister
practice, exactly?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Taiko drums. She's putting
a group together...
[RYUNOSUKE] There's a festival
coming up pretty soon.
[SAEKO] Put your backs into it!
[HISASHI]
Whoa, that's cool.
[YU]
Nice outfit!
[CHIKARA]
Okay, let's get back to work.
We gotta get to Tokyo!
[YU & RYUNOSUKE]
Yes sir, Professor Ennoshita
sir!
(phone vibrating)
[SHOYO]
Your Inter‐High prelims start
tomorrow, right? Good luck!
(phone ringing and vibrating)
[KENMA]
I guess it'll be all right...
You're coming here
too, aren't you?
[NATSU]
Let's go play jumpy rope!
[SHOYO'S MOM]
Not now, Natsu, your
brother has to study!
[NATSU]
Hmm? Aww...
[SHOYO]
Yeah! Tokyo, here I come!
(power yell)
[SHOYO'S MOM]
Keep it down, Shoyo!
[TEACHER A]
Tanaka from class 1's doing a
lot better now;
[TEACHER A]
not only does he stay awake in
class but he actually wants to
ask questions!
[TEACHER B]
Same goes for Nishinoya
from class 3! They can
do this if they try!
[TAKEDA, internal]
Maybe we really CAN make that
trip to Tokyo!
[TAKEDA, internal]
That just leaves Kiyoko's part.
[TAKEDA]
I wonder if she was
able to do it?
[KIYOKO]
Excuse me... Could I speak with
you, please?
[TAKEDA]
I wonder if she found
a new manager?
[HITOKA, internal]
(flustered) She's cute...
[KIYOKO] During Inter‐High
preliminaries last year...
[HITOKA, internal] A gorgeous
third‐year girl.
[KIYOKO] we were neck‐and‐neck
for a while with Aoba Johsai...
[HITOKA, internal]
That beauty mark near her lip
[KIYOKO] They can be a bunch of
troublemakers sometimes...
[HITOKA, internal]
Oh wow, and her hair is
[KIYOKO] But I think we're the
kind of team people want to root
for y'know.
[HITOKA, internal] (gasp)
[KIYOKO]
Whaddya say... why don't you
just try it out for a little
while?
[HITOKA]
(startled) Okay!
[KIYOKO]
(gasp) Really? Thank you!
I'll come get you
right after school!
(HITOKA stunned)
[SHOYO]
You found a new person?
That's so awesome!
(HITOKA startled) (nervous)
[RYUNOSUKE] Hey beautiful.
[YU] Who's that?
(HITOKA distressed)
[KIYOKO]
Well, team...
I'd like you to meet your
potential new manager.
[HITOKA]
Um... my name is Yachi!
(DAICHI excited)
[KOSHI]
It's so great to meet you!
[SHOYO]
Nice job, Kiyoko!
[TADASHI, internal]
She's pretty.
[ASAHI]
You a first‐year?
[HITOKA]
(shriek) Uh yes.. Yes, I'm in
class 1‐5, sir!
[TOBIO & KEI] Sir?
[DAICHI] Give her
some space, Asahi!
[ASAHI]
Huh?
(HITOKA distressed)
[KOSHI]
Huh? uh... Stop it. You're
staring at her, it's creepy!
[ASAHI]
This is really great news! Now
you've got a manager for next
year.
[SHOYO] Yeah!
(HITOKA fumbling, quivering)
[KIYOKO]
Well, it's not set in stone...
I asked her today at the very
last minute,
[KIYOKO]
so she's just dropping by on her
way to do some of her committee
work.
[KIYOKO] But she wanted
to come meet you all.
[HITOKA] Y‐Yeah, it's
very nice to meet you!
[ALL] Hello!
(HITOKA panicked)
[KIYOKO]
Easy, don't crowd her; she's not
used to you guys yet.
[ALL]
Hm?
[HITOKA]
Um... Sorry for bothering you!
[DAICHI]
Kiyoko... I had no idea that you
were out looking for a manager
for next year.
[KIYOKO]
Yeah well. I didn't feel like
all the searching I did back in
the spring was enough.
[KIYOKO]
In order for Karasuno's team
to continue to grow stronger...
[KIYOKO]
it's very important that I pass
on my responsibilities after I
graduate.
(RYUNOSUKE, KOSHI, & YU sobbing)
[DAICHI] Oh, Kiyoko!
[RYUNOSUKE & YU]
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH, KIYOKOOOO!
[HITOKA, internal]
(terrified) Who knew those guys
were so tall and intimidating?
I don't think I can come back!
Oh God! I stood next to that hot
girl for almost 2 whole minutes!
[HITOKA] What if I get killed
by one of her admirers?!
[FANGIRL] Die!
(HITOKA nervous flitting)
[KEISHIN]
(confused) You all right?
(HITOKA terrified)
(HITOKA scared)
[HITOKA]
Who's this tough guy?!
Is he a fan of hers?!
[HITOKA]
(scared) PLEASE DON'T KILL
MEEEEE!
[KEISHIN]
(shocked) Um... kill you?
(bell ringing)
[STUDENT C] Man, I'm starved!
[STUDENT D]
Let's go to Sakanoshita.
[KEI]
Tutoring sessions are
only before and after
practice. Beat it.
[SHOYO]
(grunt) Come on! Mr. Yoshida's
not here and I need to‐
[KEI]
Terribly sorry, but you'll have
to come back during my regular
business hours.
(SHOYO frustrated)
[SHOYO]
Psh, Tsukishima,
more like Sucky‐shima!
[SHOYO]
What're we gonna do?
[TADASHI] Hinata!
[SHOYO] Hm?
Hey, can you please
help me with English?
Oh sorry... I'm
kinda terrible
at English.
(disheartened)
Oh but hey... That
new first‐year manager
girl we just met.
[TADASHI]
She's in class 5, so I bet her
grades are pretty good.
Oh, that's right! Classes 4
and 5 are for college prep!
[HITOKA, internal]
(sipping juice box) What should
I do after school? Guess I could
go back...
[SHOYO]
Hey, Yachi!
Sorry to bug you.
[HITOKA]
Huh?! It's the volleyball guys!
[HITOKA, internal]
What do they want?! Oh god,
I don't remember their names!
[HITOKA]
Did they TELL me their names?!
Ahhh, what do I do?!
[HITOKA]
What kind of future can
I have if I can't remember
people's names?!
[SUPERVISOR] You're
terrible with names!
[HITOKA] Argh!
[HITOKA]
I'll lose my job and end
up homeless...
eating garbage...
Selling my organs!
(CAT snarls and hisses)
[SHOYO]
Anyway, my name's Shoyo Hinata.
[HITOKA] Huh?
[SHOYO] And this is Kageyama.
[TOBIO] Hello there.
[HITOKA] Uh, hi.
[SHOYO]
Do you enjoy studying, Yachi?
[HITOKA]
Uh... Well, I don't hate it,
but...
[SHOYO]
It'd be great if you could help
us with English... Wouldn't it,
Kageyama?
[TOBIO]
If you don't mind.
[SHOYO]
If we fail our exams next month,
we can't take the trip to Tokyo!
[SHOYO]
So we've had that four‐eyed
bully jerk‐face Tsukishima
tutoring us 'til now.
[KEI]
Why is this so hard for you?
[SHOYO]
But now he's getting really
irritated with us
because we're too stupid, so...!
[TOBIO]
Jeez, Hinata, he's
not THAT bad is he.
[SHOYO]
Fine, but wouldn't you rather
have a NICE teacher?!
[HITOKA] I... can if you
want me to... (startled)
[SHOYO] Really?!
[HITOKA]
Sure! But I'm sorry if I'm not
any nicer to you than the
Four‐Eyed Bully jerk‐face guy...
[SHOYO]
I wouldn't worry about that.
Wow, I get it now! You're
awesome at this!
[HITOKA]
Oh no, it's nothing...
(nervous laugh)
[SHOYO]
Your notes are so easy to read!
And I like your drawings too.
Yeah, my mother runs a design
company, so she's really picky
about details like that.
[HITOKA]
Oh, it's better if you leave a
blank space right here so you
can write in it later...
[HITOKA]
And it's easier to keep track if
you only use a few colors... and
then you‐
[HITOKA]
(gasp) I'm sorry! I drew all
over your stuff!
[SHOYO]
Wow, this is making perfect
sense to me now.
[HITOKA]
Oh... I‐I'm glad I could help
you out.. heh...
[HITOKA]
So, uh Hyena...
[SHOYO]
It's Hinata!
[HITOKA]
Hinata. Do you like to study?
[SHOYO]
Yeah no... I can't stand sitting
still for that long.
[HITOKA]
So you're just working hard
because you really want to go on
that Tokyo trip?
[SHOYO]
Uh‐huh! Because we get to play
practice matches with a buncha
good teams there!
[HITOKA]
That's really cool...
I don't think I've ever put
everything I had into something
like that before.
[SHOYO]
There's this school called
Nekoma High and their setter
is some kind of genius!
[SHOYO]
Plus they've got this
evil‐looking captain; with a
rooster head!
[SHOYO]
He's a crazy evil good receiver,
so no matter what kind of combos
we throw at him,
[SHOYO]
he goes like "bwaaah,
I don't think so!"
[TOBIO]
And they've got an impressive
libero too... He's a good match
for Nishinoya.
[SHOYO] Yeah, there's a lot of
good players! And not just in
Tokyo.
[HITOKA, internal] Setter?
[SHOYO]
Our prefecture has the Great
King from Aoba‐Johsai, as well
as the absolute champ Ushiwaka..
[SHOYO]
and then there's Date Tech's
Iron Wall who stand at 6 foot 3!
[HITOKA] Oh wow, that is super
tall! Does that... mean you're
like the manager?
[SHOYO] Huh? Why?
[HITOKA]
It's just, I thought only tall
people played volleyball.
And most of the guys on our
team are pretty tall...
[SHOYO]
(stunned) Oh no! I AM short...
but I'm still a starter, at
least for now!
[HITOKA, internal]
Oh my gosh! I can't believe
I judged him by his appearance!
[HITOKA]
I'm sorry!
[SHOYO]
It's cool, I'm used to it.
I may not be tall...
(HITOKA question)
[SHOYO]
... but I can fly!
(HITOKA touched)
[TOBIO]
Hinata... Don't forget to copy
this part down.
[SHOYO]
Oh, okay.
Those guys are all
bigger than me...
But... When I'm in a game...
it's like I'm a hero fighting
against my enemies...
I get so pumped...
I feel invincible.
[HITOKA]
That's impressive... You really
have a lot of passion don't you.
[HITOKA]
So I guess that makes you some
kind of tiny giant.
(SHOYO shocked)
(HITOKA startled)
[SHOYO]
Wait.. You know about
the Tiny Giant?
[HITOKA]
Um... well it's just that uh...
when they play sports on TV, if
there's a Japanese guy
[HITOKA]
who's really talented but
smaller than all the other
athletes,
they call him the tiny
giant... or something.
[SHOYO]
Oh... okay... Yeah! Then I am
gonna be the next Tiny Giant!
[TOBIO]
Hey... If you want to do that,
you have to get to Tokyo... Get
your ass to work.
(SHOYO shocked)
[SHOYO]
Can we do this again sometime?
[HITOKA]
Mhmm... The best way to learn is
by teaching, right?
[SHOYO] Wow, Yachi... Thanks so
much! You're the greatest!
(HITOKA shaken about)
[SHOYO]
Bye! See you at practice,
okaaaay?
[HITOKA]
(nervous giggle) What is my
problem? Feels like I've been in
direct sunlight for too long.
(school bell rings)
(HITOKA shy)
[SHOYO] Yachi!
(HITOKA startled)
[SHOYO]
We had a quiz in English today,
and there were questions from
what you taught me!
[SHOYO]
I got almost whole
third of them right!
(HITOKA excited)
[HITOKA & SHOYO] Woohoo!
[HITOKA] Nice job, Hyena!
[KOSHI] Goodness, that
Hinata sure does have
a way with people.
[SHOYO] I told you, it's Hinata!
[KOSHI] Doesn't he? I mean he's
already friends with her.
[HITOKA] Just Hinata!
[KIYOKO] You can just observe
for today... There's no reason
for you to be nervous.
(DAICHI leading stretches)
[HITOKA] Right!
[KIYOKO] Hmph.
[KIYOKO]
Oh! Anyway, be sure to watch out
for the strays, okay?
[HITOKA]
Okay! (internal) Strays?
[HITOKA, internal]
Stray what?! Bullets?!
[KEISHIN]
You okay, kid?
(HITOKA startled)
(nervous) (mortified)
[HITOKA]
You're the bad guy from
yesterday! Are you gonna
kill me?! (whimpering)
[KEISHIN]
Uhh... listen, I...
I'm just the coach...
[HITOKA, internal]
Oh god! I judged someone based
on their appearance again!
[HITOKA]
I'M SORRY! I'm so sorry...
(KEISHIN shocked)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Left!
Yeah!
[ASAHI]
Nice, Tanaka!
[KEISHIN]
Don't leave any room, blockers!
[TADASHI] Sir!
[KEISHIN] Heads up!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huah! Sorry, bro!
[KEISHIN] Talk to each other!
[ASAHI] Left!
[YU]
Double block!
(HITOKA gasp) (confounded)
[KOSHI]
Good one, Hinata!
[TADASHI] My bad!
[KIYOKO] Are you all right?
[HITOKA]
(snaps out of it) Yes ma'am!
It's just that I've never
watched a volleyball game this
close to the court...
[HITOKA]
It's so powerful!
[KIYOKO]
Well, when it comes
to offense...
I think we're probably
the best team around.
[HITOKA] (gasp) Whoa...
[SHOYO] Sorry!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Ahhh... Kiyoko's talking...
Her mouth is moving...
And she's smiling, too!
[YU]
They're having some girl talk!
That's so cute...
[KEISHIN]
WE'RE gonna have a talk if you
don't stop acting like that!
(YU & RYUNOSUKE shout in pain)
(KIYOKO soft laugh)
[KIYOKO] We used to be
strong... Years ago,
[KEISHIN] Now get ready
for the next play!
[KIYOKO] we made it into
the national championships.
[YU & RYUNOSUKE] Yes sir!
[HITOKA] Really?
[KIYOKO] Yeah, but these days
it's a little different.
In fact, now people have been
calling us the Wingless Crows.
[KIYOKO]
But this year.... We're
going to make it back.
I see... Amazing...
These guys are so talented!
[KIYOKO]
Huh?
[DAICHI]
Time out!
[TAKEDA]
So... you'll be glad to know we
just got a last‐minute request
[TAKEDA]
for a practice match tomorrow
against Ougi West High School.
[TAKEDA]
I said yes. They were impressed
with our performance at the
Inter‐High prelims.
(TADASHI, DAICHI, KOSHI,
& SHOYO excited)
It's important for us to
remember the disappointment
of losing to Seijoh...
But still...
[KEISHIN]
There's no need to dwell on that
feeling right now. Just focus on
winning!
(KURASUNO rejoicing)
[KEISHIN] Settle down!
[SHOYO]
Does Ougi West have a good
volleyball team?
[TOBIO]
Doesn't matter,
we'll bring 'em down.
[RYUNOSUKE]
They won't even know
what hit 'em!
(HITOKA anxious breathing)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Ever since that new girl
got here, Kiyoko's been
way different.
[YU]
Maybe she's quiet with us
because we're all guys!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Omigod, Noya, like, let's work
on our feminine sides!
[YU]
Like, okay girlfriend!
[KIYOKO]
(groaning) Next Haikyu!!
"Villager B"