Leave this one to MEEEEE!
All....
...RIGHT!
(loud cheering)
They WOOOOON!
Whoa. I don't think I've
ever seen a play like that.
Incredible. I got
goosebumps...
Well done!
Let's line up!
Right!
This puts us even at 1 and 1.
So don't go getting too cocky.
You should talk.
(whistle)
Thank you for
the game!
Their hard work paid off.
Yeah!
[Daichi]:
That guy... It seemed like
he could predict exactly
where Hinata was aiming.
If the blockers hadn't changed
the ball's trajectory...
he might have been
able to recover it.
Great game, guys! Both squads
have a lot to be proud of!
Gentlemen, no matter what I say,
it will not change the outcome.
[Irihata]:
And the sting of defeat
is not quickly healed.
You are sure to regret
some choices you made.
But still, let me say this;
And never forget it.
All of you fought well.
[Toru]:
Let's go thank everyone
who came to support us.
[Hajime]:
I couldn't do it...
I couldn't land the last shot.
How can I call
myself the ace?!
Thank you all
for coming!
(applause)
Thank you all for coming!
Hey, get over
here, guys!
All right!
[Ryunosuke]:
Get off! Geez...
Our bad!
What's that, you
stupid little freaks!
[Tobio]:
Hinata! You dumbass!
Nothing about this is funny!
We can never forget this moment,
boys. Just look at them.
We'll pay them back for this.
Yeah!
Oh! They said
our bus is here.
Fine...
[Hajime]:
Kageyama!
It's not going to be
the same next time.
You got that?
Right....
[Ryunosuke]:
I still can't get over
how close it was!
[Saeko]:
HEEEEY!
You guys are
total badasses!
So cool!
Big Sis!
Ryu! I can't believe you dug
that out! You looked so awesome!
Thanks... but can ya maybe
dial it back a bit for me?
It's embarrassing to have
you as my biggest fan.
Don't get all
bashful ya dummy!
[Ryunosuke]:
Seriously,
stop that Saeko!
Those were great
serves, Tadashi!
Thank you very much!
That last shot!
OhmyGod that last spike
was so freakin' awesome!
Thank you!
Thank you.
The last play, when I saw
Seijoh's triple block coming...
I started to remember
how it went last time....
I gotta say, Coach,
it gave me the chills.
[Keishin]:
He was in a predicament like
Asahi versus the Iron Wall.
Kageyama probably thought about
all the possible outcomes,
and felt that Hinata had the
best chance to get it done.
Or maybe... it might have
just been his pure instinct.
I cannot believe you got around
such a high block Hinata!
It's just... the Great King
reacted to the shot.
I was worried
he might dig it up.
[Shoyo]:
I mean, Oikawa was really
amazing out there...
When the bus comes,
can you load it up for me?
I'll go and fetch the guys
who haven't made it yet.
Yep!
I've got words
for you, Oikawa.
In the heat of the moment,
you get lost.
The outcome of your
performance reflected that.
There were places where you
could have utilized your skills
a lot more.
[Ushiwaka]:
It's a real shame...
but you have only your
worthless pride to blame.
Guess you think I should
have chosen differently...
and gone to Shiratorizawa
instead of going to Aoba‐Johsai.
I'm sorry, but there
aren't any teams
that are
guaranteed success.
Perhaps, but you
would have to agree...
we have a clear advantage...
in strength, skill,
and experience.
Well, well, still have an
amusing amount of confidence,
don't you?
What was it you said
about "worthless pride"?
I can't recall.
Listen up, Ushiwaka...
I've never thought that
my choice was a mistake.
And, my volleyball career
is just getting started.
[Toru]:
This "worthless pride"
you speak of...
Make sure you never forget it.
Oh, and one more thing...
[Toru]:
If you spend too much time
worrying about me,
then you're going to get
taken from a direction
you weren't
expecting.
What do you mean by that?
My old friend may be
a bit of an oaf...
[Toru]:
but he's still
totally no comparison
to me or my
skill level...
But now that he's
no longer alone,
he's a much stronger player.
Even a great white eagle can
be bested by a murder of crows.
[Ryunosuke]:
Hey! What are
you dorks doin'?
Hurry up and load up
all our gear onto the bus!
Uhh guys, what's goin' on?
If the soil is barren,
it'll never bear any fruit.
I'll show him what
we're made of...
[Shoyo]:
from our little
concrete parking lot!
Oh, wait up!
They're knocked out.
Just like you'd expect.
[Keishin]:
Can't blame 'em.
They had two matches
against formidable opponents.
Gonna have to thank you
properly, y'know.
Wha‐what's this
all of a sudden?
The team would
have been lost
without your persistence
and drive.
[Keishin]:
Because of your commitment
to rebuilding our affiliation
with our old rivals,
we were able to have
some great practice matches.
And against some real
powerhouse schools at that.
They only get so far
doing drills and laps.
You need a real opponent.
The fact that we renewed
our relationship with Nekoma
is invaluable. I don't
even think these guys
realize it yet...
or you for that matter.
You've accomplished something
truly amazing, Specs.
No way! Negatory!
Nu‐uh! No!
After we win tomorrow,
then you can shower me
in praise all you want.
That's a deal.
Now grab your stuff
and head to the gym!
Meeting started 2 minutes ago.
Yessir.
So gross. You were
drooling all over yourself.
You are disgusting.
Hey, my drool
isn't disgusting!
[Yui]:
Oh! They're back!
Congrats on making
it to the finals!
Hey, Michimiya!
How did you find out?
There was a schoolwide
broadcast earlier.
That's so amazing!
You guys beat Seijoh to go
all the way to the finals!
That's so... that's
just so amazing!
Almost as amazing
as Yui's vocabulary...
[Yui]:
Wait! Your face! That bruise!
Right.... it happened
earlier today.
[Daichi]:
It looks worse
than it is. I'm fine.
Um... Good to hear.
[Male Student]:
Alright! Way to bring
it home, Karasuno Crows!
You guys're badass!
Congratulations!
Hinata, Kageyama!
Well done, guys!
Thanks Miss Ono!
Thank you ma'am!
We got your back
all the way to the end!
You guys better win, okay?!
[Female Student]:
Do your best!
Oh man... did they all
stay after school for us?
Oh! The news report
should be starting soon!
Hello and Good evening.
[All]:
Good evening!
[Female Anchor]:
Today, at the Sendai City
Gymnasium in Tomizawa,
the quarterfinal and
semifinal matches were held
for the Miyagi Prefecture.
This tournament decides who will
represent each prefecture
in the Spring High School
Volleyball Championship
or the Spring Nations.
In the first match, underdog
Karasuno High School defeated
the powerhouse Aoba‐Johsai
to advance to the finals.
This upset shook things up!
As Seijoh was heavily coming in
to the tournament.
[Male Anchor]:
Indeed. It was
a very balanced team
headed by Captain Toru Oikawa.
I must say it's a real shame
that we won't see them
in the finals.
Geez, they could show us a bit
more! We were won, after all!
No kidding!
No fair. Why are they
only showing Seijoh?!
Isn't that how
it always is...?
Sorry, guys, we gotta win a few
more to get the headlines.
Now on to the second
semifinal match.
The squad everyone has their
eye on, took care of business
and also advanced
to the finals.
[Female Anchor]:
Of course, that's
Shiratorizawa Academy.
Okay, now here comes
They are undefeated and hold
three consecutive wins
so far in this tournament.
They were lead by their Ace,
Ushijima Wakatoshi
who was recently chosen to be on
the national 19‐and‐under team.
They cruise to
a pretty safe win,
taking the match
in straight sets.
[Male Anchor]:
Yes. They finally have
a roster where they can aim
for the long‐cherished desire
for a national championship.
In fact, it may be safe to
assume that we could see
a sweep this year.
[Female Anchor]:
How long will Karasuno stay
competitive against
Shiratorizawa
overwhelming talent?
Definitely something
to watch out for.
The finals will be broadcast
live on this channel
starting tomorrow
morning at 11:00 AM.
This will decide the winner
of the Miyagi Prefecture,
you do NOT want to miss it!
Alright guys. Tomorrow we face
Shiratorizawa Academy.
[Keishin]:
Not to freak you out, but in the
three years since Oikawa joined
Aoba‐Johsai they have never been
able to beat Shiratorizawa.
That's right. Not a single win.
That's why they're called...
"The Absolute Champions."
Their team consists of top‐tier
guys from our prefecture,
and Ushijima is just the start.
They're known as the best around
for a reason.
Shiratorizawa is even stronger
than you might think.
And I'm sure you realize nobody
believes we can win this.
[Keishin]:
Huh? Let it out, Ginger.
None of that matters, Coach!
That's what
I think anyway!
Hey! Don't mouth off
to him like that!
Oh, woah! No! That's
not how I meant it.
It's cool. Floor
is yours, kid
S‐sure!
I'm talking about the fact that
no one thinks we can win!
That didn't
matter last match!
So what others
expect of us,
doesn't mean
anything in the end!
So, once again we will
be the underdogs.
Let's show 'em all
one stunning upset!
Yeah!
You guys have been called...
"The Wingless Crows."
You should all be proud
that not a single person
can call you guys
that anymore.
[Takeda]:
Now the crows are
flying the high skies
proudly with the wind
beneath their wings.
And I'm sure that
you guys can go anywhere!
Higher than anyone,
and farther than anyone!
All right, everybody,
the time has finally come!
Let's win again tomorrow
and head to the
national championships!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yessir!
[Keishin]:
All right! Hurry up
and get your butts home!
Hit those pillows
hard and rest up!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yessir!
[Keishin]:
All right,
get outta here!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yessir...!
[Shoyo]:
Kageyama.
Wait. Will you
set for me?
Huh? Th‐they can't
be... They are!
Oh, hey, Yachi!
Can throw us a few?
But You already played
two matches today.
You should really
go get some rest!
But if I
went home now,
I'd still be super wired!
Pretty Please!
Please help us!
Uh...
I'm ready!
Here!
Yes!
Let's do it again!
Sure.
(Shoyo spiking)
Again, Kageyama!
[Tobio]:
Sure.
[Shoyo]:
What's wrong, Yachi?
Ah, I'm sorry!
It's just... I
remembered something...
What's that?
The last time I was helping you
guys with practice like this,
you two ended up
in that huge fight.
Wait, did she?
What?! You don't remember?!
Hinata you charged in
grabbed onto Kagayama!
And then he shoved you on the
ground! I was really worried!
And I was scared to would
kill each other, you know?!
Uh...
Yeah, uh...
We're sorry...
Oh, no, no! I didn't
mean it that way.
When I was watching the matches
today, I got to thinking...
[Yachi]:
If I hadn't become the manager,
then I would've missed out
on so much! I had no idea
what I was getting into!
There's so much passion, and
joy, and panic, and everything!
And when you came out on top,
it was just overwhelming!
I got the chance to see
how hard everyone worked
to grow and master
their position.
And then see it all
come together.
I never would have gotten to
experience something like that
without you guys!
And so, thank you!
No! We should
thank you!
You actually helped
us out ton!
You were at all
of our practices.
I mean, without her there,
we might not have been able
to master the new
fast attack, right?
Really? Even me, Villager B,
was of use to you?
Yes! Of course! We had the
best Villager B in the world!
Wait, was uh...
that a compliment?
Of course it was! And if
you're thankful for her help,
you should make
sure she knows!
Right... Thanks.
What?! Is that really
all you have to say?
Even after everything
she's done for us?
Shut up, Hinata, you moron!
I do appreciate her, okay?!
Now, now, i‐it's okay...
What's this about?
[Yachi]:
Uh... Kiyoko!
You know, getting proper
rest is very important...
It is essential to preparing
for your next match.
I‐I'm sorry! Come on,
we're done now! Let's clean up!
Hurry, hurry!
Fiiiine...
[Tobio]:
It's your fault that
we got into trouble, you know.
[Shoyo]:
Uh, excuse ME, you
wanted to practice, too!
Sorry, they wanted to practice
so I was keeping them company.
No it's fine, you practiced
with them... thank you for that.
Sure!
[Kiyoko]:
Yachi, it's
already dark out,
would you like to walk
to the bus stop together?
[Yachi]:
Yes, please!
[Kiyoko]:
And you two... make sure
after you're done
cleaning up.
[Shoyo/Tobio]:
Yes ma'am!
[Shoyo]:
Y'know what, Kageyama?
I wonder if the Tiny Giant
felt this way...
on the night
before the finals?
I am pretty nervous, but...
I'm super excited, too!
Tomorrow... we win.
Yeah!
But man, who'd guess that
Karasuno would make it
all the way to the finals?
And defeat Seijoh, too?
It's like a revival of
their old veteran team...
Well, speak
of the devil...
Ushiwaka.
H‐hey!
Tobio Kageyama...
and Shoyo Hinata .
We made it
to the finals.
No matter what you think of us,
we are going to defeat you...
and go to
the nationals!
I'm looking forward to it.
See you on the court.
I wanna play him right now!
All right! Next stop,
Spring Nationals!
Yeah!