[Terushima]:
It's up! Nice!
It's a feint!
[Terushima]:
All you!
Again? This time,
I'll make sure to stop it
with something
other than my face!
A back‐court attack!
A break
point, huh?
That scared the
crap out of me;
I totally thought
you were gonna hit it!
His teammates weren't
expecting it either.
Yeah, I know, but he
hit it pretty calmly.
Better be on our toes...
gotta watch him.
Johzenji's not bad...
They've been doing well
since the timeout.
Yeah...
They're making sure to
observe their opponents.
[Keishin]:
They're planning ahead.
This could be trouble.
[Misaki]:
I'm not saying you
guys need to take
it slow and steady.
You guys may
look like idiots,
but you're not
really idiots, right?
Right!
I know it's fun. But having
a good time doesn't mean
you shouldn't
be thinking.
[Futamata]:
Left, left!
[Tsuchiyu]:
Nice!
[Bobata]:
It's up! Last hit!
[Keishin]:
If it's too close to call
whether or not they'll make
a shot, don't block it,
just pull back.
That was great!
If you can stop it,
I have no complaints!
Yeah, being able to make
the moves you want to make,
and having the
skill to execute,
is when you can
truly play freely.
And as you'd might expect, the
further you go, the more players
Have both of
those abilities.
It's all you,
Tsukishima!
[Futamata]:
Here he comes,
Number 10!
Hey... listen up!
Johzenji hasn't been able to
stop Hinata's quick attacks
yet... Take it
right here, you guys.
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice receive!
Number 10 jumped out!
Here it comes.
Hey... wait a sec...
[Spectator 1]:
Johzenji's blockers are
leaving Number 10 open?!
I guess we don't have
much of a choice.
If we can't block it...
we're better off
sending everyone
to receive.
Whoa, they actually
made that work!
After they left
Number 10 all alone,
they were able
to counterattack!
Yeah, that was sick!
I know it's fun.
But having a good time doesn't
mean you shouldn't be thinking.
I sure do love it when the
simulations in my head play out
in real life!
It's workin' now!
[Takinoue]:
A two‐point game, huh...?
Aoba‐Johsai went with
this kind of counterattack
against us, too...
Hinata's spikes are
still pretty light.
[Shoyo]:
I hate being blocked, but why
is it that I get even more
pissed off when the
blockers just ignore me?!
Kageyama! I got a plan!
I want the next one...
[Terushima]:
Let's get one more!
Serve's up!
Got it!
[Shoyo]:
I can see it.
You serious?!
Nice kill!
They're quite a bit
different than they were
back in the
Seijoh match.
[Ryunosuke]:
Hinata! Give 'em
another one!
A received that
from so close!
If we can touch it...
Then it's all ours!
Let's go!
If we're hitting the ball
to an open area on the court,
they're going for a one‐touch
instead of a receive.
It's mine next time!
Hinata, you know you haven't
used it yet today, right?
You know, your
new special attack.
[Daichi]:
Nice receive!
[Ryunosuke]:
Do it, Hinata!
Lets goooo!
[Hitoka]:
Match point!
[Terushima]:
Alright, here we go fellas.
It's time to get serious.
[Tsuchiyu]:
Got it!
A‐another synchronized
attack?!
[Misaki]:
They're not considering the
possibility of failure at all.
All they think about...
is the joy of success.
Heads up, you guys!
Now they're changing it up!
YEAH!
Oh, yeah!
They just made it
to the top 8!
We got as far
as we could...
[Terushima]:
This is it?!
Dammit... and I was finally just
starting to get into it!
He looks like he could
still keep going, doesn't he?
Freakin' me out.
[Anabara]:
You did a great job.
I didn't see
it at first, but...
you knew them
far better than I did.
It's because of you they
didn't completely collapse.
[Anabara]:
I want to
thank you for that.
It's nothing...
[Team Johzenji/ Team Karasuno]:
Thank you for the game!
So it's not just my
imagination, is it?
[Futakuchi]:
I'd say their quick attack
has definitely evolved.
Alright then, Aone, we'll go on
ahead... Don't be too long.
Okay, boys...
I know you can get
excited out there...
but don't get
out of control.
[Anabara]:
The only reason you got
as far as you did, is because
Misaki was here to
smack you in the tushies.
Anyway, I'm proud of you.
They're all yours.
U‐um... okay so...
[Misaki]:
You guys, make sure you don't
give Runa too much trouble.
She's just a first‐year, y'know.
I'll still be keeping
an eye you.
And... that more serious play
style you were just doing...
Well... um..
I think it's a good thing.
Let's go guys. The next
team's already here.
[Terushima]:
Uh... thank you...
for everything!
You guys did it!
Woo!
Uh, woooo?!
Okay, you guys... she
doesn't have enough hands
for all your high fiving.
Uh... right...
Woo!
Tomorrow, I
will stop you.
I'm beating you!
Shut up!
Was he waiting here just
to tell Hinata that...?
(whistle blowing)
[Shoyo]:
Is the game on
court B over?
[Tobio]:
If so, the winner is
our next opponent.
[Masayoshi]:
Way to go, way to go, Ta‐ke‐ru!
Way to go, way to go, Takeru!
Way to go, yeaah!
YEAAAAAH!
His whole family is here
to cheer him on...
Before the prelims, that's
the school Coach was saying
to be careful of.
So if we wanna play
Date Tech...
we gotta get
through THEM first!
[Takeda]:
Everyone! You've all worked
VERY hard here on day one!
[Team Karasuno]:
Thank you!
Wakutani South,
our next opponent,
is not like any other team
we've played before.
They have their
third‐years like us.
They're an extremely
polished team.
[Keishin]:
They've got Nekoma's defense and
tenacity, and more experience.
Even if your attacks
aren't landing at first,
don't get
frustrated, alright?
Yes, I'm looking at you two,
you little psycho meat‐heads.
It'll be just fine...
We've got their backs, okay?
[Daichi/Yu]:
We're counting on you guys!
[Keishin]:
Well, look at that... he makes
it sound better when he says it.
Alright...
Our job is to
survive tomorrow.
[Daichi]:
Karasuno, fight!
[Team Karasuno]:
Fiiight!
Gooo... Fiiiight... Ta‐ke‐ru!
Go Go, Takeru!
Win, win, Takeru! YEAHHHHH!
There's more today than
yesterday. His whole family!
So is it just me,
or do you seem jealous?
Come on, you guys,
concentrate!
Uh, hey Coach...
is something wrong?
We need to get ourselves
more pumped up...
Maybe just it's my coach's
intuition talkin'...
But these Wakutani
South guys...
[Keishin]:
They might be a
tough match for us.
[Referee]:
Captains.
Let's have a good game.
We won't let
our guard down.
That's flattering.
[Shimada]:
Hey.
Oh, Shimada. Hello there!
Are you by yourself?
Yeah, Takinoue
has work today.
But he did say he might be able
to swing by in the afternoon,
[Saeko]:
Man, I am freaking
out here!
Stuff like this really
gets my panties in a twist!
H‐hello!
She looks...
kinda... familiar
So I guess you two have been
taking care of my little Ryu
for me... I'm Saeko,
his big sister.
Tanaka's big sister!
Guess I see it...
Ryu! Tanaka! Yoo‐hoo!
Oh? Big Sister!
[Saeko]:
I love you,
you big dummy!
I'm here to make sure you
don't screw this up!
[Team WakuNan/Team Karasuno]:
Let's have a good game!
Take 'em down!
Now, Day two. You gotta
take care of business!
Bring it on!
[Nakashima]:
Give it a good serve!
Got it!
All right, start off
with a quick attack
[Shimada]:
and give 'em
a good scare!
Oh, yeah!
Nice kill, Hinata!
What the hell
was that just now?!
A quick attack, huh?
Was that a fluke?
[Nakashima]:
All right, listen up!
We'll cut the next one quick!
Yeah!
Y‐yeah!
Y'see that?
WakuNan doesn't seem surprised
by that quick attack...
[Nakashima]:
Nobody calls the
current Karasuno
"The Clipped Crows" anymore.
The most surprising team
in the entire prefecture...
We're super lucky to be able
to go against them!
Looks like they got together
before the game
and figured out
how to work against Hinata.
They're not showing
any signs of being flustered.
[Takeda]:
They're not having
a bad matchup against us...
they're the type of team that we
struggle against, aren't they?
Yeah. Based on how things
have been so far,
we've always dealt better with
teams that aggressively attack
with their prominent weapons.
But team that keeps
its pace remains silent
and monitors what we do
That's the team we're
gonna struggle against.
They can cause us fits.
Seijoh and Nekoma are
perfect examples of that.
I see...
So we're up against a team
that has prepared themselves
for our quick attacks.
Now, what are we gonna do?
Hey, Hinata, you do know
a powerhouse school
may be keeping an eye
on you don'cha?
It's true... they're studying
you and all your moves, too.
[Daichi (echoing)]:
You and all your moves, too...
[Hinata]:
A powerhouse is studying ME!
[Daichi]:
Man, he's totally
upstaging us!
It doesn't matter, 'cause
I'm going to surpass myself!
Hey, if you keep on
only watching Hinata,
you're askin' for it!
Just like a
captain should,
he knows what buttons to push to
get his players all revved up.
[Asahi]:
Serve it up, Kageyama!
That felt good!
So strong!
[Kawatabi]:
Nice receive!
Check it out, man!
Pineapple‐head is
running around from behind!
Got it!
Aw, yeah!
Ya like that, don'cha?!
Wow! Did you see how
far that guy just ran?!
A delayed attack...
So that's WakuNan's weapon:
It's their combination play.
I mean, their
average height
isn't really all
that impressive.
Well, this shows
why they're always
at the top of
the prefecture
Yeah. But that's not the
only thing WakuNan is about.
Huh?
Don't react to each and
every thing the spikers do!
Go after
the ball!
I‐I know that...
in my head!
The brain and the body
do not always agree...
I know all about it.
[Yu]:
Nice receive!
It's up! Cover me!
Takeru! Last shot!
We're gonna stop this!
Ready... now!
[Spectator 1]:
A deflection!
[Team WakuNan]:
Alright!
[Shoyo]:
He just aimed at the
very edge of my hand!
So, Takeru's aerial
techniques are pretty dangerous.
Almost as troublesome as
their combination play...
Takeru Nakashima...
[Keishin]:
Right now, in our prefecture,
his play‐style may be the most
similar we've ever seen to
that of the "Tiny Giant."
This kid is somethin' else...
Take it to 'em, Takeru!
Alright!
[Spectator 2]:
Nakashima again!
He's good!
They've been keeping pace
with us the whole time.
We've stayed
neck‐and‐neck.
Neither team has been able
to pull away from the other!
Takeru has a well‐trained
eye on the court...
He and Hinata both
have a level of vision
that can make something
out of nothing.
Yeah.
Now I'm not sure just how much
control this Takeru kid has.
But unlike
our little red,
who fine‐tunes where
to aim every shot,
I think he's being
creative with the angles.
[Keishin]:
I think he's changing the
angles from spike to spike.
Like, making an angle to hit
the hands of the blocker,
creating deflections
and rebound arcs.
Tsukishima, it's
all over your face.
Well... as a blocker,
[Kei]:
it's only natural to be
sick of spikers like that.
Let's get one, now!
You can do it!
That was the middle
of his chest!
Even if he knew where it
was going, that was fast!
Karasuno's Number 10
isn't gonna lose
against WakuNan's
Number 1...
Dammit!
You were almost able
to pick that one up!
You'll get the next one.
Don't worry about it.
You got this!
It's a piece of cake!
Half of that was JUST to
taunt you. Don't fall for it!
What the‐
Well... I see
what they're doing.
WakuNan has committed
one of their blockers
to focus solely
on Hinata for now,
but I guess they're choosing
not to chase him too much.
They've decided
to deal with Hinata
using a tall
middle blocker...
[Keishin]:
They choose to narrow the shot
line instead of stopping it
so it's easier
to receive.
They've come to realize
they can't shut him down.
They know that would be
impossible. On the other hand,
they're not givin' him the
run of the court, either.
However...
Look, I know we're in the middle
of a spectacle, here.
It's the next generation
of Tiny Giants.
But please, don't forget about
our tried and true method.
Right.
I think this
dude's after my job.
[Daichi]:
Just as I thought. Their
middle blocker is onto Hinata,
and the other two will
deal with all other spikers.
But... if you're going
to stop our ace...
You have to have
yourself an "Iron Wall"!
Is that so, huh?
Yeah!
Go, Asahi!
You crushed it!
Yeah, thanks...
All right, everything
is fine. Everyone is calm.
Let's keep
going at it...!
Ugh, this is crap...
Okay, okay, now,
let's cut one down!
[Nakashima]:
Number 3, Number 3!
It looks like Karasuno
is attacking more
from the left side.
That guy with the beard,
he can kill it!
Oh, there's finally
a two‐point lead.
Looks like this match might
be going somewhere after all.
All right, this is our chance!
Build up some momentum!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yessir!
I hate these guys...
Hey, Tabi.
What?!
Over there, on the right edge,
there's a really cute girl
in the
third row.
What? Seriously?!
Where is she?! Whooooaaaa!
I want the ball!
Yeah, yeah...
Send it to me, I'm gonna kill
the crap out of it!
Well played, Takeru. You know
his personality all too well.
TAKERU!
From way back, I've survived
living in the Jurassic Park
of free spirits.
I'm gonna go
play outside!
[Takeru]:
If my house is Jurassic Park...
...this is still a zoo at best!
Don't underestimate
the hardships
of the second‐born son!
Tenacious WakuNan! Watch out...
our best is yet to come!
Yeah!
Their captain's
a pretty good fit.
He creates a solid
foundation for them.
Yeah, if the last match was
a competition of style...
[Keishin]:
...this is a collision
of captains.
[Nakashima]:
Number 11, Number 11!
Whoa, they dug
it up again!
They both connect with
the ball really well...
Gah, they dug it up again!
I'm having a hard time
just watching...
This is the longest rally
we've had today...
[Shimada]:
Whoever gets this
point will gain the momentum!
Keep it up! Keep it goin'!
Make sure to get this one!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yessir!
Takeru, comin' your way!
[Kawatabi]:
Whoa! Triple block!
Another deflection...!
(rallying cheers)
Uh... what the‐?
Uhh... Daichi?
[Shoyo]:
I wish MY family
would come to the games!
[Kei]:
I'd never want
anything like that.
[Ryunosuke]:
I understand EXACTLY
how Tsukishima feels.
[Kei]:
What? I agree
with Tanaka...?
Not sure how I
feel about that.
Next episode of Haikyu!!
"The Fight of the Spineless"