[KIYOKO]
Oh hello there, Yachi...
Are you done changing?
(HITOKA startled)
[KIYOKO] If you wait a second, I
can walk you home... I need to
change too.
[HITOKA]
Oh no, I'm fine! Actually,
I'm glad to walk YOU home
if that would be more
convenient for you!
[KIYOKO]
Oh don't be silly.
[HITOKA]
(speechless) Huh?
[KEISHIN]
Alright Specs, I give up.
What is with the face?
[TAKEDA]
Oh, it's nothing
that serious, really.
It's just that the bus we
were going to borrow for
the Tokyo trip has been
claimed by another club...
So it looks like we'll have to
come up with an alternate here
at the last minute.
This trip keeps getting
more expensive... I'm not
sure what we should do.
[KEISHIN]
Well... I could try asking
for donations from some of
the alumni...
[KEISHIN]
But budgeting issues are just
gonna keep popping up.
[TAKEDA]
(sigh) I know I'm asking
a lot; I'll check with
some other people.
Plus... if worse comes to
worst... I've got some savings.
[KEISHIN]
Nononono, I can't let you do
that! You gotta send your future
kids to college!
[SHOYO] YACHIIIIIIIII!
(HITOKA startled)
[SHOYO]
Are you gonna be our
new team manager?
[HITOKA]
Oh, um...
[SHOYO] Are ya?!
(HITOKA nervous)
[RYUNOSUKE & YU]
Hey, first‐year chick!
Listen up!
Here's the thing... You
have no choice but to
join the Volleyball Club.
[HITOKA] Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE] Cause now that
you're around, Kiyoko's
talking to us a lot more.
[DAICHI]
That's not how you
recruit her, idiots!
[KOSHI]
I'm so sorry, they can't help
how stupid they are.
[HITOKA] O‐Oh no, they're fine!
Actually... I'm really happy...
[SHOYO] Huh?
[HITOKA]
You see, this is the first time
that anybody's wanted me
specifically...
Up until now, I've just sort of
fallen into whatever group I was
a part of...
[HITOKA]
Even in school plays I'm usually
just a face in the crowd.
Like, "Villager B" or
a tree or something.
[BOTH]
A tree?
[HITOKA]
And now... even though I'm
nothing but some random girl
and I don't know the first
thing about volleyball
or managing a team, somehow I
was lucky enough for Kiyoko to
ask me to join the club anyway.
[HITOKA]
But still, I doubt I can be of
any help to you‐ Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE]
I know just how you feel.
If Kiyoko said to me:
[KIYOKO]
"Why don't you come over here so
I can take all of your money."
[RYUNOSUKE]
You bet your sweet ass
I would go with her.
[YU] Yeah, that's what
I'm talkin' about!
[HITOKA] That's...
not what I meant...
[SHOYO]
What a cool thing to say!
[ASAHI]
I bet I know what that
conversation's about.
[SHOYO] Huh? That's
right, I forgot!
[HITOKA] Oh?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh? (gawk)
[YU]
Sweet! We'll see ya in Tokyo,
Nekomaaaa! (excited yelling)
[RYUNOSUKE]
(riled up laughing) You punks
are goin' down!
(SHOYO excited yelling)
[MADOKA]
Honey? Mommy's got another work
meeting to attend this evening,
so expect me to be home
a little late tonight.
[HITOKA]
'Kay... Be careful out there,
Mom.
[MADOKA]
Please have the house cleaned
up before I get back.
[HITOKA]
Uh‐huh!
[MADOKA]
Oh? What's this?
[HITOKA]
Hmm?
Oh! I meant to tell you...
I've been invited to be
a manager of the boys'
volleyball team at school.
[MADOKA]
Really?
(doorbell ringing)
[MADOKA] Just a second,
I'll be right down.
[EMPLOYEE] All right.
[MADOKA]
Karasuno's volleyball team's
been to nationals before,
haven't they?
They must be pretty good.
[HITOKA]
Yeah!
They've really been
making a comeback recently!
[EMPLOYEE]
The taxi just
pulled up outside.
[MADOKA] What do you
know about volleyball?
(EMPLOYEE & HITOKA surprised)
[HITOKA]
N‐not much, but I'm
gonna study up so‐
[MADOKA]
(sigh) That's all
well and good...
but just make sure you
do your best, I know that
everyone on the team will.
[MADOKA]
You don't want to be the lazy
one do you?
(HITOKA surprised,
into sad sigh)
(EMPLOYEE frustrated sigh)
[MADOKA] You'll have to make
breakfast tomorrow, okay?
[HITOKA]
Uh, yes ma'am.
[EMPLOYEE]
Um hey... Don't you think you
were a little harsh with her?
I mean, she IS your daughter.
[MADOKA]
What? I wasn't 'harsh' with her!
[EMPLOYEE]
I've seen how pessimistic she
can be, and honestly I think
you're the main reason why.
[MADOKA]
Well, excuse me for wanting my
child to be a strong person!
[MADOKA]
If she loses it over one small
criticism like that...
[MADOKA]
...then I can only imagine what
the real world will do to her.
(HITOKA moping)
(school bell ringing)
[KIYOKO] Is something
bothering you?
(HITOKA startled)
[KIYOKO]
For what it's worth...
I used to play sports,
but I never knew anything about
volleyball or what it takes to
be the manager of a whole team.
[HITOKA]
Huh?
[KIYOKO]
But the thing is...
you don't always know you have
a passion for something
before you start doing it.
[KIYOKO]
You don't need to have strong
feelings about it
or be on some kind of
mission from day one.
[KIYOKO]
Sometimes, the things you fall
into by chance turn out to be
the most important ones of all.
[KIYOKO]
As long as you go into it with
a tiny bit of wonder... you're
all set.
[KEISHIN] Hinata, Tsukishima!
[SHOYO] Sir!
[KEI] Yeah?
[KEISHIN] Since both of
you are middle blockers,
[KOSHI] The floor's gotten all
wet...
[KEISHIN]
I want you to get to the point
where you can use
your block as a weapon.
[KEISHIN]
When I'm through with you two,
you'll even be able to
block Ushiwaka.
[KEISHIN]
Be sure to keep that in mind
during the practice match today,
you got that?
[SHOYO] Right!
[KEI] Sure.
[KEI]
(internal) Yeah right,
we'll never block that guy.
[KEISHIN]
Okay then... back to work!
[SHOYO]
Okay!
[KEISHIN]
(pensive) Okay
seriously, dude...
Are they gonna pass
these exams or what?
[TAKEDA]
Uhh... Well...
[KEISHIN] I'm worried
about these Stooges.
[TAKEDA] Yeah...
[KIYOKO]
The Ougi West High School team
will be arriving at 4:30!
(ALL acknowledges)
[KIYOKO]
Hey, Yachi...
Could you line up
a few folding chairs along
the side of the court?
Maybe... about eight?
[HITOKA]
Uh... okay! I can handle it!
[KIYOKO] Take one at a
time if you need to!
[RYUNOSUKE] Kiyoko's
smiling and I like it.
[YU]
This world of ours is
a beautiful place.
[SHOYO]
Need help?
[HITOKA]
Oh no, I'm fine!
You just go do your thing!
[SHOYO]
Okay! (slap self)
I am not gonna lose this!
[HITOKA]
Hinata... Today's game is just a
practice match, isn't it? It's
not real?
[SHOYO]
Yeah.
[HITOKA]
And uh... you're studying hard
so you can take a trip...
for ANOTHER game
that's not real...
Why sacrifice so much
just for something like that?
Huh? I want to be strong...
so that I can win.
[HITOKA] Oh... That makes sense.
[SHOYO] Hmm?
[HITOKA]
I'm sure you must have a whole
bunch of reasons, huh?
[SHOYO]
Huh? What? Reasons for winning?
[HITOKA]
Uh, I guess so.
[SHOYO]
Does anyone really need a reason
for wanting to win?
(HITOKA nervous gulp)
(practicing drills)
[SHOYO]
Kageyama! Do you think you need
a reason for wanting to win?
[TOBIO]
A reason? That's a pretty dumb
question...
I mean, do you think you need
some kinda reason for eating
food when you're hungry?
[SHOYO]
I dunno... let's see...
(forceful pondering)
[HITOKA, internal]
Oh... so it's the same
as hunger for them.
[HITOKA] Forget it...
That was rhetorical.
[SHOYO & TOBIO] Rhe... tortical?
[KEI]
She said it's rhetorical! A
question that doesn't require an
answer! We just studied that!
(TOBIO & SHOYO stunned)
(speechless)
[OUGI WEST]
Hey, we made it!
[DAICHI]
Huh? Get ready!
[KURASUNO]
Yes sir!
[KIYOKO]
We should probably go line up
with them too.
[HITOKA]
Okay!
Wow... All of those guys are so
tall! (notice)
[SHOYO]
Do you really need a reason for
wanting to win?
[KIYOKO]
You don't need to have strong
feelings about it
or be on some kind of
mission from day one.
[KOSHI]
Step back a bit, Hinata.
[SHOYO]
Oh, okay!
[DAICHI]
Alright guys!
[EVERYONE]
Thank you for the game!
[OUGI WEST ALUM]
So today's game is with
Karasuno, huh? I know them.
[OUGI WEST ALUM]
That's the team they call the
Wingless Crows.
[OUGI WEST GM]
(hearty laugh) From what I
understand, that nickname
doesn't apply to them anymore.
(OUGI WEST ALUM confused)
[OUGI WEST GM] At Inter High
prelims, they went a full set
against Seijoh.
[OUGI WEST GM] The game went to
a deuce and the score climbed
into the 30s.
[OUGI WEST ALUM] Really?!
[OUGI WEST ALUM]
Well, I guess they do have
Nishinoya from Chidori‐yama and
Kageyama from Kitagawa First.
[OUGI WEST GM]
Yeah well. That's not all
they've got.
[OUGI WEST ALUM]
Hm? So there's more?
[OUGI WEST GM]
Number 10... He's a
little spark plug.
Karasuno's lucky to have such
a strong first‐year on their
center line.
[OUGI WEST GM]
Sometimes I get chills just
watching that kid play.
[OUGI WEST GM] They're moving
up. Keep an eye on those guys.
[TAKEDA]
Oh! Thank you so much for
traveling all this way,
gentlemen.
[YU]
Nice rip!
[OUGI WEST 1]
Nice kill!
[KOSHI]
[DAICHI]
It's almost time
to start! Suit up!
[KURASUNO]
Sir!
(HITOKA flustered)
[KOSHI]
Hm?
(laughter) You put it on
backwards!
(HITOKA trembling)
[RYUNOSUKE] Nice one.
[KIYOKO]
Calm down... They're just boys.
[YU]
Hey Asahi!
What's that weird string
you have in your hair?
A shoelace?!
(ASAHI chuckles)
You mean my headband?
Thank you...
Coming from you, that's
a real confidence boost.
[DAICHI] Don't slouch.
[RYUNOSUKE] you changing
up your look, Asahi?
[ASAHI]
Yeah well sorta...
Hmm? Hey uh what's up, Kiyoko?
[KIYOKO]
If you keep tying your hair so
tight, you'll go bald one day.
(ASAHI shocked)
[ASAHI]
So I did this.
(YU laughing)
Guess I better be careful too.
[TADASHI]
Y'know a lot of girls
like bald guys.
[RYUNOSUKE] I'm not
bald, pipsqueak!
[YU] It's awful.
(SHOYO battle cry)
[KEI] Don't you think you should
maybe put your uniform on,
Tanaka?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey, you're not the boss of me!
[HITOKA]
They're so scrappy...
[KIYOKO]
Well of course... They're
crows... So they pick fights.
[RYUNOSUKE] I already
told you, I'm not bald!
[KIYOKO]
But when it's game time, they
(long whistle)
[DAICHI] Over here!
[KEISHIN]
This is the first time we've
played against another team
since the Inter Highs.
[KEISHIN] Remember how that
felt... It was rough, right?
[KURASUNO] Yes sir!
[KEISHIN]
Heh. So make sure it doesn't
happen again today!
[KURASUNO]
Right!
[DAICHI]
Karasunooo... fight!
[KURASUNO]
Fiiight!
[OUGI WEST 1] Let's go!
[OUGI WEST] Yeah!
[TAKEDA]
Has our team played
Ougi West before?
[KIYOKO]
No, this is the first time.
(HITOKA soft gasp)
(long whistle)
(HITOKA gasps)
(pre‐serve hype)
(whistle)
(ALL celebrate)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice, Kageyama!
[TOBIO] Thanks!
[HITOKA] Wait, does
that count as a point?
[DAICHI] Again!
[KIYOKO] Hey Yachi...
that's one for your side.
[HITOKA]
Ah! Right, sorry!
[OUGI WEST 1] Cover, cover!
[YU] Watch Number 8!
[8, internal]
It's just a single block...
[DAICHI]
Good save!
[HITOKA]
He's got great reflexes!
[YU] Kageyama!
[TOBIO] Here!
(whistle)
(KURASUNO cheers)
My arm would rip right
off if I tried that...
[YU] Good one, Captain!
[OUGI WEST ALUM, internal]
They've got excellent control...
[RYUNOSUKE]
Left!
[HITOKA]
Oh wow... You can
hear the impact!
(soft laugh)
Crazy, right? But... if
you get yourself distracted by
those two power attackers...
[HITOKA]
Oh? (surprised)
[KIYOKO]
...you'll lose sight
of our secret weapon.
[SHOYO] I may not be tall.
But I can fly!
(whistle)
[KIYOKO]
If anyone's one step behind...
they'll never catch him.
Okay... Higher!
I can get it higher!
[TOBIO]
You got it!
[HITOKA, internal]
He's not even satisfied
with that?
(whistle)
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[EVERYONE]
Thanks for the game!
[HITOKA]
That was incredible! How do I
describe it uh... like... uh...
[SHOYO] Like FWAAAAH right?!
[HITOKA] Mmhmm! FWAAAAH!
[SHOYO] Then you should join!
[HITOKA] (shock) W‐Well, I'm not
so sure...
[SHOYO] You know
you want to, Yachi!
[KEI] She can't use words
either... She's gonna fit right
[MADOKA]
Just make sure you do your
best. I know that everyone
on the team will.
[MADOKA]
You don't want to be
the lazy one, do you?
[HITOKA]
But... you have such a great
team and I'm just Villager B
who doesn't know
anything about sports...
[HITOKA]
I think I'd just
get in your way‐
[SHOYO]
I played Villager B one time!
But people didn't like it.
(HITOKA question)
[SHOYO] Yeah, 'cause
I tried to stand out more
than the main character.
[TOBIO]
Oh Villager B, huh? Wow. (smirk)
[SHOYO]
Huh?! Are you makin' fun
of me, butthole?!
[SHOYO]
Villager B is cool...
Cooler than anybody on
the whole planet.
(HITOKA concerned)
[TOBIO] Pff, yeah, okay.
Whatever you say.
[SHOYO]
Well, what kind of
roles have YOU played?
[TOBIO]
Uh. Let's see.
The freakin' moon!
[KEI] Wow, so important...
[SHOYO] Oh dude, that's
pretty awesome!
[HITOKA] Villager B is cool...
[TOBIO] Yeah I know.
[HITOKA]
Cooler than anybody
on the whole planet.
(HITOKA determined)
[SHOYO]
You're a lifesaver, Yachi!
Thank you so much for tutoring
us on a Saturday!
[TOBIO]
Yeah, thanks.
[HITOKA]
Sure thing...
Hope you both pass!
[SHOYO]
Sorry for any trouble ma'am!
[MADOKA]
Not at all... I hope my sweetie
did a good job tutoring you.
[SHOYO]
Yeah! Now I KNOW
we'll pass! Maybe!
[HITOKA, internal]
Maybe?
We will not let your
help go to waste!
You're like our muse!
(HITOKA & MADOKA embarrassed)
M'Kay let's see. Muse
is a noun that means...
"an entity that inspires
excellence and achievement in
music or art."
[HITOKA, internal]
Not exactly fitting, but
I'm glad they've been paying
attention...
[MADOKA]
That's great... Best
of luck to you then.
[SHOYO]
Thank you! Heh, I can't wait
for all of us to go to Tokyo
together!
[HITOKA]
Ah! M‐me too uh! (internal) Oh
great... I hadn't mentioned that
part to my mom yet...
[SHOYO]
See ya next week, Yachi!
[HITOKA]
Uh, see ya!
[MADOKA]
What's this about Tokyo?
[HITOKA]
(startled) Oh... W‐Well I was
gonna tell you...
[EMPLOYEE]
I'm really sorry about being
late. I got hung up. Are you
ready to go?
[MADOKA]
Sorry, dear, I've got to get to
my meeting now... Looks like
I'll be home late again tonight.
[HITOKA]
Mm‐hm
(EMPLOYEE staring)
[MADOKA] Now then, shall we?
[EMPLOYEE]
(shocked) Now wait,
hang on a sec!
[EMPLOYEE]
Your daughter's trying to tell
you something over here! What is
it, sweetie?
[HITOKA]
Oh I'm fine, don't worry about
me! You have a good day!
[EMPLOYEE]
Ah... Well, if you're sure...
(HITOKA nod)
[EMPLOYEE]
(annoyed) Workaholic...
[SHOYO]
Yachi's notes are perfect!
She should like major in
note‐taking!
And after she joins the club,
we'll have TWO managers!
We'll be like one of
those big fancy schools!
[TOBIO] Uh‐huh.
[SHOYO] What's with you?
Do you not want her to join?
[TOBIO]
That would be Yachi's decision,
wouldn't it?
[SHOYO]
(grunt) Man, no wonder you don't
have a girlfriend.
[TOBIO]
(pissed) No one asked you!
(seething)
[SHOYO]
Oh! Crap, I must've left my
textbook at Yachi's place...
I better run back and grab it!
Later, Kageyama!
(TOBIO annoyed) (yawn)
[HITOKA] Here.
[SHOYO] Thanks, I really
appreciate it...
That was close; I'm
so glad I remembered!
[HITOKA]
Um... do you have a quick
second? I uh have a question.
[SHOYO]
Huh? Yeah, sure.
Huh? You're afraid to join
for a dumb reason like that?
(HITOKA wounded)
[SHOYO]
I've messed up lots of times!
I hit Kageyama in the head with
the ball...
[SHOYO]
I threw up in Tanaka's lap...
...and knocked the
VP's toupee off!
[SHOYO]
But that doesn't make
me bad at volleyball!
[HITOKA]
Yeah I'm not sure if
that's the same thing.
[SHOYO]
You do WANT to be our manager,
don't you?
(HITOKA startled) (nod)
[SHOYO]
Then that's enough
reason to do it!
[HITOKA]
Hmm... Maybe I... Mmm..
[SHOYO]
Hmm? I know, it's because of
something your mom said to you,
isn't it?
[HITOKA]
Uh, w‐well... How
should I put this...?
[SHOYO]
I get it. We'll just ask her!
(HITOKA startled)
[SHOYO]
She's at the train
station, right?
(HITOKA nervous affirmative)
[HITOKA, internal]
This is just like something out
of a girls' manga!
Except the guy doesn't
usually run so fast!
(panicked running)
(HITOKA stumbles, pant)
Wait a second.
Look, Yachi... you should
make your own choices.
[SHOYO]
If you want to join then join!
[HITOKA]
Whether I join the
volleyball team or not,
if I keep thinking this
way, then nothing will
ever change for me!
[HITOKA]
I have to speak up for myself!
You're right. I'll talk to her.
[HITOKA]
Thanks a lot, Hinata.
[EMPLOYEE]
I'm guessing you didn't figure
out who you are right away
either, did you?
[EMPLOYEE]
Well that's why I think it's
unfair of you to expect that
from your daughter.
[EMPLOYEE]
Why don't you just let the girl
find herself in her own good
time?
(MADOKA annoyed sigh)
[HITOKA]
MOOOOM! (heavy panting)
[MADOKA]
Honey?!
(HITOKA heavy pant)
(exhale) (inhale)
[HITOKA]
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE VILLAGER B!
[MADOKA] Huh?
[EMPLOYEE] Who's Villager B?
[HITOKA]
I'm sure now! I'm gonna be the
volleyball club's team manager!
(PEOPLE gawking)
[MADOKA] Ah... oh...
Good luck, dear.
[HITOKA]
So... home for dinner?
[MADOKA]
Uh. Yeah sure.
[HITOKA] I'll have it ready!
(EMPLOYEE grins)
(HITOKA shocked)
(SHOYO grin)
(HITOKA giggle)
[SHOYO]
All right! Two managers;
now we're in the big leagues!
[HITOKA]
Um... Hinata? There's something
I need you and Kageyama to help
me with...
[SHOYO]
What's up?
[EMPLOYEE]
(shock) Are you crying?!
[MADOKA]
No! Shut up. Get me a tissue.
[HITOKA]
Excuse me! I have a thought.
[TAKEDA]
Whatcha need?
[HITOKA]
Um, I heard we were short
[HITOKA] on funding
for the Tokyo trip.
(TAKEDA surprised)
[HITOKA]
I think I might have a solution.
[YU]
"Harold, he lies below but
can not open fire"...
[YU] "Use this phrase to
memorize the elements"...
[RYUNOSUKE] "Savoir‐faire...
noun... tact in any situation."
[YU]
Well, if you say so...
[MADOKA]
You know that's completely
useless, right?
[HITOKA]
Uh, whaddya mean?
I wouldn't even give that
thing a second glance.
[MADOKA]
So, what are you saying here?
Try to consider who your
audience is.
[MADOKA]
What do you think will make
people stop in their tracks and
read what it has to say?
(HITOKA thinking)
(streetside chatter)
[ANNOUNCER]
He might be surrounded by
players as tall as 6'‐
(SHOYO gasp)
[HITOKA]
Um... Hinata? There's something
I need you and Kageyama to help
me with...
[HITOKA]
What do you call that cool thing
when you jump and hit the
ball... a spike, right?
[HITOKA]
Could I maybe take a photo
of you guys doing that for
a poster?
[HITOKA]
I'll take the picture
when you jump.
[SHOYO]
Okay! Ready, Kageyama?
[TOBIO]
Ready.
[SHOYO]
Wow that's me.
(school bell ringing)
(after test chatter)
[STUDENT A]
Sweet, it's over!
[STUDENT B]
So how do you think you did?
[TAKEDA] M'kay... please pass
your exam papers forward.
[TEACHER] Um, Mr. Takeda?
[TAKEDA] Oh?
[TEACHER]
You've got a call...
Somebody saw a poster.
They wanted to know the best
way to make a donation to the
volleyball club.
(TAKEDA listening) (amazed)
[SHOYO]
Ugh, it's hot...
[KOSHI]
It's just for a second. You too,
Tsukishima... Let's all line up!
This way!
[DAICHI]
Listen... Exams are over...
Which means that Yachi's
officially coming on as a
team manager as of today.
[KIYOKO]
Here y'go.
(HITOKA surprised)
(HITOKA gasps, tremoring)
[DAICHI] Ahem, Readyyyy, go!
[HITOKA] Huh?
[ALL]
Welcome to the Karasuno Boys'
Volleyball Club, Miss Manager!
[HITOKA]
(touched) I promise
I'll do my best!
[DAICHI]
Congrats... Next order of
business is Tokyo! Oh yeah,
but first...
[TEACHER]
Okay... It's time to
hand back the exams guys.
(dramatic groaning)
[TEACHER]
Boo hoo whatever.
First up is, Andoh.
[ANDOH]
Here...
[TEACHER]
Enokida?
[ENOKIDA]
Here.
[TEACHER]
Ohyama?
[HITOKA]
Exam scores are coming in!
[SHOYO]
Oh man...
[HITOKA]
Don't worry! You
worked really hard!
[SHOYO]
Uh‐oh, I don't remember
writing my name...
[HITOKA]
What?! But that's the easiest
part of the test...
[HITOKA]
Next Haikyu!!
"Center Ace".