(SHOYO gasps)
(whistle)
(long whistle)
[SHOYO]
There is an enormous wall in
front of me, blocking my way.
[SHOYO]
I can only wonder what's
on the other side?
[SHOYO]
What does it look like...
from the summit?
[SHOYO]
I'll never be able to see over
that wall. Not on my own...
[SHOYO]
But...
If I have my teammates
by my side...
[SHOYO]
I just might catch
a glimpse of it.
(call‐outs/
practice drills)
(whistle)
(more call‐outs)
(HISASHI grunt)
[DAICHI & RYUNOSUKE]
Nice receive!
[ASAHI]
Here we go...
[RYUNOSUKE]
I don't think so, buddy!
(CHIKARA dejected)
[RYUNOSUKE]
YEAH!
[SHOYO & RYUNOSUKE]
Booyah! (laughter)
(smug grin)
(TOBIO startled)
Uh... booyaaahhh...
[RYUNOSUKE] You'll get there.
(TOBIO startled)
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Serve's up, Cap'n!
[YU]
Right here!
[ASAHI]
Bring it left side!
[KOSHI, internal]
Okay. I'll do the high set
that Asahi likes. Here!
[KEISHIN] (impressed) Yeah...
[YU] Chance ball!
[CHIKARA]
Leave it to me!
[TOBIO]
Here comes another one!
(whistle)
[KEI] You guys will fall
for anything, won't you?
[TOBIO]
Shut your tall four‐eyed mouth!
[KOSHI]
Whoa, easy!
[KIYOKO]
Hm?
(TADASHI exhales)
(whistle)
[KOSHI]
Go for it!
[TADASHI, internal]
(sigh) That could've been
better.
(internal) What's the next move?
(shocked)
(grins)
[SHOYO]
Hey, it's that
awesome move of yours!
Uh‐huh! It's Rolling
Thunder... YEAHHH!
(SHOYO & YU pumped‐up)
[RYUNOSUKE] My bad, I was
totally open that time!
[KEI]
There they go.
Okay! Let's start from the top!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Serve it up, Tadashi!
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hinata!
[ASAHI, internal]
We gotta block this.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Nice cover!
(surprised)
(long whistle)
(TOBIO, SHOYO, RYUNOSUKE,
KAZUHITO, & HISASHI celebrates)
[KEISHIN]
Good! Let's call it a day!
Come on, Coach,
just one more set!
[KEISHIN] Huh?
[TOBIO] Yeah, just one!
(sigh) Look, fellas...
constant practice can only
get you so far...
Captain, can you talk
some sense into these‐
(RYUNOSUKE grins)
[KEISHIN]
...knuckleheads.
[SHOYO, internal]
I want to play more. More!
[SHOYO]
Hey... You're not tired, right?
Toss me some sets!
[TOBIO] Huh? Sure thing!
[DAICHI] Hm?
(RYUNOSUKE confused)
[RYUNOSUKE]
How the hell do you
have so much energy!?
[KEISHIN, internal] They're
getting better every day...
[DAICHI] We gotta wrap it up
guys!
[KEISHIN, internal] but
what we really need
[DAICHI] We still
have to clean the gym!
[KEISHIN] is in‐game experience.
[SHOYO & TOBIO] Yes sir...
[KOSHI] Don't forget you also
need to cool down, okay, guys?
[KEISHIN] We have got to set up
some practice games soon.
[ASAHI] Not so hard! Ah jeez...
[KEISHIN, internal]
But I can't ever get the
Neighborhood Association
together...
[TAKEDA]
Hey! Argh! (pain)
(KEISHIN startled)
(TAKEDA pained)
[SHOYO] What the‐?!
[RYUNOSUKE] Take?!
[KEISHIN]
Are you alright?
[TAKEDA] We're going!
(ALL startled)
[SHOYO]
Going where?
[TOBIO]
Uhh... You've got a nosebleed!
[TAKEDA]
(determined) Tokyo!
(ALL shock)
[SHOYO]
Tokyo, Tokyo?
[TAKEDA]
Mm‐hm!
So that means we...
we get to...?!
(baseball practice)
[SHOYO] We get to play Nekoma?!
(KENMA sneezes)
[KUROO] Hm? (surprised)
[YAMAMOTO] Gross, dude!
[YAKU]
Use a tissue!
(SHOYO excited gasp)
[TOBIO] We've got
a practice match?
[TAKEDA]
Mhm. But this time around
we won't just be playing
against Nekoma.
(SHOYO & TOBIO question)
[TAKEDA]
Nekoma is part of the
Fukurodani Academy Group.
They're an association of
schools from around the
Kanto region,
who hold practice games with
each other all the time.
[TAKEDA]
So, get this... Thanks to
Coach Nekomata... we get
to participate too!
[TAKEDA]
Now we've got some other people
to practice with!
(RYUNOSUKE & YU excited)
Most of the time,
groups like that
are built on long‐standing
relationships
that take years to establish...
So it's hard to get in without
having some kind of special
connection...
We should thank Coach Nekomata
for the favor.
[KEISHIN]
You boys should say thanks to
Takeda too; I'm sure he had to
ask him a million times.
[TAKEDA]
Ah! It was nothing! It helped to
mention the old Coach Ukai‐
[ALL] Thank you!
(TAKEDA startled)
(TAKEDA happy sigh)
[TAKEDA]
In the past few years...
we've sort of drifted apart from
many of the schools we used
to have a good rapport with.
[TAKEDA]
And a lot of the coaches old
Coach Ukai was friends with...
well they've mostly
transferred... or just retired.
So this is our chance!
Now let's make the most of it!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[TOBIO]
And that set of theirs... I will
figure it out this time!
(SHOYO shocked)
[KENMA]
(shiver) Ah..
I think I'm starting
to catch cold...
[KENMA] I feel a chill.
[YAMAMOTO] Huh? Oh no!
Not 'til AFTER the tournament!
[YU]
Let's go make Karasuno
High proud okay!
[YAKU]
(shivering) That's weird; it's
kinda cold out today, huh?
[YAMAMOTO]
Not Yaku too?!
[RYUNOSUKE]
(excited yell)
Hope you're ready, city boys;
you've got it comin' now!
[KEI]
God, you are so stupid.
[TADASHI]
Please stop saying that...
Man, I can't wait to kick
some ass!
I'm on fire!
[KUROO]
Alright settle down, Yamamoto.
[SHOYO]
I'll get through their wall...
I know I will!
(TOBIO determined)
[TAKEDA]
Starting this weekend,
they'll be busy
playing in preliminary matches
for their Inter‐High tournament,
so it won't be
happening right away.
We're invited, but we still have
to get school permission
and the finer details
to work through...
[TAKEDA]
There is a good amount of
red tape to be dealt with. But
we'll talk about that later.
[TAKEDA]
I just wanted to confirm
that you wanted to go.
[DAICHI]
'Course we do!
[ALL]
Let's do this!
(smile) Ah! Oh, yeah!
[TAKEDA]
I've a faculty meeting
to go to, so I'll leave
it to you for now...
You can take care of all
the volleyball stuff, Coach.
[KEISHIN] Sure thing.
[ALL] Thank you!
(TAKEDA startled)
[ASAHI] We're about to
be pretty busy guys.
[DAICHI] Uh‐huh.
[KOSHI]
An away game, huh... It's your
first one, isn't it?
[KIYOKO]
Mm‐hm. So I'll do my best too.
(confused)
(eager)
[KEISHIN]
Let's get this place
cleaned up and go home!
[ALL]
Yes sir!
[SHOYO]
Now that really hit
the spot! (burp)
[STUDENT A]
Dude, who's that girl?
[STUDENT B]
She must be a third‐year.
[GIRL A]
Pretty!
[SHOYO]
What's going on over here?
(shock) It's Kiyoko!
[KIYOKO]
Huh?
[STUDENT A]
Huh?! Hinata,
do you really know
this hottie?!
Wh‐wh‐what are you
doing... uh.. here?
[KIYOKO] Hinata... Hey there.
[SHOYO] Gah!
[KIYOKO]
I was wondering if you happen to
know any first‐years who haven't
joined a club yet.
(confused)
(RYUNOSUKE angry yelling)
(RYUNOSUKE annoyed breath)
[RYUNOSUKE]
"Monthly Volleyball" did an
article about that butt‐weasel
Oikawa!
[SHOYO] Woah!
(TOBIO annoyed sigh)
[KOSHI]
I'm not surprised;
he's really talented...
Well, what does it say?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Uhhh... Let's see here...
"Toru Oikawa's favorite food is
milk bread...
His personal motto is,
'if you're going to hit it,
then hit it 'til it breaks'"?!
(RYUNOSUKE annoyed)
[KOSHI]
That's what the story's about?
(startled)
[YU]
Yeah, yeah, who gives a crap
about corny stuff like that?!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh? Listen to this... Even
though they're about to
graduate,
[RYUNOSUKE]
looks like almost all of
Seijoh's third‐years are
staying on the team...
to try and get revenge
on Shiratorizawa.
[RYUNOSUKE]
That's cute and all, but it's
not enough to beat me!
[SHOYO]
OR MEEEE!
[KOSHI]
Stop! You're gonna tear it up!
Good grief...
Hm? Ushiwaka?
[SHOYO]
(surprised) Japan!?
[DAICHI]
Hey! Come on outside guys;
it's time to run some laps.
[KOSHI]
Daichi... Ushiwaka made
the World Youth Team!
(ASAHI gasp)
[DAICHI] Huh?!
[TADASHI] World Youth Team?
[KEI]
He represents Japan on a team of
the world's best young players.
Only one school can represent
Miyagi Prefecture at the Spring
Nationals...
and if we want that
school to be us...
[DAICHI]
We have to take down
Oikawa and Ushiwaka.
(determined)
(aggressive exhale)
[DAICHI]
Alright then...
Let's get to wooork!
[ALL]
Yeah!
(TAKEDA nervous breathing)
(TAKEDA sighs)
[TAKEDA, internal]
This is reality, Takeda.
Just accept it and
don't lose your head.
[TAKEDA, internal]
These kids have spirit; they'll
be just fine. They can do it if
they try, right?
(TAKEDA uncertain whimper)
[TAKEDA, incoherent mutterings]
They can do it they can do it
they can do it they can do it
they can do it...
[TEACHER]
Huh? Oh my gosh. Are you okay?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Here we are... at Karasuno's
infamous Heartbreak Hill.
Now! I want 10 uphill dashes to
the midpoint! We're going up in
pairs! Ready...
[DAICHI]
Ready...
Hey give it your best,
Tsukishima! Ready...
(clap) (KOSHI & ASAHI running)
[DAICHI]
Ready...
(clap)
(HISASHI & KAZUHITO grunt)
[DAICHI]
Ready...
(determined)
(power yell, into panting)
(stunned)
(RYUNOSUKE, CHIKARA, & TADASHI
exhausted panting)
[CHIKARA]
(pant) You did it, Tsukishima.
(TOBIO & SHOYO power‐yelling)
[CHIKARA] Huh?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey birdbrains, you do know
that's the wrong way, don'tcha?!
[KEI]
I'd say probably not... Oh well.
(TOBIO & SHOYO yelling)
[SHOYO] Huh?
[TOBIO] Hm?
[CROW]
Birdbrains, birdbrains,
birdbrains...
(TOBIO panting)
[SHOYO] Hey wait... what
happened to the rest of the
team, huh? (panting)
[SHOYO]
Aw, you got us lost out here
didn't you, Kageyama?
[TOBIO]
(annoyed) You mean you did!
(SHOYO & TOBIO growling)
[SHOYO]
Huh? Where are we?
Wakano District 3?
[TOBIO]
So we're in Wakano, huh?
Shiratorizawa's not too far.
[SHOYO]
Hey, isn't that the school
where Ushiwaka goes?
[USHIWAKA]
Someone say my name?
[SHOYO]
Whoa, it's you!
You're... that guy!
(TOBIO & SHOYO gawking)
[USHIWAKA]
Yeah, I'd better go. See ya.
[TOBIO]
(gasp) We're from the
Karasuno volleyball team!
And we want to go to your
school and spy on you!
[SHOYO, internal]
Gah! Is he crazy?!
You can't TELL people
you're gonna spy on 'em!
[USHIWAKA]
Karasuno...
You're the team with that
lightning‐fast quick attack.
(TOBIO & SHOYO startled)
[USHIWAKA]
Do what you want. Letting you
watch won't change anything.
[USHIWAKA]
It won't make you any better
and it certainly won't make
our team worse.
[USHIWAKA]
Feel free to come take
a look. I'll even let you
follow me back.
If you can keep up that is.
(TOBIO & SHOYO startled)
[TOBIO]
Yeah, let's go...
I'd like a peek at the team
we'll be defeating at Nationals.
[SHOYO]
Mhmm. Are you out here
running by yourself?
[USHIWAKA]
The rest of the team is out too.
They're just lagging behind.
[SHOYO]
Huh?
Ah! Kageyama!
You got a head start!
[TOBIO]
Yeah, not my fault you're slow!
[TOBIO, internal]
I knew he'd be a fast runner.
(surprised)
[SHOYO]
Oh boy, I can't wait to see
Shiratorizawa!
[TOBIO]
Ahh! Would you please shut up?!
You're like a little puppy out
for his first walk!
[TOBIO] Shut up! Shut up!
(SHOYO laughing merrily)
[SHOYO]
Whoaaa... It's huge!
Check out the main building!
It looks like a fancy hotel!
[SHOYO]
And look how gigantic this
athletic field is!
[SHOYO]
Wow! There's so much stuff, they
need sign‐posts! Kageyama,
horses! There's horses!
[SHOYO]
Huh! They have a bus just for
volleyball!
[TOBIO]
You better not get us lost in
here too, Hinata.
[SHOYO]
Whatever Dad!
[TOBIO]
Wait, where's Ushiwaka?!
[SHOYO]
Omigod, I think we are lost!
(SHOYO & TOBIO heavy breathing)
[SHOYO]
I think this is the gym for
volleyball club.
[TOBIO]
Yeah.
[SHOYO]
Hey! Is he in there? Move over!
Lemme see! Let me see!
[TOBIO]
Ugh! Don't push me!
(game chatter)
[SHOYO]
Hey look. There's another
high school here...
Are they in the middle
of a practice match?
[TOBIO]
That's a... college team.
[SHOYO]
College team?!
[TOBIO]
Yeah, they are THAT good...
None of the high
schools in the area
are good enough to
challenge them...
To get their practice...
they have to travel or
play college teams, dummy.
[SHOYO]
Well excuse me...
[USHIWAKA] Took you a while.
(TOBIO & SHOYO startled)
[TOBIO]
My name is Tobio Kageyama
from Karasuno...
Would you mind if we
watch you guys play?
[USHIWAKA]
Kageyama huh...
From Kitagawa First?
[TOBIO]
(surprised) Yeah...
I applied here but...
[USHIWAKA] No surprise.
(TOBIO & SHOYO startled)
[USHIWAKA]
I saw you play once when you
were in middle school...
What good is a setter who
won't devote himself to
his team's ace?
(TOBIO serious) (question)
(SHOYO cracking up)
[SHOYO] He's right; you're
not really the "devoted"
type, Kageyama!
[TOBIO] Hey!
[SHOYO]
But the "Great King" is like the
best setter in the whole
prefecture...
and HE'S not a devoted
type of guy either.
[TOBIO]
Nngh! What does this have to do
with Oikawa, you turd licker?!
Oikawa... I wish he would have
come here with us... He is an
excellent player.
(SHOYO gasp)
Well you're the ace here...
so that means he'd
be devoted to YOU.
[USHIWAKA]
Regardless of where he is
or who he's playing with,
Oikawa can bring out the
best in his entire team...
[USHIWAKA]
A weak team will become a
powerful one... And a stronger
team will become unstoppable.
[USHIWAKA]
That's Oikawa's talent.
Even the most healthy sapling is
only as strong as the soil in
which it grows...
If the soil is barren,
it will never bear any fruit.
[SHOYO]
Barren soil?
What does that mean?
Outside of Oikawa...
Aoba‐Johsai's weak...
That's all there is to it.
[SHOYO]
Think so, huh?
Well, if you think Seijoh is
barren soil...
then I guess that makes us a
concrete parking lot doesn't it?
(USHIWAKA surprised)
[TOBIO, internal]
What's with him? Normally he'd
be shaking in his shoes in front
of a guy like that.
[USHIWAKA]
Sorry if this offends you...
But I don't have time for a team
that couldn't beat Aoba‐Johsai
in the prelims...
[USHIWAKA]
You can talk all you want,
but I'm not listening.
(USHIWAKA shocked)
[SHOYO]
I'm Shoyo Hinata, from the
Kurasuno parking lot.
[SHOYO]
And I'm going to nationals.
After I kick your ass.
[JANITOR]
Hey you two... What do you think
you're doing here, you can't be
here without permission!
[SHOYO]
Anyway... Thank you for showing
us around the school... See ya.
[TOBIO]
Look. If Oikawa is supposedly
the best setter in the
prefecture...
I will be even better...
Just watch me.
(TOBIO grunts)
[USHIWAKA]
Stamina, speed, swiftness,
Jumping‐power, AND spirit...
[USHIWAKA]
Shoyo Hinata...
And Tobio Kageyama.
(snickers)
[TOBIO]
That was some big talk.
We're not even good enough to
defeat Aoba‐Johsai yet,
and much less
Shiratorizawa y'know.
[SHOYO]
We just need to beat ONE team.
[TOBIO]
Well, for starters, yeah.
[SHOYO]
That's why we're
going to Tokyo...
If we want to get stronger,
then we need to play as many
tough teams as we can!
[TAKEDA]
(awkward throat clear)
So, about that trip to Tokyo...
[TAKEDA]
We're planning to do it next
month. It'll be here before you
know it.
[TAKEDA]
We need your parents' permission
for this kind of thing,
so I'll be sending you all
home with the paperwork...
[TAKEDA]
Luckily, the school's already
given the go‐ahead to make the
trip during the school week.
(ALL happy)
[TAKEDA] Although...
It'll be tricky.
(SHOYO serious)
[TAKEDA] Final exams are
also next month... You do
know that, don't you?
(KEISHIN shocked)
(silence)
[TAKEDA]
Don't you?
I'm sure you can guess
what I'm about to say.
[TAKEDA] If you fail
in even one subject...
(YU & RYUNOSUKE quivering)
[TAKEDA]
You'll have extra
lessons on weekends.
(TOBIO nervous quivering)
(SHOYO quivering)
[TAKEDA]
And of course Tokyo...
You'll be out.
[SHOYO] What happens if
we miss the exam?
[TADASHI] Makeup exam?
[SHOYO] But what if
you miss the makeup?
[TADASHI] Makeup‐makeup?
[SHOYO]
Then let's just keep pretending
we're sick until after the trip!
[KEI]
If you fake being sick, you
can't go on the trip either.
(SHOYO horrified)
[KEI]
Sorry... Next Haikyu!!
"Direct Sunlight."