(drills/practice)
[TADASHI]
Huh?
(TADASHI cowers)
[ASAMUSHI]
Hey man, Nice kill up there!
(HITOKA terrified)
[MINAMIDA] Well done!
[STUDENT A]
Man, did you see the angle!
[KAKUGAWA]
Nice kill!
(long whistle)
[EVERYONE]
Thank you for the game!
(CROWD cheering)
[HITOKA] I got a look at him up
close, he was so intense.
[KAKUGAWA GM]
Well you look like you're
in pretty good form today
Hyakuzawa. I think we got this.
[HYAKUZAWA] Uh yessir.
[MINAMIDA] And look I don't see
anyone out there anywhere near
your size.
[MINAMIDA] You should tear
these guys apart.
[HYAKUZAWA] Yeah okay.
[NURUKAWA]
If there's any rules you don't
understand, feel free to ask.
[HYAKUZAWA]
I think I'm getting
them figured out now.
[KOMAKI]
About No.3 and No.9. You've
already seen how they serve.
So then... Let's get
'em up in the air.
[KOMAKI]
Now yes it's true that these
guys gave Seijoh a hard time...
but that's nothing to us.
[KOMAKI]
We just need to remember our
strengths and take our game to
them.
[KOMAKI]
Now let's go!
[KAKUGAWA]
Yessir!
[SHOYO]
Oh?
[DAICHI, internal]
This may only be the
preliminaries, but we need
this win to move forward.
[RYUNOSUKE, internal]
Even if we're up against someone
6'7" or whatever...
[KURASUNO, internal]
We're definitely gonna win!
(whistle)
[KOSHI]
Make it a good
one, Tsukishima!
[MINAMIDA]
Musshi!
[ASAMUSHI] I got it!
[KOMAKI] Hyakuzawa!
[OHNO]
Gonna start by challenging
them with a straight ball!
[UKAI]
They're wanting to start off on
a good note with a shot from
their ace.
[MINAMIDA]
It's a triple block!
Well. Not that it really
matters or anything.
[SHOYO, TOBIO, & RYUNOSUKE]
(internal) Oh crap?
(CROWD cheers)
(KAKUGAWA celebrates)
[KOSHI] Oh man, that shot was
completely above the block...
[MINAMIDA] Nice kill, Hyakuzawa!
(HITOKA worried)
[STUDENT A] D'you freakin'
see that?
[STUDENT B]
What's the point in even
trying to block that?
[DAICHI]
Coming in from the left!
[KOMAKI]
Hyakuzawa!
[YU]
Sorry, cover!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hinata, go for the last shot!
[SHOYO]
If I spike this, I'll get
blocked...!
[KOMAKI, internal]
(gasp) It's a lob!
(whistle)
(KAKUGAWA celebrates)
(HITOKA concerned)
[TAKEDA]
That guy's really stinkin' tall.
Well normally... that last shot
would have gone over the block
no problem.
[MINAMIDA] Get ready
for another one!
[HYAKUZAWA] Alright.
[KEISHIN] But this
[SHOYO] I'm really sorry! I
think that last ball might have
been a bit low.
[KOMAKI]
[ASAHI] Shake it off.
You're fine!
[KOMAKI]
just follow the ball.
[RYUNOSUKE] Next one, next one!
[DAICHI] All right, let's get
one back.
[KOMAKI]
[HYAKUZAWA] Alright.
[SHOYO] Okay!
(HITOKA surprised)
[HITOKA, internal] More and
more people keep showing up.
[STUDENT C] See, that's the
guy who's 6'7".
[STUDENT D]
Man, you weren't kidding.
[MIKAKO]
Wow, he's a monster!
[OHNO]
Hmm? Oh, hello there Mikako.
[MIKAKO]
Oh uh! Hey there how
are you doing Ohno?!
[OHNO]
Hey Coach, this is my neighbor.
Mikako here is the counselor
for our middle school
volleyball team.
[MIKAKO]
Hi. I can't believe how
tall he is. That blocker
is really intimidating.
[MIKAKO]
All the players on my team
are pretty small.
[MIKAKO]
So I can't help but sympathize
with the Kurasuno boys. It's
gotta be tough.
[OHNO]
Un‐uh‐uh..... Don't
worry about them.
[OHNO]
Take a look at little number
ten, he won't even pay that big
guy any mind!
Isn't that right, Coach?
[UKAI]
It's true he's at a
disadvantage.
In both his height
and his power...
[UKAI]
In basic terms, pure
strength and size
can be a formidable obstacle
[UKAI]
something that keeps ordinary
people at bay.
At least that's true...
if you fight them head‐on.
(TOBIO sigh)
[SHOYO]
Hm? Why are you wriggling your
fingers around like some crazy
old wizard, dude.
(TOBIO questioning)
(SHOYO alarmed)
[TOBIO]
Well...
I'm feeling something.
The ball seems to fit my
hands even more perfectly than
usual...
[MINAMIDA]
It's up! Above the net!
[DAICHI]
Push it over, Hinata!
[KOMAKI, internal]
Go ahead. In a shoving match
above the net,
it's impossible for
Hyakuzawa to lose.
(SHOYO shock)
(CROWD cheering)
(OHNO & MIKAKO shocked)
(whistle)
[YU]
Let it go!
[STUDENT E] There. Karasuno
finally got a point.
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[STUDENT F]
Only because of an unforced
error.
[STUDENT E]
I'd never heard
of Kakugawa before,
but now that's all people
are talking about.
[STUDENT F]
That's what happens when you
have a guy 6'7" on the floor.
[STUDENT E]
A real one‐man show, huh?
(ASAMUSHI annoyed)
[STUDENTS, internal]
Oh man! I think he heard us?!
[ASAMUSHI]
Nobody here gives the
rest of us respect.
[MINAMIDA]
Oh whatever who cares.
[ASAMUSHI] Wha‐?
[MINAMIDA] Stay focused.
Number nine's serving.
[MINAMIDA] Let's shove it right
back down their throats!
[YU] Give it to 'em, Kageyama!
(whistle)
(CHIKARA & HISASHI surprised)
[KOSHI] He mis‐hit it!
[ASAMUSHI]
I got it!
(KAKUGAWA making call‐outs)
(whistle) (KAKUGAWA cheers)
[DAICHI, internal] There's no
way... we'll reach a ball that
high. Although...
[KOMAKI] Nice kill, Hyakuzawa!
[CHANTS]
Let's go Kakugawa!
[KEISHIN]
(surprised) Do it, Specs.
[TAKEDA]
Uh? Right.
(long whistle)
[STUDENT A]
A time out, huh...
[STUDENT B]
Karasuno doesn't know what
to do about that guy.
(CROWD cheers)
[HITOKA, internal]
(frustrated) No. That's not
true. It can't be!
[INAGAKI]
Looking really good out there!
Not too bad for someone
playing in their very first
official match, huh?
[HYAKUZAWA]
Okay, thanks.
[MINAMIDA] Don't let
it bug you okay.
[ASAMUSHI] Hm? Huh?
[MINAMIDA]
Listen, just like how all the
other teams have their ace, well
we have Hyakuzawa.
[MINAMIDA]
And the more we help him be
successful, the better it'll
be for all of us.
[MINAMIDA]
Even if he's the only one
in the spotlight.
[MINAMIDA]
So. All we have to do is make it
look like it's no accident
Hyakuzawa's on the team.
[KOMAKI]
That's right. Our job is to put
everything we have
into capitalizing on
Hyakuzawa's raw power.
[KOMAKI]
They can call us what they
want... But this is how we play.
It's how we win.
(ASAMUSHI & MINAMIDA agreeing)
[INAGAKI]
What's wrong?
[HYAKUZAWA]
That No.10...
He's so short and he's jumping
around so desperately,
I kinda feel sorry for him.
[INAGAKI] What, are
you kidding me, man?
[HYAKUZAWA] Uh... no.
[ASAMUSHI]
I understand.
He doesn't stand a chance.
Even though his opponent across
the net has only been playing
for six months or so.
[ASAMUSHI]
That's a bitter pill to swallow.
I know that passing and
technique can be hard...
But seriously.
[HYAKUZAWA]
The game's pretty simple.
[SHOYO]
No matter how high I jump,
it gets hit from above me.
What am I supposed to do?
[DAICHI]
First off, calm down.
[YU]
Hinata... There' a lot more to
volleyball than just air combat.
(SHOYO confused)
[DAICHI]
Bring it in.
I've noticed a little something.
(long whistle)
[MINAMIDA]
Left, left!
[KOMAKI] Hyakuzawa! Yours!
[SHOYO] Here it comes.
[DAICHI]
After watching the previous
game... And warm ups.
[DAICHI]
I don't think No.9 can hit any
shots in multiple directions.
[YU]
He only shoots cross‐court...
in whatever direction his body
is facing.
[KEISHIN]
After watching them practice...
I'm thinking he must have
just started playing
volleyball fairly recently.
[SHOYO]
So then he's kinda like
Lev Haiba from Nekoma.
[KEISHIN]
Kinda, but he doesn't
have the speed or the
dexterity that Lev does.
[KEISHIN]
On the other hand, this
Kaiju kid is still tall and
powerful enough to overwhelm
others with what he does know.
[DAICHI]
So, when that No.9 is
striking the ball...,
[DAICHI]
We can disregard the possibility
of any line shots.
[YU]
Yeaaaah!
[OGASAWARA]
He's jumpin' sideways!
[HITOKA] Go guys!
(HYAKUZAWA surprised)
(whistle) (CROWD cheers)
[AYA & OGASAWARA] All right!
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[HITOKA] (amazed) He almost
wasn't able to get it over him.
[OHNO]
Way to go, Karasuno!
Somehow our boys have
figured out how to counter
that big guy's attack!
[UKAI]
Now to figure out how to
land an attack of their own.
[DAICHI]
Crush it Tanaka.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Alright. Got it.
[TOBIO]
Today I...
I feel good.
[SHOYO]
Huh?
[TOBIO] Daichi.
[DAICHI] Uh‐huh.
[TOBIO]
Hey uh I'm feeling really good
out here right now...
can I try out that
new quick attack?
[DAICHI] Uh...
(SHOYO excited panting)
[HITOKA] What the...? He's
looking really weird.
[DAICHI] Calm down, Hinata.
[OGASAWARA]
Our dog makes that face
when we show it some food
and it's hungry!
(UKAI chuckle)
(whistle)
[ASAMUSHI]
It's all yours!
[MINAMIDA]
I got it!
[KOMAKI]
Hyakuzawa!
[YU]
Aw yeah!
[KOMAKI]
Remember, no matter how many
tricky moves No.10 tries to do,
[KOMAKI]
just follow the ball,
you can always block him
wherever he ends up.
[HYAKUZAWA]
Okay... Just follow the ball...
(HYAKUZAWA shocked)
(ASAMUSHI & INAGAKI shocked)
(whistle) (KOMAKI shock)
(CROWD goes wild)
[STUDENT B]
There it is! The super
quick‐attack!
[HITOKA, internal]
It's slightly different from
what they've been doing until
now...
(HITOKA laughing)
[OGASAWARA] Yachi, are
you having an episode?
[OHNO] Woo‐hooey!
That short No.10 is amazing!
[UKAI]
Most likely, the tallest player
And the one that makes the
biggest fool of him... may be a
kid that's only five‐foot‐four.
[HYAKUZAWA]
I know that passing and
technique can be hard...
But seriously.
[HYAKUZAWA]
The game's pretty simple.
[HYAKUZAWA, internal]
What the hell is this?! I'm 6'7"
and this kid can't be
more than 5'4"!
[HYAKUZAWA]
How can he possibly
be above me?!
(whistle) (KURASUNO celebrates)
[STUDENT A] It's that fast
attack from No.10 again!
[STUDENT B]
How many has it been now?
[YU & RYUNOSUKE] Oh yeah.
That's right. You know it.
[SHOYO]
AAh!! How'd you like that?! Did
[YU] Oh yeah.
[DAICHI] You guys, shut up!
(ALL startled)
[SHOYO, YU, & RYUNOSUKE]
S‐sorry...
[TAKEDA]
If we can start landing fast
[KEISHIN]
No, not exactly...
Takeda, you're thinking about
what Karasuno used to be.
(whistle)
(SHOYO inhale, exhale)
[DAICHI] You got this Hinata.
[SHOYO, internal]
There he is. Over in the corner.
Sugawara said it was so
nobody would go after
him with their serve.
[SHOYO, internal]
Well, it's not like I can
actually aim my serve anyway!
[CHIKARA]
It's not all that unusual to
see spikers that concentrate
only on attacking.
[CHIKARA]
But in Kakugawa's case, it seems
No.9 is sorta being protected by
the other members of his team.
[TAKEDA] When No.9 is in
the back row, I feel a
little better.
[KOMAKI] Nice receive!
[KEISHIN] Don't go letting your
guard down, Specs.
[MINAMIDA] Double block!
[SHOYO]
Hyah!
[TAKEDA]
(startled) Oh my God!
[INAGAKI]
It's coming back over! Get under
it for a direct set!
The big fellow only practiced
hitting every ball that goes up
high,
[MINAMIDA] Ready...
Coming your way!
[KEISHIN]
I don't think he spent much time
Which means, whenever No.9 is in
the back row, the aerial combat
is right at the net...
[KEISHIN]
...the advantage is ours!
[MINAMIDA]
No.10! 10!
(whistle) (KURASUNO celebrates)
[TAKEDA]
That makes it set point!
[KEISHIN]
Yeah, here we are.
[HITOKA] Just one more!
[OHNO] C'mon boys don't let up!
[OGASAWARA]
Coach Ukai. Is the fast
attack that Shoyo is doing
still First Tempo?
[UKAI]
Do you remember everything
I taught you about tempo?
[OGASAWARA]
Yeah!
[HYAKUZAWA]
Nice receive!
[OGASAWARA]
Whenever the ball goes
up really high,
so the spiker can slowly
make his approach to the
net That's Third Tempo.
(whistle)
(KAKUGAWA celebrates)
[ASAMUSHI]
Nice, Hyakuzawa!
[AYA]
And when the spiker's approach
starts at the same time
the set is going up.
That's Second Tempo.
[ASAMUSHI] All right!
[MINAMIDA] Good one, Musshi!
[OGASAWARA]
When the spiker starts
his approach first
and the set is adjusted to where
he goes. That's First Tempo.
[ASAHI] Nice one, Nishinoya!
[UKAI] To be successful against
the block...
you must make contact at
a higher impact point than
the blocker.
[UKAI]
In this particular case, the
winner is whoever can reach the
pinnacle first.
Now the quick‐attack from the
little fella... I would not
technically call it First Tempo.
[UKAI]
At the moment when the setter
is tossing the ball,
[UKAI]
the spiker's approach and
takeoff have already been
completed.
[UKAI]
It's almost Minus Tempo!
(whistle) (long whistle)
(KURASUNO celebrates)
[AYA & OGASAWARA]
Minus Tempo, Awesome!
(CROWD astonished)
[UKAI] Don't you even think
about trying that yourselves,
kids.
[OGASAWARA]
Huh? Why can't we Coach?
[UKAI]
Those two are the only ones
who could pull off an attack
strategy that preposterous.
[SHOYO]
Ahhh... Hey. You know how you
asked before the game if I was
wimping out on you?
[SHOYO]
Was that because you knew that
this fast attack was gonna work?
[TOBIO]
No... I just knew that I was
feeling a little better than
usual today.
[SHOYO]
Then, why would you
say that to me?
[TOBIO]
Well I mean...
you put in a lot of
practice didn't you?
[TOBIO] Like, on stuff
other than quick‐attacks.
(SHOYO surprised)
[TOBIO]
Well... that very first feint
you did got stuffed pretty
easily.
[SHOYO]
Oh shut your face!
Okay rather than just chasing
number ten around..
let's focus on all
their other attacks.
[MINAMIDA] Sounds good.
[KOMAKI] We know that our
blockers
are having trouble
with that guy,
but the same goes for them
with Hyakuzawa. We can do this.
(exhale through nose) So it's
going to be a slug fest.
(long whistle)
(whistle)
[TOBIO] Nice receive!
[MINAMIDA] Here we go,
number ten!
[MINAMIDA]
Cover it!
[KOMAKI]
Hyakuzawa!
(whistle)
[HYAKUZAWA]
Yeah!
[YU]
Dammit...
[DAICHI]
Shake it off!
Whatever they score
[DAICHI] on us
we'll get it back!
[YU] Right!
[DAICHI]
That's why we increased
the number of weapons in
our arsenal!
[OGASAWARA]
Coach Ukai. If I have to go up
against someone who's that much
bigger than me...
[OGASAWARA]
is using an attack like Shoyo
and Kageyama the only way to
win?
[UKAI] (cracks up)
No no, of course not.
[OGASAWARA] Bwah.
[UKAI] If you can't win with
one or two, you simply
increase your numbers!
[TOBIO] Nice one, Noya!
[OGASAWARA]
Oh! Four different players
started moving at once!
[UKAI]
A synchronized assault
at First Tempo!
(whistle)
[RYUNOSUKE] Yeahhh!
[DAICHI]
Nice one, Tanaka!
[KOMAKI, internal]
No.10 alone is already
[HYAKUZAWA]
I'll take a point back!
(KOMAKI surprised)
[HYAKUZAWA]
It's what I'm here to do, right!
Just leave it to me guys.
[KOMAKI]
Hm?
[KEISHIN]
I don't believe this guy...
He should be pretty
worn out by now,
but he seems to be getting
more and more powerful.
[KOMAKI] Front, front!
[ASAMUSHI] Nice receive!
[HYAKUZAWA, internal]
It may be true that I don't have
very much experience out here...
[KOMAKI] Hyakuzawa!
[HYAKUZAWA, internal]
...But I can still score points!
[RYUNOSUKE] Sorry,
that went big!
[KOMAKI] Hyakuzawa! Do a direct!
[HYAKUZAWA, internal]
[HYAKUZAWA]
And slam it to the ground!
(whistle)
[HYAKUZAWA]
Yeah!!
(SHOYO annoyed)
(whistle)
(KURASUNO celebrate)
[KOSHI] Tanaka, nice kill!
[HITOKA] Yes it's match‐point!
[STUDENT E]
Karasuno's rotation right now
has pretty short blockers, maybe
Kakugawa can catch up.
[DAICHI]
I think I just heard some
chatter from the fans
about how short our front
line is right now.
[DAICHI]
Must look small next to a guy
who's six, seven.
[RYUNOSUKE & SHOYO]
(shocked) What was that?!
[STUDENT E] He could hear me?!
[STUDENT F] There's
no freakin' way.
[DAICHI]
All right listen you guys...
If we can't block the ball...
receive it.
(SHOYO & RYUNOSUKE agreeing nod)
[MINAMIDA]
It's up!
[KOMAKI]
Hyakuzawa! It's all you, man!
[DAICHI]
Give it a second! Not quite yet!
If a wall isn't going to work...
[DAICHI]
We go with something else!
(HYAKUZAWA shocked)
A soft block, get it!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Asahi, nice!
[ASAHI]
Good one, Tanaka!
[HYAKUZAWA, internal]
If it's not a fast‐attack...
then you're doomed, little man!
[BOKUTO]
Spiking isn't all about slamming
it onto the floor, y'know.
(INAGAKI & MINAMIDA reaching for
the ball) (floor dive)
[SHOYO]
...Hyaah!!
(whistle) (long whistle)
(KURASUNO & CROWD cheering)
[HITOKA] All right! They won
even without even needing the
black‐belly lantern!
[OHNO] Boo‐yah!
[OGASAWARA] Black‐belly lantern?
[UKAI] Off the partial block?
Was it coincidence, or did he
intentionally do that?
[SHOYO, internal]
I got a point... with something
other than the fast attack!
(surprised)
[ASAHI] Yes you did it, Hinata!
[DAICHI] Well done, little man.
[YU] We made it past
the first round, guys!
[RYUNOSUKE] All right!
[HYAKUZAWA] Inagaki.
[INAGAKI] Hmm?
[HYAKUZAWA] You know how I said
volleyball was a simple game...
[DAICHI] Hinata, come line up!
[HYAKUZAWA]
Guess I take that back.
[KEISHIN]
Kakugawa and their monster
No.9... They're going to be
pretty damn scary next year.
[RYUNOSUKE & YU]
Kiyoko, we'll hold
your baggage for you!
[KIYOKO]
Uh I already took care
of most of it.
(RYUNOSUKE & YU feeling useless)
[DAICHI] Hey! Let's move it,
guys.
[KIYOKO]
Say Yachi. I'm gonna go check to
see if we've forgotten anything.
[KIYOKO] You can go on
ahead if you want.
[HITOKA] Okay!
[TOBIO]
You've gotten pretty good at
attacking, but your receives are
still absolute dog‐pile.
[TOBIO]
And did you really have
to yell "hyaah!"?
[SHOYO]
Hey I got the stupid
point didn't I?
[YU] "hgya!"
[RYUNOSUKE] "hgya"?
(SHOYO shocked)
[CHIKARA]
Oh by the way...
I'm sure you guys
[CHIKARA] are all doing your
summer break homework, right?
[YU & RYUNOSUKE] "hgya!"
[CHIKARA]
And I'm sure you remember how
I said I wasn't gonna help you,
right? Right?
[TADASHI]
Ennoshita is such a smarty...
(SHOYO focused)
[HITOKA]
Hinata? Is something wrong?
[SHOYO]
This is it Yachi.
We'll finally get to stand in
the same court as
the Great King and Ushiwaka!
[TOBIO]
Hmm...
[SHOYO]
(shriek) Oh man
I forgot my lunchbox!
(TOBIO yawn)
[TERUSHIMA]
Come on, it's just
your phone number.
What's the big deal, girl?
[KIYOKO] I don't think so...
(SHOYO surprised)
[KIYOKO] Yeah no... I uh
have someone waiting for me.
[SHOYO]
(shock) Wah, someone's
[TERUSHIMA] Doesn't take long to
share a phone number. C'mon.
[SHOYO]
And Tanaka and Nishinoya
[KIYOKO]
I'm sorry, guys. I've gotta go.
[TERUSHIMA]
Just gimme your digits. It'll
only take a second, Darlin'.
[SHOYO]
GAHH! (freaking out) Oh hey
Kiyoko!
(KIYOKO surprised, panicked)
[SHOYO]
I see you found my lunchbox!
Thanks! That's great! Let's get
[TERUSHIMA]
Hold it, hang on.
We weren't finished talking yet!
[KIYOKO] Hey! Hinata!
[TERUSHIMA] Now where were we?
Oh yeah your number.
[SHOYO] Excuse me!
(KIYOKO surprised)
[TERUSHIMA, internal]
Whoa! This little fella
has some ups...! Oh?
[TERUSHIMA]
Karasuno...
[SHOYO]
Kiyoko is extremely busy,
she's our manager
[SHOYO]
and we really need her for some
important team business right
now.
[TERUSHIMA]
Oooh. You guys beat that 6'7"
guy. That's not bad.
[SHOYO]
(startled) Um well,
yeah.. we did.
[TERUSHIMA]
Aw maaaan... I was hoping to
play against that big fella,
this is so saaad.
[SHOYO]
Play against him?
So it was a pretty exciting
first round wasn't?
[SHOYO]
Um... are you on one of the
teams that got past the first
round?
[TERUSHIMA]
You kidding? Yeah sorry we
didn't have to play in the first
round.
[SHOYO]
Oh! So. You were in the top
eight in the preliminaries?
[TERUSHIMA]
Well. More like the top four.
[SHOYO]
Wait the... the top four?!
[TERUSHIMA]
Later, kid. If we do end up
going against each other in the
tournament...
I'm sure it'll be
a real good time.
[SHOYO]
(curious) Who was... that guy?
So uh... I guess he doesn't need
your phone number anymore. So
that's good.
[KIYOKO]
(sigh of relief) Yeah for some
reason, all his attention
completely shifted over to you.
[KIYOKO]
Anyway, thank you. That was nice
of you. Oh. Here's your lunch.
(SHOYO embarrassed)
[KIYOKO]
That wrapping for your lunchbox
is different.
[SHOYO]
(shock) Oh no. That's not...
it's my little sister's,
it's not mine...!
Definitely not mine.
(KIYOKO gentle laugh)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey Noya. Kiyoko is a bit late?
[YU]
I don't like it.
(TERUSHIMA & BOBATA
intimidating)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Hey... What are you lookin' at‐
(DAICHI annoyed)
(YU whistles)
[SHOYO]
Sorry about that guys!
[TOBIO]
Try and get your crap together,
dumbass!
[YU & RYUNOSUKE]
Kiyoko, we're glad
that you were safe!
[DAICHI]
Did you find
everything you needed?
[KIYOKO] His lunch.
Look how adorable it is.
[SHOYO] (mortified)
Aw man. Kiyoko!
(YU, TOBIO, DAICHI, & KEI
laughing, mocking)
[RYUNOSUKE]
Is some loser making
moves on Kiyoko?!
[YU]
That is total bullcrap!
[RYUNOSUKE]
From now on, we don't ever let
her out of our sight!
[RYUNOSUKE] We'll take turns
going to the bathroom, if we
have to!
[YU] Yeah!
[CHIKARA] She'll never have any
interest in those goons.
[YU] What!?
[CHIKARA]
Next episode of Haikyu!!
"Growing Fast"