It's out...?
We did it... We took
the first set from Seijoh!
We took the first set!
Yeah!
C'mon, guys!
Take the second one too!
Sorry about that.
That was clearly
a ball for Kindaichi!
Not only did he rob
him of the ball,
but he knocked
it out of bounds?!
On top of that,
we were at set point!
Where do I even start
discussing this with him?!
That was
really dangerous!
Iwaizumi!
Right, right! That! Yes!
That needs to be said first!
Uh... I'm okay,
don't worry about me...
It's been a while since
I've been in a game,
so I wanted to
get involved early.
That's still no reason
to do that, y'know!
What's up
with that guy?
Subbing in someone like that...
What's wrong with Seijoh?
Hey, that guy from before...
He's in the starting lineup now!
If they're subbing him
in for Kunimi...
then I bet he's gonna be pretty
quick on his feet... Watch out.
Look, you can do
what you want...
but if I find you're
dragging us down,
then I'm gonna
have you subbed out.
Just don't start screwing things
up, or you're back on the bench.
Yessir.
Hey, I just told you
the exact same thing!
That guy... He challenged
Iwaizumi every chance he could.
and lost each and every
time he fought him.
Iwaizumi's the only one
he always listens to.
Like he's
the alpha dog.
[Yahaba]:
Yeah. It'd be better if
he'd answer to Oikawa though.
[Kentaro]:
True. He is the team
leader, after all.
Listen, guys, if we keep
this good energy going...
the second set's all ours!
Yeah!
[Yu]:
Serve us up
a good one, Asahi!
[Watari]:
It's out!
Ah! Dammit! I'm sorry!
[Koshi]:
We'll get the next one!
[Chikara]:
Shake it off!
[Daichi]:
Don't cry!
What'd you say?!
[Matsukawa]:
Go for it, Oikawa!
It's out!
Sorry!
[Hajime]:
Let it go!
What is wrong
with Oikawa today?
He just missed
another one.
Did you see how
fast that was?
If that hit me,
I would have lost a limb!
I think his aim is
slowly getting better.
[Ryunosuke]:
Kill it, Tsukishima!
[Toru]:
Nice cover, Iwa!
All right, which of these
three is it gonna be?
Mad Dog, it's yours!
An open set to the right?!
"Mad Dog"? Is that really his
nickname? That's so awesome!
C'mon, guys!
Hang on...
What's he doing?
[Shimada]:
Look where he's
approaching the net.
[Hajime]:
Triple block!
[Takinoue]:
Whoa, that was a crazy cut shot!
[Matsukawa]:
Nice kill!
That's why he did
it that way!
Huh?
[Shimada]:
When you end up
facing the blockers...
you have a few options
for which course to hit.
Of course, it makes
it easier for you
to land square against
the block, right?
But he hit that ball
as if he was slicing it
from the side of the blockers.
Hitting with his right hand
from the right side allows
for a crazy‐strong cut shot.
[Saeko]:
How cool!
Mad Dog is so rad!
[Hanamaki]:
Iwaizumi's serve!
It's coming back!
Chance ball!
Damn, that's my fault!
Those two serving back‐to‐back
is putting a lot of
pressure on us...
And on top of that,
this "Mad Dog" kid...
Oh... a double
quick‐attack?
Don't disappear on me, even Mad
Dog won't bite too many times.
Keep on coming
after it, 'kay?
Shorty caught on that
you weren't the one
hitting, Kendaichi.
A‐ah, yeah sorry!
Guess I sorta chickened out!
[Toru]:
Iwa, let's get
another one!
[Hajime]:
You got this!
Kageyama!
Yeah!
Well done, nice receive!
A C‐Quick!
A‐are you all right?
Y‐yeah... I'm good.
It's that Number 16 again!
That's three points in a row!
They're landing them, but the
combo plays look a bit sporadic.
Ever since 16 subbed in,
the rhythm of their
attacks has changed.
[Hanamaki]:
Kyotani, nice kill.
Serve up a point,
Iwaizumi!
Sorry!
We finally got
a point back.
[Toru]:
Makki, nice!
Not so fast!
And now...!
After some flashy
moves from 16...
[Tobio]:
a broad jump
from Kindaichi!
Yeah!
Hmm? Look at him,
he's ticked off that he's
being used as a decoy.
Although that
obsession to attacking
is raising his
effectiveness as a decoy.
How 'bout we make those fangs
of yours even sharper.
Let's lock this down...
This team now... is not
the same Seijoh we know.
[Watari]:
Kindaichi's up!
Got it!
[Ryunosuke]:
Left!
[Shoyo]:
Center!
So they decided to always
have one mid‐blocker glued
to Hinata.
[Toru]:
It's up! Cover it!
Got it! Kyotani, to you!
Sorry, it's close to the net!
[Toru]:
Triple block!
If he hits, he'll be stuffed!
Mad Dog, bring it back!
That was a great block!
Gotta say, that was a pretty
brave full swing he did there...
What're you doing?!
Why didn't you try a fakeout
or a lob or something?!
A spike doesn't feel as good
if it doesn't crush somebody
and land for the kill!
Get it together!
[Irihata]:
Now, now, Mizoguchi.
Everything will work itself out
when the time comes, okay?
Uhh... right.
So, uh... who's quick
on their feet again?
I just said he might be!
Oh, so he doesn't like
doing fakeouts, does he?
Well that guy's
missing out!
[Toru]:
Makki!
[Daichi]:
Nice, Nishinoya!
Nicely done,
Makki! Mad Dog!
[Saeko]:
It's that shot he hits
from the side again!
This time I'll
stop him for sure!
We've been saved...
They were going up
against a triple block...
and they decided to go
at it with a hard hit...
A move like that doesn't
come without its risks.
That kid's unpredictable
and marches to his own drum.
Seeing as how he hasn't been
in any other match before...
[Keishin]:
Number 16 must be a
double‐edged sword for them.
That spike from Number 16...
It's like "WHOOSH" and "ZOOM,"
and it looks totally awesome!
I know, right? Doesn't it?
[Toru]:
What Mad Dog has, on top of
the obvious jumping skills,
is extraordinary back
and abdominal strength.
He arches back well
to build up his power,
and snaps it out
with incredible force!
It releases so strong,
if it gets past the blockers,
it's not easily picked up.
So he finally
nailed it...
Nice job. You're using
him well, Oikawa...
If it were me, I'd have
already sent it to someone else.
Ah, yes, tenacious and daring
at the same time...
To make use of Mad Dog...
you can't be skittish about it.
[Hajime]:
Do it, Mad Dog!
[Ryunosuke]:
It's out!
His serves are
extremely dynamic!
[Takinoue]:
We're deadlocked...
It's anybody's game.
Yeah... He lands
a lot of shots...
but then he also makes
a lot of mistakes.
It's your serve,
Iwaizumi!
[Watari]:
Cover, cover!
Makki, last shot!
Got it!
[Toru]:
One more, one more!
[Shoyo]:
He spatched
the receive!
[Yu]:
Watch the left!
Oh, you think so, huh?
Mad Dog! The timing is
earlier now! Second tempo!
I'm fully aware that he's
a double‐edged sword.
All the more reason to
make the best use of him!
Right on!
That's a really
nasty angle...
The ability to peel the
blockers off the ball...
Only a setter knows
how good that feels.
Keep hanging in there!
Nice receive!
Center!
You can do it!
[Ryunosuke]:
You got this, Hinata!
Back row again without
getting the chance to spike...
This one's mine!
[Tobio]:
Nice receive!
All right, let's go!
[Hitoka]:
Hinata's going for it!
My first back‐row attack!
Did you think now was really
the best time to use that?
Oh, yeah, I
thought so, too.
Keep calm... keep calm...
keep calm...
Thanks for messing
up my debut...
Do not punch
him in the face...
I thought they'd
get that side‐out...
They'd better cut
this lead down quick.
[Shimada]:
Sugawara's being
called to the bench?
Are they changing up
their setters again?
I thought Kageyama wasn't
doing all that badly...
It's just that Oikawa's
doing that much better.
It looks... like they're
switching him in...
but not for Kageyama.
I cannot let them
run away with this one...
[Keishin]:
I'll do whatever it takes.
[Hitoka]:
So Sugawara's subbing
in for somebody?
This is a very tactical
player substitution.
Don't use big, stupid
words like that...
Uh, aren't you
in college?
So, look... some subs
are for when get injured,
and some are for when you want
to bring in pinch servers
or one‐point blockers.
This is a very tactical
player substitution.
In the last match
against Seijoh...
they only subbed this guy
in as kind of last resort
after being cornered.
[Shimada]:
But this time, they're
probably subbing him
to try and snag the win.
It's gonna be hard to
make a countermeasure
now that that wildcard Number 16
is runnin' around in there.
But still... we're not
gonna let them off the hook.
Right... and there's
still this guy.
[Hajima]:
Your serve, Cap!
All right, here it is.
The serve toss feels good...
The reality of this rivalry
is starting to take shape...
It's gotten more intense with
each time we see each other.
Neither side can surrender
victory to the other,
and both teams have undergone
training as a result.
We keep getting better,
but at the same time...
...so have they.
At some point, something
will have to give.
[Hajime]:
Let's get that point!
Up front!
[Daichi]:
Nice receive, Nishinoya!
Over here!
Tanaka!
[Daichi]:
Triple block!
Yeah, nice one, Bro!
Thank... God...
[Takinoue]:
Oh, here he comes. Interesting.
[Koshi]:
All right, we're gonna catch up!
[Team Karasuno]:
Yeah!
[Asahi]:
All right, it's all you, Suga!
Yeah.
[Watari/Yutaro]:
Bring it on!
[Asahi]:
Come on, Suga!
Serving right after you get
subbed in is nerve‐wracking.
But there's only
one place to aim.
[Hanamaki]:
Kyotani!
Y'see that?!
[Shimada]:
At this rate... Number 16'll
be late to attack!
Yeah!
[Shimada]:
A side‐out!
[Chikara]:
One more of those, Suga!
[Toru]:
Again...!
Mad Dog is a natural wing
spiker, but he's the type who
aggressively to
do quick‐attacks.
Moving him around through
serves keeps him from starting
his approach for a spike.
[Mizoguchi]:
Karasuno's Number 2
really puts us in a bad spot.
[Ryunosuke]:
Nice receive, Cap'n!
Sugaaaa!
Okay!
Kageyama moved to offense?
[Yutaro]:
They've got FIVE spikers?!
YEAAAAAAH!
WOOOO!
That... was a nice kill...
Ah, dang it...
His line shots are
so freakin' good!
Oh, wow! That thing they just
did, was called a two‐setter!
Agh... more of your crazy
technical terms... so then...
[Saeko]:
That makes it a tactical
one‐point two‐setter!
That right?
Kinda long...
All right.
[Chikara]:
Keep it goin', guys.
This is a well‐timed
substitution. Just might work.
I guess a third‐year WOULD be
really good at receiving, huh?
Oh, I get it.
In volleyball, each player's
constantly being rotated
to new positions on the court.
The front row and back row
both have different
jobs to do...
Each spot in the
rotation's different.
And I would say our most
vulnerable formation
for offense and defense is when
Tsukishima's up to serve.
[Shimada]:
It leaves us open.
We only have two
spikers up front.
And Tsukishima can't
block from the back row.
The fact that they can
aggressively score points
even in the trickiest part
of their rotation...
[Shimada]:
that's saying something.
So what do ya think, guys?
Eh... let's pull
him out now.
Good thinking.
[Yu]:
All right, Suga!
Your turn to serve!
Yup. He's aiming
for Mad Dog!
Got it!
[Toru]:
Makki, nice!
As always, they're
quick to adapt!
Good job out there, Suga!
Thanks.
Man... I wanted to at
least get us to a tie.
[Tobio]:
Tanaka!
YEAH!
[Koshi]:
Nail it, Kageyama!
[Toru]:
Iwa!
They were able
to get it up!
Coming your way!
Here!
Number 16... You see how
they're so focused on him?
It's obviously a big part
of their offensive strategy.
Yeah... I think so.
[Takinoue]:
Maybe they're trying to draw
attention to Number 16
and then send it over
to someone else.
No matter how much the
ball goes to Mad Dog,
I won't be fooled again!
[Tobio]:
Tanaka!
Got it!
[Toru]:
Nice one!
[Hanamaki]:
I know the reason
It was the one extra punch that
we needed. He came in to attack.
Mad Dog!
If he can't do that,
we're in trouble.
Damn!
It's Getting there,
it's getting there...
(whistle)
Just when it was
getting good!
Well, Seijoh got to
20‐points first, I guess.
But even if we were
to drop this set...
we already took the first ,
so we just need the last,
and everything'll
be easy‐breezy!
No...
[Shimada]:
It's better to take this set
by any means necessary.
If we fail now...
we could lose it all.
[Hajime]:
Kindaichi, one more point!
[Daichi]:
Up front!
Sorry!
Don't aim so hard!
[Daichi]:
Go, Tanaka!
Let's go!
Very nice receive!
Acting as if you're not aware is
actually a form of being aware.
[Hajime]:
Here goes Mad Dog!
COME ON!
That kid's gettin'
on my nerves...
[Keishin]:
Subbing in Number 16
was a gamble...
Must have been a risk
Seijoh was willing to take.
And it's already paid off.
Which is exactly what
I was afraid would happen.
Now, Specs!
Right!
Again? So quick!
Looks like Karasuno used up
all their time‐outs.
With their new weapon Number 16,
they racked up
points wicked fast.
But unfortunately, I think
that what they were really doing
for most of this set
was getting him revved up.
[Irihata]:
Mad Dog may be problematic when
he first steps onto the court...
but then, the fireworks begin!
This is not good...
You see...
When the momentum swings this
wildly, at the beginning...
it can set a tone that drives
the rest of the match.
[Shimada]:
At this rate, Seijoh
definitely has the upper hand.
Somehow, we've gotta take this
set or we might not come back.
[Hajime]:
This is your chance, Mad Dog!
[Daichi]:
Let's get this point!
[Team Karasuno:
Yeah!
I know, Tadashi.
Just be patient.
Please... put me in!
[Toru]:
Looks like your engine's
warming up, Mad Dog.
Let's keep going and
end this, shall we?
[Hajime]:
Let's end this with
one shot, Mad Dog!
[Mad Dog]:
Yessir.
[Toru]:
Why do you only
I'm not sending any sets
to you anymore!
Next Episode of Haikyu!!
"The Fight of the
Previously Spineless"