[Vega] All said and done,
it's gonna come
down to a handful
of decisions we
make out here...
[Nicky] Well, who
we are has always
been defined by what we do.
How is this different
from any other time?
[Vega] Out here, our choices
affect not only our lives,
but the lives of all the people
we've sworn to protect.
We can only hope...
... we make the right ones.
[Mason] Breaking into
"Mission A," altitude, 8,000.
Atmospheric pressure,
zero‐point‐eight.
[Toni] That's our cue, Marines.
Gear up. Prep for drop.
[scattered breaths]
Ah‐‐oh, yeah!
Lookin' good in
that armor, Kamille!
You know nothin' gets me hot
like seein' you go commando.
Seriously...?
Careful, Essex‐‐you're gonna
make your hand jealous.
[Essex] Heh.
No worries, babe.
She's your second biggest fan.
And she knows how to party.
Heh...
[Essex cries out in pain]
[Milque] And‐‐strike fifty.
Well, whatever else
happens today,
at least we can't get shot down
any worse than that, am I right?
Yo, Nicky.
You okay, kid?
Yeah, he's fine. He's just ready
for some action. Aren't ya?
You seen any sign of that
tactical package yet?
Still waiting on it. Our omnis
are synched and linked...
... but there's nothing in the
way of mission specs so far.
Makes me uneasy.
Does Command usually wait
for the last possible minute
to tell us who the enemy
is, sir? Seems weird.
Ya gotta be ready for anything.
Like Commander Shephard always
said, nothing is ever simple.
Damn, Vega, sucks for you
that Shepard's dead...
You two would have made
a really cute couple.
[Essex makes kissing noises]
[Milque and Kamille laugh]
You think I'm ashamed
to show respect
for someone who saved
billions of lives?
I'm proud to follow
that example.
Laugh it up all
you want, pretty boy.
I know who my heroes are.
Okay, someone's a
little defensive...
Whatever, man. You want
a hero to worship,
I'm right here, baby.
[Toni] That so?
[Vega] Attention!
Let's get this straight.
What I see here is a squad
of highly trained
special forces.
But you're not
warriors. Not yet.
Today we find out what
you're made of, Marines.
It's time to earn that uniform.
Our final Mission specs
are in from Command.
I'm syncing to your omnis now.
Take a good look.
[Toni] Let that sink in... This
is what you're up against...
Think tough. Think built
like a brick shithouse.
That's right, virgins.
Your first dance goes to
the Krogan Blood Pack,
the meanest bunch of reptilian
uglies in the Terminus.
Krogan are like walking tanks;
they've got thick, armored skin,
two sets of vital organs‐‐
Relax, Nicky;
just aim for the head.
[Toni] The bastards are
currently laying siege
to our colony on Fehl Prime...
It so happens to be
one of our top pharma
processing facilities...
Meds we pull outta this rock
cure our sick kiddies
across the galaxy.
Lot of civilians down there...
Sitrep shows the Blood Pack
just outside the perimeter,
hammering the colony K‐barriers.
They get in, we'll be scraping
up colonists for a week...
So‐‐we hit 'em fast,
we hit 'em hard;
shuttles strafe their lines.
Then we insert ourselves between
the enemy and their objective,
and vigorously
negotiate their defeat.
It won't be easy; things are
getting messy down there.
But that's why
they called us...
We're Alliance Marines, people!
This is what we do!
Any questions?
Then who's ready to go
kick some krogan ass?!
Sir! Alliance Marines
are, sir! Hoo‐rah!
[Brood sneers, laughs]
[Treeya] Christine,
what should we do?
The Alliance Marines
are coming! Just hold on!
[Brood growls, grunts]
[guards scream]
[Guard A] The Barrier's down!
[Christine shudders]
[Christine gasps]
[Christine cries]
[Treeya] Christine!
[Christine] I'm okay.
‐‐Dammit!
‐‐You're not a soldier.
Stop taking chances.
No, we've got to hold them
off... Just a little longer!
Brood! Well done; you have
earned your place as my second.
Sir.
[Archuk] Now,
unleash the vorcha.
[Brood laughs]
[various growls and snarls]
[varren roars]
[scattered gasps]
[Guard B] They're animals...
‐‐[Guard C cries out]
‐‐[Guard D] Shit!
[Guard E cries out]
[Brood chuckles]
[Brood] An... air strike...?
No!!
[krogan grunts]
[Guard F] Alliance drop
ships! We're saved!
[guards cheer]
[Christine sighs] They made it.
[Treeya] And not a
moment too soon.
[Mason] Get off our lawn,
ya dirty space turtles!
[Toni] Put us down, Mason.
Roger that, Cap. Now prepping
for quick dump. Fifteen seconds.
[Toni] On your feet, Marines!
"A" Squad, aft hatch!
"B" squad, fore hatch!
[Mason] Dust off in 5... 4...
Shit!
[Gamma Pilot] Abort! Abort!
Alpha and Beta are down!
Repeat: Alpha and Beta are down!
[Mason] Roger, Gamma‐‐abort
confirmed. Evasive maneuvers!
Dammit.
[Mason] Breaking off
to re‐engage!
[Brood growls]
[scattered yells]
[Vega pants]
Goin' down...! Brace for impact!
Now! Send the humans
to their gods!
[varren roars]
[scattered grunts]
[Marine Z pants, grunts]
[Marine Z screams, cries out]
[Treeya] What's
happening out there?
[Christine gasps]
[Treeya exhales]
[Vega grunts]
[Vega groans]
[scattered groans and grunts]
[Milque coughs]
[Milque] Our pilot
is so fired...
[Mason coughs]
Yeah? Well, I got one
better for ya... I quit.
[Toni] Move Marines!
Evac this bucket!
[Toni grunts]
Whoa, Captain, that looks bad...
I said move! That's an order!
[Toni grunts]
[Essex] You heard him! On me!
[scattered grunts]
You too, Vega!
Better bite down, sir.
[Toni makes muffled grunts]
[Vega] On three...
[Toni screams]
[Brood grunts]
[Vega pants, grunts]
[Vega yells]
[Brood] Go!
Search for survivors!
[Vega grunts]
[Vega pants]
Move!
[Essex yells]
[Milque] Come on, Vega!
You can make it!
[Mason cries out]
[Nicky] Sir!
Incoming!!
[Kamille] Can anyone see them?!
‐‐[Mason] We are so screwed!
‐‐[Kamille] How many are there?!
[Essex] We can't hold
them off for long!
[Nicky] What do we do?
Sir! What do we do?!
[Vega] Hold your fire!
Cease fire! Essex! Kamille!
[Kamille]
What the hell, Vega?!
You guys are just burnin'
Thermal Clips at this range.
Save it for when it counts.
[Mason moans]
You gonna live there, flyboy?
I told you... I quit that job...
[Vega] That's a "yes."
On your feet.
[Mason grunts]
[Archuk] Hold your fire!
[scattered groans]
Alliance! Show yourselves and be
granted an honorable execution!
Wow... Some negotiator.
Milque, I need you to give
Nicky your power cells.
See what you can do about
upgrading my K‐barriers.
Okay... That's great for you,
but now what am I supposed
to use for shields?
Shields? You still got a big
rock to hide behind, don'tcha?
Flyboy, look after the captain.
Right. Already on it, boss.
Listen... You've
got to get up top
and keep their snipers off me.
Nicky, you'll radio me tactical?
That's a big affirmative, sir.
And what the hell
are you gonna do?
A krogan never
turns down a chance
for glory on the battlefield.
So I'm gonna go out there
and give them what they want,
which should buy the
two of you enough time
to move around and flank them.
[Kamille and Essex exhale]
[Essex] Hold on... I'm not
running into that firing squad!
No... we circle all the
way around their line
and come in behind them...
It's crazy, but it could work.
We're gonna have to
make it work, or we all die...
That is, unless you got
a better plan, Essex?
Hey, why're you askin' me?
You're squad leader,
at least for another
two minutes, anyway...
[Milque grunts]
[Archuk laughs]
[Archuk grunts]
Here they come.
[Vega pants, grunts]
Nicky! Where's my tactical?
It's coming in now, sir.
They're clustered at your 12,
forty meters and
holding position.
I show one sniper
already zeroed in on you.
[Milque] Roger that. I got 'em.
[Vega] Not yet. Hold your fire
till Essex and Kamille engage.
Wait.
[Sniper grunts]
[Archuk grunts] It seems this
one has accepted my offer.
[Vega grunts]
Okay... Let's dance.
Come on...
[Vega pants]
[Vega grunts]
[Vega yells]
[Archuk roars]
Flanking team, where the
hell are you? Talk to me!
[Kamille] Almost there.
One hundred meters.
[krogan yells]
Here...
Catch. I won't be needing it.
[Essex gasps]
[scattered murmurs]
Heh, well, so much for
lookin' cool before I die...
[Krogan Y] There! On the ridge!
Idiot.
[Essex] You know you love me!
[vorcha gasp]
[Kamille winces]
[Essex] Hey!
That's no way to treat a lady!
[Brood groans]
[Brood grunts]
[Brood winces, grunts]
[Milque cries out, coughs]
Last grenade...
Gotta make it count!
[Vega grunts]
Dammit!
[Vega pants, grunts]
[Archuk yells]
[Vega grunts, yells]
[Vega grunts]
[Vega winces]
[Archuk] You are brave,
human. Die with honor.
[Archuk screams]
[Archuk snarls]
Brood! Find the one controlling
the drone and kill them!
[Brood] There. I have you now...
[Nicky grunts, gasps]
[Archuk sneers]
[Vega yells]
[Archuk roars]
[Archuk grunts]
[Vega gasps]
[Archuk roars, Vega grunts]
[Archuk and Vega grunt]
[Vega groans]
[Archuk grunts]
[Archuk laughs]
Now you die.
You first.
[gun clicks]
[Archuk laughs]
[Vega gasps]
[Archuk moans]
[Archuk] I like you...
A fighter to the bitter end!
[Milque pants]
[Milque] You alright, Vega?
[Vega] Yeah. Think so.
[Milque] Good... cause
once we get outta this...
...the next drink's on you.
[vorcha yells]
[Kamille pants]
[Essex] Ha!
It's almost too easy!
[Essex grunts]
And that, ladies and gentlemen,
is free drinks for life.
[Essex sighs] I think I pretty
much drained my power cell...
Yeah, maybe one more
good shot if I'm lucky...
[varren snarls, Essex gasps]
[Kamille grunts]
Shit! Kamille!
[Essex grunts]
[Essex shudders]
[Brood and Essex grunt]
Milque!
[Milque] I don't have a shot!
Shit!
[Brood grunts]
Now... say goodbye.
[sound of gunshot]
[Brood groans]
[Vega pants]
[Essex] Whoa...
[Milque exhales]
See? We make a pretty good team!
[Kamille snarls]
Look, the dog thing
was an accident, okay?
Yeah, and so was this!
Asshole...
[Essex groans]
Sorry! Hot damn...
[Brood grunts]
[Essex chuckles] Hello...
Get on with it!
[Essex] Gladly.
[Vega] Essex!
Stand down, Marine!
We are not murderers!
This is war, man!
‐‐Yes!
‐‐[Brood groans]
You're right! This is war!
And now, this krogan
is a prisoner of war.
You two gonna kiss or what?
Nicely done, squad leader.
[Essex grunts]
That's the last of 'em;
we did it, sir.
That was insane, goin' out
there as bait, y'know...
I thought for sure you were
gonna get us all killed...
But hey... I guess I gotta
be wrong sometime, right?
[Kamille] I think
what he means is...
We owe you one... Big time.
It's "Vega," yeah?
Tell you what...
Vega here deserves
a goddamn medal.
Not to brag, but technically,
I took out more of
'em than he did.
"Technically," you almost
took me out, too!
You're still in the dog house.
[Vega] It was a
team effort, guys.
Look, will you drop it already?
I said I was sorry.
[laughter]
Vega... Hell of a
battle there, son;
that's the kind of leadership
I'd expect from a veteran.
It was the training, sir.
Don't sell us that crap!
I never taught you that kind
of soldiering and you know it.
Quit playin' coy and accept
the compliment; you earned it.
Your courage under fire saved
a lot of good people, Vega.
And it's for their
continued safety
we'd like you and your
squad to stick around...
Hold down the fort.
Admiral, the Blood Pack
is finished here...
All due respect, but we're
a special forces unit.
Can't you just assign a
standard security detail?
I'm giving you
an order, soldier.
The Fehl Prime facility
and all of its inhabitants
are a very valuable
resource for the Alliance.
It is far too important
for us to leave undefended.
Are we clear?
Yes, sir, we're clear.
[Hackett] I see from your badge
you remember the Normandy.
I try to, sir; I think
everyone should.
It's good to have heroes,
Vega, but don't be too eager
to follow in
Shepard's footsteps.
That kind of greatness only
comes at a great cost...
Remember that. Hackett out.
[Toni] Well, Lieutenant...
Welcome to the
Terminus Systems...
[Messner] All right,
it's all yours...
Let's get this baby unloaded!
[dock tech] We're clear!
[Kamille] Three meters...
Two... One...
And we're docked...
Hold it there, Vega.
[Vega] Copy that,
Kamille. Standing by.
[Mason] Explain something to me.
First the cannon, now full‐on
military‐grade barriers?
Seem like overkill
to anybody else?
I mean... we haven't seen a
hostile in, what, two years?
And they got us tricked out
to take on a whole fleet.
[Nicky] You're clear to
retract the cables, sir.
[Vega] Nicky.
We've been over this.
You don't have to
keep calling me sir.
[Milque] Heh. Kiss ass.
Would you just do your job?
[Milque] Callin' 'em
like I see 'em.
Don't hate the messenger.
[Essex sighs]
Just wastin' their time...
My gun already packs all the
firepower this place needs.
Oh, please, I've seen
your "gun," Essex...
Hate to be the one to break it
to you, but... not that big.
I'm guessin' we've all heard
the rumors at this point.
Ah‐‐! What?!
[Nicky] He means the ones
about entire colony populations
disappearing without a trace.
Yeah, I've tried askin'
around division about that,
but no one wants to talk.
Official word from
Command is "no comment."
Duh, what'd you expect...?
Command doesn't talk
to grunts like us‐‐
you gotta read
between the lines.
"Here, have a big
gun and shut up."
That's their comment...
Probably all some
Cerberus conspiracy
they're trying to
keep under wraps.
[Vega] I dunno‐‐this one doesn't
smell like Cerberus to me.
It's not their style.
[Tech 1] Yo, Vega!
Last of the Agri‐Dome's Special
Brew... On the house, buddy!
Well, I can never say
no to a free drink!
Then I recommend you
plan on staying drunk,
'cause we still owe you plenty.
Nice work on the new
defenses, by the way.
Ah... It's what we do.
Hola, James!
Hey, April! Hola, chispita.
‐‐Whatcha doin'?
‐‐Waiting for you!
You ready for duty? Attention!
Yes, sir, Lieutenant!
Okay, then you'll need this...
Welcome to Delta
Squadron, Private.
April, Vega's working. Sorry.
Nah, it's no problem, Christine.
Hey, Treeya. Uh, I mean... Hi.
Lieutenant.
[April] Why you always
gotta stare at her like that?
[April grunts]
I'm not staring‐‐
and soldiers don't pout.
Come here. I need a new lookout.
Whaddaya say, huh?
Only if you teach me
how to shoot that.
[Vega] Well... I don't
think your mom
would like that too much...
No, Mommy says
it's a good thing!
She says you're gonna
use it to protect us
if the bad guys come back!
Is that true? Are you gonna?
She's right; that's
exactly what I'll do.
And you can help me by stayin'
on the lookout, Private.
Yes, sir, Lieutenant
James! Hoo‐rah!
[April laughs]
You sure have a way
with that one, Vega.
I'd swear she was
your little sister.
Ew, gross! We're married.
Okay, "Marine," I think
you've pestered Vega
enough for one day.
[Vega] Okay, off you go.
There... Thanks, Vega.
'Kay! Over and out, sir.
[Vega] You be good.
‐‐[Tech 2] Later days.
‐‐[Tech 1] See you, Vega.
Surely this can't be right...
[Vega sighs]
[Mason] You're
killing us, chief.
Better make a move
while the gettin's good.
Unless you're cool with me
cutting in on your action.
Look, I've already
tried talking to her...
She just doesn't seem all
that interested, you know?
If blushing and sighing's
your idea of talk, man,
then we really need to
work on your delivery.
[Vega gasps] April's badge!
[Essex] Seriously.
I don't get it.
What's he see in her, anyway?
You kidding me? You
got eyes, don'tcha?
Everybody's crazy
for some blue.
[laughter]
[Vega] Hm?
[Vega sighs]
Whoa... Just in the
nick of time, right?
Hey, you're Vega, aren't ya?
Saw ya on the vids...
Hope you don't
mind me saying it,
but you really gave those Blood
Pack sons of bitches what‐for
a couple of years back...
Made me proud to be a human.
And you are...?
Right, where's my manners?
Name's Messner,
private importer.
I run goods all over
the Terminus‐‐
vehicles, consumables,
the usual boring stuff...
It pays the bills.
[Messner] Ah, a hero
and a gentleman!
[Messner laughs]
Must be nice havin' him around.
Some would say.
Hey, wait a second...
What's that supposed to mean?
[Messner] So, uh...
this is new...
You mind ringing up
the powers that be
and gettin' this bad boy open?
[Vega] Hey, Whitman...
You gonna make me
say "pretty please" or what?
C'mon, man, let us in.
Afraid I can't, Vega. I'm sorry.
We've upped security
for classified ops
and you're not
cleared for entry.
You either, Doc.
There are materials in
the research department
that belong to me! You
cannot just lock me out!
I know, but it's not my call.
You can lodge a complaint with
Command if you want, but...
...it's not gonna get you in
here any quicker. I'm sorry.
[Treeya sighs] Typical...
[Vega] Hey! I'll get
your stuff back!
Let go of my arm...
Sad to say, this is the sort
of idiocy I've had to deal with
since you Alliance grunts
took over our research post.
Like you even care.
Cut 'em some slack, huh?
I'm sure the Alliance
has a good reason
for locking down your lab.
That they declined to share
with their own security
detail? Spare me.
Roger that... It's Captain Toni.
He wants to see us ASAP.
I can help you with
your work, Treeya, just‐‐
Really? So suddenly
you're an archaeologist?
You don't know
anything about it.
Why, 'cause I'm a grunt? Try me.
Vega! The boys in
Control are picking up
some kind of anomalous signal
out of Sector Nine,
near the old ruins.
I knew that something
seemed off...
Whatever it is out there,
Doctor, it's playing hell
with our long‐range
communications.
Might be one of your
relics. Might not be.
Either way, I need it gone.
Understood, Captain.
We'll take care of it.
I want you all combat‐ready,
in case there are any hostiles
who wanna get cute...
And last bit of bad news,
our APC is down for a
suspension overhaul,
so it looks like you'll have to
double‐time it out
there on foot.
[Messner clears his throat]
Had a Volus pay me in trade a
while back with a used Mako.
What say we give
it a test‐drive?
Treeya, you and Messner
are with Milque back there.
Mason, you be ready to
back us up with the Mako.
Roger that.
Let's go, Delta Squad!
Cut south and flank
the signal point.
[Essex grunts affirmatively]
Nicky, find a good spot
for Milque to set up
his sniper rifle.
Scanning the area.
‐‐Hill looks good.
‐‐Hill looks good...
‐‐Smart‐ass.
‐‐I just said that.
‐‐Hill it is!
Nicky... you're with me...
We're going up the middle
for a closer look.
Yes, sir!
[Vega] What've you got for me?
[Nicky] I don't know
what it is, but...
...Captain Toni wasn't kidding
about the interference!
[Vega] Bounce your scan over
to the doctor's omni‐tool.
[Nicky] On it.
[Vega] Is this one of
your relics, Treeya?
I can't make it out very
clearly in the image...
... but the object is not
native to this system,
I'm sure of that much.
Never seen anything
like it before.
Didn't fall out of
the sky, either.
That crater's too small
for a re‐entry impact.
But hey, look on
the bright side‐‐
at least it's not
taking potshots at us.
Wherever it came from,
it's emitting a powerful
wide‐frequency burst;
no question it's what's
jamming our communications.
I think it's done enough
jamming for one day.
[Essex] Boom time?
No! You can't just
destroy an artifact
because you don't
understand it! Stop!
‐‐[Treeya gasps]
‐‐Whoa, hold it there, Doc.
[Treeya breathes]
[Milque] That last
step's a doozy.
[Treeya gasps]
[Treeya shudders]
[Milque chuckles]
Graceful.
Sorry, Treeya, but this isn't
an archaeology expedition.
Command sent us
here with orders
to take out a potential
threat, not study history.
[Milque] One more step and
she would've been history.
[Vega grunts] What
was that, Milque?
[Treeya] Nothing!
It's nothing...
The Mako's the other way.
Where are you going?
I can still figure out
where it came from.
I've never seen
anyplace like this.
Brutes like you could never
hope to appreciate it.
Just don't touch anything.
[Mason] Wow... Still
running after, what...
five thousand years
or something?
[Treeya] Five? That's nothing.
More like seventy thousand,
at the very least.
Seventy thousand?!
[Messner whistles]
[Treeya] That shouldn't
surprise you.
After all, the Protheans
are long gone,
but the mass relays they built
are still the cornerstone
of intergalactic travel.
[Nicky] True enough,
but flying into a relay
is a pretty simple task...
What you're doing... is actively
interacting with this device!
[Treeya] Just think of it...
Civilization as we know it
depends entirely on the
mass effect fields created
by the exposure of Element
Zero to electrical current.
Transportation...
Communication...
Even those weapons of
which you're so fond.
[Messner] It is handy,
I'll give ya that...
[Vega] So what went wrong?
If these Protheans
were so powerful,
what happened to them?
Fifty thousand years ago,
they simply vanished...
For better or worse,
Lieutenant...
that question's become
my life's work...
My mentor Liara T'Soni's
made great strides
towards solving it‐‐
maybe she can help.
Dr. Nuwani. It's
good to see you.
You as well, Dr. T'Soni.
I found an unknown object
in the ruins on Fehl Prime
and wanted to get your input.
[Messner] Is it my imagination,
or do they all look alike?
[Liara] Hmm...
Well, it's not Prothean,
I can tell you that...
In fact, it doesn't match
anything I've ever seen.
Based on the cursory
inspection I've given it so far,
these are some very
advanced bio‐mechanics.
[Liara] This could
be Reaper tech.
They're an ancient race of
sentient starships who've
marked all other intelligent
life for destruction...
Hence their attack
on the Citadel.
[Messner] Uh, hold up‐‐that ship
went for the Alliance's jugular
because it wanted to?
Don't tell me you believe that!
With all due respect,
Dr. T'Soni, that ship
was nothing more
than a dreadnaught
piloted by a rogue
Spectre agent.
I saw it, Treeya.
I heard it speak.
What's more, I am sure that
the Reapers are responsible
for the Prothean disappearance
fifty thousand years ago.
And now after the information‐‐
[Treeya] Dr. T'Soni?
Nicky. Find that signal.
So talking starships ate
your space mechanics...
You buy any of that?
I wouldn't wait on that
signal... It's long gone.
I respect Dr. T'Soni and her
contributions to the field,
but the fact remains that
none of the major civilizations
have any record of
the Reapers' existence.
The truth is, she's become
obsessed with them‐‐
to the detriment of her career
and her professional reputation.
She has been regarded
as little more than a...
conspiracy theorist
ever since she ran off with
your Commander Shepard.
Hold on! You mean she actually
knew Shepard personally?!
Hey! Careful!
Finally, they got something
to talk about... Way to go.
[Vega groans]
[Toni] Delta Squadron!
Come in, over!
Say again? It's no good.
We're getting that
interference again. Except...
[Vega] Except what?
[Nicky shudders]
Back to the colony! Now!
[scattered hushed dialogue]
[colonists gasp]
[screams from crowd]
[men scream]
Move it, people!
[Toni grunts]
Go! Everyone, get to the vault!
[Toni grunts, gasps]
[scattered yells and shrieks]
[various indistinct
shouts and yells]
[Whitman] I'm sorry,
I have my orders!
I can't let you in without
proper authorization!
[colonist] So you're just
gonna let us die out here?
Well, I say... screw that!
[indistinct dialogue from crowd]
[indistinct yells and
screams from crowd]
[pained yells and screams,
sound of gunfire]
[Milque] There...
I got multiple targets.
[Nicky] Whoa‐‐what the
heck are those things?
Looks like they're all
carrying weapons...
Great, so I guess we can
rule out a social visit...
[Nicky] I don't see
any of the colonists...
Oh, shit... Get down!
[grunting]
[Vega] You ever seen
these things before?
No, never... Though that
ship appears to be based
on the same technology
as the object we found.
[Vega] Alright‐‐then until we
know what's going on here,
we assume they're hostile.
We go in stealth for recon,
through the sinkhole,
below their sight lines. Clear?
Vega, maybe someone
should stay back on lookout?
Someone's gotta watch the Mako.
[Kamille] Right‐‐more like
someone's gotta grow a pair.
Just sayin'.
[Essex grunts]
[Vega] Come on.
Watch your step.
[Vega and Treeya gasp]
[Essex gasps]
Where's Vega and Treeya?
[Kamille] Still over there.
Great, so they can fly...
Suddenly, I'm missin'
the Blood Pack...
[Vega sniffs]
Come on.
[Essex] Man, there's
swarms of 'em up there...
So where do you think
all the colonists went?
[Vega] Stay here!
[Vega] Hey... Can you hear me?
He's got a pulse...
It's like he's been...
... paralyzed...
What the hell...?
There's no visible
signs of battle...
[woman's voice screams]
[Vega] Let's go!
[Vega] Hold up.
Okay, we're close,
but we're about
to lose our overhead cover.
We'll be easy to spot
if we move as a group.
All of you stay here
while I check it out.
[Vega grunts]
I'm coming with you!
Wait! Treeya!
Vega...
Cállate.
[Treeya exhales]
[Treeya sighs]
I told you to stay.
[Vega] Fine.
[April pants intensely]
[April] Mommy! Help!
[Christine] April! We've gotta
keep running, baby!
[Christine pants,
April whimpers]
[Christine gasps]
[April shudders]
Mommy!!
[Vega grunts]
[Vega] No...
[Vega pants]
[Vega] Christine...? Damn it!
[Vega grunts]
[Vega] April? No...
No, no, no, no, no, no!
You gotta hang on for
me there, soldier...
I'll find a way to save you...
Yo prometo...
[Treeya] Are they...?
[Vega] No... Just paralyzed,
like the others.
They're coming... This way!
[Treeya gasps]
[Treeya] What are they doing?
[Vega] We go out there now,
we just get ourselves killed.
There'll be a chance
to help them...
But we have got to be smart.
[Vega] Let's get
back to the squad...
[Mason] We saw 'em carrying
people off in those pod things.
Question is, what for?
[Essex] Gotta be for
some kinda experiments
or somethin', ya think?
Yeah, or maybe for food.
[disapproving grunts]
Or maybe not.
I don't give a damn
what their reasons are.
All I care about now is
getting everyone back safely.
Let's save the
"why's" for later
and start coming up
with a plan of attack.
For starters, how 'bout we get
ahold of some bigger guns?
Yo, Nicky.
Yes, sir.
[Vega] Check our stores;
see what we've got that
can take on that ship.
Well, not to interrupt, but...
is that big cannon
just for show?
[Vega] Right. Here's the plan.
We make our way to the
top of the security tower
to activate the turret.
But we'll need a diversion
while it's powering up.
Flyboy, you light up the fuel
stores to draw 'em away from us,
then you run like hell. Got it?
[Mason] Shit, I'm gonna
quit for real this time.
[Vega] The rest of
us will move up
along the
maintenance scaffolds.
Milque, I'm counting on
you to watch our backs.
[Milque] Mm‐hmm...
Just once, I wish someone would
watch my back for a change...
I can't even count all
these damn things!
[Vega] Essex, Kamille‐‐you two
stand here and stay guard.
Alright, let's move!
Lead the way, chief.
[sound of footsteps,
trailing off]
Hey. What do ya know?
We're finally alone.
Don't you ever quit?
Now, we can get this
thing online, right?
Absolutely.
That's the easy part.
Problem's gonna be waiting
for the cannon to fully charge.
It's probably a good idea
to stay away from the
windows right now.
[Treeya] What's happening
to our people, Lieutenant?
[Vega] Hold on... We
can track their omnis
to see where
they've been taken.
Okay, here it is.
Looks likes the hostiles
have 'em split
into two groups...
[Treeya] So they're being
stowed for transport? But why?
[Nicky] Cannon fifty
percent charged.
[Vega] Ahh...! This is
taking way too long.
Any way to speed things up?
[Nicky] I'm doing
what I can, sir.
[Messner] Yeah, well,
it's not enough.
The bugs are
gonna start heading
back this way any second.
Can we activate the turret
with the charge we've got?
Well, theoretically, but
there's no way of knowing
whether or not it'll
do any damage.
Wouldn't decreased
destructive power
be ideal in this situation?
We want to minimize the risk
to the colonists on board, yes?
Good point. We'll fire
with what's built up.
Looks like they've got it ready.
Sure took 'em long enough.
Alright. The turret's in
position. Awaiting your order.
Fire!
[Nicky] Our shot's
been deflected!
[Vega] Son of a...! Damn it!
[Nicky] Enemy drones
en route, sir!
Go! All of you!
Nicky, stay with Messner!
[Nicky] Yes, sir!
[Vega] Treeya...
Hey, snap out of it!
Let's go! Treeya!
[Treeya shudders]
[Vega] Dios mio...
[Milque] Shit,
that's not good...
Aah!
‐‐[Milque] Mason!
‐‐Yeah, you can thank me later.
Now how 'bout we get
the hell outta here?
[Vega grunts, yells]
[Treeya cries out]
[Vega braces]
[Vega] Hang on to me!
[Vega and Treeya grunt]
We made it...
[Vega] Not yet.
Come on... Jump!
[Essex] Vega!
[Kamille] Vega!
Treeya! Over here!
[Vega grunts]
[Essex] Almost there!
You got it!
[Kamille] You better
get her inside.
[Essex grunts]
I'm out!
[Essex] Guns are no good
against these swarms anyway!
Get below with the others!
[Kamille] Gah!
[Kamille struggles, screams]
Kamille!
[Vega] What's the hold‐up,
Nicky?! Get the door closed!
Almost there!
[Vega] Hurry!
[Vega growls]
[Essex] Son of a bitch‐‐
they just keep coming!
[Milque] Comin' through!
I'll be damned...
[Mason exhales]
[Mason] I think that
oughta buy us some time...
[Vega] How we doin'
on the door, Nicky?
All over it, sir...
I'm sealing it up now.
[Vega] Everybody, inside!
Where the hell's Kammy?
[Essex sighs]
I'm sorry, man. They got her.
[Mason gasps]
What?! How?! I thought you
were supposed to have her back!
[Essex] Oh, shit!
[Mason grunts]
[Essex and Mason yell]
[Vega] What's going on?
Little ones, crawling through
the gaps! They're inside!
Just go, Mason! Move it!
Guns don't work on
these little bastards!
I'll have to use my
biotics to hold 'em back!
[Nicky] Door's closing, people!
Stand clear of the hatch!
Come on, you two,
stop screwin' around!
[Mason grunts]
[Mason] Essex, you
dumbass! Get in here!
You're steppin' all
over my big moment!
C'mon, man... Just trying
to look cool before I die...
[Vega and Milque pant]
Alliance Command,
this is Fehl Prime...
The colony is under attack...
Repeat, the colony
is under attack...
Alliance Command, do you co‐‐
[Vega] How's Essex?
[Milque] He got stung,
but... he's alive...
It's only a matter of time
before they figure
out where we are.
I'm with the doc. We're
sittin' ducks in this place.
Here... I say we get to the
shuttle and break for orbit.
Now you're talking. We can send
out a distress call to Alliance
once we're clear of
the jamming signal.
Uh, sir. Are you seeing
what I'm seeing?
[gasps]
[Mason] Son of a bitch...
You're kidding me, right?
[Messner sighs] You should
have waited, Lieutenant.
[Mason exhales lightly]
"Should have waited"? For what?
[Treeya moans]
[Messner] The cannon
was only at half power
when he fired on their ship.
[Mason] That true?
Our only shot, and you blew it?
It was my fault.
I made the call...
I was just trying
to minimize any
collateral damage.
"Collateral damage"?! What the
hell you call all this, man?!
We lost Kamille out there!
I know! But I haven't
given up on Kamille yet‐‐
or any of our people!
We fight smart,
we fight together,
and we will get them
back! Who's with me?!
I am, sir... We're Marines,
it's what we do.
Now, if Essex is still
alive out there,
then I'm goin' out to get him.
I'll help.
[Vega] How's he
holding up, Nicky?
[Nicky] There's been no trauma
to his circulatory or
respiratory systems...
[Treeya] And no sign of
neurological impairment.
[Nicky] He just can't move.
We'll get you back on your feet,
Essex. You just hang in there.
Not like he's got a choice...
[Nicky] Entire colonies
vanishing overnight...
I thought it was just a
silly rumor... but now...
[Treeya] The Alliance
must not have known
what sort of foe they
were up against...
I mean, they certainly
didn't prepare
any of us for this contingency.
They lacked the proper intel...
It looks as though
they did know
about the bugs and
their paralytic sting,
but I'm not seeing
anything on file
about those humanoid
raiders or their ship.
Wait... There's a note at
the bottom of this report...
Something about work having been
done on a potential antidote...?
Good catch...
Keep poking around...
If they perfected a cure,
I want to track it down and
stick Essex with it ASAP.
‐‐[Nicky] Vega!
‐‐What'd you find?
[Nicky] A file on
our new friend.
He's one of the
reasons security's
been beefed up around here.
According to the Alliance,
Messner's been spying on us
and reporting back to his
employer... AKA Cerberus.
[Vega] What?!
[Messner] Well,
this is awkward.
[Treeya] Wait, what is Cerberus?
[Vega] A bunch of damn
human supremacists!
[Messner scoffs] Says you...
[Vega growls] Pendejo!
[Messner] Temper, temper...!
They think humans should
be top dog in the galaxy,
and do whatever it takes
to make that happen,
no matter who gets
caught in the crossfire!
[Messner] You get that
from a leaflet, Vega...?
Hey, I know our bosses
don't see eye‐to‐eye,
but we're on the same
team for a change.
Cerberus was trying to
cook up an antidote, too...
They wanted me to figure
out the abductions...
Think of all the people
we can save with this info!
[Vega] We still don't know
who these bastards are.
[Messner grunts]
Cerberus knows...
Knowing stuff is
kind of our thing.
We've taken to calling
'em... Collectors.
[Mason] Bullshit.
Hey, we're a group with
a profound distrust
of alien species.
We keep tabs on all of 'em,
even the mythical ones...
In stories, they show up,
"collect" some
unwitting species,
and take it back home,
beyond some distant mass relay.
[Vega] Yeah? What for?
[Messner] Your guess
is as good as mine...
They don't leave a
forwarding address,
and it's a one‐way trip
for whatever they grab...
That's everything Cerberus
knows about 'em, honest.
[Treeya] I very much doubt that.
Hey... come on...
I can't help but wonder if these
"Collectors" had anything to do
with the mass disappearance
of the Protheans.
[repetitive, echoing thud]
[Milque] What was that?!
[Messner] I didn't do it.
[Vega exhales] It's
coming from downstairs!
[Brood grunts]
I remember you...
The Alliance marines who
bested the Blood Pack,
and their battlemaster, Vega.
Thought they shipped
you off to the Citadel
months ago to stand trial.
They didn't have the quad.
So they kept me here
as a test subject.
Figured it was safer
than transporting me.
I know the score, human.
You're outnumbered
and outgunned,
but I can get you
off this rock.
All you have to do
is open the cage.
[Milque] Keep on dreaming, ugly.
You're still a Blood
Pack mercenary.
I think we'll take our
chances with the bugs.
[Mason huffs]
[Brood] Mmm...
[Treeya] Vega? Are you alright?
[Vega] Christine and April...
They counted on me
to protect them.
Do you think I made the wrong
decision back there, Treeya?
I think you did what any
good leader would do...
There was no "right"
choice, so you made
what you thought was
the "best" choice.
If I were Commander Shepard,
I would have found a way
to save all those people.
Well, you're not Shepard;
you're James Vega.
You know, it's funny‐‐
Admiral Hackett gave me
some similar advice once...
I know how hard you try
to protect everyone...
Sometimes, circumstances
make that impossible...
You can't blame yourself, James.
Vega! Doc! I think
I found something
you're gonna want to see...!
[Nicky] I've been looking
through these science files
like you told me to,
and I tracked down
the latest version
of the antidote.
It tested at a
success rate of 69%.
How many humans have they
tried this stuff out on, Nicky?
Essex would be the first.
[Vega sighs] Guess we don't
have much of a choice...
[Treeya] This is the one, Vega.
How do we know
it won't kill him?
We don't... But Essex is a
stubborn bastard. Do it, Treeya.
[Treeya] Administering antidote.
[Nicky sighs]
Metabolic‐stasis...
[Vega] English, Nicky.
[Nicky] It's not working.
[Vega sighs]
[repetitive, echoing thud]
[gasps]
That krogan doesn't
know when to give up.
[Vega growls]
Vega... We got
company... It's for you.
[booming thud]
[Vega grunts lightly]
So what is it?
[Milque] Nothing friendly,
that's for sure.
Here they come.
[Mason grunts]
[electronic zipping noise]
[Mason gasps]
[Mason] Kamille...?
That you? Kammy?!
Wait! Mason!
[Mason pants, laughs]
[Milque] Mason!
[Milque] Shit! What the
hell is that thing?!
[Vega] Fall back! Nicky,
find us a way outta here!
[Milque] That armor's
too damn thick!
[NIcky] All clear...! This way!
Treeya...!
[Treeya pants]
What about him...?
[creature roars]
[Vega] No time!
[Treeya and Vega pant]
[Nicky] I'm locking down the
security doors behind us.
It should buy us a minute!
[Vega] Nice work, Nicky!
[panting continues]
[Vega] Hey, hold up!
What's wrong, sir...?
The exit is this way!
[Vega] We're taking a
quick detour... Follow me!
[Vega] You said you can
get us off this planet.
You ready to make good?
I had a ship hidden nearby;
as far as I know,
it's still there.
[Treeya] He's lying!
We can't trust him...
[Vega] We have to
trust him, Treeya...
We've got nothing to lose;
if he can't help us,
everyone dies, him too.
Heh. You spared my life
two years ago, Vega.
I repay my debts.
Now... let's hurry.
[Nicky] All clear!
[Brood] This way!
[Brood roars]
[Brood] Get in.
[Brood] Now... where to?
[Vega] Anywhere...
Just get us outta here!
What's going on?
[Brood] Hard to say...
Friends of yours?
[Vega growls]
[Vega] Keep it off us! Hit it
with everything you've got!
Ahh!
[Milque] Any better
ideas, chief?!
[Vega] Don't stop! Keep firing!
[grunts]
[Milque] How many arms
does this thing got?!
Vega!
[Nicky] Augh!
[Vega] Nicky!!
[Vega gasps]
[Essex] Ha, ha, ha!
[Essex roars]
What the hell...?
Hey, it's Essex!
[Essex yells, grunts]
[Vega] Outta the way!
[Vega grunts]
[Vega groans]
[Vega growls]
Chew on this!
[Vega pants]
Heads up, Vega...! I'm comin'!
[Essex] Got'cha!
[creature shrieks]
[Nicky shudders]
[Vega] Nicky!
How bad is it?
That depends, sir...
Does... anyone else see Essex?
It's really me, kid...
Still in the flesh,
thanks to you...
Your antidote worked.
We did it, Doc.
You did real good, Nicky...
Now, you hold on, Marine.
I'm with you, sir... We've
still gotta save our people...
[Nicky exhales weakly]
[Vega sighs]
No...
[Messner] That's a damn shame...
So... what do we do now?
We'll be lucky to get off
the ground in this bucket...
Oh, she'll get off the
ground‐‐I guarantee that!
I just won't promise
how far she'll go...
Then how 'bout the old ruins;
can we make it
at least that far?
It's gotta be better than here.
What's the difference?
They'll shoot us down
the second we're airborne.
[Messner] Any way you slice it,
our odds are long.
Collectors don't make a
habit of leaving witnesses.
Do you have any weapons?
Hmph! What kind of
a question is that?
You're speaking to a krogan.
[Brood] We live for weapons.
[Vega] Our only real option now
is to complete our
initial objective...
We have to disable the
Collector ship's engines...
But we'll have to do
it from the inside.
What? That's suicide!
The creepy eye thing'll
open up before we get close!
We'd be... well... evaporated.
That's just about
the gist of it.
[Messner] Hell, even
factoring out the eye,
we'd never break
through their shields.
Why not fly directly
into the eye?
Take the fight to them
and punch through
where they least expect it.
What...? It's an idea.
As crazy as that sounds...
I think you might actually
be on to something there.
Way I see it, we can
take a chance...
or we can choke to
death in this pit...
Good marines laid
down their lives
for the people
trapped up there,
and I'll be damned if I'm gonna
let their sacrifice
be for nothing!
If I go out, I'm going out
fighting for their memory...
Anybody here feels the same way,
you're welcome to join me.
Essex, you in?
[Essex] Hm.
[Essex] Well, I suppose
the fumes these tanks
are spewing out would
give us some cover...
This swill tastes
of varren dung!
My ship's cannon is
still operational...
If we get close enough,
we can blast our way inside.
Then it's just a matter
of reaching the others...
And once we
administer the antidote,
maybe then they
can join the fight.
[Milque sighs]
Give me that damn thing...
But I'm still calling
this a suicide mission.
I'll need more than a
drink to change my mind.
Look, Milque... You've been
right about everything so far...
But you gotta be wrong sometime,
and I'd say you're about due.
Whoa, man...
That's harsh drivin'!
[Brood] We're in, aren't we?
[Messner] You say that
like it's a good thing.
[Milque] Look at all of 'em...
I guess we're the only
ones who made it
outta the colony... Lucky, huh?
Yeah, tell that to
Kamille and Nicky.
What do they want with
all these humans, anyway?
Ah, I hate bugs
on my windshield.
We gotta stop this ship;
head for the drive core!
Let's try a short cut.
Wait‐‐do you even know
where you're going?!
[Brood] No, I just want to smash
a few more walls! Hang on!
[Vega] Here! This is it!
[Vega] Essex, Milque‐‐
port side! Let's go!
[Essex] Yeah...! Come on!
Who wants some?!
[Vega grunts]
[Essex] Here...! You like that?!
Payback's a bitch, huh?!
[Milque] Behind us!
[Treeya] Vega!
[Vega] Thanks... Watch it!
Nice shooting...
I think you're a natural.
Thanks.
[Vega] Brood! Take
out that drive core!
On it.
[Messner] Sorry, I
can't let you do that.
[Brood grunts]
Buh‐bye...
[Essex struggles]
Dammit...!
[Messner] Woo!
Rise and shine, Doc!
This is the moment you
don't want to miss!
From the sound of things,
your colony's just been
reduced to a pile of ashes.
[Messner] You made
quite a mess down there,
and Collectors aren't
too big on evidence.
But hey, you fought the
good fight‐‐right, Doc?
These guys usually don't
face much resistance.
Don't beat yourself up.
You've been working for them...
How could you do this?
[Messner] I've saved more
than I've sacrificed, Doctor.
If you weren't so hung up
on petty details,
you'd realize that.
[Treeya] How dare you...?!
Those are innocent lives
you destroyed, Messner!
They were your own people!
Look, everything
I've done has been
in pursuit of Cerberus goals...
After we figured out the
Collectors were the ones
making off with the colonists,
I got in touch, I lured
them out with a colony
that would be easy
pickings, and voila.
[Treeya] That artifact
among the ruins...
The one that jammed our
long‐range communications...
You put that there!
You were summoning them!
But to what end?
What was Cerberus thinking?!
[Messner] Frankly, that we might
learn something‐‐and we have.
Guilt‐trip me all you want,
I've gathered data on
their ships and weapons,
ascertained their strengths
and weaknesses‐‐
hell, I even know
about their home base,
out beyond Omega Four relay...
Just think of all
the knowledge!
Don't tell me that
doesn't excite you!
All it does is sicken me!
None of that is worth the cost!
Gotta wonder, though...
Why are they juicing us...?
They're not using that
DNA slurry for food,
I can tell you that much.
Tell you what...
I'm gonna let you
put that brain of
yours to use, Doc.
I've got a puzzle
that needs solving,
and you're just the
asari for the job...
Figure it out fast enough,
and you might be able to
save some colonists, hm?
And after I do... What then?
You paralyze me
and pack me away?
Hey, I'm just giving
you a chance
to do something
important with your life!
And as you're about to
find out... I'm not asking.
[Treeya struggles]
[Treeya] No! Let go of me!
You won't get away
with this! Vega! Vega!
[Vega snarls, grunts]
[Vega] Oye! Feo!
[Vega grunts]
[Vega pants]
[Vega yells]
[Vega] Sweet dreams, asshole.
[unidentified groaning]
[Vega] Brood...? Brood!
[Brood struggles] Vega...?
[Vega] I'm here.
Here... Take my power cell.
You'll need it...
[Brood coughs]
And what about you, big man?
I'm finished. But maybe
you can still use it
to fight your way out.
You freed me from that cage,
Vega, and gave me the chance
to die with honor in battle,
the way a krogan should...
For that... I owe you a
debt I can never repay...
[Brood exhales]
Vaya con Dios, hermano.
[Essex] So‐‐no
biotics... no guns...
[Essex sighs] All I've got is my
knife and a couple of grenades.
Same here. We're pretty
much dead in the water, huh?
Not quite. Brood gave me a
power cell for you, Essex...
Better yet... We've still
got the antidote, too.
[Milque] Wait‐‐but
we never took it.
So why didn't we stay
paralyzed like the others?
[Vega laughs] C'mon,
man... Why you think
our last drink
tasted like shit?
You mean you just spiked
it without telling us?!
Seemed like a pretty
smart move at the time.
Great... So what's our move now?
Free the colonists...
and get the hell out.
[Essex] Hm.
You, uh... really think it's
going to be that easy?
No, no, but I think we
can get the Collectors'
processing system to
do most of the work.
And how we gonna do that?!
They run the pods through here
on this conveyor line, right?
So what do you wanna
bet's on the other end?
The holding area we
saw when we flew in...!
[Vega] Right. So I'll rig
the antidote to disperse
and send the pod
back down the line.
You guys get started
on the people in here.
[Milque coughs] Smells even
worse than it tastes!
[Vega] Here we go...
Pod's away. Cross your fingers.
[Milque] Hey, Vega... So once
we wake everyone up...
We're already off planet...
How do we get off this ship?
[Vega] April...
Earth to Vega‐‐
you listening, man?!
[Vega] I hear you,
Milque. Give me a sec...
I just found April.
[Milque] Tch...
[Vega] Hey, soldier,
you're gonna be alright.
Just one more thing I need
to do and then I'll be back.
Alright! Milque! Essex!
Time to move‐‐let's go!
We need to get our
hands on Messner.
This is Prothean
technology, right?
Some kind of telepathic
data repository?
I don't know what it's
doing on a Collector ship,
but I want to find out.
I wouldn't have dragged you down
here except that, well, you see,
it doesn't seem to interact with
human minds all that well...
I threw some "volunteers"
at it, just to be safe,
and it fried their
cerebral cortices.
But Doc, you're a whole
different breed of guinea pig...
Yeah... You'll do it willingly.
'Cause maybe it'll tell you what
happened to your Protheans,
and maybe that information
helps you save some lives.
[Messner] C'mon.
You know you wanna.
[Treeya shivers]
[Treeya gasps]
[Reaper] You will submit.
[Reaper] You will ascend.
[Reaper] And you will serve.
What'd you see?!
Liara T'Soni... She
was right all along
about the fate of
the Protheans.
Fifty thousand years ago,
the Reapers wiped them out.
Why do the Collectors
have this thing?
[Treeya sighs]
They are the Protheans...
remade by the Reapers
to serve them.
I need to know why Collectors
are taking human colonies!
Ask it yourself!
Once I get this last
piece of the puzzle,
I'll know all their secrets!
I will own them!
‐‐Do it again!
‐‐[Treeya] No!
[Messner] And this time,
tell me everything!
They're building
Reapers... out of...
... our DNA.
Let me get this straight.
We swoop in, kick Messner's ass,
grab Treeya, and bolt‐‐
that's the plan?
And one more thing: the intel
Messner has on the Collectors
will help Alliance Command
protect hundreds of colonies‐‐
thousands, maybe
millions of lives.
We bring it back,
whatever it takes.
Takin' a page from
Shepard's book, huh?
Save the girl, save the galaxy,
go home heroes.
That about right?
Maybe... But right now,
I'll settle for just
getting us all home.
I've done what you asked,
now let me go, this instant‐‐
Ah, shut up.
[Messner] Hah!
It recorded! Yes! Now I
have everything I need!
[Treeya] Take your hands off me!
[Messner] I'm on your side!
[Essex] Why aren't
they attacking?
It's like they're not
even looking for us.
[Milque] Far as they know,
we're already juiced.
Probably never had
anyone escape before.
[Essex] That'll
change in a hurry
once the all colonists
start waking up.
We need to get 'em outta here.
Yeah, and I think we
might just be in luck.
Say, Milque. You're up.
I am?! For what?!
Remind me... You started in
the pilot's program, right?
Think I remember
hearing that once.
Yeahhh...? And I got kicked out,
'cause I couldn't fly for shit.
What're y‐‐oh, fuck that!
Guess you're just
gonna have to learn
in a hurry, aren't ya? Hop on.
[Vega] We've still got a fix
on Treeya's omni‐tool.
That's where me and
Essex are headed.
You get this bucket in the air
and come pick us up. Got it?
Okay, but don't
complain if I'm late!
[Vega] Just be there.
Sure, guys... but if I
actually pull this off,
this time, free drinks for life
are not even gonna cover it...
[VI Translator] Your usefulness
has decreased to zero, human.
You have allowed
Alliance soldiers
to threaten our mandate.
Hey, without me, those soldiers
would've taken out
your drive core.
How 'bout a little appreciation?
[VI Translator] Negative.
It is time for your ascension.
[Messner] What...?
No way! Don't even try it!
Anything happens to me,
this data goes to the Alliance!
[Messner and Treeya pant]
[Messner] I mean it!
I'll give 'em all your secrets!
[VI Translator] Your threats
are meaningless, human.
You really want to take
that chance, do you?
You think you had trouble
with a few Marines?
What're you gonna do when
you find the entire fleet
parked outside the
Omega 4 relay? Huh?!
Would that "threaten
your mandate"?!
Now, now, what you say we
just be reasonable here...
[VI Translator] Incompetence
cannot be tolerated.
In addition to soldiers,
you have allowed this
asari aboard our ship.
She will taint our
human material.
Don't like the blue chick?
Fine! I'll throw 'er out for ya!
Don't touch me, Messner...
[Treeya struggles]
No! Let me out!
[Messner gasps]
You bitch! Give me that!
[Messner grunts]
[Treeya gasps]
[Vega grunts]
[Vega] Treeya!
[VI Translator] Eject the asari!
[Treeya screams]
[Vega] Treeya!
No!
Go on, man; never
keep a lady waiting.
I'll take care of these bugs.
[Vega] Thanks, Essex.
You watch yourself,
Marine. Hoo‐rah!
[Essex grunts]
[Essex] Hngaah!
See ya!
[Essex] You're next, ugly!
[Treeya] Vega!!
[Vega growls] Hang on!
[Treeya screams]
[Vega growls]
Nooo!!
[Vega grunts]
So you took the antidote
when I wasn't lookin', eh?
[Vega groans]
I guess you think you're
pretty clever, don'tcha...
you stupid grunt?!
[Messner and Vega grunt]
[Messner] How's that
workin' out for ya...?!
[Vega groans]
[Messner and Vega pant]
Adios...
[Vega yells]
[Messner shudders]
We're not done. You've still
got something I need.
Try not to die
before I get back.
[Messner shudders]
Come in! Treeya!
Treeya, do you copy?!
[Treeya] Yes, Vega.
I can hear you.
[Vega] Any idea where you are?!
I've started to descend...
into the atmosphere...
But so has the ship‐‐
you don't have much time!
[Vega] I'm coming, Treeya!
[Essex grunts]
[Essex] Heads up, asshole!
[Essex groans]
Still with me, Essex?!
Aw, hell yeah! As long
as they keep on comin',
I'll just keep
knockin' 'em down!
[Essex gasps]
Essex!
[Vega roars]
[Essex gurgles]
[Essex coughs]
[Vega growls, grunts]
[Essex groans]
Collect this... you bitch!
[Essex struggles, yells]
[Vega] Essex!!
Dammit...
[Vega] C'mere!
[Messner groans]
[Vega grunts]
Where's the data?!
[Messner shudders]
[Vega yells]
[Vega grunts, struggles]
[Vega roars, grunts]
[Vega] It's about
damn time, Milque!
Hey! Better late than never!
[indistinct chatter]
Mommy! We can move again!
That's right, honey.
Now, I need you to be
a brave girl for me.
We're gonna be okay.
Yeah! Lieutenant James is
gonna save us. He promised...
But where is he?
He's here... right?
Don't worry, he
hasn't forgotten.
Vega'll be back soon,
I guarantee it.
Yeah, I know that!
But he needs me,
I'm s'posed to be his lookout!
[Christine] April!
[Toni chuckles]
Brave kid you got there.
Come on! The data!
Where the hell is it?!
Listen... I can pay you
as much as you want;
just name your price...
Please, Vega... Help me.
You just can't leave
me here like th‐‐
[Vega] You made your choice.
[Milque] Vega! We got more
drones inbound! Time to go! Now!
Not yet! I haven't found
Messner's data cuff!
[Treeya] He doesn't have it!
What? Treeya‐‐you have it?
Yes.
She's lying! Just...
take me with you!
It's yours! Anything! I don't
wanna die! Not like this!
No! Nooo‐‐!!
[Vega grunts]
We're coming, Treeya!
The Reapers were responsible
for the Prothean disappearance.
You have to warn the Council.
We will; that intel's going
straight to the Alliance!
We'll pick up the
colonists first,
then we're coming after you!
Milque! Track her position‐‐
don't lose her! And punch it!
Roger that.
[Treeya] There's no time, Vega.
You'll have to make a choice...
And the loss of one is better
than the alternative...
One life... in exchange for
the lives of so many others...
I know you'd try to save
everyone if you could.
But circumstances have made
that impossible, I'm afraid.
It's not your fault.
I know you well enough
to know you'll make
the best choice...
and I understand.
[Vega] No!
[Toni] Vega! Come in,
Vega! Do you read?
We're taking fire here, Vega!
We need to evacuate, now!
[Vega] Captain. Lieutenant
Vega here. I copy.
I'm gonna try to
reach you, sir, but...
‐‐[Christine] April!
‐‐[April] Hey, is that James?!
Lieutenant James, can you
hear me? It's Private April!
We're still here! Mommy and
me are waiting for you!
Vega, what do we do, man?!
[Vega pants]
[Treeya] It's okay, Vega...
You can do what needs to
be done. I know you can.
[Vega and Milque grunt]
[Vega yells]
[Treeya gasps, shudders]
We've analyzed
your report, Vega.
Now, is there anything
else you wish to add
to the official record before we
make our final determinations?
No, sir. It's all there.
We understand that
you found yourself
facing a very difficult
decision, Lieutenant...
and you chose to
rescue a single civilian
carrying intel on
these "Collectors,"
at the cost of hundreds
of colonist lives.
[David Anderson] We don't
envy you that position, son.
This intel will
not only help us
stop the Collectors
in the short term...
but in the long term...
it will aid humanity
with ship and
weapons technology.
You also proved the
effectiveness of an antidote
that will protect our people
against the Collector swarms.
In short, you're a hero.
And for exemplary
service to the Alliance,
you're being commended.
Congratulations,
Lieutenant Commander Vega.
[Milque laughs]
Congrats!
Your new orders, son.
Perhaps you'll follow in
Shepard's footsteps after all.
You might even work together.
Sir...?
Turns out the reports of
Shepard's death were...
well, let's just
say "premature."
So, what'd they give you?
Thank you! Let's see it.
Oh, hot damn! They want you
to put in for the N7 program!
You'll be with the
best of the best!
Right up there with
Commander Shepard...
Just sayin... y'know...
[Vega sighs]
Uh... Look, I don't know if
this means anything to you...
But I think you're
a hell of a leader,
and I'd still follow you into
battle anytime, anywhere, sir.
Thanks, but I don't
deserve that.
It's a chance to
start over, isn't it?
To move forward...
To live the hero's life
you've always wanted...
I don't know what I
want anymore, Treeya...
but I know I'm no hero.
Whoa, this looks even worse
than I imagined it would...
[Vega groans]
[Vega] That's April's...
[Vega moans, Treeya gasps]
[April's voice]
You're gonna protect us
if the bad guys come back!
Is it true? Are you gonna?
[Vega groans, Treeya sobs]
How could we let this...?
[Treeya sobs]
[Vega grunts, pants]
[Vega pants]
[Treeya sobs]
Hey! Watch it! What's
wrong with you?!
[Vega pants]
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...!
[Hackett's voice] For exemplary
service to the Alliance,
you're being commended...
You're a hero...
[Vega screams]
[Anderson's voice] In the long
term... it will aid humanity
with ship and weapons
technology...
[Hackett's voice] ...proved the
effectiveness of an antidote...
[Milque's voice] ...you're
a hell of a leader...
The best of the best!
[Treeya's voice]
I know you'd try
to save everyone
if you could...
[April's voice] He promised!
[Christine's voice]
Close your eyes, baby!
[unidentified voice screaming]
‐‐[April's voice] Mommy!
‐‐[Treeya's voice] I know
you'll make the best choice.
[Tech's voice]
They're not comin'!
[April's voice]
We're still here!
[Toni's voice] We need
to evacuate, now!
Vega, what do we do, man?!
[Vega and Milque grunt]
[Vega yells]
What's happening? Where's James?
[indistinct yelling
and dialogue]
They're not comin'
for us... are they?
[Toni] Vega, it's now
or never, son.
[Vega shudders]
[unidentified voice] Look out!
[scattered yelling
and screaming]
[April] Mommy?
Hush... It's okay,
baby... It's okay...
Just close your eyes, honey...
we're going home...
[yelling and screaming
in background]
[yelling and
screaming over radio]
James said he'd come back...
He said he'd save us,
Mommy. He promised!
[April sobs]
[Toni] God have mercy...
[Vega screams]
[Milque gasps] What
did you do, man?!
[Vega and Milque grunt, pant]
[Vega seethes]
Nooo!!
[Vega] I did this!
I made the choice!
I abandoned them to die!
[Vega yells, pants]
I didn't know how to
save you! I'm sorry!
I would've given
my life if I could!
There just wasn't enough time...
Ahem! This is Alliance
Marine... Private April!
Reporting for
duty, sir! Hoo‐rah!
[April giggles] It's too
big for me! Here.
[Vega grunts, pants]
[Vega gasps]
[Treeya] Vega...
Why... Why did you...
choose me...?
Because... at the
time, I thought
I was making the
best decision...
Now... I just don't know.
[Vega] But I'm glad you're here.
[Vega] Maybe it's too
late to change things.
Maybe I can't bring 'em back.
But what I can do is
spend the rest of my life
trying to make it
count. For their sake.
Goodbye, Private April...
We'll never forget you.
[Vega] We'll never
forget any of you.
[N7 Pilot] Coming in hot.
Prep for drop.
[Vega] For Kamille...
[Vega] Mason...
[Vega] For Nicky...
[Vega] Essex...
[Vega] Captain Toni...
[Vega] And for April...
[Vega] Today... I'm gonna
make all of you proud.
Go!
This is what we do, Marines!
Go, go, go, go, go!!