Hello?
Nagisa?
Whoa. Been a while.
Ha! Hey, Karma!
Hold up. How did you...? How did you even get in here?
I thought Isogai had the only key.
I could ask you the same thing, couldn't I?
Guess we're both guilty.
You haven't changed a bit.
What're you doing here all by yourself?
Nothing much.
Everybody else is showing up tomorrow.
Thought I should set something
up to give 'em all a little scare.
Seemed like too good of an opportunity to pass up. Heh.
Why not?
So you won't be here either?
Whaddya gonna do?
Those government agency visits
determine where you'll end up, right?
Aren't your nerves shot?
What, you don't think my acting skills are up to
snuff? Give me some credit. I know how to play the part.
They're looking for an ideal candidate
and that's exactly what they're gonna get.
Just a stepping-stone toward the work I really wanna do.
I'm not gonna let myself trip over it. Trust me.
I admire your resolve, Karma.
You really are a piece of work.
Hey.
Uh?
Whaddya say we go exploring?
This place hasn't changed much either.
You're surprised? We're the ones who bought it.
Yeah, but it was totally your idea. Mountain and all.
I didn't want some random nobody screwing things up.
Well, I mean,
that, and we could turn a healthy profit by rebranding
this dump as a tourist attraction and reselling.
Koro-sensei, I'm back.
Is that...?
Yeah. Looks like he kept his own copy.
Really takes you back.
Class 3-E. The End Class.
Known by us misfits as the Assassination Classroom.
Right! Ready!
Aim!
Fire!
Looking back, that's the day it all started.
Huh? You mean when he took credit for the...?
Yeah.
So I'm the one who blew up the moon.
Huh?
Next year, I intend to do the same to Planet Earth.
But never mind that now.
I'm gonna be your new teacher. Isn't that exciting?
There are so many things wrong with this picture.
It was a strong first impression.
Uh, I'm Karasuma, I'm from the Ministry of Defense.
What, uh... What I'm about to tell
you we in the business call "classified."
Aw, hell. I'll just come right out with it.
I'm gonna need you to kill this
thing for the sake of mankind.
We were all like, "Seriously?
What's this thing doing in our class?"
Threw us for a loop.
What were the chances, right?
Suddenly we were government-sanctioned assassins.
I'd call that a promotion.
We only had a year.
The target was our teacher.
What do you say we hit the books and make
the final year of your lives a productive one?
Yeah.
And not only could he move at the speed of sound,
a straight-up nuclear blast wouldn't tickle him.
Crazy.
He had his weak points, though.
'Course, they turned out to be part of his charm.
Even with this handicap, I'm too fast for you!
Only in your dreams do you have
any hope of getting the deed done!
Oh.
Kill him! Ah!
Ah! Wait, wait, wait!
This wasn't part of the deal! Easy!
Oh, crap! Oh, crap! Oh, crap! Oh, crap! Oh, crap!
Well, your notes are bound to come in handy at some point.
Right! That's why I'm jotting everything down.
I'd even go so far as to say we had our pick.
Kind of strange he wound up having so many, though.
'S just how the Octopus was.
Yeah. He really put himself
on the line to try to teach us.
It seemed to be what he lived for.
That promise, right? Heh.
Teaching was his passion.
Nothing was more important to him.
There's no denying that, huh?
Still, you gotta admit,
his methods were a little unorthodox.
Nagisa. 'Sup?
It's been a while.
Karma. You're back?
I come back from suspension and find
out I've got a cephalopod for a teacher.
Kinda awkward.
Like you didn't take the assassination thing in stride.
Oh, come on.
No way you can be this big of a pushover.
Don't get me wrong: I loved our assignment.
Killing our teacher? Come on.
You definitely threw yourself into it.
More than we did, anyway.
I don't know about that.
I can't be the only kid who's ever
wanted to throw their teacher under the bus.
Literally, I mean.
They play favorites, abuse authority,
always covering their asses.
Not all of 'em, no, but a lot.
See, at that point, I'd had my
fair share of crappy teachers.
If at first I thought the Octopus was in that league,
who could really blame me?
I feel I've taken exceptionally good care of you today.
Hmph.
Just so we're on the same page here,
you pretty much consider
yourself a teacher above all else?
That's right.
Cool.
And you wouldn't think twice about putting
your life on the line to save a student.
What sort of teacher would I be if I did?
That's awesome. Good to know.
So... I can kill you.
Knew there had to be a way.
What's it gonna be, Teach?
You gonna swoop down to save me
and get blasted in the process?
Or you gonna be the sort of
teacher who lets one of your kids die?
But you're absolutely in the right. Not a question.
And I stand by you.
I'm not the bad guy here.
All I did was put a bully in his
place. Little jerk had it comin'.
Are you out of your mind or just stupid?
What possessed you to think attacking your class's
star pupil like a mad dog was something I'd let slide?
This young man happens to have a future!
If this interferes with his exams, it's on my head!
He said he'd stand by me.
So much for that, I guess.
Damn... I'm totally gonna die.
I've been willing to turn a
blind eye on account of your grades,
but you've tried my patience once too often.
This is it. This is how it's gonna go down.
Son of a bitch screwed me over.
So that's it. He's dead to me now.
What are you waiting for, Koro-sensei?
Let's do this!
You either die for real, or I kill your reputation.
Well done!
A splendidly premeditated assassination attempt.
Full marks.
Neat, huh?
I knew your body couldn't take being
plucked out of freefall at the speed of sound,
and had I moved any slower, you would've shot me.
What a tangled, and sticky, web we weave, eh?
What the hell?
Is there anything these tentacles aren't capable of?
Can't shoot me now, can you?
Oh, and for future reference,
students do not die on my watch.
Ever.
Take that to heart for the next time you jump.
I got nothin'. Un-friggin'-believable.
He won't die. The teacher in him especially.
It took some weapons-grade strategizing
on his part to bring me around.
And to think he pulled it off at Mach 20. Heh.
He was the most involved teacher we'd ever had.
Always looking out for us, even though we wanted him dead.
Okie-dokie. Last but not least.
So have you decided on a prospective career, Nagisa m'boy?
Sir, I... I think...
Well, uh... I think I have a talent for killing people.
We all know I don't have any other strengths.
So, I mean, what else can I reasonably shoot for, right?
Koro-sensei, should I...?
Should I become an assassin?
Please, sir. What path should
I follow? 'Cause I don't know.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Nagisa's mother, Ms. Hiromi Shiota.
Yes, yes. Please, have a seat. Good to see you.
Trekking up the mountain is
quite a journey; you must be tired.
Might I offer you a refreshing beverage?
If I may say so, madam, you're quite stunning.
I see where Nagisa gets his looks.
Why, thank you!
You know, if only this one had been born a girl,
I'd have groomed her to be my ideal!
Not quite sure I follow you.
Well, you see, I wasn't allowed to wear my hair long,
and a girl is ever so much prettier with flowing locks.
Oh, Nagisa. What I wouldn't give to
have had such lovely, full-bodied hair.
I was so mad when he started tying it back
for school this year, but it looked so good,
I just had to let it slide, as
long as he wouldn't cut it off.
Ah, but we're here to discuss his future. We
can't afford to discourage them at this age.
Children are such impressionable
creatures, wouldn't you agree?
So I've come here, with all due respect, to
talk about what we can do to get him out of E Class.
And I trust you spoke with Nagisa on the matter?
Oh, he's too young to understand
what's at stake, believe me.
And at any rate, it's my job as a parent to
steer him clear of the mistakes I made at his age.
Mom.
I don't...
Hush up now, sweetheart.
The adults are talking.
Yes, well...
I believe I'm starting to get a clearer picture
of how Nagisa became the person he is today.
Uh!
Yes.
High schools, colleges, and hairstyles,
ma'am, forgive me for saying so,
are decidedly not a parent's prerogative!
I'm sorry. Nagisa must be permitted to live his own life.
You'll get nowhere foisting your complexes onto him.
Ms. Shiota, let me be perfectly clear.
Unless Nagisa so desires,
he will not be allowed to leave E Class.
What the hell is your problem?!
Since when does a teacher talk like that to a parent?!
How dare you! "Foisting my complexes onto him"?
Of course! That explains your attitude at home lately!
This bald idiot's been giving you ideas!
Well, watch this!
When I'm done with you, your eyes will be wide open!
Koro-sensei.
Hmm.
That was a bit more tactless than I'd planned.
Still, though... there's a lesson to be learned here.
You need to communicate your intentions
more clearly from now on, speak your mind.
All obstacles must be removed.
It's time I gave you a new outlook on life.
Nagisa.
Mom?
This is where it all started going downhill.
When you started disobeying me.
This place turned you into a monster.
Burn it to the ground with your own hands.
Get your life back on track.
I don't want to!
I brought you into this world, Nagisa!
I scraped to send you to cram school, then private school!
You have no idea what it cost me!
I do everything for you!
Every night dinner's on the table,
no matter how exhausted I am from work!
Does E Class do that for you?
I made you who you are!
You owe me! You will do what I tell you!
You need to communicate your intentions
more clearly from now on, speak your mind.
Back then, my life was a game.
I was trapped in round two of the Mom RPG.
Yeah, not a real good place to be stuck.
Still, our class made me realize I had special talents.
A gift. Assassination was kind of like my calling.
What was I supposed to do?
Where's a junior high nobody supposed
to go with a skillset like that?
Mom and I were in a stalemate.
Too caught up in our drama to move forward.
But that night...
Mom.
Believe it or not,
I'm giving this class everything I've got.
Before I graduate, I'll get results.
And when I do, I'm cutting my hair,
and paying back every scrap you've spent on me.
If you can't find it in your heart to forgive me...
...then I'll graduate again.
From you.
Mom. I'm grateful that you had me.
Grateful that you raised me.
It may be asking a lot,
but if you can just be happy that you have a child
that, all things considered, turned out relatively okay,
that's all I need to be happy.
Who are you, Nagisa? What in the world have you done?
Certain unsavory types have made
this their after-hours hangout.
I recommend you give the area a wide birth at night.
Now, then, ma'am,
Nagisa has quite a bit of growing left to do, I agree.
What he needs more than anything is a loving mother.
Don't take his stubbornness so personally.
Every little birdie needs to leave the nest at some point.
That's the way of things.
Weird as it sounds,
Koro-sensei made it possible for us
to talk things over like mother and son.
No kidding?
That's when I decided
whatever path I chose, she wouldn't have to worry.
So, uh,
about all the unpleasantness the other evening.
Looking back on it now, I always knew.
My boy's grown up.
He's ready to cut the apron strings.
That business about graduating from me,
you meant every word.
I don't know where you found the strength to
say it, but somewhere along the way, you got tough.
Just, please, for right now,
stay with me a little longer, till you're of age.
That's all I'm asking.
The world'll be yours soon enough.
I'm not ready to let go of my baby just yet, Nagisa.
Whatever else I may be, I'm still your mother.
It was a crazy year, looking back.
I felt like a knot slowly coming undone.
Something inside was breaking free.
I'd never trusted authority figures.
With the Octopus always in our business, though,
well, I guess I loosened up a little.
Yeah.
Koro-sensei had his flaws, but somehow
they came off like part of the plan.
Remember how awkward he could be?
Still, even at his weirdest, you knew he genuinely cared.
True enough, I suppose.
But there were some things he never saw coming.
Like Kayano.
Blew me away.
Who'd have thought she had tentacles?
Talk about flying under the radar.
Let no one say she wasn't a first-rate actress.
I can't imagine how she kept it together for so long.
The pain must've been unbearable.
You'd have never been able to tell, though.
None of us had a clue.
She was obsessed. Hell bent.
Nothing would stand in the way of her revenge.
Right, for her sister's death.
Poor Miss Yukimura.
It wasn't Koro-sensei's fault.
Maybe not, but she died protecting him.
That's why he promised to teach us.
He was an experiment.
A highly developed life form created by a madman.
He said in a year he'd do to the
Earth what he'd done to the moon.
But in reality, it was just a
countdown to his own annihilation.
He was a killing machine living on borrowed time.
Wasn't he supposed to be quite
the looker in his former life?
Supposedly.
Not that he ever backed it up with pictures or anything.
Miss Yukimura was smitten
enough to give him that awful tie.
But if that's her taste.
Yeah, maybe so.
Makes me sad, thinking about her.
Reminds me that we never really had to kill Koro-sensei.
Man, I was royally pissed when you tried
to walk back the assassination agreement.
That was a rough one.
Far as I was concerned,
you were undoing the whole point of the class.
I'm not even sure it's possible.
But instead of killing Koro-sensei,
I think we should try to save him.
Save him?
By like, finding a way to keep him
from self-detonating come March, or what?
Where do we start?
Well, I don't know. Yet. But...
Totally! I'm game!
Koro-sensei's way too good of a
bug-hunting buddy to let explode!
Kurahashi.
Thank you for bringing it up.
If you hadn't said something, I would've.
Saving him's the least we can do.
So you're on board?
But I'm against it.
We get wantin' to save him and all,
but how do we know it's even doable?
Well, I...
Wow. Listen to you.
Getting a tad full of yourself there, chief.
Granted, you're the most gifted one in our class.
But seriously,
we should just up and scrap the whole assassination plan?
What about the underdogs?
Those of us who work ourselves sick just
to squeak by on what little talent we have,
how're we supposed to feel?
You're like a hot chick tellin' her homely
friends there's no point trying to find a man.
Of course you don't have a problem with
changing the rules, you've already won the game.
That-That's not what I'm trying to say.
Besides, I'm not the gifted one. Between
you an' me, you're the better assassin.
Okay, hearing you talk like
that just pisses me off even more.
You know what your problem is, Nagisa?
You've got no respect for how hard
this is for everyone who isn't you.
Whoa, whoa! Where is this coming from?
I'm just telling you how I feel!
Do you have an axe to grind with Koro-sensei or something?
He took us to the movies! He's made learning fun!
That's my point!
Why do you think he bothered? Huh?
He didn't want us to end up like a
bunch of whiney, half-assed jerks!
And look at you!
Assassinating him is what this entire class is
based on. You're just trying to find a loophole!
You wanna undermine what Koro-sensei's done?
Or do you have the mind and the body of a ten-year-old?
Hm?
Huh. What's with that look?
Aw, the itty-bitty mouse wanna roar?
Feel like he could take on a lion?
No, I...
Got somethin' to say?
Kick my ass for once and you can say whatever you like.
Oh, don't be shy. What're you afraid
of? Let's settle this like men. C'mon!
I am not...
...a whiney, half-assed jerk!
You little!
Knock it off!
What the hell are the two of you trying to prove?
Okay. I don't think I can hold him back.
Damn it, Karma! Will you chill out already?
"A good old-fashioned schoolyard fight?
Outstanding!"
I can't really do the voice.
No kidding.
The whole class was split right down the middle.
Yep, Koro-sensei arranged a battle royale to settle
whether or not we should go through with killing him.
One side for. One against.
Both had their arguments.
Both cared about him in their own way.
Yeah, but even if we'd wanted to,
saving him was a pipe dream.
At the time, I thought it was a reckless idea.
I hated everything about it.
I know.
But I'd have done anything to save his life.
You got carried away.
Your emotions made you lose sight of the bigger picture.
Admit it.
No. You're wrong.
Am I?
Ever since we met as first-years,
to put is simply, I've looked up to him.
He did whatever he pleased, without fear.
And he was absolutely brilliant.
All of a sudden, we were hanging
out and I felt six feet tall.
That was halfway through our first year.
But it wasn't long before I learned
that all good things come to an end.
He could do whatever he pleased because
he had the strength to back himself up.
Not a place I was ever gonna be.
He must've gotten bored sharing the stage with a Nobody.
By the time they suspended him, we'd
gone back to being just classmates.
He's always been a harmless little mouse.
A guy with my rep has to be
on high alert around most folks.
Not with him, though.
Looking back on it now,
I'm the one who put the distance between us.
Even then, there was something
about him that made me nervous.
I could put my guard down around him.
But for some reason, he had me on edge.
I couldn't deal.
Before long, we'd drifted apart.
And here we are.
A couple of third-years in a class on
assassination, staring each other down.
This is it.
The only way to get our point across is to win.
You are so going down!
Now!
I've got this!
Heh!
I'll knock you on your ass and take
my sweet time with the final blow!
Aw, that's all you've got?
Holy crap. He's taking Nagisa's attacks on purpose.
Karma is first and foremost a combat assassin.
He relishes process: The bargaining, the strategy.
Only when he's gone through the
moves will he deal the decisive blow.
Nagisa, on the other hand, is a pure assassin.
Single-mindedly searching for the
one strike that will secure victory.
Karma has trained himself to take a beating.
Hit after hit, he'll stand his
ground and give as good as he gets.
Should he hold out indefinitely,
Nagisa will have no honorable choice but to accept defeat.
Let's be real.
There'll never be another place like this. Not ever.
No one else is gonna let me be honest about how I feel.
But I will kill him.
'Cause, like it or not, it's the right thing to do.
What the...?
That's the last ounce of strength he's got.
He bit his tongue to keep from dropping!
Go for it, Nagisa.
Come at me with all that natural talent I never had.
I'll break you over my knee like a twig.
This game is mine.
It's all channeled into that blade.
Dodge and his bloodlust will dissolve.
What the...? What's he doing?
You are going to hear me out!
The element of surprise.
Nagisa sacrificed his greatest
skill to create a red herring,
opting to finish with a martial arts move.
All to make a simple point:
Karma's own specialty has, in the end,
been turned against him.
Exactly like I tried to do to him.
Playing by my terms, he's making it
impossible for anyone to contest the outcome.
Ugh. Damn it.
At this rate, I'm toast!
He's got a knife!
Oh, no!
No, I can't fight.
I'm probably way too big of chicken to even try.
Uh, unless it was absolutely a matter of life and death.
I give up.
Uncle. Uncle.
You win, Nagisa. Good job.
Are you listening to me?
That's enough!
Red Team has surrendered.
Game over. Blue Team is the winner!
Yeah!
I actually... won? I beat Karma?
'Fore you start doin' a little victory
dance, let's make one thing perfectly clear.
You left your back wide open to attack.
I just couldn't bring myself to stab you.
Talk about being stuck between a rock and hard place.
No one would've been satisfied with me winning that way.
Can't believe you managed to get
the drop on me with martial arts.
Seriously, dude, who'd have ever thought
I'd be beaten at my own game like that?
You killed me.
Right, you wanna save Koro-sensei?
Talk, I'm listenin'.
Are you really? No joke?
Quit staring at me like that.
You look like mousetrap cheese.
I've seen fewer bruises on a week-old peach.
Wow, even in defeat, you can't
bear to waste a single insult, huh?
Good ol' Karma.
Please.
Look, why don't we drop all the back-and-forth?
I'm really not feelin' it after that fight.
So, what? We talk to each other like human beings?
Feels kinda weird after all this time.
Fine. I'll start us off.
Give me your hand, old friend.
Thanks, Karma. Old friend.
True feelings tend to bubble up when
under pressure from a big decision.
Often as not, there's conflict.
But look, in the end, harmony reigns.
Because these boys and girls have fought in earnest,
they've come to see and appreciate one's true feelings.
Only because I didn't want to paralyze you.
Sometimes conflict can be the best
opportunity to strengthen a friendship.
Is that another lesson?
Without strife, we can't grow or learn a damn thing?
You're the first person I ever fought like that.
I wasn't sure I'd be able to do it.
I got you pretty riled up.
Guess in the end it taught you a lot about yourself.
Yeah.
You know,
that fight forced us to be honest with each other.
That dam was gonna break sooner or later, trust me.
I've tangled with my share,
but hands down, the one 'tween us?
That was the pinnacle.
Still, we were just dumb kids. There's no denying it.
Yes!
Consider this the Assassination
Classroom's out-of-season research project!
Ground control to Major Tom: The ISS has been hijacked!
Things took a turn.
The class came around to the idea of saving Koro-sensei.
Man, the lengths we went to.
Ever think a bunch of junior high kids
would resort to hijacking a space station?
Not in my wildest dreams.
Never thought I'd fly faster than Koro-sensei, either.
For one shining moment, we surpassed our teacher.
There's never been a better school trip.
Right?
Once you've been in outer space,
there's not much on Earth that can rattle you.
Ain't that the truth.
The data changed everything.
The odds of Koro-sensei exploding?
A perfectly acceptable 1%.
Might as well have been zero for all we cared.
Life was good.
Our happy ending seemed right around the corner.
Except...
No matter how many assassination techniques
we'd mastered, we were still just kids.
The "Powers That Be" weren't about
to leave saving the world up to us.
We were basically pawns.
The government was using E Class just to buy time.
I'll never forget what happened that night.
I take it that was the last of
the career counseling sessions?
Mmm-hmm.
My, such exciting prospects these children have.
The only task that remains is
editing the E Class yearbook.
Seems I'll be spending my nights here for a while.
Oh yeah?
Mew?
Write about yourself.
You should preserve your wisdom.
There's no getting around it.
Unconventional as this class has been,
we've all learned something.
The students. Me.
Report.
Yes, sir. He's in the classroom by himself.
He'll be there for the foreseeable future.
Well done, Special Agent Karasuma.
You heard the man.
March 6th. Commence with the assassination.
What in heaven's name was that?
My tentacles!
Since he has the poor manners to be alive,
he'll likely hedge his bets and make a run for it.
But no matter. We're ready.
Tonight will be a night of surprises.
What the...?
What's all the light?
We were so naïve.
Somehow we got it in our heads
this would all end peacefully.
The government left nothing to chance.
They had everything in place.
Right down to the smallest, most horrible detail.
Buff, buff, shine, shine.
Make is sparkle, make it gleam. That's the way!
Nothing like cleaning to pass the time!.
It's a bit lonely, yes.
But there's no point worrying at this late in the game.
Of course, if I had one wish...
...I'd like to see them again.
Just one last time.
I'm up a creek.
At least that's what everyone's thinking right now.
Alas, I'm a super-being capable
of moving at Mach 20 speed.
Fortunate, given how much I have left to do.
I can't bring myself to choose!
That does it!
The E Class yearbook will have to be super-sized!
The Spear of Heaven will be
fully charged in about three hours.
Shame that magnificent bastard'll
be obliterated so completely.
Seems a waste of good test samples.
The things we do in the name of world peace.
Do the kids have a chance? Can they pull it off?
Report.
There's an intruder on the mountain, sir.
Someone's gotten past the police line.
It's more than one!
This is a nightmare!
I can't get a visual on how many!
Think you can mess with us?
Way to go. Good teamwork, you three.
What the hell?
We've got a sniper!
Our position is compromised, send reinforcements...!
This squad's been neutralized, we're good.
Nice.
Squads C and D are MIA!
Status report, now!
All right, Okajima, I'm there.
About another 50 meters.
Oh, God! How many of them are there?
Hey! Lemme down!
Huh?
Karma!
Nagisa.
Heads up! The guy's still moving!
Stupid teenagers...
Hey, dumbasses! What do you think you're doin'?
Finish what you started, instead of
high-fiveing each other like losers!
I thought that sounded like you.
Koro-sensei.
You've come so far. Look at you.
The laser's almost charged up.
So it would seem.
I imagine they'll probably try firing
the killing shot just shy of midnight.
We have to leave! Let's try to find a way out of here!
Oh, I know! You could take us as hostages or something!
I'm sorry, children.
There's no stopping this now.
Too many people are aware of my existence.
You knew it'd come to this eventually.
You knew it all along.
Even if I don't explode, the cat's out of the bag.
We'd be fools to think the world would
accept the existence of something like me.
Sooner or later, they'll want me out of the picture.
It's a perfectly reasonably reaction.
So time's up, is that it?
Mew?
The risk is still less than 1%!
And I don't care what other people
say, I'll take those odds any day!
We've been a helluva lot closer to you
than any of the jerks runnin' this show.
They have an obligation to hear us out!
Like we're just gonna take it? Bullshit!
Next government suit crosses my path...
Terasaka. All of you.
Permit me to give you a word of advice.
In life, we travel upstream,
thrashing against the mighty current of society.
More often than not,
things simply won't pan out as you'd wished.
Don't apportion blame.
Society is in a circumstance of its own.
Resist the temptation to renounce it.
Believe me, your time and energy
are far better channeled elsewhere.
When hardship prevails, say "that's life,"
and marshal your dignity toward navigating
the disappointment as best you can.
When the water calms, ask yourself:
If society tosses me about like a piece of driftwood,
is it wiser to stay the course, or find another way?
If E Class has taught you
nothing else, take this to heart.
In the Assassination Classroom,
you don't have to face hardships head-on.
You can run. You can hide.
Launch a sneak attack if it's not against the rules.
Avail yourself of unconventional methods.
Whatever you choose, above all else, be determined.
Don't give frustration the last word.
The beauty of trial and error is that there's always hope.
Never forget.
When the moment calls for a decisive strike,
you are an assassin!
Ugh. Unbelievable. Of all the times to lecture.
Thank you.
Your rescue efforts move me
more than you could possibly know.
I'm embarrassed to admit that
I've been holding back tears.
Aren't I a mess?
By the way, Nakamura.
I couldn't help but notice how delicately
you carried yourself during the last battle.
And, uh, do I smell something sweet, by chance?
Your ears are as sharp as your nose.
It's been exactly one year to
the day since the moon blew up.
And if I remember correctly,
Miss Yukimura designated today as your birthday.
Yeah, it's no big deal, but I mean, if you wanna shower
me with praise for getting it here intact, then I...
Uh, hey!
Sorry,
but this is my first taste of sweet in a week!
Don't you dare get your drool on it!
Ugh. So gross.
All right, guys: Let's sing!
And go!
Happy birthday to you!
Dude, do we even Happy birthday to
you! ...have the rights to this song?
Happy birthday, dear Koro-sensei.
Happy birthday to you!
My wish already came true.
C'mon! Blow out the candle!
There's just the...
A far greater reward than I could ever deserve.
And many more.
Shiro!
Yanagisawa.
The hour is upon us.
So then, permit me to give you the
gift of the world's cruelest death.
Hello, there.
You do know who I am, don't you, sir?
Shame you never really knew me.
Maybe another time.
It's been fun, though.
I thought if I could pass my skills on to an apprentice,
the scope of my work would broaden.
And, well, he volunteered so
eagerly, how could I not accept?
Here was a boy who coveted power.
So power I taught him, in spades.
To inspire loyalty,
I emphasized the chasm between our respective gifts.
Hm.
Not terribly effective.
Unless you want the blood spilt to be your own,
master the method I actually taught you.
I shouldn't have been so hard on him.
Truly, I shudder to think how much I didn't know.
He wanted your approval.
Everything he did was just to get your attention.
Believe me.
I'm sorry.
You were the first student I took under my wing.
And I never gave you credit.
Die!
Run!
Listen to me, class.
There's something I neglected
to mention in my earlier lesson.
A clever assassin may avoid confrontation for a while,
but sooner or later, the fight will come.
And when it does,
every last ounce of strength will be put to the test.
In my case...
...that would be now!
You just won't let go of this
fantasy of being an educator, will you?
Deranged little guinea pig.
Answer me this, teacher!
Why do you suppose we chose this of
all moments to launch our final offensive?
You will protect them, right?
That is what a teacher's meant to do.
What the hell's goin' on? Where are the children?
Are you all right, sir?
Koro-sensei!
Koro-sensei, no!
Koro-sensei...
Coral the guinea pig with his precious
students and this was all but a forgone conclusion.
Sorry, boys and girls: You chose poorly.
Showing up here tonight only increased
the likelihood of his dying by our hands.
How does it feel?
Watching your students quake with despair as
they realize how much of a hindrance they've been?
Do you understand now?
They are your greatest weakness!
He's absolutely right. It... It's...
That is preposterous!
You're a fool if you think I'll
believe it's that cut and dry!
These children, they've risked life and limb to save me.
What they've gone through just to
be here tonight is extraordinary!
Their determination. Their unflappable spirit.
Students like these are the
greatest gift a teacher could ask for!
They are not a hindrance! They are not a weakness!
They are my class!
And I am proud of each and every one of them!
Call it what you will, but when the chips are down,
I will give my life to protect them!
Yes, that's all fine and good.
Now, then: Let's continue.
Where were we? Yes, of course!
Mind that you pay close attention.
Idiot!
What the...?
Make a run for it, sir!
Find a place to hide; you need
to recover. I'll buy you some time!
Kayano what are you doing?
Ah-ha.
Even with the tentacles excised,
your kinetic vision remains.
No, Kayano! Stop this at once!
It was all my fault.
I brought us down.
Because of me, everyone had to face the truth.
We'd been like a family and I ruined it.
So, please, just let me do this.
As your student, I owe you one.
You can't put this on yourself, Kayano!
Sooner or later, we all would've had to face reality!
Your actions simply made us take stock and...
Don't worry, Koro-sensei.
I've got this.
All I have to do is try. My sister taught me that.
So did you!
Unbelievable!
What are the odds of having both
sisters die right in front of me?
Tragic ends must run in the family, eh? Ha!
Can you imagine if I'd kept her around as a back-up wife?
Too bad for me.
It looks like I have a thing
for women destined to be impaled.
There it is!
Oh, but you are a devastating creature when
your emotions twist past the point of endurance.
Black indicates well-nigh unimaginable power.
At last your true colors are on full, glorious display!
But alas, considerable though
your power may be in this form,
the new and improved you will negate it effortlessly.
Thank you for playing.
Behold his final attack.
We need to get out of here!
Are you for real?
C'mon! We're wasting time! He's distracted!
If we stick around, it'll only make things worse!
You can't be serious!
Living to fight another day is a
perfectly reasonable battle tactic!
What? A white light?
But he... His tentacles are still black!
No.
He's gone back to yellow.
Nuh-uh, that's red!
He's green!
And blue!
And white!
Every color.
Every emotion. Every element of my past.
My entire life...
...mixed together into pure white energy!
Treasured pupil,
may your graduation... help you find peace.
Shit! No, no!
The barrier liquefies tentacles!
Damn you!
What are these flowers for?
I just thought they looked pretty is all.
Figured making arrangements might, I don't know,
come in handy one day or something.
Sorry, master. I can move them.
Hm...
No. Leave them here.
You've got a keen eye. Nicely done.
You really mean that, sir?
I can make a fresh bouquet every morning!
I suppose you could,
but I'd rather you study chemistry.
With what you know now, you'd be lucky to kill a mosquito.
If I'd only seen that smile,
I might've led the poor boy
down an entirely different path.
The tentacles spoke to me,
asked me what I wanted.
And I said, to be acknowledged by you.
To be like you.
But you are.
You are and you always have been.
More than you understood.
If by chance we meet again, on the other side,
let's pick up where we left off.
The fight was over,
but none of us were shouting for joy.
Koro-sensei, Kayano's...
Oh, Kaede.
Why don't we lay her down?
Not so fast. One moment, please.
Sorry, I'd rather her cells not
come into contact with the soil.
Huh? What is that?
You're looking at Kayano's blood and somatic cells.
I gathered as much as I could
before she fell to the ground,
and stored them in a sterile membrane
of compressed air for safekeeping.
I set a few tentacles aside for protecting you.
Of the rest, I used some for fighting and some for this.
Okie-dokie, then.
Time to string these cells together one by one.
Faster. And more accurately.
You see, class,
I've been improving my skills for some months now.
If what happened to Aguri repeated itself,
I was adamant about being prepared.
Now, some cells couldn't be recovered,
so I'll leave strategic gaps.
Those I'll fill with tiny bits of mucus.
In a few days, what cells are there will have
regenerated in sufficient quantities to replace them.
I'm a little low on blood. Type AB donors, if you please.
I think the wound's starting to close up!
He didn't use a single stitch.
Didn't leave so much as a mark!
In a moment, her heart will start
beating and she'll come back to life.
I didn't mention this earlier
for fear of sounding ghoulish,
but if ever your bodies were torn to shreds,
I was ready and able to put
them back in order piece by piece.
The ultimate student-teacher relationship, really.
Because it requires, above all else,
that I properly acknowledge you.
What did you...? You saved me again, didn't you?
As many times as necessary.
After all, your sister would've done the same.
The important thing
is that you not make the same mistake twice.
Aguri, thank you for giving me this past year.
Such a beautiful gift.
I hope against hope I've been worthy of it.
As we watched him collapse,
we couldn't shake the impression.
He looked spent, but happy.
Come now.
What kind of assassin let's a target
linger indefinitely on the brink?
Don't you understand?
At this point, we're just running out the clock.
I'm sorry, children.
All good things must come to an end.
That's life. That's the nature of the classroom.
The red light from above began to swell,
indicating eloquently, cruelly, that the hour had come.
It hurt, but we didn't have a second to waste.
Guys.
We have to make a decision one way or the other.
We could stay out of it.
Leave Koro-sensei's fate up to them.
Let's take a vote.
Who here doesn't want to kill him?
All right, thank you. Hands down.
Who wants to kill him?
They were a part of us.
Our guns. Our knives. Our teacher.
This is it. This is our answer.
We're assassins. Our target... is our teacher.
These were the nonnegotiable terms of our bond.
The only way to graduate with honor.
We knew what had to be done, and it hurt.
You can't move if we're all pinning you down,
that right, sir?
Precisely, Nakamura my dear.
Though I can't help but feel you're
being a tad bit lax on that grip.
We didn't give much thought to why.
Just tried to focus on the task at hand.
He'd praised us. Scolded us. Nurtured us. All year.
And here we were holding him down,
clutching for all we were worth.
Your heart, it's... it's under your tie, you said?
Which one of us is gonna...?
Guys, please.
Let me. I'll do it.
Sure, I got no beef with that.
Well, you are the head of the
class, so I suppose it makes sense.
Sir...
It's all right.
You can actually stab through the tie.
There's been a hole in it since
the day it was... given to me.
I decided to leave it like
that. For... sentimental reasons.
Ah, before you proceed,
let me say farewell to my fellow educators.
Miss Irina, are you sure you won't join in?
I'd hate for you to miss out on the bounty.
No thank you. I'd really rather not.
Who gives a damn? It's only money.
What I've learned in this class is more valuable.
It isn't about me.
It's about the bond you share with these kids.
Indeed.
Mr. Karasuma.
I thank you.
You've had a hand in molding these
children into what they've become.
If you please,
continue to guide them on their way after I'm gone.
Of course.
You've given me no end of trouble over the past year.
But, even so, it's been a year I'll never forget.
Rest in peace, Koro-sensei.
Quite.
Okie-dokie, class. It's about that time.
There so much more I could say, but alas,
I'll be lucky to squeeze in what I can.
In lieu of tearful goodbyes, if you'll indulge me...
...I'd like to call roll, one final time.
When you hear your name called, please say "here."
Look me squarely in the eye and answer in a loud voice.
Once we've gone through everyone,
you may commence with the assassination.
Wait!
Please tell me that you're all present and accounted for!
I don't want the last thing I do
to be marking one of you absent!
Get on with it!
Very well, then.
Karma Akabane.
Here.
Yuma Isogai.
Taiga Okajima.
Here.
Hinata Okano.
Manami Okuda.
Yes, sir! Here!
Meg Kataoka.
Here.
Kaede Kayano.
Yukiko Kanzaki.
Here.
Justice Kimura.
Here!
Hinano Kurahashi.
Nagisa Shiota.
Here.
My sweet, young assassins...
Sosuke Sugaya.
Here.
As you ready yourselves
to snuff out a life...
Tomohito Sugino.
Here.
...you understand better than
anyone the value of what's lost.
Kotaro Takebayashi.
Here.
Ryunosuke Chiba.
Because you've studied...
Ryoma Terasaka.
Yo.
Fretted...
Rio Nakamura.
You know it.
Turned it over and over in your mind...
Kirara Hazama.
Here, sir.
Rinka Hayami.
Here.
And in the process,
without even realizing it,
given that life meaning.
Sumire Hara.
Here.
It's been a privilege watching you grow.
Yuzuki Fuwa.
Here!
But the best part was growing right alongside you.
Hiroto Maehara.
Koki Mimura.
Here.
So please...
Takuya Muramatsu.
Yeah.
...in this moment...
Toka Yada.
Here!
...let me be the finest expression
of your bloodlust.
Taisei Yoshida.
Here!
If I die knowing I've helped these
28 souls find a brighter future...
Autonomous Intelligence Fixed Artillery,
Ritsu.
Here.
...I die exquisitely happy.
Itona Horibe.
Here.
All things considered,
I'd say it's been an exceptionally fun year.
I say this with all sincerity.
It's a privilege to be assassinated by you.
As a fellow spirit, from one traveler to another,
give a yell for all life...
...and strike.
This is it. This is the part where I kill him.
I'm shaking.
Why can't I stop shaking?
Don't kill me with anguish in your heart, Nagisa.
Nice deep breath.
Give us a smile.
Goo-Goodbye... Koro-sensei.
Goodbye, Nagisa.
The bare minimum,
that's all I could bring myself to say.
Gratitude. Regret.
I put everything I felt into that blade.
Like I was channeling my soul.
With every fiber of my being,
I thanked him... with my knife.
As his life ebbed away,
it was as if he were saying, "Congratulations."
Very soon, it would be midnight.
Graduation day at Kunugigaoka.
We'd finished the year a little early.
Time to turn our sights on what lay ahead.
Now then,
where are we on what you'd like to be when you grow up?
Any progress?
Well, actually,
I think I want to be a teacher, sir.
Granted, I can't get up to Mach 20.
I'm not exactly, you know, invincible,
and my brain doesn't have the processing power of yours,
but still, I want to mold young minds like you.
Excellent. I think we've got it.
A bureaucrat, eh? Interesting choice.
If I may say so, administrative duties seem rather, um,
restrained for someone of your temperament.
Well, remember the last quake?
How the politicians were completely useless?
I won't disagree with you on that.
The country should've been paralyzed, but it wasn't.
Everything kept functioning.
Who do we have to thank?
Behind every talking head at a podium
is some bureaucrat pulling strings.
That's what real power's all about.
Does that make sense?
You know, I take it back.
That's a good fit for you.
Hey, Karma.
Hm?
It's a nice day. Let's get some fresh air.
Why not?
"Assassination."
Adding that to the curriculum was life-changing.
Think of all the incredible
experiences we had because of it.
Yeah.
Where would I be if I'd never met him?
It's not every day a teacher inspires
you to follow in their footsteps.
Koro-sensei was special.
He made me who I am.
Look at us now,
working hard to forge our own path in life.
All because of that one year.
Pretty crazy when you think about it.
I know.
We turned out exactly as the Octopus wanted.
Heh.
Karma.
Aw, c'mon.
They're cleaning this place tomorrow anyway, right?
Yeah. Without you.
Makes me sad.
I kinda get the feeling he'd
be proud to see what we've done.
Been nice if he could'a stuck around. Just sayin'.
Huh?
Don't mind if I borrow this, do you?
Wherever you are, Teach. Give 'em hell.
But of course!
Same to you.
Dumbass.
Come on, Nagisa. We should go.
Hey! What're you doing?
Hurry. I'm lockin' up.
Hang on, I'm coming!
Hm. Memories.
This was Class 3-E: The Assassination Classroom.
The bell is silent. Life goes on.
Huh.
Gotta say, I'm likin' the looks of my new wallet.
Nice try, tough guy.
Better luck next time.
All right, people.
Let's get started, shall we?