[NONOKA gasps]
[NONOKA yelps]
[NONOKA]
Akari! Help me! Please!
[NONOKA screams]
[NONOKA]
Help!
[NONOKA gasps]
[NONOKA] Why that nightmare
after all these years?
[GIRL 9A]
Wait for me!
[GIRL 9B]
We're leaving without you!
I feel really
lightheaded again.
Must be low blood sugar.
--[crashing noise]
--[AKARI yells]
Uh, what're you
doing down there, Sis?
Are you stuck?
[AKARI] I'm fine, it's just
Aria's coming to visit,
so I'm trying to clean up.
Do you know where the vacuum is
or if we even own one?
I've been at it all morning,
but the house's
only gotten messier!
[NONOKA]
Don't dwell on that dream.
All that bad stuff
is in the past.
I live with Sis.
And we're safe and happy here.
[AKARI]
Nonoka!
Can you please
tackle the kitchen?
I still haven't cleaned the
dishes after dinner last night!
Sure!
[doorbell rings]
[AKARI]
She's here!
Hang on, I'm coming!
[ARIA]
Good morning!
I'm your new roommate.
I'll be staying here a while.
[AKARI] Huh?
How long is a while?
You fled for your safety?
Yep.
It's all because there's been
a series of attacks lately
targeting Butei.
Including me, I'm afraid.
Miss Takamagahara's
the one who said
to lay low for a while.
She says that I could
especially be in danger
due to all the
bad guys I've caught.
There are bound to be
some who get released
and then come
after me for revenge.
[AKARI] But the number of
crimes you've solved
should give you the
confidence to get through this.
It's like that they hate you
means you must be
the best Butei.
Don't know about that,
but thanks.
Anyway, that's the reason
I need to stay with you guys.
It's also a good chance
for me to observe you
in your day-to-day life.
Yes, ma'am! I agree!
We'll do whatever it takes to
make our home into your home!
It's small, but there's nothing
we can't change for you.
Just ask.
Whoa, hey, I won't
boss you around.
What kind of guest
would that make me?
[ARIA] As I suspected:
No parents. Living alone.
[RAIKA] Wait, what?
She moved in with you?
[SHINO whimpering]
[AKARI]
It's just temporary!
There are bad guys
out there gunning for her.
She needs a place to lay
low until it all blows over.
[SHINO whimpering]
So outside school,
you're with her all the time?
Do you even have room for her?
It's fine.
We're not there that
much during the day,
and at night she'll
sleep with me.
[SHINO]
No!
It's weird to have my
mentor in my house,
but it should be lots of fun.
We can do all the cooking
and shopping together.
And along the way I'll really
get to pick her brain.
There are so many things
I can't wait to ask her
and do with her!
[RAIKA]
That's adorable.
You're like a bride
on her honeymoon!
Oh, please,
it's nothing like that.
Stop making fun of me, Raika--
[SHINO mumbling]
[RAIKA]
Hey, Shino. What's wrong?
[AKARI]
Bad juice box?
Hear that?
Oh, yeah.
Aria Kanzaki and
Akari Mamiya are now...
...sharing a bed!
[YUYU, YAYA] We have to tell
Miss Urara right away!
[AKARI]
Your selection looks great!
Oh! Hey there, Akari!
You've gotta try the yellowtail!
[AKARI]
Ooh! I'm hungry already!
You know, since you're one
of my favorite customers,
I'll give you 20 percent off.
[AKARI]
Thanks! I'll take two pounds!
[GIRL 9C]
Mommy, look, it's Akari!
[AKARI]
Hey, you! What's up?
[MOTHER 9A]
Shopping, huh?
You get lots of good stuff?
[AKARI]
Yeah!
My favorite candy store even
gave me some free samples.
Here, take one!
[GIRL 9C]
Thanks, Akari!
[AKARI]
Bye!
[GIRL 9C]
See ya soon, thanks again!
[ARIA]
That was fun.
Everyone around here
seems to know you.
You're popular!
[AKARI]
I guess.
I'm glad I had the chance
to come along with you.
I normally don't get to
shop in places like that.
Actually, never!
Well, that's interesting.
So if you don't go
to the marketplace,
then where do you go
for clothes and groceries?
Oh, well...
Almost every piece of clothing
I wear is custom-made.
And for food, I eat out,
or have it delivered.
When you're not in danger,
your lifestyle's so much
more glamorous than ours.
Oh, uh, where you going?
[SHINO, TAKACHIHO scream]
Don't wet your pants,
ladies, they're just blanks.
Takachiho? And Shino?
What are you two doing?
Stopping by to
say hi or something?
Yeah. Just being... friendly.
Well, that's one way
of putting it, at least.
[laughing]
[ARIA]
Your tailing skills are awful!
And you can't lie worth a damn,
because your flushed face
give away your feelings.
[KIRIN]
Yo, yo!
Kirin and Raika in the hizzouse!
What's going on?
How are the newlyweds?
Wow!
Looks like everyone's
coming over!
Perfect timing!
We just bought
all these groceries,
now they can help us cook!
Yeah, but there's no way
we have enough aprons.
[TAKACHIHO] You can just
leave that part to me!
Yuyu! Yaya! New mission!
[ALL laughing]
[SHINO]
Here, let me help!
[RAIKA]
This is gonna be good!
[ALL chattering]
[SHINO, TAKACHIHO groaning]
[YUYU, YAYA]
Scrubby-scrubby-scrubby-scrubby!
[KIRIN] All right,
get over here, Raika.
Time to loofah your back!
[ARIA]
Hey!
Are you awake, Aria?
[AKARI gasps]
[AKARI] You were just
pretending to be asleep?
More Butei lessons.
Always be on guard,
even when asleep.
Add that to
your wall of wisdom.
[AKARI]
Aww...
Aria, slow down.
Do you really get up
this early every morning?
Just to train?
[ARIA]
Not all the time,
but I will be every day
I'm staying with you guys.
[AKARI] How far do you
plan on going today?
[ARIA] Oh, we'll probably
just do a 10K,
since it sounds like you're
having a rough time back there.
[AKARI]
10K?
[AKARI yelps]
[AKARI panting]
[ARIA]
Okay, ten kilometers!
Take a breath if you need to.
[AKARI] I think... I might
have... a heart attack.
Hey. Look over there.
It sure is pretty, huh?
I thought this view would be
a good way to start your day.
[AKARI]
Yeah.
Well, we better get going.
Once we're back home,
we'll do strength training.
[AKARI groans]
[AKARI sighs]
No more exercise!
[NONOKA]
Hey, welcome back.
You look tired.
Where'd everyone else go?
[NONOKA]
Oh, they're still sleeping.
You want some water, Sis?
[ARIA]
Whoa there. Are you okay?
I'm fine. Just a dizzy spell.
I'm not totally
awake myself yet.
[AKARI] You guys, Aria's even
more incredible than I thought!
In fact...
She's so good, I wonder
if I'll become even half
of what she is.
I can't believe you watched
a romantic sunrise together.
It's not fair. So not fair.
[RAIKA]
Don't be so hard on yourself.
You're not even
her official Amica yet.
You are doing the best you can.
[AKARI]
Well...
From there, you'll
work your way up
to becoming her partner.
You'll travel
around the country,
and pull off secret ops
with cool code names.
You'll get better
and move your way up,
step by step.
Yeah. Thanks for the pep talk!
I'll do my best!
[ARIA]
You wanna become more like me?
[AKARI]
Yep!
See, I've realized that
I even if I learn under you,
carry the same gun as you,
and train as hard,
or harder, than you...
Well, it still won't be enough
to make me as good as you.
You really wanna
be like me that bad?
[AKARI]
Yes! I do!
[ARIA]
But why?
[AKARI]
"Why"?
Well, uh...
Because I admire you. Yeah.
And because you're
the perfect Butei!
[ARIA] But there are plenty
of other S-Ranked Butei
out there to emulate.
I still don't get why me.
[AKARI]
Uh... Well...
Because of your sense of honor,
you follow the full Butei Code!
[ARIA]
What?
You could easily be
a super deadly S Rank.
But you never hurt
the criminals you capture.
So that's why.
Hang on.
This is a lot to process.
You're not mad at me, are you?
[ARIA]
No, I'm just thirsty.
Mind getting me something
from the store?
We'll talk after, I promise.
I'd be happy to!
Is black tea okay?
[ARIA]
You decide!
I'll pay you back later.
[AKARI]
Coming up!
[ARIA]
One more thing!
[AKARI]
Yeah?
Get me a double pack
of peach buns, too.
Sure!
[MAN 9A]
She's making a break! Go!
[SHINO]
They're after her!
[TAKACHIHO]
I'll follow the van.
You tell Akari.
[SHINO]
Got it!
Akari, hey!
[AKARI]
Shino! What are you doing here?
It's an emergency! With Aria!
[AKARI gasps]
[TAKACHIHO]
Yuyu! Yaya!
Go immediately to this spot
on the map I'm sending you.
Once you're there,
start following a white van.
License plate--
[SHINO]
Takachiho just texted.
She says that Aria's
headed toward
the redevelopment zone,
down on the water.
Do you know anything
more about the white van?
How many guys were in it?
We weren't close enough
to make 'em out.
All we know is
she started running
and then they
started chasing her.
That errand...
Aria sent me into that store to
keep me out of danger.
She knew.
I reported this all to the
school, as well as Raika.
She should be headed to
the same place we are now.
[ARIA] Well... Just me and
the abandoned buildings.
Good way to make sure no
innocent people get hurt.
You guys look like you're
playing cops and robbers
in your backyard.
I'm guessing you've got
a grudge against me.
[MAN 9B growls]
Shoot her!
[MAN 9B]
Split up! Outflank her!
[ARIA]
Bad aim, bad strategy...
They really are amateurs.
[ARIA]
Three more to go.
--[gunshot]
--[MAN 9F groans]
[ARIA]
Make that two left.
--[thunk]
--[MAN 9G gasps]
A good Butei
conserves her bullets.
Just one more guy.
Better make that 12.
Well, gonna have to take my
time and get 'em one-by-one.
--[gunshot]
--[ARIA gasps]
[RAIKA]
Freeze! We're Butei!
[YUYU] We've got the
whole area surrounded!
[YAYA] If you resist,
don't expect any mercy!
[TAKACHIHO] It was easy
for us to find you.
It'll be easier for my gun.
Where's the police backup?
Don't worry.
They'll be here soon!
We can't afford to wait!
Jonathan! Attack!
[MEN cough]
Yuyu! Yaya! It's your turn!
Right. Let's do this!
Hose 'em down!
[KIRIN]
Well done! Threat neutralized!
[RAIKA sighs]
This battle was starting
to make me nervous.
You there, Aria?
You can come out now!
We saved you.
You're okay! Ar--
[ARIA]
Akari! Watch out!
[RAIKA]
Damn, more than I thought!
Akari!
[ARIA]
Akari! Take it!
[AKARI gasps]
You think you can
hit them from down here?
[MAN 9M yells]
[AKARI gasps]
Akari! You've gotta shoot!
[ARIA]
Now!
--[gunshot]
--[MAN 9M yells]
[ARIA]
Reki!
[RAIKA] So this whole
gun fight came out of
some robbers wanting to
retaliate against Aria?
[TAKACHIHO]
Huh...
[TAKAMAGAHARA] The police
said they're part of a larger
bank robbing gang she foiled.
So it's a simple revenge hit.
[SHINO] Wait, it's just
a coincidence, and not related
to all the other Butei attacks?
[TAKAMAGAHARA]
We'll have to investigate more,
but at the moment, no,
it doesn't look like it.
Anyway, you all did great.
I see everyone's ranks
moving up soon.
[KIRIN]
What about Akari?
[RAIKA] They'll probably
come down pretty hard,
since Aria almost got killed
because she hesitated.
[TAKACHIHO] I'll take it
upon myself to cheer her up
with words of encouragement.
And my hands, if she lets me.
Poor Akari.
[ARIA]
Akari.
[AKARI]
Yes, ma'am!
I appreciate you
coming to assist me.
It kept the bad guys
off-balance.
So let's focus on
the positives first.
And then talk with your friends
on where you can improve.
Anyway, excellent effort.
Thank you for saying that.
I was worried you were
really gonna lay into me
for hesitating with my gun.
Know what I mean?
Oh! That's right!
[AKARI] I didn't get this back
from you on my own, so...
You don't have
to do that, Akari.
[AKARI gasps]
Your Amica test is done.
It doesn't feel right
to make you mine now.
[AKARI gasps]
I think the best thing for
you would be to transfer
to a department where
they don't use firearms.
You should hand in the
form for that tomorrow morning.
Um... Is this...
...all because I hesitated
to shoot that one guy?
Don't worry, I swear I
won't lose my nerve again!
That's not the only
reason you should transfer.
What?
Because you didn't shoot,
I was able to see
that you and I are
different types of Butei.
Even different types
of women altogether.
[AKARI]
Wait...
What does that mean?
[ARIA]
It means I finally understand
what I've been feeling
since we first met.
That while I work best alone,
you work best in
a team of friends.
Even if you mastered
everything about me,
you wouldn't gain much,
as a Butei or a person.
I would!
[ARIA]
Stop trying to be another Aria.
Instead, you need
to follow the path
that lets you be the best Akari.
There's so much
I can learn from you!
Being your Amica's
what's best for me!
You're perfect!
But there are so many
things that I can't do.
It should be obvious
I'm not perfect.
That you can't see that
just tells me how little
you know about me.
Then I'll have to work harder!
Whatever it takes to become
your partner, I'll do it.
No questions asked! Okay?
Then why didn't you shoot
that guy when I told you to?
[AKARI gasps]
And I'm not saying you should
have killed him, either.
If you couldn't even
manage to fire into the air
to scare him,
what makes you think
you can be my partner?
But there's another
bigger reason
why I won't make you my Amica.
I'm always working some
of the most dangerous cases.
If you're by my side,
that'll just put you in danger
of getting hurt, or worse.
That... doesn't scare me.
I still wanna do it!
[ARIA]
Be honest with yourself.
You were relieved when
Reki shot that guy for you.
And you even said
one of the biggest reasons
you admire me is because
I don't shoot to kill.
[AKARI]
Aria, no...
[ARIA] I've known for
a while you've been hiding
something from me.
Something big.
And I think now's the
time to finally bring it
out into the light.
So, I want you to shoot,
right here, right now.
[AKARI]
I can't.
[ARIA]
Akari.
No!
Do it!
[ARIA] Forehead, right eye,
left eye, throat, and heart.
Every single shot
is a kill shot.
[AKARI] If I had shot
when you told me to...
That perp, he would be dead.
Even a Butei shouldn't
have a skill this perfect!
[sobbing]
[ARIA]
No! Wait!
[AKARI sobbing]
[KYOCHIKUTOU] I heard you used
another diversionary tactic.
[RIKO] Yep! I paid off some
more useless small fries.
And it worked.
They kept Aria
and Reki tied down,
and we got exactly
what we needed.
So, our operation
can officially begin.
We can start abducting
or killing our targets.
Mine is, of course,
my dear old friend Aria Kanzaki.
And I need you to
eliminate her sooner
rather than later.
It's hard for me to do my work
when there's an S-ranked Butei
running around the city.
[RIKO]
Don't worry about me and Aria.
Piece of cake.
What about your end?
[KYOCHIKUTOU] A poisonous
flower is about to bloom.
So yes, you're right.
It's time for me to begin.
[RIKO] I think it's best
if we go radio silent
from here on out.
Even if you get in trouble,
don't come running to me.
[KYOCHIKUTOU] I'm glad my sister
came all the way out here
to meet us.
Mine is an easy job, Riko.
Like pulling out a weed.
The name of the
person I will kill...
...is Akari Mamiya.
[KINJI]
Move! Two gunshot wounds--
[AKARI] Aria is supposed
to be perfect.
The most perfect Butei ever!
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
I want it.
I want it more than I've
ever wanted anything.
Now come play with me.