[AUDIENCE cheering]
[ARIA]
Thanks, everyone!
Thank you! You're all so great!
[AKARI] All you guys in
the back, everyone up top,
I love you all!
[ARIA] But now, I'm afraid
I've got some sad news.
My bandmate, Akari Mamiya,
this is her final concert.
I'm forcing her out of the band,
and show business.
[AKARI]
Whaaat?!
Why, Aria? What did I do?
[ARIA] It's what you are,
a pathetic E Rank Butei.
The lowest rank there is.
But you said that was okay...
[ARIA]
I expected you to progress
when I made you my Amica,
but you're still E Rank.
I gave you a shot, but
I can't wait around forever.
Please, wait! Don't go, Aria!
[ARIA]
Goodbye, Akari.
I'm moving on with a more
deserving group of friends.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[AKARI]
Shino? Raika? This isn't fair!
Just 'cause you've got
a higher rank than me?
You too, Kirin? And Nonoka?
Don't do this! You guys!
You can't leave me
behind, please!
[AKARI groaning]
[NONOKA]
Hey, Sis, are you okay?
Wake up, Sis!
Nonoka!
Give Aria back to me!
What the...?
Sorry.
[laughing]
Can you blame Nonoka
for being mad?
No, but I was still dreaming,
and it was a bad one.
It was just a dream,
don't be so glum.
[AKARI] Yeah, but I'm scared
that it might come true.
[door opens]
[GIRL STUDENT A]
Is that Hotoegee?
[GIRL STUDENT B] What's she
doing in a Year 1 classroom?
Settle down, please,
I have an announcement.
Why is Shino with her?
That's a good question.
Okay, everyone,
please be quiet now.
I'm your school council
president, Shirayuki Hotogi.
I have a message
from the Masters.
As I'm sure you're all aware,
next week, Year 1 students
will take the Quartet test.
However, going by
the sign-up sheets,
many of you have not yet
decided on your groups.
Quartet? What?
This is required, mandatory
for all Year 1 students.
So please submit
your teams to us.
That is all.
[AKARI] What exactly
is Quartet again?
[SHINO] It's actually
a pretty crucial event.
[RAIKA]
Teachers told us about it,
and it's been up on
the bulletin boards.
But you probably
weren't paying attention
because you're so
preoccupied with Aria.
[AKARI]
Yeah, probably.
Quartet's a type of test,
a fight between two
groups of four people.
You can team up with anyone.
So, we can pick whoever.
Oh?
Does that mean you can have
an intern in the group?
I didn't realize that.
The most important thing
is their ability.
That's all that matters.
Even a junior high student is
allowed to participate with us.
Huh. I guess that
does make sense.
[RAIKA giggles]
[SHINO] So, yes, you can team
up with your Amica, Kirin,
since that's what
you're wondering.
[RAIKA]
What?!
What gives you that idea,
I didn't say anything like that!
Uhh, but I guess it
would seem strange
if I didn't team up with her,
since she's my Amica.
[RAIKA groans]
[SHINO]
Oh, guess what?
I heard that that it's possible
to raise your rank
if you get a good
score on the test.
[AKARI]
So let me get this straight,
are you saying that I may become
a D rank if I get a good score?
Yep, but the only way
for you to do it is to win.
[chuckles]
What if we...? I mean...
Yeah, I know.
We should team up.
[SHINO] So the three of us
together, plus Kirin.
Let's win this thing.
Heck yeah! Let's do it!
[SHINO]
Well, that's a relief.
I didn't wanna let
Shirayuki down.
I mean, y'know, since
she's my sister now.
[BOTH] Uh? Did you
just call her your sister?
Hang on, Shino. We saw you
helping Shirayuki earlier.
Does this mean...?
[SHINO]
Uh-huh!
I still don't quite believe it,
but she accepted
me as her Amica!
So, let's see, which team
are we fighting against?
Oh. There we are.
Wait, Takachiho.
Urara Takachiho.
She's that A-ranked brat
who defeated you in
battle the other day.
Her family owns the
Takachiho Financial Group,
and she's so pretty that CVR
asked her to join them.
CVR? What's that?
It's a very specific department.
They specialize in honeytraps.
Y'know, strategies based
around physical charms.
[AKARI]
Huh? That's a department?
Sure is! I'm actually in CVR.
Of course, my division, well,
it's much more specialized.
Hey, would ya quit
hangin' off me?!
[TAKACHIHO]
Yuyu. Yaya. Laugh at them.
[YUYU, YAYA laughing]
[TAKACHIHO]
Yuyu, Yaya. Stop.
Were you girls talking about me?
Ooohh, my, my, my, my, my.
I can't believe I have to fight
a pathetic E rank like you
a second time.
I hope they're not
going easy on me
due to my family's donation.
And your friends don't
look impressive either.
Is that an intern?
Back off. She's my Amica.
Really? Your Amica's from CVR?
What are you,
some kind of pervert?
[RAIKA growls]
You bitch!
[RAIKA]
What? Hina Fuma?
I figured she'd be
useful during Quartet.
So I hired her to join my team.
[growls]
You lack both
technique and elegance.
[gasps]
Nobody hurts my mentor!
[KIRIN yells]
[whimpers] That was just a joke.
Ow!
Kirin, no!
[YUYU, YAYA]
Heave-ho.
[AKARI yelps]
Are you okay?
[TAKACHIHO]
Shino Sasaki.
Your father's an
armed prosecutor.
Yeah, so what of it?
[TAKACHIHO] Please,
don't act like you're unaware
of our fathers' hatred
for each other in court.
Oh, I'm well aware.
Your family is nothing
but armed lawyers.
[chuckles]
You're the heir of one
of the wealthiest families
in the Butei world.
And I know where
you come from as well.
Tottori Prefecture.
[TAKACHIHO gasps]
[TAKACHIHO] I am not
some backwoods hick!
[TAKACHIHO panting]
[YUYU]
Uh...
Takachiho?
[TAKACHIHO clears throat]
[TAKACHIHO] One's Quartet team
should be carefully chosen
for skill and strategy.
But you just went and picked all
of your loser friends instead.
You have no chance
of defeating us.
[growls]
[ARIA]
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
[gasps]
[TAKACHIHO]
Well then...
[TAKACHIHO laughing]
[TAKACHIHO]
See you on the Quartet field.
[ARIA]
Quartet, huh?
Because I'm a transfer student,
they've never required me
to take part in that test.
Oh, really?
Wait. listen! Guys!
I bet you we can get Riko
to help us practice!
Riko? Riko Mine?
Yeah! I served as
her Amica last year.
Is that so? Not sure
if she's dependable.
So, she'll help us!
Now let's make a practice plan!
Hey, we can hold a
training camp at my house!
Whoa! Are you sure?
Anything to beat her family.
The Tottori Sand Dunes are
beautiful. They're glorious.
They shimmer in the moonlight
beneath the magnificent
Mount Daisen.
There's even a festival held
there during the summer.
It was my dream in life to
walk among those sand dunes
with Aria by my side.
But she deemed me unworthy
of being her Amica,
while that amateur somehow
lives up to her expectations.
Utterly unforgivable. Truly.
That Akari Mamiya is
nothing but a dirty thief.
[TAKACHIHO growls]
[TAKACHIHO]
You will pay, Akari.
[RAIKA]
Whoa.
This place is enormous.
Nonoka, you can take off now.
What's the big deal?
I just wanna meet your friend
Shino before I leave.
Oh, hey! You're here!
[ALL]
Thanks for having us!
Hi, my name's Nonoka Mamiya.
Thank you for being such
a good friend to my sister.
[SHINO]
So cute!
Her little sister's almost
as cute as she is!
Here ya go, Sis.
Your PJs are packed in here.
Oh. I packed your pillow too!
You've got a really
thoughtful little sister.
Yeah, kind of hard to believe
you two are related.
What does that mean?
Will you be joining us and
staying overnight, Nonoka?
What? Oh, no, I'm going home.
It's not like she's part
of our Quartet group.
I mean, she doesn't
even go to Butei High.
[NONOKA]
Well I guess I'll get going.
[gasps]
Hey, are you all right?
[NONOKA]
I... I just got a little dizzy.
Are you sure you're okay?
You should probably stay
here and rest after all.
[NONOKA]
No, really, it's not that bad.
Why don't you lie
down for a while?
I'd feel much better if you did.
Okay. If you guys insist.
[SHINO] All right!
They're both staying the night!
[SHINO] As you all know,
Quartet is happening Monday.
And since today's Friday,
that gives us the entire
weekend to spend training.
Now, here's our opposing team.
Takachiho. Hina Fuma.
And of course, the twin
sisters, Yuyu and Yaya.
The theme of the match we've
been assigned to fight is:
Poison.
Each team will be designated
by a specific bug,
and will carry attack flags with
a picture of that bug on them.
The teams will also be
given a single flag
with a picture of an eye on
it that they need to protect.
Whichever team's attack flag
touches the eye flag first
is the one to win.
So you lose if your eye gets
stung by a poisonous bug?
[SHINO]
You got it.
It looks like we're
the bee team.
Oh, gross, bees
totally creep me out.
The test is held
on the mega-float,
and takes place within
Zone 11 of Butei High.
Anything in the zone
can be utilized.
And those are
the basic rules.
Sounds pretty simple.
Yeah, right?
But you've gotta think of all
the skills they'll be testing.
Hiding, attacking,
withdrawing, and so on.
[RIKO] Here she is!
My little Rin-Rin!
Riko, you're here!
I'm so happy you came!
Well, I couldn't turn down
a request from my old Amica.
[KIRIN] Oh, thank you so much.
It means the world to me!
[AKARI] How does Riko Mine
always look so beautiful?
[RIKO] Poison, huh?
That brings back memories.
ust know that I believe Butei
should protect themselves.
I refuse to protect
my underclassmen.
Although, I am happy
to train them.
[RIKO] We'll train you to deal
with the twins, Shino.
[MAIDS] I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me, I'm so sorry!
[RIKO] The strongest amongst
you will guard the flag.
Just remember to
trust your friends
and buy them time no
matter the circumstance.
[yells]
[AKARI yelping]
Why am I the only one that
got stuck riding this thing?!
[RIKO]
Trust me, will you?
A Butei needs to know
more than just fighting
if she wants to survive.
Yeah. But, but-- Ah!
Ow, ow, ow.
[RIKO]
She is certainly earnest.
Amicas tend to think
like their mentors.
I bet I can learn a lot
about Aria from her.
[laughing]
That's gotta be the saddest
thing I've seen! Ha, ha!
Oh, I recognize you. Riko?
Yep! Everyone's
busy training now,
so I came up to check on you.
You feel better now
that you got some rest?
Oh, yeah, thanks,
but I'm okay now.
I felt a little dizzy,
that's all.
[RIKO] Good to hear.
I'm glad you're okay.
[NONOKA] So, is there anything
that I can do to help my sister
and everyone train?
[RIKO] No. You don't
need to worry about them.
But you're a really
sweet kid to ask.
[RIKO] It's too bad sweet
kids go to an early grave.
Uh-oh, are you feeling dizzy?
Kinda, yeah.
From that horse thing.
I'm fine. But hey, are you
feeling better now, Nonoka?
[NONOKA] Yep. 100%!
Done waiting! I'm eating!
I'm famished after today!
Oh! You're not choking, are you?
How 'bout I feed you
like old times, Kirin?
Say "ahhh"!
[KIRIN] Oh! Stop, Riko,
I can eat on my own.
Are you jealous that no
one's feeding you, Sis?
No, that seems a little weird.
[RIKO] Don't be silly, Kirin.
You used to love this.
Excuse me! There's a time
and place for goofing off.
But not while we're in
the middle of training.
She needs to maintain her focus!
I see. You're totes jelly.
You're going crazy with
jealousy! Aren't you cute?
What? I am not.
Anyway,
I heard that Shirayuki accepted
you as her Amica, Shino.
That's right.
[AKARI] Oh, yeah, I've been
meaning to ask you.
How did you end up scoring
an interview with her?
Huh? Uh. Well, to be honest,
I asked the Masters to
make a recommendation.
Just from looking at you
I can tell you have very
strong feelings for someone.
[gasps]
I believe that you
and I are a lot alike.
[SHINO]
Huh?
I can give you some training
to win over your love
while at the same
time determining
if you're properly
fit to become my Amica.
Uh. Thanks.
Cooking is one of
the most reliable
and fastest ways to win
over someone's heart.
[SHINO]
I'll do my best!
Never accept never!
[SHIRAYUKI] Infrared cameras
are more effective
on swimsuits than underwear.
That's excellent info!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Make sure you run the pictures
through analytical software.
And back up all the files
on three drives, right?
Shirayuki's pouring all of
her love into these lessons!
[BOTH laughing]
Destroy your rivals right away!
Destroy my rivals!
Especially if she has pink hair!
Bring her down as
soon as you see her!
You really know your stuff!
[SHIRAYUKI]
How dare you even think
of making a move on my Kkn!
Oh, yay!
You mean it? You're
making me your Amica?
Well, of course!
She really is such
an amazing person.
[AKARI]
Uh, Shino?
[RAIKA] Hey. You went
dead silent. Uh...
[SHINO giggles]
[SHINO] It's gotten so late.
Why don't you stay the night?
Oh, I'm okay.
And besides, I'd hate to
cut in on someone's game.
[KIRIN giggles]
Don't forget.
Butei Charter Article 6.
"Think for yourself,
and act on your own."
[GROUP]
Right!
[ALL]
Thank you for training us!
[KIRIN] Hey, Raika.
You're not still upset, right?
[RAIKA sighs]
If it's any consolation to you,
I'm flattered by
all the jealousy.
Please don't be upset with me.
I'm not mad at you or
anything. It's just...
What is it?
[RAIKA] It's just that
I'm not really sure
if you want me
to be your mentor.
[gasps]
I mean, Akari's got Aria,
and Shino's got Shirayuki.
They're both incredible
and you're stuck with me.
A Year 1 student who's
only good at sports.
I would never wanna be
anyone else's Amica.
You don't even realize how long
I've had my eye on you, do you?
[gasps]
Wait, you have?
Yeah.
Ever since I popped in to
observe the gym with my friends.
But I was worried that you
wouldn't want to accept me.
I'm so tiny and weak, I'm like
the exact opposite of you.
I was too nervous to
strike up a conversation.
When I finally asked
to be your Amica,
I had to muster up every
ounce of courage I have.
Hey, Raika. Kirin.
They sent me to tell you
our bedrooms are ready.
[RAIKA]
Cool.
Well, then. Ready?
Yep! Let's go!
This here is
Miss Akari's pillow.
And this is a brand new replica!
Wow.
Fantastic work!
[MAIDS]
Thanks!
[SHINO]
Akari's actual pillow.
I'll give her the new one and
tell her I got it dry cleaned!
I'm giving her a new one,
so it's okay, right?!
Oh, Shirayuki,
you'd be so proud of me!
[AKARI] I have to get
good at riding this,
so I'll practice all
weekend if I need to!
[yelps]
C'mon. I will raise my rank.
I'm not gonna let that
dumb dream come true.
[ARIA]
What exactly are you doing?
[gasps]
[AKARI]
Aria!
So. This is part of
Riko's training, huh?
How come you're the only person
out here still working?
And here I was a little worried
you might've already gone
to bed for the night.
Why are you pushing
yourself so hard?
[AKARI] Because Takachiho
told me that I can't do it.
[ARIA]
She did?
[AKARI]
She used the phrase you told me
to remove from my vocabulary.
[sighs]
Jeez...
You sure are stubborn,
you know that?
But that's actually one of
the things I like about you.
We've known each other
for a while now.
How long has it been since you
became my Amica in training?
[AKARI]
A few weeks.
[ARIA] I've been giving
you lessons when I can
but do you feel like
you're mastering them?
[AKARI]
Uh. Well, I'm trying.
Let's go a quick round.
A one-on-one match
will give me the chance
to see exactly how much
you've improved.
[AKARI]
Uh! You mean right now?
Try to at least
hide your surprise.
You do remember, right?
You've gotta get this back
if you wanna beco--
That was actually better
than I expected.
But your moves are too simple,
allowing your opponent
to read them.
You have to be flexible
when you fight.
Be flexible. I can do that!
You're not there yet.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
[ARIA]
But...
...your moves seem to be
gradually growing similar
to mine.
I'll be on the
Quartet sidelines,
so make sure you win, okay?
[gasps]
[AKARI]
Thank you, Aria!
[TAKAMAGAHARA]
Hiding flags and passing them
to your other team members
is accepted within the rules.
Rubber bullets are the only
bullets you're allowed to fire.
But be careful because a
headshot can still kill someone.
Let's all do our best.
[TAKACHIHO]
Ugh!
Seriously?
[TAKACHIHO] Don't talk
to me like we're equals.
It's insulting.
What's that old saying?
One's soul dwells
within their pupils?
[chuckles]
Well, good luck, girls.
[AKARI]
We won't lose!
[TAKACHIHO] I wonder...
Could this be fate?
--[SHINO] Akari!
--[RAIKA] You focus on me!
Please, be careful!
[TAKACHIHO]
Did that hurt?
[AKARI] I don't care
what you say about me.
[TAKACHIHO]
How fortuitous.
The chance to bring
you down myself.
[AKARI]
I am not gonna fall!