[pants]
Huh?
[explosion]
[KIRIN screams]
[gasps]
[roars]
Huh?!
[RAIKA]
Ha!
Hmph!
Ahh...
Kirin! I'm here to rescue you!
Prince Raika, you're my hero!
[KIRIN] Go, Prince Raika!
Defend my honor!
Ahh... What a truly
wonderful dream!
My prince, Raika, really is...
my one, true love!
[FEMALE STUDENT 3A] Oh, wow!
I grew an inch since last Fall!
[FEMALE STUDENT 3C] Really?
Must be all that milk you drink.
[AKARI thinking]
Today, the upperclassmen
are giving us physical exams.
And the one assigned to me
is Aria! I'm so excited!
[SHINO grumbles]
[SHINO thinking]
Stupid Aria gets to hog Akari
all day every day.
My beautiful Raika.
Oh! Too loud.
Is there something wrong?
Yeah. Recently,
I can't shake the feeling
that someone's
been spying on me.
Huh?
[ARIA] Line up!
First off I have to
see how tall you are.
What type of
firearm we assign you
will be determined
by this and your build.
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
[ARIA]
Shino Sasaki.
Looks like anything bigger than
an M4 carbine will be too much,
so we'll stick with that.
[ARIA] Raika Hino,
since you're so tall,
you can handle a longer rifle.
The Belgian FAL
should do the job, nicely.
Akari Mamiya, just 139
centimeters. Hmm...
[AKARI]
Hmph...
I don't wanna carry around
this super weird gun!
[RAIKA]
You look so cute with it!
[AKARI] Measure me again,
Shino, come on!
[RAIKA]
Why?
It's not like you've grown
in the last minute.
Bottom-right and top-left...
Bottom.
[SHINO thinking]
Her little mouth hangs open!
She's so cute when
she tries to concentrate!
Right. Top. Left. Bottom. Left.
Bottom. Top. Right.
Top-right.
Bottom-right. Top-left.
Great. All done.
[ARIA thinking] Raika Hino.
Her vision is incredible.
[SHINO] How the
heck can you see those?
[AKARI]
It's, like, super vision!
Hey girls, come on!
You can't give up!
Aria, I feel like I might...
[ARIA sighs]
[ARIA]
Five more minutes!
[RAIKA]
Roger!
[KIRIN thinking]
She's so cool!
[ARIA] This last test checks
your overall fitness.
It also serves as
a stress reliever
for the poor upperclassman
who got stuck dealing
with you all today.
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[ARIA] I want the three
of you to attack me!
[AKARI thinknng]
That's right!
If I find an opening
in her defense,
I can get my gun back! Okay!
[SHINO thinking] Three on one
means I can crush Aria
in the confusion!
I know S-Rank Buteis
are the strongest,
but let me test that firsthand.
[RAIKA] Come on!
Shino! Akari!
Not bad.
[sighs]
And that's Baritsu,
a hand-to-hand combat passed
down in my family.
But firing two guns at once...
...isn't the only type of
fighting I know how to do.
Baritsu.
Oh, boy.
I hope that my beloved
Prince Raika is okay!
I can't assess you just
by fighting like this.
Akari, Shino, I want
you two to spar.
But hand to hand
combat only, no guns.
Wait, I have to fight Shino?
Happy to wrestle her, ma'am!
[SHINO thinking]
Oh, how could I hate Aria
when she's letting me get
skin-to-skin with Akari?
[ARIA]
Raika, you'll spar with...
Let's see... You!
Wanna help us out?
Hmm?
Me? Fight a girl? Seriously?
[ARIA]
Yes. A co-ed fight with Raika.
Whenever you're ready,
go at her.
[SHINO]
Akari!
[AKARI]
What are you doing?!
[FEMALE STUDENT 3A]
A co-ed fight?
He might kill her!
[MALE STUDENT 3A]
No way, it's Raika Hino!
[FEMALE STUDENT 3B]
Go for it, Raika!
[FEMALE STUDENT 3C]
Make us ladies proud!
[ARIA]
Ready, fight!
[HODORIGO growls]
You bitch!
[ARIA]
That's enough!
[MALE STUDENT 3A] Are we sure
she's biologically female?
[FEMALE STUDENT 3A]
Oh, stuff it! She's amazing!
[ARIA] Well, sorry about your
arm there, thanks for helping!
She cheated!
You man-chick!
Yeah, whatever.
I'll take you any time!
[KIRIN thinking] She gets
more amazing every hour!
I feel so tingly now.
My heart's beating
like a drum! Wait...
[ARIA]
Hmmm...
Stop tickling me!
You'll make me wet my pants!
[ARIA]
Hey, that's not real sparring!
[AKARI] Well, she'll
probably give me and Shino
bad marks for the tickling.
But you were amazing,
Raika, fighting that jock!
[SHINO] And not only
did you beat a guy bigger
than any of us,
you made it look easy!
[RAIKA] Thanks.
But I just did what I do.
[AKARI] I know how well you
fight against bigger opponents,
so I never doubted you'd
clobber that sexist pig.
[RAIKA] True.
You've watched me kick butt
and take names
since junior high.
[AKARI] Yep! I know every
bit of you, inside and out!
[SHINO]
Don't forget, though,
the real lesson here is
we were no match for Aria.
[AKARI]
No, ma'am!
[RAIKA]
Oh, I'm sorry.
No. I'm sorry
for bumping you.
[AKARI] Wow.
That is one pretty girl!
She's Riko Mine,
a Year Two student.
[RAIKA thinking]
If I was a girly girl like her,
no one would ever
make fun of me.
She cheated! You man-chick!
[AKARI]
What's wrong, Raika?
[gasps]
Oh. Nothing.
Let's go home.
[RAIKA] Hang on, Akari,
aren't you supposed to be
working with
Aria this afternoon?
[AKARI] Yeah, but she said
something came up
at the last minute.
[SHINO] Then let's
go get some leaf pies!
Huh? Ah!
[RAIKA and SHINO]
Huh?
[splutters]
So that's it then.
The something that came up
and took Aria's attention away
from Akari was a date.
Wait, he's... he's Kenji
Tohyama from year two.
He was already an
S-Rank Butei last year.
Even defeated his teacher
in his entrance exam.
A first-year student
with an S Rank?
[SHINO] He's a natural, alright!
With a ranking like that,
it's no wonder Aria
has the hots for him!
Well, how 'bout that pie?
[SHINO] Hey, Akari!
What about the leaf pies?
[AKARI]
We'll go next time! Promise!
[SHINO thinking] Stupid Aria!
Always stealing Akari!
[AKARI thinking]
Kinji Tohyama.
He's a strong Butei,
but what kinda person is he?
[KINJI]
And just who are you?
[AKARI shrieks]
[AKARI]
Kinji Tohyama!
I'm sorry.
Weren't you the one hanging on
to the monorail the other day?
Why've you started
following me around?
[AKARI] Because..
Because it's not fair!
[KINJI]
Hmm?
If you had any idea
how hard I've worked
to get close to Aria, you'd
never swoop in and steal her!
[KINJI] Yeah, I don't know
what you're talking about.
You're like- in love with her?
[AKARI] What? No!
It's just like, well--
I'm sorry if this looks
a certain way to you.
To be honest,
it's annoying that Aria keeps
following me around so much.
You... think she's annoying?!
You're annoying!
[KINJI] Whatever. By the way,
your tailing skills suck.
What junior high are you from?
[AKARI]
Um, just a public junior high.
I transferred into Butei
the second half
of my last year there.
Public, huh?
[AKARI]
Hey...
There's nothing wrong...
with a public school!
[KINJI thinking]
Pubic!
Ahh!
[HINA] Master!
[KINJI]
Fuma! Help me!
The current's
taking me away! Help--
[HINA]
I'm coming!
Just try to grab a branch!
[AKARI] The kids at
this school are weird.
[AKARI]
Using him?
[ARIA]
That's correct.
I'm not really into Kinji,
I'm just using him to help get
to the bottom of the
investigation I'm conducting.
[AKARI] Okay that
makes sense, I guess.
So what are you investigating?
Put it this way, if I
told you, I'd have to kill ya.
Oh.
Remember what I said.
You can't take part
in my missions yet.
I know that it can
sting to hear that.
But you're still going
through Butei training.
[AKARI]
Right.
[ARIA] Much of what
you need to know
is in the lessons
I've given you.
One: Crimes and criminals don't
wait for a Butei to be ready.
Two: Always be punctual.
And three...
[AKARI]
Yes?
[ARIA]
And three:
Pay more attention
to your surroundings.
Your classmate Shino Sasaki
had been acting strange.
But you didn't
notice it, did you?
Never repeat...
...a mistake more
than once. Bye.
[AKARI sighs]
I knew I had a lot to learn,
but I didn't think
I was this far off
from being able to help her.
[sighs]
At this rate, I wonder if I'll
ever become her official Amica.
[RAIKA] Your name's Kirin Shima,
right?
You're still just
a kid in junior high.
what are you doing
asking me to meet you here?
[KIRIN] Madame Raika,
please allow me to
become your new Amica!
Uh?
Huh?
Let me be your Amica, Raika!
Uh, no thanks.
It's still my first year.
I can't have an Amica yet.
Your class rank
has no bearing on that.
It was no big deal
last year when Riko Mine
made me her Amica as a freshman!
[RAIKA]
Riko?
Don't compare me to her.
I don't care, it's still a no.
[KIRIN]
Mistress Raika, please!
[AKARI]
See ya, later!
Why is she so stubborn?
[AKARI]
I'm sorry for spying.
I got carried away trying
to follow Aria's advice.
[RAIKA]
No apology necessary.
I don't care about her.
[AKARI]
Don't be so cold.
I think that Kirin Shima
seems kinda cute.
Why don't you wanna help her?
Because I don't want to, 'kay?
[AKARI]
She's not your type?
[RAIKA] Look, can we just
talk about something else?
[HODORIGO]
What, Raika?
I'd put that she-beast
at the bottom.
[MALE STUDENT 3A]
Yeah, I'm with you there.
She's a dude!
Ha! Totally.
She's almost as tall as
our boy Hodorigo here!
With no dissenting votes,
we put Raika at the
bottom of the Hot List!
You guys shut up!
[AKARI]
Raika!
Yeah, what?
I'll be just a minute.
You think what those cave men
say about my looks bothers me?
You're funny.
Go back to class,
I'll catch ya later.
Um. 'Kay.
[RAIKA cries]
Pay more attention
to your surroundings.
[AKARI thinking]
I guess I haven't gotten
to know Raika well enough
to tell that something
like that would hurt her.
[RAIKA]
I gotta jet. See ya!
[AKARI]
Oh, okay.
[KIRIN] So, where you
think Raika's going?
[gasps]
[KIRIN]
Akari!
There's something
important I wish to discuss.
[MALE STUDENT 3A]
She's a dude!
We put Raika at the
bottom of the Hot List!
[RAIKA thinking]
Get outta my head.
I gotta go to my special place.
Relieve some of this stress.
So why am I hiding
on a train with you?
Because you want
to help me be her Amica.
You know what it's like
to crave the guidance
and attention of someone
just a little bit older.
But I've already
learned once today
I'm no good at tailing people.
Don't worry.
Despite her great size,
Raika's very inattentive
of her surroundings.
I've stared holes through
her since we got on this train
and she hasn't noticed me yet!
[AKARI thinking] It must
have been Kirin spying on her
this morning in the gym.
Why's she in
the fashion district?
Oh, my gosh,
what if she's into--
[GIRL SHOPPER 3A]
You look adorbs!
[GIRL SHOPPER 3B]
Totes adorbs.
[GIRL SHOPPER 3C]
I feel good in it, too!
[STORE CLERK 3A] Thank you for
coming to see us again, Raika!
I have some new costumes
that just came in today
that you might like.
Can... I try them all?
Of course!
Try on any costume you want.
That's what this
store's all about!
[thinking] Deep down, every
girl longs to be a princess.
So Raika relaxes
by cosplaying!
I never would have guessed
that in a million-billion years.
Whatever floats her boat.
Uh oh, looks like
developmental regression.
It's a serious problem!
Regression?
At Butei, girls are
supposed to have
the same competitiveness
and aggressiveness as boys.
That kind of stress
makes some girls
unwind by doing childish things,
like playing dress-up!
If she starts regressing
in other areas of her life,
she might need to
see a psychologist!
[AKARI]
Whoa.
[KIRIN]
Don't indulge, Raika.
You've never looked prettier.
Oh, really? I don't know.
[RAIKA thinking]
She's only being nice.
I look silly.
[KIRIN] In my fantasy the
prince saves the princess.
[KIRIN]
Well, now it's opposite day,
and this princess
is saving her prince!
[RAIKA] What are you
guys doing here?
Uh... Well... we were...
The real question is how
a Butei didn't even notice
we were here until
you turned around!
[RAIKA] If you tell people
at school about this,
I'll kill you!
Kill them?
I'm more than happy
to keep my mouth shut,
provided that you
give me a chance.
Just a chance to
become your Amica.
[AKARI]
Alright, ladies!
This match is to
determine if Kirin Shima
becomes Amica to Raika Hino.
You're both free to use
any weapons you like,
except guns or knives.
The winner is the first girl
to get the other flat on her
back or to say, "I give up!"
[AKARI] Wait, a sec!
I don't wanna be referee!
So, do I have your word?
[KIRIN] If I win, you promise
that you'll make me your Amica.
[RAIKA] Fine, but if I win...
...you stop following me around!
You can't fight me!
I'm too cute!
[RAIKA] You left
yourself open to this!
Jonathan the Third
special giraffe move!
Well, that's it:
Kirin Shima is the winner!
[RAIKA]
Uh... Huh?"
[KIRIN]
I'm now your Amica! Hehehe!
[KIRIN] I love my big sister,
and my big sister loves me.
I love my big sister and
my big sister loves me.
One question, Raika,
why was your end game so bad?
[KIRIN]
Bad?
You got her on her
back with a foot move.
Now, I've seen Raika dodge
that sort of thing before
and counter with
a joint lock and flip.
But she didn't do
it with you, Kirin.
You think my big sister
lost to me on purpose?
But why?
I... decided I was okay
with it... Your thing?
The thing where I grudgingly
declare you to be my Amica.
Congrats.
You won me over!
Kirin, you impressed her
with your persistence and skill!
You really think so?
Will you stop making me
seem like such a softy?
[RIKO]
Oh, hi, Kirin.
And girls from yesterday.
[KIRIN]
What a nice coincidence!
Oh, I know!
I love how cute you all look.
Thanks. Oh, guess what?
I'm the Amica for the
big upperclassmen here!
Well, you both
made great choices.
Now take good
care of each other.
Right, sure.
[RIKO] Catch ya later,
kiddos! Akari...
...I'll see ya soon.
Riko is something
else, isn't she?
Kirin, are you sure you
made the right choice?
You were the Amica to one of
the prettiest girls in school.
It's true that beautiful Riko
was always very nice
and protective of me.
That said, unlike ours,
the relationship was
strictly platonic.
My sweet Raika.
it's my duty to tell you how
gorgeous you look in that dress.
[RAIKA]
Hey, wait.
What are you doing?
Get off of me!
[AKARI thinking] Well,
that was kinda weird.
I wonder how Riko knows my name?
[ARIA]
Nothing?
[HINA]
Yes.
I checked all of Akari
Mamiya's school records
and found nothing special.
Or bad, or even remotely
out-of-the-ordinary.
[ARIA] What about anything
with her family?
[HINA]
No red lights.
It does look like she lives
with just her little sister,
separate from
her parents, though.
[ARIA]
Hmm...
[HINA] We're looking
at one of two things.
Either she's lived a
totally boring life, or--
She's doing a masterful
job hiding her past from us.
[HINA] So, I take it you want me
to continue the investigation?
[ARIA]
Yes, please.
Something about her...
really bothers me.
[ARIA] It's like a gut
feeling--that she's dangerous.
[AKARI]
Quartet? What?
[TAKACHIHO] I can't
believe I have to fight
a pathetic E Rank
like you a second time.
You lack both
technique and elegance.
while that amateur
somehow lives up
to her expectations.
[AKARI] She used
the phrase you told me
to remove from my vocabulary.
[TAKACHIHO] You have
no chance of defeating us.