[AKARI laughs]
Octopus fishing is so fun!
[ARIA gasps]
Oh hey, you caught something!
[AKARI gasps]
[AKARI]
I did it, I caught one!
[AKARI laughs]
[AKARI yelps]
What, seriously? Stop!
[AKARI giggling]
[AKARI groans]
[AKARI]
Oh man, that hurt.
[AKARI gasps]
What's the matter, Sis?
Oh. Please don't tell me...
Why is... that wet?
But... You're in high school!
Where's your control?
No, I didn't!
I would never, I mean,
someone else must've--
[AKARI]
Oh, wait.
I opened that right
before I went to sleep.
Oh, thank goodness.
I was so embarrassed for you.
I know. I'm so relieved.
[AKARI]
Yeah, well...
I guess I know why I was
dreaming about the ocean now.
Yeah, that's cause
and effect for ya.
[AKARI]
Aria was in my dream, too.
Ma'am...
Akari is walking eastward,
accompanied by her sister.
They appear to be
headed towards the bridge.
You may have won
the battle, Shino,
but I will always win the war.
That's the Takachiho way.
Yes. It is.
Let's get there before they do.
Whole unit! Move out!
[YAYA gasps]
Hey, wait! We weren't ready!
[YUYU] What does
she mean, "whole unit"?
She's only got us!
[NONOKA] The supermarket on
the other side of the bridge
is having a sale.
It's one per customer,
but you can buy half
a dozen eggs for 50 yen.
Whad'ya say we have fun
and take the long way?
Works for me!
We can eat as many omelets
as we want with all those eggs!
Oh, man, I can't wait!
[TAKACHIHO]
Oh, my!
Is that who I think it is?
[TAKACHIHO]
Bonjour!
Akari. What a coincidence.
Total coincidence.
Yeah. Talk about
a crazy coincidence.
[AKARI]
Takachiho!
Hey, Yuyu! Yaya!
Oh, it's you.
Uh, thanks for sending the
beautiful roses the other day.
[TAKACHIHO chuckles]
Well, my pleasure.
I should be thanking you for
all that your sister has done.
That's nice.
Well, we were just heading
to the grocery store.
They've got a really
great special on eggs.
A carton for 50 yen!
Oh, wow!
You've just enticed me
to tag along.
[NONOKA]
Huh?
Oh, you don't mind.
The more the merrier, right?
[NONOKA] Sure, but it's
kind of a long walk to--
We can get more eggs now!
Happy to help.
And we happen to be out for a
long stroll right now, anyway.
[chuckles]
[AKARI]
Talk about embarrassing, right?
Nonoka almost had me convinced
that I really did wet the bed.
[NONOKA]
Enough, Sis.
Quit talking about pee,
we're drinking tea here.
She gets carried away. Sorry.
That's okay.
For the record, it was
nothing more than some water
I accidentally spilled.
It wasn't pee, okay?
It was silly.
And it made me have a dream
about the ocean and an octopus.
The ocean, you say?
Oh my!
[TAKACHIHO]
Perfect!
I can bring up my invitation
without raising suspicion.
Hot damn, I'm good.
Even my luck is good!
[TAKACHIHO]
That reminds me...
Do you happen to
be free tomorrow?
Yeah, I think so.
[TAKACHIHO]
Well, then.
How about we make your dream
of the ocean come true?
I'm inviting you
to the water park
the Takachiho Conglomerate owns.
We'll have the place
to ourselves,
and I've got an
extra swimsuit for you.
Whoa! Really? Awesome!
Are you serious?
We don't have
octopuses, though.
[TAKACHIHO chuckles]
Oh, sweet, defenseless
little goldfish.
I'll lure you into the pool
and show you just how
deep my friendship goes.
[laughing]
Were you saying something?
[TAKACHIHO gasps]
Just that I'm excited!
Let's hear who's coming!
Count off!
One!
Two.
[YUYU]
Three!
[YAYA]
Four!
Five!
And six!
Make that seven!
Hey, cool!
No way!
I don't remember
inviting you guys!
Little did you know,
we were tracking
you tracking Akari.
I know you tried
to throw me off guard
with your little
speech the other day.
And now here you are,
making your move.
So, then, "the more
the merrier," right?
[AKARI]
Mm-hmm!
I certainly think so!
Oh, hey, yeah,
do you mind if Aria comes?
I'd love to invite her
if that's cool!
[TAKACHIHO]
Uh...
Um... Well, uh...
Of course, you can!
You're welcome to invite
as many friends as you want!
Fantastic!
[TAKACHIHO]
Oh damn it!
And right when I had Akari
in the palm of my hand!
This is all your fault for not
being cautious enough!
You asked for this punishment!
[NONOKA]
Hey, um...
This is kinda weird...
This is part of her education!
I'm not doing it out of cruelty!
You worthless idiot!
[YUYU]
Thank you for teaching me!
[TAKACHIHO]
Shino...
[SHINO] I owe you
an apology for earlier.
And why would you apologize?
Because yesterday's enemies...
...could be today's friends.
[ARIA]
No, I'm too busy for that.
Well, I don't
wanna go to a pool.
What pool?
But Takachiho's
opening it just for us.
We'll have it to ourselves!
The place is called
Spa Resort Takachiho.
And it's not only a pool,
it's like a full-on water park!
Please come, Aria!
No. I just don't like
swimming, all right?
Don't you mean
that you can't swim?
Hey! Who told you that?
I can swim just
fine with floaties!
Wait, what're you doing here?
How did you get in my dorm room?
Annoying. Go home already, Riko.
[AKARI]
Floaties?
Please ignore that.
That wasn't meant for you.
Oh, that's a fun thing
I can tell her!
Why don't you
join us? Please?
C'mon, Aria!
Hey, I wanna go to the pool
with you guys, too!
Please?
[ARIA]
All right, fine.
Jeez, this place looks amazing.
Pools with freakin' beaches?
Just how filthy rich can
Takachiho actually be?
Welcome home, Raika!
Surprise! Welcome home, Raika!
Aren't you happy to see us?
Whoa, hey, Kirin!
What're you all doing here?
How could I pass up
on Takachiho's offer?
It'd be rude not to invite
my friends to join us.
We were just trying to
decide which swimsuits
to wear at the pool.
Why the heck are you
doing that at my place?
Because I brought
some bathing suits
for you to try on.
Y'see?
Which one do you like?
I know you'd look
great in this one!
Try this, you've got
such a perfect figure!
[MOYU]
Totally wear a G-string!
[RUI]
No, wait, look at this one!
[RAIKA]
Wh--What the hell, you guys?
Really...
Here ya go!
What d'ya think of this one?
What?!
Are you sure that thing's
not an eyepatch?
I'll pick out my own
bathing suit!
Now gather these up and go home!
[KIRIN sniffling]
[KIRIN crying]
[KIRA]
Hey... You made her cry!
[ALL] You made her cry,
you made her cry!
Hey, okay, I give in.
I guess I can wear one of these.
Aw, you're so sweet, Raika!
Let's all wear super cute and
risqué swimsuits tomorrow
to show Raika our support!
[ALL]
Okay!
[RAIKA]
I'm a sucker.
We both have deep-seated
feelings for Akari.
Enough to bond over.
[SHINO] I take it you
have a plan in place?
I can't see you inviting Akari
without an elaborate
strategy already mapped out.
[TAKACHIHO chuckles]
You're more perceptive than
I give you credit for, Shino.
[snaps]
[TAKACHIHO]
This bikini is meant for Akari.
As you can see, it's
the same design as mine.
Except that Akari's
has been constructed
from a very special fabric.
One that shrinks in water.
[SHINO]
It shrinks?
[TAKACHIHO]
Oh, yes.
Gradually and subtly,
without being noticed.
Until it's as thin as string.
[SHINO]
Seriously?
[TAKACHIHO] A bathing suit
that practically disappears.
Oh, no!
Why, it's likely to come
undone and reveal everything!
That's... incredible!
But hold on.
What if she gets
out of the water
before her bathing suit
can fully shrink?
[TAKACHIHO chuckles]
Please, I have thought
this plan through.
Sit back and observe.
There's an emergency feature.
If the water is warm...
[SHINO gasps]
[TAKACHIHO] ...the swimsuit
instantly shrinks.
I've already prepared
a trapdoor to a heated pool
as a foolproof backup plan.
[SHINO] I should've
expected nothing less
than cunning from you.
In that case...
I'll contribute
by applying the skills
I've learned from my mentor.
[TAKACHIHO]
Hm?
Beautiful memories should
be preserved on video.
What better way
to enjoy them later?
I'll record the whole ordeal
for posterity utilizing this.
[SHINO]
Clearly recorded. In HD.
[SHIRAYUKI]
If it's for the sake of love,
there's nothing wrong
with a little
stealthy electronic
surveillance!
Now go fly to Tokyo
and find my precious Kin!
I'll oversee the surveillance.
And I will oversee
the incident itself.
[BOTH]
The secret alliance is formed.
Welcome, friends,
to the Spa Resort Takachiho!
Hey, good morning, Takachiho!
[TAKACHIHO] As I promised,
the place is all ours!
[AKARI]
Whoa! All right!
I can't believe we overslept!
She's gonna spank us to death!
[BOTH yelp]
[YAYA]
Wait... Which one's Akari's?
[YUYU]
It's gotta be this one!
Huh?
Here! This is for you!
It's the exact same as mine.
I thought it'd be
cute to go twinsies!
Oh, wow, thank you so much!
[NONOKA]
Whoa, Sis! Be decent! Here!
[AKARI]
Thanks. Good catch, Nonoka!
I can't wait!
Aren't you dying
to get into the pool?
Would you shut up already?
I'm here to chaperone and make
sure nothing dumb happens.
They're all way too excited.
I invited Reki for backup.
Well...
You can still go
swimming, correct?
How many meters will you swim?
And how much are you
gonna pad your chest?
[ARIA]
Holes Driver!
[RIKO groans]
[REKI]
One. Two. Three.
[bells ring]
[ALL squeal]
--It's a real life beach!
--This is so cool!
[RIKO]
A cotton wrap! A loincloth!
You're so fashionable!
[ARIA] Is that like some
traditional Japanese swimsuit?
[HINA]
Exactly, you got it.
Oh, ladies.
Take a quick moment to look up.
Look up?
[AKARI gasps]
[RAIKA]
Whoa!
[SHINO]
It's so pretty!
Well, look at that.
I guess you truly are
a woman after all.
Huh?
You look so cute
in that swimsuit, Raika!
What?
You said cute?
I look cute?
Freakin' cute?
[RAIKA squeals]
[RAIKA]
You jerk!
I don't wanna
hear things like that!
[TAKACHIHO laughs]
[RAIKA]
Take that!
[AKARI]
I'm gonna spash you!
[ALL laughing]
[gasping]
[AKARI]
Dolphins!
They're so cute!
[TAKACHIHO]
They're actually robot dolphins.
[AKARI]
That's awesome!
[TAKACHIHO]
What's happening here?
Why is it not shrinking?
Look at me!
This is amazing!
[SHINO]
Oh yeah.
The infrared camera does
work nicely on swimsuits.
I'm too scared, Raika!
Kirin, you can't just
go around grabbing my--
[yells]
Holy crap, Kirin!
Here we go!
[KUU laughing]
You're doing so
incredibly awesome, Kuu!
This starfish is really cool!
And super cute!
[RAIKA yells]
Stop!
It's okay, Raika,
we're almost to the bottom!
[RAIKA screams]
[ALL squeal]
Uh, hey, Raika...
OMG! Everybody's looking
right at us!
We can't do this in public!
[ALL]
You should kiss her!
Kiss her!
That's messed up
on so many levels!
[glass clamoring]
[NONOKA]
Uh...
Sorry for the interruption.
I uh, I didn't know
that uh, y'know,
the two of you were a uh...
What? No!
It's not what it looks like!
[KIRIN]
It's exactly what it looks like!
[RIKO]
Hey, Aria!
Hop in, it feels great!
How can you sit there
and waste this opportunity?
I can swim, Riko!
As long as it's
shallow enough to stand.
[RIKO] Your little legs
are probably too short.
[ARIA]
Riko!
[ARIA gasps, yells]
[ARIA]
Help!
[RIKO laughing]
Reki!
I am... a single bullet.
[RIKO yells]
[RIKO]
Hey, that hurt!
[ARIA] I am so gonna
pump you full of holes!
[RIKO]
Whatever.
Aw, is the deadweight mad?
[ARIA]
Holes! Holes!
[AKARI]
Hey, Aria!
Do you wanna play
split the watermelon?
[ARIA]
Split the watermelon?
[AKARI]
Yeah!
[ARIA]
You can be so childish.
Thank you, but no thank you.
I have no interest
in any of that.
Besides, it's just downright
wasteful to play with food.
[RIKO]
Sounds like fun to me!
[ARIA]
Hey, cut it out, Riko!
Let go of my hand! Seriously!
[RIKO]
All of us can play together.
Aria! A little to the right!
[AKARI]
Now a little bit lower!
You're almost there!
[TAKACHIHO]
There you go!
That's it, right around there!
Split it Butei style!
It's so much more exciting
using real bullets!
[TAKACHIHO]
The most delicious watermelons
are grown in Tottori.
[YUYU, YAYA gasp]
[HINA]
Perfect split!
[KIRIN]
Oh! This looks amazing!
[ALL chattering]
[AKARI]
It looks amazing!
[ALL chattering]
What do we do here?
We obviously gave
Miss Urara the swimsuit
that was supposed
to be for Akari.
Maybe if we can
get it to dry...
[YUYU]
Come on, come on!
[YAYA]
It's not getting bigger!
[YUYU, YAYA]
Please get dry!
Here, try this, Akari.
No, you should eat mine first.
[BOTH]
Ahh!
[AKARI gasps]
I found 10 yen!
All right. What're you
trying to pull here?
What am I...?
What do you think
you're trying to do?
Silly me!
It's just an old,
rusted bottle cap.
[NONOKA]
Aw, jeez, Sis.
Quit pickin' stuff
up off the ground.
[TAKACHIHO] It looks like
her suit hasn't shrunk any!
What's going on?
[SHINO]
I'm not crazy.
Her swimsuit's the one
that's shrinking.
[TAKACHIHO]
Ready?
It's about time for
the new ceiling cycle.
[AKARI]
Oh! Beautiful!
[TAKACHIHO] It hasn't shrunk
in the slightest bit yet.
Well then, time for plan B.
Open the trapdoor,
and soak her in warm water!
Oh crap!
That's the final resort button!
No! This is so bad!
[TAKACHIHO] We can get an
even better view over here.
[AKARI]
Cool. Okay.
[TAKACHIHO] This is precisely
where the trapdoor is located.
The two of us will just slip
into our little love room alone.
[YUYU, YAYA yell]
[TAKACHIHO] What the hell
are you two doing?
Don't do it, Miss Urara!
Everyone'll think
you're a pervert!
[TAKACHIHO]
Stop it!
[SHINO]
Yep. I knew it.
They must've switched
the suits on accident.
[SHINO]
We're aborting the operation!
[AKARI]
Operation?
I'm not aborting anything!
Are you betraying me?
[YUYU, YAYA yell]
[TAKACHIHO, SHINO scream]
What the hell?
This is my heated love spa.
Thank you so much for
ruining the operation.
[SHINO gasps]
[SHINO]
Uh... Takachiho!
[TAKACHIHO screams]
What?!
Why? Why am I naked?!
[YUYU, YAYA]
Hey, Miss Urara?
[YUYU]
Uh... We are so sorry!
[YAYA] We accidentally mixed up
the bathing suits earlier!
[TAKACHIHO] Those two are
the most useless idiots
this world ever crapped out!
[TAKACHIHO]
Give me your swimsuit right now!
[SHINO]
Are you crazy?!
Then I'd be naked!
What were you gonna do
to Akari down here?
This room is straight
out of a sleazy motel!
[TAKACHIHO] You have no right
to ask me that question!
Don't act like you
weren't planning on
doing the same thing!
[AKARI]
What's going on?
[YUYU]
Avert your eyes!
[YAYA]
Nothing to see down there!
[TAKACHIHO] Oh, whatever,
you creepy voyeur!
[RAIKA]
What a day.
It was definitely
a full one, wasn't it?
For real! I had tons of fun!
Hey, at least we were able to
obtain a bunch of good footage.
And we procured
the cup and silverware
that she used earlier.
I guess it worked out okay.
How about that?
She rarely loses heart.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Found him!
I'm not taking this camera
off him for the entire night.
[HODORIGO] Oh, well look at
that, I found you a balloon.
[HODORIGO'S SISTER]
Yay! Gracias, Big Bro!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Who the hell are you?!
[AKARI]
Oh, hey, what's up, Aria?
Today turned out
pretty fun, huh?
And I got in some nice
lounging by the pool time.
Whoa! Where'd all those
peach buns come from?
[ARIA]
Peach buns?
[AKARI]
I did it! I got it!
I got my gun back!
Why's it so...?
[ARIA giggles]
[AKARI]
Aww! That is so not fair!
Yeah, you're right.
But you know, life's not fair.
Which reminds me...
I'm sorry that I was
so mean to you yesterday.
Spending time with you guys...
Well, it was all right.
So how about it?
Should we hang out together
again sometime soon?
You really wanna... hang out?
Tell ya what.
I'll come visit you
at your place.
[ARIA]
I'm your new roommate.
I'll be staying here a while.
[AKARI] There are bad guys
out there gunning for her.
She needs a place to lay low
until it all blows over.
[ARIA]
Akari! You've gotta shoot!
[ARIA] It should be obvious
I'm not perfect.