[ARIA] Akari, I'm giving you
your first official operation.
[ARIA] You take down the enemy
trying to kill your sister.
I've even come up with
a code name for this.
I was inspired by the first
letter of both our names.
[ARIA]
Operation Double A!
[KYOCHIKUTOU] This is your
last chance to be smart.
Come and join the IU, Akari.
You'll be so much stronger
than Aria Kanzaki.
Nothing you say will
ever make me join you!
[KYOCHIKUTOU] Did you know that
oleander means "dangerous love"?
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Now come play with me.
Let's see which is
more important to you:
Not surrendering, or saving
your sister from annihilation.
Tonight's gonna go
even better for me
than it did two years ago.
You've managed to make
so many fun friends
for me to murder.
[AKARI] Calm down.
There's gotta be an explanation.
Remember what Aria told you.
And three,
pay more attention
to your surroundings.
[AKARI gasps]
[AKARI]
Nanowires!
How perceptive.
Of course, you'd have to be
an amateur to overlook them.
Thanks for not disappointing.
[AKARI]
Get back here!
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Let's clear out all the riffraff
standing in our way.
That'll give us the chance to
have a nice, long conversation.
Kyochikutou escaped!
She's heading toward
the north side!
She's using wires
as her foothold!
[KIRIN]
Copy that!
Hina already has
that position covered!
[HINA] Not the easiest
angle to shoot from.
[HINA] Sorry to break it to you,
but I'm your opponent.
[KYOCHIKUTOU] Allow me
to grant your final wish.
Tell me, how would
you like to die?
[HINA] Oh, I plan to die
a peaceful death
on the tatami mat!
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Oh...
[HINA]
Poison gas?
That's just desperate.
My mask blocks poison.
You'll have to do
better than that!
[KYOCHIKUTOU] Did you
really think I'd poison you
with an inhalant?
That's evidence of an
utter lack of imagination.
I could never enjoy
such a dull exercise.
[HINA]
She tricked me.
You just dove through a cloud
made of poison and acid.
It doesn't melt
organic material.
But it does enter through
the pores of the flesh.
Uh-uh.
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
You've been trained in
poison resistance, huh?
Although... you're too
worn out to keep fighting.
[HINA groans]
[HINA]
Please, don't!
In our clan, exposing
a female ninja's face
is even worse than
exposing her naked body!
I know. I'm trying
to humiliate you.
Y'see? There now.
I'm looking at your naked face.
[HINA gasps]
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
A bonus relaxant for you.
Sleep tight.
Kyochikutou took down Hina!
Seriously?
Afraid so.
But she managed
to put a tracker on her.
It looks like Kyochikutou's
headed towards the station.
It seems that she's packing
poison gas in her arsenal, too.
We need to minimize the risk
of citizen casualties,
so lure her to a wide open area.
Good plan.
Let's do this.
[RAIKA] Which direction
is Kyochikutou headed?
[KIRIN]
From your location,
she's currently headed
west-northwest.
Makes sense.
So the plan is to avoid
fighting in crowded areas
and tighten the
encirclement around her?
[KIRIN]
Yep!
Do everything
you can to make sure
that she doesn't escape!
[KIRIN] I'll take this time to
make sure that Hina's all right.
Oh, man.
Kyochikutou's pretty
dangerous, huh?
Miss Urara.
What're your orders?
I think you would be
best utilized
if you went to backup Kirin.
You want us to what?
Why order that?
[TAKACHIHO] Because I know
that she could use your help.
And I'll be just fine.
I can handle
Kyochikutou on my own.
Wait, are you sure?
Don't do this!
Please let us come with you!
[TAKACHIHO] You really
don't get it, do you?
I want the credit, and
I don't want to share it
with anyone else.
[YUYU, YAYA]
Yeah, but --
[TAKACHIHO] Don't forget
what Aria told us.
The group that
Kyochikutou belongs to...
They're an international
crime syndicate.
This task is well
beyond your abilities.
Miss Urara,
are you saying this...
...because you're actually
worried that we might get hurt?
[TAKACHIHO growls]
[TAKACHIHO]
You take that back!
I only care about me!
That is why!
Be quiet! Honestly...
This is a job for
an A-rank Butei!
You two do as I told you!
[TAKACHIHO]
Kyochikutou changed her route!
She's heading towards
the warehouse district!
Don't worry,
I'm still right on her tail!
[KIRIN]
Copy that!
[RAIKA]
What's her current position?
[KIRIN] 300 meters
directly ahead of you.
It looks like she's hiding
out by the third warehouse.
Copy that.
I'll figure out how to hold her
here until the others arrive.
[RAIKA]
She's not here?
[KYOCHIKUTOU] A scorpion
would never run away
from some measly ants.
[RAIKA]
When did she...?
[KYOCHIKUTOU] You honestly
believed I wouldn't notice
that someone attached
a tracker to me?
[KYOCHIKUTOU] I doubt you
wanna fill that lovely body
of yours with poison.
So why do you show so much skin?
[RAIKA]
Wh-What's happening to me?
[RAIKA groans]
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
How does it feel?
Don't you just love
that tingling sensation?
[RAIKA groaning]
[KYOCHIKUTOU] You look
so cute when you're angry.
Well, have fun.
[RAIKA gasps, groans]
And don't forget
to writhe in pain.
It... It hurts so bad...
[RAIKA groans]
[KIRIN]
Raika?
Raika, are you okay?
[TAKACHIHO] I figured I might
try running interference.
[KYOCHIKUTOU] Such a beautiful
friendship you have.
So nice, truly,
it warms the heart.
[TAKACHIHO]
Did you say friendship?
[chuckles]
That is putting it lightly.
Friendship doesn't even
come close to describing
my true feelings!
[TAKACHIHO]
Hold it!
This is weird.
I don't remember this
area being so large.
[KYOCHIKUTOU giggles]
[TAKACHIHO gasps]
[KYOCHIKUTOU laughing]
[TAKACHIHO]
Wait, did she...
[laughter continues]
[TAKACHIHO]
Dammit! Her poison gas!
It must be a hallucinogen.
If that's how
she wants to play,
I'll just have
to shoot them all!
[thud]
[TAKACHIHO]
I didn't... even move?
Have I just been
lying here this whole time?
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Sounds like you were having
a pretty fun dream there.
[thud]
[radio buzzing]
[TAKACHIHO]
It's Takachiho.
Are you all right?
[TAKACHIHO]
I... let my guard down.
Just hang in there!
Where are you?
Miss Urara!
[TAKACHIHO] Akari. I hope
that... you can... hear me.
Kyochikutou...
She's headed towards...
the bridge.
She knows...
about the tracker on her.
Please be careful.
I got it. Thank you!
We better hurry.
I should have heard about
Kyochikutou's arrest by now.
[ARIA]
Akari...
Reki? Is something wrong?
I have a message for you
from Ms. Takamagahara.
You do? Is it urgent?
[ARIA]
Wait, what?
[horns honking]
It looks like they've
shut down the bridge.
There was a massive
pileup earlier.
They've got it closed until
emergency crews can clear it.
For real?
This doesn't feel right to me.
[KIRIN]
I know.
I think Kyochikutou
caused the wreck
to create a place
to fight Akari.
We've succeeded in luring her
into a wide open area,
but she's been crushing all
of us one by one in return.
You'll have to take
her down together.
Akari.
Don't let her get
anywhere close to you.
Her fingernails are poisonous.
[KIRIN]
Lie down, Raika!
You shouldn't be moving yet!
[SHINO] I get the feeling
the police haven't realized
that Kyochikutou
caused the accident.
Looks like it'll take a while
before they get things
under control.
[AKARI]
Right.
We're Butei, and crimes
don't care if we're ready.
[SHINO]
I'll ambush her from below.
Keep her attention
on you until I'm ready
to make the attack, all right?
[AKARI]
I'm on it.
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Show me some gratitude.
I went to all this work
to create a nice stage
for our final showdown.
This isn't funny!
[KYOCHIKUTOU chuckles]
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Face it, I'm a deadly poison
and you're simply not
good enough to purify me.
[AKARI] Just gotta keep her
distracted until Shino's ready.
[AKARI]
What's with the suitcase?
You think you're gonna flee
the country or something?
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Oh, this?
My friends in IU insisted
that I take it with me.
I didn't think
I was strong enough
to use it,
but they reassured me,
it's completely recoilless.
Y'know...
I'm glad I brought it
with me after all.
[AKARI gasps]
It's rude to make
a point of standing
so far away from me.
A Gatling gun?
[KYOCHIKUTOU chuckling]
Akari, no!
[AKARI gasps]
[AKARI]
No, Shino...
You saved me...
But the...
The bulletproof
uniform wasn't enough.
Please, Akari.
Shino!
Please don't change.
You can never forget
that you're a Butei, okay?
And as Butei,
we don't... we don't kill.
Shino... No...
Shino, no!
Now that's a letdown.
I was looking forward
to making her suffer
with a slow-acting poison.
[AKARI]
Kyochikutou...
And what's this?
Takamakuri.
Oh, right, of course.
Your hands are
poisonous like mine.
I really should've guessed.
How could I have not seen
something so obvious?
I'm guessing you have it
smeared on your fingers?
Well I suppose you'll show me...
your Mamiya technique.
[YUYU]
Miss Urara...
Here, this will help.
It's a Fuma family antidote.
[KIRIN]
Don't, Akari! Hold back!
Butei are never
supposed to kill!
Please, Akari!
Are you listening?!
Don't worry about it.
Have some faith in her.
[KYOCHIKUTOU] I've heard this
technique described before.
"Slipping through
a thousand arrows,
death is caused
by a single touch
without leaving
a scratch on the body."
[KYOCHIKUTOU laughs]
Takamakuri.
A midrange combat
poison technique.
But what kind of poison is it?
[AKARI]
My success rate for Takamakuri
is only one in three.
If I fail, she'll
probably kill me.
But I have to try!
If your fight with
Takachiho had been real,
you wouldn't have made it.
[AKARI]
That's right.
Don't forget who you are
and what you are.
Stay calm.
I'm a Butei, and I'm here
to arrest her for her crimes,
not take revenge.
So why'd you freeze up?
Come on, I'm very eager
to see Takamakuri.
You need incentive?
How 'bout those thousand arrows?
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Or in this case, bullets!
[AKARI]
There was no lightning.
I failed!
Okay... what was that?
Takamakuri is not
a poison technique.
Human bodies have
hidden oscillations
caused by small
electric currents.
Takamakuri harnesses
those oscillations
to throw at your opponent
when you rotate your body
to create a gyro effect.
[AKARI] The feeling I had
when my mom taught it to me
is coming back.
I won't fail next time.
You think I'm falling for that?
[AKARI]
Don't be hasty.
The right moment will come.
[AKARI]
Her gun is jammed!
More Butei lessons.
Always be on guard,
even when asleep.
She's a lot calmer
than she looks.
[AKARI]
So it was just a trap!
All of Aria's lessons are
keeping me alive right now.
I'm not so sure
if it's actually worth
sticking around here
if Takamakuri
really isn't a poison.
But I kinda wanna finish this.
[AKARI yells]
[KYOCHIKUTOU screams]
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
She wasn't lying.
It's not a poison.
[AKARI]
Is she okay?
She'll be just fine.
Her wounds are shallow.
It turns out she was
using a weak ammunition.
Her bulletproof uniform
deflected direct hits,
so that's good.
And everybody else
is okay, too.
They're recovering just fine
thanks to Hina's antidotes.
They should be back up and
on their feet in no time at all.
Good. That's a relief.
You'll regret this.
You've got big trouble
headed your way.
I should've known that
you'd be a sore loser.
I'm only stating the facts.
Things would've gone
a lot easier for you
if you'd just obeyed me.
What was that
supposed to mean?
Oh, she was just
trying to freak us out.
C'mon, let's go see how
Raika and the others are doing.
[ARIA]
Akari!
[AKARI, KIRIN gasp]
[AKARI]
Aria!
Why aren't you in the hospital?
[ARIA]
Reki rushed over to give me
urgent information from school.
We still don't have
official confirmation,
but Kyochikutou supposedly
wasn't the only infiltrator
we have to deal with.
It's not over.
There's another IU goon.
[SUIMITSUTOU] I'm not a
big fan of people bullying
my little sister.
Little sister?
Yeah, you heard me.
Kyochikutou's my
precious baby sister.
Pleased to meet you.
[SUIMITSUTOU]
My name's Suimitsutou!
[ARIA]
Our time together?
Well, it was pretty fun.
[ARIA]
Take care, Akari.
You'll make a great Butei.