[SHINO]
Oh, Akari...
Hey. The rich girl's back.
And big shock,
she's by herself.
Who really wants to
hang out with someone
that arrogant?
[SHINO]
So what?
I don't care if I'm all alone.
I don't care.
[AKARI]
Hey, Shino!
[SHINO gasps]
[SHINO]
Akari!
[laughs]
[AKARI]
Oh, Shino!
[SHINO]
Akari!
[AKARI]
You're the best!
[SHINO]
No, you are!
[BOTH laugh]
[SHINO]
Why, Akari?
[AKARI]
Over here, Aria!
I'm so sorry!
I hope you haven't
been waiting too long!
I have, Akari.
Five minutes, in fact.
As a Butei, you are
expected to be punctual.
And especially as my Amica.
Don't be late again.
[AKARI]
Yes, ma'am!
[AKARI] She's taking
a huge chance on me,
and I've already screwed up.
[ARIA] I've gone ahead
and submitted the report
of our Amica contract
to the school.
But don't forget.
This doesn't mean
I've accepted you yet.
Not until you take this back.
You won't truly be my Amica
until you can
accomplish that task.
Right! I remember!
[ARIA] If you see an
opportunity, try to take it.
[AKARI]
Roger!
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
Maybe wait for a
more strategic opportunity.
Let's go.
[AKARI]
Sure!
[AKARI] The Amica program
is part of our training
to become armed
detectives at Butei High.
Upperclassmen select
the underclassmen
they find most capable
and then mentor them.
And I've got the honor
of being Aria's Amica!
Well, technically,
I'm still in training.
But still.
I'm walking side
by side with her!
I know that she'll
accept me one day soon.
And then I'll finally be
her official Amica!
[ARIA]
Here we are.
[AKARI] Whoa! She's got
a VIP room in the dorm!
[ARIA] It only makes sense for
you to have your own room key
as my Amica.
You will be assisting me
very frequently from now on.
[AKARI]
Of course!
And I'll do my best!
[AKARI]
Gotcha!
[ARIA]
C'mon in.
[AKARI]
Huh?!
Wow... It's so big!
[ARIA]
Is it?
My room at home is
ten times bigger than this.
[AKARI]
Wait... What?
Ten times?!
[AKARI sighs]
[ARIA] I'm sure that you've
already heard about this,
but I come from a noble family.
The Holmes family, specifically.
[AKARI]
Hold on... Holmes?
[ARIA]
As in the Sherlock Holmes.
I can assume you've
heard the name.
I am the fourth generation.
[AKARI]
Whoa...
She's already trusting
me with her secrets.
[ARIA]
Here's your first task.
Contact SSR for me.
Order some silver bullets to
fight against stealth criminals.
[AKARI]
Uh...
[ARIA] Can you assemble
a Yagi antenna?
Marksmanship?
Forensics? Driving?
What're your skills?
There's gotta be something.
[AKARI]
What's that?
[ARIA] It's a paraglider
I use for missions.
I need to improve its
turning functionality.
Here, follow these instructions.
You can stitch it together.
Uh, okay!
[ARIA] Just stick
to those directions
and you won't screw it up.
I've got something
I need to take care of.
I'll be back.
[ARIA] Akari's attack
was clearly based off
a Japanese martial art.
But... It's not karate,
judo, or aikido.
[HINA] The technique she used
was most likely Tobiugachi.
It's the same
technique ninjas use
to remove an enemy's
eyeball or internal organs.
[stomach growls]
[ARIA]
Some upfront payment.
Dig further into her past.
[HINA] Ah!
Thank you so much!
[ARIA]
She works for way too cheap.
[HINA] I'll conduct a
comprehensive investigation
into Akari Mamiya's history.
Something bothers me
about her too.
[yelps]
[AKARI]
Talk about sad.
This is the only thing
that I can really do.
[ARIA yawns]
It's later than I thought.
[ARIA] Has she been
sewing this entire time?
[ARIA]
She finished the whole thing.
I thought it'd take
at least two days.
[AKARI gasps]
Oh, Aria!
The way you sewed this...
[AKARI]
Oh, yeah, I backstitched it.
I figured it'd be
stronger that way.
Really? Backstitching?
[AKARI] Yeah, you pull the cloth
to the side with each stitch
and then loop back through
the same needle hole.
It's the strongest way to
hand stitch cloth together.
But I... I can redo it
if you don't like it.
No, it's great. Thank you.
It looks like we've uncovered
one of your strengths.
You are a hard worker.
[AKARI crying]
Thank you, Aria!
[ARIA] Hold on a minute.
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
[AKARI]
Nothing at all!
Everything is so great!
[ARIA]
She really is an odd girl.
Is she like this
in her everyday life?
[AKARI] And then, Aria used
the paraglider I sewed for her
to get the drop on those
criminals this morning!
Really?
Sounds like you were
actually helpful, huh?
[AKARI]
Yeah!
I worked all night to
have it ready for her!
And then Aria used it!
[SHINO] It's like she
only cares about Aria.
She came soaring out of the
sky and rescued the victim.
Aria is so amazing.
[AKARI] She already submitted
our Amica contract
to the school.
It's great!
Of course, I'm still
just in training
until I get my
gun back from her.
So what gun are
you packing now?
Oh, well, I've still
got my other gun.
Y'know, the Micro-Uzi.
It's pretty good for
getting the job done.
That's true.
Anyway, sounds like
she's gonna accept you.
Although it'll probably
take a little while.
Yep.
But I promise you it'll happen
no matter how long it takes!
So, are you ready head out now?
Oh, hey!
We can grab some
leaf pies on the way home!
[AKARI]
Oh, sorry, I can't.
Aria's heading out
of town on a mission
so I have to help her prepare.
She needs me to pack
all of her nightgowns
and underwear for her!
And besides, I can't really
eat sweets right now.
Aria told me that I could
stand to lose some weight
when I had a sleepover at
her place the other night.
[SHINO]
She stayed overnight?
[AKARI]
All right!
I'm out, see ya later, guys!
[RAIKA]
Yeah, yeah, sure.
You do your best.
[SHINO gasps]
You okay?
[SHINO]
Uh... I'm fine.
I just got a little dizzy.
[RAIKA] She won't stop going
on and on about Aria, huh?
I guess she's pretty happy.
Are you ready to get going?
Those leaf pies sounded good.
Oh, no.
I'm kind of tired.
I feel a little sick, actually.
Uh, you need something
from our class?
Uh... No! Never mind!
Good day, Miss Shino.
Welcome home.
[MAID 2B] Please, let me
take your bag for you.
[MAID 2C]
Oh, no, Miss Shino.
Is something wrong?
[MAID 2D] Are you all right?
You seem upset.
--[SHINO] Shut up!
--[door slams]
[SHINO] Aria this, Aria that,
I'm so sick of it!
What is wrong with Akari?
She's supposed to be my friend!
Aria! Aria! Aria!
[SHINO] I have to do something
before I lose her to Aria.
Try to calm down, Shino.
Just use the Akari box.
Take it all in!
Akari's essence!
[SHINO]
Oh, Akari!
We'll be friends for eternity!
[AKARI] I mean, we've
become friends now, right?
So we'll always be friends!
[SHINO]
Yeah, of course, we will!
These leaf pies
are delicious, huh?
Here, please, have mine!
Wait...
Come on, this is not the
time to escape from reality!
[SHINO]
Aria H. Kanzaki.
S-Ranked Butei.
Aria the Quadra.
With the London Bureau of Butei
since she was only 14 years old.
She has an impeccable
arrest rate
of apprehending
99 perps in a row.
[SHINO]
She's strong.
It's too dangerous to
eliminate her directly.
[MAID 2A]
Miss Shino.
I brought your dinner for you.
[SHINO] Just leave it
outside the door!
[typing]
[SHINO]
Yes! That's it!
This is how I can win
my sweet Akari back!
[laughing]
[gasps]
So Aria...
Do you know how long
you're going to be away?
[ARIA] I'm not sure yet, but
don't slack off while I'm gone.
You keep working hard
on your own, okay?
Think you can do that?
Yeah!
You can totally count on me!
[yells]
[AKARI]
Ow!
Make sure you
lock the place up.
Of course.
[groans]
[AKARI]
Well, Aria.
I hope you have a safe trip.
[ARIA]
Hmm...
Is there something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Let's go.
[ARIA] So what're ya
gonna do while I'm gone?
[AKARI] Shino invited me
to hang out at her house.
[ARIA]
Who's Shino?
[AKARI]
Oh, Shino Sasaki.
Y'know, the girl with dark hair
when I took your test?
[ARIA]
Oh, I think I remember her.
Are you two pretty close?
[AKARI]
Yeah! Really close!
[ARIA]
Huh...
I'll see ya later. Work hard.
[AKARI]
Okay!
[SHINO]
Akari!
[AKARI]
Hey, Shino!
[SHINO]
Done with your training?
Ready to head to my place?
[AKARI]
Yep!
I can't believe I've never
been over to your house before.
[AKARI] I didn't know
you lived in a palace!
[SHINO]
She is so cute!
I can't help it, I've gotta
get some pictures of her!
[MAIDS]
Welcome home, Miss Shino.
My, my. What's this?
Oh, how adorable!
And unexpected!
[MAID 2D]
What a nice surprise!
[MAIDS] She brought a friend
home for the first time!
Hey, y'know...
You're gonna get tired
carrying that heavy gun around.
We can hold onto it
for you, if you want.
Sure. Good idea.
Here ya go.
[MAID 2B]
It'll be in safe hands.
This is great!
Uh, hey... the leafy part
is edible too, right?
Sure is.
Yeah, they're called
caraway leaves.
They add a more enticing
smell to the meat.
It's similar to parsley.
[SHINO]
Oh!
Try the lemon balm over there.
It has calming and
cardiotonic effects.
Supposedly chewing one
leaf before battle
allows you to exhibit
your full power.
[AKARI]
I'm impressed, Shino.
You really know your stuff.
Oh, c'mon.
I don't know all that much.
[SHINO squeals]
I like her so much!
She's so great!
[AKARI]
Your garden's huge!
[SHINO]
That's the fountain,
and there's an herb garden
just over there.
[AKARI]
The size is incredible.
I feel like I could
get lost in here.
[AKARI] It's starting to
get a bit chilly, huh?
[AKARI]
Uh... Hey, Shino.
I think we might've
gotten locked out.
[AKARI]
Uh, Shino?
Akari.
Do you know about
the three-day rule?
The cancellation clause?
It's a stipulation
within the Amica Contract.
If the junior loses a fight
in the first 72 hours,
the rule states
that the contract
then has to be terminated.
All because the mentor
couldn't protect her junior.
And the contract can't
be renewed afterward.
[AKARI] I've never even
heard of that rule.
Our contract was approved by the
school at 8 PM three days ago.
Only fifteen more minutes.
[SHINO]
Understand...
I let you keep your knife so
you're not defenseless.
[AKARI]
Huh?
What are you doing?
[SHINO] I suggest...
that you break up with Aria.
[AKARI gasps]
[SHINO]
A sword won't cut through
your bulletproof uniform,
although it might
break your bones.
But don't worry...
I'll be at your side to
care for you the whole time.
[AKARI gasps]
No...!
[SHINO]
You really are quite agile.
Just like a swallow.
[SHINO]
But that doesn't matter.
I can cut a swallow in flight.
[AKARI] Her sword
technique is deadly.
[SHINO] In the
swordsmanship passed down
through the Sasaki family,
we're taught the art of iai-giri
without using the sheath.
The lack of friction provides
for the fastest sword technique,
hence the discarding
of the sheath.
I haven't actually mastered
this technique, but--
[SHINO]
Turning Swallow Cut!
Oh, Akari...
This is all your
own fault, Akari.
[SHOP CLERK 2A]
You lucked out.
You got the last pie.
[AKARI] Can I get
a leaf pie, please?
Ugh, you're sold out?
[SHINO]
Um... Y'know...
I'm not really that hungry.
Are you sure?
That's so nice!
Here, I'll give you half.
Don't you just feel lucky to
eat a fresh leaf pie like this?
It's so good.
[AKARI]
Isn't it?
[SHINO]
Hold on, wait a minute.
Let me pay you for my half.
Oh... I've only got my card.
[AKARI]
Don't worry about it.
You can pay me back later.
[SHINO]
You mean I'll see you again?
[AKARI]
Mm-hmm!
I mean, we've become
friends now, right?
So we'll always be friends!
[SHINO] I just accidentally
made my first friend.
[SHINO]
I don't want to lose you.
So I have to do this!
Please, Akari.
Just break up with Aria.
I don't understand.
Why are you doing this?
Nothing's going to stop me!
I will be Aria's Amica!
[AKARI]
Her sword...
If I can just get it
away from her...
I'll use Tobiugachi
to take it!
[SHINO] I know about
your technique.
I watched you use it
when you fought
against Aria the other day.
It's obvious
what you're planning.
To take my sword.
But I've planned ahead.
It's very unlikely you
can use that technique
if your opponent
is out of your reach.
You can only use it
when you are
in close enough
proximity to them.
Samurai would carry a short
and long sword with them.
Up until this point,
I've been using a short sword.
And this is the long sword.
It's commonly called
a "laundry pole."
[AKARI]
Whoa, it's huge!
[SHINO] I won't let Aria
take you away from me.
I won't!
What?!
She dodged it.
[SHINO yells]
[AKARI yells]
[SHINO]
Now you lose.
[ARIA]
Akari!
If you want to be my Amica...
You've gotta handle
these things on your own.
[SHINO]
You just stay there.
Now that you've seen this,
I'll deal with you next.
[SHINO]
Akari is mine.
She's mine!
[SHINO]
Her bulletproof tie?
[SHINO screams]
Wait, I don't get it.
Why are you here?
Your friend down there...
She was acting weird
the other day.
But hey, you won.
[SHINO crying]
Akari hates me now!
I'm gonna have to go back
to being all alone again!
Oh, Shino...
Sorry.
I didn't realize that I
was being so insensitive.
It's okay, Shino.
I don't hate you.
You don't hate me?
Do you really mean that?
Mm-hmm.
So you still like me?
Please say that
you still like me!
[AKARI]
Well, yeah.
[SHINO] Oh, Akari,
I like you so very much!
We'll always be friends,
right, Akari?
Right? Right?
[ARIA] I wonder if
those two are actually
getting along today.
If a friend of mine
tried to pull
some psycho junk
like that on me...
I think I might
cut them loose.
[RAIKA]
What's wrong, Akari?
You look a little down.
[AKARI]
Uh... Yeah...
Yesterday was weird.
[AKARI]
Poor Shino.
I wonder if she's okay.
[SHINO]
Hey, good morning, guys!
[AKARI]
Uh... Hi, Shino.
About yester--
Akari!
I did some research
after you went home.
Have you heard anything
about the Amica group?
[AKARI]
No, I don't think so.
It's a cool system
where underclassmen
get to form
their own group.
They receive instructions
from their own mentors,
but the underclassmen
can all train together!
So guess what?
I requested an Amica contract
with Shirayuki Hotogi!
[AKARI, RAIKA]
Really?
So, what do you say?
We should totally form
an Amica group!
Huh? Huh?
[AKARI]
Huh?
I mean we are best friends,
so it only
makes sense, right?
I suppose it does.
We are friends, I mean,
you said you still liked me,
which means that we're still
the best of friends, right?
[AKARI]
Well, I mean yeah, but...
[RAIKA]
Uh, hey, come on.
Can you at least pretend
to be normal?
[ARIA]
Huh?
They're still friends?
Seriously?
[ARIA] She is a very,
very strange girl.
[KIRIN]
My one, true love!
[RAIKA] If I was a
girly girl like her,
no one would ever
make fun of me.
[KIRIN] If I win, you promise
that you'll make me your Amica.
[RAIKA]
Fine, but if I win,
you stop following me around!