[POLICE RADIO 10A]
Daiba One to HQ.
Casualty count unknown.
[POLICE HQ RADIO]
This is HQ.
Copy that, Daiba One.
Backup en route.
[POLICE RADIO 10B]
Daiba Six, reporting 0830.
Requesting emergency deployment.
[POLICE HQ RADIO]
This is HQ. Copy that request.
[POLICE RADIO 10A]
Daiba One to HQ.
Several Butei personnel
have secured the hijacked bus.
Please stand by.
[POLICE RADIO 10A] All the
hostages appear unharmed.
[KINJI] Move!
Two gunshot wounds to the head!
Alertness level E3V4!
If we don't get her to surgery
in the next five minutes,
we're gonna lose her!
[HINA] I can't believe
Mamiya's so skilled
in the art of gunplay.
I know. I never saw this coming.
[HINA] Where in the world
did this girl come from?
I'm as stumped
as you are, Hina.
[ARIA]
I don't...
I just don't know
what to do now.
We're losing her!
[WOMAN 10A]
I heard it was a busjacking,
and the maniac got away!
[MAN 10A] Just what we need,
more gun violence.
[MAN 10B] I thought this
was a car accident?
[AKARI]
This can't be!
But there are so many
things I can't do.
It should be obvious
I'm not perfect.
[AKARI] Aria is supposed
to be perfect.
The most perfect Butei ever.
[RIKO humming]
[humming continues]
[RIKO giggling]
[AKARI crying]
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Hello...
[AKARI gasps]
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
...Akari Mamiya.
Come with me.
[SHINO]
Where's Akari?
We haven't seen her either.
She won't answer her phone.
Hey, look!
Maybe she followed
her to the hospital?
I'm guessing it was you
who shot Aria?
I did not,
but I'm working with
the person who did.
[AKARI]
Why shoot her?
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
She's a target for IU.
They've been after her
for quite a while.
And so has my friend,
who's interested in her.
As for me, my only
interest lies with you.
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
It's been a while.
[AKARI gasps]
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
I want your family's technique.
The poison Takamakuri.
[AKARI gasps]
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
I know you know it.
That's right.
Your pretty eyes give it away.
I do love those
Mamiya family eyes.
You see, I'm not a bad person.
I actually like you.
So much so...
I think I'll make you my pet.
[AKARI gasps]
[TAKACHIHO]
You in black!
Only I'm allowed to
mess around with Akari!
[AKARI]
Takachiho!
She's no one's pet but mine.
Interesting...
But she can't stop
what's already taken root.
Yes. It will bloom.
Either tonight, or by
end of day tomorrow.
But...
If you give yourself
over to me, completely,
like a loyal dog,
she won't have to suffer
the poison's effect.
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
This is where to find me.
Hold it right there!
[AKARI gasps]
[AKARI]
Nonoka!
Oh, there you are!
Thanks for coming!
I know it's short notice.
So how is she?
[AKARI]
Well... Too soon to tell.
[NONOKA] I know that
she'll pull through.
[AKARI] I don't know
how long I'm gonna be here,
so you'll have to
fend for yourself.
I want you to take
the train to Nagano
and stay with our aunt.
[NONOKA]
Wait... What's going on?
[AKARI]
I'll explain later, promise.
What's wrong?
[AKARI]
Nonoka?
Are you okay? Nonoka!
Well, I talked to the doctors.
They say for now her
vitals have stabilized.
But she's lost all her vision
in both of her eyes.
Help me...
I don't know what to do.
[AKARI]
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
The only thing I can do is
surrender myself to Kyochikutou.
[SHINO]
Akari...
[RAIKA]
Can't imagine how hard this is.
[TAKACHIHO] Has she ever had
this bad of an episode before?
I just know
she'll pull through.
If it weren't for
my family's traditions,
she wouldn't be here.
[KIRIN] What are the
Mamiya family traditions?
It's... nothing.
I've done nothing to earn
the right to be Aria's Amica.
I shouldn't have
argued with her.
I'm sorry, you guys.
I lied to you.
A person with my past
should never have
enrolled in Butei High.
[AKARI]
Centuries ago,
members of the Mamiya family
were spies for the Shogunate.
We were the equivalent of
the secret agents of today.
It was a dangerous
job back then,
and every day brought with it
another life-or-death battle.
[AKARI]
But out of that,
my ancestors developed
fighting techniques
they've passed down
to the present.
[MISUZU]
Akari. Nonoka.
Pay attention now, girls.
We Mamiyas have our own
special fighting techniques.
But since we're no
longer in the old days
of the Shogunate,
teaching you girls
this stuff is more
a way to honor
our family's history.
But while we may
live in peaceful times,
you can never be sure
it will last.
If that time ever comes...
[AKARI, NONOKA]
Yeah, yeah!
You must have the skills to
defend the regular people.
Right!
[MISUZU]
You're up, Akari!
I got it! I got it!
[NONOKA]
You did Tobiugachi!
That's good, but you
need to work on
turning your
opponent's momentum.
'Kay!
[MISUZU] All right,
since using real ingredients
is way too dangerous,
we're gonna use
colored sand and weeds
to learn how to mix poisons.
[NONOKA]
Cool!
[AKARI sneezes]
Oh, Akari.
You're messing up every other
Takamakuri batch you make.
If this keeps up, you won't be
able to use poison in battles.
It's a skill we teach
only to the eldest child,
so please master it.
I will!
Yeah. I know.
But then, just two years ago...
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
If you Mamiyas were as smart
as you think you are,
you would've surrendered.
Where'd Mom go?
We're supposed to
run away in an emergency,
with or without her.
That was her rule!
[AKARI gasps]
[NONOKA yelps]
[AKARI]
Nonoka! Are you okay?
Careful!
Go on! Get out of here!
The Mamiya bloodline.
You've openly defied the IU.
Refusing to share your coveted
techniques has forced our hand.
And that's the reason why
we're attacking you like this.
However, you're still
hiding some, aren't you?
For the sake of the girl
in my left hand,
that's unfortunate.
I will be poisoning her.
[AKARI]
Nonoka!
[KYOCHIKUTOU] You should never
forget the name Kyochikutou.
One day we'll meet again.
[AKARI]
After that night,
all the remaining members
of the Mamiya clan
scattered and went into hiding.
[HINA]
This poison's nasty stuff.
Her eyesight's gone,
and the rest of her
senses will soon follow.
Within eight days,
her life will go, too.
[AKARI gasps]
[HINA] Nonoka's condition is
caused by Fuchou Poison.
For two years after you're
injected, nothing happens.
Then you start fainting, your
senses go, and you're dead.
It's Kyochikutou's M.O.
[SHINO]
What do we do?
[AKARI]
Nonoka...
[HINA] On behalf of the
Fuma clan, I apologize.
Fuchou was originally
developed by us.
But a few years back,
Kyochikutou stole the recipe
and began using it for evil.
[TAKACHIHO]
She's a monster.
[KIRIN] There has to
be some kind of antidote.
[HINA]
It can be neutralized,
but only by the one
who injected it.
That means the person
who can save your sister
is also the one
trying to kill her.
[SHINO]
Akari?
[AKARI]
I'm going to see Kyochikutou.
Please don't do it!
We'll come up with a plan!
[AKARI]
Don't follow me!
This is the only move
I have left. I'm going.
[ARIA] A heroine sacrificing
herself makes for a good story,
but it's not a real answer.
Just a way to
avoid bigger problems.
You're up!
But your head...
This is more
important than me.
I overheard almost everything.
IU is coming after
the Mamiyas, too, huh?
I don't know what to do.
They're my enemy, too.
I can help.
But I need you to
be honest with me.
Listen, Akari.
Ever since we met,
you've been hiding
your background
and suppressing your
true abilities from us.
And that's why your Butei
rank stays so low.
Isn't it?
Had you been up front with me
and said IU was your enemy,
we could have approached
this differently.
[AKARI] The Mamiya family
techniques are used
for killing people.
I didn't feel
comfortable telling you.
I get it.
Your family history
doesn't exactly square
with your conscience.
But what about honoring
your mother's wishes?
The techniques could be used
not to hurt, but to protect.
I...
I do want that!
That's why I want to be...
...a Butei.
You want to change
those traditions
while keeping them alive.
Because you've learned that
the Butei law forbids killing.
[AKARI]
Uh huh.
It's just been a struggle to
get rid of the fighting habits
I was born into.
That's not in your blood,
it's in your head.
You can get over this!
[AKARI]
I can't do it. I've tried.
Quit it with that!
Now what was the first thing
I taught you, Akari?
[ARIA] I don't ever wanna
hear you say the words
"I can't" again for
the rest of your life.
Trust me.
The only thing that phrase does
is hold back your potential.
[AKARI]
But I can't remember them now!
I'm so disconnected
from those techniques
they seem like magic.
But in pushing all
that old stuff away.
I've been unable to
learn any new wisdom!
I have nothing now,
whether it's skills or family!
--[AKARI crying]
--[ARIA] You're wrong.
There's one thing
you're forgetting, Akari.
Something that can help
you get through this.
All right, then. What?
Turn around and you'll see it.
[ARIA] That's right.
You have something I don't.
You have that great
group of friends.
[AKARI]
Yeah, that's right.
Listen up, first years!
Recite Charter Article One!
Always trust in your
comrades and help them!
My friends...
[ARIA]
Akari.
I'm giving you your
first official operation.
[ARIA] You take down the enemy
trying to kill your sister,
and I will take care
of the person
who came close to killing me.
I've even come up
with a code name for this.
I was inspired by the
first letter of both our names.
[ARIA]
Operation Double A!
[KIRIN]
Hey, guys?
Guys, you can
hear me, right? Guys!
[RAIKA] Don't act so nervous.
Keep it cool.
[KIRIN]
What're you talking about?
I'm not acting nervous.
I'm not nervous.
See? Totally not.
You're nervous!
Yeah, it's me.
Kirin you're talking
like a person
who drank a whole pot
of black coffee.
Perfect spot.
I'm so good at this.
She went to this position
because they told her to.
But her ego is so...
...beau-ti-ful!
Shut up!
I'm trying to focus!
Let's go!
Roger!
[RECEPTIONISTS gasp]
I'm here! Let's talk!
[door opens]
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
So here's the situation.
[KYOCHIKUTOU] Nonoka is
dying from Fuchou Poison.
I'll give you the antidote...
...if you give me Takamakuri,
your clan's most secret poison.
As an additional prize,
I also get you.
[AKARI]
Takamakuri isn't a poison!
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Don't play dumb with me.
[AKARI]
That's our book of secrets!
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Deadlier than a thousand arrows.
It kills with one touch.
And this book says it
doesn't even leave a mark.
No trace.
Only poisons can act like that.
Some examples:
Arsenic is tasteless, odorless,
and dissolves in water.
One kilogram of botulinum
can wipe out mankind.
And oleander, aka Kyochikutou.
So you see...
Poisons are my very identity,
so I make it my life's work
to know them all.
So... Give me Takamakuri.
I want it.
I want it more than I've
ever wanted anything.
[AKARI gasps]
[AKARI] I'd never give it
to a psycho like you!
You're done!
This hotel is completely
surrounded by my Butei friends!
Oh. Well that's surprising.
[AKARI] We've all taken
classes in basic siege craft!
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Not what I meant.
I'm surprised to see
a bunch of tree frogs
not running from
a poisonous snake.
[KYOCHIKUTOU] This is your
last chance to be smart.
Come and join the IU, Akari.
This is your invitation.
I'll help you master skills
you didn't even know you had.
You'll be so much stronger.
Stronger than Aria Kanzaki.
Nothing you say will ever
make me join you!
The party's started!
[AKARI]
Where are you?
[KYOCHIKUTOU] Did you know that
oleander means "dangerous love"?
[KYOCHIKUTOU]
Now come play with me.
How would you like to die?
[RAIKA] Don't worry,
I'm still right on her tail!
[TAKACHIHO] I'll just have
to shoot them all!
[SHINO]
Akari, no!
Wait, what?
[KIRIN]
Hold back!
Butei are never
supposed to kill!
Come on, I'm very eager
to see Takamakuri.
[AKARI]
Kyochikutou...