- ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS.
NO CHICKENING OUT.
WHOEVER LOSES HAS TO
START THE WAR WITH CLASS D.
HOPE YOU'RE READY, YUUJI.
- PLAIN OLD ROCK, PAPER,
SCISSORS IS LAME.
TOO BAD IT'S NOT
ROCK, PAPER, KILL.
- WELL, IT'S NOT.
I'M CALLING ROCK.
- YEAH, IT WAS DUMB.
ALL RIGHT, YOU CALLED IT.
NOW, IF YOU DON'T USE ROCK,
I'LL KILL YOU.
ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
- ( sputters )
- BETTER GET MOVING.
- YOU FREAKING TRICKED ME.
- FIRST OF ALL,
YOU WALKED INTO IT.
SECOND OF ALL, YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT CLASS D TENDS
TO GO EASY ON THE GUYS
THAT ARE HOTTER.
- I SEE.  SO THEN I GUESS
I SHOULD BE OKAY, RIGHT?
- UH, NO.
YOU'RE NOT HOT, DUDE.
- WHATEVER. IF THERE WAS A
RANDOM CHART OF MY HOTNESS,
IT'D BE FILLED UP
WITH ONE SOLID COLOR.
- LOOK, A RANDOM CHART.
- AND YOU ONLY FILL UP 5%.
- I HATE YOU ALL.
- DON'T FORGET, WE'RE ALL
COUNTING ON YOU, DUDE.
- ( whimpers )
I THINK I NEED AN ADULT.
- ( theme song plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THIS AFTERNOON,
AS PLANNED,
AN S.T. WAR BETWEEN
SECOND YEAR CLASSES
F AND D
WILL TAKE PLACE.
SHOULD BE INTERESTING.
- INDEED.
I DO ENJOY STUBBORN IDIOTS.
DO YOU THINK THEY ACTUALLY
HAVE A CHANCE OF WINNING?
I WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT THAT.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- I'M CONCERNED ABOUT
CLASS-F STUDENT
YUUJI SAKAMOTO.
HIS SCORES HAVE BEEN DROPPING
WITH EVERY TEST HE TAKES.
- AND HE'S THEIR REP?
WHAT EXACTLY MAKES THEM THINK
THEY'LL BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT CLASS D?
IS THIS ALL SOME
KIND OF JOKE TO THEM
OR DO THEY THINK
THE S.T. WARS ARE A SILLY GAME
TO PLAY WHEN
THEY'RE BORED?
- NO, MA'AM,
I DON'T BELIEVE SO.
HAVE A LOOK.
- ( gasps )
- CLEAR THIS STUFF UP.
GOT TO BE PREPARED, GUYS.
EVERYTHING HAS TO BE PUT AWAY
BEFORE THE BATTLE.
- WE'LL NEED THIS SPACE.
I'M GUESSING OUR NEW GEAR
IS GONNA TAKE UP
MORE ROOM.
- I WILL BE SO GLAD
TO GET RID OF THESE BOXES.
- IT'LL BE LIKE WE'RE
REAL, LIVE PEOPLE, HIMEJI,
WITH A REAL, LIVE CLASSROOM.
- YUP, WE'RE GONNA DO IT
THIS TIME FOR SURE.
- THAT LETTER,
WHY DO I KEEP
GETTING THE FEELING
IT'S FOR YUUJI?
BUT EVEN IF IT IS,
HE'S ALREADY WITH SHOUKO.
- ( gasps, pants )
- MAYBE SHE STILL WANTS
TO GIVE IT TO HIM.
- EXCUSE ME.
DO WE NEED ALL OF THESE?
YOU REALIZE THE CAPTIONS
LESSEN MY ROLE.
- SO CLASS F HAS DECIDED
TO START A WAR WITH US
BECAUSE THEY DON'T
WANT TO USE BOXES ANYMORE.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S TOO DAMN BAD.
- ( booing )
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- WE'RE GONNA
SHOW THOSE LOSERS
THAT THEY'RE EXACTLY
WHERE THEY BELONG,
WITH THE GARBAGE!
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S WORK
ON OUR STRATEGY.
- STRATEGY, DUDE,
DON'T BE SO DRAMATIC.
WE'VE GOT HIMEJI, HELLO.
THAT'S LIKE AN AUTOMATIC WIN.
- HE'S GOT A POINT,
YOU KNOW.
HER STRENGTH IS
CLASS-A LEVEL.
- BUT, STILL,
YOU NEVER KNOW.
- OKAY, LISTEN UP.
CLASS E LOST BECAUSE
THEY DIDN'T KNOW
MIZUKI HIMEJI
WAS IN CLASS F.
HOWEVER, SINCE
WE KNOW THAT STRATEGY,
WE HAVE THE ADVANTAGE.
AS YOU KNOW,
OUR ROOM IS LOCATED
AT THE END OF THE NEW BUILDING.
AND OF COURSE,
THEIRS IS IN THE OLD ONE.
SINCE OUR FIGHTING POWER
WILL NEED TO SPREAD
OVER A LARGE BATTLEFIELD,
WE'LL HAVE THE UPPER HAND
BECAUSE OUR SCORES
ARE MUCH HIGHER.
- IF HIMEJI GOES IN THERE ALONE,
SHE'S DONE FOR.
IT'D BE EASY FOR CLASS D
TO ATTACK HER.
SHE'LL BE SURROUNDED
AND WON'T BE ABLE
TO REACH THE CLASS REP.
- GREAT, THEN WHAT
ARE WE GONNA DO?
- WE'LL USE SOMETHING
I LIKE TO CALL
BLITZ TACTICS.
FIRST, CLASS F
WILL MARCH
RIGHT INTO
THE ENEMY'S TRENCHES,
ATTACKING THEM
FROM THE REAR.
THIS IN TURN WILL
CREATE AN OPENING
IN THEIR DEFENSE.
THEN, HIMEJI...
- YES.
- YOU'LL BE UP NEXT.
YOU'RE MAKING A SURPRISE ATTACK
RIGHT DOWN THE CENTER.
THAT'LL THROW EVERYBODY OFF
AND YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO TAKE DOWN THEIR TOP GUY.
- GOT IT.
- WE CAN'T SPLIT UP THIS TIME
OR WE'LL DIE.
FORGET THE DEFENSE.
IT'S ALL ABOUT THE ATTACK!
WE GOT ONE SHOT AT THIS.
NO SCREWING AROUND, ALL RIGHT!?
CLASS D
IS GONNA EAT THOSE BOXES!
- THEIR DEFENSE
WILL BE WEAK SINCE
THEY'LL LIKELY
PUT ALL THEIR ENERGY
INTO ATTACKING US.
FORTUNATELY,
THE CLASS REP'S SCORE
IS PATHETICALLY LOW.
IF HE'S NOT GUARDED,
WE CAN TAKE HIM OUT
WITH ONE SHOT.
- Class D: OH!
- F HAS GOTTEN COCKY.
LET'S GO OUT THERE
AND CRUSH THOSE IDIOTS.
- Fukuhara:
AND JUST LIKE THAT,
THE WAR BEGAN.
- OKAY, LET'S DO THIS.
- YEAH!
- AKIHISA,
TAKE THE FRONT LINE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE
THE UNIT LEADER.
- WHAT? WHY ME?
- WHY? BECAUSE
IT'LL CONFUSE THEM.
DUDE, WE'VE NEVER
DONE THIS BEFORE.
AND THEY WON'T KNOW
HOW TO RESPOND TO IT.
TRUST ME.
YOU'RE OUR ONLY HOPE.
- YEAH, OKAY.
- ( boxes scraping )
- ARE THOSE SNAKES?
- I'M A SNAKE.
- ( sighs )
- SUMMON!
- WORST PLAN EVER!
- OH, WOW, HOW
ARE YOU STANDING HERE?
- BECAUSE BY SOME
FREAKING MIRACLE I DIDN'T DIE.
FIVE OF OUR PEOPLE
WERE JUST SENT TO
REMEDIAL CLASS, YOU JERK.
- KOUTA, LET'S TAKE
A LOOK AT THE LIST.
CHECK IT OUT. TELL ME WHAT
THEIR LINEUP WAS LIKE.
- THAT ONE, THIS ONE, AND HER.
THEY WERE ALL ON THE FRONT.
AND... HEY, I DON'T SEE
THE GUYS ANYWHERE.
- I DON'T DO GUY PICS.
- I SEE.
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
ANY OF THESE CHICKS
ARE GOOD AT MATH.
- SWEETNESS, GUESS
THAT MEANS I'M UP.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
ALL PART OF THE PLAN.
WE'VE MADE SURE TO SECURE
HASEGAWA. WE GOT THIS.
- HEY, ANYONE ELSE REMEMBER
THAT TIME I ALMOST DIED?!
SUGAWA, GO AHEAD AND
MAKE THE PREPARATIONS.
- ROGER THAT.
- Yuuji:
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
PREPARE TO ATTACK!
- MR. HASEGAWA,
MAY WE HAVE YOUR APPROVAL?
- APPROVAL GRANTED.
- SUMMON! HERE I COME.
IT'S AS IF YOU THINK
I'LL BE LESS OF A MATH GENIUS
IF THERE ARE MORE OF YOU.
- ( grunting )
- TAKE THIS, JERKS.
- ( screaming )
- ( groans )
- THOSE WHO DIED, MEET ME
IN THE REMEDIAL CLASSROOM.
- UGH! AW, MAN.
- I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO TAKE A CLASS
FROM IRON MAN.
- THAT'S NOT EVEN
A REAL CLASS.
IT'S TORTURE!
- WELL, THEN IT MUST BE WORKING.
JUST YOU WAIT.
YOU'LL SOON BE IDEAL STUDENTS
WHO STUDY TO RELAX,
ATTENDING PHILOSOPHY CLUBS
ON THE WEEKENDS.
SO PREPARE YOURSELVES.
- ( groaning )
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S ATTACK
THEIR LINE OF DEFENSE.
- ( cheering )
- IT'S THE CLASS F REP,
HE'S ENTERED THE NEW BUILDING.
- OKAY, MOVE IN.
- WE'VE GOT TO
KIDNAP HASEGAWA.
- EXCUSE ME?!
- SOME OF THE D-TROLLS
CAPTURED MR. HASEGAWA
AND ARE HOLDING HIM
IN THE BATHROOM.
- FORGET HIM.
IT'S A TRAP.
- BUT WHAT ABOUT MINAMI?
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH THE MATH FIELD?
- HOLY CRAP.  NO WAY.
THAT'S MR. TAKENAKA.
WHERE'D HE COME FROM?
- ( pants )
LET ME CATCH MY BREATH.
I APPROVE THE FIGHT
IN CLASSICAL LANGUAGE.
- OH, GREAT.  OF COURSE
THEY PICKED THAT ONE.
- DON'T WORRY,
I GOT YOUR BACK.
- SUGAWA!
- I NEED YOU
TO BUY ME SOME TIME.
- OKAY, WE'RE ON IT.
RIGHT, MINAMI?
- WHY'RE YOU ASKING ME?
( gasps )
- LOVE MONKEY!
SORRY IT'S COME TO THIS.
- WHAT? MIHARU?
- I DON'T KNOW THAT
I CAN EVEN LOOK AT SOMEONE
WHO'S BECOME A PUPPET
IN THE MAN SHOW,
MUCH LESS FIGHT THEM.
- OH BOY.
- BUT I'M GONNA TRY.
SUMMON!
THERE'S A BATTLE
IN EVERY LOVE STORY,
PRAIRIE DOG,
DON'T LOSE HOPE.
IF DESTINY WANTS TO
TEST OUR HEARTS, LET HER.
WE WILL SURVIVE THIS.
- WILL SOMEONE HELP ME?!
- CLASSICAL LANGUAGE, RIGHT?
- THANK YOU.
- ( music plays )
- Sugawa: MAY I HAVE YOUR
ATTENTION PLEASE.
THIS IS AN URGENT MESSAGE
FOR MS. FUNAKOSHI
IN THE MATH DEPARTMENT.
- IT'S SUGAWA!
- AKIHISA YOSHI IS SHIRTLESS
AND WAITING FOR YOU
IN FRONT OF CLASS D.
HE SAYS IT'S IMPORTANT.
- ( gasps )
- Fukuhara: PERHAPS A LITTLE
EXPLANATION IS NEEDED HERE.
MS. FUNAKOSHI IS
A 45-YEAR-OLD SINGLE WOMAN.
AND THAT MAY BE ENOUGH.
IF NOT,
LET'S JUST SAY SHE'S ONE
WHO BELIEVES IN EXTRA CREDIT.
- PLEASE HURRY,
MS. FUNAKOSHI.
YOUNG YOSHI SAYS IT'S
NOT ABOUT THE ASSIGNMENT.
SCREW THE ASSIGNMENT.
THIS IS ABOUT A MAN
AND HIS FEELINGS.
- SHUT UP!
- LOOK, IT'S MS. FUNAKOSHI.
- WHERE?! ( whimpers )
- YOSHI, YOU ARE THE MAN, MAN.
BEST LEADER EVER.
- THAT'S WHAT WE CALL
TAKING ONE FOR THE TEAM.
- COME ON, GUYS.
LET'S SHOW OUR LEADER
IT WASN'T ALL FOR NOTHING.
- All: YEAH!
- I'M GONNA GET YOU, SUGAWA!
- I WOULDN'T GET TOO COCKY,
CLASS D.
I THINK WE BOTH KNOW THERE'S
MORE THAN ONE MATH TEACHER.
HEY, THERE KOUTA,
GO GET MR. TAKENAKA.
- ROGER.
HEY, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO CHECK THE WIG.
- ( gasps )
I HAVE TO GO BE
IMPORTANT NOW!
( cries )
- ALL CLEAR!
- MS. FUNAKOSHI,
PLEASE APPROVE US.
- ( growls )
- OH, GOOD, I CAN WIN NOW.
TAKE THIS!
- ( crying )
- ( groans )
- THE PATH IS CLEAR.
- HIMEJI, YOU'RE UP.
- RIGHT.
SUMMONING MY AVATAR.
SUMMON!
- IT'S TOO LATE.
THIS IS OVER.
- EMERGENCY.
- KOUTA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( gasping )
- YOU'RE SURROUNDED.
I CAN SEE THEM
ON THE SPY CAMERA.
- THERE HE IS.
THAT'S THEIR REP.
- NOW'S OUR CHANCE.
LET'S GO.
- NOT SO FAST,
DEFEATING ME ISN'T THAT EASY.
- THAT KID MADE
A FOOL OF US, DIDN'T HE?
ALL THIS TIME, I THOUGHT
THEY MEANT TO INSULT HIM
BY CALLING HIM A SMART ASS.
- NO, WAY.  I HEARD YOU HAD
THE LOWEST SCORE EVER.
OH, YOU DID?
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
BUMMER, I GUESS I FORGOT TO ADD
MY LATEST SCORE TO THAT LIST.
INTENTIONAL INFO LEAK,
PRETTY HARD NOT TO FALL FOR.
- ( gasps )
- BUT I DIGRESS. LET'S GO!
- MIZUKI, BUT WHY?
- SO SORRY.
- ( groaning )
- WHAT A BUNCH OF CHUMPS.
TOO EASY.
- Fukuhara:
TIME FOR MORE "BAKA AND TEST."
- WE ACTUALLY BEAT THEM.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
- WAY TO BE SMART, MAN.
WHEN DID YOU START
STUDYING AND STUFF?
- AT THIS STAGE OF THE GAME,
IT'S NOT IMPORTANT.
WE'VE GOT BIGGER THINGS WE NEED
TO BE THINKING ABOUT.
LIKE BEATING CLASS A!
- ( groaning )
- FIRST THING WE NEED TO DO
IS DESTROY CLASS B.
WHO'S IN?!
- CORRECT ME IF I'M WRONG,
BUT ISN'T NEMOTO IN CLASS B?
- AFTER EVERY ONE OF US
HAS TAKEN A RECOVERY TEST,
WE'LL BE READY TO
DECLARE WAR ON THAT JERK.
HEY, AKIHISA, LISTEN UP.
I NEED YOUR HELP WITH SOMETHING
AND YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN DO IT.
- WHY DO I LET YOU
DO THESE THINGS?
- I'M JUST AMAZED
YOU KEEP FALLING FOR IT.
- ( screams )
- CLASS F HAS
DECIDED TO START
A CUTE LITTLE WAR
WITH US.
WELL, THEY'LL
LEARN SOON ENOUGH.
- I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU'VE HEARD ABOUT THIS.
BUT CLASS F DEFEATED
BOTH CLASS E AND CLASS D.
- ARE YOU AFRAID OF
THE LITTLE FREAKLINGS, YUUKA?
- OH, PLEASE.
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
CLASS C HAS ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
- THEN WHY WOULD
YOU EVEN SUGGEST
THAT CLASS B
MIGHT BE IN DANGER.
- I WAS SIMPLY THINKING.
- ABOUT THE MYSTERIOUS
WINNING STREAK?
EITHER THEY'RE CHEATING OR
HAVE SOME KIND OF SECRET WEAPON.
FIGHTING THEM HEAD-ON
ISN'T A VIABLE OPTION.
- YES, AGREED.
- JUST WAIT.
I'M WORKING ON A STRATEGY.
I'LL PAY THEM BACK FOR WHAT
THEY DID TO ME THE OTHER DAY.
- Yuuji: SO THAT'S HOW
IT'S ALL GOING DOWN.
I NEED YOU GUYS TO
TEAR IT UP OUT THERE.
WE'RE NOT GONNA
STOP WINNING NOW.
- YEAH!
- Yuuji: ALL RIGHT,
GET OUT OF HERE.
- All: SEE YOU LATER.
- ARE YOU SURE
IT WAS A GOOD IDEA
FOR US NOT TO MAKE
THE EXCHANGE WITH CLASS D?
- POSITIVE.
I'M PLANTING SEEDS AS THEY SAY.
- I THOUGHT IT WAS SOWING.
- JUST SIT BACK, RELAX,
AND WATCH WHAT HAPPENS.
- WHAT HAPPENED IN HERE?!
- WELL, IT'S OBVIOUS WHAT
HAPPENED, BUT WHO DID IT?
- I'M GUESSING CLASS B.
NOBODY ELSE SPRINGS TO MIND.
- I GUESS THEY WERE
TRYING TO SABOTAGE
OUR RECOVERY TEST BY
BREAKING OUR PENCILS IN HALF.
- LIKE WE CAN'T JUST
SHARPEN THE OTHER SIDE.
- LAME.
- ( gasps )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU OKAY?
- OH, YEAH, IT'S NOTHING.
- ( gasps )
NEMOTO'S GONNA GET IT!
- AFTER WE KILL HIM,
I'LL EAT HIS LIVER!
- JUST CALM DOWN.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO LOSE OUR COOL HERE.
- WHY NOT?
- BEATING THEM IN THE S.T. WAR
IS GONNA BE ENOUGH PAYBACK.
FREAKING OUT ABOUT THIS CRAP
IS WHAT CLASS B WANTS
BECAUSE IF WE LOSE FOCUS,
WE WON'T WIN.
- Fukuhara: AND THUS,
BEGAN THE SHOWDOWN
BETWEEN CLASS F
AND CLASS B.
- GET READY, GUYS.
KILL THEM ALL!
- YEAH!
- THERE THEY ARE!
LET'S KICK SOME BUTT.
- CLASS F
IS ON THE WAY.
- AFTER ALL THAT,
PATHETIC.
PROCEED AS WE PLANNED.
THEY STILL DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- CHARGE!
- NO, WAY.
THEY'RE TOO STRONG.
WE CAN'T BEAT 'EM.
- ( grunts )
- ARE WE REALLY GONNA
GO THROUGH WITH ALL THIS?
- IT'S CLASS B. WE KNEW THEY
WERE STRONG COMING INTO IT.
- YOSHI!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I DIDN'T THINK IT
WAS YOUR TURN YET.
IT'S NOT, BUT YUUJI
SAID FOR YOU TO USE THIS
IF YOU FEEL TRAPPED.
- WHAT IS IT?
HA! YES!
OKAY, YOU GUYS, LISTEN UP.
I JUST FOUND OUT THAT
THE CLASS B REP
NEMOTO HAS A GIRLFRIEND.
- WHAT?!
- HE'S SEEING
THE CLASS C REP, YUUKA KOYAMA.
- WHAT?!
- GET THIS.
I KNOW FOR A FACT
THAT SHE'S BEEN MAKING
HIS LUNCHES EVERY DAY.
- WHAT?!
- ONCE THEIR OUTRAGEOUS
FURY REACHES ITS PEAK,
THE F.F.F. INQUISITION
DELIVERS MERCILESS SLAUGHTER
IN WAYS THAT WOULD MAKE
THE REMEDIAL CLASSES
OF THE IRON MAN
FEEL EUPHORIC.
- THIS IS UNFORGIVABLE!
- GUILTY!
- HOW DARE HE CHOOSE
TO BE HAPPY!
IF WE ALL HAVE TO SUFFER
FROM BEING ALONE,
SO SHOULD HE!
- WHAT'S WITH THOSE GUYS?
CAREFUL, THEY LOOK
REALLY DANGEROUS.
- ( groans )
- WHO'S ON TOP NOW, JERKS?
COME ON, GUYS, LET'S GO.
- WHAT'S GOING ON WITH THEM?
- WHY AREN'T THEY AFRAID
OF THE REMEDIAL CLASS?
- WHAT IS IT?
- CLASS F IS ACTING CRAZY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOTTEN INTO THEM.
WHAT DO WE DO?
THEY'VE ALREADY TAKEN OUT
A LOT OF US, SIR.
- I THINK I SMELL
AN INSURANCE POLICY.
- THOSE WHO DIED, MEET ME
IN THE REMEDIAL CLASSROOM.
- THANK, SUGAWA, I'LL NEVER
FORGET THE SACRIFICE YOU MADE,
EVER.
OH, AND I JUST REALIZED
I'M NOT EVEN MAD
ABOUT THE COUGAR THING ANYMORE.
- I HAD A FEELING YOU
WERE HOLDING A GRUDGE
AGAINST HIM ABOUT
MS. FUNAKOSHI.
- THE SIZE OF OUR GROUP
IS SHRINKING.
WE NEED TO CHANGE FORMATION.
- Boys: RIGHT, OKAY.
- ANYONE FEELING WEAK,
SHOULD GO TAKE A RECOVERY TEST.
- HUH?
HEY, HIMEJI.
NEMOTO? WHAT THE CRAP?
- THAT WAS REALLY MEAN OF YOU
TO MESS UP OUR CLASSROOM.
WHY DID YOU HAVE
TO DO THAT?
- EXACTLY WHAT
PROOF DO YOU HAVE
THAT IT WAS CLASS B?
- THERE ISN'T ANY.
- ( laughs ) FINE, OKAY.
WE DID IT.  ARE YOU HAPPY NOW.
- THAT DOES IT.
I'M SUMMONING MY AVAT--
- OOPS, THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE,
WASN'T IT?
- ( gasps )
- COULD THIS BE A THANK YOU NOTE
FOR SAVING YOU
THE TROUBLE OF FINDING
EVIDENCE OF OUR WORK?
- DON'T OPEN IT.
- AND WHY NOT?
IS IT A LOVE LETTER?
TALK ABOUT
AN UNEXPECTED BONUS.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
PEOPLE STILL DID THAT.
HOW ADORABLE.
- STOP, GIVE IT BACK
TO ME RIGHT NOW.
- NOT YET, I HAVEN'T EVEN HAD
THE CHANCE TO READ IT.
YOU KNOW, I SHOULD
PROBABLY READ THIS
WHEN I'M NOT
IN SUCH A HURRY.
- WHY ARE YOU BEING THIS WAY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'LL
HELP ME WIN OR ANYTHING.
BUT I'LL TAKE IT
IN LIEU OF INSURANCE.
THANK YOU, YOU'LL GET IT BACK
AFTER THE WAR'S OVER.
THAT IS IF I DON'T
CHANGE MY MIND OF COURSE.
( laughing )
- ( banging )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
DID YOU LEAVE THE FIGHT?
FIGURED YOU KNEW
BETTER THAN THAT.
- DON'T START, DUDE.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR HIMEJI TO BE TAKEN
OUT OF THIS BATTLE.
- DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
- ( sighs ) FINE.
SHE'S OUT.
HOWEVER, BY REMOVING
HER FROM THE BATTLE,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
TAKE OVER HER ASSIGNMENT.
- OF COURSE, YEAH.
- I NEED YOU TO LAUNCH
A SURPRISE RAID ON THEM.
USE THE METHOD
OF YOUR CHOICE.
CAN YOU HANDLE IT?
- SURE, I'LL TRY.
SCREW THAT!
I'LL MAKE IT HAPPEN.
- THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
GO GET THEM, CHAMP.
- Akihisa: JUST ONE THING.
- Yuuji: WHAT IS IT?
- NO WAY, ARE YOU
REALLY GONNA DO THAT?
- IF I HAVE TO LAUNCH A SURPRISE
RAID ON CLASS B ALONE,
THEN IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
- WORKS IN THEORY,
BUT WHO'S GONNA GIVE YOU
SUMMONING APPROVAL?
- I DON'T NEED IT.  I'VE GOT
THIS LITTLE GEM, REMEMBER?
AWAKEN!
GO!
- ( shouts )
( grunts )
- IT'S NOTHING.
- ( grunts )
- ( screams )
- ( bangs )
- ( rumbling )
- WHOA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
- ( grunts )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
AKIHISA?!
- YEAH, I'M MORE THAN OKAY.
NO MATTER WHAT
HAPPENS TO ME...
I MADE A PROMISE AND
I'M GONNA MAKE THIS WORK.
I WON'T GIVE UP.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT THOSE JERKS DO.
THIS ONE'S FOR HIMEJI!
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- ( rumbling )
- ( screams )
THERE HE IS.
- DID YOU REALLY THINK
I WOULDN'T BE PREPARED
FOR THIS SORT OF THING?
I KNOW YOU WERE LOOKING FORWARD
TO SURPRISING ME.
- SHUT UP.
- KOUTA, WHERE ARE YOU?!
- WHAT THE HELL?
- OUR BATTLE WILL BE
IN HEALTH AND PHYS ED.
SUMMON!
- NO WAY,
HE CAN'T DO THAT.
HE CAN'T JUMP IN THERE
WITH A TEACHER.
- Fukuhara: OH, BUT HE CAN.
IRON MAN IS NOT ONLY
ABLE TO APPROVE BATTLES
IN EVERY SUBJECT, BUT HE CAN
JUMP WITH THE BEST OF THEM.
- UGH! KILL ME.
THIS WAR IS OVER.
CLASS F IS THE WINNER.
- ( cheers )
- IT'S A SHAME YOU GUYS LOST.
GOOD TRY THOUGH.
- YUUJI.
LISTEN UP, I'VE GOT A LITTLE
PROPOSAL FOR YOU GUYS.
- Class B: HUH?
- NOW, USUALLY, THIS
IS WHERE WE TRADE STUFF.
WE TAKE YOUR THINGS AND
LEAVE YOU WITH CARDBOARD BOXES,
BUT WE'LL SKIP THAT
UNDER ONE CONDITION OF COURSE.
- WHAT CONDITION?
- WEAR THIS.
YOU'LL LOOK HOT.
I PROMISE.
OH, AND YOU HAVE TO DO
WHATEVER I TELL YOU TO
FROM HERE ON OUT.
- WHAT?! THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
WHAT MADE YOU THINK
I'D EVER AGREE TO THAT?
- WE'LL MAKE SURE
HE AGREES TO IT.
- WE GOT YOUR BACK, YUUJI.
- I THINK THIS COLOR
REALLY BRINGS OUT YOUR EYES.
- Nemoto: ARGH!
I AM NOT WEARING A DRESS!
- ( banging )
- Nemoto: YOU'LL REGRET THIS.
GET OFF ME.
- DID YOU GET WHAT YOU WANTED?
I DID.
- YEAH.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HERE YOU GO, HIMEJI.
IT'S YOURS.
- THANK YOU, YOSHI.
IT MEANS SO MUCH TO ME
THAT YOU DID THIS.
I WAS COMPLETELY
WORRIED ABOUT IT.
- I KNOW, I COULD TELL.
I WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT IT.
- SORRY, GUESS I SHOULD
HAVE MAILED IT EARLIER.
IT'S MY FAULT.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE IGNORED
THE CHAIN LETTER'S
INSTRUCTIONS.
AND NOW I'VE BROUGHT
EVERYBODY MY BAD LUCK.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I WAS AFRAID
TO SEND THE LETTER
BECAUSE SO MANY
BAD THINGS HAPPENED.
I DIDN'T WANT ANYONE
TO GO THROUGH ALL OF THIS.
SO I KEPT IT,
BUT THEN I REALIZED...
A LOT OF GOOD THINGS
HAPPENED TOO.
SO IT MUST NOT
BE THAT CURSED.
I DON'T NEED
TO HOLD ONTO THIS.
I SHOULD EXPRESS
MY FEELINGS
WITHOUT HIDING
BEHIND A LETTER.
I KNOW THIS WON'T BE EASY,
BUT TELLING SOMEONE
IN MY OWN WORDS HOW I FEEL
JUST SEEMS RIGHT.
CAN I START WITH YOU?
- YEAH, SURE,
I'M HERE TO HELP.
- I WANTED TO ASK YOU,
CAN I--
CAN I CALL YOU AKIHISA?
- AH, WELL, NORMALLY
I'D SAY YES,
BUT YOU MIGHT NOT
WANT TO SAY THAT
AROUND THOSE
F.F.F. GUYS, YOU KNOW?
- I DON'T CARE ABOUT THEM.
IS IT ALL RIGHT WITH YOU?
- Akihisa: OKAY.
- YUUJI, WHY ARE YOU OBSESSED
WITH THE SUMMONER TEST WARS?
IS IT THE BOXES?
- OF COURSE NOT.
SHOUKO, THIS ISN'T ABOUT DESKS.
THIS IS ABOUT
PROVING TO EVERYONE
THAT LIFE DOESN'T
REVOLVE AROUND TEST SCORES.
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
AND THAT'S WHY
I'M COUNTING ON YOU
NOT TO GO EASY ON THEM.
- I WOULDN'T DREAM OF IT.
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
- Fukuhara: QUESTION 12,
"WHAT DO YOU CALL
THE LAST SCENE IN A STORY
SUCH AS A NOVEL OR PLAY
WHERE THINGS GET RESOLVED?"
- Akihisa: FINAL BOSS BATTLE.
- Fukuhara:
YOU NEED EXPERIENCE POINTS.
- Akihisa: NEXT TIME,
"LOVE, COURAGE,
AND OUR BATTLE
HAS JUST BEGUN."
TEMPORARY.
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.