- HEY, YOSHII.
- SIR!
- SUMMON NOW.
- Fukuhara: THE AVATAR
OF PROBATIONARY STUDENT
AKIHISA YOSHII
HAS SPECIAL SKILLS.
NOT ONLY CAN HE ACTUALLY TOUCH
OBJECTS IN THE REAL WORLD,
BUT BECAUSE HE HAS
HIGHLY INCREASED STRENGTH...
- GO GET THE WORLD MAP.
- ALL RIGHT.
- Fukuhara: THE TEACHERS FORCE
HIM TO HELP WITH THEIR CHORES.
- YOSHII! THEY NEED
SIX MORE DESKS
IN THE AUDIO-VISUAL ROOM
RIGHT NOW.
YOSHII! THE SOCCER GOAL POST
NEEDS TO BE MOVED BACK.
- AGAIN? WHY AM I THE ONLY ONE
WHO GETS ORDERED AROUND?
- YOU'RE A PROBATIONARY STUDENT.
GET USED TO IT.
- MAN, THIS TOTALLY SUCKS.
- Fukuhara:
THE PROBATIONARY STUDENT
FEELS THE EXACT SAME
PAIN HIS AVATAR FEELS.
- YOU'VE GOT A POP
QUIZ COMING UP
SO BE SURE TO REVIEW WHAT
YOU'VE LEARNED SO FAR.
- I'LL POP YOUR QUIZ
NEXT TIME MISTER JERKFACE.
- IDIOT.
- ( theme song playing )
- Fukuhara: TODAY IS SUNDAY.
HOWEVER...
- THAT'S IT FOR TODAY.
BUT MAKE SURE YOU GO OVER
IT AGAIN WHEN YOU GET HOME.
- Students: YES, SIR .
- Fukuhara: BUT EVEN
ON A SUNDAY,
CLASS F SOMETIMES HAS A
REMEDIAL LESSON.
- HE'S GONE, YOSHII. NOW TELL
US WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU.
- WELL, I TRIED TO
KICK HIS FACE IN.
- IT APPEARS TO HAVE
BACKFIRED ON YOU.
( stomach rumbling )
- I'M SO HUNGRY.
MY STOMACH'S NOT USED
TO ALL THAT HEAVY LIFTING.
HE REALLY WORKED ME HARD.
- YOUR AVATAR SEEMS REALLY COOL
BUT HE'S KIND OF A DRAG.
- ( bell rings )
- YUUJI. LUNCHTIME.
- SHOUKO. WHY ARE YOU HERE?
CLASS A DOESN'T HAVE
REMEDIAL WORK, DO THEY?
- I WAS STUDYING BY MYSELF.
IF YOU'RE AT SCHOOL ON A SUNDAY
THEN I'LL BE AT SCHOOL TOO.
- HOW 'BOUT... 'DON'T'.
- I STAY AT HOME WHEN YOU DO,
EVEN DURING THE WEEK.
- I HOPE YOU MEAN YOUR HOME.
- LOOK WHO DECIDED TO MAKE
THEIR OWN LUNCH TODAY.
- WHAT IS THAT THING?
- ONE SIXTY-SEVENTH
OF A CUP OF NOODLES.
- WHY ONLY ONE SIXTY-SEVENTH?
- ONE HALF OF ONE HALF
OF ONE HALF OF ONE HALF...
- AKIHISA. THAT'S ONLY ONE
SIXTY-FOURTH, YOU GOOBER.
- YOU'RE NOT REALLY A WHIZ
WITH THE FRACTIONS, HUH?
- I'M ALL DONE EATING.
- THAT'S PATHETIC.
- A HOBO WOULD LAUGH
AT THAT LUNCH.
- SOMEBODY HAS TO DO
THE RIGHT THING.
AKI, DO YOU WANT TO
SHARE MY LUNCH WITH ME?
- REALLY?
- YEAH, I MADE LIKE THIS
MASSIVE LUNCH TODAY
AND IT'D BE SILLY FOR
ME TO THROW IT OUT.
- DO YOU WANT SOME?
- OF COURSE!
- GIVE ME A SEC, OKAY?
MY BAD. LOOKS LIKE
I LEFT IT AT HOME.
- AW, MAN.
- AND AFTER I WORKED SO HARD...
- DON'T PRETEND.
IT'S AGAINST THE LAWS OF NATURE
FOR YOU TO DO GIRLIE THINGS
LIKE SHARE YOUR LUNCH
WITH A DUDE OR CROCHET.
IT'S LIKE A SPINE CRUSHING
PILE DRIVER!
I TOLD YOU THAT I JUST FORGOT
TO BRING IT! YOU IDIOT!
- CLOSER. LOWER.
- ( both grunting )
- LOOKING IS NOT ALLOWED.
- Yuuji: MY EYES!
MY FREAKIN EYES!
- IT'S CERTAINLY
NEVER BORING IN HERE.
- EXCUSE ME.
IS THIS THE CLASS
FOR ALL THE IDIOTS?
- HAZUKI? WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING HERE?
- HEY, SIS...
- YOU'RE HAZUKI?
- YUP. AND YOU'RE THE IDIOT.
- IMPRESSIVE, MAN.
I DIDN'T THINK EVERYBODY
IN THE WHOLE WORLD
KNEW HOW STUPID YOU WERE.
- NOT THE WORLD, JUST THIS AREA.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
I'VE MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
- HEY, HAZUKI.
EXACTLY HOW DO YOU KNOW AKI?
- SIMPLE. HE'S GOING TO BE
MY HUSBAND SOMEDAY.
WE'VE BEEN DATING FOR A WHILE
AND LATELY WE'VE STARTED TO TALK
ABOUT GETTING MARRIED.
- All: WHAT?
- Fukuhara: THE TWO OF THEM
KNEW EACH OTHER BEFORE TODAY
BUT THAT'S A STORY I WILL
HAVE TO SAVE FOR ANOTHER TIME.
- OKAY AKI. WHAT'D YOU DO
TO MY SISTER?
- ORDER. THE INQUISITION
IS NOW IN SESSION.
- Akihisa: WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU GUYS DOING TO ME?
- THE INQUISITION
ACCUSES AKIHISA YOSHII,
OF BREAKING OUR BLOOD
BROTHERS BOND,
WHICH PROHIBITS US
FROM ALL CHICK STUFF
LIKE DATING OR FEELING THINGS.
HOW DO YOU FIND?
- All: GUILTY! GUILTY!
- ANY LAST WORDS
FROM THE DEFENDANT?
- LAST WORDS? WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE WHOLE TRIAL THING?
- GUILTY. DEATH PENALTY.
- SO WHAT GRADE
ARE YOU IN HAZUKI?
- I'M IN FIFTH GRADE!
- SOMETHING TELLS ME YOU'RE
WAY TOO SMART FOR THIS GUY.
- WOW. I REALLY LIKE
YOUR PINK HAIR.
- YOU'RE SO SWEET, HAZUKI.
- ( screams )
- WELL, WHAT BRINGS YOU
OUT THIS WAY?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT!
HERE. YOU LEFT THESE
THIS MORNING.
- THE LUNCHES I MADE.
THANKS A LOT, HAZUKI. HOW SWEET.
I'M GLAD YOU BROUGHT ME
MY REALLY BIG LUNCH.
- SEE? TOLD YOU I WASN'T LYING.
I'M PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF MAKING
LUNCHES AND ALL THAT STUFF.
- NOW I SEE. IT'S STARTING
TO MAKE SENSE.
YOU NEVER WAKE UP EARLY AND
YOU WERE TAKING SO MUCH TIME
GIGGLING AND MAKING NOISE
IN THE KITCHEN. I DIDN'T GET IT.
BUT NOW I SEE YOU WERE
DOING IT ALL FOR A...
- I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT SHE'S TALKING ABOUT.
SHE'S SO WEIRD.
- I KNOW. WHAT SHE'S TRYING
TO SAY IS THAT YOU GOT UP EARLY
TO MAKE LUNCH FOR YOSHII.
- AS IF! I WOULDN'T BOTHER
MAKING A LUNCH FOR AKI.
- WELL, WHY'D YOU
WAKE UP EARLY THEN?
- I DIDN'T MAKE AN EXTRA LUNCH.
IT'S A GERMAN TANK.
- I MAKE MODELS.
- A GERMAN TANK?
- A SWEET KING TIGER
AT ONE THIRTY-FIFTH SCALE.
- IT'S NOT FOOD?
- Yuuji: THAT SHOULD BE A TASTY
LUNCH AND IT'S BIGGER THAN
ONE SIXTY-FOURTH
OF A CUP OF NOODLES.
- WHO CARES HOW BIG IT IS?
- NEVER KNOW. IT MIGHT
BE GOOD, JUST SAYIN'.
- IT'S A PLASTIC MODEL.
I CAN'T EAT IT.
- NOBODY IS EATING MY ONE
THIRTY FIFTH KING TIGER TANK.
HAVEN'T THE GERMANS
BEEN THROUGH ENOUGH?
- HEY, IS SOMETHING
WRONG? HIMEJI?
- WHAT? NO.
NOTHING'S WRONG WITH ME.
- IS THAT YOUR LUNCH?
- YOU MADE YOUR LUNCH TODAY TOO?
- I DID. BUT I'M
TERRIBLE AT MAKING FOOD.
- ( stomach rumbling )
- OH, WOW.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
I ACTUALLY MADE THIS
FOOD FOR YOSHII.
YOSHII, IF YOU'RE STILL HUNGRY
YOU CAN HAVE THIS.
- ORDER! THIS INQUISITION
IS NOW IN SESSION.
- Akihisa: HEY!
HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
- Sugawa: GUILTY. DEATH PENALTY.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT I'M BEING ACCUSED OF.
- Mizuki: PLEASE DON'T!
IT'S NOT HIS FAULT!
WELL, UM...
YOU SEE, I...
GIVE ME A SECOND.
YOU'RE ALL JUST STARING.
I MADE IT FOR...
- WE TORTURE FIRST, THEN DEATH!
- THAT'S A FRIKKIN
REAL FIRE PEOPLE!
( screaming )
- WHERE'S MY SISTER?
- IDIOT.
- Mizuki: BAKA AND TEST.
- I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD BE SMOKING.
- I'LL BE FINE.
BEING BURNED ALIVE
IS A SMALL PRICE TO PAY
FOR A BITE OF THE FOOD
YOU BROUGHT ME.
- SWEET. YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME.
I THOUGHT IF YOU ATE IT HERE,
WE WOULDN'T... YOU WOULDN'T
BE BOTHEREDBY ANYONE.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY.
WHOA! THAT LOOKS SO GOOD!
- YOU'RE TOO NICE.
I TOTALLY FORGOT TO GET
YOU SOMETHING TO DRINK.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- HIMEJI, SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL
AND SMART AND ON
TOP OF EVERYTHING,
SHE'S AWESOME AT COOKING.
- Yuuji: IN OTHER WORDS,
TOO GOOD FOR YOU.
- STOP THAT. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- Hideyoshi: I THINK I SHOULD
TRY SOME AS WELL.
- HIDEYOSHI, NO!
DIAL IT DOWN.
WHEN DID YOU GET SO STINGY?
( choking )
- YUUJI?
HIDEYOSHI? WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU GUYS?
WE HAVE TO GET THEM TO THE
NURSE'S OFFICE RIGHT NOW, DUDE!
NOT KOUTA TOO!
NO, DON'T TELL ME.
THEY ALL ATE THE LUNCH.
WELL, THAT SUCKS.
IT LOOKED LIKE REALLY GOOD FOOD.
( exclaims in disgust )
( screams )
THAT WAS CLOSE.
THE HANDS OF DEATH
NEARLY TOOK AWAY MY SOUL.
THAT PROVES IT THEN. THEY'VE
ALL BEEN POISONED BY HER FOOD.
THE SMELL ALONE NEARLY KILLED
ME. I GUESS I'M LUCKY.
- AKIHISA.
- YOU'RE NOT DEAD!
- HIGH FIVE. COME ON. DON'T
LEAVE ME HANGING LIKE THIS.
- HIGH FIVE?
- IF THIS IS THE END FOR ME,
I WANT TO GO OUT WITH A
SEMBLANCE OF MACHISMO.
THOUGH PERHAPS I'VE DISPLAYED
ENOUGH THROUGH THE YEARS
IN MY CROCHET CIRCLE.
- OH, MAN. HER FOOD
HAS STARTED TO WARP HIS BRAIN.
- I MADE SOME OF MY SPECIAL TEA.
- THANKS, HIMEJI.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE THEY ALL OKAY?
- THEY'RE FINE.
TAKING A NAP AFTER EATING
HELPS YOUR DIGESTION.
- IF YOU DO THAT YOU'LL END UP
GETTING AS FAT AS A COW.
- I'D RATHER BE A
COW EATING GRASS
THAN HAVE TO KILL MYSELF
EATING YOUR FOOD.
- HERE, HAVE SOME TEA.
- YOU MADE IT FOR ME
WITH YOUR VERY OWN HANDS.
THIS IS BAD. WHAT DO I DO?
( evil laughter )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU DON'T FEEL LIKE EATING?
UH, NO. YOUR FOOD JUST LOOKS
TOO PRECIOUS TO EAT.
- I KNEW IT.
BRINGING YOU LUNCH WAS DUMB.
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
THIS IS SO AWESOME OF YOU.
LOOK HOW HAPPY I AM.
- THAT'S GOOD.
- I'LL BET YOU'RE THE TYPE
WHO LIKES TO SNEAK LITTLE
NIBBLES OF YOUR COOKING
IN THE KITCHEN
WHILE YOU'RE MAKING IT?
- THEY SAY IF YOU EAT
WHILE YOU'RE COOKING
THAT YOU END UP GAINING WEIGHT.
AND BESIDES...
BESIDES WHAT?
- I WAS HOPING THAT YOU'D BE
THE VERY FIRST ONE TO TASTE IT.
- THERE'S NO ESCAPE NOW.
SHE HAS YOU TRAPPED.
WHAT A CRAPPY ANGEL. YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO AGREE WITH HIM!
- AKIHISA.
- YUUJI!
- HAVE A NICE NAP?
- YES, THANKS HIMEJI.
WOULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
I REALLY HAVE A CRAVING FOR
SOME OOLONG TEA RIGHT NOW.
- SURE. I'D LOVE TO.
- WHAT DO I DO?
- MY FRIEND, LET ME GIVE YOU
SOME WORDS OF WISDOM.
LISTEN WELL.
SINCE ANCIENT TIMES
THERE HAVE BEEN CERTAIN SPICES
THAT WERE KNOWN TO ACT
AS ANTIDOTES.
AND BEFORE REFRIGERATION
WAS INVENTED,
SPICES WERE USED TO CURE FOODS
FOR STORAGE.
THAT SAID, WHEN IT COMES
TO A WOMAN AND HER COOKING,
THE ONE SPICE THAT ALWAYS RISES
ABOVE ALL OTHERS IS LOVE.
YOU MEAN I HAVE TO...
- THAT'S RIGHT, AMIGO.
YOU CAN NEUTRALIZE
THE POISON.
WITH YOUR LOVE.
- GOODBYE. I KNOW
WHAT TO DO NOW.
THIS IS JUST THE FIRST TEST
OF MY TRUEST LOVE.
I HAVE FAITH. ANY TRIALS I FACE,
I CAN OVERCOME WITH THE
STRENGTH OF MY HEART.
AS LONG AS I HAVE THE SPICE
OF LOVE STINKING UP MY SOUL,
THERE'S NO POISON
THAT CAN STOP ME!
LOVE DOESN'T PROTECT
AGAINST POISON. CHECK.
- AKIHISA WAS
SUCH A BRAVE FRIEND.
- AMEN.
- OH MY. WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOSHII WHILE I WAS GONE?
- HE SAID AFTER LUNCH
HE FELT LIKE A NAP.
- IF YOU SLEEP AFTER EATING,
YOU'LL BECOME AS FAT AS A COW.
- OH, YEAH. WHATEVER
HAPPENED TO SHIMADA?
- AFTER ALL THAT WORK,
I WISH I WOULD HAVE JUST BEEN
HONEST AND ASKED HIM TO EAT IT.
- IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE.
BUT THERE'S ACTUALLY A SUBJECT
THAT HIMEJI IS BAD AT.
( stomach rumbling )
NOW I'M EVEN HUNGRIER
THAN I WAS BEFORE.
- AKI.
- HEY, STUPID, WAIT UP!
- HAZUKI, HEY.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE MY SISTER MIGHT BE?
UH, COME TO THINK OF IT,
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
( stomach rumbling )
- DID YOU HAVE LUNCH?
- THERE'S BEEN A LOT GOING ON
SO I HAVEN'T REALLY HAD
ANYTHING CONSIDERED FOOD.
- THEN YOU MUST BE STARVING.
- MMM, YEAH. I SHOULD HAVE
EATEN MINAMI'S LUNCH EARLIER.
- YOU MEAN BIG SISTER'S?
- UH-HUH. IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN NICE TO SEE
WHAT KIND OF LUNCH
SHE COOKED UP.
I BET IT WAS GOOD.
- OKAY!
AKI! YOU CAN STILL HAVE THIS...
- HEY, BABY ITS LUNCHTIME!
- YOU NEED TO GET SOME FOOD.
- I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
I WORKED REALLY HARD MAKING
THIS SPECIAL LUNCH
JUST FOR MY GORGEOUS LADY!
- WHAT ARE YOU EVEN DOING HERE?
CLASS D'S NOT MEETING TODAY!
- WELL IF YOU'RE HERE ON A
SUNDAY, THEN I'LL BE HERE TOO.
I'LL STAY HOME WHEN YOU DO,
EVEN ON A WEEKDAY.
- WHY IS THIS STUPID ACADEMY
FULL OF FREAKIN'
SCHIZOID STALKERS?
- AW SWEETIE, CAN'T WE SPEND
AN AFTERNOON OF PURE BLISS
TOGETHER EATING LUNCH?
- I GUESS WE COULD CHECK
FOR HER OVER THAT WAY.
- LEAVE ME ALONE! NO!
GET AWAY FROM ME! GET! NO!
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HER PROBLEM IS.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
SHY AROUND ME.
HONEY! SUGAR LIPS!
I REALLY DON'T LIKE HER.
FORGET IT, I HAVE TO FIND AKI.
HE'S WAY MORE IMPORTANT.
( panting )
- Hazuki: HI HO SILVER, AWAY!
FASTER! GO HORSEY! GO!
- WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO RUN IN THE HALLWAYS.
- ( laughing )
- AKI. NOW'S MY CHANCE.
NOTHING'S GOING TO GET
IN MY WAY THIS TIME.
- Sugawa: AND SO
THE TRUTH IS REVEALED.
YOSHII HAS HAD TWO GIRLS MAKING
LUNCH FOR HIM THIS ENTIRE TIME!
I FIND THAT
TO BE UNFORGIVABLE.
I SAY DEATH TO THE TRAITOR!
- All: DEATH TO THE TRAITOR!
- HOLD ON. IT'S ALL
A MISUNDERSTANDING.
IT'S NOT TRUE.
I JUST...
WELL, I...
( laughs )
- WHAT? HEY!
HOW DO YOU GUYS DO THAT!
LET ME GO! COME ON! YOU'RE
ALL A BUNCH OF MOUTH BREATHERS.
I CAN HEAR YOU!
- WHAT AM I TRYING TO DO HERE?
- Hazuki: GO HORSEY! GO! YAH!
FASTER! GO FASTER!
- RUNNING IN THE HALLWAYS
IS FROWNED UPON, HAZUKI.
- THIS ISN'T HALLWAY, SILLY.
- OH, YEAH. LOOKS LIKE
I'M RUNNING OUT OF GAS ALREADY.
- HE'S COMING RIGHT TOWARD ME.
AKI!
- MINAMI.
- THERE YOU ARE.
I'VE BEEN PLAYING HORSEY
WITH MR. DUM-DUM OVER THERE.
- THAT'S NICE.
BUT TRY NOT TO BUG HIM TOO MUCH.
- SURE.
- HEY, AKI.
DID YOU MANAGE
TO GET LUNCH TODAY?
I SORT OF HAD SOME.
BUT NOT REALLY MUCH.
I SEE. SO UH, DID YOU, UH...
WELL, IF YOU THINK YOU MIGHT
STILL BE HUNGRY...
I THOUGHT... WUH...
- WUH?
WUH... DANG IT...
( stuttering )
WHAT FOOD DO YOU THINK
HOKAIDO'S BEST KNOWN FOR?
- ( screaming )
- EVERYBODY KNOWS HOKAIDO'S
BEST DISH, SOFT SHELL CRABS.
HEY, KUBO.
IT'S WEIRD SEEING PEOPLE UP HERE
ON A SUNDAY.
ARE YOU HERE STUDYING
BY YOURSELF?
CLASS F HAD SOME REMEDIAL WORK.
( stomach rumbling )
- SOUNDS LIKE YOU
HAVEN'T HAD LUNCH.
- YEAH. NO. NOT REALLY.
- WOULD YOU LIKE
TO ACCOMPANY ME?
- YEAH. BUT I DON'T HAVE MONEY.
- OH, WELL, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I SUPPOSE I CAN COVER YOU
SINCE ITS JUST LUNCH.
- HECK YEAH!
I'M COMING WITH YOU.
- I GUESS WE'LL SEE YOU LATER
THEN, SHIMADA.
I'VE GOT A GREAT IDEA,
WE CAN QUIZ EACH OTHER FOR
MIDTERMS WHILE WE'RE EATING.
- MIDTERMS? UH, YEAH.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
- WELL, DID YOU EAT?
- NOT AT ALL. I WAS PLAYING WITH
STUPID-HEAD. I GUESS I FORGOT.
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG TO BE
SKIPPING MEALS.
IT'LL KEEP YOU FROM GROWING.
- DIDN'T YOU MAKE
THIS ONE FOR AKI?
- NO, GOOFBALL. WHY WOULD I DO
SOMETHING AS SILLY AS THAT?
I MADE IT FOR YOU.
- CAN WE EAT OURS TOGETHER?
- OF COURSE.
SORRY HAZUKI. I FORGOT I STILL
HAVE ANOTHER CLASS TO GO TO.
WHY DON'T YOU HEAD ON HOME?
- SURE. WATCH ME RUN FAST.
- MAN, I'D LOVE
TO SCARF LUNCH A
BUT I SHOULD
PROBABLY BE COOL
AND ORDER LUNCH B
SINCE IT'S CHEAPER.
- HEY, THERE, YOSHII.
- HEY, MR. FUKUHARA.
- PERFECT TIMING. I CAN'T SEEM
TO GET THIS LID TO OPEN UP.
WOULD YOU MIND
SUMMONING YOUR AVATAR
TO SEE IF HE CAN
GET IT OFF FOR ME?
- THAT'S A PIECE
OF CAKE FOR HIM.
I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR.
SUMMON!
OPEN!
( crying )
- THOSE WHO DIE GET
A REMEDIAL CLASS. YOSHII!
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS. WHAT?
COME ON! I HAVEN'T
EVEN EATEN YET.
- I ONCE WENT SIX MONTHS
- HE'S SO CUTE. AND
HE DOESN'T KNOW IT.
- Akihisa: IT WASN'T EVEN
A REAL BATTLE!
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING.
- I WILL EAT NOW.
- WHY ARE YOU SUCH
A FREAKING SPAZ ALL THE TIME?
HOW STUPID CAN YOU BE?
IS ANYONE GONNA
MAKE LUNCH FOR YOU?
NO. YOU EAT LUNCH ALONE
BECAUSE YOU'RE A CHICKEN.
IDIOT.
- NO! NO! NO!
( panting )
- AKI.
- ARE YOU REALLY
GONNA TOSS THAT?
UH, YEAH.
- WELL IT'S JUST BECAUSE...
SOMETHING...
SEE, I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD GO
AROUND WASTING STUFF LIKE THAT.
GLOBAL WARMING
IS KILLING OUR PLANET.
AND IF YOU THROW
THAT FOOD AWAY
THEN YOU'RE
A PLANET KILLER TOO
AND THE GHOST OF A DEAD HOMELESS
DUDE MIGHT HAUNT YOUR BATHTUB.
WHICH IS ALSO WHY YOU SHOULD
RECYCLE AND HUG A SPOTTED OWL
AND TRY TO STOP TALKING
SO MUCH IF YOU CAN,
IT'S MOSTLY HOW I FEEL.
- ( chuckles )
HERE.
DO YOU WANT IT?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO...
- WELL, I GUESS I COULD
TRY TO EAT IT.
I NEVER LIKE TO SEE FOOD WASTED.
MINAMI?
- IDIOT.
- ( theme song playing )
- Fukuhara: QUESTION 5.
WHAT DO YOU CALL THE
SPORT IN WHICH YOU GO
FROM CHECKPOINT TO CHECKPOINT
USING A MAP AND A COMPASS?
- Akihisa: ROLE-PLAYING GAME!
- I KNEW THAT WOULD BE
YOUR ANSWER.
- NEXT TIME! MAPS, TREASURES,
AND STRIKER SIGMA FIVE!
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.