- ( students chattering )
- Fukuhara: HERE
AT FUMIZUKI ACADEMY,
THE SCHOOL FESTIVAL KNOWN AS
"THE REFRESHING FESTIVAL"
IS FAST APPROACHING.
BECAUSE THIS SCHOOL
IS CONSIDERED SPECIAL
IN REGARDS TO ITS
SUMMONER TEST WAR ABILITIES,
THEY ALWAYS RECEIVE
A SIGNIFICANT TURNOUT
OF FRIENDS, FAMILY
AND STUDENTS.
IN ORDER TO LIVE UP
TO SUCH HIGH EXPECTATIONS,
THEY BEGIN PREPARING FOR IT
VERY EARLY.
SOME ACTUALLY WORK HARDER
ON THE FESTIVAL
THAN IN THEIR CLASSES.
"SOME" DOES NOT INCLUDE
YEAR 2, CLASS F.
- ( boy groans )
- HE'S FADING.
I GOT YOU, LITTLE BUDDY.
KOUTA, ARISE!
- Fukuhara: THEY WERE
PRACTICING C.P.R.
- ( upbeat song playing )
- IT HAD BEEN A FEW DAYS
SINCE THE PREPARATION BEGAN.
STUDENTS WERE DECORATING AND
PREPARING THEIR CONTRIBUTIONS.
"STUDENTS" DOES NOT INCLUDE
YEAR 2, CLASS F.
- Hideyoshi: PLAY BALL!
- Fukuhara: THEY WERE
PLAYING BASEBALL.
- ( boys cheering )
- COME ON, YOSHII,
LET'S GO.
- BRING IT.
YOU'RE SO ON.
- ( Akihisa's voice ) ALL RIGHT,
WHAT'VE YOU GOT FOR ME, YUUJI?
CURVE BALL.
ON IT.
AT HIS HEAD?
WHAT THE FUNHOUSE?
- YOU'RE CRAZY!
I'M NOT GONNA BEAN SUGAWA!
- NO HOLDING BACK.
RIGHT IN HERE.
- YOU'RE NUTS!
I CAN'T DO THAT!
- HEY, YOU PUNKS.
THAT BETTER NOT BE THE SMELL
OF SLACKING OFF.
- IRON MAN, HI.
- YOSHII, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- I'M STANDING ON A HILL DOING
WHAT EVERYONE ELSE IS DOING.
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS PICK ON ME?
IT'S NOT FAIR.  THE CLASS REP'S
RIGHT THERE.  ISN'T HE
SUPPOSED TO BE IN CHARGE?
- ( sighs )
- FORKBALL?
THROW IT WHERE?
AT HIS JUNK?
- DAMN IT!
STOP BEING A DOUCHE!
I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT.
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S ALL HIS FAULT.
- SHUT UP!
ALL OF YOU, JUST GO BACK
TO YOUR CLASSROOM.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONES WHO DON'T
HAVE A PLAN FOR THE FESTIVAL.
I SUGGEST YOU GET ON IT.
- Students: FINE.
- ALL RIGHT,
CHECK IT OUT:
WE HAVE TO DECIDE
WHAT TO DO FOR THIS FESTIVAL.
SO IF YOU HAVE ANY IDEAS,
JUST RAISE YOUR HAND.
KOUTA, WHAT YOU GOT FOR ME?
- ART GALLERY.
- AND WHAT KIND OF ART
ARE YOU HOPING TO SHOW?
- MYSTERY PHOTOS.
- WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
JUST WHAT IT SAYS--
PHOTOS OF MYSTERY.
ONLY IN OUR BOOTH,
WE REVEAL THE SECRETS.
- WELL, IT'S A START.
GO AHEAD AND WRITE IT DOWN.
- ALRIGHTY.
PHOTO GALLERY?
SECRET...
OR MYSTERY?
AND THAT'S WHERE WE REVEAL
STUFF AND THINGS.  GOT IT.
- GREAT.
ANYONE ELSE?
- HIMEJI, LET'S HEAR IT.
- I WAS THINKING
MAYBE IT WOULD BE FUN TO BUILD
A LITTLE WEDDING CAFE.
IT'S LIKE MAID CAFES,
EXCEPT ALL THE GIRLS WEAR
WEDDING DRESSES INSTEAD.
- O.M.G., IT'S PERFECT.
ALL THE GIRLS
ARE GONNA LOVE THAT,
PROBABLY AS MUCH
AS THE GUYS.
- NO GUY WOULD BE CAUGHT DEAD
IN THAT CAFE.
- YOU GOT THAT?
WRITE IT DOWN.
- I THINK I REMEMBERED
ALL THAT.
SO IT'S A WEDDING RESTAURANT,
OR--?
- ANY OTHER IDEAS?
- WE COULD ALSO DO
A CHINESE CAFE.
NO OTHER CLASS WOULD DO THAT.
WE COULD SERVE DIM SUM.
PLUS CHINESE CULTURE
IS SUPER DEEP,
LIKE, EMO-DEEP.
THEY'RE ALMOST
AS HARDCORE AS THE EUROPEANS,
EXCEPT WITH PANDAS.
- YOU GET ALL THAT?
WRITE IT DOWN.
- THINK SO.  A CHINESE-EUROPEAN
EMO PANDA CAFE THING?
- DUDE, WHAT THE HECK
DID YOU JUST SAY?
YOU CAN'T JUST WRITE DOWN
EVERY OTHER WORD, BUDDY.
- TURDLINGS, WHAT JOLLY HOLIDAY
IDEAS HAVE YOU COME UP WITH?
- HI.  WE HAVE
AT LEAST THREE RIGHT NOW.
- YOU MUST WANT
A REMEDIAL CLASS.
THAT'S FINE BY ME.
- WHY WOULD WE WANT THAT?
- PATHETIC.  YOU LITTLE BRATS
AMAZE ME SOMETIMES.
THIS IS A GREAT OPPORTUNITY
FOR YOU.
DON'T YOU WANT TO MAKE SOME
MONEY SO YOU CAN UPGRADE
YOUR CRAP EQUIPMENT?
- WAIT, SO DOES THAT MEAN
WE COULD BUY NEW DESKS
WITH THE MONEY WE MAKE?
- WHOA, I NEVER EVEN
THOUGHT OF IT THAT WAY.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT WOULD BE ALLOWED.  AWESOME.
- YOUR SCORES DON'T SEEM
TO BE IMPROVING
AND THERE'S REALLY
NOWHERE ELSE TO GO
AFTER CARDBOARD BOXES,
UNFORTUNATELY.
IT MAKES ME WONDER
IF THE EQUIPMENT
IS INTERFERING
WITH YOUR STUDIES.
IF SO, WE HAVE OUR
PRIORITIES WRONG.
PUNISHING YOU SHOULD NOT BE
MORE IMPORTANT.
I'LL TALK TO THE PRINCIPAL
ABOUT IT TODAY.
- DO YOU MEAN IT?
- WHAT IS THIS WORLD
YOU SPEAK OF WHERE WE DON'T HAVE
TO STUDY ATOP CARDBOARD MATS?
- IF WE CAN, IT WOULD REALLY
HELP ME CONVINCE DAD.
- WHAT'S YOUR DAD
HAVE TO DO WITH THIS?
- NOTHING.  SORRY,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
- UH, YOU WERE SAYING
THAT SOUNDS AWESOME.
- ALL RIGHT, WE'RE READY
TO TAKE A VOTE THEN.
WHICH OF THESE THREE IDEAS...
- WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
- THAT'S AWESOME.
WE'RE GONNA GET SO MANY
CUSTOMERS WITH THIS.
- HOPE SO.  WE SERIOUSLY CANNOT
AFFORD TO FAIL THIS TIME, AKI.
BRING YOUR A-GAME.
PROMISE?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"THIS TIME"?
- WELL, I TOLD HER
I WASN'T GONNA SAY ANYTHING,
BUT IT'S MIZUKI.
HER PARENTS ARE WANTING HER
TO SWITCH SCHOOLS.
- DID SHE JUST SAY
WHAT I THINK SHE SAID?
CHANGE SCHOOLS?
SHE CAN'T DO THAT.
WE STILL HAVE SO MUCH
WE HAVE TO DO TOGETHER.
SHE'S THE ONLY SLICE OF A MENTAL
BREAK I HAVE FROM CLASS F.
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO ALL OF US
IF SHE CHANGES SCHOOLS?
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
EVERYONE WILL FALL INTO
A DEEP DEPRESSION.
WE'LL HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO GROW MOHAWKS
JUST LIKE IN
"FIST OF THE NORTH STAR."
VIOLENCE WILL BREAK OUT.  THERE
WILL BE LOOTING IN THE STREETS.
AND THE ONLY WOMAN LEFT FOR US
TO FIGHT FOR WILL BE HIDEYOSHI.
- ( laughing )
- I THINK HE MIGHT BE HAVING
A SYSTEM MELTDOWN.
- LIKE HE HAS A SYSTEM
TO START WITH.
- COME ON, YOU GOTTA
SNAP OUT OF THIS.
- HIDEYOSHI, WOULD YOU STILL
LOVE ME IF I HAD A MOHAWK?
IT WOULD COME WITH
WASHBOARD ABS.
- WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
YOU'RE SO WEIRD SOMETIMES.
WHAT DOES THAT HAVE TO DO WITH
MIZUKI CHANGING SCHOOLS?
- WHY DO THEY WANT HER TO CHANGE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE YEAR?
- THEY'RE JUST WORRIED
ABOUT HER.
THEY DON'T THINK
HER GRADES WILL IMPROVE
IF SHE HAS TO STAY
IN CLASS F.
- THAT'S NOT ALL.
IT'S THE WHOLE ENVIRONMENT HERE.
SHE'S AROUND DUDES WHO ONLY COME
TO SCHOOL TO SCREW AROUND
ALL DAY.  IF I WAS HER OLD MAN,
I'D BE WORRIED TOO.
- SO, YEAH, THEY THINK
IF SHE GOES TO A SCHOOL
WITH A MORE NORMAL ENVIRONMENT,
SHE'LL BE ABLE TO FOCUS.
- BEFORE-- CONVINCE HER DAD
TO KEEP HER HERE--
THAT'S WHAT SHE MEANT, HUH?
- MM-HMM.
- SO MAYBE IF WE BUY A FULL SET
OF DECENT EQUIPMENT,
IT'LL LOOK LIKE A NORMAL SCHOOL
AND SHE'LL BE ABLE TO STAY.
- GOOD PLAN.  THAT MEANS
WE CAN'T FAIL.  YOU GOT THAT?
- HEY, YOU GUYS, WE'RE BACK.
- WHAT IS THAT STUFF?
- IT'S A DISH KOUTA MADE
FOR THE CHINESE CULTURE CAFE.
WE WERE HOPING
THAT YOU WOULD TEST IT OUT.
- THEY'RE SESAME DUMPLINGS.
- COOL.
YEAH, I'LL TRY 'EM.
HEY, THOSE ARE
PRETTY GOOD.
- YUM, LOVING THE CRISPY OUTSIDE
AND CHEWY INSIDE.
- AND THEY'RE NOT TOO SWEET.
GOOD JOB.
- THESE WOULD GO REALLY WELL
WITH TEA.
- I'LL GO MAKE SOME RIGHT NOW.
- WAIT, I'LL HELP YOU.
- WOW, ARE THEY REALLY
THAT AMAZING?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TRY.
THAT IS DEFINITELY
A VERY CHEWY INSIDE.
IT'S NOT TOO SWEET
OR SPICY.
IT'S-- ( mumbles )
- WHAT HAPPENED?  ARE YOU OKAY?
- KOUTA, WHAT DID YOU DO?
DID YOU REALLY MAKE
ALL THOSE DUMPLINGS?
- OF COURSE.
EXCEPT I ONLY MADE
THREE OF THEM.
WHERE'D THE OTHERS COME FROM?
- BY THE WAY HE'S ACTING,
I'D SAY
THAT HIMEJI TRIED HER OWN
VERSION OF THE RECIPE.
- THAT WAS CLOSE,
LIKE FOOD RUSSIAN ROULETTE,
EXCEPT WITH
FIFTY-FIFTY ODDS.
- ( Akihisa laughs ) IS THAT
YOU, GRANDFATHER?  I MISSED YOU.
- Hideyoshi: THAT KIND OF STUFF
ONLY HAPPENS TO HIM.
- ( students chattering )
- Fukuhara: THE DAY
OF THE SCHOOL FESTIVAL
HAD FINALLY ARRIVED.
- WELCOME TO CHINESE CAFE
OF EUROPE.  WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE?
- IS THERE A DOCTOR
IN THE HOUSE?  WHO KNOWS C.P.R.?
- Fukuhara: OH, WAIT,
YOU'VE SEEN THIS ALREADY.
- YOSHII, WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH
PEOPLE IN THE KITCHEN.
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
HELP US OUT?
- WHATEVER.
I GUESS I'LL DO IT MYSELF.
- Mizuki: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
COME AGAIN.
- WELCOME TO CHINESE CAFE
OF EUROPE.
WE'RE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHO OUR CUSTOMERS'
FAVORITE WAITRESS IS.
PLEASE FILL OUT OUR SURVEY
AND TURN IT IN TO ME
WHEN YOU LEAVE.
- CHECK IT OUT.  IT TOTALLY
LOOKS LIKE A CAFE IN THERE.
- I KNOW.  WE'RE GETTING
SO MANY CUSTOMERS TOO.
THOSE NEW DESKS
ARE AS GOOD AS OURS.
- HEY, HOW LONG DO YOU
EXPECT US TO WAIT?
- HEY, PINKY,
HURRY IT UP, HUH?
I DON'T HAVE ALL DAY
TO SPEND IN HERE, YOU KNOW.
- WHAT?
I'M SORRY.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE YET.
- ( groans ) SERIOUSLY?
WE'VE BEEN HERE FOREVER.
- WHAT KIND OF JACKED-UP CAFE
IS THIS?
WHY ARE WE THE ONES
WAITING ON YOU?  HELLO?
- REALLY SORRY.  I'LL BE THERE
IN JUST A MINUTE, OKAY?
- DOUCHEBAGS.
WHY ARE THEY ACTING LIKE THAT?
- THIRD-YEAR GUYS
TRYING TO GIVE HER A HARD TIME.
- THIS SUCKS.
- I'M FREAKIN' HUNGRY.
DO I HAVE TO GO
COOK IT MYSELF?
WELL AT LEAST
THAT'S A START.
YUMMY.
IT'S LIKE A CRISPY GUMBALL
EXPLODING IN MY MOUTH.
- IT FEELS LIKE
A CHINESE WONDERLAND.
- OH, NO.
THIS IS BAD.
300 JOULES.
CHARGE!
- 300.
ROGER THAT.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
- THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
- YOU'VE DONE THIS BEFORE.
- I TEND TO LIVE MY LIFE
VERY CLOSE TO DEATH.
- VERY DEEP.
WHAT JUST HAPPENED IN HERE?
WHOA.  NO WAY.
- IDIOTS.  WHAT KIND OF FREAK
EATS THE DISPLAY FOOD?
- I'M-- I'M ALIVE.
WHAT WAS IN THAT?
- YOU LITTLE PUNKS.
ARE YOU TRYING TO KILL US?
GET OVER HERE.
- COME ON, SURVIVAL MODE,
HELP ME OUT HERE.
- ( bell dinging )
- CONGRATULATIONS, YOU TWO.
YOU WON.
YOU HIT THE JACKPOT.
- WAIT, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WE WIN A PRIZE OR SOMETHING?
LIKE CASH?  THE HELL IS IT?
- OF COURSE YOU GUYS
WIN A PRIZE.
IT'S BETTER THAN CASH.
IT'S, UH...
ONE OF THESE.  YUM.
- I DON'T WANT THAT.
YOU WON'T GET AWAY
WITH THIS.
- NO WAY.  WE'RE GONNA
CLOSE THIS DUMP DOWN.
- OH, PLEASE.  WE DIDN'T
FORCE YOU TO EAT THOSE.
- SHUT UP.
WHO'S IN CHARGE--?
- IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M YUUJI, THE CLASS REP.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE NOT
HAVING A GOOD TIME.
WHAT SEEMS TO BE
THE PROBLEM?
- WELL, FOR ONE, MY BUDDY JUST
GOT PUNCHED OUT FOR NO REASON.
- WE WERE NEGOTIATING.
THEY ALWAYS SAY
TO START THINGS OFF
WITH A PUNCH, DON'T THEY?
- I'M GONNA PUNCH YOU
IN THE HEAD, YOU BASTARD!
- AND THEN,
YOUR FOLLOW-THROUGH
SHOULD ALWAYS
KICK IT UP A NOTCH.
- MAN, THAT FREAKIN' HURT.
TSUNEMURA.
HEY THERE.
HOW'S IT GOING?
- AND NOW,
TO CLOSE THE DEAL,
I OFFER UP MY PRO WRESTLING
BACKBREAKER HOLD.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
I THINK I KIND OF GET IT.
- OKAY, FINE.
AND NOW,
NEGOTIATION COMPLETE.
- THAT'S A PRETTY
INTENSE LOCK HE'S GOT.
- HE REALLY KARL-GOTCHED
HIS FACE OFF.
- GOODBYE.  THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING IN.
- Minami: WHY'S IT ALL SLOW
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- IT'S SORT OF WEIRD.  WE SHOULD
BE GETTING A LUNCH RUSH.
- Yuuji: IT WON'T BE GOOD
IF IT STAYS LIKE THIS.
- HELLO AND WELCOME.
WHAT THE--?
- HEY, YOU GUYS.
DUMMY.
- HAZUKI, SO GOOD
TO SEE YOU.
- THANKS, YOU TOO.  I CAME
TO HELP YOU WITH THE FESTIVAL.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
TELL ME.
- THANK YOU.  THAT'S SO NICE.
- SURE.  ANYTHING FOR YOU.
BESIDES, YOU'RE MY FUTURE
HUSBAND.  IT'S MY JOB.
REMEMBER?  HOW COULD YOU FORGET
OUR VERY FIRST KISS?
- Akihisa: HEY, WHAT AM I DOING
ON THE FLOOR?
- Minami: KOUTA, I NEED FORKS.
FIVE SHOULD BE ENOUGH.
- Mizuki: I NEED SOME TOO,
SO GET 10, PLEASE.
- NO!
( screams )
- Sugawa: QUIET.  WE ARE
ABOUT TO START THE INQUISITION.
SURVEY SAYS,
DEATH PENALTY.
- ( Akihisa screams )
GET OFF ME!  I'M INNOCENT!
- I'M SORRY YOU CAME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
WE'RE PRETTY DEAD RIGHT NOW.
NOT SURE WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT I DOUBT ANYONE ELSE
WILL BE COMING AT THIS POINT.
- WE APPRECIATE IT.
WE JUST DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING FOR YOU TO DO.
- OKAY, BUT I REALLY
WANTED
TO WEAR A CHINESE DRESS
LIKE YOU GET TO.
- 100 MEAT BUNS,
AND STEP ON IT.
- Yuuji: GO GET THEM
YOURSELF.
- IS THIS BECAUSE OF THAT
CRAZY RUMOR I HEARD?
- A RUMOR?
- YEAH.
- ON MY WAY HERE I GOT LOST,
SO I ASKED ANYONE I RAN INTO
WHERE MY STUPID POTATOHEAD
BOYFRIEND'S CAFE WAS.
THEY ALL SENT ME TO THE RIGHT
PLACE RIGHT AWAY.
- YOU'RE ALREADY
A HOUSEHOLD NAME.
- YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT ME?
- YEAH, BUT THAT'S NOT ALL.
THEY TOLD ME
I SHOULDN'T COME HERE.
THEY SAID IT WAS FILTHY
AND TO STAY AWAY.
- THAT'S TERRIBLE.
- BUT WE ALL CLEANED
THE WHOLE PLACE, AND TOTALLY
DECORATED HARDCORE.
- THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
ALL OF OUR CUSTOMERS WERE HAPPY.
THEY GAVE US
GOOD REVIEWS ANYWAY.
- YEAH, ALL BUT TWO
OF THEM.
I KNOW.
IT'S THE TSUNEKAWA DUO.
THEY'RE THE TWO JERKS
WHO CAME IN EARLIER.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- TSUNEMURA AND NATSUKAWA--
THEIR NAMES COMBINED,
YOU KNOW, LIKE FANCY
CELEBRITY COUPLES.
- OH, I GET IT.
- I'M GONNA MAKE 'EM
BEG FOR MERCY.
JUST WAIT UNTIL I FIND
THOSE PANSIES AGAIN.
- SPIT IT OUT.  WHERE'D IT
COME FROM?  WHO'D YOU TALK TO?
- AT ANOTHER CAFE,
WITH THE PRETTY SISTERS.
- ON IT.  I WON'T REST
UNTIL I FIND THEM.
- DOES THIS MEAN NEW DESKS
ARE NO LONGER THE PRIORITY?
- I GUESS THIS IS THE CAFE
HAZUKI WAS TALKING ABOUT.
DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
ANYTHING SHADY IS GOING ON.
- WE DID
JUST GET HERE.
- WELCOME HOME, MASTER.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- SHOUKO, YOU LOOK
SO PRETTY IN THAT.
- THANK YOU.
I KNOW.
I WON'T LET YOU LEAVE.
I'VE MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
MISS ME?
- IT'S TIME TO GO, YOSHII.
WOULD YOU LIKE A MENU?
- Akihisa: THANKS.
LET'S SEE, I WILL HAVE...
WATER, PLEASE.
- CERTAINLY, SIR.
WHAT CAN I GET YOU,
MASTER?
- TO START,
YOU CAN EXPLAIN THIS TO ME.
- OUR LIST OF SPECIALS.
FIRST IS A HONEYMOON
WITH A MAID.
DINNER AND
MAKE OUT WITH A MAID.
OR JUST SWEET KISSES
WITH A MAID.
SUPPLIES ARE LIMITED.
I SUGGEST YOU ORDER QUICKLY.
- SCREW THAT!
- NOW THIS IS
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
IT PUTS THAT CHINESE JOINT
TO SHAME.
I'M ALREADY 1000% SOLD.
CLASS F SUCKS.
- DUDE, I KNOW, RIGHT?
THAT PLACE SMELLED
LIKE FISH AND PISS.
AND THE WAITRESSES?
COULDN'T HAVE BEEN UGLIER.
ALSO, CAN WE TALK
ABOUT THE NAME?
"THE CHINESE CAFE OF EUROPE"?
- ( both laughing )
- A-HOLES.
NONE OF THAT'S TRUE.
- EH, THE NAME WAS
KIND OF LAME.
I'M GOING AFTER THEM.
- NO YOU'RE NOT.
NOT RIGHT NOW ANYWAY.
OUR REPUTATION
IS BAD ENOUGH AS IT IS.
DON'T BE SUCH AN IDIOT.
- WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST WE DO?
LET ME SEE.  SHOUKO, WE NEED
TO BORROW YOUR MAID COSTUME.
- MY PLEASURE.
- ( screams ) NOT NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU SAID YOU WANTED ME
TO TAKE MY MAID COSTUME OFF.
- I DID NOT.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
I JUST SAID WE WANTED
TO BORROW IT, LIKE, LATER.
- I HAVE AN EXTRA ONE.
- WILL YOU QUIT ACTING
LIKE I DID SOMETHING WRONG?
- SO, UH, WHAT'S
THE DRESS FOR ANYWAY?
- FOR HIDEYOSHI.  HE'S ABOUT
TO BE A BIG HELP TO US.
- GOTCHA.
I SEE WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DOES THIS LOOK WOMANLY ENOUGH?
- Yuuji: MM, YOU ARE HOT, MAN.
IT'S ALMOST STUPID HOW HOT.
- Hideyoshi: IT'S THE MAKEUP.
I PICKED UP A FEW TRICKS
HERE AND THERE.
- Akihisa: WAIT, IS THAT A BRA?
- THE BEST PERFORMANCES
REQUIRE FULL COMMITMENT,
RIGHT DOWN TO THE UNDERWEAR.
- PANTIES TOO?
- SERIOUSLY, I DON'T KNOW WHY
ANYONE WOULD TORTURE THEMSELVES
BY GOING THERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- EXCEPT MAYBE OTHER
MEMBERS OF CLASS F
WHO ARE USED TO THE STENCH.
- ( both laughing )
- Tsunemura: CAN I HELP YOU,
GORGEOUS?
- ( Natsukawa whistles )
DAMN, YOU'RE HOT.
- HEY, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
A LITTLE LOWE--
- Akihisa: GO TO HELL!
- I'M IN TROUBLE.
- NO WAY.
YOU'RE THAT DUDE FROM CLASS F.
- DAMN IT.
ARGH! HELP ME.
THIS DISGUSTING BOY WON'T STOP
LOOKING UP MY SKIRT.
- WHAT?
THAT'S NOT A CHICK.
- HOW CAN ANYONE DEGRADE A WOMAN
LIKE THAT, AND IN PUBLIC TOO?
- THAT IS B.S.  WE WERE
JUST DEFENDING OURSELVES.
- Yuuji: I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR IT.  I SAW YOUR BUDDY
TRY TO GIVE HER
A T-TWISTER.
- ARGH!  THAT PERVERT
SNAPPED OFF MY BRA.
- WHAT THE HELL?
WHY WON'T IT COME OFF?
- LOOK AT HIM.
MAN, TALK ABOUT DESPERATE.
- THAT IS SO NOT
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
- ( people chattering )
- WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE.
YOU'RE ALL A BUNCH OF TOOLS.
- HEY, HOLD IT.
- IT LOOKS GOOD,
BUT IF IT ISN'T AUTHENTIC,
IT WON'T HAVE
THE SAME EFFECT.
I JUST NEED TO FIND
SOMETHING SCARIER IN GENERAL.
- BASTARDS.  THEY'RE NOT GONNA
GET AWAY WITH THIS.
- THEY'RE BEGGING FOR US
TO MAKE THEM PAY FOR THAT CRAP
AND I DON'T CARE
IF IT TAKES US ALL YEAR.
- WHAT DO WE DO?
- I HAVE AN IDEA.  FOLLOW ME.
COME ON.
- WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
I MUST HAVE JUST FALLEN ASLEEP
AND HAD A NIGHTMARE.
MAKES SENSE,
AFTER SEEING THAT.
I SUPPOSE THE WAY
TO REVERSE THAT
IS TO THINK
OF SOMETHING BEAUTIFUL.
OH, SO BEAUTIFUL.
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
- IT MUST MEAN I'M THINKING OF
MY SWEET YOSHII FAR TOO MUCH.
THAT GIRL'S FACE--
I COULD'VE SWORN IT WAS--
NO.  WHAT IS WRONG
WITH ME?
AM I TRYING TO MASK
MY FEELINGS FOR YOSHII
BY IMAGINING HIS EYES
ON A BEAUTIFUL GIRL?
WHY DIDN'T I GET
HER NAME?
I KNOW WHY--
BECAUSE I'VE GOT YOSHII.
BUT I STILL SHOULD HAVE
TALKED TO HER LIKE ANY OTHER
TESTOSTERONE-FILLED MAN
WOULD HAVE DONE.
NO, YOSHII IS
ALL THE WOMAN I NEED.
WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO?
- WHATEVER IT IS,
DO IT FAST.
- HELLO THERE.
THANKS FOR COMING.
- MINAMI, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE GETTING MORE CUSTOMERS.
- YEAH, WE ARE.
I GUESS THEY PULLED IT OFF.
- OKAY, DONE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO NOW?
- DAMN, WE LET THEM
GET AWAY.
- WHAT'S OUR PLAN B?
WE CAN'T JUST LET THEM
GO SOMEWHERE ELSE
AND SPREAD THOSE RUMORS.
- ( panting )
- HMM?
- HEY.
WHAT'S WITH YOU?
- BAD NEWS.  ONE OF OUR
WAITRESSES HAS BEEN KIDNAPPED.
- ( phone ringing )
- YOSHII'S PHONE.
- Natsukawa: Hey.
You messed with
the wrong guy, limp wad.
- Tsunemura: Now it's our turn.
We're having some fun
with one of your waitresses
while you're out.
- We thought we'd play
a little game with her.
I wonder what will happen to
your sales now that she's gone.
- DON'T YOU DARE
DO ANYTHING TO HURT HER.
- Are you threatening us now?
I wouldn't if I were you.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
WE'LL TAKE VERY GOOD CARE
OF HER, I PROMISE.
- ( hangs up )
- ( dial tone )
- BASTARDS.
THEY'RE GONNA DIE!
- ALL RIGHT, LISTEN.
WE NEED YOUR SKILLS.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN FIGURE OUT
WHERE THEY'RE HIDING?
- IT MIGHT TAKE A WHILE.
- WELL, GET TO IT.
- HOLY-- ARE THOSE FROM
THE SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS
AROUND THE SCHOOL?
- THAT'S WEIRD.
WHY DO THEY KEEP THE CAMERAS
SO LOW LIKE THAT?
- 'CAUSE THAT'S WHERE
I KEEP THEM.
I'VE SET UP VIDEO MONITORING IN
32 PLACES THROUGHOUT THE SCHOOL.
- I DON'T SEE THEM.
DO YOU THINK THEY LEFT?
- I SET UP AUDIO TOO,
IN 57 PLACES.
- CHECK THAT.
MAYBE WE CAN HEAR 'EM.
- ( overlapping conversations )
Natsukawa: Now you're
asking for it.
Gonna make you
pay double this time.
Tsunemura: Don't threaten me
with a good time, buddy.
Look at your face.
You look so scared.
- Natsukawa: What did I
tell you? ( laughs )
- BINGO.
- CAN YOU TELL
WHERE THEY ARE THEN?
- P.E. STORAGE ROOM.
- LET'S GO.
- HEY.
- OH.
- ( girls scream )
- Boy: WHOA, MY RAMEN.
- WATCH IT.
- ( exclaims )
SORRY.
- MY CUTLETS.
- I'M UP.
- I'M ON THE WAY, MINAMI,
HIMEJI, WHOEVER.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- NO WAY.  HOW'D YOU KNOW
WHERE WE WERE?
- ( yells )
HIMEJI.  MINAMI.
- HEY, AKI.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HIMEJI AND MINAMI
ARE STILL AT THE CAFE.
- HIDEYOSHI, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
- THEY SAID THEY WANTED
TO PLAY WITH ME.
I LIKE GAMES,
SO I FIGURED, WHY NOT?
- SAID THEY WANTED
TO PLAY WITH YOU, HUH?
- I HATE MY LIFE.
- Fukuhara: AND THAT CONCLUDED
THE FIRST DAY
OF THE REFRESHING FESTIVAL
FOR THE SCHOOL YEAR.
- DID WE MAKE
ANYTHING TODAY OR--?
- WHOA, AFTER WE
PAY EVERYTHING OFF,
WE HAVE EXACTLY ENOUGH
TO BUY NEW DESKS.
- REALLY?
- HOLD ON.  WHAT ARE THESE
HUGE SALES FROM?
- WOW, THAT'S A LOT.
OVER 500 SOLD,
"PHOTO COLLECTION 'A'
OF EXCLUSIVE SHOOT"
BY KOUTA TRADING
AND COMPANY.
- ALL SOLD OUT,
LIMITED EDITION.
- WELL, IN ANY CASE,
TODAY WAS A TOTAL SUCCESS.
- PRINCESS PEA HEAD, CONGRATS.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
- AWW, THANKS.
YOU TOO, HAZUKI.
YOU HELPED US OUT A LOT TODAY.
WE REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
- YEAH, A LOT OF THOSE SALES
WERE BECAUSE OF OUR
HOT WAITRESSES TOO.  YOU GUYS
WERE THE MAIN ATTRACTION.
- ALL RIGHT,
THE VOTES HAVE BEEN COUNTED.
SO I CHECKED THEM TWICE TO MAKE
SURE, AND THE WINNER IS...
- I'M NOT TRYING TO BE
A BAD SPORT.
I DIDN'T EXPECT US TO WIN.
- THIS IS SO EMBARRASSING.
HOW DO I EXPLAIN THIS
TO MY SELF-ESTEEM?
- FIRST PLACE.
GOOD JOB, MAN.
I KNOW THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN
VERY OFTEN.
- EVERYTHING'S WRONG HERE!
- STOP THE FUN!
LISTEN, TURDLINGS.
THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT.
I WENT TO TALK TO THE PRINCIPAL
TODAY ABOUT YOUR EQUIPMENT.
SHE SAID SHE'LL CONSIDER THIS
A SPECIAL CASE
AND WILL ALLOW YOU
TO USE YOUR PROFIT.
- ( cheering )
- I'M NOT DONE!
THERE'S ONE CONDITION.
THERE WILL BE
A SUMMONER TEST TOURNAMENT
ON THE SECOND DAY
OF THE FESTIVAL.
THE ONLY TEAM WHO WILL BE
ALLOWED TO PURCHASE
THE NEW EQUIPMENT
WILL BE THE ONE THAT WINS.
- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
- IT'S A RANDOM TOURNAMENT
BETWEEN TWO SELECTED TEAMS.
THEY'LL KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT EACH OTHER
EXCEPT THAT
THEY'LL BE ENEMIES.
- THAT SUCKS.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHOULD WE DO IT?
- DUMB QUESTION.
OF COURSE WE SHOULD.
- IF YOU WANT TO PARTICIPATE,
COME UP WITH A TEAM
AND REGISTER.
NOW GO AWAY!
- ( upbeat song playing )
- Fukuhara: AND SO THE DREAMS
OF YEAR 2, CLASS F
CARRIED ON
INTO THE NEXT DAY.
SPEAKING OF DREAMS,
HERE COMES SOMEONE
WHO IS CHASING ONE OF HIS OWN.
- ( sighs )
I CAN'T HELP BUT
WONDER WHO SHE WAS.
- CHECK IT OUT.  I'LL GIVE YOU
A DEAL IF YOU LIKE IT.
- THAT-- THAT'S HER.
- YES. HOW MUCH?
- HEY THERE.
KOUTA, ARE YOU SLINGING SMUT?
- YOSHII, NO.
SHE'S NOT-- IT!
IT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING
TO ME, I PROMISE.