- ( insects chirping )
- ( dog barking )
- Fukuhara: BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
AKIHISA YOSHII WAS STUDYING.
- I'VE GOT TO WIN THAT SUMMONER
TEST TOURNAMENT TOMORROW
NO MATTER WHAT.
I HAVE TO, FOR HIMEJI'S SAKE.
WE CAN'T LOSE.
- NOW THEN, I'LL START
WITH JAPANESE HISTORY.
I DON'T SUCK AT THAT.
- YOU'RE STUDYING SO HARD.
GOOD BOY.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I'M A NICE SISTER
WHO WANTS TO HELP YOU.
MY INITIAL PLAN WAS TO MAKE
SOMETHING HOMEMADE
FOR YOU TO EAT, BUT I DIDN'T
HAVE A LOT OF TIME,
SO I HOPE THIS INSTANT RAMEN
WILL BE GOOD ENOUGH.
- WAIT, WHAT'S THAT?
- IT'S MAYONNAISE.
I WROTE ON IT TO LET YOU KNOW
I PUT MY WHOLE HEART
INTO MAKING IT
SO YOU'D BE ABLE TO PUT YOUR
WHOLE HEART INTO STUDYING.
- OH, HOW NICE.
- I WILL NEVER BACK DOWN
FROM A CHALLENGE.
- THANK YOU.
THIS SOUP KIND OF REMINDS ME
OF THAT SZECHWAN STYLE
SUPER-SPICY RAMEN,
EXCEPT NOT NEARLY AS SPICY.
IT'S SOUR BUT AT THE SAME TIME
HAS A FLAVOR
THAT MIGHT BE FROM A FRUIT
OR A VEGETABLE.
WHAT THE HELL ELSE
WAS IN THERE?
- AT FIRST I WROTE
ON THE NOODLES WITH KETCHUP,
BUT THEN IT GOT
ALL DISSOLVED ON ME.
- I THINK YOU FORGOT
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE SOUP.
- WELL, WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE
RICE BALLS INSTEAD?
- SURE.
THEY'RE NORMAL ENOUGH.
- OKAY, IT'S WRAPPED
WITH A PIECE OF SEAWEED
THAT STILL SMELLS
LIKE THE OCEAN.
MAYBE THAT'S WHY IT HAS
SO MUCH SALT IN IT.
THE RICE IS COOKED SLIGHTLY
SWEET AND FLUFFY SOFT.
BUT THIS TEXTURE IS,
WELL...
- HEY, AKIRA, WHY IS THE TEXTURE
OF THIS RICE BALL
NOT THE SAME AS LIKE
A REGULAR RICE BALL?
- DON'T WORRY,
I ALREADY KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO SAY
TO ME, AKI.  YOU'VE HEARD
OF THAT SPANISH DISH CALLED
PAELLA BEFORE, HAVEN'T YOU?
- YEAH, IT'S KIND OF
MY FAVORITE MEAL EVER.
- TO MAKE PAELLA TASTE THE WAY
IT'S SUPPOSED TO, THEY COOK
THE RICE AL DENTE, WHICH MEANS
THEY DON'T LET IT GET SOFT.
I PUT MY HEART INTO
NOT COOKING THE RICE
SO IT'D BE JUST LIKE YOUR
FAVORITE MEAL EVER.
AND VOILA-- LOOK AT ME.
APPARENTLY I DID IT PERFECT.
THE RICE IS AL DENTE, RIGHT?
- ( giggles )
- ( groans )
RICE BALLS AREN'T SUPPOSED
TO BE AL DENTE!
HOW DID YOU MANAGE TO UNDERCOOK
RICE IN A RICE COOKER ANYWAY?
- Fukuhara: GOOD QUESTION.
THE WORLD IS FULL
OF MYSTERIES, ISN'T IT?
- ( upbeat song playing )
- Fukuhara: THE SECOND DAY
OF THE REFRESHING FESTIVAL.
- OKAY, GUYS,
THIS IS HOW MUCH WE SOLD.
- ( cheering )
- AND NOW, WITH ALL THE MONEY
WE MADE, WE CAN BUY SOME NEW
DESKS AND STUFF.
- NOT SO FAST.
WE CAN'T BUY ANYTHING
UNTIL WE GET APPROVAL.
- TO GET THAT APPROVAL,
WE HAVE TO WIN
THE SUMMONER TEST TOURNAMENT.
- IT'S THIS RANDOM STYLE
TOURNAMENT WITH TWO-PERSON TEAMS
THAT FIGHT OTHER
TWO-PERSON TEAMS.
HIMEJI AND MINAMI
WILL BE OUR MAIN DUO,
AND YOSHII AND I
WILL PLAY AS THEIR BACKUP.
- DOES THAT MEAN THE REST OF US
DON'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING?
- NOT AT ALL.
WE NEED YOU AND KOUTA.
YOU TWO WILL HAVE
A SEPARATE MISSION.
- SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
WE'LL SO ROCK THIS.
- HEY, IF WE DO REALLY WELL, WE
MIGHT BE ABLE TO MAKE EVERYONE
RESPECT CLASS F
A LITTLE BIT MORE TOO.
- WE HAVE TO WIN IF WE WANT
TO STOP HIMEJI'S PARENTS
FROM MAKING HER
SWITCH SCHOOLS.
- YOU PROMISED TO STUDY.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU WERE
TELLING THE TRUTH, AKI.
- UNLESS YOU BRING UP YOUR
SCORES IN THE RECOVERY TEST
BEFORE THE TOURNAMENT STARTS,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO COMPETE, YOU KNOW.
- I'M GOOD.
I STUDIED WITH AN EXTRA EMPHASIS
ON JAPANESE HISTORY.
- THAT'S GREAT.
HERE, CHECK THIS OUT.
- I DON'T GET IT.
- JAPANESE HISTORY ISN'T
ON THE LIST FOR THE TOURNAMENT.
- WHAT THE HELL?
WHY DID NO ONE TELL ME THAT?
- Nishimura:
WE WILL NOW GET
THE SUMMONER TEST TOURNAMENT
UNDERWAY!
- ( fanfare )
- HOORAY, WE'RE HERE TODAY AT
THE SUMMONER TEST TOURNAMENT.
IT'S THE MAIN EVENT OF THIS
YEAR'S REFRESHING FESTIVAL.
ANY THOUGHTS YOU'D LIKE TO SHARE
WITH US, MISS TAKAHASHI?
- MY PREDOMINANT
THOUGHT IS
I'D LIKE TO SEE OUR STUDENTS
DO THEIR BEST.
- Nishimura: IN THE BLUE CORNER,
FROM YEAR TWO, CLASS F,
YUUJI SAKAMOTO
AND AKIHISA YOSHII!
- IT'S ON,
LIKE DONKEY KONG.
- YEAH.
- OH, COME ON.
DON'T GIVE UP JUST BECAUSE YOU
PROBABLY ALREADY MADE US LOSE.
- AND IN THE RED CORNER...
- YOU SEE?
STOP BEING A CHICK.
WE'RE STARTING
WITH CLASS E.
THOSE GUYS ARE ALMOST
AS STUPID AS YOU ARE.
- THAT'S TRUE.  I GUESS
WE'VE FOUGHT THEM BEFORE,
SO WE MIGHT WIN IF WE DON'T
SCREW UP TOO MUCH.
- ...YEAR 2, CLASS B,
RITSUKO IWASHITA
AND MAYUMI KIKURI.
- SAY WHAT?
THEY CHANGED IT.
- WE HAVE TO FIGHT
CLASS B?
- HOLD THE PHONE!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- I THOUGHT WE WERE SUPPOSED TO
FIGHT SOMEONE FROM CLASS E.
- SORRY.  I'M NOT REALLY SURE
WHAT HAPPENED.
- IS THERE A PROBLEM?
- LOOKS LIKE THERE'S SOME KIND
OF MECHANICAL ISSUE.
- WELL, THEN TAKE CARE OF IT.
WE'VE GOT OTHER MATCHES TOO.
- THEY'RE IDIOTS.
AT LEAST WE'LL WIN.
- YEAH, MIGHT AS WELL
GET IT OVER WITH.
- WOW, THIS WAS SURE UNEXPECTED.
- WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO, YUUJI?
- NO CHOICE.
WE'RE GONNA WIN THIS THING.
- SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
WILL HAPPEN, MISS TAKAHASHI?
- WE'VE JUST STARTED
THE TOURNAMENT,
SO MANY OF THE BATTLES WILL BE
SIMILARLY UNBALANCED.
THIS ONE IS
F VERSUS B,
SO I HIGHLY DOUBT
IT'LL BE MUCH OF A FIGHT.
- Nishimura: THE SUBJECT
FOR THIS ROUND IS...
MATH!  BEGIN.
- SUMMON!
- NOT BAD, BUT I'D EXPECT
AS MUCH FROM CLASS B.
OUR TURN.
SUMMON!
- NICELY DONE, YUUJI.
HOW COME YOU HAVE
SUCH A HIGH SCORE?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I'VE BEEN STUDYING NONSTOP
SINCE I FOUND OUT WE NEEDED
TO WIN THE TOURNAMENT.
- WE'D HAVE TO BEAT
CLASS A.
YUUJI, YOU REALLY THINK
WE'LL GO THAT FAR?
- WE HAVE TO.
- FOR SHOUKO?
- ( bell ringing )
- Shouko: HERE COMES THE BRIDE.
- SHE ASKED ME WHERE I WANT
TO HAVE OUR WEDDING.
THIS IS IT.  IF I DON'T WIN,
MY LIFE MIGHT AS WELL BE OVER.
I'VE GOT TO SHOW HER
I'M THE ONE IN CHARGE FOR ONCE.
- YEAH, BUT I DON'T THINK
WE CAN BEAT THEM.
- DUDE, YOU'RE
IN THE SAME BOAT AS ME.
NOW PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER
AND GET ONBOARD, DAMN IT.
- OKAY, YUUJI.
LET'S TAKE THOSE B-GIRLS DOWN.
SUMMON!
- NOT WITH THAT SCORE,
WE WON'T.
- SHUT UP.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
- OH, LOOK,
THEY'RE NO MATCH FOR US.
ARE YOU AS SHOCKED AS I AM?
- CAN BARELY CONTAIN MYSELF.
WE SHOULD GIVE 'EM A BREAK
AND END IT FAST.
RITSUKO.
- MAYUMI.
- Together: READY, SET, GO!
- HOW NICE.  YOU SEEM TO BE
IN SYNC FOR THE MOST PART.
- FOR A COUPLE OF CHICKS
WHO'RE ACTING LIKE THEY'RE NOT
FRENEMIES, YOU GIRLS ARE
PULLING OFF A BANG-UP JOB.
- PREPARE YOURSELVES, LADIES,
BECAUSE YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET
A LOAD OF REAL TEAMWORK
RIGHT IN THE FACE.
- ALL RIGHT, AKIHISA.
- YUUJI.
- Together: THEY'RE ALL YOURS.
- HUH?
- WE CAN'T LEAVE IT
UP TO EACH OTHER.
THEN NO ONE'S DOING ANYTHING.
- YOU TOOK MY LINE,
YOU DEMENTED BONEHEAD.
- SO IT APPEARS OUR TEAMWORK MAY
BE ON PAR WITH YOURS AFTER ALL.
- Girls: WHAT?
- AKI, SHUT UP.
IT'S TIME FOR SOME STRATEGY.
- UH, STRATE-WHAT?
- WHILE AKIHISA ATTRACTS
ONE OF THE GIRLS' ATTENTION.
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR MOVE
AND TAKE DOWN THE OTHER ONE.
- HOW CAN I DO THAT?
BOTH OF THOSE PEOPLE ARE ME!
- BE LIKE THAT THEN.
FINE, I GUESS WE CAN
JUST FIGHT TOGETHER.
- WE'RE SUPPOSED TO
FIGHT TOGETHER.
- I'LL BE IN CHARGE
OF THE ATTACKING.
YOU DO WHAT YOU CAN
TO BE THE SHIELD.
- BUT IF I DO THAT,
I'M GONNA GET HURT!
I FEEL WHAT HAPPENS
TO MY AVATAR, REMEMBER?
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND THE TERM
"TEAM PLAYER."
SINCE YOU DON'T GET IT, WE'LL
HAVE TO FIGHT HEAD TO HEAD.
- WHAT A GREAT IDEA.
- YE GODS.
- HIYAH!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M NOT HITTING HIM.
- Fukuhara: A PROBATIONARY
STUDENT,
AKIHISA IS ACCUSTOMED TO USING
HIS AVATAR FOR CHORES.
THAT HAS MADE HIM QUITE ADEPT AT
MOVING HIS AVATAR QUICK AS HELL.
- ALL RIGHT, MY TURN.
KA-POW!
YES!
HOW ARE YOU DOING, BRO?
- NO.  THIS IS BAD.
- IN YOUR FACES!
- SUCK IT, LOSERS!
- ( crowd murmuring )
- SO, UH, JUST ME, OR DOES THIS
MAKE US LOOK LIKE JERKS?
- THIS IS NOT WHAT I WOULD CALL
A PROUD MOMENT FOR OUR SCHOOL.
- AS AN EDUCATOR, THE ONLY
RESPONSIBLE RESPONSE
I CAN HAVE IS TO HOPE
THE SAKAMOTO-YOSHII DUO LOSES.
- YOU WHAT?
NO FAIR.
YAY.
- THE WINNER IS
THE SAKAMOTO-YOSHII TEAM
IN THE BLUE CORNER!
- OH MY GOD,
THAT WAS AWFUL.
- I HAVE NEVER BEEN SO
EMBARRASSED IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
- ( crowd yelling, booing )
- AWW, MAN, PEOPLE CAN BE
SO HARSH SOMETIMES.
- WE WON THIS ROUND, YAY.
- Fukuhara: AND SO,
BATTLE AFTER BATTLE
WAS FOUGHT
IN THE FIRST ROUND.
THE LOSING TEAMS
WERE DISQUALIFIED.
- Nishimura: IN THE BLUE CORNER,
FROM YEAR 2, CLASS F,
YUUJI SAKAMOTO
AND AKIHISA YOSHII
UP AGAINST,
YEAR 2, CLASS C,
KYOUJI NEMOTO
AND YUUKA KOYAMA.
- WE'RE FIGHTING
CLASS B AGAIN?
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
- SO WE'RE TAKING ON NEMOTO.
- YOSHII AND SAKAMOTO?  NO.
HOW DID WE END UP WITH YOU?
- WHAT ARE YOU SCARED OF,
KYOUJI?
THEY'RE TWO OF THE DUMBEST KIDS
IN THE WHOLE SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW THIS BATTLE IS,
LIKE, TOTALLY IN THE BAG.
- YEAH, I'M AWARE OF THAT.
- THE SUBJECT THIS ROUND IS...
ENGLISH!  BEGIN.
All: SUMMON!
- YUUJI.
- HOW CAN I HELP YOU, AKI?
YOU SAID YOU'D BEEN
STUDYING NONSTOP
SO WE COULD BEAT
CLASS A!
- I CAN ONLY STUDY
ONE SUBJECT AT A TIME.
- WE BOTH HAVE CRAPPY SCORES.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO NOW?
- CALM DOWN, BRO.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA
THAT JUST MIGHT
HELP US WIN.
HEY, KOUTA.
THE JOURNAL, PLEASE.
- UH, WHAT JOURNAL?
- Fukuhara: KYOUJI NEMOTO'S
PHOTO COLLECTION.
"PLEASE TAKE A LOOK
AT THE NEW ME."
NEMOTO, AFTER LOSING A PREVIOUS
SUMMONER TEST WAR,
WAS FORCED TO DRESS LIKE A WOMAN
WHILE KOUTA PHOTOGRAPHED HIM.
KOUTA HAS SINCE GATHERED THE
PHOTOS AND PUT THEM TOGETHER
IN A LESS THAN FLATTERING
COLLECTION.
- I THINK THIS SHOULD HELP
WITH THE NEGOTIATIONS.
- I SEE.
I STILL HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
HOW AWFUL HE WAS TO HIMEJI.
OKAY, LET'S NAIL HIM WITH IT.
NEMOTO!
IF YOU DON'T WANT US TO PASS OUT
THIS PHOTO COLLECTION,
YOU'D BETTER LISTEN UP.
- BACK DOWN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE GONNA
LET HIM OFF.
- GIVE ME
SOME CREDIT, DUDE.
NEMOTO, TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS!
- THAT'S ME IN A DRESS!
YOU WIN THIS ONE, SAKAMOTO.
WE SURRENDER.
YOU GUYS ARE OFFICIALLY THE
WINNERS OF THIS ROUND, MAN.
JUST DON'T--
DON'T SHOW THOSE PICS.
- IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT, KOYAMA?
DO WE WIN THIS ROUND?
- YOU WIN.
WE DON'T WANT TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
- Nishimura: THE WINNER IS
THE SAKAMOTO-YOSHII TEAM
IN THE BLUE CORNER.
- PLEASE, YUUKA,
YOU HAVE TO LET ME EXPLAIN.
- KYOUJI...
WE'RE SO BREAKING UP.
- OH, PLEASE NO!
BUMMER.
- Fukuhara: BUMMER.
THUS THE SECOND ROUND
ENDED ON A HIGH NOTE.
- GOOD JOB.
WAY TO GO.
- GOOD JOB, YEAH.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
- YOU'RE THE SMARTEST
IDIOT EVER.
- THAT'S SO SWEET, HAZUKI.
HOW DID YOU GUYS DO ANYWAY?
- WE DID WELL.
WE WON TOO.
- A PIECE OF CAKE.
- THAT'S SO AWESOME.
WOULDN'T IT BE COOL IF BOTH OUR
TEAMS MADE IT TO THE FINALS?
- THIS IS STRANGE.
- YOU MEAN, LIKE, SPECIFICALLY?
- WHY'D WE ONLY FIGHT
SMART CLASSES?
- I FIGURED IT WAS JUST BAD LUCK
SINCE IT'S ALL PICKED RANDOMLY.
- IT DIDN'T SEEM
THAT RANDOM TO ME.
HIDEYOSHI, KOUTA,
PREPARE OUR NEXT STRATEGY.
- ROGER.
- SURE, YOU CAN COUNT ON US.
- Akihisa: WHAT STRATEGY?
- IF I'M RIGHT, THE NEXT TEAM
WE'RE UP AGAINST
WILL HAVE EVEN HIGHER SCORES
THAN THE LAST ONE.
- Nishimura: IN THE RED CORNER,
FROM YEAR 2, CLASS A,
SHOUKO KIRISHIMA
AND YUUKO KUNOSHITA.
- BIG SURPRISE.  THEY'RE PUTTING
US UP AGAINST CLASS A.
TOLD YOU SO.
- YEAH, YOU DID.  GOOD CALL.
- HIDEYOSHI, LIKE A BOSS.
- I GET IT.  HIDEYOSHI TOTALLY
TRADED PLACES WITH HIS SISTER.
IT WAS A STRATEGY FOR TWINS,
WASN'T IT?
- DID YOU HONESTLY THINK
THAT WOULD HAPPEN?
- HIDEYOSHI?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M NOT AN IDIOT LIKE HE IS.
- SORRY, THAT WAS MY BAD,
YOU GUYS.
- Yuuji: WHAT THE HELL?
- YOU FORGET--
I KNOW HOW YOU THINK, YUUJI.
- NOW I HAVE NO CHOICE.
IT'S TIME FOR OUR TRUMP CARD.
- OUR TRUMP CARD?
ARE YOU SAYING YOU HAVE A PLAN?
- I AM.  NOW THEN,
I WANT YOU TO SAY WORD FOR WORD
EXACTLY WHAT I TELL YOU TO.
- SOUNDS GOOD, MAN.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
I'LL DO WHATEVER
IT TAKES.
- "SHOUKO, I HAVE SOMETHING
I WANT TO TELL YOU."
- SHOUKO, I HAVE
SOMETHING I WANT TO TELL YOU.
- "I WANT TO WIN THIS TOURNAMENT
NO MATTER WHAT."
- I WANT TO WIN THIS
TOURNAMENT NO MATTER WHAT.
- "AND IF I DO, I SWEAR..."
- AND IF I DO, I SWEAR...
- "I WILL PROPOSE TO YOU."
- I WILL PROPOSE TO--
- "I LOVE YOU, SHOUKO."
- WHAT THE HELL?
WHY WOULD YOU WANT ME
TO SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- JUDO CHOP!
- ( groans )
- ( clears throat )
( deep voice )
AND IF I DO, I SWEAR
I WILL PROPOSE TO YOU,
BECAUSE...
I LOVE YOU, SHOUKO!
- HOW AWFUL.  WE JUST LOST.
- BAD SHOUKO!
FINE.  I'LL FIGHT THESE
JACKWAGONS BY MYSELF.
- Nishimura: THIS ROUND'S
SUBJECT--
HEALTH AND
PHYSICAL EDUCATION.
BEGIN.
- SUMMON!
- YEAH, WELL, I'VE GOT ANOTHER
PLAN.  YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
WAIT TILL YOU GET A LOAD
OF MY AVATAR THIS TIME, FOOL.
SUMMON!
- SUMMON!
- SEE THAT?
SUMMONING A SUBSTITUTE.
GO AHEAD AND BEAT THAT
KILLER TECHNIQUE IF YOU CAN.
- THEY ARE TOTALLY CHEATING.
- THIS IS SO NOT GOOD.
- ( moans )
- ( punch lands )
- ( deep voice ) I LOVE YOU.
HELP ME, SHOUKO!
- WE'D LIKE TO WITHDRAW.
- BAD SHOUKO!  NO!
- SINCE THE TEAM IN THE RED
CORNER WITHDREW, THE WINNER IS
THE SAKAMOTO-YOSHII TEAM
IN THE BLUE CORNER.
- YOU SON OF A BITCH!  WHAT THE
HELL KIND OF STUNT WAS THAT?
- DON'T BLAME ME.
IT'S YOUR FAULT SHE SAW THROUGH
YOUR STRATEGY TO START WITH.
- SO WHAT IF IT WAS?
THAT DOES NOT MEAN YOU HAVE TO
RUIN THE REST OF MY LIFE.
- I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY ACTUALLY GOT AWAY
WITH THAT STUNT.
- PLEASE, THERE'S NO REASON
TO FIGHT.  WE ALL ADVANCED
TO THE SEMIFINALS,
AND THAT'S A GOOD THING.
- YEAH, GOOD POINT.
BOTH OF OUR TEAMS
MADE IT THIS FAR,
SO ONE OF US MIGHT BE ABLE
TO WIN THE WHOLE THING.
- THAT'S WAY COOL.
I'M GOING TO SUPPORT YOU 100%
NO MATTER HOW CRAZY TINY
YOUR LITTLE BRAIN IS.
- YOU ALWAYS SAY THE SWEETEST
THINGS.  THANK YOU, HAZUKI.
- KICKING OFF THE SEMIFINALS
IN THE RED CORNER,
FROM YEAR 2, CLASS F, MIZUKI
HIMEJI AND MINAMI SHIMADA.
- WELL, THAT'S AWKWARD.
- IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
THIS JUST MEANS
A TEAM FROM CLASS F
WILL ADVANCE TO THE FINALS
NO MATTER WHAT,
SO WE DON'T HAVE TO PUSH
TOO HARD TO WIN HERE.
- YEAH, THAT MAKES SENSE.
WE CAN JUST LOSE FAST SO THAT
HIMEJI AND MINAMI WON'T HAVE TO
LOWER THEIR SCORES ANY.
- DON'T BE STUPID, YOU DUMMY.
GO FOR IT.
- HAZUKI?
- I'M CHEERING FOR YOU,
SO IF YOU LOSE,
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU.
- ( Akihisa's voice ) I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG TO UNDERSTAND
WHY I HAVE TO DO
WHAT I'M ABOUT TO DO.
- IF YOU WIN, I'LL GIVE YOU
A GROWN-UP KISS
FOR DOING A GOOD JOB.
- HUH?
- NOT ONLY THAT, BUT I'LL EVEN
TAKE A BATH WITH YOU TOO.
- Both: WHAT?
- A BATH TOGETHER?
- AND I BET YOU'LL BE WAY TIRED,
SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT WASHING YOUR BACK.
I CAN DO IT.
- Both: WHAT?
- ALL OF A SUDDEN
I FEEL AS THOUGH WE SHOULD
TAKE THIS ROUND SERIOUSLY.
- HOLD ON.
NO NEED TO GET ALL PSYCHO.
- IT'S TIME TO DIE.
- All: IT'S TIME TO DIE.
- EXCEPT WE MIGHT THINK
IT'S RUDE IF YOU GO EASY ON US.
- PLEASE DON'T.
IF WE FIGHT SERIOUSLY,
I'LL BE IN PAIN
FROM AVATAR FEEDBACK.
- KILL THE TRAITOR!
- KILL HIM.
- WE'RE ON THE SAME TEAM,
SO WHY DO I FEEL
LIKE I'M PLAYING
AN AWAY GAME RIGHT NOW?
- THERE'S NO REASON
TO FREAK OUT, DUDE.
WE'RE JUST GONNA LOSE FAST
AND WALK AWAY.
- YOU WILL NOT BE FORGIVEN
IF YOU LOSE ON PURPOSE.
- SHOUKO?
- YOU DID SWEAR TO ME
WE'D GET ENGAGED IF YOU WON
THIS TOURNAMENT, RIGHT?
SO IF YOU LOSE ON PURPOSE,
WE'LL GET MARRIED NOW.
- EITHER WAY
I'M GETTING PUNISHED.
- WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO, MAN?
- WE HAVE TO WIN.
THERE'S NOTHING ELSE
WE CAN DO AT THIS POINT.
- BUT HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO BEAT THEM?
THEY'VE GOT
BETTER SCORES.
- THE SUBJECT THIS ROUND--
CLASSIC JAPANESE.
BEGIN.
- Girls: SUMMON!
- MINAMI'S AVATAR
ONLY HAS SIX POINTS.
SHE MIGHT AS WELL
ALREADY BE DEAD.
- MIGHT AS WELL.
OKAY THEN, LET'S GET 'EM.
- OKAY.
- Both: SUMMON!
- SERIOUSLY?
- I FEEL BAD ABOUT IT,
IF THAT HELPS.
- YOU GUYS NEED TO GIVE UP,
SO QUIT RUNNING AWAY FROM US.
- LET US SEND YOU TO THE
AFTERLIFE WITH A SINGLE BLOW.
- YEAH, AS GREAT AS THAT SOUNDS,
IF I LET THE TWO OF YOU
BEAT ME RIGHT NOW, I MIGHT
ACTUALLY DIE FROM THE PAIN.
- FOCUS.
FIND A WAY TO BLOCK
HIMEJI'S WEAPON
AND LET ME TAKE CARE OF THEM.
- RIGHT, I'M ON TOP OF IT.
HERE GOES.
- HUH?  WHA--?
- THAT'S NOT FAIR.  YOU LET GO
OF THOSE RIGHT THIS INSTANT.
- BOOBY SNATCHER!
- OKAY, YUUJI, YOU'RE UP.
JUST MAKE SURE YOU DON'T HIT ME
WITH THAT ATTACK.
- THE WINNER IS
THE SAKAMOTO-YOSHII TEAM
IN THE BLUE CORNER.
- WHATEVER.
I MEAN, IN THE END
SOMEONE WAS GONNA WIND UP
BEATING ME ANYWAY.
- DEATH TO THE TRAITOR!
- WAIT.
YOU GUYS ARE OVERREACTING.
LET ME GO.
WHY DOES THIS ALWAYS
HAPPEN TO ME?
- DON'T WORRY, MAN.
I WON'T LET YOUR USELESS DEATH
BE IN VAIN.
- HOW IS A USELESS DEATH
NOT IN VAIN?
- I'VE OBTAINED
SOME INFORMATION.
INFORMATION?
- YOU WERE RIGHT, YUUJI.
- I KNEW IT.
THANKS A LOT, KOUTA.
AKI, WE'RE TAKING
THE FINALS SERIOUSLY.
- COOL.
- Fukuhara: THE FINAL BATTLE
WILL BE HELD IN FRONT OF
THE REST OF THE STUDENT BODY.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
ONE OF THE TEAMS IN THIS BATTLE
IS FROM CLASS F, COMMONLY KNOWN
AS THE STUPID ONES.
- APPARENTLY WE MAY HAVE TO
REVISE OUR PREVIOUS PERCEPTION
OF THIS PARTICULAR CLASS
FROM THIS POINT ON.
- MAYBE NOT.
THEIR OPPONENT
IS THE DUO
FROM YEAR 3, CLASS A.
- DUO FROM YEAR 3, CLASS A?
- Nishimura: IN THE RED CORNER,
FROM YEAR 3, CLASS A.
SHUNPEI NATSUKAWA
AND YUSAKU TSUNEMURA.
- THEY'RE FIGHTING
THE TSUNEKAWA DUO?
- THAT DOESN'T SEEM FAIR.
- NOT AT ALL.
- Natsukawa: HOW DID YOU
FATHEADS MAKE IT THIS FAR?
- ( Akihisa whimpering )
- WELCOME TO THE END, JOKERS.
- I HATE THAT GUY.
- WE'RE GONNA CRUSH YOU,
MORONS,
UNTIL WE CAN'T
CRUSH YOU ANYMORE.
- ( both laughing )
- YOU STILL HAVE A BRA
ON YOUR HEAD.
- I KNOW.
IT WON'T COME OFF.
- PERVERT ALERT, YO.
- YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO PUT IT ON ME, ASS.
- HEY, CHEATERS.
YEAH, WE KNOW THE TRUTH.
- WHAT?  WE DO?
- YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN FIXING
OUR OPPONENT SELECTIONS
THIS WHOLE TIME, HAVEN'T YOU?
- WHAT?  WE WERE TRYING
TO PUT YOU OUT OF YOUR MISERY
AS FAST AS POSSIBLE.  DIDN'T
WANT YOU TO GET EMBARRASSED.
- EVEN THOUGH IT'S A SHOCK
YOU MADE IT THIS FAR,
AT LEAST WE'LL BE ABLE TO SETTLE
OUR SCORE FROM YESTERDAY.
- Yuuji: FINE WITH US, ASSHATS.
LET'S RUMBLE.
- Tsunemura: GUESS WHAT--
ENGLISH IS GOING TO BE
OUR SUBJECT THIS ROUND,
AND THAT HAPPENS TO BE MY FORTE.
- Nishimura: PREPARE FOR BATTLE.
- SAY WHAT?
- HOW COME IT'S NOT ENGLISH?
- Yuuji: NICELY DONE, KOUTA.
- EASY AS PIE, FELLAS.
- YOU READY, MAN?
- YEAH, WE GET TO PULL
THE STRINGS THIS TIME.
AND THE HANDICAP SHOULDN'T BE
TOO MUCH FOR YOU.
- NO.
- Both: SUMMON!
- SUMMON!
- WHAT THE WHAT?
- NO.  THEIR SCORES
ARE EVEN WITH OURS.
- AKI NORMALLY ONLY HAS, LIKE,
60 POINTS AT THE MOST.
- HE DID STUDY.
GO GET 'EM, BOYS.
- YOU'D BETTER BE READY,
'CAUSE WE'RE NOT HOLDING BACK.
- BRING IT ON.
- FACE.
OH, NO.
HOW DARE YOU?
YOU'RE JUST CLASS F.
- YOU'RE GOING DOWN!
- I'VE GOT A LITTLE
SURPRISE FOR YOU.
THE DIFFERENCE
IN OUR EXPERIENCES.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE A PROBATIONARY STUDENT,
AREN'T YOU?  WOW, SO ALL
THOSE HITS ON YOUR AVATAR
MUST HAVE HURT YOU TOO.
( laughs )
- AKIHISA.
HEY, YOU NEED TO PULL
YOURSELF TOGETHER, MAN.
YOU CAN STILL FIGHT,
CAN'T YOU?
- HELL YEAH.
- THE POOR LOSER
DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING LEFT.
I GUESS I MIGHT AS WELL
FINISH HIM OFF.
- I'M GONNA GET YOU,
SUCKER!
- TAKE THIS.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- I CAN THROW MY WEAPON TOO.
THIS IS REALLY GONNA HURT.
HERE IT COMES.
- HEADS UP.
- Nishimura: THE WINNER IS
THE TEAM IN THE BLUE CORNER!
- NO WAY.
- WE LOST.
- ( crowd cheering )
- Woman: THE CHAMPIONS OF
THE SUMMONER TEST TOURNAMENT
HAVE BEEN DECIDED--
THE YUUJI SAKAMOTO,
AKIHISA YOSHII TEAM
FROM YEAR 2, CLASS F.
- WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
WE DID IT.
- GO US.
- Tsunemura: NO WAY IN HELL
ARE WE GONNA LET THIS HAPPEN.
- Yuuji: OH, REALLY?  AND WHAT
ARE YOU GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
- Natsukawa: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU GUYS CHEATED ON EVERY
SINGLE BATTLE YOU HAD.
- CAN'T CHEAT
AT A BATTLE OF WITS.
- PLUS, WHO ARE YOU
TO CALL US CHEATERS?
- SHUT UP.  WE'RE THE ONES
WHO ARE GONNA
RAT OUT YOUR CHEATING
TO EVERY TEACHER IN SCHOOL.
- YEAH, IF WE CAN'T BE
THE WINNERS, NO ONE CAN.
- THEY'RE HEADING
TO THE P.A. SYSTEM.
THEY'RE GOING TO EXPOSE US.
- HOLD ON.
IF THEY DO THAT, THEY'LL GET
OUR WIN TAKEN AWAY FOR SURE.
- AKIHISA.
- OF COURSE.
- I NEED TO BORROW THIS
REAL QUICK.
- STOP.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- THEY WILL NOT
RUIN THIS FOR US.
WE HAVE TO WIN
THE CHAMPIONSHIP
SO WE CAN BUY STUFF
TO MAKE OUR CLASS LOOK BETTER.
NO ONE IS GONNA MAKE HIMEJI
CHANGE SCHOOLS.
I SWEAR IT!
NAILED IT.
- YES, YOU DID, AKI.
- ( both scream )
- Both: NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO!
- UH...
- WHOOPSIE.
- YOU IDIOTS.
- Both: HAVE MERCY ON US!
- Hazuki: THAT DOESN'T LOOK SO
GOOD.  BEING STUPID HURTS, HUH?
- Minami: YEAH, SERIOUSLY.
I MEAN, THERE IS SUCH A THING
AS OVERKILL, YOU KNOW.
- Akihisa: YOU JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND THOSE GUYS.
- Kouta: WE HAD TO PAY TO GET
THE DAMAGED BUILDINGS ALL FIXED.
SO MOST OF THE MONEY
WE MADE
WAS USED FOR THAT
INSTEAD OF BUYING NEW STUFF.
- ( Akihito groans )
- Yuuji: WE HAVE JUST ENOUGH
LEFT TO BUY A FEW SMALL TABLES.
- Hideyoshi: CLEARLY,
WE GOT AHEAD OF OURSELVES.
- Akihisa: LOOKS LIKE IT.
I WONDER WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
WITH HIMEJI NOW.
- HI, EVERYONE.
- Akihisa: HIMEJI.
- Minami: OH, HEY, WHAT'S UP,
GIRL?  WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- I WAS JUST TALKING WITH MY
FATHER FOR A LITTLE BIT.
- Hideyoshi: YOU MEAN YOUR
FATHER SAW THE TOURNAMENT?
- Kouta: WELL,
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
NO, ACTUALLY IT WAS FINE.
MY FATHER SAID IF I WANT TO STAY
HERE, I NEED TO STUDY HARD
AND THAT I PROBABLY NEED TO WORK
ON MY PHYSICAL STRENGTH TOO.
- HUH?
- Minami: ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- I AM.
HE ALSO SAID
I HAVE REALLY GREAT FRIENDS.
- HE'S RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
- ( upbeat song playing )
- Takahashi: THE CLOSING PARTY
HAS NOW STARTED.  ALL STUDENTS,
PLEASE REPORT TO THE SCHOOL
BUILDING FOR THE FESTIVITIES.
- ( students chattering )
- YOU HAVE TO
LET ME EXPLAIN.
THIS IS ALL JUST A NASTY
MISUNDERSTANDING.
CAN'T WE START OVER?
PLEASE LISTEN, PLEASE.
DON'T WALK AWAY.
PLEASE COME BACK TO ME, YUUKA!
- YUUJI, YOUR PROMISE.
IT'S TIME TO PROPOSE.
- DAMN IT.  YOU CAN'T
TORTURE A PERSON INTO MARRIAGE.
THAT'LL NEVER HOLD UP
IN COURT.
( screaming )
- UM, SO, AKIHISA...
- WE WERE KINDA WONDERING
IF YOU'D--
I MEAN,
WE'D LIKE MAYBE--
- I WANNA FOLK-DANCE!
COME ON, STUPID!
- OKAY, I WOULD LOVE
TO DANCE WITH YOU, HAZUKI.
- SHE STOLE OUR
DANCE FROM US.
- HOW COULD YOU, AKIHISA?
HOW?
- I DON'T THINK I'LL EVER
UNDERSTAND CHICKS, MAN.
- Fukuhara: CHEEKS BLUSHING
FROM THE BURNING FLAMES,
THE STUDENTS
HELD THEIR HEARTS CLOSE,
EVEN IF THEY WERE
ON THEIR SLEEVES.
AND THE NIGHT WORE ON.
THE END.