- LET ME THINK.
HOW SHOULD I DO THIS?
HMM.
I THINK I'LL MAKE IT FUN.
- ( murmuring )
- HEY, WHAT'S HAPPENING, YUUJI?
- CLEARLY, SOMETHING'S GOING ON.
- WHAT KIND OF SOMETHING?
SPONSORED BY FUMIZUKI ACADEMY,
COMPETE FOR PRIZES,
BEGINNING OF THE YEAR CONTEST?
- ( theme song playing )
- Fukuhara: AKIHISA YOSHII
HAS FOUND A TREASURE.
- I CAN'T REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
I ATE THIS GOOD.
SURPRISE ATTACK!
( munching )
OH, MAN, THESE BREADCRUMBS ARE
EVERYTHING I THOUGHT THEY'D BE!
THEY TASTE JUST LIKE REAL BREAD!
I WISH I HAD SOME JELLY
OR SOMETHING.
THEN THIS BREAKFAST
WOULD BE PERFECT!
- Fukuhara: ONE MAN'S TRASH
IS ANOTHER MAN'S TREASURE.
- ( stomach growling )
MAN, I WONDER HOW LONG
THOSE BREADCRUMBS ARE
GOING TO LAST ME.
- Fukuhara: THIS IS FEE THE FOX.
A MASCOT CHARACTER
FOR THE LOCAL AMUSEMENT PARK.
SHE IS VERY POPULAR
AMONG YOUNG CHILDREN.
- HEY, THIS IS...
- I JUST EXPLAINED WHAT IT WAS
IN MY NARRATION.
- WHAT IF THE KID WHO DROPPED
THIS COMES BACK FOR IT?
THEY JUST MIGHT. I'LL LEAVE
IT HERE SO THEY CAN FIND IT.
- COME ON, WHERE ARE YOU?
WHERE DID YOU GO?
- WELL, HEY THERE, HAZUKI. WHAT
ARE YOU DOING ON THE GROUND?
- OH, HI, STUPID YOSHII!
HOW ARE YOU?
I DROPPED SOMETHING EARLIER,
SO I'M LOOKING.
- DID YOU FIND IT?
- NO. I CAN'T FIND IT ANYWHERE!
IT WAS A LIMITED EDITION
FEE CELL PHONE STRAP.
- NO WAY! I JUST SAW
ONE OF THOSE OVER THERE!
- I'M FREAKING OUT RIGHT NOW!
- FEE!
- IS EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT, YOSHII?
- OH, SWEET, MR. FUKUHARA?
NICE TIMING! I NEED MY AVATAR!
- AND WHY EXACTLY
DO YOU NEED IT?
- BECAUSE IT'S RIGHT OVER THERE!
IT'S AN EMERGENCY!
- YOU'RE OVERREACTING, BUT I'LL
APPROVE IT JUST THIS ONCE.
- ALL RIGHT! I'M ON THIS!
SUMMON!
NOW, GO BRING BACK FEE!
IT'S UP TO YOU!
DON'T LET IT DIE!
- ( crashing )
- ( Akihisa exclaiming )
( whimpering )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
MY GOODNESS, THAT WAS REAL DUMB.
- ( groaning ) YEAH, I KNOW.
- JUST WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
OR WERE YOU THINKING AT ALL?
- MORNING, PRINCIPAL.
HOW ARE YOU?
- THAT WAS IDIOTIC! YOU'VE BEEN
TOLD YOUR AVATAR IS NOT A TOY!
- I KNOW THAT. I'M NOT STUPID!
I WAS JUST TRYING TO RESCUE FEE.
- ( both gasp )
- ( Akihisa exclaiming )
- WELL, MAYBE THIS WILL
TEACH YOU
NOT TO GET TOO ATTACHED
TO CHILDISH THINGS.
- ( crying )
- OH, YEAH?
WELL, MAYBE THIS WILL TEACH
YOU NOT TO BE SO RUDE!
- I'M WITHDRAWING
MY SUMMONING APPROVAL.
YOU SHOULD NEVER USE YOUR
AVATAR FOR VIOLENCE, YOSHII.
- VIOLENCE? WHAT?
I WAS TRYING TO HELP HAZUKI!
- AVATARS WEREN'T MEANT TO
BE USED BY IDIOTS.
WHEN YOU'RE UPSET TRY MAKING
THE INTELLIGENT DECISION.
AND THEN YOU MIGHT ACTUALLY GET
SOMETHING YOU WANT FOR A CHANGE.
- ( Hazuki sobbing )
- YOU ALL RIGHT, KIDDO?
- I'M FINE. DON'T WORRY.
- SORRY.
- I WONDER IF THIS IS WHAT
THE PRINCIPAL WAS TALKING ABOUT.
- THEY'VE LISTED
ALL THE PRIZES RIGHT HERE.
- WHAT? FREE CAFETERIA
MEALS FOR A YEAR? NO WAY!
- BRAND NEW VIDEO GAMES?
- THIS SEEMS RATHER EXTRAVAGANT.
- OH, LOOK AT THAT.
IT SAYS THEY'RE ALSO GIVING
AWAY A SECRET ITEM.
- FEE, NOIN, AND EIN LIMITED
EDITION CELL PHONE STRAPS!
- GIVE ME! GIVE ME! GIVE ME!
- WHAT ARE YOU LIKE FIVE NOW?
WHY THE HELL WOULD YOU WANT
THOSE THINGS?
- WHY DO YOU CARE?
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO GET THEM!
- Hideyoshi: THIS IS A MAP
OF THE ACADEMY.
- Akihisa: SO, I HAVE TO
SEARCH FOR IT HERE?
THAT'S COOL. I'M REALLY GOOD AT
FINDING TREASURE BOXES IN RPG'S.
- Hideyoshi: AND THESE
ARE THE TEST QUESTIONS.
- CRAP.
- ANSWERING QUESTIONS WILL
GIVE YOU THE COORDINATES
TO THE PRIZE LOCATIONS.
THEY PUT TICKETS THERE
THAT YOU CAN EXCHANGE
- FOR WHATEVER IT IS
YOU ACTUALLY WON.
- THAT'S JUST GREAT.
YOU MEAN YOU HAVE TO KNOW
STUFF IN ORDER TO WIN THINGS!
HOW LAME!
- THIS IS FIRST COME
FIRST SERVE.
BUT IF YOU RUN
INTO DIFFERENT TEAMS,
YOU CAN USE YOUR AVATARS TO TAKE
THEIR TICKETS AWAY FROM THEM.
- SO, BASICALLY THERE'S NO
WAY I'M GOING TO WIN
THIS STUPID THING.
HOLD ON! I'VE GOT HIMEJI!
- EVERYONE SHUT UP AND SIT DOWN.
CHECK THIS LIST TO FIND THE TEAM
YOU'LL BE ON FOR THE CONTEST.
- WHO'S ON MINE?
YUUJI AND HIDEYOSHI?
WAIT, WHO ARE THE GIRLS
PAIRED WITH? KOUTA! NO FAIR!
- I DECIDED TO GROUP
TROUBLED STUDENTS TOGETHER.
IT'S MORE FUN FOR ME THAT WAY.
- WHAT! NO!
THAT'S JUST NOT FAIR!
I'LL TAKE HIDEYOSHI
SINCE HE'S CUTE.
BUT WHY WOULD YOU GIVE ME YUUJI?
HE'S NO HELP AT ALL!
- WHATEVER. LIKE WORKING WITH
YOU IS A DREAM COME TRUE.
- YOU HAVE UNTIL AFTER
THE SCHOOL BELL RINGS.
DON'T SCREW IT UP CLASS F!
YOU WILL BE GRADED ON THIS.
- Yuuji: EACH SET
HAS THREE QUESTIONS.
- THE ANSWER TO
THE FIRST QUESTION
SHOWS AN X-AXIS ON THE MAP.
THE SECOND ONE SHOWS
THE Y-POINT,
AND THE THIRD SHOWS THE Z,
WHICH WILL TELL US
WHAT FLOOR IT WILL BE ON.
- SWEETNESS! ALL OF THE
ANSWERS ARE MULTIPLE CHOICE!
PIECE OF CAKE, MY FRIENDS.
-WHY, ARE YOU GOOD
AT MULTIPLE-CHOICE QUESTIONS?
- I THOUGHT YOU KNEW
MY AREA OF SPECIALTY.
WELL, THEN,
LET ME SHOW YOU HOW I ROLL.
- YOU KNOW FOR A SECOND,
I ACTUALLY BELIEVED
YOU WERE SMART.
- I USE MY STRIKER SIGMA FIVE
FOR MATH!
FOR MODERN LANGUAGE,
THE PROBLEM BREAKER!
AND I USE THE SHINING FOR
HISTORY! THEY ALMOST NEVER FAIL!
- YEAH, I'M SURE THEY DON'T.
DID YOU USE THOSE TO FIGURE
OUT IF YOU LIKED HIMEJI?
- SHUT UP. JUST WATCH.
- DO WE HAVE TO?
- ROLL! STRIKER SIGMA FIVE!
FINISH!
HECK, YEAH! I GOT IT!
SIX-FIFTY-TWO FOR THE X-AXIS,
TWO-THIRTY-SEVEN FOR THE Y...
AND Z IS FIVE! FOUND IT!
THE TARGET IS OVER THERE!
- SO THE TARGET IS IN THE SKY?
- YOU CAN GO GET IT.
- THIS IS WEIRD.
I THINK THEY MUST HAVE
SCREWED UP THE QUESTION.
- IT'S NOT THE QUESTION
THAT'S SCREWED.
- Yuuko: WE FOUND IT!
- Aiko: COOL!
- YAY, US! WE FOUND
ONE OF THE WINNING TICKETS!
- I GUESS WE GOT
THE ANSWERS CORRECT!
- BECAUSE WE'RE AWESOME!
- WELL IT APPEARS YOUR X AND Y
NUMBERS WERE ACCURATE.
- SEE? I TOLD YOU STRIKER
SIGMA FIVE WAS INCREDIBLE!
- WHAT'S INCREDIBLE IS
YOU BELIEVE THAT CRAP.
- IT'S A YEARS WORTH OF FREE
DESSERT FROM THE CAFETERIA!
- WE SHOULD SPLIT IT, YOU GUYS!
- I DON'T WANT IT.
- WHY NOT? YOU ON A DIET NOW?
- NO. INSTEAD, IF WE FIND THIS,
LET ME HAVE IT.
- YOU WANT TWO TICKETS SO YOU
CAN GO TO AN AMUSEMENT PARK?
- SHE'S GONNA TAKE
HER BOYFRIEND WITH HER!
- NO, I'M GOING TO TAKE
MY HUSBAND.
- I JUST GOT A REALLY
CREEPY CHILL.
- YOUR LIFE IS CERTAINLY
COMPLICATED.
- ( grunting ) BESIDES MATH,
I'VE GOT NOTHING!
WOW, YOU'RE ON FIRE.
- HEALTH AND PHYS ED.
THAT'S ALL I CAN DO.
- I'M ALL DONE!
- YOU'RE SO GOOD!
LET'S GO GET SOME TICKETS!
- WAIT! DO YOU KNOW
WHERE THIS IS?
WHOA. I'M GOING
IN THE GIRLS' LOCKER ROOM.
- COME ON!
WE'VE GOT PRIZES TO FIND!
- ( breathing heavily )
CAN'T BELIEVE I'M IN THE GIRLS'
LOCKER ROOM RIGHT NOW.
BUT WHERE ARE ALL THE GIRLS?
- Fukuhara: THEY'RE NOT HERE.
- THIS WOULD BE EASIER
IF IT WASN'T SO MESSY.
- YEAH, SOME CHICKS CAN BE HUGE
PIGS WHEN GUYS AREN'T AROUND,
YOU KNOW?
- NO VALUE HERE.
WHAT WITH NO GIRLS CHANGING.
- WHAT'S WRONG KOUTA?
YOU DON'T LOOK GOOD.
- I'M JUST FINE!
AMAZING ACTUALLY.
- OH, NO! KOUTA!
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M STRONGER THAN THIS.
- KOUTA!
- Kouta: THIS IS HARDER
THAN I THOUGHT.
- WELL, NOW,
LET'S SEE WHAT AN IDIOT'S
DETERMINATION LOOKS LIKE.
- Minami: BAKA AND TEST!
- LET'S ROLL. PROBLEM BREAKER!
- SHOULD BE AROUND HERE.
- IN OUR CLASS?
WONDER WHAT THIS IS.
- WELL, GENIUS, ITS CLEARLY
NOT A TICKET.
- TALK ABOUT WEIRD.
MAYBE I SHOULD SHARPEN IT
DOWN OR SOMETHING.
- LIKE ALL THE WAY DOWN.
- OH, I GUESS YOU FOUND IT, HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THIS YOUR BASKET?
- UH-HUH. IN THE BASKET
THERE'S SOME... UH...
- YOSHII?
- YES? WHAT IS IT?
- I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF YOU LIKED SWEETS AT ALL?
- YEP. I LOVE THEM.
- WONDERFUL!
BECAUSE INSIDE THE BASKET
ARE SOME DELICIOUS CHIFFON CAKES
I BAKED EARLIER THIS MORNING.
- WAIT, ARE YOU TELLING ME YOU
KNOW HOW TO BAKE STUFF, TOO?
DON'T TELL ME!
- THAT'S RIGHT, YOUR
LITTLE PROBLEM BREAKER,
IT REALLY DID FIND A PRIZE.
- YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN
SUCH A GREAT GUY.
- WE WILL NEVER FORGET YOU.
- WHY ARE YOU ALL TALKING
LIKE YOU'RE AT MY FUNERAL?
- IF YOU BOYS ARE HUNGRY, YOU'RE
MORE THAN WELCOME TO HAVE ONE.
GO ON. EAT UP!
OH, I'M SO SORRY, BUT IT
LOOKS LIKE I'M SHORT A CAKE.
- ( all exclaiming )
- THERE ARE THREE CHIFFON CAKES,
BUT THERE ARE FOUR OF US!
THAT MEANS,
ONLY ONE CAN SURVIVE.
- ( crowd cheering )
- WELCOME TO THE FIRST
CHAMPIONSHIP MATCH,
GUYS AND GIRLS! ROCK, PAPER,
SCISSORS TO THE DEATH!
- ( cheering )
- IF I LOSE... I DIE!
- WHERE'D KOUTA AND MIZUKI GO?
THEY'VE BEEN GONE FOREVER.
- ( all grunting )
- MAN! THIS TOTALLY SUCKS!
I CAN'T ANSWER ALL THESE
QUESTIONS BY MYSELF!
- DON'T WORRY, BABY!
- MIHARU?
- I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- I ANSWERED ALL YOUR QUESTIONS.
- HEY! STOP!
- OH, PLEASE DON'T
BE LIKE THAT, BABY!
DON'T YOU KNOW HOW HARD
I WORKED ON THOSE FOR YOU.
IF WE CHECK THE COORDINATES
TO THE ANSWERS AGAINST THE MAP,
I KNOW THIS IS GOING TO BE
HARD TO BELIEVE.
BUT IT TURNS OUT
THE BEST PRIZE CAN BE FOUND
- UNDERNEATH YOUR BRA!
- WHAT?
- YOU BETTER LET ME
SEARCH MYSELF.
I PROMISE TO BE
AS GENTLE AS I CAN.
- NO WAY FREAK JOB!
GET OFF OF ME!
- I CAN'T DO THAT.
REMEMBER WE'RE GOING TO BE
GRADED ON OUR PERFORMANCE.
THE NUMBERS DON'T LIE.
LUCKY FOR YOU I GOT HERE FIRST!
- YOU'RE MAKING A HUGE MISTAKE.
STOP!
- WELL IF THAT'S TRUE,
THEN WE MIGHT AS WELL MAKE A
MISTAKE TOGETHER,
- DON'T YOU THINK, BABY?
- NO!
- SERIOUSLY,
I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY'RE WASTING
EVERYONE'S TIME LIKE THIS.
I'M HERE TO ADVANCE MY
EDUCATION NOT PLAY GAMES.
THE MAP POINTS
TO THESE COORDINATES.
THIS IS YOSHII'S SHOE LOCKER!
I CAN'T BE FOUND AROUND HERE!
I'VE GOT TO LEAVE NOW.
SOMEONE MIGHT THINK I'M ABOUT
TO PUT A LOVE LETTER IN THERE!
BUT STILL, I MEAN, I'M HERE AND
THE TICKET COULD BE INSIDE.
NO, STOP!
I GOT TO THINK ABOUT THIS.
NOW SOMEONE MIGHT
GET THE IMPRESSION
I'M ABOUT TO STEAL A LOVE LETTER
FROM HIS LOCKER INSTEAD! NO!
IT'S THE PRIZE IN HERE
I'M AFTER
AND THAT'S THE EXCUSE I'LL GIVE
IF ANYONE ASKS ME ABOUT IT!
BUT, WHAT IF IT'S
A CREEPY PERSON?
THEY COULD THINK WHATEVER
IS INSIDE HIS SHOE LOCKER
IS A PRIZE IN AND OF ITSELF!
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO HANDLE
THAT KIND OF COMPETITION!
NO! WHAT NOW?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO!
- Fukuhara: YOU COULD
STOP SCREAMING.
- I SHALL TRY.
LET'S ROLL SHINING! ANSWER!
- HERE IT IS!
WAY TO GO, HIDEYOSHI!
- I DON'T BELIEVE I HAD
ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT. HA!
- OKAY, LET'S SEE WHAT WE GOT.
WHAT? TRY AGAIN?
- SO THIS WASN'T
THE RIGHT PLACE AFTER ALL.
- SHOOT! I BET THEY GAVE US
A TRICK QUESTION.
- I GUESS YOUR MAGIC STICK
FAILED. SHOCKER.
- MAYBE I SHOULD CHANGE THE WAY
THE POINTY PART IS ANGLED.
- I SERIOUSLY DOUBT THAT
WILL INCREASE ITS ACCURACY.
- WELL, HOW ABOUT...
THIS? LOOK.
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
YOU ANSWERED THEM?
- YOU SURE YOU GOT
THEM RIGHT, YUUJI?
I MEAN, I DON'T
WANNA GO ANYWHERE WEIRD
BECAUSE THEY'RE WRONG.
- Yuuji: UNLIKE YOUR STUPID
PENCIL ANSWERS?
- WELL, ACCORDING TO YUUJI,
THIS SHOULD BE THE PLACE.
- YOU WERE RIGHT! IT'S HERE!
HEY, HOW'D YOU FIGURE OUT
ALL THOSE QUESTIONS?
- SIMPLE, I JUST LOOKED
FOR ALL THE ONES I KNEW
AND ONLY ANSWERED THOSE.
- I'M STILL FAIRLY
IMPRESSED THOUGH.
- BUT YOU'RE RANKED LIKE LAST
IN ALL THE TESTS...
TELL ME YOU DIDN'T CHEAT, YUUJI!
- HARD TO BELIEVE I MIGHT
KNOW SOMETHING?
- YOSHII. WHAT PRIZE DID WE WIN?
- LET'S SEE.
IT'S THE VIP TICKET
TO THAT AMUSEMENT PARK.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
FOR A COUPLE.
- ACCORDING TO THE TICKET,
THE COUPLE IS INVITED
TO A SPECIAL EVENT
REFERRED TO AS THE
WEDDING EXPERIENCE.
- NICE. THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
YUUJI, YOU WANNA USE IT
AND TAKE SHOUKO?
- PUT THAT AWAY
BEFORE SHE HEARS YOU!
IT WON'T JUST BE AN EXPERIENCE.
SHE'LL MAKE IT REAL!
GET THAT DISGUSTING
THING OUT OF MY FACE!
I DON'T WANT TO SEE IT!
- IF YOU'RE SURE. HIDEYOSHI?
YOU WANT TO GO WITH
ME ON SUNDAY?
- NO. IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
FOR A COUPLE!
- SO THEN ARE YOU SAYING
THAT YOU DON'T LIKE ME?
- I'M A GUY.
- REJECTED!
THE PAIN IS MAKING ME COLD.
I HAVE TO END THIS MISERY!
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY!
BUT HIDEYOSHI! I LIKE YOU!
- WHY ARE YOU ACTING
LIKE A JACKASS?
- HOW CAN YOU ASK
ME THAT QUESTION?
YOU KNOW WHY I'M DOING THIS.
IT'S CAUSE OF THE
LEGEND THAT SAYS
IF YOU CONFESS YOUR LOVE
UNDER A SPECIAL TREE,
YOU'LL NEVER FEEL PAIN AGAIN!
- THERE'S NO LEGEND LIKE THAT.
-THERE IS TOO. THE TREE WAS USED
TO BUILD OUR SCHOOL, DUH.
AND ACCORDING TO THE LEGEND,
HIDEYOSHI IS THE NAME
OF A HOT CHICK.
IN OTHER WORDS,
IF I CONFESS MY LOVE TO
HIDEYOSHI IN THIS SCHOOL,
I'LL BE HAPPY FOREVER!
- All: WHAT DID YOU SAY, YOSHII?
- THERE ARE SO MANY HOLES
IN THAT LOGIC,
- I HONESTLY DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE TO BEGIN.
- All: WE LOVE YOU,
HIDEYOSHI KINOSHITA!
- ( all chattering )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HAVE YOU ALL GONE CRAZY?
- OF COURSE. EVERYTHING WE FOUND
WAS COMPLETELY WORTHLESS.
- THIS CHALLENGE IS DIFFICULT
FOR IDIOTS.
- DOESN'T LOOK LIKE THERE ARE
A LOT OF PRIZES LEFT ANYMORE.
- I WONDER WHAT THE SUPER SECRET
PRIZE MIGHT HAVE BEEN.
- HEY! NO ONE'S FOUND THE FEE
CELL PHONE STRAP YET!
- YOU WANT TO KEEP PLAYING?
REALLY?
- THE ONLY QUESTIONS REMAINING
ARE THE HARDEST ONES.
I DON'T SUPPOSE YOU'D WANT TO
RANDOMLY DIG
THROUGH THE SCHOOLYARD FOR IT?
- RANDOM? MAYBE? I GOT IT!
I KNOW THE REST OF THE ANSWERS!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
I'M CHOOSING EVERY SINGLE ANSWER
THAT'S AVAILABLE ON THE TEST!
- EVERY ONE?
- BECAUSE, THERE'S
A TICKET HIDDEN
WHERE AT LEAST ONE OF THESE
X'S AND Y'S ARE CROSSED.
WHY DIDN'T I
THINK OF THIS BEFORE?
- WHAT ABOUT THE HEIGHT?
- EASY. CHECK ALL FLOORS!
- THERE ARE WAY TOO MANY.
WE CANNOT GO THROUGH ALL
OF THESE AND SEARCH THEM.
- SURE WE CAN. WE'RE NOT DOING
ANYTHING ELSE, ARE WE?
- THIS IS UNREASONABLE.
- YEAH, IT IS,
BUT IT SOUNDS INTERESTING.
WE CAN'T SOLVE THE
QUESTIONS ANYWAY.
LET'S SHOW THIS SCHOOL
IDIOTS
CAN THINK OUTSIDE
OF THE BOX TOO!
- I THINK WE SHOULD GO FOR IT.
- ME TOO.
LET'S GO!
- I'LL GO CHECK THE
FOURTH FLOOR!
AKIHISA, YOU'RE ON THE FIRST.
HIDEYOSHI, YOU TAKE THE SECOND!
- OKAY!
- GOT IT!
- CLEANING CLOSETS? NOPE!
- NOPE!
- ( exclaims )
- OCCUPADO.
- LOCKER! NOPE!
- NOPE!
- A DOG?
- ( screaming )
- WHICH ONE?
- ( girls screaming )
- ( screaming )
- TRASH BIN!
- NOPE!
- NOPE! WHY ME?
- LADIES ROOM! NOPE!
- NOPE!
- OH?
- Toudou: SOMEONE IN HERE.
- FISH TANK! NOPE!
- NOPE!
- SON OF A...
- ONE MORE TIME! NOPE!
- NOPE!
- OCCUPADO.
- ONE MORE TIME!
- I'M IN HERE.
- OH, GOOD. IT'S OPEN.
WHAT AM I DOING IN HERE?
- ( all panting )
- Yuuji: DAMN IT.
WE FOUND NOTHING!
- MAYBE THERE'S JUST
NOTHING LEFT.
- NO, WAIT! WE HAVEN'T
CHECKED UP HERE YET!
- BUT, WHERE COULD THEY HAVE
POSSIBLY HIDDEN SOMETHING?
- GET OUT OF TOWN. THE FEE
STRAP STILL HASN'T BEEN FOUND.
IT HAS TO BE HERE.
THIS IS IT! I WAS RIGHT!
CHECK THIS!
WE FOUND IT EVEN THOUGH WE
KNEW NONE OF THE ANSWERS!
- REALLY?
THAT'S FUNNY CONSIDERING I
FOUND IT BECAUSE I DID KNOW.
- ( gasping ) IT'S HER!
- YUUKO! WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- ACCORDING TO THE RULES,
WE CAN TAKE IT BY FIGHTING WITH
OUR AVATARS, ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- THIS IS BAD.
- I'LL APPROVE IT.
- Girls: SUMMON!
- Boys: SUMMON!
- THIS IS NOT GOOD AT ALL.
THERE'S NO WAY WE'LL WIN.
- WHO'D HAVE GUESSED WE'D END UP
HAVING TO FIGHT THESE GIRLS?
- YOU GUYS, WHAT NOW?
- WE WILL NOT HOLD BACK.
- ARE YOU JERKS READY?
- OKAY THEN, BYE-BYE!
- ( girls screaming )
- ( bell chiming )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- YOU RAN OUT OF TIME.
- WAIT, DOES THAT MEAN...
- WE GOT IT!
- WE WON!
- YES. WE ROCK!
( laughing )
AWESOME!
IT'S THE FEE CELL STRAP!
OH, SWEET! IT'S A SET OF THREE!
- WELL, GOOD FOR YOU.
- I CAN'T WAIT TO GIVE
THEM TO HAZUKI.
HEY, WHAT'S THIS?
- Hideyoshi: MAYBE WE ENDED UP
WITH THE SECRET ITEM.
- I WONDER WHAT THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO DO. LOOK, THERE'S A MANUAL.
"IRON BRACELETS... THEIR
ACTIVATION WORD IS, AWAKEN."
- THAT DOESN'T TELL US ANYTHING.
- YEAH, WHAT HAPPENS AFTER
THEY ACTIVATE?
- WELL, LET'S TRY IT!
- All: AWAKEN!
- IT'S A FIELD!
- AND NO TEACHER!
- All: SUMMON!
- THIS IS BEYOND COOL!
- WITH THESE BRACELETS,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO SUMMON OUR
AVATARS WHENEVER WE WANT.
- THE FIELD MIGHT BE KIND OF
TINY, BUT WHO THE HECK CARES?
- HOLD ON! WHY DO MY CLOTHES
ALWAYS END UP TORN OFF?
- AKIHISA, NOTHING HAPPENED
TO YOURS, RIGHT?
- NO, I GUESS NOT.
- LOOKS LIKE ONLY AN IDIOT
CAN USE THEM.
- WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE AN IDIOT, TOO, YUUJI!
- YEAH, BUT YOU'RE
A FIRST RATE IDIOT.
- WHAT?
- AN ULTIMATE IDIOT.
- UH-UH!
- YOU'RE THE SUPREME IDIOT!
- WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- INTERESTING.
OBVIOUSLY THERE ARE STILL
IMPROVEMENTS TO BE MADE.
FUNNY.
BLUNT SCISSORS AND
FOOLS CAN BE VALUABLE
IF YOU MAKE WISE USE OF THEM.
REDEEMING QUALITIES CAN BE
FOUND ANYWHERE IN ANYONE.
- ( theme song playing )
- Fukuhara: QUESTION SIX.
WHAT STROKES DOES THE INDIVIDUAL
MEDLEY IN SWIMMING CONSIST OF?
- Akihisa: ANIME SONG MEDLEY,
POP MUSIC MEDLEY, AND CHOCOLATE!
- Fukuhara: I DO
HAPPEN TO LIKE CHOCOLATE.
- Akihisa: NEXT TIME, ME, POOLS,
AND SWIMSUIT PARADISES AND...
- Fukuhara: THIS WILL BE
ON THE TEST.