- GOOD MORNING, YUUJI.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL OUTSIDE TODAY.
ARE YOU HUNGRY? HERE.
YUUJI? YOU LOOK SLEEPY.
- SHOUKO, TOSS ME MY CELL.
HELLO, IS THIS THE POLICE?
I'D LIKE TO REPORT AN INTRUDER.
( theme song playing )
- YUUJI, WHAT IS THIS?
- WELL, I DON'T KNOW. I'VE
NEVER SEEN THAT BOOK BEFORE.
- REALLY? BECAUSE IT WAS HIDDEN
UNDER A FALSE BOTTOM
IN THE THIRD DRAWER OF YOUR DESK
WITH A SCHOOLBOOK COVER
DISGUISING IT.
- HELLO? DID YOU HAVE
AN EMERGENCY? HELLO?
- I'M SORRY. I MADE A MISTAKE.
- ALL RIGHT, IF YOU BURN IT,
I WILL FORGIVE YOU.
- WHY WOULD I DO THAT? WHAT
DO I CARE IF YOU FORGIVE ME?
- FINE. I'LL TAKE CARE
OF IT MYSELF.
- YOU CAN'T JUST TORCH
SOMEONE'S STUFF!
( Yuuji screams )
SO TELL ME WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE ANYWAY?
- LET ME SHOW YOU.
- WAIT. THE VIP TICKET
FOR THE AMUSEMENT PARK?
HOW DID YOU GET THAT?
- SOMEONE GENEROUS
GAVE IT TO ME.
- YEAH, RIGHT, SOMEONE GENEROUS.
AKIHISA WAS THE ONE
WHO ENDED UP WITH THOSE TICKETS.
- Akihisa: WASN'T ME.
I'M NOT GUILTY!
- WE HAVE SPECIAL PASSES
TO THE WEDDING EXPERIENCE.
( phone ringing )
- Akihisa: HELLO?
WHO MAY I ASK IS CALLING?
- ( in menacing tone )
I'M GONNA KILL YOU!
- WHAT? BUT WHY?
WHO ARE YOU? PLEASE DON'T.
- WELL. IT'S TIME. LET'S GO.
- NO WAY.
- SO YOU LIED TO ME?
- I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- YOU PROMISED THAT
YOU WOULD GO OUT WITH ME
BACK WHEN YOU LOST THE ST WAR.
- I DON'T REMEMBER THAT AT ALL.
- IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
YOU SWORE IF YOU
BROKE YOUR PROMISE,
YOU WOULD MARRY ME RIGHT AWAY.
- OKAY, NOW YOU'RE JUST
MAKING THINGS UP.
- ( firecrackers exploding )
- OF COURSE. THIS IS
ALL AKIHISA'S FAULT.
I'M GONNA KILL HIM.
ARGH! WOULD YOU LET GO?
HOW COME EVERY TIME YOU TOUCH ME
IT HAS TO HURT?
- COUPLES ARE SUPPOSED TO WALK
ARM IN ARM LIKE THIS.
- REALLY?
BECAUSE I DON'T SEE ANY OTHER
CHICKS USING BRUTE FORCE!
- HELLO, LOVERS! WE'D LIKE TO
GIVE YOU A BIG FAT WELCOME!
( phone ringing )
HELLO?
- HEY, YOU JERK WAD, I BET YOU
GUYS THINK YOU'RE REALLY FUNNY,
DON'T YOU?
- RUN! I'M INNOCENT!
- IF THAT'S TRUE, THEN WHY
THE HELL ARE YOU RUNNING?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE A PART OF
THIS WHOLE THING TOO, HIDEYOSHI!
- WHO DID YOU SAY? I HAPPEN TO
BE A MEMBER OF THE STAFF HERE.
THIS IS MY OCCUPATION. I AM NOT
ACQUAINTED WITH THIS PERSON
TO WHOM YOU ARE REFERRING.
- REALLY? I'M SUPPOSED
TO BELIEVE THAT?
( phone ringing )
- OH HEAVENS, MY HAND
JUST SLIPPED FOR NO REASON.
- OF COURSE IT DID.
- MAY I PLEASE HAVE
YOUR TICKETS NOW, FOLKS?
- HERE.
- WHOA! WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT.
YOU HAVE VIP PASSES WITH YOU!
ALPHA CALLING BRAVO.
I'VE CONFIRMED THE TARGET.
WE HAVE A CODE SEVEN AND ARE
SHIFTING TO OPERATION WEDDING.
REPEAT: OPERATION WEDDING.
- WE'RE STANDING RIGHT HERE.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE CAN'T HEAR YOU!
- PLEASE CALM DOWN, SIR.
IT'S NOT YOUR CONCERN.
- YOU WERE JUST
TALKING ABOUT ME!
- NOW THEN,
IT'S ABOUT TIME FOR US TO TAKE A
COMPLIMENTARY PICTURE.
- SMILE.
- SHOUKO, SORRY!
AM I SUPPOSED TO NOT NOTICE
IT'S YOU DOWN THERE BEING YOUR
PERVERTED SELF?
HEH!
- YUUJI, BE NICE.
- OKAY, I'LL DO MY BEST.
- GOOD. I'LL REWARD YOU LATER.
- NO! HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU,
I DON'T GIVE A CRAP
WHAT YOUR UNDERWEAR LOOKS LIKE.
- Shouko: I WILL NEVER
FORGIVE YOU FOR THAT.
- STOP IT! PUSHING DOWN ON
SOMEONE'S TEMPLES LIKE THAT
CAN CAUSE BRAIN DAMAGE!
- CHEESE!
- Shouko: CHEESE.
- Yuuji: WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS PICTURE?
- IT'S A FREE SOUVENIR
FOR THE HAPPY COUPLE.
- IT'LL BE PUT UP IN
THE PARK'S PHOTO STUDIO
SO EVERYONE CAN SEE IT!
- YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
- YUUJI, DON'T BE SHY.
- I'M NOT BEING SHY. I JUST
DON'T WANT THIS PICTURE UP.
- COOL! CHECK IT OUT, BABY!
LET'S HAVE THEM TAKE
OUR PICTURE, TOO!
- WHATEVER YOU WANT, SUGAR.
HEY, LITTLE DUDE!
YOU CAN GO AHEAD
AND TAKE OUR PICTURE NEXT.
- UNFORTUNATELY, GOOD SIR,
THIS SERVICE IS ONLY AVAILABLE
TO OUR VIP TICKET HOLDERS.
- WHAT? WE'RE CUSTOMERS, TOO,
AND JUST ASKING FOR ONE PICTURE,
SO WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
WOULDN'T YOU RATHER HAVE
A HOT COUPLE ON DISPLAY
INSTEAD OF
THOSE LAME TWEENIES. WELL?
- IT'S TRUE. I MEAN, LOOK AT US.
IT'S NOT LIKE HIGH SCHOOL KIDS
CAN COMPARE, RIGHT?
- HOLD ON.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- I WILL NOT ALLOW THEM
TO TALK THAT WAY ABOUT US.
- DON'T LET THOSE JERKS
GET TO YOU, OKAY?
- ALL RIGHT THEN,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
- WE WANT TO HAVE A PICTURE
JUST LIKE THEY HAD!
- ALL RIGHT. IF YOU INSIST,
WE'LL DO IT.
PLEASE COME THIS WAY.
IF YOU COULD PUT YOUR HAND
RIGHT HERE.
NOW, SQUEEZE AS HARD AS YOU CAN.
- ( man groans )
- CHEESE.
- Girl: CHEESE.
- WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- SAID YOU WANTED US
TO TAKE THE SAME PICTURE.
- I HOPE YOU RUN FAST,
'CAUSE I'M GONNA KILL YOU!
- GO-GO! BURGER HEAD'S
LOST HIS MIND!
- ARE YOU MAKING FUN OF ME,
YOU PUNK?
- WOULD YOU LIKE FRIES
WITH THAT, SIR?
- OF COURSE. YOU KNOW, IF
YOU WANTED TO LEAVE INTSEAD,
I'D BE COOL WITH IT.
DOESN'T IT BOTHER YOU AT ALL
THAT EVERYONE CAN SEE
WHAT YOU'RE DOING TO ME?
- DON'T BE SHY. RELAX.
- I'M NOT BEING SHY, I JUST
PREFER NOT BE HURTING!
- BUT THIS IS HOW COUPLES WALK.
- IT'S ARM IN ARM,
NOT ARM IN PAIN!
- GREETINGS TO THE ADORABLE
LOOKING COUPLE OVER THERE!
- SEE. I TOLD YOU
WE LOOKED LIKE A COUPLE.
- SHE'S A GIANT FUZZ BALL.
WHAT DOES SHE KNOW?
- I AM FEE THE FOX.
PLEASE ALLOW ME TO SHOW YOU A
FUN AND INTERESTING ATTRACTION.
- EARLIER I COULD'VE SWORN
AKIHISA WAS OUT
ON A DATE WITH SOME CHICK.
- WHAT? YOU SAW YOSHII?
WHERE IS HE? WHERE DID THEY GO?
- HELLO, THERE, HIMEJI.
- ( train whistle toots )
- I AM FEE THE FOX.
PLEASE ALLOW ME TO SHOW YOU A
FUN AND INTERESTING ATTRACTION.
- LOOK, IF YOU WANT TO PLAY
INNOCENT, THAT'S FINE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST TELL US WHERE
WE SHOULD GO THEN, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY! DON'T MISS THE HAUNTED
HOUSE RIGHT OVER THERE!
YOU SHOULD GO NOW!
- AWESOME. SHOUKO, WE'RE GOING
ANYWHERE BUT THAT HAUNTED HOUSE.
- WAIT! YOU HAVE TO GO!
WHY DON'T YOU WANNA?
- BECAUSE I'M SURE YOU GUYS HAVE
SET UP SOMETHING STUPID THERE.
- PLEASE! GO TO
THE HAUNTED HOUSE!
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS OUT
ON IT! PLEASE!
- NOT HAPPENING.
- STOP RIGHT THERE, YUUJI!
I'M NOIN, AND I WILL NOT
LET YOU MAKE FEE CRY ANYMORE!
- OH, COME ON, YOUR HEAD'S
ALL MESSED UP, AKIHISA.
- HOW RUDE!
WHICH PART IS MESSED UP?
- YUUJI, NOIN IS
THE ABSENTMINDED ONE.
- I DON'T CARE.
WHAT KINDA FOX WOULD HAVE
HIS HEAD ON BACKWARDS?
- YOSHII! YOU PUT YOUR HEAD ON
THE WRONG WAY!
- WHAT? DAMN IT! NO WONDER
I COULDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
- HURRY AND FIX IT BEFORE THEY
FIGURE OUT WHO WE ARE!
- Akihisa: WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHERE AM I?
- THE SAD THING IS, THEY REALLY
THINK THEY'VE FOOLED US.
- OH, BY THE WAY,
HOW DID YOUR DATE WITH THAT
SUPER HOT COLLEGE CHICK GO, MAN?
- WHAT?
- YOSHII, I HEARD
WHILE WE WERE WORKING
ON THIS VERY
IMPORTANT ASSIGNMENT
THAT YOU WENT OUT ON A DATE.
- WAIT. WHERE'D YOU HEAR THAT?
- MINAMI'S ON HER WAY
HERE NOW.
WE THINK WE NEED TO SIT DOWN
AND TALK ABOUT IT.
- NO! BAD IDEA. THIS PARK IS
SUPPOSED TO BE FOR AMUSEMENT
NOT A-FIGHTING!
- HEY! WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON HERE, AKI?
- HOW'D SHE GET HERE SO FAST?
TRASH CAN! AND GROUND!
- YOU'RE GONNA TELL US
EVERY SINGLE DETAIL.
- AND YOU NEED TO TELL US
THE TRUTH, TOO.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
- LET'S GET OUT OF HERE, SHOUKO.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO RIDE
THE FERRIS WHEEL
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
SHOUKO? WHERE'D YOU...
- ( dramatic music playing )
- EVERYTHING SET UP,
THE HAUNTED HOUSE IS READY.
- STOP THAT!
- WE'RE GOING WHERE THEY WANT.
- AH, WHAT THE HELL
DID HIDEYOSHI SAY TO YOU?
- THAT I CAN JUMP INTO
YOUR ARMS IN THERE.
- SIGN THIS BEFORE ENTERING.
- SIGN WHAT?
- LIABILITY WAIVER.
SUCH WAIVERS ARE OFTEN PREPARED
IN THESE TYPES OF DANGEROUS
SITUATIONS. JUST IN CASE.
- REALLY? SO THIS PLACE IS
ACTUALLY DANGEROUS?
AT LEAST THAT'LL
MAKE IT INTERESTING.
WHAT'S IT SAY?
WAIVER: I, YUUJI SAKAMOTO,
WILL LOVE SHOUKO KIRISHIMA
AS MY WIFE
AS LONG AS I LIVE AND WILL SHARE
MY JOYS AND SORROWS WITH HER.
SO I SWEAR?
- HERE'S A PEN.
- AND A REGISTERED SEAL.
- INK PAD TO STAMP IT WITH.
- WHAT THE HELL?
AM I THE ONLY ONE
WHO FINDS THIS
ENTIRE THING RIDICULOUS?
- UNDER THE CARBON SHEET
IS A SECOND SHEET,
YOUR MARRIAGE REGISTRATION FORM.
- HOW CONSIDERATE.
- NO, IT ISN'T!
- Shouko: BAKA AND TEST.
- PLEASE, COME THIS WAY.
- WOULD YOU MIND
HOLDING MY BAG FOR ME?
- MAKE SURE WHAT'S INSIDE
DOESN'T FALL OUT.
- AS YOU WISH.
WELL THEN, I HOPE YOU ENJOY
YOURSELVES
WHILST BEING
THOROUGHLY TERRIFIED.
( finger snaps )
- ( eerie music playing )
- SO THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
AN ABANDONED HOSPITAL?
I GUESS IT'S NOT
TOO BAD, CONSIDERING...
- Recorded voice: HIMEJI...
- WHAT'S THAT?
- THAN SHOUKO...
- IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU.
- HIMEJI'S MORE THAN...
- WEIRD. IT'S LIKE SYNTHESIZED.
I WONDER
IF HIDEYOSHI'S DOING IT.
- WHATEVER. IT'S NOT
SCARY AT ALL.
- HIMEJI IS MORE MY TYPE
THAN SHOUKO.
- WAIT... WHAT?
- SHE'S GOT BIGGER BOOBIES, TOO.
HIMEJI IS MORE MY
TYPE THAN SHOUKO.
SHE'S GOT BIGGER BOOBIES, TOO.
HIMEJI'S MORE MY TYPE
THAN SHOUKO...
- YUUJI, IS THAT TRUE?
- OKAY, GUYS! VERY FUNNY!
YOU GOT ME. I'M SCARED.
- YUUJI, PREPARE YOURSELF.
- CRAP! WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
SHE'S REALLY GONNA HURT ME!
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- PLEASE CALM DOWN!
IT'S JUST A TRICK!
- ( girl screams )
- ( breathing heavily )
- HOW DID IT GO?
I BET THAT RIDE MADE YOU WANT
TO GET MARRIED, DIDN'T IT?
- WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'D WANT TO GET MARRIED?
- BECAUSE THEY SAY WHEN A MAN
AND A WOMAN FACE DANGER TOGETHER
THAT COUPLE FORMS
A SPECIAL BOND.
- THAT ONLY WORKS WHEN ONE
OF THEM ISN'T THE DANGER
THE OTHER ONE IS FACING!
- YUUJI, I THINK
IT'S LUNCHTIME.
- FINE. ALL THAT RUNNING AROUND
MADE ME HUNGRY ANYWAY.
- ( music on PA )
- Fukuhara on PA: UM, ATTENTION,
GUESTS, ATTENTION GUESTS.
WE'VE PREPARED A SPECIAL MENU
FOR THOSE WITH A VIP TICKET
AT THE RESTAURANT TODAY.
AND DURING LUNCH, A SPECIAL
PERFORMANCE WILL BE HELD.
- NICE. A SPECIAL MENU.
- FOLLOW US TO THE RESTAURANT.
- RIGHT THIS WAY.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, SHOUKO?
- NOTHING. I'M JUST
REALLY HUNGRY.
- ME, TOO.
THAT WAS PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
- I'M WITH YOU,
OF COURSE IT WAS.
- ( both gasp )
- GOOD AFTERNOON, EVERYONE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING TO
OUR SPECIAL PERFORMANCE TODAY.
- BELIEVE IT OR NOT, WE ACTUALLY
HAVE A BEAUTIFUL YOUNG COUPLE
DINING WITH US WHO
ARE VERY EXCITED
ABOUT GETTING MARRIED SOON!
- EXCUSE ME?
- IN THEIR HONOR, WE'VE ARRANGED
A GAME TO CELEBRATE THEIR UNION
AND TO SHOW OUR SUPPORT!
GET READY, EVERYONE,
BECAUSE IT'S TIME FOR
THE SUPER DELUXE GRAND
WEDDING EXPERIENCE.
- YAY! LET THE SHOW BEGIN!
EVERYONE CHEER!
- DAMN IT! THEY'VE LOCKED
THE EXIT!
- IF THEY ANSWER THE FOLLOWING
FIVE QUESTIONS CORRECTLY,
THEY'LL BE ABLE
TO EXPERIENCE
OUR EXCITING AND ROMANTIC
WEDDING PACKAGE!
AND IF THEY WANT TO GO AHEAD
AND GET MARRIED AT THE TIME,
IT WON'T BE A PROBLEM.
- OH, IT'S A PROBLEM!
- WILL MISTER YUUJI SAKAMOTO
AND THE LOVELY MISS SHOUKO
PLEASE HEAD TOWARD THE STAGE?
- NO, WE WON'T!
- WEDDING EXPERIENCE?
WE WILL NOT FAIL.
- IT'S A DREAM COME TRUE!
- LET GO OF ME, SHOUKO!
- AREN'T YOU EXCITED?
- THIS BLOWS.
I HAVE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- ALL RIGHT,
LET THE QUIZ BEGIN!
- OF COURSE! WE HAVE TO ANSWER
THE QUESTIONS CORRECTLY!
THIS WILL BE A PIECE OF CAKE
TO LOSE.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS GIVE
THE WRONG ANSWER!
- QUESTION NUMBER ONE!
- BRING IT ON! I'VE GOT
THIS THING IN THE BAG!
- WHEN IS MISTER YUUJI SAKAMOTO
AND MISS SHOUKO'S ANNIVERSARY?
- OKAY, I DON'T THINK I
UNDERSTAND WHAT THEY'RE ASKING.
- I KNOW.
IT IS EVERY DAY.
- CORRECT! EVERY DAY IS AN
ANNIVERSARY! GOOD JOB, LOVERS!
QUESTION NUMBER TWO!
- I'M GONNA GIVE THEM
SUCH A WRONG ANSWER,
THEY WON'T
KNOW WHAT HIT 'EM.
- TELL US WHERE ARE YOU GOING
TO HOLD YOUR WEDDING?
- ( beeping )
- MACKEREL COOKED IN MISO!
- THAT IS CORRECT!
- ( audience cheering )
- IS NOT!
- IS TO! YOU'VE PLANNED TO
HAVE YOUR UPCOMING WEDDING
HELD IN THE PHOENIX HALL WHICH
HAS RECENTLY BEEN NICKNAMED
"MACKEREL COOKED IN MISO"!
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU JUST NICKNAMED IT
THAT, DIDN'T YOU?
- Akihisa: QUESTION
NUMBER THREE!
- NOW I GET WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
MAKE MY NEXT ANSWER WORK.
- WHERE DID YOU TWO
MEET THE FIRST TIME?
- I GOT IT!
( screams )
- GRADE SCHOOL.
- THAT'S CORRECT!
- FINE! I'LL GIVE UP BEFORE
THEY CAN EVEN ASK IT THIS TIME!
- AND NOW FOR QUESTION NUMBER
FOUR! THE TWO OF YOU...
- I DON'T KNOW!
- CORRECT.
- IT'S NO USE.
THEY WON'T LET MY ANSWERS BE
WRONG NO MATTER WHAT I DO.
THIS IS THE END FOR ME.
- HELLO! NOT FAIR!
WE ARE PLANNING TO GET MARRIED,
TOO, YOU KNOW.
WHY ARE THEY THE ONLY ONES
WHO GET THE SPECIAL FANCY
TREATMENT, HUH?
- YEAH. WE WANNA PLAY
YOUR STUPID GAME.
- LOOK, BURGER HEAD... I MEAN,
SIR, WE'RE NOT DONE YET.
- NOW YOU LISTEN TO ME,
YOU STUPID FOX.
I'M A CUSTOMER, TOO! YOU JERK!
- HE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
WE WANT A WEDDING THINGIE.
AND WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO HAVE IT, TOO!
- WELL, YEAH, BUT...
- DON'T GIVE ME THAT
"WELL, YEAH BUT" CRAP!
WE'RE GONNA DO IT,
SO JUST GIVE US WHAT WE WANT!
- OH MY GOD, YOU GUYS,
I'M SO SMART! I HAVE AN IDEA!
WHY DON'T WE ASK THE
LAST QUESTION.
IF THEY GET IT RIGHT, THEY WIN,
BUT IF THEY GET IT WRONG, WE DO!
- I DON'T THINK THAT'LL WORK.
- PERFECT! I KNOW I'LL BE
ABLE TO ANSWER THEM WRONG.
THEN I CAN FINALLY GET OUT OF
THIS WHOLE WEDDING NIGHTMARE!
- HEY!
- ALL RIGHT. LISTEN UP, KIDS,
HERE'S THE QUESTION!
WHAT'S THE CAPITOL CITY
OF EUROPE?
- ( all mumbling )
- CONGRATULATIONS! MISTER YUUJI
SAKAMOTO AND MISS SHOUKO HAVE
WON THE EXCLUSIVE
WEDDING EXPERIENCE!
- AND NOW WE'D LIKE TO PRESENT
TODAY'S MAIN EVENT!
THE WEDDING
STARRING YUUJI AND SHOUKO!
- FIRST, LET'S WELCOME OUR GROOM
WITH A WARM ROUND OF APPLAUSE!
- ( audience cheering )
- YOU REALIZE I'M GONNA KNOCK
YOUR TEETH OUT FOR THIS.
- AND NEXT,
THE GROOMS PROFILE!
WE DON'T HAVE THIS PART READY
YET, SO WE'LL JUST SKIP IT.
- WHAT?
- FINALLY! WELCOME THE BRIDE AS
SHE MAKES HER GRAND ENTRANCE!
- ( mellow music playing )
- ( Yuuji gasps )
- SHE LOOKS SO PRETTY!
- UM, YUUJI?
TELL ME THE TRUTH. DO YOU REALLY
THINK THAT I LOOK LIKE A BRIDE?
- ALL THINGS CONSIDERED,
YOU LOOK PRETTY NICE.
I MEAN I'VE DEFINITELY SEEN
WORSE OUT THERE.
- YUUJI?
- YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
- I'M SO HAPPY.
- WAIT... DON'T CRY.
- THIS IS A DREAM COME TRUE.
- A DREAM?
- I WANTED THIS SINCE...
SINCE WE WERE KIDS.
I PRAYED FOR THIS MOMENT.
I'VE ALWAYS DREAMED
OF BEING ABLE TO MARRY YOU.
I DREAMED THAT ONE DAY
I WOULD GET TO BE THE BRIDE
OF YUUJI SAKAMOTO.
I NEVER THOUGHT IT
WOULD ACTUALLY HAPPEN.
AND HERE WE ARE.
YOU AND I,
STANDING LIKE THIS TOGETHER.
I'M JUST REALLY HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
AFTER ALL, I'M HERE WITH YOU.
THIS DAY IS EVERYTHING
I'VE EVER HOPED FOR.
- SHOUKO, I...
- OH, MAN. THIS IS BORING!
- ( grunting )
- CAN SOMEONE DO SOMETHING
INTERESTING, PLEASE?
NO ONE CARES ABOUT
YOUR LOSER LOVE LIFE.
SO HURRY UP, SO WE CAN
GET THIS THING OVER WITH!
- YEAH, WE'VE GOT STUFF TO DO,
YOU KNOW.
ENOUGH WITH THE CHIT CHAT.
SHUT UP ALREADY AND GET
TO THE FREAKIN' POINT!
- DOES ANYONE ELSE
THINK IT'S WEIRD
THAT HER DREAM IS
TO BECOME A BRIDE?
I MEAN, WHAT,
SHE'S LIKE TWELVE, RIGHT?
- NOT TO BE RUDE,
BUT THAT IS WAY CREEPY.
- MAYBE WE'RE ON ONE OF THOSE
PRACTICAL JOKE SHOWS?
- ( both laughing )
- Girl: C'MON!
WHERE ARE THE CAMERAS?
- I DARE YOU TO SAY THAT AGAIN!
WHAT DO YOU CARE?
WHY DO YOU TWO
HAVE TO BE SO RUDE?
I THINK YOU BETTER GET OUT OF
HERE BEFORE I KICK YOU OUT. SO.
- WAIT, YOSHII!
- WHAT?
- YOU'RE ABOUT TO MESS UP
THE ENTIRE EVENT!
- BUT THEY... THEY WERE
SO MEAN TO SHOUKO.
-I CAN'T JUST DO NOTHING!
- Yuuji: SHOUKO...
- (people chattering )
- ( panting )
- Mizuki: YOSHII!
DID YOU SEE HER ANYWHERE?
- Akihisa: SHE DIDN'T
GO THIS WAY.
- Hideyoshi: YUUJI!
WHERE DID SHOUKO GO?
- Yuuji: I DON'T KNOW.
- WHY NOT?
- WELL, DO YOU KNOW WHERE
SHE MIGHT BE?
EVERYONE'S REALLY
WORRIED ABOUT HER.
- I'M NOT. I DON'T CARE.
- ( all gasping )
- I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
I HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
- Mizuki: YOU HAVE TO WHAT?
I HAVE TO PEE. SEE YA.
- THAT WEDDING WAS A JOKE.
TALK ABOUT TOTAL CRAP, RIGHT?
I MEAN LOOK AT THE COUPLE.
- OH, YUUJI, I'VE ALWAYS
DREAMED OF MARRYING YOU.
HOW'S THAT? SOUND LIKE HER?
- YEAH, YOU REALLY DO. THAT WAS
PERFECT. SHE WAS SO PATHETIC.
- ( both laughing )
- HEY, YOU TWO.
- WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT,
HIGH SCHOOL BOY?
- WELL, IT'S REALLY NOT
THAT BIG OF A DEAL, BUT...
- WHAT?
- I THINK THE THREE OF US
NEED TO HAVE A TALK!
- Yuuji: HEY.
I WAS BEGINNING TO WONDER
IF YOU'D SHOW UP.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I FIGURED YOU'D COME HERE.
- YUUJI...
- WHAT IS IT?
- DO YOU THINK
MY DREAM IS WEIRD?
- SHOUKO, THERE'S SOMETHING
I REALLY NEED TO SAY.
YOU SHOULDN'T FEEL THE WAY
THAT YOU DO ABOUT ME.
IT'S A BIG MISTAKE.
SEVEN YEARS AGO, I WAS STUPID.
AND YOU GOT SUCKED INTO
ALL THAT.
I WAS ONLY EVER TRYING TO TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY, THAT'S ALL.
NOTHING ELSE.
ALL THIS TIME YOU'VE BEEN
WASTING YOUR DREAMS ON ME.
AND I KNOW I'M NOT WORTH IT.
- ( Shouko whimpers )
- BELIEVE ME. I'M REALLY SORRY.
- YUUJI, I...
- LISTEN TO ME. YOUR DREAM
IS NOTHING TO LAUGH AT!
YEAH, YOU MAY HAVE PICKED
THE WRONG GUY,
BUT I THINK CARING ABOUT SOMEONE
FOR SUCH A LONG TIME
IS A WONDERFUL THING.
WHAT YOU WANT IS AMAZING,
AND YOU SHOULD BE PROUD OF IT.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES YOU
SO SPECIAL.
ALTHOUGH, YOU PROBABLY WANT TO
GO WITH THE RIGHT MAN NEXT TIME.
IT MIGHT WORK OUT BETTER.
( chuckles )
WELL, THEN, GUESS IT'S NOT EVERY
DAY YOU ALMOST GET MARRIED.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL HAVE SOME KIND
OF SOUVENIR FROM IT, RIGHT?
- BUT, YUUJI, WAIT.
- OH, YEAH! I ALMOST FORGOT.
THANKS FOR THAT
LUNCH YOU MADE.
IT WAS DELICIOUS.
LET'S GO HOME.
IF IT GETS ANY LATER, PEOPLE
WILL THINK WE'RE TOGETHER.
- YUUJI!
- WHAT NOW?
- I KNEW IT. I KNEW THERE WAS NO
WAY I COULD BE WRONG ABOUT YOU!
- ( theme song playing )
- Fukuhara: QUESTION 8:
WHAT DOES 'COMPUTER' REFER TO
IN THE JAPANESE LANGUAGE?
- Akihisa: SUPER
ELECTRONIC BRAIN!
- THAT SOUNDS PRETTY TOUGH.
- NEXT TIME: LOSS OF CONTROL,
LABYRINTHS,
AND THE AVATAR
INSTRUMENTALITY PROJECT!
- THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.