[SELESTINA] The mock battle with
the Lab in the Capital City
of Kankunen is almost underway.
With Ernesti leading the charge,
the Order of the Silver Phoenix
brought their new mech,
the Tzendolg,
and three Silhouette Knights
equipped with Option Works.
We're here, majesty.
As requested. The Order
of the Silver Phoenix!
Aah! Who does this
little brat think he is?
A horse and rider.
Interesting design.
This might actually
be challenging.
It explains why the
Ambassador recruited us.
I thought fighting a bunch of
kids would be boring as hell,
but this might be fun.
[AMBROSIUS] I'm sure you're
wondering who that young man is.
He is Commander of the
Order of the Silver Phoenix,
and the brains
behind these new units.
May I present the
renowned Ernesti Echevalier.
The child?
Surely that can't be him.
He developed the newest
Silhouette Knight in a century?
The boy must be
a bonified genius!
[MAN 7D]
He looks barely out of diapers.
That's quite enough--
These valiant warriors
didn't travel all this way to
hear the prattling of old men.
Warriors. Prepare for combat!
[OLVER chuckles]
[OLVER] I think his majesty
wants to see the fight
more than anybody.
[SELESTINA]
Despite the uneven numbers,
the match was deemed
fair due to
the Silver Phoenix's
unique designs.
Ernesti's four units
would be pitted against
all six of
the Kaldatoah Darschs.
Strategy would decide
the victor.
So, like in standard practice,
one mounted rider
is worth the same
as three infantry units.
But that's for humans,
not mechs.
And they're all using
enhanced Telestales to boot.
We'll have a major disadvantage.
I can't wait to see what
the Laboratory engineers did
with the Telestale's design!
Oooo! Let's ask them
for a ride later!
Mm-hmm. I shouldn't be surprised
this doesn't faze you,
and yet...
So, uh. How do you
want us to fight these guys?
Should we take three
of them at the same time?
Yeah, about that.
I think I have an idea.
[EMRYS]
Hello, beautiful.
Looks like Fremmevilla's been
up to some amazing things.
I'll have to play catch up.
[BOY 7A]
Prince Emrys!
This whole area's
about to be a warzone!
We should get out of here!
[EMRYS] It's my first day home
and a party's about to start.
You're not going to
make me miss it.
Come on! Don't make me beg.
[PILOT 7A]
Are both sides prepared?
Begin!
Move! Second platoon,
you take the rider.
[ALL PILOTS]
Roger!
Don't be afraid,
it's three against one.
The bigger they are.
We'll handle it the same
as any demon beast.
Activating Magius Jet Thruster.
Deploy from stored position.
Initiate air intake.
Let's go!
[laughing]
[hollers]
That Silhouette Knight is...
Airborne?
Zerxes! He's on you! Watch out!
[ZERXES]
Bad move, kid!
He dodged it! Damn!
[yells]
--[BOY 7A hollers]
--[EMRYS] Did you see that?
Can you believe
Silhouette Knights
are capable of
such crazy speeds!
That's one down!
Now it's an even two on two!
Let's show them
what Tzen can do!
Too quick!
[EDGAR]
Split the unit?
[ERNESTI]
Yes. We can take advantage
of the Tzendolg's speed.
It's the only way.
Of course, they'll split
into two as well.
When they do, I'll strike.
The unit heading for
the Tzendolg will be caught
completely off guard.
You're sure you can do this?
Yes. Of course, that means
you'll be in a three v two.
I know it's not ideal, but we'll
have to make do with this plan.
No need to worry about that.
I gotta shield. The one
and only Edgar from Laihiala!
We couldn't even scratch it!
[DIETRICH]
Heads up!
If you're not careful,
I'll rip you to pieces!
Damn. His power is
on another level.
--[EDRA] What?
--Activate Lightning Flail!
Edra! Drop your shield!
[EDRA] Huh?
[groans]
Not bad!
Guess this won't be
as easy as I thought.
[ALL gasp]
[AMBROSIUS]
So, the Silver Phoenix begins
with field advantage.
But for some reason,
Ernesti's unit
seems to have stopped cold.
Ha! I don't know what kind of
trick that little brat used,
but pulling it off
must have drained
an enormous amount of mana.
[ERNESTI] Well, crap. I was
prepared for this to a degree,
but down to 20%? I might
as well be out of the fight.
I need to let it
rest and recharge.
They'll just have to
make do without me.
It hit! We lost some armor!
Hang in there!
They already adapted
to it's speed.
Truly, they are the best
the Aruvans have to offer.
If you pretend it's a demon
beast, it's easy to handle!
These kids are nothing!
Show them how wrong they are!
[EDGAR grunts] I've never seen
such precise sword play!
[EMRYS] Hmm. Interesting.
The Silver Phoenix may have
more power at their disposal.
But my Darsch is balanced,
and easy to manouver!
[grunts]
The Aruvans are living
up to their reputation!
One wrong move
and it's all over!
Your Silhouette Knight
is wild and untamed.
It takes all your focus
to control it.
Which means, the longer
you're in combat,
the more your own mech
starts to work against you.
[AMBROSIUS] The Laboratory's
machines are steady and firm.
While the Silver Phoenix's
are diamonds in the rough.
It's like watching
a brawl between
a trusted stallion
and a bucking bronco.
Will the tried and true
method yield victory?
Or is the future to
be paved by the reckless?
Addy! Let's go
at these guys head on!
You got it!
[PILOT 7B]
Philia, they're coming!
Let them! I'll hit them
with everything I have left!
[PHILIA]
What?
[yells]
[ZERXES groaning]
Aah! I'm running on empty!
Come on, don't give up
on me now!
Edra! Quickly, while he's
slowing down! Do it!
[EDRA]
Understood!
[DIETRICH grunts]
Well, how rude!
I take one little break
and you forget about me.
[EDRA]
The same trick won't work twice!
Then how about a new one?
You don't stand a chance
when I'm serious!
Is it really moving like that
or am I hallucinating?
Now it's game over!
[ALL gasp]
[hollering]
[thud]
That's enough!
I've seen what I need.
The new units are exemplary.
That was a splendid battle!
Knight Runners,
I salute you all!
[clapping]
[EMRYS]
The boy. What's his name?
I think... it's Ernesti
Echevalier, your highness.
Hm. What an interesting kid.
If you hadn't drained
your mana, I'd be through.
We should use the same mech
so it's an even fight next time.
No. I didn't lose
because of the machine.
I just lack experience.
Humility's a virtue,
but there's nothing wrong
with taking a compliment
from a fellow Knight Runner.
Uh! Thank you very much!
Darn it. Not one kill.
I took out two, so I'm happy.
Yeah, same here.
Yeah! I saw! Good work!
[ADELTRUD giggles]
[GEIST]
Ernesti Echevalier!
[ALL]
Hm?
[GEIST panting]
Aah!
Who's that?
Dunno. Looks like
a Laboratory Knightsmith.
How does that knight-and-rider
model even function?
How do all four legs
work in unison
despite the unit's large frame?
What kind of secret are
you hiding? Answer me!
[ARCHID]
Huh?
[gasps]
Excellent question!
It's quite simple, actually.
I added a second
Ether Reactor to compensate!
Yes! Two reactors would
explain it! Quite clever!
But how did you make
the blue one attain
such incredible speed
and maneuverability?
And the white one!
What was that metallic wire
it shot from its wrist?
I call them
Magius Jet Thrusters!
That's how the Toybox is
capable of such high speeds!
And as for the Lightning Flail,
if you like, I can send
the Silhouette Gear
that was the basic model
to the Lab so you
can play with it!
Ooo! I'd appreciate it!
No, Ernie.
There's no stopping him.
He's on a roll.
Should've known Ernie wasn't
the only mech enthusiast around.
Maybe this is what he'll look
like in the next 80 years.
[OLVER]
It looks like things turned out
just as your majesty had hoped.
[AMBROSIUS] No one
can deny Ernesti's designs
are revolutionary, but they
are far too unpolished.
Unless it is refined,
even the greatest ore
cannot show its true value.
So Ernie is your ore,
and you want the Lab
to do the polishing.
To refine their prototypes.
Make them practical?
I'm counting on you, Olver.
Someday, perhaps soon, we'll be
taking him to the village.
I'll be sure to let them know.
After all, that's why
you keep me around.
That was fun, Chief Geist!
I'll come to your lab someday
so we can talk more!
[GEIST laughing]
Young brats.
Don't count me out.
I still won't let you beat me!
To think there was still
this kind of passion within me.
I thought the fire
had burned out long ago.
[SELESTINA]
Things didn't slow down
after the mock battle had ended.
Two months passed and
the Lab finished polishing
the Kaldatoah Darschs,
giving birth to the Kaletole,
the new mass-production model.
Meanwhile, the Silver Phoenix
developed the Tzendolimble,
a one person version
of the Tzendolg.
Further enhancing
the mech's fighting power.
...then jerk it back
real hard! It's easy!
Sorry, can we take a break?
[birds chirping]
[door creaks]
[EMRYS] Hey, sorry, old timers.
Didn't mean to keep you waitin'.
I was training the Knights
and things got
a little passionate.
Think a couple of them
might have soiled their armor.
Were they slackin' off
while I was away
or am I just that good?
[chuckles]
Woo! That Kaletole, though!
A hell of a toy.
Any chance I could
get one those just for me?
Emrys! Sit down
and shut up, boy.
[LEOTAMUS] I hope they
taught you more than how to
run your mouth in Kuschpercha.
Otherwise, Martina and I will
have a little talk of our own.
Enough. I called you here
for a reason. Let's get to it.
I've been king
of our fair country
for nearly four decades.
I don't know about you,
but that's long enough for me.
I'm leaving the throne to
Leotamus, effective immediately.
Grandpa.
[SELESTINA]
In the Western Year of 1280.
Ambrosius, the Lion King,
gave up his long rule
and bequeathed the throne
of Fremmevilla
to his son, Leotamus.
In the same year,
at Laihiala Academy...
[ERNESTI]
I can't believe we've graduated.
It barely feels like
any time has passed.
I'm just surprised they
didn't kick all of us out!
[BATSON] Yeah, all we did was
cause trouble and skip classes.
[ADELTRUD] They're probably
glad to finally be rid of us.
Thanks, Laihiala Academy.
We'll always be in your debt.
[SELESTINA]
After their graduation,
Ernesti and the Order
of the Silver Phoenix
were relocated to the newly
constructed Fort Orobesius
to continue
their Knightly mission.
[SELESTINA]
But soon afterwards...
Uh? A summon from the capital?
[EMRYS]
Great! You made it!
Guess good things really do
come in small packages.
I suppose they do.
I didn't expect you
to be here. It's an honor.
I heard you were
studying in Kuschpercha.
Is there a reason you're
back in Fremmevilla so soon?
My old man's warming
the throne now.
Seemed like a good reason
to come back home.
Please, time is wasting.
I know you're busy, Ernesti.
But I need a custom
Silhouette Knight made,
and I'd like you
to design it for me.
[ERNESTI]
I'd be happy to, your grace.
But I thought you already
had the Reidis ol Vila.
It's an amazing unit
in it's own right?
Why would you need a new one?
[AMBROSIUS] That is the king's
Silhouette Knight.
He became Leotamus's the moment
he ascended to the throne.
I may be retired,
but with no Silhouette Knight
I can't entertain myself.
And after your remarkable
accomplishments,
I know there is no one
better suited to the task.
N'at case. Make one for me
while you're at it!
--[ERNESTI] Uh?
--[AMBROSIUS] Mmm.
Would it be possible
for you to make two of them?
It won't be a problem.
So, what kind of mechs
would you like them to be?
That's easy.
Everyone knows the most
important trait is power.
[ERNESTI]
Right.
--Then, power.
--[ERNESTI] Okay.
--Followed by power!
--[ERNESTI] I see.
[ADELTRUD]
He's a muscle-head.
Any preference on how it looks?
The sky is the limit!
[EMRYS]
Super-strong, uh, like a lion!
People should think of
Gramps when they see it!
Will that work
for you, your grace?
It should do nicely.
As long as it's not too
unbalanced, do what you like.
[ERNESTI]
Understood!
I promise these new units
won't disappoint.
They will be worthy
of your nobility.
[ADELTRUD]
He's got that look again.
[SELESTINA]
Ernesti returned to Orobesius
filled with excitement,
and immediately began to work
on the royal Silhouette Knights
for Ambrosius and Emrys.
The seasons passed
in the blink of an eye.
The units were completed
and brought to Kankunen.
Oh, wow.
[ERNESTI] I'm proud to present
the Goldleo and Jilbatiga!
As requested, the units
are incredibly powerful
both in offensive
and defensive capabilities.
They should serve you well
and keep you safe.
Both of you are
important to Fremmevilla.
So, only the best will do.
[laughs] They're even better
than I was hoping!
[AMBROSIUS] Hmm. A golden lion
and a silver tiger.
I see. Well, then.
In that case...
[AMBROSIUS, EMRYS]
I'll take... this one!
[BOTH]
Uh...
Come on. You can't handle
a flashy one like this.
You're not exactly
the vision of youth anymore.
I'm aware. I'm equally aware
of your inexperience, boy.
A cub has to earn the right
to be called a lion,
and you haven't done that yet.
That so? Well, there's
no time like the present.
I'll show you everything
I learned in Kushcpercha.
[AMBROSIUS] You intend to
take it with a show of force?
Very well, boy.
I'll put you in your place.
I'm so confused.
They're both muscle-heads.
Shouldn't you be
takin' a nap, old timer?
Better show me
some respect, lad.
You're not too old
for me to spank you!
Part of me wants to stop them,
but I'm kind of afraid to.
[ADELTRUD]
Mm-hmm.
[EMRYS]
Have at you!
[EMRYS grunts]
[AMBROSIUS chuckles]
[ERNESTI] I had no idea he was
so proficient with a spear!
If this is how he is
when he's 60,
I can't imagine what
he was like in his prime.
Honestly, with a name
like "the Lion,"
I think it's pretty clear
what he was like.
[STEPHANIA] I heard the
former king looked just like
Prince Emrys when
he was in his prime.
I've heard he was quite the
force to be reckoned with.
His presence on the
battlefield was always welcome.
He would lead the charge himself
cutting a path of
destruction with his spear.
Once, when our unit
was surrounded,
and it appeared as if
our deaths were certain...
[KNUT] My prince,
I'll open the way through!
At least you will make it out!
[AMBROSIUS laughs]
Don't be foolish!
[gasps]
Everywhere you look
there are enemies!
This is the kind of battle
a Knight Runner dreams of!
[laughing]
Not only did he break through
those demon beasts,
he managed to save us
in the process.
Even those mindless beasts
feared him after that.
They say that a man's
position changes him.
And in his case,
it was for the better.
It must have been
difficult for you.
If that hadn't been
a training weapon,
I'd be eatin' dirt
right about now.
That's my gramps for ya.
S'like charging a brick wall.
[panting]
[chuckles]
Well, I'm not gonna
win this by thinking.
My victory lies here
within my blade!
Such impatience.
You left your feet wide open!
[gasps]
--[EMRYS] You're mine!
--Think again!
[EMRYS]
What?
He used the explosion
from the back weapon
to keep from slamming
into the ground.
Way to use your head, Emrys!
[yells]
Spirit conquers all!
It appears your time
in Kuschpercha
wasn't wasted after all, my boy.
Did you hold back on me?
[AMBROSIUS]
Don't be stupid.
My claws just aren't
as sharp as they used to be.
The golden lion is yours.
Take it!
Considering what I went
through to get this bad boy,
I'll make sure
not to embarrass myself!
Wow, he's fired up, isn't he?
--Tell me, Ernesti.
--Sire?
Despite the difference
in appearances,
the Jilbatiga and Goldleo
are on equal footing, yes?
Yes, sir! In every way.
It didn't make sense to build
one stronger than the other.
Very good.
[EMRYS] I'll make
you proud, Gramps! Ha-ha!
[ERNESTI] Hold on.
This was his plan all along!
Whether he won or lost,
the prince would
still be better off!
[QUITTERIE]
One who would disrupt
the journey has appeared.
A whispering evil
lies upon the forest.
[MESSENGER 7A]
Understood.
I shall send
a rider immediately.
[ERNESTI]
Next time: "Secret &amp; Quest"!
The world's mysteries call me!