[SELESTINA] After a successful
trial of the Telestale's
new armaments, Ernesti
discovered a flaw in his design.
The unit's mana drained rapidly.
Unless he could fix this,
the design would not
be suited for actual combat.
It's like we thought.
New output killed it.
Fuel efficiency's nonexistent.
Figures. Unfortunately,
we can't make any changes
to the Ether Reactor.
That would fix everything.
Couldn't we just increase
the mana storage capacity?
Sure, but we'd have to
install extra Crystal Tissue
to compensate for it.
But, more tissue
means more mana usage.
We'd be back where we started.
How can we break the cycle?
No problem! This sort of thing
is Ernie's specialty!
--It is?
--Yeah, silly!
You're the one who
kept saying the new Knights
don't have to look human.
So, you don't have to stick
to human muscles! Right?
Yeah! I didn't think of that!
If our goal is mana capacity,
then the Knight's form
doesn't really matter.
Of course,
it's kinda embarrassing
you came up with it.
Hey! What's that mean?
[bird chirping]
Gently. Almost.
Good! Stop there!
[ARCHID] Whoa. What are you
adding to our gears?
They look pretty intense.
It would be easier
to show than tell.
[BOTH]
Uh?
Kid. Addy. Ready when you are.
[ARCHID]
All set.
Let the test begin!
First, we'll try
the wire anchor!
[ADELTRUD, ARCHID laughing]
[ERNESTI grunts]
[ADELTRUD gasps]
I'd call that a
successful field test.
Agreed! Let's move on!
This is a new ranged weapon
made with the Strand-Type
Crystal Tissue.
We're calling it the Scorpius.
It would be faster for
you to use it than for me
to explain how it works,
so just give it a whirl.
'Kay. Like this?
Here goes. Ah!
--Yes!
--Crazy!
Uh. Are you sure it's okay
to fire this thing in town?
Yeah! Now, fire multiple shots!
Multiple?
[ARCHID]
Uuh...
[ERNESTI] It's an
automatic-fire siege weapon!
It works better than I thought!
Ernie, what's the point
of having something like this?
--Huh?
--[ADELTRUD] Seriously.
Why make grapplers
and siege weapons
unless you're going to use them?
[ERNESTI]
Mmm.
Honestly, I hadn't
thought of that.
I just wanted to
challenge myself
and see if I could pull it off!
For a genius,
you're kind of an idiot.
[SELESTINA] Meanwhile,
the plan to increase
the amount of Crystal Tissue
had run into some problems.
[ADELTRUD] It looks so dumb!
It's all bulky now!
It's almost too heavy to move.
Back to the drawing board.
Maybe some kind of
external pack would work?
It's totally different
than before! There's no balance!
This selfish machine's
gonna give me gray hairs.
[TEACHER 1B] The Aubigne
Mountains range so far,
they effectively split the
continent of Zetterlund in two.
To the west of the mountains
lies the western kingdoms,
the so-called Occident.
And, of course,
our fair kingdom of Fremmevilla
encompasses the eastern half.
We're connected to
the Great Bocuse Forest,
where the demon
beasts originate.
[ERNESTI] It's frustrating.
I'll have to consider
the Telestale complete, for now.
But, I already know
what my next step will be.
I wanted to speak to you
about this new unit, Ernesti.
When you started this project,
I expected little more than
an improvement to the basic
Salodreah model, but this!
You've made something completely
different, haven't you?
Yup! There's never been
a Silhouette Knight like it.
I see. Should I
inform his majesty
that you're ready
to present the unit?
No. Not yet. He asked for
the best I had to offer.
We still have a long way
to go before it's ready.
If he wasn't so impressive, this
kid'd be downright terrifying.
The Telestale is a foundation.
One that I intend to build
a marvelous castle on top of.
That's what it's going to take
if I truly want
to shock the king.
Very well. But keep the
"shock" to a minimum.
My heart can't take it.
Now, then.
It may not be finished,
but I should turn in
some form of report.
The king doesn't need
to be bothered with it.
Submit a report
to the Lab instead.
You mean the Silhouette
Knight Lab, right?
Filling them in now would help
streamline the overall process.
Great idea, boss!
[LAURI]
Hmm.
[SELESTINA] Lauri was concerned
about the effect the new unit
would have on the laboratory.
Developing Silhouette
Knights had always
been a major government project.
How would they respond
when they learned
a single Knight Runner
student had done it?
Their reaction
may not be favorable.
Only time would tell.
What do we do?
About what?
[ADELTRUD]
Our promise with Dad, stupid!
Isn't now the right time?
Oh. Right, we said we'd tell him
whenever Ernie made progress.
We might as well.
If we don't, he'll find out
from the laboratory.
It's better if we
get to tell him ourselves.
Good point!
We can't have any of them
taking credit
for Ernie's hard work!
[JOACHIM] Make sure this
gets to Marquis Dixgard.
[MESSENGER 4A]
Of course, sir.
I understand.
I'll have all the students
involved with the project
gathered at once.
We gettin' a reward
or somethin'?
[ENGINEER 4B] Somehow,
I doubt they're that generous.
As you may have guessed,
you've been summoned here
because of your involvement
with the new Silhouette Knight.
We, too, are Knights.
The Order of the Scarlet Rabbit,
sent by Marquis Dixgard.
I am the commander,
Sir Morten Fredholm.
This feels off.
[MORTEN] Do not be alarmed.
The Marquis has taken
an interest in your project and
wishes to see it for himself.
We'd like you to send all these
new units to Fort Casadesus
along with sufficient
personnel to operate them.
The Marquis' time
is extremely valuable.
With that in mind,
we'll be leaving immediately.
'Scuse me, sir? This is
obviously terrible weather
to be operating
Silhouette Knights in.
Can't we wait it out?
Afraid not.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
Shut up! Do you
want to jinx them?
--Think before you talk, stupid!
--'Kay! I got it!
[SELESTINA] Unfortunately, Kid's
feeling turned out to be right.
[PILOT 4A]
Shaker worms!
[DIETRICH]
Why'd it have to be worms?
[HELVI] I've never
seen a shaker that big!
Sounds like the perfect test,
don't you agree?
Stop being so damn calm!
It's freaking me out!
These demon beasts
like to lurk underground.
They can be very
difficult to deal with,
but if you keep calm
and listen close,
you can predict
where they'll go.
Glad you could join us!
[MORTEN yells]
Edgar! I'll let you
take care of the big one!
Helvi! Dietrich!
Switch to quad-link mode!
[DIETRICH, HELVI]
Roger!
Burn it up!
They're actually
pushing it back!
[MORTEN]
Now! Charge!
[HELVI yells]
[giggles]
[GUY 4A grunts]
Good. I'm glad they survived.
If the new unit's
so weak that a shaker worm
can take it down, then we've
wasted our time here.
It works. And if it's
as powerful as it seems,
we can't let those
Scarlet Bunnies keep it.
I agree, but still, it's said
that even a single ant
couldn't find a way
into Fort Casadesus.
Once they're safely
within the walls,
even our Order of
the Bronze Fang
won't be able to get to them.
[KERHILD] Idiot.
Leave it to a man to think
force is the only
viable solution.
If you use your brain
for once, you'd see.
We already have the answer.
[ADELTRUD sighs]
I could really use
a dose of Ernie in my life.
I haven't seen or hugged him
for a week straight!
Do you know if our father
passed on the message, Kid?
--Eh?
--You know!
Why is that Marquis
coming to see the new unit
instead of his majesty?
How am I supposed
to know? Jeez.
This whole thing
was your idea, Archid!
I'm not the one who wrote,
"it's the single
greatest thing ever," am I?
[ADELTRUD]
Shut up! I had writer's block!
[BATSON]
They're back!
They're coming this way!
--[laughing, hollers]
--Finally!
[ENGINEERS chatter]
[DAVID] All right,
don't get too excited.
If every tool in
that shop isn't pristine,
there's gonna be hell to pay.
--[ARCHID] Boss!
--[DAVID] Uh!
--Welcome back!
--Where's Ernie?
[DAVID]
Yeah. You wanna take this one?
Did something happen?
Where's Ernie?
He and the Telestale
will be staying at
the Fort for the time being.
[BOTH]
Uuuuh!
[KNUT] You saw
the new design in action.
What was your impression of it?
[MORTEN] In terms of speed,
output, and firepower,
I'd say it's vastly superior
to the Kaldatoahs.
I have no choice but
to give it high marks.
[sighs] "It's the single
greatest thing ever," huh? Eh.
--[MORTEN] Sir?
--Never mind.
It seems these new units
will be a great benefit to us.
We will treat them the same way
as their predecessors.
Sir.
[KNUT]
The Silhouette Knights represent
our kingdom's
greatest accomplishment.
It took nearly 300 years
for the original
Salodreah to be replaced,
and the current Kaldatoah's have
been in service for generations.
Compared to that, this
arrogant child's "hobby"
makes creating a Silhouette
Knight look like child's play.
[MORTEN] His majesty would be
excited over the boy's success.
--That's a problem.
--[MORTEN] Hm?
That boy. He's up to something,
and I will find out what it is,
no matter what.
[grunts]
Father, we need to talk.
[JOACHIM]
Stephania? Why are you here?
Would you mind clearing
the room for a moment?
There's an urgent matter
I need to discuss with you.
An urgent matter?
Wait. How'd you
get here from Laihiala?
I need to talk to you alone.
Very well.
[JOACHIM]
All right. What's this about?
You owe me an explanation.
Not until I get
a straight answer.
Father, what'd you
tell the Marquis?
[KNUT] Ernesti Echevalier.
You've been busy as of late.
It's a pleasure
to see you again, sir.
What can I do for you?
[KNUT]
You can go over the new unit.
And you won't
leave anything out.
[thunder cracking]
[chalk tapping]
[ERNESTI]
Okay. So, as you can see,
by replacing the old
Crystal Tissue with the refined
Strand-Type Crystal Tissue
and re-fitting
the Telestale with it,
we achieved nearly two times
the output of existing units.
Please refer to the paper
I gave you for the next part.
As I said before, the biggest
flaw in the Telestale's design
is it's running time,
apart from that.
I can refine it a bit more.
Especially in terms
of production cost.
We can expect
improvement in regard
to those two points
in the future.
--Now!
--[gasps]
[ERNESTI]
The most important part of all.
The Ether Reactor must still
use existing technology.
That's the biggest roadblock.
It makes it hard to
improve anything further.
I hope you can understand
my dilemma here.
Anyway, that's all there is
to tell about the new unit
and its future
development plans.
I hope it met your expectations.
Yes.
Do you have any
further questions, sir?
Of course. Plenty.
[ERNESTI]
Go ahead.
As you know, I've been given
full authority here.
That means over you
and the unit's development.
In other words, the project
is no longer yours.
Any evaluations
and decisions are mine
to make from here on out.
The explanation you just
gave me will be the one
I give to his majesty, verbatim.
Do you have
any problem with that?
--Not at all!
--Excuse me?
[ERNESTI] That means I won't
have to give his majesty
the same explanation
myself, right?
I'll leave it
in your capable hands.
[gasps]
Of course,
if you have new questions,
I'll happily answer them!
[giggles]
[KNUT] Uh. You're saying...
y-you're okay with that?
Okay with what?
I'm confused, sir.
Honor! Wealth! Status!
Your future! All of it!
[ERNESTI]
I don't understand.
What're you playing at?
Just what do you intend
to do after this?
[ERNESTI] Well, I'm still
only a first-year student
at the Knight Runner
middle school, sir.
I suppose I'll focus
on graduating--
[KNUT] Stop lying to me,
you irreverent brat!
This is a serious matter!
Don't you understand
what you've done?
I, uh, developed
a new Silhouette Knight?
Don't make it sound so simple!
Feels silly to explain this,
but I'll do it anyway.
Listen! Ever since the
founding of our kingdom--
no, since the dawn
of written history itself.
No Silhouette Knight has ever
been designed by one person.
Such a feat was deemed
to be impossible! Look!
The development of a Silhouette
Knight is a major endeavor!
For over half a millennium
they were only achieved
through time and the hard work
of countless personnel.
But you. You go and
make it look easy!
Then you have
the unmitigated gall
to request access
to the Ether Reactor,
our kingdom's most vital secret!
Why are you even pretending
to be a normal child?
Well, if it helps, the Telestale
isn't the final unit
I was going to show the king.
[KNUT] It wasn't? You're telling
me you're not finished yet?
Of course not!
I was challenged!
The king wanted to see
the best machine I can make,
and I'm gonna give it to him!
[gasps]
[sighs]
"The single
greatest thing ever?"
[ERNESTI]
Yeah!
[rumbling]
--[AMBROSIUS laughing]
--[KNUT coughing]
[AMBROSIUS]
What do you think of that, Knut?
The Crystal Tissue could
only support a maximum
of ten weights before, but now
we've taken it up to eleven!
Well, the future
is bright, indeed!
[KNUT] Don't tell me you
intend to continue this folly?
Of course, I do!
How will we ever improve
unless we fail first?
[laughing]
I don't get it. Why?
Why do all this?
What is the point?
Because it's my hobby, sir!
[KNUT gasps, exhales]
I see. Very well, young man.
I'm satisfied.
[STEPHANIA] In other words,
you thought it'd be best
for Ernie to meet
the Marquis himself?
More or less, yes.
That's great! We don't need
to worry after all.
Why's that?
'Cuz. It's Ernie
we're talking about.
[ADELTRUD]
Oh.
Truthfully. I'd be more
worried for the poor Marquis.
[JOACHIM]
No. If I were you three,
I'd be worried about
myself right now.
[ADELTRUD]
Uh?
I know for a fact
that school wasn't cancelled.
You'll make up for it.
[ALL chuckle nervously]
Let's hear what you have
to say for yourselves.
I just realized something!
If I'm to entrust everything
to you, it might be best
to tell you all of
my future plans for the unit.
Have a look at this.
You mean there's more?
What are you talking about?
This book represents
my life's work!
I believe everything
it contains makes me worthy
of learning the secret behind
Fremmevilla's Ether Reactor.
Now. Relax, this might
take us a while.
[KNUT gasps]
Maybe if I tried loose--
[ADELTRUD]
He's so late!
Aaah! Doesn't he care about
what this does to me?
I can't go on like this!
I need him here now!
You don't think
he likes Casadesus
more than Laihiala, do you?
--[EDGAR sighs]
--[DIETRICH chuckles]
I'd stay there, too.
'Specially if there were no
whiney brats to put up with.
Oh, yeah?
I can be mean, too! Mop head!
Mop head?
He is late. If Ernesti
was only supposed to explain
the Telestale to the Marquis,
he should have been back sooner.
You see? I was right!
I'm gonna go talk to him!
And if he won't
come back with me,
I'll drag him
out of there by force!
You realize how long it'll
take to get there on foot?
Not to mention the demon beasts.
That's what a
Silhouette Gear is for!
It can run faster than a horse,
and it's got weapons to boot!
I'm goin' with you, sis!
--[EDGAR] You can't do that.
--Huh?
Think about this.
Ernesti is there
at the official invitation
of Marquis Dixgard.
You'd need a pretty good reason
to pull him out of there.
Got one?
[HELVI]
Pot, meet kettle.
You've been whining about
losing the Telestale
ever since they
took it out of the shop.
We know the Earlcumber's
special to you.
But I've seen the way
you look at the new ones.
Even if I liked them,
it doesn't matter.
The school's duty and
my individual feelings
are separate.
We have more than
the Earlcumber.
The other one's still got
a few overhauls, too.
Other one? You mean Guair?
[DAVID] It's already
equipped with sub-arms
and the new Strand-Type
Crystal Tissue.
It's practically a new unit.
Once the overhaul's done,
it won't be stayin' here.
All new units go to
the Marquis, after all.
We'll have to send it
to Fort Casadesus.
Is that a fact? Interesting.
[DAVID]
It'll need an escort.
And since those
Scarlet Rabbit chumps
aren't here to do the job,
we'll just do it ourselves.
[BOTH chuckle]
You won't get
objections from me.
I was itching for another
field trip, anyway.
Heh!
Thanks, boss! You're the best!
Uh, sure!
[SELESTINA] Several days
later near the Fort,
a tragedy befell
the small village of Darie.
[MONSTERS growling]
[roars]
[WOMAN gasping]
[LOOKOUT 4A] Distress
signal from Darie Village!
Multiple duel-class
demon beasts on site!
[bell ringing]
[KERHILD]
They're way too predictable.
Proof that peace
breeds weakness.
The fools don't suspect a thing.
Get ready to move out!
It's been awhile
since we've had a war.
Let's make it
a good one, shall we?
[SELESTINA] A demon beast
attack of this scale
was common in Fremmevilla.
Ernesti and the others
were oblivious
to real danger
outside their walls.
But soon, he would be
part of an event
that would shake
the world to its core.
[ERNESTI]
Next time: "Hide &amp; Seek"!
An evil shadow is calling me!