[ERNESTI gasps]
No, come back!
I haven't built any of you yet!
You can't leave me like this!
Please, robot!
Don't go, I'm begging you!
[ADELTRUD sighs]
How can someone be so huggable?
This is becoming a habit.
Every time I doze off, Addy
grabs me then passes out, too.
I'm not her personal teddy bear.
[ADELTRUD]
Cuddle wuddle.
Addy, time to wake up.
I can't move with you on me.
But you're just so warm, Ernie.
It makes me happy.
[ERNESTI]
Mmm.
[ADELTRUD laughing]
Okay! I'm up!
Stop! You're so mean, Ernie!
That's not what you said
a second ago.
Rise and shine.
We're almost home.
[SELESTINA] After the Casadesus
Incident came to a conclusion,
Ernesti and the others
returned to Laihiala.
Meanwhile,
the Telestale was sent
to the nation's
greatest research lab.
The renowned
Silhouette Knight Laboratory.
[GAIZKA]
What's the hold up?
A pre-pubescent child
designed this pile of scrap!
How long could it
take you to analyze?
With all due respect, sir,
this Strand-Type Crystal Tissue
and back-arm technology
are unlike anything
we've seen before.
The script work alone
will take us some time.
Not to mention the work
he did on the Magius Engine.
Don't look so damn impressed!
Where's your pride
as a lab member?
[OLVER]
Chief.
Yelling won't get
the work done any faster.
How wonderful! If it
isn't director Olver!
What brings you to our
humble corner of the lab?
Last I heard, you sat
in your chair so long
you sprouted roots!
I had to see the new
unit for myself.
Innovations are something
of a rarity around here.
I'm quite eager to read
your analysis of the unit.
When should I expect it?
When it's ready and
not a moment before.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I am
far too busy for this nonsense.
As I feared. This lab has been
stuck in a rut for so long
this project may have been
too much for us.
His majesty won't
be happy about this.
Unless, he intended for this
to shake us up a bit.
[GAIZKA] Stupid brat!
Sucking up to the king
doesn't make you
cock of the walk!
[grunting]
Enjoy this while you can.
Once I've figured out
how to use your unit
to create a new
mass-produced model,
your part in Silhouette Knight
history will just be a footnote!
[laughing, coughing]
[AMBROSIUS] I see.
So, he's back at Laihiala.
Yes.
I know you have
your reservations,
but we need their power.
I don't need to tell you
how complicated
things have gotten around here.
Yes.
[AMBROSIUS] Those damn raiders
didn't help matters.
[KNUT]
I've been thinking about that.
I believe someone from the
Occident may have sent them.
[AMBROSIUS]
Mmm.
[SELESTINA] The Occident is the
name given to the countries
west of Fremmevilla.
Which lie beyond the border
of the Aubigne Mountains.
The very thought is enraging--
The only reason why
they have peace is due to
our constant efforts
to fight off the demon beasts.
The attack on Casadesus
must have been ordered
by someone who's
forgotten that fact.
Whoever is behind this
treachery, we must respond.
As of now, I'm putting you
in charge of the Azure Hawk.
Consider it a chance to atone
for your failure at the Fort.
Yes. I will, sire.
Now then, I can't wait
to see what young Echevalier
has in store for us next.
The future's looking
bright indeed.
As you say, sire.
[ALL]
You're a Knight Commander?
Yup! It was just made official.
I'm in charge of the
Order of the Silver Phoenix.
But don't worry, I'll continue
my studies through graduation,
like all the other students.
That wasn't my concern!
His majesty should be
sending an official notice
with all of the details soon.
Until then, you should know that
the Academy of Knight Runners
and its facilities will serve
as our base of operations.
Ah! That's wonderful!
Right?
So, it's finally happened.
I always said you would
take over the school
but for it to happen so soon...
[DAVID] I wasn't really thinkin'
about it when I agreed, but...
...we're a Knightly Order!
How 'bout that?
Consider yourself lucky, boss.
At least you got
to be there. Not me.
I was stuck in the infirmary
with a concussion and bedpan.
He was worrying
himself sick, too.
I think he was afraid
we wouldn't let him join.
That's not true! Take it back!
Things have gone
from interesting
to insane around here.
With Ernie in charge, this is
gonna be one hell of a ride.
[distant clanking]
Good, you're all
already here! Perfect timing!
How's Batson piloting a gear?
Ernie! Did you do
somethin' weird?
Not at all! Care to tell them
what makes this design special?
It's got a miniaturized
Magius Engine inside it!
[chuckles]
Even someone like me can use it.
But that's high-grade
military tech!
Where the hell'd you
get your hands on it?
From the government!
I asked for it,
and they gave it to me!
Gave it to you?
Hold on. I thought
the engine was secret.
Well, not as much
as Ether Reactors.
But, yeah, they're not
something you can just ask for.
Guess the rules
don't apply to Ernie.
Batson's not the only one
who can use the new design.
Every one of the
Knightsmiths should be able
to operate them
with minimal practice.
You don't say.
We could get twice the work
done with those babies.
[ARCHID]
Hey! Ernie!
Big news! Really big!
--What the--?
--Well, I'll be.
[DIETRICH] This day
just keeps getting better.
Two companies of Kaldatoahs.
The Marquis apologizes
for the delay.
It's no problem!
Your work is impressive.
I might even let you
tune-up the Haimerwort.
If that happens,
you won't be disappointed.
So, there's definitely no
backing out of this now,
is there?
It's tough,
but it'll be worth it!
I wish you could see your face.
I've never seen you so happy!
Yeah!
Everyone. The time has come
to hit them where it hurts!
Hit who where?
I'll get to that. The Order
of the Silver Phoenix
may be new,
but we've been fulfilling
our knightly duty
for some time now.
The development of
a new unit, right?
Yes. His majesty has
given us the greater goal
of making the best machine
we possibly can.
But that's not all he's done.
He's issued a challenge
for our Order,
and I think you'll all
be excited about it.
In ten months, we'll have
a mock battle with a unit
developed by
the Silhouette Knight Lab.
--Wha--?
--[HELVI] Whoa.
Wait, you mean the Lab?
--We're gonna cream those guys!
--This will be great!
We'll show 'em what
a real mech is made of!
I'm glad to hear it!
Now, let's make a
Silhouette Knight so amazing
it'll blow the roof off
the Laboratory!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Building on
everything we learned
from the Casadesus Incident,
I want to make a mech that has
superior speed and mobility.
Makes sense.
It would help a lot.
Right. And this is what
will help us achieve it.
Um...
What the--?
What am I lookin' at?
[BOTH]
Doesn't it look like...?
[ERNESTI]
Mm-hmm!
Great! Put it
over there, will ya?
[DIETRICH]
We're only making one new unit?
[ERNESTI] We have a lot
of work to do in ten months.
But don't worry.
I'm preparing Option Works
so it can adapt
during the mock battle.
What are Option Works?
Equipment that will
allow us to use new tactics!
Take the Flexible Coat
for example.
Instead of holding a rod
like the back weapon sub-arm,
this sub-arm will hold
a protective shield instead.
The possibilities are limitless!
Let's take it one
at a time. Okay?
Okay.
You might finally make
your dream come true, Ernie.
That's what I'm hoping.
[ERNESTI]
I only get glimpses of it.
But there's a robot made just
for me somewhere in my head.
The new unit
and the Option Works
are all vital stepping stones
towards finding it.
I can't reach it in my dreams.
But when I'm awake,
these hands can make
all of my dreams a reality.
[SELESTINA]
With the new Silhouette Gear,
the Knightsmith's
could complete their work
with superior speed
and efficiency.
Of course, it didn't hinder
the time-honored practice
of slacking off.
--[BOTH gasp]
--[ERNESTI giggles]
[SELESTINA]
The months flew by.
[STUDENTS chattering]
I'm afraid this may be
the last time I get to enjoy
your softness and warmth Ernie.
Gee. That's a real shame.
I'll come visit
every chance I get!
Don't go changing on me!
[screams]
Okay, that's enough!
[sighs]
[SELESTINA] Graduation came
and went at Laihiala Academy.
As new Knight Runners left,
a fresh batch
of students arrived.
[DAVID]
All right, newbies!
I expect you to work those nubs
you call fingers to the bone!
You slack, you die!
[RECRUITS whimpering]
Okay, boss. You've had
your fun, now back down.
Welcome to
Laihiala Academy, students.
By the order of his majesty,
all the facilities
belong to the Order
of the Silver Phoenix.
Remember that.
You are students,
but you are also
apprentices to our order,
and we expect you
to behave accordingly.
Now, I'll introduce you
to our commander.
Say hi to Ernesti Echevalier.
It's a pleasure to have you.
--Is this a joke?
--Commander? A child?
--He's tiny!
--[GIRL 6A] I think it's a girl.
You're no student. Who are you?
[NORA]
Nora Frykberg, sir.
On paper, I'm just
another student,
but in reality, I'm an agent
of the Azure Hawk.
[ERNESTI] Have there been any
developments in the case?
I've had all of
the suspicious people
in the school dealt with.
[NORA] I've also deployed
personal all around Laihiala,
and put up a barrier.
Rest assured, information
leaks won't happen again.
But we still don't know
where the Telestale is
or who was behind its theft.
We lost track of the attackers
at the Aubigne Mountains.
So, you think it's the work
of another country, is that it?
Yes.
Excellent work, Nora.
Thank you for the report.
Since espionage
is your specialty,
I'll leave the
investigation to you.
Understood, Knight Commander.
[STUDENTS chattering]
She was with Ernie
for an awfully long time.
And I'm sure the conversation
turned more than "friendly."
I don't like this.
If that's the kinda girl
that Ernie is into,
then how do I compete with that?
Ernie!
Uh, hey, Addy. What's wrong?
I want to pilot
a Silhouette Knight, too!
[gasps]
That's great!
And your timing is perfect!
Really?
But before we start,
there's something else
I'd like you
to help me with, first.
[chuckles]
[BATSON]
Okay, it's all secured!
[ERNESTI]
Roger! Thank you!
Aren't you afraid
they'll get mad at us?
We didn't ask if we could
use this Kaldatoah.
It's for new tech.
They'll understand.
You ready? Observe and
take measurements!
[ADELTRUD]
You got it!
Okay, let's fire it up!
[gasps]
[boom]
--[PILOTS scream]
--What the hell?
Ow, my everything!
I don't think that was
supposed to happen.
No kidding.
[running footsteps]
[ADELTRUD]
Ernie!
[BOTH]
--[ARCHID] You okay?
--[ADELTRUD] Answer us! Please!
[ADELTRUD]
Ernie! Wake up!
[gasps]
Oh, good!
You're still with us.
Looks like you came out
of it without a scratch.
It's a miracle you were
only knocked out
after that much force.
That isn't what happened!
The mech came
grinding to a halt.
The thrusters completely
drained the mana pool
almost instantaneously.
Maybe if I--
[BATSON]
Ernie! Calm down, okay?
I'm fine! It's just that--
[grunts]
This equipment won't work.
It's not out of
the question yet,
but it will need some
serious re-designs.
Ernie.
But that'll take months!
Would you think about
what just happened?
[gasps]
'Kay.
[BATSON] I really think
it's too dangerous to build.
Why don't we work on
something else?
[ERNESTI]
Why? This wasn't a total loss.
We know how much power
it's capable of.
I'm done thinking
about what happened.
I see the issues.
So, let's make some
improvements and try this again.
We'll re-examine
the overall scale
and output power of the spells.
Then, make a control system
we can adjust on the fly.
We can deal with the mana issues
by altering the machine then--
S'cuse me. Aren't you
forgetting something?
David is not going
to be happy about this.
[DAVID]
Idiots! What were you thinking?
--[ADELTRUD chuckles nervously]
--I told you.
You demolished
a brand new Kaldatoah
and nearly got yourselves
killed doing it!
I hope this taught you a lesson.
Mm-hmm. As a matter of fact,
we learned a lot from this!
I've already come up
with some improvements
we could implement easily--
Then you didn't learn
your lesson very well, Ernie!
You're done here
until you do! Got that?
Yes.
Wow. Ernie's so adorable
when he gets sad.
[sighs]
You sure you wanna
give the kid some time off?
Good point, he might get bored.
Who knows what he'd do.
All right everybody!
Let's get back to work!
Let's start on
the new unit then.
For this we'll need
two Knight Runners,
and I'd like
Kid and Addy to pilot.
[BOTH]
Uh?
[grunts]
[DIETRICH] So, this new mech
will be a two-seater?
When were you
planning to tell us?
--I just did.
--Cute.
[ERNESTI] This mech
is unlike any before it.
That includes everything from
the chassis to the controls.
[ERNESTI]
It will be complicated to pilot,
so splitting the task
between two people is ideal.
But it will require
Knight Runners who can
work together
in perfect harmony.
[HELVI] That's why
you chose Kid and Addy?
[ERNESTI]
Yup!
Steady! Steady! Okay!
[DIETRICH] You're putting in
two Ether Reactors?
[ARCHID] This thing's
going to be a real monster!
[ADELTRUD grunts, screams]
--Addy!
--You okay?
[ERNESTI]
Say something! Addy!
[ADELTRUD groans]
[ENGINEER 6A]
The armor's in pieces.
[ENGINEER 6B] Well, it wasn't
fully attached yet.
I'm sorry. I goofed up.
You have nothing
to be sorry for, Addy.
Don't get so down.
It's okay. Really.
The size of the machine
and the mana it burns
are on a different
level entirely.
So basically, it's a giant mess.
[HELVI]
What is this?
The poor girl is covered in soot
and you're all
just standing around.
Let's get you clean.
[ADELTRUD]
Uh. Uh?
Yeah, I needed that.
But I feel bad being out here
while the others are working.
Well, stop it.
We're Knight Runners--
they don't need us
for the grunt work.
So, relax, and let
the sweat wash away.
Oh. I should've invited Ernie.
It would be perfect!
Hold on. You're way too young
to be bathing with a guy!
Oh, please, you don't
think I know that?
Of course I wouldn't,
but Ernie isn't a guy!
Ernie is just Ernie!
Ooh. I see.
Why are we
cleaning up this mess?
Even Knights do the grunt work.
[ERNESTI]
Edgar.
There's something
I'd like you to see.
For you.
'Kay, what's it for?
You can use it as a weapon,
but it's for your mech.
I had a special Emblem Graph
imprinted onto
the dagger's blade.
It matches the Emblem Graph
on the depression
inside the slot.
How clever!
It's a key for the unit.
Right! I'm hoping
it'll help prevent thefts.
Without the dagger,
no one can pilot this mech.
That's wonderful! I think
that the Casadesus Incident
will be the last of its kind.
Yup!
♪
[SELESTINA] And so,
the Order of the Silver Phoenix
and Silhouette Knight Laboratory
completed their mechs.
[GAIZKA chuckles]
[SELESTINA] Only three days
remained until the mock battle.
The excitement was palpable.
Well, I've gotta
hand it to you, silver.
It's a work of art.
Yeah.
Thanks for everything.
Now, let's show the Lab
what we're made of!
The king wanted the best,
then that's exactly
what we'll give him!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[horns play]
[laughing]
[MAN 6A gasps] What a
powerful frame and stride.
They practically
radiate strength!
Ah. So, they summoned
the Aruvans
for this little demonstration.
Only the finest
Knight Runners would do.
Anything less would be
an insult to the king.
And speaking of the finest,
I am proud to introduce
the next-generation
mass production unit.
Created by the
Silhouette Knight Laboratory
to lead our fair
Kingdom of Fremmevilla
into a bright
and glorious future!
Though they are
based on the Telestale,
I have personally improved them
in almost every aspect!
They may look like
the Kaldatoah,
but our Darsch is
a completely new machine!
We've decreased the amount
of Strand-Type Crystal Tissue
as compared to the Telestale,
so the power output
compared to
the original model is...
[clears throat]
...only a humble 30% greater.
--Thirty?
--That's incredible!
[GAIZKA chuckles]
However,
we've also added
an additional Capacity Blame
which not only serves
to improve the units defense,
but also solves the rapid drain
on the mana pool!
We've even added two
Silhouette Arms to the back
of the frame to hold the rod!
As a result,
the weapon is more mobile,
easier to control,
and therefore more effective
at crushing any
and all opposition,
making this
the greatest creation
our lab has ever produced!
Splendid work. I've come
to expect great things
from the Laboratory,
and you haven't disappointed.
Your reputation as the finest
Knightsmith in the country
is well-deserved, Master Geist.
You honor me, your majesty.
And now, lords and ladies.
You've come to see
the Darsch in action,
and what better way
to test a Silhouette Knight
than with a worthy opponent?
I'm sure by now
you've all heard of the one
who made the Silhouette Knight
the Darsch is based on.
The group who, by my command,
have formed
a new knightly order.
Enter Order of
the Silver Phoenix!
Those footsteps
are awfully bizarre.
[GAIZKA]
Uh?
[hollers]
Is that a Silhouette Knight
or some twisted joke?
Uh...
An interesting design choice.
This new commander breaks the
rules even more than I'd heard.
[AMBROSIUS chuckles]
[BOTH chuckle]
[ERNESTI] We are honored
to be here, your majesty.
Thank you.
This is our latest
prototype, the Tzendolg.
As well as two Telestale
derivatives equipped with
our new Option Works
and the Guair custom!
As commanded,
the Silver Phoenix has arrived!
[ERNESTI]
Next time: "New &amp; Old"!
They're telling me
to burn bright!