[LAURI]
Greetings, majesty.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is my grandchild,
Ernesti Echevalier.
It's an honor to meet you, sire.
[AMBROSIUS] The reports said
the child was a boy.
[ERNESTI] It's true.
I can prove it, if required.
Fearless and straightforward,
despite his appearance.
He is Lauri's.
Thank you for inviting us,
your majesty.
I'm impressed. He's quite
composed for someone his age.
I wish more children
showed such respect.
I'm honored by
your praise. Majesty.
I'm sure, by now,
you've wondered why
I summoned you here, Ernesti.
Your victory the other day was
"unexpected" to say the least,
and presented
quite the conundrum.
I'm unsure how
to reward you for it.
Thank you. But Ernesti
doesn't require a reward.
He's still a child.
[AMBROSIUS]
Child or no,
I cannot fail to
compensate someone
who defeats a behemoth
single-handedly.
What is it you desire?
Name it and it shall be yours.
Anything?
[ERNESTI] Calm down. He can't be
asking me this out of goodwill.
There's a motive.
I should assume this is
some sort of test on his part.
Should I just say
I don't need anything?
Or throw caution to the wind?
And if I choose the latter,
what do I ask for?
The latest model
of Silhouette Knight?
No. No, this is
the chance of a lifetime!
I should ask for something
impossible to obtain.
Something I'll never have
another chance to get!
[ERNESTI] In that case,
I ask for this, sire.
I want knowledge.
Knowledge that can't be found
in any books. Only you
can grant this to me, sire.
I want to know how
to make an Ether Reactor.
The heart of a Knight!
--[gasps]
--[KNUT] Uh!
You ingrate! How dare you
take advantage
of the King's generosity?!
That is one of our country's
greatest treasures!
A secret kept for generat--
Dixgard. That's quite enough.
You are correct,
young Echevalier.
I am the only one who can
grant you such knowledge.
But, I must ask,
what will you do
once you've learned the
mysteries of the Knight's heart?
[ERNESTI]
Okay, this is it!
[ERNESTI] As I'm sure
you're aware, majesty,
I'm currently learning
to be a Knight Runner
at Laihiala Academy,
but my ultimate goal is,
and has always been, to acquire
my own unique Silhouette Knight.
[AMBROSIUS] Aah. Now that's
a wish I could easily grant.
You should have asked for that
instead of the Ether Reactor.
Sorry. I wasn't clear enough.
I meant, I want to build
my own Silhouette Knight.
It won't be special unless
I make it with my own hands.
You believe you can make a
Silhouette Knight from scratch?
[ERNESTI]
I do, indeed.
[AMBROSIUS] And why is this
so important to you?
Because... it's my hobby, sire!
[AMBROSIUS laughing]
What a ridiculous answer!
You surprise me, boy.
And that is not an easy feat!
Sorry! Please be merciful.
I promise to give my grandson
a stern talking to.
--[AMBROSIUS] Granted.
--[gasps]
The knowledge shall be yours.
--Majesty!
--[AMBROSIUS] However,
slaying a mere behemoth is not
enough to justify your request.
If you truly want
the Ether Reactor,
you must first prove
to me that you can make
good use of its power.
Okay, how would you like me
to go about that, your majesty?
[AMBROSIUS]
Build your Knight.
Though, for this challenge,
you will merely
need to create a chassis.
If your new design impresses me
and can satisfy my standards,
then I will grant your wish
and your dream
will be a reality.
[giggling]
I won't fail you, sire!
[SELESTINA] The next day,
the Marquis, Joachim of Selati,
invited his children back
from Laihiala Academy.
[STEPHANIA]
Father. It's good to see you.
[giggles]
Indeed. It seems
you're doing well.
So, uh, what's the reason
you summoned us here, Father?
[JOACHIM]
Stephania informs me
that you two are rather close
to Ernesti Echevalier.
[ARCHID]
Um. Yeah?
[JOACHIM]
His majesty the king has taken
quite a liking to him, as well.
[BOTH gasp]
[JOACHIM] I'm interested
in the boy's progress.
If he is successful in any way,
let me know at once.
I would like to be the first
to inform his majesty.
I don't know-- If we do that,
will it help Ernie?
Yes, of course.
Though, I would appreciate it
if you didn't tell him
we talked about this.
I don't want it to distract him.
His task is daunting enough.
[GUY 3A]
Hey, is this right?
[GUY 3B]
No! This one goes here!
That one goes there!
If I see anyone slacking,
you'll get my foot up your ass!
What happened here?
I just replaced this
Crystal Tissue!
It looks like it's
been to hell and back.
How did they put it through
this much stress in one night?
Beautiful.
Uh!
Even like this they're elegant.
In their own way.
The form collapses,
and only the wreckage remains.
This is true,
refined beauty! Uh!
And then, when you realize
you're responsible for it,
you're not sure
whether to feel guilty
or proud of the destruction!
Who the hell are you?
Please, don't you
mind him, boss!
Sorry! David!
I was just leaving!
Hold it!
So, kid.
You're responsible for this?
I'd like to hear
how you managed it.
[DAVID]
Sorry, can you go over it again?
Sure! It's simple.
I copied out all of the scripts
from the Magius Engine,
did the calculations myself,
and used the custom scripts
to pilot the unit.
[DAVID] Let's say,
hypothetically, that you did.
What does any of that have to do
with the way Guiar fell apart?
Well, I was effectively
a stand-in for the engine.
That allowed me
to remove all its limiters
and do whatever I wanted.
I took every ounce
of mana it had to give
and used it to attack.
Of course, that depleted
the enhancement magic
holding the frame together.
That sound like
a decent summary to you?
Or were you busy
pissin' yourself?
[ERNESTI chuckles softly]
Yeah, that about
sums it up, boss.
[ERNESTI]
Dietrich really surprised me!
He was incredible out there!
I would have been roasted
without his help!
That last attack on
the behemoth would have been
impossible to pull off alone.
We made a great team!
[DIETRICH] No. Please.
I didn't do anything.
Why are you so gloomy?
It's a time to celebrate!
We should be
praising the Guair!
Sure, kid. Whatever.
Let's get back on topic.
You're telling me,
if you use your full strength,
any Knight that you piloted
would end up just like Guair?
If it's a current model?
Yeah, it would
pretty much be scrap.
Ugh! You idiot!
We can't build a new unit
every other day!
You don't have to!
I've already come up
with the solution.
[DAVID]
Is this really Crystal Tissue?
It would increase
structural integrity tenfold!
And power!
I call it the
Strand-Type Crystal Tissue!
[DAVID]
Huh. Amazing.
We only swapped out
30% muscle mass,
and it worked great!
Each fiber is
fairly weak on its own.
But weaving them together
dramatically increases
their strength.
And, compared to laying them
out in a straight line,
this allows them
to expand and contract
over a greater distance, which
leads to greater energy output!
Well, I'll be damned.
Instead of just
repairing all these units,
we're giving them an upgrade!
Before you do,
I have one more idea.
What if we made an alteration
to the humanoid shape?
[DAVID]
Hmm. All right.
I'll hear you out. Lay it on me.
--[HELVI] Boss.
--'Bout time!
Good to see you again!
Oh, Ernesti?
What are you doing in here?
Ah, just living the dream.
Pardon?
[ERNESTI]
Helvi, I wanted to talk to you
about the Trandorkis.
[HELVI] Yeah.
It's a real mess, isn't it?
[ERNESTI] Don't worry,
the boss will have it
as good as new in no time.
In fact, he'll make it
even stronger
and faster than before!
--Really?
--Yup!
But we need your help.
That's why we called you here.
All right.
[ERNESTI] Silhouette Knights
have only ever had
two arms to work with.
But when you stop
to think about it,
it's not as efficient
as it could be.
To use magic in combat,
Knight Runners need to switch
from sword to rod, and
vice versa for melee combat.
It takes time,
and in that split second,
while the Knight Runner
is vulnerable,
a demon beast could
gain the upper hand.
True. But we're so used
to swapping on the fly,
it's a simple matter.
Sure. But I think we can
make it even simpler.
Humor me for a moment.
What if... we added another pair
of arms to the back of the unit?
Aah?
[ALL]
Uh...
Interesting thought.
But that form is traditional.
Silhouette Knights have always
been based on humans.
That's part of the reason we're
able to operate them so easily.
I mean, sure, we could
put arms in the back,
but how are we
supposed to move 'em?
No need to worry.
They're not going to be
fully-functional limbs.
They're only purpose will be
to hold the rod
so the pilot can fire them.
It's a crude design, but it will
work for the testing phase.
For convenience, we'll refer
to the rod the sub-arms
are holding as
the unit's "back weapon."
We'll use a dedicated script to
control the sub-arms movement.
This will include gripping
and moving the back weapon.
We'll also add an aiming
function to the basic controls.
And with a targeting reticle
on the heads-up display,
all the Knight Runner
has to do is aim and fire.
[HELVI] It's simpler
than I thought it would be.
With enough practice,
I bet I could use the sword
and rod at the
same time, no sweat.
Their form may be "human,"
but Silhouette Knights
are just advanced tools.
If there's some function
we want them to have,
don't you think we should
change that form to create it?
Tell me, silver hair.
You sure you're a human?
I mean, how do you
come up with these ideas?
I've never seen or heard
of anything like 'em.
[ERNESTI]
Because they don't exist!
That's why I'm making them!
It's called invention!
[ARCHID]
Hey, Ernie.
[ERNESTI]
What's up?
[ARCHID]
If you add those things,
Silhouette Knights
will get even stronger.
[ERNESTI]
Yup. That's the plan.
Be honest. Once you finish them,
you'll fight the
demon beasts again, right?
Uh. Well, yeah.
Of course, I will.
That's a Knight Runner's
job, after all.
The entire kingdom
counts on us for protection.
[ARCHID]
Then let us help.
There must be
something we can do.
[ADELTRUD] Please, Ernie!
The thought of you facing
demon beasts by yourself
is worse than death!
I don't ever want to
feel that helpless again.
Let us fight
those monsters with you!
The next time you face a demon,
I won't be stuck in a carriage!
You taught us magic,
so you can teach us
to be Knight Runners, too!
[gasps]
You got it!
And I've already come up
with the perfect plan!
You're sure you can
pull this off? Honest?
[ERNESTI] I am.
I just need your permission.
[LAURI] Most of the units
are being repaired now,
what your proposing would keep
them out of commission longer.
The creation or major overhaul
of a Silhouette Knight
is complicated.
The whole process
will require parts and time,
not to mention
plenty of manpower.
If I'm going to achieve
a simpler way
to construct Silhouette
Knights, I need this.
But, first, I'll make
a practice model!
Thank you all for coming out.
As you can see, this new
machine is far simpler
than a full-sized unit.
They'll be essential
for testing,
and I'd like all of
you to construct them
with Batson leading the project.
Us? Make those things?
[SELESTINA] And so, Ernie's new
plans were set in motion.
Soon, the entire school
would be involved.
[DAVID hollering]
The new Crystal Tissue
worked as we intended,
but the underlying framework's
completely blown out!
I didn't think of that!
[laughing]
Guess we'll be burning
the midnight oil on this one.
We're counting you! Good luck!
Okay! Time to get
some training in!
Take it easy, you moron!
We just finished
tuning that one!
[ADELTRUD]
Mm?
Ah. Your frame's
so cold and hard.
My dear, you're perfect!
No fair. I would do anything
for Ernesti to say that to me.
Why can't I be a made of metal?
[EDGAR grunting]
[ERNESTI]
Hey, Edgar! How's it feel?
I think they're running
pretty smoothly!
I'm still trying to walk!
[yells]
Fun, huh? It just takes
some getting used to.
Look, Ernesti. I get that
these Silhouette Gears
are important to you and all,
it's just, the controls
are complicated,
and they use too much mana.
There's no way using these
will serve as a replacement
for Silhouette Knight training.
You really think so?
One, two!
--[ARCHID] Alley-oop!
--One, two!
Well, those two are unique.
Couldn't you incorporate
a Magius Engine, at least?
That way... I could operate
this thing with ease.
[DIETRICH]
Quit complaining, Edgar!
It's pathetic!
You're the top knight
in Laihiala! Act like it!
What have you done
with Dietrich?
[DIETRICH] Very funny.
These Gear things really
force you to think about
how much mana you're using.
Knight Runners of any level
could learn a lot
training with them!
[ARCHID] Hey, D!
Wanna play tag? You're it!
[DIETRICH]
Not for long!
[ADELTRUD, ARCHID laughing]
He sure changed. What happened?
[SELESTINA] After tons of
research, trials, and revisions,
a modified Silhouette
Knight was completed!
Now, it was time
to put Ernesti's
new alterations to the test!
[DAVID]
All set?
When you're ready,
try standing up!
--[BATSON] Yeah!
--It stood!
Now, try taking a step or two!
Nice and easy!
[sighs]
[DAVID]
Okay, stop!
How's it feel?
[HELVI] About as rough
as you'd expect.
It's got a lot of power,
so it's hard to make it
work the way I want it to.
We'll worry about
tuning it after the test.
Our goal for today
is seeing those in action.
Those Silhouette Gears
are really something else.
Just goes to show they're
more than meets the eye.
[HELVI]
Deploying the sub-arms now.
Displaying reticle.
Lock target. And fire!
[ENGINEERS gasp]
It's even more accurate
than I'd hoped!
[HELVI] Test fire complete.
Retracting sub-arms.
[DAVID]
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Looks good!
[ENGINEERS crying, laughing]
Uh, they're happy about
something like that?
Isn't it more impressive if you
use the magic yourself, Ernie?
Well, with this, we can
increase firepower at will!
But what's important is that
our hard work payed off.
This Silhouette Knight
took its first steps today.
And that is worthy
of a few happy tears.
I don't really get it, but I'm
happy for you, nonetheless.
Congratulations, Ernie!
[EDGAR] What's your take
on this new equipment, D?
[DIETRICH] Hmm, well.
It won't just help with
long-range combat,
but close quarters, too.
I like it.
[EDGAR]
True, but it's one thing
if we're up against
demon beasts.
What happens if we have
to fight the new unit?
[HELVI] I'll tell you.
You'll get knocked flat
on your "Top Knight" backside!
With this new power,
no one's a match for me!
Even the great Edgar couldn't
go toe-to-toe with my baby.
Somehow, I doubt that's true.
Do you have the guts
to find out?
[CROWD murmuring]
[EDGAR] Jeez. They didn't have
to make a big deal of this.
It's only a mock battle.
[HELVI] You better not
think of backing out on me.
[DAVID] If you're both ready,
we can get this started!
This is the last trial!
We get to see what
our new unit can really do!
To my right, the new
and re-named Telestale,
and its opponent,
the battle-hardened Earlcumber!
[DAVID]
Knights! Bow!
Take positions!
It may be shiny and new,
but that won't decide the fight.
It always come down to skill!
I won't forget you, Trandorkis.
Thank you. For everything.
Let's go, Telestale!
--Begin!
--[gong rings]
Why isn't she taking advantage
of her longer-range?
Let's give a proper hello!
[HELVI grunting]
The Strand-Type's
power is unreal!
I didn't think it was possible!
But if being around Ernesti
has taught me anything,
it's that moving forward means
throwing away what you know!
Well, that's Edgar for you.
Stubborn as a wall.
Any other pilot would've
been done for by now.
Helvi's using the Telestale
like she's had it for years.
And that,
my silver haired friend,
is the reason
she's a test-runner.
[DIETRICH] She's pushing it
awfully hard, though.
[ERNESTI]
Probably taking advantage
of the superior output.
And there's plenty of tuning
to do on the control system.
Fighting with precision
isn't viable yet.
So, it's strength versus skill.
Can't wait to see who wins.
Her close-range magic is tough!
I can't counter it!
I don't like
to gamble in a fight,
but being backed into
a corner just isn't fun!
[HELVI]
A head-on attack?
I'd expect nothing less
from you, Edgar!
If you're going all out,
then so will I!
[HELVI]
Gotcha!
How the hell did he
manage that block?
Come on! We just built that!
That's how you want to play?
Fine, we'll take it up a notch!
Give him everything
we've got, Telestale!
This fight is over!
[HELVI]
Uh!
Oh! Out of mana!
[DAVID]
Thanks to all of you,
the new Tellestale
passed its trials.
Great work, everyone.
Moving forward,
we'll deal with the decreased
fuel efficiency that we
discovered in the mock battle.
Ahem. Well,
enough of that. Drink up!
[ENGINEERS]
Yes, sir!
[ENGINEERS laughing]
Get over there
and cheer Helvi up.
Why me? You do it!
--I'm excited!
--Why?
Won't get the king
reward you for all this?
You practically
made history today!
Yeah! You've changed the
Silhouette Knight forever.
Well, not quite yet.
The Telestale may be finished,
but it's nowhere near completed.
We've got a long way to go.
Was afraid he'd say that.
We're walking
a difficult path, here.
It can't be trod
in just one day.
[EDGAR chuckles]
Yeah, okay.
[door creaks]
[KERHILD] Hmm. So, his pet
project isn't finished yet?
All right. We'll stick
around and see
what else he has in store.
[SELESTINA] By this time,
a tiny thorn had already
embedded itself
in Laihiala Academy.
Unfortunately, no one,
not even Ernesti,
had noticed its presence.
[ERNESTI]
Next time: "Light &amp; Shadow"!
Machiavellianism is calling me!