[SELESTINA]
The merchant city of Fontanie
was once a beacon of prosperity.
But sadly, once it fell
to Zaloudek's army,
the radiant city vanished
and was replaced
by cold desolation.
[EMRYS]
I hardly recognize the place.
Last time I was here,
every day was like a festival.
[ADELTRUD]
The silver phoenix...
...soars through the night.
[gasps] Ernie!
[giggles]
[whispering] Keep it down, Addy!
[ARCHID] They were watching us
more closely than I expected.
[sighs] It's a good thing
we snuck in separately.
How's our "product"
coming along, Nora?
They're ready and
waiting, Young Master.
You all know what to do.
The royal family's
suffered long enough.
Let's roll out!
[KOJASS]
That mech just flew!
It wasn't launched,
it actually flew!
[EDGAR] Now, Aldirat.
Show her your power!
[ERNESTI]
...carved a path in the sky!
[KERHILT growls]
[ERNESTI]
Young Master, can you keep up?
Yeah, this is easy!
[EMRYS yelps]
[EMRYS]
Thanks.
Think nothing of it, Highness.
[ERNESTI] According to intel,
the princess is being kept
in the top floor of
a tower in that castle.
[ADELTRUD]
Hold on, there are four towers!
[NORA] Security was so tight,
I couldn't find out
which one she was in, sadly.
So, I guess that gives us
a one in four chance?
[ERNESTI]
Yeah.
But, to be safe, we'll hit
all four towers at once.
[SOLDIER 10A] I'm tellin' you,
they were out to here!
[SOLDIER 10B]
Damn! Which bar was this?
[ERNESTI] Nora. We'll
need an escape route.
Consider it done.
[ERNESTI]
Go in hard and get out fast.
[ADELTRUD]
Roger!
--[ARCHID] On it!
--[EMRYS] Right!
[crash]
Sorry for the intrusion.
I'm guessing you're
Lady Martina?
You are?
I mean you no harm.
The opposite, in fact.
I'm Ernesti Echevalier.
Knight Commander of the
Order of the Silver Phoenix.
Considering your wild entrance
and calm disposition,
I assume that you're
from my homeland.
You should be rescuing
the princess, not me.
[SOLDIER 10C]
Hey! What was that racket?
Please, don't worry.
My friends will have her soon.
In that case, lead the way.
[SOLDIER 10C]
Who the hell are you?
Sir Knight, shall we go?
I'm sorry if this
gets a little rough.
Now hold on tight.
[ISADOLA] Cousin Rys!
Is it you or am I dreaming?
Hey, now. No waterworks.
We still have to
get outta here.
Come on, I'll carry you.
Okay!
[ADELTRUD]
Ah-ha! Have no fear!
The Order of the
Silver Phoenix is...
[ARCHID] Of course,
I hit the one in four.
Uh...
[ARCHID]
How's it going?
I'm looking for the princess.
Is that you, by any chance?
It is. And, you are?
[ARCHID] My name is Archid,
I'm here to rescue you.
Rescue me? Who sent you?
[clanging]
Sorry, there's no time.
You'll just have to trust me!
Even if we manage it,
what will we do after we escape?
[ARCHID]
Uh--
My homeland is all
but a memory, now.
There's no one I can rely on.
Even if I go with you.
I have nothing left.
Please, leave me be.
I won't tell anyone
about you. Just go.
Wha--? No way!
[clanging]
It'll be all right.
You have lots of people
you can count on!
I just know it!
Now, let's bust out of here
and defeat the Zaloudek!
'Kay?
I don't have that
kind of strength.
No real power to speak of.
[ARCHID] You do! The fact
I'm here proves that!
You have the power to
drive people to action!
The same way you moved me!
You just have to use it!
You believe that?
Sure do! And, from
now on, you have us!
We'll protect you, I swear it!
I'm not worthy of being
protected by anyone.
If people were to
suffer because of me,
I couldn't live with it.
Come on!
I don't get it, why do
you think this way?
If they're willing to fight
for you, you should trust that!
[clanging]
Princess!
I am Archid Alter.
And from this day forward,
I am your Knight.
I will take up my sword for you
and fulfill my duty.
My lady. I await your order.
Name it, and I will
see it done at once.
Okay.
Will you take me from
this place, my Knight?
You bet.
[ELEONORA]
So high!
Not for long. Look over there!
[ISADOLA]
Eleonora!
[ELEONORA]
Isadola!
[GIRLS giggle]
Princess. You okay?
Yes. Thanks to my
valiant Knight, Archid.
Her Knight, huh?
Addy...
Great work, everyone!
Let's put this place behind us.
[clanging]
[gasps]
[DOROTEO]
You imbecile!
[SOLDIER 9C whimpers]
Prepare the Levitate
ships for launch!
That means now.
[SOLDIER 9C]
Uh-- Sir!
[KOJASS] Things are finally
getting interesting it seems.
Don't you think so, my dear?
I suppose I can go
with you this time.
It might prove fun.
These rodents will
no doubt head east
to make their escape.
Yes! Of course!
There are no Kuschperchan
remnants to the west. Clever.
Also, there's that so-called
"Order of the Reaper."
They've been operating
out of the east, as well.
It's possible they're
involved, and if so,
this could prove hazardous.
You sound worried.
Do you lack faith
in this ship, my lord?
Surely your design can
withstand a few raiders.
Oh, no.
If they defeat us, it won't
be the fault of my dear
Levitate ship or its
brilliant design, General.
On the contrary.
It will be the fault of the
bloated fool commanding it.
That's you.
[DOLOTEO growls]
Truthfully, I'm teeming
with excitement.
These raiders could be worthy.
Unlike the rabble
we've fought so far,
we can use them to test the
true might of my creation!
[KOJASS laughs]
Drink up, men!
The Ether is fine!
[SELESTINA] The next day,
the Levitate Ship
of Doloteo Mardonnes found
the Order of the Silver Phoenix
and quickly intercepted them.
Prepare Tyrantos for launch!
Helm, move us
directly above them!
[ARCHID]
Heads up, guys.
[ADELTRUD] That must be
what D told us about.
I can't believe they
already found us.
Damn flying ships!
[ERNESTI]
It's so wonderful!
It's not a blimp or a balloon,
but an actual ship that
sails through the sky!
Beautiful!
But how did they
even come up with it?
I have the advantage
of knowledge
they could never possess
and yet they have somehow
carved themselves
a path in the sky!
[ERNESTI]
It's too much!
I have to see it up close!
What the...?
Somethin's coming at us!
Is it a projectile?
No, it's too big.
[SOLDIER 10E screams]
It's him! The demon!
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH yelp]
[ERNESTI] It's more
incredible than I hoped!
It uses wind magic as
a source of propulsion!
So innovative!
But that shouldn't be enough
to keep its weight airborne.
How do they compensate?
I have so many questions now!
That mech just flew!
It wasn't launched,
it actually flew!
Somebody other than myself
used a completely different
design philosophy
and accomplished it without
sails or air magic!
General! I need to see more!
Shake that bastard off!
[ERNESTI]
Whoa!
[SOLDIER 10F]
Die, monster!
[SOLDIER 10D] All the Tyrantos
have been wiped out!
Put everything into the engines!
Take us back to Fontanie!
Not yet! I haven't gotten
a good look at it!
It's really flying.
[laughs]
How dare it try to
encroach on my sky!
[laughs]
[ERNESTI]
Hey! Where are you going?
All right, then.
But you haven't seen
the last of me, air ship!
[KOJASS]
The sky is mine.
Mine, and no one else's!
I claimed it!
Whoever you are, you'll soon
learn how reckless it is
to try and take it from me!
The next time we meet
it will be your end!
[SELESTINA]
The Western Grand Storm would be
one of history's most
notorious conflicts,
and the genius of both
Ernesti and Lord Kojass'
would be at the core of it all.
[CRISTOBAL]
Why even bother coming back?
[DOLOTEO grunting]
[DOLOTEO]
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
That's quite enough barbarism.
It's turning my stomach.
[CRISTOBAL growls] There's no
way those Kuschperchan mutts
pulled off something so brazen.
So, who did this?
The Eleven Flags?
Or maybe those weaklings
from the Locar Federation?
[DOLOTEO] I'm afraid our
adversary won't be as easy
to deal with as they were.
Why's that?
They were monsters.
Two of their Silhouette Knights
were like a horse and rider,
racing down the road
at incredible speeds
while pulling large chariots.
And inside the chariot
is the true terror.
A demonic Knight
wreathed in flame,
flying on wings of death.
What sort of nonsense
are you spouting now?
[CATARINA] A flying Silhouette
Knight? That's impossible.
[KOJASS]
I assure you, it isn't.
I saw it darting around
like a gadfly myself.
My Levitate Ship could
do nothing but run.
It was upsetting.
[DOLOTEO] Duke Fernando's
wife and daughter
were among the royals who fled.
The duchess hails from beyond
the mountains to the east.
She's the daughter of Ambrosius,
the former King of Fremmevilla.
The beast guards?
That would explain a lot.
But it won't stop me from
making Eleonora my wife.
And if they resist, I'll wipe
Fremmevilla off the map!
[SELESTINA] Ernesti's knights
met up with the rest
of the Order at Nishirie,
a relay station
on the old Kuschperchan highway.
Welcome back.
That was exhausting.
That was easy.
Don't be a wimp.
We both know you were
just acting tough
for your precious princess.
Uh!
[LETONMAKI] Your Highness!
Thank goodness you're safe.
Baron Letonmaki, it's good
to see that you are safe.
And you, Viscount Bekkel.
I only wish we had died
instead of the King.
But... it hasn't been
all bad news, of late.
This young merchant
recently approached us
with an interesting proposal.
Merchant?
Knight. I think
you'd better explain.
Of course. Why don't
we head inside, first?
Understand.
The Kuschperhcan Silhouette
Knight, the Lesvant,
is a solid mech with
a great history.
Though, compared to the
new Zaloudek units,
they fall behind in
firepower and endurance.
But don't worry.
The Silver Phoenix
Merchant Association
can offer a solution.
All the details are
in those reports.
Interesting.
How do you plan to
get the materials?
Oh, that's the best part.
My "brokers" are among the
most talented in Fremmevilla.
They'll get everything
we need from the enemy.
Ah. I see.
Well, Princess?
What are your thoughts?
It seems good.
Young Knight.
If this is indeed a trade, then
you'll want something in return.
What might that be?
Silhouette Knights.
More specifically,
any of the enemy units
our order captures or destroys.
We want exclusive rights
to their parts and chassis'.
Nothing more.
Not a bad deal,
all things considered.
[ERNESTI]
Thank you, Duchess. Now then.
We'll be heading out to rip,
break, and crush the enemy!
Keep the place warm
until we get back, 'kay?
[EMRYS chuckles]
[OFFICER 10A]
That's not Kuschperchan.
Well, whoever they are,
they're on the wrong side.
Get in there and
teach them a lesson!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[OFFICER 10A]
Glory to Zaloudek!
Kuschperchan scarecrows?
They look different.
Shoot now!
[SOLDIERS screaming, groaning]
[OFFICER 10A]
All units... retreat!
I don't believe it.
We routed those barbarians!
That was for Shild Trider!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[BATSON]
Hey!
It's time to change shifts!
Kuschperchans, grab a bite
and get some rest!
Way to go! It's just
hard at first.
You'll get used to it.
Keep up the good work!
[DAVID] Mm... Well, this should
be easy enough to make.
But, I gotta ask. Does the
Ikaruga really need it?
I won't be the one using it.
Since I'm the only
one who can fly,
I figured everyone else
could use anti-air weapons.
You won't get any
complaints from me.
Knocking a flying ship out of
the sky would make my day.
All right, fine.
Just give me some time
to put it together.
Right.
Here's hoping it's ready
before the Zaloudek
decide to launch
another offensive.
This battle is against time.
When we're out here,
the war feels so far away.
It's almost non-existent.
So, uh.
Eleonora is heir to the
Kuschperchan throne, now.
Poor thing. S'not fair.
That is what it means
to have royal blood.
She can't run from this, nephew.
You cheer her up.
Why don't you go pay
her a visit, Rys?
[EMRYS]
Oh, uh... Sure thing.
So, I got nothin'.
We need to help
Eleonora. Any ideas?
Helvi, you're a lady.
What would help
you out of a funk?
Uh-- So just because I'm a lady,
I'd know how a princess feels?
Right, dumb question.
You jerk!
[sighs] Kiss and
get it over with.
[BOTH]
Uh--
Just sleep in the same
bed! That'll do it!
And make sure to snuggle
so she's nice and warm.
[ERNESTI]
No.
We're supposed to cheer her up,
not traumatize her.
Aw!
You got an idea, Ernie?
Well, if she was a mech,
I could figure out most of
her problems by listening
to the engine noise,
but in this case...
These two are useless.
Then why don't you
give it a try?
You're the one who made a vow
of Knighthood to her, Kid.
Cheering her up is your job now!
[GROUP chuckles]
A vow? Interesting.
Addy's right. If you
are her Knight...
...then it's your duty!
Make us proud!
Uh... Uh...
Sounds like this matter
is settled then!
Kid will find a way to
cheer up the princess!
[GROUP chatters, applauds]
Eleonora?
It's Isadola.
I brought a visitor.
[ELEONORA]
Come in.
[door clicks]
Oh, it's you.
Yo! How's it going?
I heard that you
weren't feeling well.
You're here to persuade
me to take the throne
like everyone else, right?
Huh? Well, actually...
I just came here for a visit
and to try and cheer you up.
[ELEONORA] As we speak, blood is
being shed on the battlefield.
Some in my name.
How can I be cheerful,
knowing such things?
[ARCHID groans]
Huh?
You wanna get outta here?
[GROUP gasps]
You've been cooped up
for days now.
Fresh air would do you good.
You're not a prisoner
in a tower anymore.
Come on! It'll be fun!
Um. Okay.
[DAVID] I told you I want
this ready by morning!
Complain and you work double!
[ARCHID]
Boss! You got a minute?
That a joke?
You know the answer--
[ELEONORA]
Um.
Thank you for all
your hard work, sir.
Your Majesty!
[ARCHID]
So... you feeling any better?
[ELEONORA]
Yes.
[ARCHID]
Glad to hear it.
[ELEONORA]
Knight?
[ARCHID]
Hm?
I don't understand
how you can be so kind
to a coward like me.
Hey, come on.
Stop talking like that.
Nobody thinks you're
a coward, all right?
Least of all me.
I think you're
pretty courageous.
If anyone says differently,
I'll knock 'em out.
[CATARINA]
I have a job for you.
The princess is being
protected by this
"Silver Phoenix
Merchant Association."
Get her back.
Not that I'm
ungrateful, Highness.
But royal gratitude isn't
nearly enough to risk my skin
against a foe that powerful.
[CATARINA] Succeed,
and I'll grant you peerage
and land in Kuschpercha
when the job is done.
[KERHILT]
You're serious?
[CATARINA]
It would mean the restoration
of the Hietakannas Household.
That's what you want, right?
[KERHILT]
They're calling themselves
the Silver Phoenix Merchants
or some other ridiculous alias,
but they're just
children playing soldier.
Tonight, we get our lives back!
[BAD GUYS]
Right!
I think I'll use the
Vendobadahla Custom.
[gasps]
What do you want
with the princess?
What's with this thing?
It won't budge!
[gasps]
Did you think you could steal
from us a second time?
Everyone, mount up!
They're never stealing another
Silhouette Knight again!
[KERHILT]
Those morons screwed it up!
If I try to run now,
I lose my chance.
[thud]
You won't be getting
away that easy.
Out of my way, brat!
[KERHILT] Nice mech. They've
made more improvements.
[gasps] So, it's you!
I've improved, too!
It won't be like last time!
Oh! You're the kid
I played with before!
I was hoping I'd get
to finish the job!
[growls] It's pretty quick
despite that fat ass!
I think it's time
that we finish this!
I won't spare you a second time.
[growls]
Now, Aldirat.
Show her your power!
This's one's for Helvi.
And the Trandorkis!
[KERHILT]
I guess that's that. Damn it.
I should have finished you
off back in Fremmevilla.
Oh, well. Too late for regrets.
All the attackers
have been slain.
They won't trouble us again.
Or anyone else, for that matter.
I'm sorry you had to deal with
such trouble on my behalf.
[ARCHID] Stop it.
We don't need an apology.
Keeping you safe is
what makes us happy.
You're our princess,
and we're your Knights.
It's as simple as that.
[giggles]
Well done, my Knights.
You have served me well.
Our pleasure, Your Highness.
[ERNESTI]
Next time: "Hit and Away"!
My rival is calling me!