[CARLITOS] Stand proud,
my valiant Black Knights.
You are the pride of
the Zaloudek Kingdom!
I am thrilled beyond measure
to share this moment with you.
Remember it well.
Long ago,
these western lands were
ruled as one nation.
With one king
presiding over all!
The name of that
kingdom was Phadaabaden.
Today, we are all that remains
of that great legacy.
Which means the west
is our birthright!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
The time has come!
We will reunite this land!
And any who oppose us
will be crushed under foot!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[SELESTINA]
On this day in history,
Carlitos Bilt Zaloudek,
eldest son of Bardomelow,
King of Zaloudek, declared war
on the surrounding nations
of the Occident.
It was the beginning
of what future generations
would come to know as
the Western Grand Storm.
[SOLDIERS]
Glory to Zaloudek!
[NOBLE 9A] I was certain
the Locar Federation
would hold out longer
than a mere month.
[NOBLE 9B] The "Federation"
is just a collection
of tiny nations. They're no
match for Zaloudek's might.
Even so, it should
have taken longer
than a month to overcome them.
I agree.
Something must have
happened in Zaloudek
to embolden them.
Something that would
quickly enhance their power
and drive them to ambition.
In any case, they'll
be coming here soon.
Shild Trider's defenses
must be reinforced!
So, it's true?
[AUGUSTI]
Eleonora.
I heard the servants gossiping.
They said that war is
practically at our gates.
There's no need to
concern yourself, my dear.
Shild Trider's walls have
always stood strong.
We'll send those invaders
home in stitches.
Thank you for that, Father.
I'm sorry for worrying.
[crashing]
[PILOT 9A] Their moves
are totally different!
[PILOT 9B]
Where'd they get this power?
[PILOT 9A gasps]
What the...? Look out!
[PILOTS scream]
[SOLDIERS scream]
[SELESTINA]
Using the Tyranto.
Zaloudek's new cutting-edge
Silhouette Knight.
The Black Knights broke through
the Kingdom of Kuschpercha
with brutal efficiency.
[SELESTINA] But then the war
took an unexpected turn.
Zaloudek's rapid advance,
which had gone
virtually unopposed,
suddenly halted outside
the mighty walls
of Shild Trider.
There, they waited.
Silent as death.
When King Augusti of Kuschpercha
learned of this development,
he gathered his forces
at Shild Trider.
Here, they hoped they could
finally turn the tide of battle.
[CRISTOBAL]
It's time, Mardonnes.
Indeed, Highness.
I wish I could see their faces
as they realize their fate.
What... What are those?
Buzzards? No, wait.
Black ships coming
from the skies!
Incoming!
[CRISTOBAL laughs] Like pigs
to the slaughter, they come.
The Kuschperchans are more
foolish than I thought.
If they had known about
our Levitate ships,
I doubt they would
have gathered here.
Attention, proud Order
of the Bronze Wing,
this is Cristobal.
Tonight, we'll feast in
the halls of Shild Trider!
Show them the meaning of fear!
[DOROTEO]
All Knight Runners to positon!
We'll be dropping
the Tyrantos shortly!
Blow Engines. Full-reverse!
[PILOTS groan]
[SOLDIERS yell]
[PILOTS groaning]
[SELESTINA] Never in the
history of this world
had there been an
attack from the sky.
Kuschpercha was immediately
backed into a corner.
[PILOT 9C] Stand firm!
Defend the castle at all costs!
[PILOT 9C groans]
[KERHILT] Kuschpercha will
be a memory after tonight.
There's glory to be had.
I better get some while
I have the chance.
[rumbling]
Martina.
Thank you so much for
supporting my brother.
I only wish we could have
returned you to Fremmevilla.
It was my honor
to serve, Highness.
Eleonora.
I wish your mother could
have seen what a wise
and beautiful woman
you've grown into.
I am so proud of you,
and she would have been, too.
You must escape with
Martina and Isadola.
You're not coming?
What are you going to do?
As king, I must fulfill
my duties to the people.
No. You can't!
You have to leave!
Try to understand.
I cannot run and leave our
people to suffer these invaders.
Our Knights are fighting them,
and I should be there
to lead the charge.
Take care of her. For me.
Even if I die trying.
[AUGUSTI] Isadola,
she'll need your support
through all of this.
Yes. Highness.
I'm heading out!
Prepare the Royal mech!
[AUGUSTI]
I am Augusti Valio Kuschpercha!
King and defender of this realm!
In accordance with
the ancient ways,
I request a duel
with your commander!
[CRISTOBAL]
I am Cristobal,
son of King Bardomelow
of Zaloudek!
And I accept your
challenge, old man!
Well, let's go.
Come on!
[gasps] What are you doing?
I... I can't leave my father!
Stop!
No!
[gasps]
[ISADOLA]
You brat.
Don't you get why his majesty
asked for something
as old-fashioned as a duel?
He's buying us time to escape!
If you go back, his sacrifice
will mean nothing!
[gasps]
[ISADOLA] You are heir to
the throne of Kuschpercha.
Act like it!
But I don't want him to die!
Let Uncle! He can fight
in father's pla--!
Do you feel that pain?
It means you're still alive!
Get up and keep living for him!
[MARTINA]
We should keep moving.
It's not safe for us here.
And by dawn, it will
be even worse.
[AUGUSTI]
Bastards. What happened?
What kind of power made you
willing to become butchers?
[gasps]
[groaning]
[cackles]
[AUGUSTI screams]
[AUGUSTI] Well done,
young Prince of Zaloudek.
This battle is yours.
Now, end it!
You knew you would lose,
yet you fought with honor.
I respect that. Farewell.
[SELESTINA] By the time the
sun peeked over the horizon,
both the king of Kuschpercha
and Delvancul had fallen.
At the same time, Shild Trider,
which had stood as a bastion
of strength and pride
for so long, fell to
Zaloudek's might.
[CARLITOS]
Kuschpercha is no more.
The Occidents are
as good as mine, now.
Cristobal has taken to
commanding well, it would seem.
Yes, but he cannot be
trusted with politics.
Don't fail me, sister.
Leave it to me, dear brother.
[MARTINA] We're close
to the Duchy's territory.
Once we cross the river,
we'll be safe.
We'd be there now if it
weren't for those ships.
But, no, they have
to buzz around us
like Gadflies in a pig's sty.
Such undignified words.
What would Emrys say
if he heard you?
"What are you waiting for?
Give them a good
whack, Isadola!"
[horse whinnies]
Why'd you stop?
Checkpoint.
What do we do?
[SOLDIER 9C] Who are you,
and where are you headed?
[BINDER]
My name's Binder.
I'm from the next village over.
Just going to help
some relatives.
[SOLDIER 9C]
Huh. Well, isn't that sweet?
And I suppose these
delicate flowers
are nothing but farmhands, huh?
Either way, you might
as well turn back.
There are no relatives
left to help.
The Duchy is under
Zaloudek's control,
and Duke Fernando is dead.
I saw his head roll personally.
[BOTH gasp]
[ISADOLA]
How dare you!
Let go of her!
[SOLDIER 9C]
Oh, my.
For the wife of a farmer, your
arms are surprisingly gentle.
Isn't that right,
Princess Martina?
[ERNESTI] Young Master,
is something wrong?
[EMRYS] That checkpoint flag.
It's not Kuschperchan.
[SOLDIER 9D]
Huh? A carriage?
[SOLDIER 9D gasps]
[SOLDIER 9D]
No, what is that?
Excuse me!
We are the Silver Phoenix
Merchant Association!
We have trade goods and rare
trinkets from over the mountain!
[SOLDIER 9D]
As if we'd believe that!
What kind of merchants
use a monstrous carriage
like that for simple trading?
[ERNESTI]
There are lots of demon beasts
beyond the mountains!
Conventional covered wagons
simply won't do the jo--
[PILOT 9D]
Enough! Be quiet and don't move!
[PILOT 9E] We're searching
you and your cargo!
[ERNESTI]
Looks like the rumors had merit.
Something's wrong here.
[EMRYS]
Yeah, my old man's usually right
about these things.
You'll have to
excuse my ignorance.
I don't recognize that flag.
Is it Kuschperchan?
[SOLDIER 9D]
Kuschpercha is long gone!
This checkpoint and
everything beyond it
belongs to the
Kingdom of Zaloudek!
Well, Young Master!
You heard him.
If Kuschpercha is gone,
there's no point
wastin' my time with
the likes of you!
Howling...
[EMRYS]
Blast!
[PILOT 9D] They just broke
through with a single strike!
[ERNESTI] Now that's
not nice, Young Master!
This is diplomacy. Let's put
our best foot forward.
[ERNESTI] If you don't mind,
Ikaruga will join the fun!
It's your grand debut, so,
let's show them what you can do!
That's one down.
[PILOT 9E gasps]
Damn it!
That's two.
[PILOT 9D]
Take this, you bastard!
What? How is this possible?
Sub-arms alone shouldn't
stop a Tyranto!
And three.
[PILOTS yell]
Long-range, huh?
Sure, I'll play!
[PILOT 9G screams]
That's two more!
[PILOT 9H]
No! Stay away!
[PILOT 9H screams]
And, that's six! Who's next?
[SOLDIER 9D whimpers]
Spare us!
[EMRYS]
Ha. Not worth my time.
Ernie goes out and
before you know it,
their whole garrison's
surrendering.
[ARCHID]
Like you didn't see that coming.
[HELVI]
What's wrong, Edgar?
This new unit. Look familiar?
[HELVI, DIETRICH gasp]
[DIETRICH] Back weapons!
And strand-type crystal tissue!
[HELVI] Well, now we know
how Zaloudek got so strong.
[ERNESTI] Are you talking
Silhouette Knights?
You can't talk robots
without me around!
Now let's see.
You guessed right, though.
The technology used in this unit
is the same as the Telestale.
And I think we all know
where it came from.
[EDGAR]
They stole Helvi's Trandorkis.
It didn't deserve that.
So, the thieves from Casadesus
were connected to Zaloudek
somehow. Unforgiveable!
Don't worry, they'll
get their comeuppance.
At least we know what
happened to the Trandorkis.
And, since they're obviously
stealing our ideas,
it's safe to assume
this unit is ours, too.
Which means, it's okay
for us to take it!
What? Hold on.
That's not very Knightly.
Let's think about it.
I wouldn't expect any less
from ol' silver hair.
Fess up. You want to take a peek
at the enemy mech, too,
don't ya, boss?
You're damn right!
What's the plan, "Young Master"?
Well, we're Merchant's, right?
So, we'll stick to our business,
and beat the living crap
out of anybody who
stands in our way.
That sounds good!
Maybe I'll actually
get to fight.
What is our business, exactly?
What do all merchants want?
Lots and lots of
product! [laughs]
[SELESTINA] Shortly afterwards,
soldiers in the Zaloudek army
began to whisper of a
monstrous horse and rider
that ferried the grim
reaper himself.
He wore a demon mask and hunted
along the eastern road.
[CRISTOBAL] Let's get one
thing straight, Princess.
I'm not here out of concern.
And I don't like small talk.
So, I'll just get
straight to the point.
You're going to be
my wife. End of story.
N-No, I won't!
You think you have a choice?
If you try my patience,
I'll drug you until you comply!
And if you keep acting up,
I'll just kill you and make
the other girl my queen.
Your choice.
Isadola? You can't!
[ELEONORA]
Father. I need you.
I don't know what
I'm supposed to do.
[CRISTOBAL]
Tch. What a pathetic girl.
How can I punish her
if she won't fight back?
[DOROTEO] You're not
calling off the wedding,
Your Highness?
I'm not that stupid.
If I throw a wrench
in my sister's plan,
I may as well slit my throat.
What's your take on
the rumors of late?
This "Demon-Masked Reaper"?
Probably just Kuschperchan
rebels causing mischief.
They'll vanish, eventually.
Take them out!
Or I'll do it myself--
No, Highness, you mustn't.
You shouldn't involve yourself
with such trivial matters.
It would only validate
their rebellion.
If it's trivial,
you shouldn't have
a problem crushing them.
Damn it all.
What am I to do
about this prince?
[KERHILT] Sounds like you're
in quite the rough spot.
I wouldn't mind
getting involved.
Your sending that
idiot son of yours
to look for the rebels?
I can watch his back.
Keep him safe.
If what I've heard about
the Bronze Fang is true,
I would welcome your help.
[KERHILT] Very well. I'll
find this "Reaper" for you.
And once I have, you can
swoop in and kill it.
Not a bad deal,
wouldn't you agree?
[SELESTINA] Thanks to reports
from Nora of the Azure Hawk,
the Silver Phoenix
found out about
Princess Eleonora's plight,
and was moved to action.
Gah, I wish this
was Cristobal's face.
A death that quick would
be way too merciful.
If he lays one finger on her...
[ERNESTI]
We won't let him.
Now finish up, because we've
got a princess to rescue!
[SELESTINA] Just as Ernesti was
putting his plan into motion,
Zaloudek's army
deployed Levitate ships
to locate and destroy him.
[gasps] Seriously?
[PILOT 9I] Yes. Just like
the Bronze Order said.
[GUSTAV]
So those are the riders carrying
the grim reaper, eh?
Supposedly, they have
a powerful Knight
with them, as well.
But I doubt they'll
prove a challenge.
After today, I,
Gustav Mardonnes,
will be known as the man
who conquered death.
[SOLDIER 9E] Captain D!
Two flying ships approaching!
Didn't think it
was possible, but,
I guess Ernie's not
the only person
who can make crazy
machines like that.
Pretty sure that crest
is Zaloudek, too.
That rules out any chance
that they're friendly.
Prepare for a
long-range assault, boys!
[DIETRICH] We shoot first.
Light up the sky!
I guess they're not intimidated
by the Levitate ships.
They might actually
be a challenge.
I'm sending out the
Silhouette Knights!
We'll finish them
with our blades!
[DIETRICH]
More of those copy-cat Mechs.
You Black Knights are nothing
but cowardly thieves.
I have no reason to fear you!
But you have every
reason to fear our wrath!
Prepare to meet your maker!
[PILOT 9I] He's totally
different than those
Kuschperchan training dummies!
[DIETRICH]
You blocked it. Not bad.
But no matter how
thick your armor,
it can't match a behemoth!
[PILOTS gasp]
[GUSTAV]
Get outta here, weaklings!
The glory for this
kill belongs to me!
[DIETRICH]
Wh-What the hell, man?
Think you have enough swords?
What's the point of that?
Why else would I
have this many?
Swords are strong!
Therefore, the more I have,
the stronger I'll be!
It's logic!
[DIETRICH] Oh, I get it.
You're just some massive idiot.
You have a nice
pair of blades, too.
But, they won't help!
None who face the
Swordsman survive!
He might be an idiot,
but he's got skill!
[GUSTAV laughs]
So slow! Come on!
You might as well
be standing still!
I'm already bored, so I
think I'll finish you off!
It does look like I'm
at a disadvantage here.
But you're all alone.
Sending your goons away
was a bad move.
Huh?
[HELVI yells]
[groans]
What, did you think all I did
was haul that carriage around?
Think again, creep!
Damn you! You'll pay for that!
[DIETRICH] Where'd that
smoke bomb come from?
[GUSTAV]
What are you trying to pull?
Till next time!
[DIETRICH]
Wait!
Shoot them down!
[GUSTAV] Hey, crimson!
You weren't half bad!
Honor demands a rematch,
so don't die until then!
[DIETRICH]
Those flying ships are cheating.
Not to mention a major problem.
If we'll be dealing
with them from now on,
Ernesti will have to make
an effective counter measure.
Ah!
[KERHILT] Never thought I'd
see Gustav the Sword-Lover
put up against a wall.
That smoke bomb
was you, wasn't it?
How long have you been here?
Couldn't say.
[GUSTAV]
I don't need help.
Oh? So that withdrawl
was strategic?
I'll thank you this time.
But it won't happen again.
[ERNESTI]
Next time: "War and Princess"!
The drums of war are calling me!