[car horn honks]
[GUY 1A]
We're changing the specs
this close to the deadline?
[KURATA]
Huh?
Those morons in sales
didn't even ask us!
I've already hit a hundred
hours of overtime
and I'm tapped out.
Hell, it's not like
we have a choice.
They got us by the balls.
Relax, guys,
I've got this covered.
[GUY 1A]
Huh?
[GUY 1B]
How you gonna do that?
Well, they did hire me
for my skills as a programmer.
Unfortunately,
we don't have enough time
to do the job the right way.
I'll just give it
the old college try.
[music plays]
[KURATA]
Oh my gosh!
A neutral grade
Mephisto Mark Two!
I didn't know it was out!
I can't believe they actually
carry the High Divine models
in a place like this! Nice!
[laughing]
[GUY 1C] I thought I'd
be looking for a new job.
Kurata's a freakin' wizard.
[GUY 1A] If by wizard
you mean nerd, then yes.
[GUY 1B]
Yeah, he's a mega otaku.
Apparently, he's filled a room
in his apartment
with plastic models.
[GUY 1A]
Like, girly models?
[GUY 1C]
No, like anime giant robots.
[GUY 1B]
I don't care if he's an otaku!
Mr. Kurata's my hero!
His programming's
the stuff of legend!
[GUY 1C]
Well, he's a genius.
[car horn honks]
[crosswalk beeping]
[car engine revs]
[KURATA]
So, the models I bought today,
the pile I have at home,
and the ones that
will come after this.
I'll never get to build them.
This isn't fair!
[BIRD caws]
♪
How is His Highness
faring these days, Father?
Well, I hope.
King Ambrosius is
as healthy as ever, dear.
Keeping his strength is
part of his duty, after all.
The prosperity of our fair
Fremmevilla hinges on his might.
And, with the ever-rising
threat of demon beasts,
that might will soon be tested.
I think he knows it, too.
He just presented the Knight
Runners of Laihiala Academy
with a large sum of money
and a rather splendid speech.
It's his way of telling us
to raise more Knight Runners,
and do it quickly.
That husband of yours
will have his hands full.
[SELESTINA] There's no need
to worry about Mathias, Father.
[gasps]
[LAURI] Perhaps not,
but I can't help worrying
about my grandson there.
I can understand that.
Ernesti isn't as developed
as the other boys
his age. He's small.
But I can't shake the feeling
that he's destined
for greatness.
[BOTH gasp]
Ah!
[hollers]
[LAURI grunts]
Curse your wretched kind!
[grunting]
[LAURI yells]
[LAURI grunts]
[gasps]
Ernie, no!
Ernie!
[guttural exhale]
[ERNESTI gasps]
[KURATA]
No way. Is that...?
[ERNESTI]
A robot?
[MATHIAS]
Stay back! We'll handle this!
[LAURI]
That sounded like Mathias!
[MATHIAS grunting]
[MATHIAS groans]
[grunting]
[MATHIAS yells]
[MATHIAS grunting]
[yells]
[grunting]
[ERNESTI gasps]
[MATHIAS] Looks like
no one's worse for wear.
Yes, thanks to your
impeccable timing.
[MATHIAS] I heard demon beasts
were attacking the road.
Sorry, I came
as fast as I could.
[gasps]
[MATHIAS]
Ernie! Are you okay?
[ERNESTI]
A real robot!
What's a robot?
Do you mean
the Silhouette Knight?
Is that what
you call this thing?
[MATHIAS] Uh-huh. Each one
is powered by magic.
[LAURI]
Do you like it, my boy?
When you're older,
perhaps you could be
a Knight Runner yourself!
[ERNESTI]
Amazing.
So, if I become
a Knight Runner,
I can pilot a Silhouette Knight?
You would have to learn
magic and swordsmanship.
But, I know you can do it.
[KURATA] I get it. I was reborn
into this world for this.
To meet these
magnificent robots!
I'll do it! I'll be
the best Knight Runner ever!
[SELESTINA]
It is the Occidental Year 1268.
The Kingdom of Fremmevilla
is constantly under threat
by roaming demon beasts.
Our story begins near
the capital of Kankkunen
in the Academy City of Laihiala,
where young Ernesti
starts his journey.
[SELESTINA] The slow, repetitive
training and constant study
that most children would despise
was no problem for Ernesti.
Instead, he immersed himself.
For him, every lesson
learned was another step
towards piloting
a Silhouette Knight.
[ERNESTI] I'll add emission
and enhancement spells
to the basic
wind spell structure.
And execute!
[ERNESTI] I see! Magic works
the same way that programs do.
[gasps]
[SELESTINA] The next three years
passed in the blink of an eye.
[ADELTRUD] You're so slow, kid!
They're going to find us!
[ARCHID]
Don't be in such a hurry!
[ADELTRUD] He's supposed to
be here in the morning.
I don't want to see him!
But Mom really wants us
to meet him. What's up?
He's not my father!
And he never will be.
Noble, or not!
But he is a noble. We have to.
Fine, then you can stay here.
Nah. Someone's got to watch you.
Hey! Don't say it like th--
Addy!
[ADELTRUD screams]
[ADELTRUD]
You saved me!
You're welcome. My name's
Ernesti, by the way.
Wait, you're a boy?
You're lucky
I was training here.
Be careful, the rooftops are
slippery in the morning. Bye.
Hold on! If it's so dangerous,
why are you up here?
Suspicious! Also, I refuse
to believe a boy's that cute!
[SELESTINA] This was Ernesti's
first meeting with his
future lifelong friends,
Archid and Adeltrud.
You used magic, didn't you?
Do you think you could
teach us some, too?
Spell-craft isn't something
you can just pick up.
First, you have to develop
your mana, or "magic power,"
and that takes lots of training.
I'll do it!
If you're serious about it,
I don't mind teaching you,
but it will be tough.
So cute! Listen to you,
sounding all reliable!
Mistress! I found them, ma'am!
They're on the roof!
--Uh oh.
--We'd better go.
See you tomorrow morning?
Sure.
[SELESTINA]
Ernesti's hometown, Laihiala,
had a singular purpose within
the Kingdom of Fremmevilla.
To train the Knight Runners,
and produce the Silhouette
Knights they would pilot.
Of course, Ernesti's dream
was to become a pilot himself.
So, when the time was right,
he joined the academy.
[TEACHER 1A]
In those booklets,
you'll find a comprehensive
guide to all of your classes.
Please find the section marked
"Elementary School" and--
Fundamentals Silhouette Design?
I can't wait to take that class!
Mr. Echevalier.
That course is for
middle school students.
For now, we'll be focusing on
the development
of your magic power.
I understand that, sir.
The thing is,
I want to be a Knight Runner
as soon as possible!
Unfortunately, there are two
fundamentals you sorely lack.
A complete knowledge
of the basics, and stature.
C'mon, Ernie.
Try not to let it get to you.
Of course, the seats
would be designed
for full-grown adults.
I should have realized that.
I need to get big, and fast!
No way! You have to stay
cute and small forever!
Unless there's another way.
[gasps]
That's it!
If I can't change myself,
I'll change the
Silhouette Knights instead!
[BOTH]
What do you mean?
I'll just build one
that I can fit in!
--I think he's gone crazy.
--Build a Knight?
Of course, why wouldn't I?
Customizing's the best part!
Though, if we're talking
a redesign from the ground up,
that makes having
a complete understanding
of the design
principles crucial.
I need to get out
of that magic class
and into middle school
courses pronto!
[BOY 1A]
Na-na-na-na-naa-naaah!
--[BOY 1C] Hurry up, stumpy!
--[BOY 1A] Come get it!
[BATSON] You'll be sorry
when I catch you!
Give it back!
[BOY 1A, BOY 1B laugh]
This hammers too good
for a dirty dwarf!
It's ours now!
Guess you're
out of luck, freak!
Hey, what's going on?
They think that they can
get away with picking on me
because my legs are too short
to keep up with them.
Those dumb jerks!
I saved up for months
to afford that hammer!
They can't have it!
Wait a second!
[ERNESTI] Sorry. I was
wondering what you study here.
You kidding? I'm a dwarf,
what do you think
I'm gonna study?
My family's been
Knightsmiths for generations!
Please, forgive my ignorance.
I happen to have
a great deal of respect
for anyone involved with
Silhouette Knights.
If you're interested, I think
I can help you out here.
[PEOPLE chattering]
[BOY 1A, 1B, 1C]
♪ Batson's a slow poke! ♪
♪ His brains are
full of egg yolk! ♪
When I get my hands of them...
Let's do it, you two.
[BOTH]
Okay!
[ALL]
Aero Batson! Ready. Fire!
[BATSON yells]
[BOY 1A, 1B, 1C groan]
Okay, who the heck are you guys?
And how did you learn
a high spell like that?
[BATSON] Hold on. This kid
mastered the fundamentals
on his own and taught you two?
Yup! Impressive, isn't it?
[ERNESTI]
Hmmm.
Don't you think these rods
are a little awkward?
[ARCHID, BATSON, ADELTRUD]
Huh?
I understand why we need
to attach this catalyst
to a device in order to focus
and transform our mana.
A rod is the most practical form
to produce magical phenomena.
But I can't help thinking
the design is missing something.
[BATSON]
Looks like you've used it a lot.
But only for the usual stuff.
[BATSON]
Usual?
My point is, Knight Runners
face times when
a more precise control
of magic is needed.
Maybe changing the shape
of the basic rod
could accomplish that. May I?
Something like this.
--I don't get it.
--Yeah, looks weird.
This would give the rod
more utility.
It combines the power
of a sword to cut enemies
with a gun that fires magic.
Uh? Interestin' idea
you got there, kid.
I like it.
If you can try
to make one for me,
I'll show you what it can do.
Hell, with confidence like that
I'd be crazy to say no, right?
Fireball blast!
Seems we have some talent
in this year's batch,
wouldn't you say?
T'would seem so.
Of course, the problem
with talented students
is that some of them
are painfully aware of it.
'Scuse me! May I
make a request, sir?
Yes, what is it, Echevalier?
If I showed that
my current skills
are far beyond
the contents of this course,
could I skip magic
fundamentals and go
straight to middle school?
Young man, I highly
doubt you could produce
such fantastic results.
Then, allow me
to prove it to you, sir.
If I do, there's a class
during this period
I'd like to switch to.
[TEACHER 1A] Being the
headmaster's grandson
doesn't give you the right
to special treatment.
[ERNESTI]
I don't want any.
I'd like you to
make the decision based
solely off my abilities.
[TEACHER 1A] You do
understand that being excused
from Magical Fundamentals
would mean you possess
the same level of mana
and knowledge
as a middle school student?
I do, sir.
Very well. We'll see
why you're so confident.
Take your position.
[ALL gasp]
--[BOY 1A] What is that?
--[GIRL 1A] A rod?
[BOY 1A]
Looks weird.
First, a Piercing Lance.
Followed by a full-powered
Thundering Gale!
[ALL gasp]
He did it!
--[ARCHID] Yeah!
--[ADELTRUD laughs]
Did I meet the requirement?
If so, could I
be excused, please?
[SELESTINA]
By the end of the day,
the rumor that
an elementary school student
had performed a high spell
and was granted the right
to take middle school courses
had spread throughout
the entire academy.
However, no one could have
known that this was
merely the first of
many steps Ernesti would take
toward his destiny
of changing the kingdom,
and the world, forever.
[BATSON] The structure
of an Ether Reactor?
[ERNESTI] Yes. What they call
a magical energy transformer.
It's the engine that forms the
core of a Silhouette Knight,
or it's "heart."
Without an understanding of it,
there's no way you could be
a master of a Silouette Knight.
[BATSON] Well, yeah.
Why do you think the design
is a national secret?
[ERNESTI] Even a
Knightsmith like your father
doesn't know it?
[BATSON] We're not high enough
level for that kind of stuff.
We don't even know
what the reactor's made of,
--let alone how to build one.
--[ERNESTI] Mmm.
Are you really planning
to make your own unit
from scratch, Ernie?
Of course I am!
[BATSON] It's been a hundred
years since the Kingdom's
standard Silhouette Knight,
the Kaldatoah, was introduced.
And there have been
no advancements since then!
Even the Solodreahs
we use are made from
300-year-old schematics.
You can't make something new
and expect it to--
Don't worry. It will work.
Ernie! Get down here quick,
we're about to head out!
We'll talk more when I get back.
Be careful out there.
Even with the
high school's protection,
a demon beast
is nothing to sneeze at.
♪
[SELESTINA] Laihiala Academy
prizes field exercises
and combat training.
The middle and
high school students
in the Knight curriculum
headed to a nearby forest,
where a herd of relatively
small demon beasts
were supposed to live.
[DIETRICH sigh]
I was expecting demon beasts,
not a pleasant country stroll.
I wasn't trained
to fight boredom.
Quit your whining, D.
I'd like to keep my sanity.
[DIETRICH] Hey, what's wrong
with telling the truth?
[EDGAR]
Helvi, D! Enough!
There's more
to training than combat.
Long stretches of marching
will test your resolve
as much as any battle.
[DIETRICH] Spoken like a true
masochist, fearless leader.
At least one of us is happy.
[ARCHID]
Mm-mmm! That was perfect!
I'm stuffed!
I hope so.
You ate like a wild boar.
[STEFANIA]
You've already finished dinner?
You must have had
quite the appetite.
--Uh. Hi, Sister Stefa--
--Council President.
[STEFANIA]
"Big Sister" will do fine.
We may have different mothers,
but our father's blood
still runs through each of us.
I take it you're
the gifted Ernesti
I've heard so much about?
--Yes?
--[ADELTRUD] Uh?
[STEFANIA] Don't be surprised.
Everyone at the academy's
heard of you.
Though, I'm not sure why
you want to advance
in grade so quickly.
What about the Silhouette
Knights is so enticing?
[ERNESTI] That would take
a while to explain.
You're a little on the
eccentric side, aren't you?
Big Sis. It's not weird!
[STEFANIA]
I didn't mean anything by it.
I simply have
a fondness for kids
with looks and intelligence.
[ADELTRUD]
Uuh!
[STEFANIA] Sadly, the third-
years have night training,
so I must be off.
I hope, someday, I'll truly
get to know your mind.
[yells]
[STEFANIA giggles]
--[ADELTRUD] Hmm!
--[ARCHID] Sorry, Ernie.
Guess I hoped this
would never come up,
so I kept it from you.
The council president's dad,
Marquis Joachim Selati,
happens to be our dad, too.
He and our mom had a thing,
but she isn't a noble,
so they couldn't marry.
Which means Addy and I...
well, we're...
Excluded from the line
of noble succession, right?
I understand the situation.
Just tell me
what you need me to do.
"To do"?
Attack head on? Ignore her?
Or, ambush her at night?
Ambush. It's safer.
Wait! None of those!
Where'd that even come from?
If my friends are in trouble,
I have no intention
of ignoring that.
Whenever you need help,
I'll be there.
[gasps]
That really means a lot.
You're a hell of
a friend, Ernie.
[gasps, giggles]
Giant robots
really are the best!
Merely looking at it
brings me peace.
Every family should have one!
I heard that the academy's
Silhouette Knights
were passed down
from the military,
but this one's undergone
some extensive customization.
You almost can't tell
it started out as a Solodreah!
[EDGAR] The Earlcumber and I
have been together
for nearly two years.
I've made a few special
modifications myself.
[ERNESTI]
Good to see you, Edgar.
Are you going out on patrol
tonight all by yourself?
Uh-huh. My partner,
Dietrich's, being difficult.
You seem almost
as passionate about
Silhouette Knights as I am.
Really? I guess I can see
why you would think that.
It's important to me.
Earlcumber isn't just my weapon.
It's my armor.
My irreplaceable partner.
I'm so envious!
I wish I could speed up time
and get a partner of my own.
[EDGAR]
Well, wanna hop in?
[ERNESTI gasps]
[EDGAR]
I can't let you pilot it,
but you can sit in it.
Ooh! Yes, please!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[gasps, laughs]
[EDGAR] I figured you
wouldn't reach the stirrup.
--[ERNESTI gasps]
--Are you okay?
[ERNESTI]
Great! Better than great!
I'm actually sitting in a robot!
What's a robot?
I've never heard of it.
What every man dreams of!
[MONSTERS chattering]
[alarm rings]
Addy, wake up!
Aww. Thanks, Ernie.
[ERNESTI]
What are you doing?
A large group of demon beasts
attacked the third-years
during their night exercises.
We're getting out of here!
First and second years,
leave your things
and get in the
transports immediately!
High school students,
advance in your
Silhouette Knights
and cover their retreat!
[DIETRICH grunts]
Hm.
[horse neighs]
We'll make it out
of here alive, won't we?
There's no way to know.
My uncle died
in this same situation.
[TEACHER 1A]
No talking!
I hope Big Sis is okay.
Stefania.
Go! We're all in!
[ERNESTI]
Sir!
--[ERNESTI] I have a request!
--[hollers]
And I thought this night
couldn't get any worse.
[STEFANIA grunts]
[MONSTER roars]
[BOY 1E]
Help me!
--[GIRL 1C grunts]
--[MONSTER 1B roars]
[STEFANIA] Why are there
so many beasts here?
[MONSTERS grunting]
[gasps]
[roars]
[ERNESTI yells]
[MONSTER 1C groans]
Is that Ernesti?
--[ARCHID] You okay, President?
--Don't worry!
[BOTH]
We'll handle this!
[ARCHID]
Sonic Blade!
Riot Sparrow!
[MONSTERS roar]
My siblings. You came for me.
Yeah and we brought
the big guns with us!
Sorry we're late!
Now, let the pros go to work!
Guair! Do your thing!
[MONSTERS roaring]
[GIRL 1E, GIRL 1D gasp]
[EDGAR]
Move to a safe distance!
Helvi, clear a path
for them to retreat!
[HELVI]
Hear that, Trandorkis? Our turn!
[ERNESTI] It's strange.
There shouldn't be
this many demon beasts.
Something's off.
[MONSTERS chattering]
[panting]
Don't think you'll get through
without paying a price.
Damn monster!
[BIG MONSTER roars]
I have a bad feeling about this.
[ERNESTI]
Next time: "Hero &amp; Beast"!
The behemoth is calling me!