Everyone, run for cover!
[BOTH yelp]
[ERNESTI]
A giant weapon
modeled after the ancient
drake demon beast.
I'm surprised Zaloudek
would make something
so unorthodox.
I found you, Demon!
The Vyver will put you down
once and for all!
Prince Cristobal will
finally be avenged!
[ERNESTI] We officially have
a problem here! Crap!
[ARCHID] This is when we
put forth our best effort!
[GUSTAV]
'Kay. Was not expecting that.
[ERNESTI]
Come on!
[grunts] A new enemy weapon?
[SOLDIER 9E]
Captain D, look!
[DIETRICH gasps]
[GUSTAV] Here I thought
it would just be infantry.
But instead, I find my old
friend, the Crimson Twin-sword.
How about that?
Of all the people,
it had to be you.
Bring it!
[TOWNSPEOPLE screaming]
Please, don't panic!
We'll get you out safe!
Addy! We'll handle
the civilians!
The Silhouette Gears
are better suited to it.
Thanks, Nora! You're the best.
Ernie...
Anti-air! Don't let it near us!
A Defensive Lightning
Field? No way!
Come on!
[gasps]
They embedded a Silhouette
Knight into their battleship.
That totally destroys
the aesthetic!
Now you've made me really angry!
I won't let this violation
stand! Prepare yourselves!
He thinks he can
close the distance.
Make him pay!
[gasps]
[ERNESTI]
I see.
It's maneuverable and can
attack at close-range.
You certainly made it authentic.
Well, only a knight
can take down a dragon!
Yes, that's right, Demon.
Give it all you've got.
I'll avenge the prince
and remove Zaloudek's
greatest threat
in one fell swoop.
You're quite the powerful foe.
Good. A challenge.
It'll be more satisfying
when I beat you!
[DIETRICH growls]
[laughs]
[OFFICER 10A]
You bastards won't get past us!
I'd like to see you stop us!
It'll be entertaining!
[DIETRICH pants]
Things got chaotic.
[GUSTAV]
Hey! Pay attention!
This is a deadly duel!
One walks away!
[DIETRICH grunts]
[GUSTAV] I'm just starting.
Plenty of swords left!
Disgraceful!
Don't toss them aside--
they're part of you!
I'll pick 'em up later!
But you won't be
around to see it!
You'll be six feet under!
[DIETRICH]
We'll see about that. Kamasa!
[GUSTAV]
Uh--
He dodged it?
[GUSTAV yells]
Bye-bye!
I get it now.
That's what the
Ether Supplier's for.
That burst of power
completely overwhelmed me!
Oh, scared now?
We're just getting
started, Twinswords!
That's right! Struggle, Demon!
I finally caught up.
Misshire Javelin, fire!
The Knight's flying spears!
Lightning Field!
Shoot them down!
[DOLOTEO grunts]
[SOLDIER 12A]
Damage to lower port side!
Dammit! Send repair crews!
I need to know the extent of it!
Uh, sir!
What?!
You're wide open!
[ERNESTI]
Rough Fist! Engage!
[SOLDIER 12C]
What the hell?
[ERNESTI]
Gotcha!
Damn! All crew, strap in!
Spin the ship, full force!
[ERNESTI] Whoa! I can't
hold on much longer.
Bring that thing down!
Impressive.
This'll be even tougher
than I thought. Round two!
[KOJASS]
It's such a lovely day.
A shame I'm stuck here
instead of in the middle
of the action with
my beautiful Vyver.
I wonder, Ernesti Echevalier.
How will you try
to fight my creation?
You got me all fired up.
I can't remember a fight
that really challenged me.
This is your last chance.
Run while you still can!
You're joking, right?
I'd rather die than turn
my back on the likes of you!
Coward I used to be
is long gone!
Lightning Flail!
What's that?
[screams]
'Kay. Was not expecting that.
[GUSTAV grunts]
[yells]
Tests of strength don't
really do it for me.
Back off!
[grunts] Not happening!
Damn you, just die!
Goodbye, Twinswords!
[laughs]
[GUSTAV]
What?
The Ether Supplier
just crapped out!
I forgot! If I use
the reactor too much...
...it deteriorates
and shuts down.
Ernesti was right.
It's a double-edged sword.
I thought if I pushed you,
it might do you in.
It was a one in a million shot,
but looks like it paid off.
Oh, shut up!
That's it.
The Guairlinde is
too damaged to move.
C'mon, guys.
Give me some kinda sign
that you're all right.
[roaring]
Ernesti!
[SOLDIER 12A] Now Ankyurosa 2
has run out of mana!
Ugh! We have 13
of the damn things
and we've already
lost three of them.
Even with our extensive mana
pool, he chips away at us.
Maybe this creature
truly is a Demon.
[KOJASS]
If I had to guess.
It's about time to use
your trump card, General.
Wouldn't you agree?
Load the special
shells and fire!
A smokescreen won't save you!
[gasps]
[KOJASS]
Well, Demon?
How do you like my special
blend of metal fragments,
saltpeter, and sulfur powder?
What did you call it?
The Magius Engine Jet Thruster?
What will happen if it sucks
in enough of that smoke?
[KOJASS]
It may not destroy it outright,
but it will certainly damage
the Emblem Graph that runs it.
And once that happens,
the Demon's wings are clipped.
'Kay. We officially
have a problem here!
Crap!
Ernie!
Initiate the flame!
This is our chance!
Burn in hell, Demon!
[ERNESTI]
Not today!
Bastard. Won't go down
that easily, huh?
Fine by me!
You want another one?
They're evenly matched.
[ARCHID]
Ernie!
[DOLOTEO]
What? How is he still standing?
General! Our mana
pool is too low!
Another shot like that and
we won't remain airborne!
[gasps]
[DOLOTEO]
That's the withdrawal signal!
But, who?
[GUSTAV] It's time to go,
old man. Pull back!
[growls] Get us out of here!
They're really letting us go?
No. I bet they ran low
on mana and had to retreat.
I'm impressed they
managed to disable
Ikaruga's Jet
Thruster like that.
But that's the last
time it's gonna happen!
They look really
beat up. Don't they?
[SELESTINA] The battle between
Ernesti and the battleship Vyver
ended in a tie.
But the Kuschperchans
were so shaken,
it felt like a defeat.
It was the first time
the Order of the Silver Phoenix
had ever experienced failure.
You got too crazy with it.
The frame is a total mess now.
There's nothing we can do here.
We'll just have to
send it back home.
What will you do?
Switch to another one?
[DOLOTEO]
Horatio Kojass.
Born to a family that
researches ancient techniques.
He fled, betraying
them and taking the
Pure Ether Operation Theory with
him. Hardly sounds trustworthy.
[KOJASS grunting]
Lord Kojass.
[KOJASS]
General.
If I'd known you were coming,
I'd have tidied up.
Oh.
Congratulations on a
successful counterattack.
You must be very proud.
"Successful"?
The Demon is alive, and the
prince remains unavenged.
What exactly are you working on?
[KOJASS]
Just what it looks like.
Something new for the Vyver,
so your next "success"
will feel like one.
[DOLOTEO] And here I
thought you didn't like
to get your hands dirty.
[KOJASS]
As they say,
"If you want it done right,
do it yourself."
Is this some kind of
massive Ether Reactor?
I didn't think they
could get this big.
[KOJASS] Very observant.
I call it the "Blood Grail."
It's specifically designed
for high-density ether.
Though it's still a prototype.
Thirteen reactors
linked together
couldn't stop that monster,
so I had to do something.
You think this will
be the difference?
Turn this on, and you'll
command a power
that will make the Demon look
like an insignificant flea.
In theory.
[DOLOTEO]
Tch.
[KOJASS] But, even if it
does work as intended,
the power will be
a double-edged sword.
Once it starts to go
out of control,
nobody can stop it.
[gasps]
Again, just in theory.
Does that scare you?
Will you refuse it?
But I went to all the
trouble of putting it in.
I even have blisters.
[DOLOTEO]
Don't worry.
If it'll kill the Demon,
I'll master it.
[KOJASS] That's what I
wanted to hear, General.
Oh, right.
Equipment this delicate will
need to be monitored so,
I'll be coming along
for the next battle.
Really?
You know how Knights
speak with their swords?
Well, General, Engineers
speak with their creations.
I can't wait.
What kind of conversation
will we have?
Ernesti Echevalier.
[CATARINA] New supplies
have arrived from home.
Your behavior aside,
it's a loss to my army
not to have a knight of your
caliber on the battlefield.
It's nice to know
I'm appreciated.
But, my Swordman is scap
and I don't have a spare.
Not a problem.
[GUSTAV]
No way!
The royal Silhouette
Knight, the Alkeloryx.
The best unit in all Zaloudek.
Brother Carlitos
sent it from home.
But it won't do any
good without a pilot.
Use it as you see fit.
Really?! Thank you, Majesty!
When I'm done, the Demon
and his friends'll be in
so many pieces, the grim reaper
won't know what to do!
Reports indicate that
the first fortress
has fallen once again.
The third fortress, as well.
They're pushing too fast.
We can't keep the
ground we took.
So, this "Drake" unit.
Did it really give you
that much trouble?
Yes.
It's something entirely
different than a Levitate ship
or Silhouette Knight.
We should consider it
a new category of weapon.
Can you defeat it?
Our first battle was a tie,
but they're likely
to improve the design.
I would, and did.
I equipped the
Magius Jet Thruster
with a protective filter
that should mitigate
the effect of their
smoke shells.
They won't clip my wings twice.
But that isn't what you asked,
and to be perfectly honest,
I doubt the Ikaruga could
beat it the way it is now.
You seem oddly calm
about that, Ernie.
What's Zaloudek's next move?
[ERNESTI]
More of the same.
Their basic tactic will be
an assault from the air,
using the drake
and their airships.
The only ones who can
fight this, I'm afraid,
are my Ikaruga and the
Order of the Silver Phoenix.
All right.
We'll form a unit around
Ikaruga and counterattack.
Hopefully it's enough.
There is a chance the
drake won't show up,
in which case...
[HELVI] ...we'll have
committed our entire force,
and left the
homeland defenseless.
This war will be over quickly
if our base is destroyed.
Then we'll strengthen
our defenses.
[ADELTRUD]
Won't that just cause the enemy
to throw everything
they have at us?
[DIETRICH]
Yeah, and they just received
fresh supplies and soldiers.
I'd like to avoid a mass battle.
We don't have the
numbers to survive it.
So, is there any way
to strengthen the defenses
and take out the drake
at the same time?
--[DAVID] You idiot!
--Sorry!
As it stands, we don't
have a way to do that.
The point of the meeting
is solving this problem.
Didn't hafta hit me.
[NOBLE 9B]
Hm.
Damned if we do,
damned if we don't, huh?
[ELEONORA]
Not quite.
[GROUP]
Huh?
There is an option
no one has considered.
If the enemy is afraid
of another confrontation
with Ernesti, then...
...we should give them that
by attacking Delvancul head on.
But, Your Highness!
We can't!
You'll be left here without
a single Knight to protect you!
I wouldn't want my top
advisors worried about me.
So I'll go with you.
We'll take our full army
and the Order of the
Silver Phoenix as well.
They won't be expecting it,
that's for sure.
I know I wouldn't!
I'm through with this
constant back and forth.
Enough Knights have died for us.
Enough people have suffered
at the hands of Zaloudek.
For Kuschpercha, we'll take
back our capital, at last.
[laughs]
[ELEONORA]
My brave Knights of Kuschpercha,
these past months
have been fraught
with trials and tribulations
no nation should face.
[ELEONORA] We lost our
beloved capital to a country
of cowardly invaders.
We've lost our loved ones.
And still, we're in danger
of losing even more.
But we will rise again.
Through our own efforts,
and through the power
of our newfound friends.
Instead of letting that
night of tragedies haunt us,
we will use it as fuel.
We will retake our capital,
and avenge the fallen!
As queen,
I swear Kuschpercha will be
whole and at peace once more!
But before that peace comes,
we will remove the
invaders from our home,
and make sure they never return!
All forces, to victory!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[SOLDIERS]
To victory!
Stirring speech! Nicely done.
Do you really think so?
Yes! Being queen suits you well.
You're doing a
great job, Highness.
Don't be so formal.
It's weird having my
family call me "Highness."
You better get used
to it, and quickly.
Things have changed.
We can't go back
to how they were.
[ELEONORA]
Ernesti.
Yes, Your Highness?
What can I do for you?
As Queen of Kuschpercha,
I feel I must apologize.
You're our guests, and yet
we entrust so much to you.
I regret that
more than anything.
Please, think nothing of it.
I have my reasons for
being in this fight.
Let's just say
our interests align
and leave it at that, all right?
He's right, Elly.
Don't apologize--
you might spoil him.
Next thing you know,
he'll ask for all
your mechs and castles.
Gee, thanks a lot, Highness.
That wasn't very nice!
Yeah, but it's true!
[laughs]
[ALL laugh]
[SELESTINA] The Kuschperchan
army made their move
with haste. The goal of
the operation was to down
the drake battleship and retake
the old capital of Delvancul.
Their momentum fully restored,
they pressed on until reaching
Shilda Neryaku Fortress,
the last obstacle keeping
them from their goal.
There, they encountered
Zaloudek's army.
[HELVI]
The enemy airships are here!
Misshire Javelins. Fire!
You have your orders!
Defend the queen at all costs!
Don't let a single
enemy get through!
Show them once and for all
why the first company
of the Silver Phoenix
is known as the Shield!
[EMRYS]
Knights! Fight hard!
When those drawbridges come
down, this battle is ours!
Then it's a straight shot
home to Delvancul!
[NORA] I never expected
to go on a mission
with you, Captain Cunitz.
It is an honor.
[DIETRICH] Thanks, but it's
not that big a deal.
I just happen know my way
around a Silhouette Gear.
Our friends are counting on us.
Success here is paramount.
Right.
Let's open the door
for them, shall we?
[LETONMAKI] The resistance
is greater than expected.
Perhaps if we punched
a hole through this line...
[gasps] Majesty! Look up there!
So that's it. The Drake.
Ah.
How kind of the
queen to come to us.
Burn her to cinders in
front of her entire army!
Oh, my! As I live and breathe.
The Demon's here.
And he's gone
through some changes.
Rather odd, that.
I'm not sure what it is.
[KOJASS]
I see now. You plagiarist.
How's my Levitate Ship
working out, I wonder?
[DAVID]
Ya know, for a second there,
I didn't think we'd have
this thing ready in time.
Never underestimate the
ingenuity of a dwarf!
Is it too late to turn around?
I really don't wanna be here.
[ARCHID]
What do you mean, Batson?
This is when we put forth
our best effort!
I'm so excited, I'm shaking.
Let's do this!
[ADELTRUD]
Do what exactly?
We're the glorified
engine for this thing.
We're kinda stuck here.
What's important
is how you feel!
[ERNESTI] When I first saw
airships, I knew a design
like the Drake
wasn't far behind.
Sorry. I can't allow
you to exist.
If I don't defeat you,
this world will trend
toward larger weapons.
With each re-design,
the airships
will slowly become battleships.
If that happens,
the robots I love
more than anything
will become obsolete
or completely forgotten.
No way.
Not while I'm alive and kicking.
I'll destroy that outcome
so that robots are the future!
[KOJASS] This should
prove quite interesting.
Vyver versus Demon.
Large versus small.
I wonder whose technology
will come out on top?
Only one way to
find out, Lord Kojass.
The time for talk is over.
Ikaruga and I are ready.
Let's end this!
[ERNESTI] Final episode:
"Heaven and Earth."
The big goodbye is calling me!