[CRISTOBAL] You found
that sniveling princess?
Then what are we waiting for?
[CATARINA]
Wait, brother. Sit this one out.
Let the soldiers handle it.
Not after what she's
put me through.
First, I'll destroy her,
then the rest of her army!
And I'll make the Silver
Phoenix watch as I do it!
[ERNESTI] ...will
automatically belong to us.
[CRISTOBAL] Wait! Is that
some kind of cruel joke?
[KOJASS]
Consider it a guarantee
from the true ruler
of the skies.
[SELESTINA]
Zaloudek's army moved swiftly.
Cristobal's forces,
composed of both
the Order of the Black Jaw
and Bronze Wing,
passed through Fontanie,
the land of the former
Duke Fernado, into Baron
Letonmaki's territory.
After brutally
destroying Fontanie,
Zaloudek closed in on Nishirie
and Princess Eleonora.
[CRISTOBAL]
It's so quiet.
Are those cowards just
quivering behind their walls?
I expected a fight.
[KOJASS]
The demon hasn't shown himself?
I'll be severely
disappointed if we came
all this way for nothing.
Please, my lord.
Don't stand so close.
The windows are vulnerable.
Is there any chance we could
lower altitude, helmsman?
I can barely make anything
out from up here.
Our only job here is escorting
Prince Cristobal, sir.
Unless we're told
to do otherwise...
We can't interfere
with the battle, I know.
But you'd better hope
it comes out soon.
I didn't make this trip
just to sightsee.
[CRISTOBAL] I think we've
given them plenty of time
to prepare for their deaths.
Begin the attack.
Sire!
Show time.
And what do we have here?
What?
There they are!
[ADELTRUD]
Plain as day!
[ADELTRUD, ARCHID] Anti-Air
Weapon, Misshire Javelin!
Fire!
[OFFICER 11A] Ships five
and seven are damaged!
They can't maintain altitude!
Spears can't reach this high!
How'd they do that?
[gasps] An impressive invention!
Jeez, they're heavy.
'Kay! You're good to go!
[ADELTRUD]
Have another helping, jerks!
[SOLDIER 11B]
We lost ship four!
[SOLDIER 11A]
Stay close to the flagship!
We must protect the prince!
So that's how you want
to play this game?
[OFFICER 11B]
Curse those Kuschperchan dogs
and their cowardly weapons!
Purge the Tyrantos! Quickly!
But, sir, the pilots
are still in them!
We're too high up!
If we can't get out of
range of those spears,
we're doomed! Lighten
the ship, damn you!
I've been waiting for
this moment, Zaloudek.
[EDGAR]
First company, open fire!
You're through. I won't
let you any further.
They were waiting.
It's a trap, and I
fell right into it.
They've made a fool of me!
[ERNESTI]
Looks like the Misshire Javelins
are working as
intended. Excellent.
And Edgar's company is
cleaning up their drop force
without any issues.
Time for me to add
the finishing touches.
[laughs]
[ERNESTI]
That's one! Who's next!
Look at him. Glad
I'm not those guys.
Yeah, no kidding.
Having a flying Silhouette
Knight almost feels unfair.
It's like we're adding
salt to a wound.
Stupid. This is just stupid!
Like some sort of
bad joke! Look at him!
Using explosive power
to fly through the air.
It's so... barbaric!
He trespasses on
my sky and mocks me?!
[SOLDIER 11D] Ships two and
three have taken heavy hits.
We've lost our formation!
Highness.
We should leave before
we lose any more ships!
[CRISTOBAL]
Stay your tongue!
If I retreat, my sister
won't let me live it down.
Now, contact the Order
of the Black Jaw.
Wipe out the town
and the princess!
Sire!
[OFFICER 11C]
Advance! Crush these rebel scum!
[EMRYS]
Scum?
You're the thugs killing
innocents for your own gain.
Mark my words, Zaloudek.
you'll pay for every
last one of 'em!
[PILOT 11A]
The Golden Silhouette Knight!
[OFFICER 11C] Calm down!
He just looks imposing!
[EMRYS]
Howling Blast!
[OFFICER 11C]
What is this?
Come on.
The prince can't
have all the fun!
Second company, move out!
Keep the momentum!
We're punching a hole
in their flank
and cutting off their advance!
[PILOT 11B]
We're surrounded!
There's no way
to get to Nishirie!
[ERNESTI] So there's
plenty of time to play!
[ERNESTI] A battle between
Silhouette Knights is sacred.
Let's enjoy it.
[PILOT 11B]
The demon!
[PILOT 11B yelps]
[OFFICER 11A]
Majesty! Our allies!
The Black Jaw.
They've...
They've been...
[CRISTOBAL]
Enough! Say it already!
Their forces have been routed!
We've lost this fight, sire!
Change course.
[OFFICER 11A]
At once.
Damn you, Reaper.
Follow the flagship! Quickly!
[SOLDIER 11B]
Yes, sir!
[KOJASS]
Belay that order.
[OFFICER 11D]
Lord?
[KOJASS] If we go now, we'll
just get in the prince's way.
Wait a moment. We'll catch up
once he's reached safety.
[ADELTRUD] Look! One of
their ships is fleeing!
[ARCHID]
Batson!
You're locked and loaded!
Let 'em have it, Kid!
You won't get away!
Blow Engines seven and
eleven are damaged, sir!
We're losing speed!
[OFFICER 11A]
It's the Demon!
[SOLDIERS scream]
Stop shaking like
a child, damn you.
There must be somebody
important on this ship.
Why else would you be
the first to turn tail
and run from the battle?
[CRISTOBAL]
Demon!
Setting foot on my ship
was your last mistake.
I am Cristobal, the
Second Prince of Zaloudek,
and I will be your doom!
You should be honored!
[ERNESTI]
My, my.
Back weapons and
close-quarters combat gear.
It looks like a
standard Telestale,
except you've made
the face look so noble!
I hope that's not all,
or you're in trouble.
[CRISTOBAL]
Shut your mouth!
Damn you!
[CRISTOBAL gasps]
No way.
I'm giving it my all,
and he shrugs it off
like I'm just an insect!
[CRISTOBAL]
Wait. Demon Knight. Join me!
You're from Fremmevilla, right?
You have no real
ties to Kuschpercha.
Why fight for them?!
Come to Zaloudek and I
will give you more power
and wealth than you've
ever dreamed of!
It may not look it,
but I've got a pretty great
compensation package already.
[CRISTOBAL] Do you not
understand what I said?
As second prince and commander
of Zaloudek's armies,
I can give you whatever
your heart desires!
Just name it,
and it will be yours!
You want to be a noble?
Just say the word.
In that case, sure!
But let me clarify
something first.
Does that mean, if I ask for
the full rights to design
and export your nation's
Silhouette Knights,
as well as priority
command over your army,
you'll give it to me?
'Cause, I want that.
Wait! Is that some
kind cruel joke?
[ERNESTI]
Huh? It's no joke, I'm serious.
I'm actually a representative
of Fremmevilla's king,
and I have full authority
regarding development
and manufacturing.
I handled most of the
basic development and design
of every Silhouette
Knight you've fought
and are currently piloting.
I'm also free to alter
export arrangements,
but it's a pain,
so I don't bother.
In times of necessity,
my orders can be prioritized
over the king himself,
so, as you can see,
I have a pretty
sweet setup here.
Oh!
And I'm not interested
in noble titles,
so I'll pass on that offer.
You bastard.
How dare you lie
to me like that!
I'm Cristobal, son of the
king, you sniveling brat!
Lie? I'm not!
I swear, everything I've
said is the truth.
Can you get out of your
Silhouette Knight, please?
If you do, I promise
you won't be harmed.
But I will take the mech.
Damn you. Damn you!
[CRISTOBAL cackles]
[CRISTOBAL] Did you think
I'd beg for my life
to the likes of you?
[CRISTOBAL cackles]
Guess again!
I won't give you the
satisfaction, you Devil!
[CRISTOBAL]
Mark my words. You'll pay!
And when you do,
I'll see you in hell!
He went down with
his ship and his mech.
Amazing resolve.
The flagship is in pieces.
Is his highness...?
He died in service to Zaloudek.
We should leave now, lest his
sacrifice be in vain.
All ships, leave
the combat area!
[KOJASS]
Using explosions as propulsion.
Such a crude way
of attaining flight.
Makes me wonder what type
of person would make it.
I suppose that I'll have to
find out for myself, won't I?
I'm back! Did you miss me?
[ALL gasp]
You're okay! Thank goodness!
I take it you and your friends
were victorious, Emrys?
Duh!
Those losers didn't
know what hit 'em.
They'll think twice
before attackin' again.
Thank you. You've saved us all.
Sir Knight? Were you hurt?
This? Just a bruise.
Nothing more.
Yup!
He was so eager to protect you,
that he got his Mech's foot
caught and bumped his head.
Addy!
So, sweet.
He was probably
trying to show off
for our beloved princess.
[GROUP laughs]
Uh... Lady Eleonora?
[gasps] It's nothing.
I'm just glad you're
all back home safely.
[CATARINA]
Cristobal... is dead?
I understand your rage
and I'm deeply sorry.
All of Zaloudek mourns with you.
If I wasn't a mere...
Oh, what do you call it?
"Non-combatant."
I would have saved him.
Even sacrificed my own
life if it meant
he would survive and
lead our people!
My regret will burden my soul
for as long as I live!
Please let me help you avenge
his death, Your Highness.
As a way to atone for
my failure. In fact,
I swear, here and now,
to not rest until this is done.
May I have your blessing?
Do whatever it takes.
Anything you say, Highness.
Consider it a guarantee
from the true ruler
of the skies.
[DOLOTEO]
The prince has been slain?
No!
[SELESTINA] The death
of Prince Cristobal sent
a shock wave through
the armies of Zaloudek.
The Orders of the
Black Jaw and Bronze Wing
were routed so badly,
they had no choice
but to fall back to Delvancul.
[SELESTINA] As a result,
the Kuschperchan remnant
was able to retake Fontanie,
the core of the east,
with almost no casualties.
[CROWD cheering]
[MAN 11B]
Princess Eleonora!
[MAN 11C]
Glory to Kuschpercha!
Are you ready?
No, honestly. I'm terrified.
The thought of all the good
people who might fight and die
because I gave an order
turns my stomach.
But then... I remember
all I've seen.
Like the courage of your Knights
as they stood up to conquerors.
The hefty hammer
that a dwarf must wield.
And the Kushperchan people,
desperate for a ruler
who will serve and
watch over them
the way my father did
until his dying breath.
I'm ready. I'll pick
up his mantle.
[gasps]
And I'll be with you
until the very end.
As your knight, and as
your friend, my queen.
[WOMAN 11A]
Queen Eleonora!
[ELEONORA] As Queen Eleonora
Miranda Kuschpercha,
I declare...
Our nation will not
be forgotten to history.
Instead, we will rebuild and
make it stronger than ever!
[CROWD cheers]
[SELESTINA]
It was the Western year of 1281.
The declaration of the
Founding at Queen Eleonora's
coronation forced the
Western Grand Storm
onto a new stage, and forever
changed the course of the war.
[BATSON] Want us to salvage
the next batch?
Yeah, that'd be great.
There's plenty of
material we could use.
What about the current batch?
D'you find anything interesting?
Uh-huh. A lot!
Like this little guy.
What the...?
The heck is that?
According to one of
the airship survivors,
it's Etherite! Crazy, huh?
A concentrated chunk of Ether.
Hold on.
Isn't that the stuff in
the air that gets absorbed
into the Ether Reactors?
Uh-huh! It's how we get Mana.
Zaloudek's forces are
using something different.
This device,
which they apparently
call an Ether Supplier,
can transform this Etherite
into high-density ether
at will for a sudden
burst of power!
That's an odd design.
[ERNESTI] In other words,
they can keep supplying fuel
without having to gather
it from the atmosphere.
This device is the reason
why the Tyranto units
are able to sustain
such incredible power
and seem to never
run out of mana.
It's incredible!
A true masterpiece!
You do realize this
is the enemy's, right?
[ERNESTI] Of course, it has its
share of short-comings, too.
Just look at this degradation.
The high-density ether really
does a number on the supplier.
So much, in fact,
that they designed it
as a replaceable part.
But the Ether Reactor--
it's... the most important part
of a Silhouette Knight.
Like it's heart.
And they're tossing them
after just one use?
I doubt it was designed
to be a permanent core.
It's likely they only use it
during emergency situations.
Like wartime.
The amount of materials
they go through
must be staggering.
Oh, yeah!
I also figured out how their
"levitate ships" fly!
A device called
the Etheric Levitator
uses the natural behavior of
ether itself to defy gravity,
and achieves momentum
using air magic.
An "Etheric Levitator."
Another brilliant
piece of technology.
The amount of ether it
needs to properly function
must be astronomical!
It had a ton of Ether
Suppliers attached to it!
Unfortunately, even
the crew weren't told
exactly how it works,
so I can't know for sure.
The only person
with that knowledge
is the levitator's inventor,
Horatio Kojass.
I'd love to meet him!
I bet we could learn all kinds
of stuff from each other.
[DAVID]
Jeez, kid.
You got enough of that fearless
optimism to go around?
Some folks around here
could use a pinch or two.
[BATSON]
I know I could.
Here, Sir Knight. Say "ah."
Hold on. Please, Your Majesty.
Stop, everyone is looking at us!
Come on. It's one little bite.
[ARCHID]
Uh--
Kid's turning red. How cute!
[ERNESTI] Sorry to keep
you waiting so long.
Uh-- What are you doing?
Uh. Nothing!
Perfect timing! Join us!
Hey, help me out here.
What do you need help with, man?
She is totally into you.
[MARTINA]
Never mind them, Ernesti.
We have some important
news to discuss.
[MARTINA]
It's going well.
All of our remaining forces have
regrouped here in Fontanie.
Thanks to you, of course.
Sadly, the enemy still
greatly outnumbers us,
and there's nothing we
can do to close that gap.
I know they belong to you
according to our contract,
but would you be
willing to give us
the remaining Silhouette
Knights you have claimed?
If we could rebuild them,
they'd be a boon to our forces.
I know we're asking
a lot of you, Ernie.
I don't have a problem with it.
Please, take whatever you need.
[BOTH gasp]
To be honest, it would
take way too long
to handle all those
Silhouette Knights
with the manpower we have.
If you're willing to help us
rebuild them, we'd be happy
to give you as many
as you need in return.
Beyond that, we'd be willing
to lend them to you
for the duration of the war,
and until Kuschpercha
is stabilized.
Does that sound like
a fair arrangement?
That's perfectly fine.
Thank you so much, Ernie.
We're grateful.
Okay then.
In that case, since
the Silhouette Knights
you'll be using
technically belong
to the Silver Phoenix,
any Silhouette Knights
you defeat with them
will automatically belong to us.
[BOTH gasp]
I was just joking! Really!
No, you weren't. Come on.
You're 100 percent serious.
This sucks.
Why don't we get to
have tea and cakes
with the royal family?
[DAVID] A Knightsmith
takes pride in working
in the background. Unnoticed.
Wait a minute,
David are you crying?
Crying is just sweat
of the heart.
[SELESTINA] With help from the
Order of the Silver Phoenix,
the army of the Reborn
Kuschperchan Kingdom devoted
all its energy to
expanding the military.
The Zaloudek, still
reeling from the loss
of the prince, lost their
momentum and the Kushperchans
began to push them back.
Several months passed.
[EDGAR]
This fortress now belongs
to the Reborn Kingdom
of Kushpercha!
Let 'em hear us in Zaloudek!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[HELVI] That was easier
to take than I expected.
[EDGAR]
Yeah.
The Kuschperchan Knights
are getting better.
I'm proud of them.
Do you think the
others are okay?
I don't have reason to worry.
Ernesti and D are with them.
They couldn't be safer.
[SOLDIERS] Long live the Queen!
Long live the Queen!
[ADELTRUD] Mission accomplished!
That was a breeze!
[ERNESTI] Yeah, but there wasn't
a need for me to do anything.
Not that that's bad,
of course. Just boring.
[DIETRICH]
No kidding.
I thought I would doze off
near the end, there.
The second company prides
itself on blitz attacks,
not slow advances.
[DIETRICH]
Is that... a Levitate ship?
[ADELTRUD]
A little late.
[ARCHID]
And it's alone.
[gasps] That's no ship.
Look closer!
Everyone, run for cover!
[BOTH yelp]
[ERNESTI] A giant weapon
modeled after the ancient
drake demon beast.
I'm surprised
Zaloudek would make
something so unorthodox.
[DOLOTEO]
I found you, Demon!
The Vyver will put you down,
once and for all.
Prince Cristobal will
finally be avenged!
[KOJASS] I had planned
to construct the Vyver
some time ago, but ultimately
shelved the project.
Your use of explosions
as propellant
made my drake possible.
Thanks for giving me
the key to your demise.
[ERNESTI]
I see.
I guess if I can learn
about your technology,
there's no reason
you shouldn't be able
to adapt to mine.
Well played, Lord Kojass.
My dear Ernesti Echevalier.
[sighs]
You Fremmevians have such
difficult names to pronounce.
Well, it doesn't matter.
You'll die here
and be forgotten!
[KOJASS laughs]
[ERNESTI]
Next time: "Knight and Dragon"!
Its power is overwhelming!