[KOJASS] This should prove
quite interesting.
Vyver versus Demon.
Large versus small.
I wonder whose technology
will come out on top.
Only one way to find
out, "Lord" Kojass.
The time for talk is over.
Ikaruga and I are ready.
Let's end this!
[KOJASS] So nice of you to
join us, Mr. Echevalier!
[ERNESTI] I swear,
on the soul of my Ikaruga,
I will never let
that future come true!
[ARCHID]
I'm not gonna.
All right, we built this
ship for ramming things!
Time to test it out!
'Kay, but don't blame
me if it ends badly!
[DOLOTEO]
So, the demon intends to ram us.
Well, we won't give
him the satisfaction!
Ankyurosa! Shoot him down!
[ALL yelp]
Calm down! Port-side
jet thrusters, full power!
Run away!
[BATSON yelps]
Okay. That was unexpected.
Chase those cowards!
They fell for it!
All according to plan!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
We're counting on
you, Silver Phoenix.
Now that we're here, we can
fight as hard as we want!
[ERNESTI] Time to launch
the counterattack!
Bespiari. Awaken!
Those won't hit no many
how many you fire.
Lightning Field!
[BOTH gasp]
[KOJASS] They're filled
with some sort of liquid.
Figure out what it is!
Ah! It's oil!
[SOLDIERS yell]
--That damn demon tricked us!
--Quite clever!
Did you like them?
I got the idea from those
annoying smoke bombs of yours!
You've turned those poor robots
into glorified turrets.
I'll set them free,
one way or another!
[SOLDIER 12B]
Get those fires out!
[SOLDIER 12A]
We've lost five Ankyurosas!
Make that six!
Not yet. Not until
that bastard is dead.
We still have the Blood Grail.
Now might be your
last chance to use it.
You just have to give the order,
and you'll have the power
to crush the demon!
I like to call it,
"The Maximizer."
[gapss]
[SOLDIER 12A]
The drawbridges are coming down!
They what?
[DIETRICH]
Okay.
I saw one of the
drawbridges come down.
Nicely done.
I'm impressed, Commander.
Back at you.
You're something else.
The Azure Hawk's
lucky to have you.
[chuckles]
They really have us
backed into a corner.
My, my.
I guess there's only one way
to fight back now, General.
[DOLOTEO gowls]
Fine, we'll use
this "Maximizer."
Blood Grail, activate!
Uh, roger!
Blood Grail activation is a go!
[laughs]
[SOLDIER 12A] Linking
element crystal collapse!
[SOLDIER 13A] High-density ether
supplied to all reactors!
[SOLDIER 13B]
Maximized form engaged!
[ERNESTI]
Uh! What the--?
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[KOJASS laughs]
The dragon's blood
is overflowing!
What an incredible glow! Ha, ha!
I guess the heart was
a little too big for your body,
my dear Vyver.
Truly fascinating!
--What is that?
--[BATSON yells]
A massive, shining dragon.
For a Knight, there isn't
a more worthy opponent!
[KOJASS laughs]
Now that we've maximized,
they could throw everything
they have at us
and it won't even make a dent!
This is our chance, men!
The demon is helpless
before this power!
Feel the rage of
our fallen prince!
[grunts]
[EMRYS]
This fortress once belonged
to the noble
Kuschperchan people!
We're takin' it back! Uh?
[GUSTAV]
Ha, ha!
Bring your whole army,
it won't make a difference.
I could take your whole
pitiful nation myself...
...with my Deadman's Sword!
[SOLDIER 13C]
It's your funeral!
[SOLDIER 13D]
Outta the way!
[SOLDIER 13E]
Damn it!
[EDGAR] Everyone stay back!
This fight is mine!
Dietrich mentioned a Knight
wielding multiple swords.
I guess it's up to me
to finish the job.
You're going to let me through!
[GUSTAV]
Take this!
I'll cripple your mech the
same way I did Twin Swords!
You bastard. I won't
let you hurt anyone else!
[GUSTAV]
Fiery! I like that!
I'll slice you up in
front of all Kushpercha
and fill their hearts with fear!
[EDGAR] You're getting
ahead of yourself!
[GUSTAV]
Ha, ha!
So close and yet so far. Huh?
Aw, man!
Mission complete!
Right!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Don't let them pass!
If one makes it, I'll kill you!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Eleonora? Are you okay?
Just look.
Our friends are giving
everything for our country.
And yet all I can do is
watch them risk their lives.
But that is my duty.
Damn it! Why won't
you just die?!
[ERNESTI]
That thing is a monster.
That said, even the best
man-made inventions
can't magically grow.
So, it's wearing the
excess mana like a cloak
that nullifies
long-range attacks.
If they think my only strength
is fighting from a distance,
they've got another
thing coming.
I'll just focus my mana into my
Sword Cannons and break through.
And then, engage the drake
at point-blank range!
[DOLOTEO]
Here he comes.
Like a moth to the flame.
Incinerate the demon until
there's nothing left but ash!
You'll have to do
a lot better than that!
[gasps]
Crush him, Draconic Claw!
C'mon, stop being
so predictable.
[KOJASS] Well, so nice of you
to join us, Mr. Echevalier!
Every weapons designer
wants more power,
but your designs achieve
power by going bigger,
which sacrifices any aesthetics.
Aesthetics are for
sculptures, not weapons!
All they need to do is
function as we intended!
You couldn't be
more wrong, Kojass!
These Knights are
sculptures! Works of art!
What a shame. A crying shame!
All that technology...
All that power...
...should be in an airship!
No, a Silhouette Knight!
[KOJASS, ERNEST] Why can't you
see my design is superior?!
Burn in hell!
We missed?
A flying Silhouette Knight
is just a child's plaything!
My Vyver is the future
of weapon's development!
Your toy and others like it
will be helpless before it!
I swear on the
soul of my Ikaruga,
I will never let that
future come true!
[GUSTAV]
You shall not pass!
As long as I have
swords to swing,
I will keep you
from this fortress!
Look at the other
bridge, you fool!
The battle's already over!
I don't care!
Even if I'm the
last one standing,
I'll slice your entire
army to pieces!
Wake up, Deadman!
[GUSTAV]
Slice and dice!
I'll give you credit,
white shields.
You're even more annoying
than your crimson friend!
It can't end here!
Not when we're so close!
Come on, partner, hold
together a little more!
[gasps]
[EDGAR]
This battle is ours.
Now that I've caught you.
Are you crazy?!
And this time a smoke bomb
won't save your sorry ass.
What the--?
This'll be a bumpy ride, Edgar!
Ahh! Howling... Blast!
This isn't over!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[EDGAR]
Well done, Aldirat.
You can finally rest.
Thank you.
Disappear into the darkness
of history, Vyver,
and forever be
known as a failure!
[SOLDIER 12A] External
equipment damage exceeds 80%!
[SOLDIER 13A] High-density
ether supply is unstable!
[SOLDIER 12A] Sector eight's
gone completely silent!
Insane. It's just one
Silhouette Knight, dammit!
[KOJASS] Hmm. In terms of
the physical end product,
if not the design itself,
I suppose I can give credit
where it's due.
But don't think for a moment I'm
out of the game, young Ernesti.
What the hell just happened?
It shrank?
Take my life if
that's what you want.
But you... you will
never have the victory.
[grunts]
--Now what?
--No!
He wouldn't!
[BOTH gasp]
As long as I can kill
that sniveling brat,
the reborn Kuschpercha
won't live to see the dawn.
Queen Eleonora!
If I still had the mana,
I would just burn the Queen
and be done with it.
I'll just use the Vyver
itself as my weapon!
[SOLDIER 13F]
Your highness! Please go!
Eleonora! We should run!
I can't do that.
A Queen must never flee,
no matter how dire
the situation may be.
[ELEONORA] My Knight. I believe
that you'll protect me.
Not good! He's heading
for the camp!
Eleonora!
I won't let you!
Demon! Don't get in my way!
The Behemoth's Heart and Queen's
Coronet aren't just for show!
I'll give you a demonstration!
[DOLOTEO]
He's still stronger?
[DOLOTEO yells]
[BOTH scream]
Damn it all!
The camp's in danger!
But if I let go of it now,
no one could stop the drake
from crashing into them!
[ADELTRUD]
Queen Eleonora!
Ah! There must be
something I can do!
No way. That's too crazy,
don't even think it.
[sighs]
[ARCHID] Boss! Can you get
the ship any closer?
What're you gonna do?
What else?
Punch him till he stops!
[BATSON, DAVID]
You're gonna what?
The hell? Does that
idiot have a death wish?
Don't die on us, kid!
I'm not gonna!
[yells]
Sorry, Gustav.
It's up to you now.
Avenge me for the
glory of Zaloudek!
[SOLDIER 13F]
What's happening?
It's turning away!
[ARCHID] Think I might have
shown off a little too much.
Oh, well. As long as the Queen
is safe, I'm okay with this.
[ERNESTI]
Kid!
[ARCHID]
Uh?
Leave the Tzendolimble!
I gotcha!
What took you so long?
You kept me safe through
everything, Tzen.
Thanks a lot.
[SOLDIER 13I]
The Vyver fell!
[SOLDIER 13J]
The Bronze Wing is down, too.
At this point, our
victory is inevitable!
Advance and take back what's
rightfully Kuschpercha's!
First Shilda Neryaku,
then the capital!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[SELESTINA] The defeat of the
drake battleship resulted
in the complete loss of
Zaloudek's air superiority.
Their army collapsed in the
face of Kuschpercha's assault,
and Shilda Neryaku fell.
The capital, Delvancul,
had used all of its forces
to defend Shilda Neryaku,
and was unable to offer
any resistance as the Reborn
Kingdom's forces moved in.
[SELESTINA]
And thus, the ambitions
of the Kingdom of
Zaloudek collapsed.
[SELESTINA] The spring
of Western Year 1283.
The coronation held at
Delvancul served as a message
to the surrounding kingdoms:
Kuschpercha had returned.
And it was stronger
than ever before.
At that moment,
Eleonora became
both the de facto and dey
jury Queen of Kuschpercha.
[DAVID]
Quit slackin' off!
Get that stuff loaded...
or you'll be tastin' my boot!
[ENGINEERS yelp]
[DAVID]
You morons did a great job
tearin' these things to pieces.
Sorry about that, Boss.
If it helps, we know
they'll be better
than ever once you're done.
Heh. Stop it,
you're makin' me blush.
You're gonna be real busy
when we get back home.
That sucks.
I won't be the only one.
I'm sorry, Ernie.
Build and scrap is the
way of the world, Kid.
As long as you're
safe, I'm fine.
Besides, I have this.
There's so much
to learn from it!
[ERNESTI giggles]
Your Majesty!
Wha--?!
[ARCHID]
Uh?
Isadola, you think it's
safe for her out here?
[ELEONORA]
Please.
I don't think I could
be anywhere safer.
[ADELTRUD chuckles]
Are you well?
I guess.
You'll be leaving
soon, won't you?
Uh. Yeah.
Though, it feels weird to go
home in a Levitate Ship.
I'm still tryin'
to get over that.
My noble Knight.
I'll never forget how
you protected me.
Or the amazing things
you've done for Kuschpercha.
I don't know.
Doesn't feel like I
did anything special.
You have!
Once things calm down here,
be sure to visit us
in Fremmevilla, 'kay?
[ELEONORA]
Of course.
Well, see ya.
Ugh! You massive
idiot! Don't say bye!
If Kid was a Silhouette Knight.
I'd be rewriting
his programming.
Uh, I don't think you have
room to talk, Ernie.
That settles it.
Every guy in the order
is dumb as a rock.
What?
[ELEONORA]
Sorry.
Let me stay like this
for just a moment.
After that, I'll go
back to being Queen.
Good luck to you,
my noble Knight.
--[MAN 13A] Bye!
--[MAN 13B] Come back soon!
--[MAN 13C] Take care!
--Thanks, Rys!
[ADELTRUD]
Wasn't there something else
you could've said to her?
Nah. That was plenty.
Next time we meet, I wanna
be better than I am now.
[GUSTAV]
Just seven more mountains, boys!
We'll keep pushing until
we get back to Zaloudek.
Or until we run out of food.
[KOJASS] Hm? Variable
Magius Jet Thrusters, huh?
A truly interesting
choice, I must say.
[KOJASS]
Ernesti Echevalier.
How far do you think
your devotion to aesthetics
will take you?
Honestly, I can't wait
to find out for myself.
Of course, you'll learn
more about my theories, too.
Perhaps even sooner than you
were expecting, my young rival.
Now then, to find
another king with
delusions of grandeur willing
to buy my inventions.
[KOJASS chuckles]
[ERNESTI]
Hmm...
[ADELTRUD]
Ernie!
Let's go inside.
It's freezing out here.
I think the Boss is making
pot-au-feu for lunch!
[AMBROSIUS]
Welcome home, Silver Phoenix.
Your work out there
has been exemplary.
Especially you, Knight Runners.
Your bravery will be
a shining example
to all who come after you.
Your prowess in battle
shall be remembered by all
for generations to come.
And of course,
there's our industrious
Knightsmiths who
toiled ceaselessly
to keep our Knight
Runners in the fight.
Without your endurance.
Zaloudek may very
well have succeeded
in their grim endeavor.
And thank you, Knight Commander,
for giving my worthless
grandson some glory.
I will reward you with
anything you desire.
Nothing is off limits
this time around.
Ask and it shall be yours.
Okay then! I won't
hold anything back!
[KNUT grunts]
[DAVID]
Heh! Not bad at all, Silver.
[BATSON]
Our own Silhouette Knight lab.
I guess it's all right.
But you could've
asked him for more.
You're not as greedy
as I thought, Ernie.
What are you talking about?
Of course I'm greedy!
I'm the king of greedy!
All I wanna do is
collect the most amazing
Knight Runner technology
ever produced,
the greatest Knightsmiths
in the world,
and the ultimate
Silhouette Knights!
I can't think of a more
fulfilling life to lead!
First off, I wanna
make a Silhouette Knight
that flies more beautifully
and efficiently
than Ikaruga ever could.
But to do that,
I'll have to do a redesign
of the fundamentals.
Starting with Ether Reactors
and Crystal Tissue!
I may even need to write
a whole new set of scripts!
Something to compliment the ones
for fluid and heat mechanics.
And not just for
Silhouette Knights, either!
I wanna design
a Silhouette Gear
than can fly as well!
The skies themselves--no,
the way people live would
be totally changed forever!
But surely something
like that is impossible.
The impossible is what we do!
[DAVID]
Welp. I've heard enough.
It'll be sunset before
he's done yammerin'.
Have fun with that.
I'm going to raid the kitchen.
[ARCHID]
Same. I'm starving.
Um. Okay.
Seriously, Ernie.
Stop focusing on your
dreams and take a look
at what's around you, for once.
I do! There's a lab
and Silhouette Knights.
[ADELTRUD sighs]
[SELESTINA]
The Western Grand Storm,
which began as an offensive
by the Kingdom of Zaloudek,
brought Levitate Ship technology
to all nations of the world.
People gained
a unique way to move
from place to place, and an
exciting new era was born.
This Great Age of Airships
would also be filled with
trials and accomplishments.
But that's a story of its own.
One we'll save
for another time.
[ERNESTI]
Robots are a man's romance!