PDCH Command Center
to Section One Mobile Unit.
Targets are moving south
on Metro Expressway
Five near Ikebukuro.
Collateral damage is moderate,
repeat: moderate at present
but a civilian rescue
team is on the scene.
Do you copy?
Copy that.
Section One moving in.
Over.
All on-ramps within
the prescribed radius
have been barricaded.
Advise civilians to leave their
vehicles and vacate the area.
Over.
Local and affiliated
media outlets
have been ordered to conduct
an information blackout
as per Form Twelve,
Section Three-B.
You might want to ensure
compliance, though.
Over.
Natsuki.
Sorry...
I'm supposed to be on
shift tonight, aren't I?
Toru...
It's okay. I know she's
not really "here." ...
Of course, that doesn't explain
why I keep doing this to myself,
does it?
Section Four Command Center
to Agent Thirty-Three. Come in.
This is Agent
Thirty-Three, over.
Looks like we've got ourselves
an O-Four-Three on the Metro.
Section One's Mobile Unit has
been dispatched to intercept.
Section Four is now on
Type One Combat Standby.
Do you copy?
Copy that, Command. Out.
Let's get over there.
We're on standby...
So I heard...
It's him...
I know it is.
Keep those hoses
on full blast!
We've gotta clear
a path to the injured!
Section One
Mobile Unit on scene.
Commencing sweep operation.
Hey...! Unless that thing's
got a hose and a couple
of metric tons of water onboard,
get it the hell outta here!
This area in now under the
command of the Defense Ministry,
care of the Paranormal Disaster
Countermeasure Headquarters,
Section One...
You and your men have done a
fine job, but you can leave now.
Thank you.
We're not just gonna --
What the...?
Everyone spread out...!
We've got Category Cs...
A whole horde of 'em...
Turn your Seekers on.
Now take 'em down!
The hell's going on?!
Spray the holy water!
Clear.
Category Cs
have been eradicated.
Combat Status
Type One terminated.
Hey...
Are you still here?.
I told you to go...
Don't worry about it;
leave the cleanup to us.
What the hell is that?
Oh god no...
It's a Category B...
Open fire!
What are you doing?
How many times
do I have to--
Looks like we
have a Category B.
Yeah.
I see it.
Take the injured
and get out of here...
Now!
Hey, Natski...
The Kasha...
We can't take it
by ourselves!
Wait for Masaki and
Kudo to get here!
Just back me up!
Take a pill, man.
We're almost there.
Masaki?
Who else?
Holy water's
en route, guys.
ETA's approximately
thirty seconds.
Let 'er rip!
You wanna go
another round?
Just keep sprayin' until
there's none of 'em left.
Done.
Ya ready?
Oh yeah.
Section One's entire
Mobile unit was wiped out?
No... Only about half of them
have been confirmed dead...
The rest are still
listed as critical.
What do you think I mean
when I say wiped out?!
Tonight was a travesty...
an outright travesty.
Why did we even bother
setting up the PDCH
in the Ministry of Defense?
Pathetic....
The Ministry of Environment's
gonna have a damn field day
with this.
So looking at the numbers, the
only successful unit to date
belongs
to Section Four...
Must make you
proud, Komparu...
It would me.
Come now...
You flatter me; I just
chaperone a group of misfits...
Really... Our only
advantage is second sight...
That's all, sir.
Just like you fellas at the
Ministry of Environment...
Please forgive me
for bringing it up...
But the Ministry of Environment
has had its share of issues...
One of the SDCD's chief
Vanquishers was incapacitated.
Very unpleasant business.
Paranormal incidents
did seem to level off
after the SDCD's exorcism
sweeps three years ago,
but lately there appears
to have been something
of an inexplicable upsurge.
Do you mean to suggest that
our over-reliance on them
has come back to haunt us?
I don't mean to
suggest anything.
The spirits in question...
may not have been exorcised
to the extent we
were led to believe.
You don't mean...
Mere speculation, sir.
Nothing more.
Wow...
This stuff's
pretty high-tech.
Just a high-tech Achilles'
Heel if you ask me.
Hey show some respect.
People have died for crissakes.
Yeah, yeah.
Can you imagine
if everybody was a seer...?
I'd bet you anything
that organized religion
would soar to the top
of the charts again.
Oh, yeah...?
And what denomination
would we all belong to?
Rock n' Roll.
Bad news, guys!
What's up, Mami?
We've got another
O-Four-Three in the city...
Looks like
it's a Category B!
Let's go.
These are the enhanced
satellite images.
Whoa...
Much like the one we saw
earlier, except its spirit mass
is roughly thirty times the
density of its predecessor...
A barrier's been put in
place to contain it, but ...
of course there's no telling
how long that'll hold.
What's with all the Kashas
suddenly cropping up
right on top of each
other like this?
Who knows...? But our course
of action is clear...
Holy water to weaken it
and Mani bullets
to put it out
of our misery.
Yeah, but... if my preliminary
calculations are correct...
We'd require over two hundred
tons of holy water in this case.
But they...
They haven't even developed
a delivery system
than can drop that kind
of volume from the air!
Excellent point...
We'll have to be a bit
clever on this one.
Then again...
That is what we do best.
No sweat, guys.
The barrier's supposed
to keep 'em at bay
pretty much indefinitely.
Didn't do much good for
the Mobile Unit earlier.
You know they got
slaughtered, right?
Shut up!
Seriously?
Hey!
What the hell...?
Right. I've made contact
with the target
and am currently heading
eastbound on Gaien-dori.
I'll get on Metro
from Hamaski-bashi.
Copy that, Agent
Thirty-three...
Keep it moving in
that direction...
Over.
Agents Fifty-Five
and Seventy-Seven
have been dropped off
at the scene...
I'm heading for Shaft
Three as we speak.
Copy.
Copy that,
Eleven. Over.
I've reached the overflow
levee in Shaft Three.
Prep-work has
been completed.
Over.
ETA to Shaft Two,
approximately ten minutes.
Over.
All systems raring
to go on my end.
Over.
Copy that...
Agent Seventy-Seven?
Ready.
Let's do this thing.
I'm in Shaft Two.
Target in pursuit...
Launching cables!
Confirmed...
Target has entered Construction
Tunnel One from Shaft Two.
Compromise the levee!
Say your prayers!
I'm transmitting mantra codes
to the capsules, and presto!
Construction Tunnel One
flooding with Holy Water...
Target is... Hit!
Target spotted...
Range...
Nine hundred...
Eight-fifty
Eight hundred...
Seven-fifty.
Seven hundred...
Six-fifty...
Firing.
Misfire!
Agent Thirty-Three?
Natsuki!
Natsuki...
Son of a...
Toru...
Natsuki...
Sorry...
I really screwed up.
First time, huh?
Seventy-Seven!
Brace for impact! Now!
Man, what a rush!
Close enough for ya?
Yeah, sure.
Fifty-Five here.
This one is put to bed.
Copy that.
Nice work.
Ballsy move...
An aqueduct would be the
last place I'd ever think of
to face down a Kasha.
Yeah, but it's the best place
to avoid civilian casualties,
you got to admit.
Besides, what better way
to brew up
the volume of
holy water we needed?
You guys owe
Mami big time.
She's the one who sent
us to your rescue.
Yeah...
You're right.
Of course I am.
Man...
I dropped my--
It's a Category A...
Masaki!
Kudo...
Natsuki!
Son of a bitch!
Crazy right?
Mami!
Don't worry.
Just try to relax.
There's nothing
any of us can do...
Mami! What's going on?!
We'll be waiting patiently
in the sweet hereafter...
You really won't be
that far behind us.
No...! Alright...
We're getting out of here...
Just take this.
Aoi...!
Aoi!
Stop it! She's not
the person you remember!
You've got to let it go!
Like hell
I'll let it go!
I'm telling you
it's too late!
Move!
Aoi...
Please don't...
Shoot her.
Aoi...
Oh god...
Shoot her!
I told you...
Let it go.