Hey, Miku...
Do you mind if I copy off
your English homework?
No one told me we had
a homework assignment....
You could've picked up
the phone and called me...
I was out sick all day
yesterday, don't you remember?
Oh yeah... Crap!
What am I going to do now?
I depend on you!
Tsuchimiya!
Did you do your
English homework?
Yeah...
Of course...
Really...?!
Mind if I "borrow" it?
Um... Okay.
Sweet...!
Thank you!
Is it cool if I kind
of glance at, too?
Yeah. Sure.
Someone texting you?
Uh-huh. The hospital.
Oh, that's right.
Your mom. I forgot.
Is she okay...?
I mean, it's not like it's
any of my business, but...
It's nothing serious...
I do have to go, though.
You guys mind leaving my
English notebook in the desk
when you're done?
Thanks!
Nothing serious, huh?
Bet she's got it rough.
Sorry to pull you
out of class again.
Well... It's okay,
but I hate having to lie
to my teachers all the time.
Kagura.
You've got slobber
on your face.
This one's going in my "The Many
Faces of Kagura" collection...
I really wish
you'd delete those!
There's been a lot of paranormal
activity lately, hasn't there?
Yes...
And I've got a feeling things
are only going to get worse.
It's been over three years
since it was this noisy...
Just the calm before
the storm, I guess...
I hope not.
One pocky left!
I call it!
Hey! That's not fair!
Hey, if you snooze
you lose, sweetheart!
I couldn't agree
with you more.
Maybe sharing's not
so bad after all...
Ew! Stop it!
Oh, come on!
Don't be such a prude!
Get off me!
You're disgusting!
You love it and
you know it...
I swear, I'm gonna
bite your lip off!
Does this look like
a peep show to you?
I repeat...
Sorry we had to pull you
both out of class today.
Oh, that's okay.
What with it being our
"sacred duty" and all...
What? Why's it okay
if the Mohawk watches?!
'Cause he doesn't bat
for the same team.
That's right.
So he gets carte
blanche, then...
Sit down,
pretty boy...
Your ass...
Is distracting me
C'mon! Not cool,
man! Not cool!
So what exactly
are we up against?
The pipe foxes
have its scent.
Category B.
An Earth Spider.
One of the biggest
I've ever seen.
Have the pipe
foxes clear out.
The chimera and I will
deal with this one...
The rest of you
will back me up!
Back up again?
Don't start. You're not
ready for anything else...
Master Michael
Twelve one of these days
and maybe -
maybe- we'll talk.
I have mastered it!
Oh... Well then you'll have
to prove it to me sometime.
Now Ranguren!
Come with me!
Let's give her
some backup, boys.
On it!
Hit it with a Roar Wave!
Crack it!. Now!
Kagura...
She's a civilian?
Uh-huh.
You okay?.
Are you hurt?
That thing...
You saw didn't you?
Okay, then that'll
make this simple...
We are a special division of
the Ministry of Environment.
It's called the
Supernatural Disaster
Countermeasure Division.
Ghost hunters...?
Spirits often target people
with psychic tendencies.
Evil spirits aim to drive
you out of your mind...
Lure you to join
the ranks, so to speak.
Word of advice...
Stay away from
places like this.
And don't ever talk about what
you've seen here tonight...
We've got a nondisclosure
form for you to sign.
Hey... It's not as bad
as you might think.
At least not bad enough
for these... Right?
I guess not.
Looks like the area's
ghost-free for the moment.
Good. Mission
accomplished then...
Everyone clear out.
How did you know she'd come
here to try to kill herself?
A hunch....
You sort of pick things up
after a while in this gig.
Tsuchimiya!
It's for yesterday.
We made a box lunch
for you... You hungry?
Yes!
It's delicious.
So I've gotta ask...
What is it your mom
is so sick with?
Yatchin...!
Like I said, it's
nothing really serious.
Still, though.
How do you deal with that
and manage to get all
your homework done?
Oh, I've just always been really
good at multi-tasking, you know.
Does your dad help?
Uh, well...
He travels a lot for work
so I don't actually
see him that much.
I'm living with relatives
until mom gets back on her feet.
That sounds
completely tragic!
It's anything but...
I got a new big sister
out of the deal
who lets me tag along
with her to work...
She's awesome.
Work?
Uh, well, it's...
It's just...
A family business...
So wait, you also
hold down a job?!
As best I can.
I'm not that good; they just
consider me an apprentice.
Oh, please...
You don't have to downplay
it; that's incredible!
Really?
Really.
Stop!
Abomination!
Only the essence undiluted
of the Japanese people
is fit for the caring
of a katana!
Tea seed oil or clove oil
is all the blade may drink!
Do I even wanna ask?
Look...! This creep
just ran in here!
Ah, Master Michael.
I wasn't expecting a visit.
An honorable pleasure
to see you again, young Yomi!
Who is this?
Someone I think you should
introduce yourself to.
Uh... My name's Kagura...
Ah...!
I have been attacked
by the daughter of great
Master Tsuchimiya, yes?.
Please know me
as Michael Kohara!
You're Michael Kohara?
If the name
sounds familiar,
it's because he
forged that katana.
Yes.
The man who made
Michael Twelve... Is you?
Yes.
There isn't a piece
of SDCD equipment
that Master Michael
here hasn't constructed.
Yes.
But why is he naked?
That's not an answer!
May I, please...?
Ah-ha... He smiles
at me as bright as ever...
Like a newborn
jewel of the sky.
Because the only thing
they ever let me do with it
is haul it around.
After I've decided
you're ready for battle,
I'll let you do more.
Young Yomi... Kindly may I
inspect the Shishio, please?
It too smiles at me
as a brother...
The halo of energy surrounding
this katana bathes our world
and the next in the song
of night birds... For now.
Oh?
Its power ebbs...
Unless tended to quickly,
the smile will fade.
Guess you'll have to fight
without Ranguren
for little while, huh?
I'm sorry.
That totally sucks.
Well I guess everything
needs a little upkeep...
I'll be fine.
I wish I had a Spirit Beast
at my beck and call...
It'd be pretty handy while
yours was in the shop.
Come on, doll...
Let me scrub your back.
Have you seen much
of your dad lately?
Not really.
I'll bet you he's
feeling pretty lonely.
Why don't you pay him
a visit sometime?
Well I might if I ever thought
I could catch him at home.
I could leave
if you want me to.
You've gotta be sick
of playing babysitter.
Never!
Oh, not this again!
You're so adorable!
Come on! Cut it out,
that tickles!
You realize
I'm adopting you one day...
Really?. And the purpose
of Master Michael's visit?
He felt the Shishio needed
a few minor repairs...
He also passionately insisted on
taking most of our arsenal back
to his shop for
routine maintenance.
Did he...?
Then we'd better submit
them to him en masse.
En masse...?
But if something were
to happen in the meantime...
We'd have cause
to fully initiate
the team's newest
addition, wouldn't we?
But... she...
There's no better training
ground than combat...
And besides...
As much as we rely on him,
poor Rannie deserves a vacation.
I guess you're right.
Indeed.
Adjust their shifts.
Right away,
ma'am...
As you wish...
Oh, and...
Yes, Kiri?
Why is... Master
Michael always naked?
Good question.
Watch it!
You watch!
That old man is
something else.
How does he not get arrested
walking around like that?
Oh, we've had to bail
him out plenty of times.
Looks like we got ourselves
some paid time off,
doesn't it Yomi?
I can fight just as well
with or without the Shishio...
So what do we have lying
around the backup stockpile?
Not much, I'm afraid.
What you see is more
or less what you get.
Hey, lookie here.
You think this one
might tide you over?
Is that an iron?
More like a Vanquisher Knuckle:
The Douglas Twenty- Eight.
Steam the wrinkles
out of any evil spirit
with good old
fashioned holy water!
No dice...? Don't fret;
there're always options...
Like the Pare Eleven
Vanquisher Chainsaw!
Our Vanquisher Jackhammer,
the Jackson Thirty-Three!
Or the J. Fox Fifty-Five,
our top-of-the-line
Vanquisher Boiler...
Nice, huh?
For an appliance.
How's anyone supposed
to carry this thing?
Guess I'll take you...
Hey, Nori...
Wanna play house?
Can't... I've got
a prior engagement.
Again?
Kazuki promised
me a rematch...
You'll have a
blast without me.
Come on, Big Sis.
Let's practice!
That's a great idea!
Think you oughta be here?
Do what?
Dude, you're gonna have to make
time for Yomi sooner or later...
Whether you like it or not.
I've got the rest of my
life to make time for her.
That's the spirit.
I like her
and all... I just...
wish I'd had some
say-so in the matter...
I'm sure she'll
make a great wife.
And great mother...
Just look at Kagura...
Hup!
I feel your pain, though...
It's gotta be tough...
Having your parents
prearrange everything
kind of kills the romance,
if you ask me.
This board and
I are not friends.
I'm just trying to enjoy
my freedom while it lasts.
Sure. Fine.
Whatever; just don't set
me up as your enabler.
My what?
Yomi will hold
this against me ...
She scares me as it is.
Me too.
At least I can finally hit
something with this thing.
Is it really even
all that powerful?
Any weapon forged by Master
Michael will be powerful...
And when you add that to the
wielder's inborn psychic energy,
you've got yourself
an unbeatable combination.
Just like the Michael
Twelve will be for you.
You've got an iron
with a chain on it.
Think of it as modern art.
It's headquarters....
There's been some kind
of massive energy flux...
It's fairly close
by, isn't it?
Right.
Where are we?
It's Shimbashi Station
on the Ginzu rail line...
These days they just use it
as a night train depot, though.
Do me a favor: unless you
want a really bad hair day,
don't touch the
conductor's rail.
Why has there been
so much activity lately?
Evil spirits are drawn
to places with bad vibes,
which makes those
places more powerful
and winds up attracting
more evil spirits...
It's how hot spots are created;
like a psychic feedback loop...
Still...
Still what?
The original "bad vibe"
always has an outside source.
Whaddaya know...?
It works.
Ceiling Lickers...
Category C.
The little creeps do have kind
of a thing for concrete stains.
That's too bad.
Don't do this to me!
Yomi!
You okay?!
Sorry... I ran out
of holy water.
Yomi...
What the...?
Wait a sec, is that...?
Do not go near her!
Category D...
The reanimated body
of a dead human being.
Oh, god!
You mean she's...?!
What'll we do?
What else?
But they're...!
They are not human.
But they were
at one point!
We have a duty to
purify this site!
I don't know if I...
It'll put them out
of their misery.
Kagura!
A Vanquisher's first obligation
is to rid the world of spirits
who defile
the natural order!
I know...!
It's just...
They're all...
How the...?
Kagura!
I don't believe it.
My father.
Spirit Eater...
Come forth!
Byakuei.
Feast!
That's your
family's Ga-rei...
Its ultimate
source of power.
Ga-rei...
Byakuei.
Kagura...
Hold out your hands.
Yes, sir.
I presume you're aware of
what a Vanquisher's duty is?
Yes, sir.
Then I presume you
also know its gravity.
Sir.
Very well then...
Purge yourself of fear.
Sir.
Master, please...
Grow stronger.
On the next
Ga-Rei: Zero:
Obstinate Feelings.