You little tramp.
Don't call me that...!
Ever!
What a shame...
To think you'd
be led astray.
Of all the
Spirit Eaters,
Byakuei is clearly
the mightiest...
He's an invaluable asset to
the proud Tsuchimiya family.
I don't know which
annoys me more...
Honestly...
I don't think
I'll ever understand
what made me
look up to them.
However...
Both family
and Beast die today.
Go, Byakuei...
Feast!
Ranguren!
Hit him with a Roar Wave!
Yomi...
and Father!
Stop it. You don't
have to do this...
Please just stop...
Stop fighting!
Kagura!
I need your help!
Ranguren!
Byakuei!
Prepare yourself.
I've seen enough of this.
You're dealing with me now.
Father, no!
Kagura...!
Are you alright?
We have to help my father!
We have to do something!
It's you.
Is that-?
It's a Bane Stone.
Dad, no!
I can't believe it.
I couldn't do it.
I tried...
but I couldn't
kill her.
Izuna.
She didn't kill Kazuki...
I did.
If I'd stopped her
when I had the chance...
he'd still be alive.
It seems a Bane Stone has turned
Yomi Isayama into a phantom.
As you are aware...
they're made from the souls
of nine-tail foxes...
crystalized forms
of pure energy.
Whoever possesses one
will have limitless power
until the Stone
devours their soul...
and turns them
into a phantom.
When they synchronize with the
hatred of the nine-tail foxes,
they attempt to destroy
everything in existence.
In the incident
with May Isayama...
the use of a Bane Stone
explains a lot, don't you agree?
I do.
But that would mean...
that our treatment
of Yomi was the catalyst
that led to
this transformation.
No... Bane Stones
are forbidden...
no matter what the reason
for acquiring one...
She knew the rule and
decided to break it.
Let's go back... There's one
more thing we still have to do.
What-...
What am I doing...?
Why can't I stop this?
No...
No!
So there's no way out...
not even in death.
Stay on high alert.
The singularity
must be found.
Quickly, ma'am...
Look at the spirit
pressure map.
What's this?
We've lost radio contact with
Observation Teams One and Two...
Team Three is the only team
still sending spirit signals.
Of course. Yomi's hiding,
call Team Three at once...
Tell them to evacuate.
I'm coming, too.
But, ma'am...
Now... SDCD Disposal Team,
emergency mobilization...!
There's not much time!
Let's move.
Izuna...
We're going.
Hey, Nori!
Leave the kid alone.
In his current condition,
he'd probably end up
getting himself killed.
If you pull yourself together,
you know where we are.
Come on.
Dammit!
Are you alright...
Kagura?
I'm okay...
Are you alright, Father?
Don't concern
yourself with me.
I know that
I let you down.
I'm sorry I'm
so inexperienced.
What's wrong?
What is it, Father?
What's going on?
Bad idea... You should
have stayed at your posts.
O-maht soon-man ga
haas-ver-gun soon-nah.
Had-ash-na-gah voe-ter-ya
oon-tra-ta coom gah-nah.
Be strong, Father!
It would appear...
that I've reached my limit.
Byakuei...
is trying to break free
of the seal that binds him.
I'm no longer strong
enough to hold it.
You're wrong...! The Bane
Stone can help you recover!
The stone's power was muted
in the sealing process.
By the time it heals these
wounds, it will be too late.
Listen to me, Kagura...
It won't be long before
my soul is ripped apart...
and I die.
You can't.
Before my spirit
leaves this earthly plane,
there's something important
I must tell you.
Yes, sir.
I want to apologize.
Forgive me, Kagura.
I don't understand.
Those born into
the Tsuchimiya line
will one day inherit
our Spirit Eater, Byakuei.
And those who are capable of
bonding and handling Byakuei
are not destined to live
long and happy lives.
It was true for your mother.
It is true for me.
And someday our fate
will prove true...
for you.
I'm sorry.
The last thing I want is for
your life to end as abruptly
as your mother's.
I have always dreamed that you
would live a long, full life...
For that to happen,
you had to grow stronger.
I had no way of foretelling
when my own life
would come to an end...
That is why I pushed you
to improve and mature
as quickly as possible.
I understand it must have
been difficult for you...
spending your entire
childhood in training.
Don't, Father...
Please, don't!
I hope you can
forgive me, Kagura.
I'm so sorry.
Don't talk like that!
Look who's here.
You're too late, you know...
Every eye you had watching
me has been gouged out.
Now you won't be able to use
spirit energy to track me.
I'm surprised...
I never imagined you
would become a Category A.
Why didn't you bring
everybody else...?
They scared...?
Or perhaps they're dead.
Not that it makes
any difference.
You see, it's only
a matter of time
before I kill every last
living being on the planet.
Ah, you want
some of this?
We can't let
him get away!
Zinguji!
I never thought you would
see active duty again.
No...? Well, that's a
rather rude thing to say,
don't you agree?
You would kill one
of your subordinates?
Former subordinate,
you mean.
You're heartless.
Heartless...?
I've killed people dearer to me
than you could ever hope to be.
I'm not one
to play favorites.
Those who choose evil
are not worthy of mercy!
Can you kill me?
We know what the Bane Stone's
made you capable of.
And you think
you can stop me?
Easily... You've met
your match.
You know something, Father?
This is the first time...
we've had a real conversation.
I suppose so.
Do you think
if I had trained harder
and learned how to be
a Vanquisher sooner...
that maybe we would've been able
to talk like this a lot more?
I don't know...
There's no way
of telling that now.
What does that mean?
I'm not sure I would have
known what to say to you.
I wish I could
say otherwise.
Is that funny?
Maybe a little...
It's just...
we're family.
Yes, you're right...
We are family.
Father...? Do you think you
could tell me about Mother?
Well?
We got her...
I think.
Watch out, Ma'am!
Kiri, no!
Ma'am!
Yomi... See you
in the afterlife.
Iwahata!
What do you think,
Father...?
What should I do now?
Kagura...
Do you feel love?
Yes.
And sadness?
What about hate?
I don't know.
Kagura... Forget everything
you've ever known.
Clearing your mind is the best
way to feel entirely at peace...
Everyone with a responsibility
to bear must learn to do so.
However.
The truly strong carry
the weight of their duty
on their shoulders.
But why?
As one person who is responsible
for the lives of many,
you should never
abandon your feelings...
no matter how painful to
face those feelings may be.
So you bear it...
all of it?
There are few paths more
excruciating to follow
than that one.
Only you can choose
the one you take.
It's up to me?
Are you okay, Father?
What can I do?
It seems... the moment
has finally come.
Kagura... Take it.
No...! Please,
Father! Not yet!
I've lived a long time...
Perhaps long enough.
Goodbye...
Kagura.
Don't go, Father!
Nabu...
Hang on, Kiri.
Ma'am, is...
that you?
I'm here, Kiri.
Where did Yomi... go?
You called?
Do you wanna keep going?
Let's see if Ranguren
has an opinion.
It's my choice...
No one else's.
Are you to be going
then, Young Kagura?
Master Michael.
In my wisdom, I have forged a
thing meant especially for you.
My latest creation...
The night birds sing it
as Michael Thirteen.
Michael Thirteen.
Exactly the same
as Michael Twelve,
save for being new
and superior.
I think your soul and
it can dance together.
My soul...?
I don't know.
I wonder what my
soul does want,...
Maybe I'll never
know the answer.
Young Kagura.
On the next
Ga-Rei Zero...
"Yearning Prayer."