Spirit Eater...!
Come forth!
Now feast, Byakuei.
It's possible it
went someplace else.
Ya think?
Maybe.
I bet Iwahata's
found it by now.
Let's keep looking
just to be sure.
Hang on...
It's close!
It's close...
Hey! The hell you
doing in the road?!
doing in the road...
What the...?
Hurry, Kagura!
Cover up your ears!
Ranguren!
Oh great...
Category B.
An Echoer.
That's behind all
the signal jamming?
Signal jamming...
We'll attack in alternating
waves... You ready?
Winner gets last pocky!
What the...?!
Look out!
You're kidding me!
Get back,
Kagura...!
Ranguren...!
Roar Wave!
No way!
Sis!
I'm alright...
Just go after it!
Hey! Quit copying me!
I'm not playing!
Knock... it... off!
Stop!
Stop!!
'Bout time!
Sorry about the hold up.
You okay?
I'm good.
Oh no...
Now what...?
More?
We take them down...
Just don't kill me by mistake.
I'll try.
Hit them
with a Roar Wave!
May?!
Quickly!
Ranguren!
Roar Wave!
Now!!!
Nicely done.
Thank you, May...
For helping us, I mean.
It's great to see you...
Looks like we were after
the same bad guy, huh?
I came here to observe
you in the field...
And I can't say that
I'm impressed......
Echoers move in groups.
Everyone knows this;
it's common sense.
I'm sorry, May.
So much destruction...
All of it preventable with a
little bit of forethought...
"Sorry," indeed.
This beast...
Passed down the Isayama
line for generations...
Powerful though he is,
he will wither,
unless bridled by a
true and proper warrior...
One belongs
to your family...
But not to you.
At least not yet.
Not 'til you slough off
these childish ways.
Good luck to you both.
So, May came
to their aid...
She'd be a fine asset to us...
What do you think, Kiri?
Should we ask her to join?
She has already declined.
Ah... Well that
is quite a shame.
I believe she prefers the life
of a freelancer, ma'am,...
That and no doubt having to
share a workplace with Yomi
would damage the poor woman's
pride beyond all recognition.
True enough...
What other news?
Human-dependent
occurrences are up...
That is to say, Category D
disturbances are increasing
with no sign of abatement...
As you know, such phenomena
are manageably weak in
and of themselves,
but taken together in bulk, the
sheer density of these incidents
lately represents
an alarming trend.
It's as if forces
are gathering...
Spirits are drawn to
such disturbances...
Their power increases
by accumulation.
What we have to ascertain is the
source behind all this activity.
Unfortunately, because
of the latest incident...
Kagura Tsuchimiya
has not been assigned
to any of the
disposal teams
dealing with
Category D entities...
However the larger
workload may compel us
to reconsider that.
Of course... Although I don't
think she'll be ready soon.
No.
Perhaps Yomi mothers
her a bit too tenderly.
Kagura is a touch on the
soft side... if I may say so.
Under the right auspices,
they'd make an excellent team...
If only she were tougher...
One either wakes up
to the reality of this job
or one doesn't.
This last sabbatical was a
long one, even for you, Garaku.
Please tell me you're not still
chasing after the same quarry.
Any fool could understand
how you must feel.
But I can't in good conscience
approve of this obsession.
Obsession... That is a very
cruel choice of words...
Even so, my wife's killer
is scarcely at the forefront
of my obligations...
I only wish to see everything
dealt with as it should be.
Your first concern ought
to be for those who remain...
More specifically,
those you'd leave behind
should this business
claim your life.
None of our line stays
"behind" for long.
Perhaps so... But if the
unthinkable ever befalls me...
Yomi's ready...
The same cannot
be said for Kagura.
She's a lovely girl...
But too frail-
in body and mind-
to bear the weight
you carry.
One belongs
to your family;
but not to you-
at least not yet.
Not 'til you slough off
these childish ways.
She could've been a
little nicer about it.
Kagura...! You going to
come swim with us or not...?
Lunch break
is practically over.
It's not like I'm a
member of the swim team.
Like that matters!
Neither of us is
on the swim team.
Yeah; you also haven't
been injured.
Chlorine's a disinfectant!
Oh that's it...!
You're gonna get it!
Ugh. This gauze
is soaking wet...
That wound will fester
if you're not careful.
I'm really sorry...
It wasn't my fault!
This is a nurse's
office, girls.
Sorry.
So then... How exactly
did you get that cut?
I... accidentally walked
through a glass door...
Oh good heavens...
Aren't we the clumsy one?
Sort of.
That reminds me...
They said on the
news this morning
a bunch of office building
windows downtown got shattered.
I heard about that...!
They think it was terrorists!
It may well have been...
The really weird part, though,
was that whatever was causing
all the satellite signals
to fail earlier,
stopped right after the
windows were blown out.
Satellite signals?
Apparently, if they'd
continued to fail
in that particular district,
day-trading would've
ground to a halt,
business deals
would've fallen through;
the whole economy would've
started hemorrhaging money...
Probably sounds pretty boring
to you girls, but just imagine
having to go without
your allowance for a week.
My allowance...?
Well, good
thing it's fixed!
Speaking of which...
Try to keep this one
from getting wet.
I'll try to be
careful... Thank you.
What's with the big
ear-to-ear grin...?
You look stupid.
The only one
grinning is you...
Oh, come on...
You're just happy Nurse Misuzu
fixed your bandage, aren't you?
Have a thing for
older women, huh?
Girls! Please!
Why've you gotta
be all gross?
That's enough of that.
You're going to be
late for class
if you don't
get a move on.
Oh crap!
Thanks for helping Kagura's
leg and everything!
It's my pleasure.
Run along now, girls...
Ms. suchimiya...
Yes ma'am?
If that bandage happens
to get soaked again...
Come back and
see me, alright?
Sure...
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, ma'am.
What is it, Kiri?
Latest news from the
Observation Center...
Small, but extremely
active pockets of energy
have cropped up
around the Chiyoda Ward.
The spirit energy fields are
becoming dangerously unstable.
We'll have to put every
member on high alert then...
Have the Observation Center keep
us informed of developments.
Yes, ma'am.
I can't put my
finger on it...
but something's
not right.
Hm... I could really go for
some cream croquettes today.
But aren't they
a pain to make?
That's alright; I don't intend
on lifting so much as a finger.
Wait... What are
you getting at?
You're the lackey.
It's not like
I make the rules.
Never thought
I'd say this,
but I miss how you
used to cook for me.
Frozen?
Not on your life.
Don't get choosey...
You're lucky I'm even
willing to make these...
Anything else?
Impulse item aisle!
I second that!
Hey, Yomi?
What's up?
Am I... Am I really
all that helpful?
Where on earth did you
get an idea like that...?
May really got under your
skin, huh...? Oh, sweetie...
Don't let it
bother you...
She has her opinion of your
skills and I have mine.
We're home!
What an entrance...
Thank you...
Kagura, my dear...
Your father has
returned to us...
He's a bit drained
from his journey...
I'm sure it would do him
good to be looked in
on by his precious little
girl now that he's back...
Okay.
Kagura?
Yes, sir...
I'm coming
into the room now.
Can I help with that?
Will you be alright?
If I can manage
not to die...
It's slow to act, but the Bane
Stone does aid with recovery...
There's nothing to fear.
Yes, sir...
It must hurt, though.
Pain is nothing...
When did you
injure your leg?
I, uh...
This morning, sir.
Your guard was down.
It won't happen again,
sir. I promise.
Empty words will be no
surrogate for cold resolve
once Byakuei is
your responsibility.
Sir.
Spirit Beasts are creatures
of terrible majesty
and power, Kagura.
Byakuei,
in particular...
Our ancestors used their own
bodies to hold him in check.
They tethered their souls -
their very essence-
to that awful strength
by a great seal...
This is the heritage
representatives of our bloodline
have passed down and
protected for generations.
One summons Byakuei through
a precise loosening of the seal,
careful that his devouring
jaws seek out only spirits...
Take heed, though:
Once a soul is bound to him,
it can never be unbound.
The moment one
lets him free...
One's soul is ripped asunder
and cast into oblivion.
Never, ever forget that.
Do I make myself clear?
Sir.
Grow stronger.
Command to mobile units.
We've got multiple
Category C's running amok
throughout the city.
All units proceed to
the nearest hotspot
and eliminate all
targets on sight.
Okay, this is some
serious B.S...
Where the hell are
they all coming from?!
I've got a clean house
here... What's next?
This upsurge
doesn't bode well...
Something powerful
is on the move...
I'll let SDCD
handle the vermin.
Hey, how're things
looking near you?
Tons of Category Cs...
It's nuts!.
Why are there so many
of them all of a sudden?
Wish I knew...
Whaddaya say we split up
to cover more ground...?
Think you can handle
them without me?
Yes!
I'll catch
you later then.
Now where to?
Wow... It's so creepy
in here after hours.
Oh, grow up...
I would have hit the
one-minute mark
if you hadn't
chickened out on me.
We could've stayed
here all night
and you never
would have hit it.
What the heck...?
Some genius dropped
a hairclip! Ow...
Everyone's already
gone home for the day.
I don't think the
nurse is around.
It's okay. All I need
is a Band-Aid.
But her office would
still be locked...
Right?
You know, at night
this place looks like
it ought to be in a
horror movie or something.
What's wrong with you?
Best be on the
lookout for things that
"go bump in the night"...
I'll bet you anything some
student committed suicide here.
Enough with that...!
Uh... Oh...
Your foot again...
Wait. That's, like,
way too much blood...
'Cause it isn't mine...
Wha...?
Uh... Is that what
I think it is?
Where did it go...?
Have I been tracking
the wrong target?
What?
Show your true self!
Why? Curious?
I must rid the world of spirits
who defile the natural order.
You're funny.
Are you the one responsible
for unleashing this havoc?
That's one way of
putting it, I guess...
Spirits are attracted to
the power of my stones.
Really?
That's right...
My Bane Stones.
You...
You vile thing...!
Ah...
You know I wasn't sure at
first, but I really think
I'm starting
to like you...
Heh... You've
got secrets...
Dark ones...
I can feel it...
Envy... Hatred.
Ambition...
You can't...
How do you know that?
Trust me... I know
evil when I see it.
It gathers around me like
butterflies to a flower.
Stop...
I can't breathe...
Latchers are the last
thing we need right now.
Kagura...
Don't make me do this!
Just stay back...!
I'm warning you...!
Please!
My obligation...
Is to rid
the world of spirits
who defile
the natural order...
My obligation...
Is to rid the world of spirits
who defile
the natural order...
My obligation...
Is to rid the world of spirits
who defile
the natural order...
Tsuchimiya?
On the next
Ga-rei: Zero:
Chains of Blame.