The... Ministry
of Environment?
Yeah... We're
government agents...
The Supernatural Disaster
Countermeasure Division.
Basically, it's our job
to dispose of any ghosts
in the area.
Kagura!
Yomi... Yomi!
I'm so sorry!
Yomi... Yomi...
I had to.
I'm sorry!
Yomi!
Tsuchimiya!
Yatchin?
What the heck
is going on?! Tell us!
Her first Category D
was someone she knew?
That must have
been hard on her.
Not only that,
but it was a Latcher controlling
her acquaintance's dead body.
Not a simple phantom.
I see.
Since the incident,
paranormal activity has declined
and spirit pressure
has returned to normal
in all areas.
What about
the singularity?
There haven't been any
reports of it being seen
since it last appeared
near the Arakawa River
at nineteen hundred
fifty hours.
That makes me nervous...
I want the disposal team
downgraded to standby...
Have the observation
team keep a close watch.
Right.
And also...
Tell Kagura that I'd like
her to take some time off.
That's a good idea...
As much as we might like
to keep her around to help
with the workload, someone
in her fragile mental state
could easily make mistakes
that would put
the whole team at risk.
What a cold way
of putting it.
I could try to make this easier
for Kagura if you'd like.
If you have any ideas,
I'd love to hear them.
What do you think about
giving Yomi Isayama
some time off, too...?
If Kagura believes she's
being given special treatment,
she won't be able to relax
during her time away...
Yomi can keep her company
while providing mental care.
My.
What is it?
Oh, nothing...
I just didn't realize your
coldness could be so sweet.
Excuse me?
As I'm sure you've all
heard, Nurse Nakabayashi
was recently killed
in a car accident.
A new nurse, Itabashi, has
been assigned to replace her.
The Health Committee
will have a short meeting
right after school...
Are you paying attention,
Miss Manabe?
Yes, sir.
Make sure you
remember to attend.
You wanted to speak
with me, Brother?
I've decided to transfer
responsibility
for the family to Yomi...
a bit...
sooner than expected.
But Naraku...
Don't tell me-
No, don't worry, Yu.
I'm not dying... At least,
not that I know of, anyway.
Of course, when you're as old
as I am, anything can happen.
I'll be able to breathe easier
if the transfer takes place
while I can still walk.
I understand.
I've decided to make
everything official
when we have
the next clan meeting...
I simply
don't see the point
in delaying the
inevitable any longer...
Yu... I want you to make the
arrangements for the ceremony...
Will you?
That's quite an honor...
May.
Yes, Father?
You heard what
your uncle said...
I'll need your help
with the preparations.
Yes, sir.
Takahashi.
Here.
Tamiya.
Tsumura.
Here.
Tsuchimiya...
Is Tsuchimiya
absent again?
Oh...
Please, come in.
Is there something
I can do for you today?
No...
Not really...
Thank you.
I see. In any case,
I'm the new school nurse.
You can call me Nurse Itabashi.
It's nice to meet you.
Um... hi.
May I ask what
happened to your leg?
Oh... it was...
just some glass.
Come here.
Have a seat.
Yes, ma'am.
Glass, huh?
What happened?
I... broke a window.
How dangerous.
It looks like it's
healing up nicely...
I doubt you'll
even have a scar.
You should
be more careful.
Girls are delicate.
Yes, ma'am.
All set.
Good as new.
Thank you
for your help.
If it needs to be changed
again, please come see me.
I'll put a fresh
one on for you.
Oh, no. I didn't
hurt you, did I?
No...
It's not that...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry...
I just...
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry...
Please...
I'm sorry!
Please, forgive me.
Why are you crying?
You're the one who
killed her, remember?
Yatchin!
You did kill her, didn't you?
So what are you crying about?
Don't just sit there;
say something!
I said say something,
murderer...!
What are you crying for?
Yatchin...
Who are you going
to kill next, Kagura? Me?
Take it easy...
I'm right, huh...?
You're going to kill Miku
and me both, aren't you?
Stop it!
And I liked you!
I liked you, Kagura...
I liked you and her.
Why did it have to
turn out like this?
Don't just stand
there, staring...!
Don't you have anything to say
for yourself after what you did?
Open your mouth
and say something!
Stop it!
Go ahead...
Hit me.
I don't blame you...
You can hit me
as much as you want.
I deserve it...
It's my job...
but that doesn't
make it right.
It isn't like
I wanted to kill her...
I just wanted to
protect her...
I don't know why it
happened this way!
Tsuchimiya...
It's because...
I was wrong.
I shouldn't've done it.
I was wrong; I know that now!
So go ahead...! You're
right to be mad at me!
Just hit me...
as much as you want.
I won't stop you.
You... big dummy.
Yatchin...
I'm home!
Yomi, hello.
Uncle Yu. May.
Hello. Are you here
to see my dad?
No... Our business
is done for the day.
Naraku tells me you're doing
excellent work... Yomi.
Excellent...?
I wouldn't say that.
Don't be so modest.
You're carrying the
Shishio, after all...
It only stands to reason you
would make a name for yourself.
That weapon is our most
sacred family heirloom...
Under normal
circumstances,
you never even would
have held it, so-
You would do well to
remember that. Are we clear?
Yes.
What's wrong... Yomi?
It's nothing.
Take care of yourself.
Yeah...
I guess the Tsuchimiyas have
always been a Vanquisher family.
Someday it'll be my turn
to become a full-fledged
Vanquisher, too...
which means that I'll bond with
our family's Spirit Beast.
Its name is Byakuei
and it's been in our
family for generations.
I'll have to bind Byakuei to
my soul in order to keep it
sealed to us.
Every Tsuchimiya
before me has done it,
and it won't be long
before the duty passes to me.
Wait, so then all those times
you were absent from school,
and those texts
from the hospital
that got you out early-
Yep...They were all part of my
responsibilities to my family.
That is really messed up.
I just can't believe
there's a family out there
that forces a kid to
take on that kind of job!
I'm only doing the work
my family has always done.
That's even more messed up.
You didn't ask for this.
How can they drop
all that in your lap?
I don't know...
I just know
this is my fate.
That's the worst part...!
All this 'duty' and 'fate'
talk, it's ridiculous!
But I guess if it's
something you really feel
like you have to do,
then I can't stop you.
Well, I don't want to...
It's just how things are.
Something wrong?
No... Sorry,
it's nothing.
Hey...
You don't really want to inherit
that family job someday, do you?
Well, I-
Ma'am.
Oh, hello, Kiri.
Look at this.
We received a report from the
spirit energy observation team.
The singularity
has reappeared.
Oh, dear... It seems
there are two now.
We've tracked its progress,
and the larger one's energy
field is smaller than it was.
You're suggesting...
the singularity has divided.
Well, ma'am.
It's a possibility.
Good job...
It's too bad you're dead.
You would've been
sliced in two.
A shared strike is a loss...
It doesn't do you any
good to gain an opening
if it means you lose
an arm in the process.
Try to remember that.
I will.
Still... You've
gotten much better...
I'd been training
a lot longer than you
before I learned to deflect
like you just did.
Yomi...
I just...
I don't know if I should
keep training like this.
Kagura...
I'm scared, Yomi.
I don't think I really
understood what it meant to do
this kind of work...
I was so amazed when I saw
you use your Spirit Beast...
It all seemed so cool,
fighting evil spirits
and protecting people
all the time...
But now...
I don't know...
I'm not sure.
Kagura.
Whaddaya think
I should do?
I don't know either.
I can tell you to keep at it
or that you should quit...
but either way, it's
your decision to make...
Nobody else can
make it for you...
You'll have to choose.
You can worry about it
all you want for now...
But it doesn't matter
what anyone else says.
All that matters is you follow
what you truly believe
in your heart...
I don't think I would have
been able to make it this far
if I hadn't.
You wouldn't?
And whatever it
is you decide to do,
even if that's not working
with us anymore...
I'll stand by you, okay?
I swear...
I'll always be there
to support you.
Ah... It's Yatchin.
One of your friends
from the other day?
Yeah... She wants
to take me out to lunch.
Great...! Sounds like
a pretty good friend...
She must appreciate what
you're going through.
Not entirely...
Maybe some.
That's enough... Hey,
at least she's trying...
Now go get some lunch.
Bye! See ya later!
Hi, Noriyuki.
Yomi?
May...
I am a little
relieved, though.
About what?
Kagura seems to be
cheering up a little.
Yeah, I shoulda guessed you
were thinking of Kagura.
She reminds me a lot of
myself when I was her age.
How so?
A Spirit Beast
killed her family.
She really had no choice
but to become a Vanquisher.
That's hard to go
through alone.
All I wanted to do
was protect her...
to keep her from having to
feel the same pain I did.
Yomi...
I wanted to keep
her safe forever.
Maybe I thought
I could... But...
I guess that's over now.
I'm starting to think Kagura
doesn't need me anymore.
You should see the girl train.
She's picking up techniques
in a few minutes
that took me years to learn.
It won't be much longer before
she's the better warrior.
Kid's got a knack for combat.
It's not just a 'knack.'
It's in her blood.
She was born to the
Tsuchimiya family,
which holds the
strongest Spirit Beast...
And it's obvious that
she has the innate talent
that comes from such a long line
of incredible Vanquishers...
Kagura has something
in her that I never will,
no matter how much I try.
Yomi...
And in spite of it all,
she hasn't decided
if she even wants the job
she's inheriting...
It's ironic.
You've worked hard preparing
to be the successor
to the Isayama family...
There isn't anybody who's
more skilled with a sword...
Plus, people've been calling
you a prodigy for years now.
You're right...
but there are still some
people I just can't satisfy.
You don't need to keep proving
yourself over and over...
You should be
more confident.
I guess you're right.
And if anybody puts you down...
They'll answer to me.
You say worse things about
me than anyone I know.
I could say the same
to you... couldn't I?
Hello?
Hi, Yomi! It's me.
I'm with Yatchin and Miku.
Good... Are you
girls having fun?
Remember how she said
she'd pay for me...?
Well, I lost a card game
so now I have to pay!
Is that right?
I was just calling to see
what you wanted to have
for dinner tonight.
I don't know.
I can cook
if you want me to.
Yeah...? You don't mind...?
Are you sure?
I'm sure. I just feel
like making something.
What do you want?
I'll be okay with
whatever you decide.
But I want you to pick!
Okay then...
How about...
Vegetable curry
is always good.
Great!
I'll see ya later!
Kagura!
Well, here they are!
The parfaits here
are delicious...!
Let's-
You haven't eaten.
Are you full...?
Kagura...
You should've told us.
No...
Sorry, I must've forgotten
to mention I'm on a mini-diet.
You want it?
What the hell...?!
You didn't have
to use the corner!
You're lucky I didn't bite
your tongue off instead.
Turning it off?
I'm off the clock. They'll just
have to make do without me.
Okay. I'm home,
everybody!
I hope you're still
in the mood for curry!
Yomi...?
Uncle Naraku?
Uncle, I'm home...!
Are you here?
Uncle!
Uncle, no!
Hey...!
Sorry I'm late.
What are you doing out here?
Is dinner not ready yet?
Yomi!
Kagura...
What's wrong?
It's your father...
Yomi, I'm sorry!
Where is my dad...?
What's happening?
There you are...!
You picked a fine time to run
off and play with your friends.
We couldn't contact you...
We've been looking everywhere.
May.
Now is not the time.
Go to your father...
and say goodbye.
On the next
Ga-Rei Zero...
"Whereabouts of Revenge."