Here he comes!
Hail Mary, full of grace, the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women,
blessed is the Lord, Jesus Christ.
We've been expecting you.
I'm Alan Elbourne, and I'm the one that
summoned you here today for this reason...
Go on.
I'm listening.
It's about my sister Charlotte.
Two nights ago, she disappeared.
She was in bed, sleeping.
It was the middle of the night.
Several people told us they
saw a carriage outside our house.
The carriage...
belonged to Meier Link, the vampire.
I organized a search party of fifty men,
but it was no use. We couldn't find them.
We were ambushed.
He took my sister and killed my friends.
That's just a down payment.
You'll get the rest when you find her...
$10 million.
But you better move fast.
You've got some competition.
I've hired the Markus brothers,
and they've got a head start on you.
I don't think so.
Huh?
It may be too late for her.
Your sister may already have been tempted.
What then?
You have to get there before that happens!
What do you think we're paying you for?
That's enough!
My son is emotional. Please excuse him.
This has been difficult for all of us.
If you knew my daughter, you'd understand.
She's kind and beautiful and her loss
is more than this old soul can bear.
Now I need to ask you something.
If you find her changed, can you see
that her death is without suffering?
Be kind to her, please.
No. No! We can't do that!
It isn't right!
No, she won't be changed.
You're talking about your daughter!
Alan, listen to me.
It's not easy to ask him for this,
but it's something that must be done.
I'm sorry. You understand.
I understand your position, but...
$10 million is not enough.
What?!
How dare you?!
Stop it! Hold your fire!
I said stop!
I'll double the price.
I'll give you 20 million.
Just bring her back, one way or the other.
Aah! Aah!
Did you see a carriage go by
here with four horses in front?
Uh-uh.
Let me go!
L-Let me go!
Aah!
You're lying.
Oh, damn. We got company...
Lots of company.
Look out!
Oh, man. Is everybody OK?
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Do you believe that?
The place is overrun with them.
He must've been here already.
Well, come on.
Ready or not, here they come.
It's zombie time.
Yeah!
Come and get it, zombies!
Amen to that.
Leila, are you there?
It won't take long, Grove.
Just stay in the tank.
Lock and load.
Uhh!
Yaah!
Not so fast, buddy.
And... fire.
Gotcha.
Rest in peace. Huh?
You hear that?
Sounds like a horse.
It's moving. Uphill.
Let me try.
Right.
Right about...
Hmm.
Right there.
Huh?
Beautiful, just beautiful.
I applaud you, stranger.
Tell me what you're doing here.
If we're in the same game, we should be friends.
Tell me your name.
Mine's Borgoff-Borgoff Markus.
D.
Ah, so that's the guy-the dunpeal hunter.
I've heard about him. He's amazing.
Wake up, Borgoff. He's the
competition, not some buddy of ours.
Come on, what are we doing here?
We just helped him. Think about it.
Yeah, he's right. I agree with him about that.
We help him too much, and he'll take all the money.
If it wasn't for us, he'd be dead by now.
We do the work, and he gets the reward.
Aw, you boys should relax.
We just did the famous dunpeal a little favor is all.
A little favor we can't afford.
Hey, you ever hear the one about the owl and the squirrel?
The squirrel works all summer storing away
stuff for the winter, all kinds of nuts and seeds.
He works real hard.
Then one day, just before the first snow,
he goes outside for one last look around,
when all of a sudden, this owl swoops
down and grabs him, carries him off.
"Ah, what a shame," says the squirrel.
"What's going to happen to all that good food?"
Heh heh heh heh!
Ha ha!
Ah, that's a good one.
Yeah, hilarious.
You get it, you guys? That
stupid squirrel is all, like-huh?
Leila.
Hey, Leila, what's the rush?
What's with her?
So you're outnumbered 4 to 1. So what?
They do have a head start, but when the
sun comes up, the heat will slow 'em down.
Speaking of sun and heat, I know I don't
need to remind you of your susceptibility.
It's called heat syndrome, and the
last time you ignored it, you almost...
Don't worry.
I hate it when you say that.
What-what are those? Tracks?
Let me see.
Yes. These are definitely their tracks.
6 hours old, I'd say.
OK. Uhh.
I'm suffocating now.
Hey, what was that?
That's funny.
I could've sworn I heard something.
Quiet.
Sandmantas, most likely.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Great flesh! Sandmantas galore.
Talk about your prehistoric pigeons.
They're filthy animals. You know, they're just filthy.
Well, I guess we'd better just turn back. It's
a shame, really, 'cause, you know, we could've...
hey, whoa! Whoa, whoa!
Hey! No, no.
Go back, man. Go back. Come on. You're crazy!
Come on, man.
Please, let's just go back. No, no! Here we go! Oh!
Yaah! Not wise.
Yaah!
Aah!
Ohh!
All right, that's enough.
That was good. OK, now, we survived that. Could we stop?
Did you ever hear the expression.
"Too close for comfort"? 'Cause
that was damn uncomfortable.
What is it?
A resting house?
I didn't think anybody had those anymore.
He must be in there.
Wow, it blends in nicely.
OK. Whoa.
Here we are.
OK, I can see 'em.
How many are there?
Two, I think... a man and a woman.
Look out for the exit door.
OK. No door.
No door there.
Still no door.
No.
Are you sure about that door?
No. No.
What was that?
She's out of her mind!
Door! Door!
You're dead!
Aah! Aah!
Uhh!
Uhh! Ohh! Uhh! Unh!
I'm here for the young woman.
I wouldn't recommend it, dunpeaL.
Taking on a vampire at night is a
mission for morons and fools. Which are you?
She's here by her own choice, dunpeal.
So unless you're the kind of man who would take
a woman against her will for the money in it...
and I'm sure it's a lot.
I suggest you save your sorry ass
now and leave us to travel in peace.
I would if I could believe you, Meier.
Your credibility, however, is less
than impeccable under the circumstances.
You kidnapped the girl.
Aah!
Meier!
Uhh! Ow, my nose! My nose!
What happened? What'd I miss?
She called out his name.
It may be true, what he said.
Nah, she's just ignorant.
She's a child. She doesn't know him yet.
She doesn't know what he's capable of.
Ooh.
Oh, that poor girl. She's-she's bleeding
pretty bad. I mean, she won't last long.
It's a shame, really...
To waste all that good blood, I mean. Come on, admit it.
You're tempted.
I mean, I know you are.
Uhh...
Ma.
Mmm.
Mother.
Wait. I was just kidding, you know?
Come on, let's go. We got work to do.
The money-come on, think of the money.
Huh?
Uhh.
Hey, what did you do to me?
I bound your wound and stopped your bleeding.
That's all.
Oh, I get it.
You think you can just go ahead and tear
off the clothes of whoever you come across.
That's what you think, isn't it, dunpeal?
You should go back home and nurse your wounds.
What are you, my mother?
You called out for your mother before.
I thought you might be needing her.
Hey!
Uhh. Uhh.
Uhh.
I see her.
When the last vampire is extinct,
who will mourn our passing?
Will she?
Will anyone?
Can anyone understand this pain, this loneliness?
I told you so, didn't I?
Hmm? I said leave the girl alone.
She's trouble.
She's competition, you know.
You aided and abetted the enemy.
I hope this is the right way.
Trust me. I know how they think, these vampires.
When they're threatened, they all head for Barbarois.
They're so predictable.
Barbarois, yeah.
I really hate that place.
Full of lunatics and monsters
and that old crazy man, you know?
Does it hurt very much, Leila?
Leila?
Huh?
Your injury-does it hurt you?
Oh, no, it's fine.
I...
Grove, you should lie down.
You look tired. You need to rest.
Don't worry about me.
Leila...
Who dressed the wound? Was it him?
You can tell me.
It was him, wasn't it? The dunpeal hunter?
Mm-hmm.
Leila, I'm warning you...
He-he's trouble. He's against us.
I don't know why he did that.
Grove, please don't tell anyone, OK?
He stopped there,
but what for?
Let's find out.
Nolt and Kyle, you come with me.
Leila, you stay in here with Grove.
OK, is everybody ready?
Always.
Ready. Yeah.
Hey, Nolt,
see what's going on in there, will you?
It may be a trap.
Yeah. We'll cover you.
It'll be my pleasure, gentlemen.
Aah!
Huh?
It's nothing but a lousy piece of cloth.
What the hell?
Bastard. Unbelievable.
Hey, watch out!
Huh?
So...
You dare to enter Barbarois.
I assume it's arrogance and not
stupidity that brings you here, gentlemen.
Or perhaps it's ignorance.
You're skillful hunters, I can see,
but you are no match for the Barbarois.
5,000 years of isolation have made us invincible.
Aah! Unh!
Huh?
What?
What the hell's going on?
The shadow...
Watch out for the shadow.
What are you talking about?
The shadow? What do you mean?
Hey, Nolt?
Hey, Nolt, what the hell happened to you, huh?
He-he's dead.
No, he's not!
Come on, Nolt. Come on!
Snap out of it! Come on!
Oh, my god! Damn it, come on!
I need you!
Oh, God!
Oh!
Oh, God, we're getting close.
Those are the windmills of the Barbarois.
I really wish you'd turn back.
There must be another way.
There isn't.
I am D the hunter.
I have business with the Barbarois.
Oh, no.
So, I see you have dismounted. You have respect
for your elders. That's very considerate indeed.
I want you to stop your protection of Meier Link.
You what?
Ha ha ha. You know, you make me laugh. That's a good one.
I see you are a very humorous young
man. And beautiful, too, I might add.
Or does that make you uncomfortable to
have an old lech like me admire you so?
You take me for a fool.
Someone paid me $100 million to
protect Meier Link. Can you top that?
Well, you drive a hard bargain there, old man.
What if I can?
You really are entertaining me, Mr. Stranger.
I suppose you know our reputation.
The Barbarois serve the people of the night,
and after 5,000 years, I don't think we're
about to change our stripes any time soon.
Although, if we did for anyone, it would be for you.
I have seen many a dunpeal, but
somebody like you, I've never seen before.
That's why it's such a pity that you have to die.
I really can't let you leave here alive, now, can I?
I'm afraid you have to die, stranger. So sorry.
The Barbarois are great warriors.
You are a warrior, too, no doubt, and although
you may kill some of us, in the end, we will prevail.
I have sworn to protect the carriage.
Prepare to die.
Fool.
What's he doing in there?
Borgoff, are we ready yet?
Grove...
We have no choice. We need your help on this, Grove.
Think you can do it there, man?
Give it to me. I'm waiting.
Don't push yourself too hard now. I mean it, OK?
I want you back.
You know, I really have nothing
against the Barbarois personally.
It's a shame I'll have to kill so many of you.
Indeed, I admire your loyalty and your devotion to duty.
Yet I wonder about the fairness when
you allow one to fight against so many.
But if that will entertain you...
Ohh.
I see.
Well, you make a good argument, young man.
How interesting.
Old man...
I think the fellow is right.
Please allow the three of us to entertain our
young guest here, unless he thinks that's unfair.
Three against one... how unfair.
Three against one-unfair.
That's enough.
You mock us with your ridiculous antics, Benge.
I will not have you distracting us from the job
at hand, which is the protection of the carriage.
We'll do things my way. Huh?
What the devil is that?
Go for it, Grove! Go for it!
Kill all those guys!
Kill every last one of them!
Come on, Grove.
Hold on.
Get the carriage out, now!
Follow me, Tinkerbell.
I'm waiting for you.
Uhh!
Yaah!
Grove.
I've got to say this,
I admire that young hunter's spirit,
although he doesn't stand a
chance against Benge and the others.
Still, it's a pity I'll miss the show.
Oh, well. C'est la vie.
Wake up, D.
What's wrong with you?
It's not fair. It's not fair.
I'll show you what's not fair.
Stay there till you rot, hunter.
Aw, phooey, suckers.
Stop. I beg you.
Say good night.
Kyle, did you happen to see where that girl went?
Maybe she got caught in the wheels.
Go look.
Aah!
Nice, Caroline, very nice.
A little crude, but effective.
They're all yours.
That freakin' monster.
Is everybody all right?
Yeah, but Kyle was outside. He was up on top.
Kyle. Kyle. Where the hell are you, Kyle?
Down here.
You OK?
Quiet. They're still around.
No.
Damn. That idiot.
Well, how convenient this is for me.
Come on out here so I can finish the job.
Your time is up.
Come on, you cowards!
You're going to pay for the pain you caused my brother.
Hey, D, are you awake?
I need your help to swallow up this spell.
You're a slave driver, you know that?
Aah!
Hey, remember to watch out for the shadow, huh?
Try and stay still.
Easier said than done.
And keep your mouth shut.
Aah! Aah! Ahh! Ahh!
That was close.
Waah!
Well, the tank is full of holes.
The fuel's all gone.
We can't drive it like this anyway.
What are we going to do?
What should we do?
Borgoff, any idea?
How's Grove?
Honestly, not too great.
Borgoff, wake up. What are you thinking about over there?
Oh, nothing, really. I was
just thinking about the carriage.
Wonder where it is by now.
Well hell, man, at this point,
it's pretty much anybody's guess.
If you want my opinion,
I'd say they're either setting sail from the port of Ebral
or hiding somewhere deep in the Granerj mountain range.
I sure hope so.
Anyway, we still have to get some fuel,
and the town of Garucia isn't that far away from here.
Kyle, you go with Leila.
I'll stay here and do the repairs.
"If you are seeking the pathway to the stars,
"come to me. I pray for your
safe arrival with all my heart."
"The pathway to the stars..."
I don't know about you, but I sure miss that horse.
What was his name?
Oh, the silent treatment, huh?
Well, I got two words heat syndrome.
Look. Look, I know I'm a parasite, but
haven't I always been a helpful parasite?
Now, you may not care if you die from heat, but becoming
a piece of beef jerky is not a lifelong ambition of mine.
Yeah, well, what's the sound of one hand yapping?
How much?
Oh, no. Keep your money.
Come on. Just take it.
Let's go.
Leila!
Oh, I see.
It's him, isn't it?
Kyle, why don't you start back without me?
There's something I want to do here first.
Back off.
Have I told you you're quite
irresistible in that sexy, skintight getup?
No. Tell me about it.
I just did.
You make sure you watch your back with that guy, Leila.
I'd like a beer.
I've just been admiring your fancy weapon there.
Don't worry. I have no plans to use it anytime soon.
That's good.
That's good, because I have no plans to let you keep it.
Give it up.
You heard me, little girl.
Uhh!
Hmm. Thank you.
Well, here's to you, sheriff.
I'd buy you a drink, but...
Thank you, but no, thanks.
Oh, OK. I was just gonna say you must be awfully
busy with that new dunpeal hunter in the town now.
What dunpeal hunter?
I'd like to buy that horse.
$300,000.
And if you don't like the price, go somewhere else.
Freeze! Put your hands where I can see 'em! Now!
Sheriff, he paid good money for that.
What are you doing?
Take your money and go.
We don't want you here.
We don't sell to dunpeals in this town.
Understand?
Understand me, dunpeal?
You understand.
Wait a minute. That's my horse you're talking about there,
and I'll sell it to whoever I want if
they can afford the price I'm asking.
You can't do that. We have laws against it, Polk.
Good laws and for a damn good reason.
What laws?
Don't play coy, Polk. You know as
well as I, dunpeals aren't allowed.
Not allowed. Right.
I remember a time not that long ago when we
had vampires and dunpeals both around here, but...
And that's why we have the law!
Listen to me whether you want to hear it or
not. You weren't even born when this happened.
Do yourself a favor and listen to the story.
I'm going to tell you about the
time when the children were kidnapped.
There were ten children altogether...
Yeah, I heard about that time.
The kidnappers turned out to be vampires, of course,
and so the townspeople pooled
their money to hire a vampire hunter.
They wanted the best.
And when the hunter came,
he was a very strong and quiet man,
and he did his job, too, which was to return
the children safely back into their parents' homes.
It wasn't easy, but many vampires died
by his hands before this job was over with.
And when it was over and the children
were back home, the people attacked the man.
They said he was a dunpeal half-vampire
himself, so they punished him.
Can't say I blame them for doing that.
You can't trust 'em. That's all that's about.
They were right about that part, Polk.
He did the job.
I see, then, I'll have to take matters into my own hands.
Let him go!
And what is that?
What does it look like, idiot?
Put down your guns!
Polk, you can't know what you're doing.
Put it down.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
You don't know! Put it down now, you old fool!
I would much rather be an old
fool than what you are, sheriff.
Now, don't shoot.
I can tell you I won't think twice about
using this weapon. I might even enjoy it.
Get on your horse, stranger.
Thank you.
No. It's only fitting I thank you.
It's the least I can do.
I may be just an old fool now, stranger,
but I could never forget a face like yours.
And I'll never forget what you done for me backthen.
That's right.
I was one of them kids.
And I always felt bad about that.
The way you was treated. How nobody stopped you.
Nobody thanked you. Instead, the ignorant bastards
ran you right out of our town.
So it's true, isn't it, what they say about you dunpeals?
You don't age. Now, go. I'm getting tired.
Where's Benge?
What's taking him so long?
Well, the horses are rested now.
We better go.
Come on.
Master, what is it? May I help you, sir?
It's still light outside, master!
What?
Leave her alone, Machira.
Yes, sir.
She misses the sunlight. Let her enjoy it.
I am D, a hunter. Your father sent me.
Don't be afraid. I won't hurt you.
You sit in the sunlight. You must not be changed.
So, why do you stay with him?
Last night in the carriage, you called out his name.
Why did you call for him?
I suppose my father has not told
you that I'm in love with Meier.
You don't know who he is.
You can't be in love with him.
Well, I am. If you only knew how good he's been to me.
I love him.
Please believe me. No one else will.
You don't understand.
He is what he is, Charlotte.
You can't change him. He'll take you in time,
and when that happens, I will have to kill you.
Fine. Kill me then.
I would rather die than to go anywhere without him.
Don't take me back there! I mean it!
I simply could not live without Meier.
How sweet that is. Ha!
She loves a vampire.
So very sweet.
Idiot!
You stupid girl! Get up! We're going!
Leave me alone!
You'll do what I say!
Do you have any idea how many people
have died at the hands of your beloved Meier,
this vampire you want to protect?
None!
You fool! And you!
You stay right where you are, my friend.
Sorry, but I really don't want
to have to share any of my profits.
You understand, don't you?
It's business.
Above you.
Aah!
What's wrong? Tell me!
Too much sun!
I warned you about the heat, but you don't listen!
Come on! You can't survive unless you dig a hole!
You need to bury yourself!
Oh! Ha ha ha ha!
Hurry!
Leila? Leila, are you there?
Come in, Leila.
Yeah, I copy.
Thank God! Are you OK?
What's your position?
I'm near Lake Chiffon. Our
game is heading north from here.
We'll catch up.
Leila, do you know what's happened to the dunpeal hunter?
No. I haven't seen him.
All right. Well, take care.
Stay in touch. Borgoff out.
Ha! The tables have turned.
Uhh!
No!
Now, that cleared my head.
I really should return the favor, don't you think, honey?
Don't get any ideas.
Hey, I'm just trying to stay dry here.
If there was any other place
to go, believe me, I'd be there.
As soon as the rain lets up,
I'll be gone from here and from you.
I think I can guess your problem.
Your family was the victim of vampires.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You don't know anything about it.
All right. Perhaps I don't.
This stupid thing, it bothers me.
You really are a weird one, you know that?
In spite of being a dunpeal
hunter and all that that entails.
How did you know about my mother?
You called her name, remember?
She was kidnapped by vampires.
My father went after her. He was
trying to rescue her, so they killed him.
And after a while, my mother returned,
but she wasn't my mother anymore.
She'd been changed.
The people in the village stoned
her to death while I watched.
After that, I left home.
I met the Markus brothers and joined with them.
I wanted to be a hunter to avenge my parents' deaths.
I've seen many terrible things since then-
lives destroyed, families devastated, hopes crushed.
Every time, it seems a vampire is to blame.
I can understand why you'd choose to do it,
but the life of a hunter's no kind of life.
It's the only life I'm any good for now, and it
looks like it's the only life you've ever known,
so I suggest we make a pact.
Since we're both in it for the long haul,
whoever dies first, the other one can come
and bring flowers to their grave. How's that?
It's the rain. Makes me sentimental.
I don't know why I should care
about that. It's just I love flowers,
and I don't think I'll be getting any.
I'm all alone, after all.
We have that much in common, don't we?
That we're both hunters and we're both alone?
Oh, well. I'm being silly.
It doesn't really matter.
I'll do it.
I'll bring you flowers if I
survive this, but I don't expect to.
Oh, stop. I didn't really mean it when I said that.
And anyway, I don't really understand
why you should keep on doing this.
Because I'm a dunpeal.
I don't get to have a life, not like you.
Well, with the rainstorm last
night, they can't be too far away.
We're even now, dunpeal. Understand?
I have a very bad feeling about this.
How so?
I think I finally figured it out, Borgoff.
Well, I'm sure you're right,
if you're thinking they're headed for the castle.
Yeah, that's right, the castle-the Castle of Chaythe.
What are you thinking? We can't go in
there! It would be suicide! It would be insane!
What are you now, afraid of a little
insanity? Since when have we been sane?
We just have to get to them before they reach the castle.
There's a bridge up ahead.
That's where we intercept the carriage.
I remember that trick from the
time we got those vampires at Keldo.
Yeah. It worked that time, and it can work again now.
Leila, come in. Come in, Leila. Over.
Yeah, it's me. I copy.
What's up?
I'm on my way.
Uhh!
Don't move. I'm warning you!
Try anything funny, and you'll be blown to smithereens.
You want to try it?
I didn't think so.
We just want the girl.
Hello there!
She's still human!
Come on, get out of there! Now!
Borgoff, she won't come!
We're doing you a favor!
Come on!
I said get out of there!
Uhh!
Let that be a lesson to you,
you cowardly Barbarois animal!
Borgoff, look!
Borgoff!
What?
What the...
What, is this guy crazy?
Doesn't he know he can't exist
outside here in the sunlight?
I won't let you take her!
Oh, yeah?
Uhh!
Thanks a lot. You're making our job a lot easier.
Hot enough for you?
It's what you deserve!
Uhh!
Over here, hot stuff.
Hoo hoo! Look at him burn!
Here, a little something to help you walk.
How does that feel?
Way to go, moron.
That got him! What now? Don't you...
Look at him!
Hey, where do you think...
Why'd you let her go?
I love you.
Uhh!
I can't go on without you.
What?!
Borgoff, we should just let her kill herself,
and then we can finish him off.
What do you think about that idea?
We get the money if she's dead or alive.
Hey, you're right! OK.
Stop it!
Uhh!
Kyle!
I'll blow you to hell!
Aah!
What?!
No!
I don't want you to worry about these wounds of mine.
They will heal.
Then we shall go to the City of Night in Distant Stars.
When we go there, we can be
alone and free to love each other.
It's true. Believe me.
We'll be there soon.
We're it now.
We're the only ones left,
Borgoff. We should just give it up.
If we make it into that castle,
none of us will make it out alive.
We can't quit now.
We owe it to Kyle and to Nolt to keep going on.
Listen, Borgoff...
Shut up! I won't hear it!
Leila, what do you think?
Grove, they fear us.
They fear us because they know our reputation,
that we never give up and we never can.
If we quit now, we might as well
quit the business, and I can't do that.
I won't do it, till every last one of them is gone.
Master, do you hear?
He's coming.
The castle is nearby.
I'll stay here and deal with him.
We're getting close. The Castle of Chaythe.
Soon we'll be able to see it.
The home of Carmila, the Bloody Countess.
You've heard of her.
For 5,000 years, her rule of
terror lasted, and then that was that.
Your father, the Vampire King, grew angry.
He was impatient with her vanity,
offended by her bloodlust, her gluttony.
He grew so tired
that he killed her while she slept, impaling
her on his sword, and that was it for her.
Except she haunts the place now with phantoms
and demons, but you don't care about that, do you?
But I bet I know what really gets to you, dunpeal, eh?
What really gets to you.
The thought of those two lovebirds giving
birth to another dunpeal, huh? That's it.
See? I know you. I know how
you think. I know how you feel.
I know every move that you make. You can't-uhh!
I'm glad we could meet at last, hunter D.
You are a worthy opponent.
Who hired the Barbarois?
Who were you working for?
Uhh! It was Carmila who hired us, and as
a Barbarois, my duty has been fulfilled.
Now I can die in peace.
I gather from your letter that
you've had a rather difficult time.
I think I can understand what it's like.
Love is not unique to humans, you know.
We vampires are very susceptible.
I hope I can be of service.
We're very grateful, Carmila.
You both must be exhausted.
Perhaps you should rest first.
I'm sure that the young lady would like to freshen up.
Hmm.
You've probably heard rumors about me,
but I can assure you they all stem from jealousy and envy.
I'm not the "Bloody Carmila" they like to portray me as.
Now, behold.
That's it. That is the ship.
It will take you to the City of the Night,
where you can live peacefully at last.
You can be happy there.
There was a time, many years ago,
when every castle had a ship like this one
and the night sky was full of their flashing lights.
Those were the days when vampires flourished
and a love like yours was not so desperately impossible.
So different from today.
Our numbers dwindling, hunted and alone,
we are hopelessly misunderstood,
but you two seem to have beaten the odds.
I'm very, very happy for you.
The ship hasn't been used in years.
I've no idea if it will fly safely, but I'm
sure that's a risk you're prepared to take.
We're very grateful.
I only wish I could go with you.
You look so beautiful.
Mmm.
Why stop?
I want you, Meier. I want all of you.
Why not?
You don't know what it's like, Charlotte,
to live forever in darkness eternal,
forever thirsting for blood despite your best intention.
I can't imagine that life for you. Not for you, Charlotte.
You're so selfish, Meier.
I carry a heavy weight on my conscience...
Those villagers and the bounty hunter and
my family, they still mourn my loss, Meier.
It wasn't your doing, Charlotte.
It was my fault entirely.
Well, then we're both to blame, because
we can't know happiness, not anymore.
I wanted you to be happy, Meier, and so I
abandoned my father and my brother for you.
But their pain set the wheels in motion
for our pain, and so on and on it goes.
All we have is each other now,
and I want to be close to you.
Without that, we have nothing.
All the pain I've caused and all
the agony I feel is nothing now.
And you are everything to me, my love.
We'll talk more on our trip to the
stars, if that's all right with you.
There is some unfinished business I have to attend to.
Do not leave this room. Understand?
D.
Listen, Meier. The woman says she wants to go back home.
I don't believe it.
Charlotte.
I don't know. Something's not right.
Of course, you don't have to take my word for it.
You can judge for yourself.
Let's go.
Leila. Don't go.
Leila, don't go in there.
If you go in there, you're never coming back.
Oh, I'm coming back.
No!
Leila, check upstairs.
I'm on it.
Nice hat.
I know you hate me, D.
Please try and understand.
I loved your father.
What choice did I have?
Huh?!
Ahh!
Nolt! Kyle! Hey!
I don't believe it.
You two sure are a sight for sore eyes.
Ugh!
What are you doing? Get up.
Why aren't you listening?
I said get up.
Go away. I wanna be alone.
Get out of here!
Can you forgive me, D?
D?
I know it's been lonely for you.
I was lonely, too,
until you came along.
Did you hear, D?
It's OK, honey.
It's OK to cry.
I know. I know how you feel.
It wasn't your fault.
It wasn't.
Yes, it was!
Let go!
Wait!
Ugh.
It's just an illusion.
Carmila's playing with us.
Excellent. What fun.
I haven't had this much fun in centuries.
You don't mind, do you? It just
makes things so much more interesting.
You're doing very well, by the way, very well, indeed.
The woman. Where are you hiding her?
Borgoff, what are you doing? We don't have time for this.
Leila, are you in love with this dunpeal?
Are you crazy? What is wrong with you?
Borgoff!
Dunpeal, drop your weapon.
Drop it now! Grrr!
She took you in, didn't she?
Grr! She'll die!
I'm warning you, dunpeal.
Don't come any closer.
Enough! Now you die!
Aaah!
No!
Aaaah!
Grove!
Grove! No!
Lei... la...
Look! She's coming!
Carmila!
The spirit of Carmila!
Dunpeal hunter.
Your mother was human, but your father was a
vampire, and you have betrayed his ancient blood!
You side with humans against us!
Our people are facing extinction,
and you're contributing to their demise.
You stalk and kill your own ancestors, dunpeal.
You should be ashamed!
Your human self is your weaker self.
Humans are nothing more than livestock.
We prey on them as they prey on beasts.
This is the rule of nature!
Your time is coming to an end.
Your kind must face extinction.
You cannot survive. You must die.
That is the rule of nature.
Ah. Very strong words for a dunpeal,
but you seem to forget
our spirits are eternal.
No, Carmila.
Nothing lasts forever.
I see.
I should have known better than to
reason with your kind, dunpeal hunter.
I guess my only option is to use force.
Aaaah!
Aaah!
No! This can't happen!
Aaaah!
Are you the son of the Vampire King?
Who are you?
Who are you, dunpeal?
Such power.
Charlotte, come back. I need you. Please come back.
Mmm. Ohh.
Darling, is that you?
Oh, yes. It's me, Meier.
I'm so happy, Meier,
because we are together now, at last.
Together at last.
You made me happy, Meier.
You let me dream.
You let me dream of our beautiful trip to the stars.
Our dream.
Our beautiful, wonderful dream.
It's not a dream.
We are going to those stars, Charlotte.
Oh, my dear one.
You and I will get away from here.
We will fly together to the City of the Night
where we were meant to be free from all of this.
Where you can rest, my love, finally, and be free.
Yes.
Freedom... at last.
My precious, precious love.
Let's go...
Away from here.
Stop right there, Meier.
I'm taking her back, back to her family, who loved her.
She knew I loved her best of all.
You can't understand it. You've never loved a human.
I've never killed one, either.
You struggle to resist this nature
of ours, but it can't last forever, D.
The urge for their blood is stronger.
If that day comes, then another will hunt me.
It's as simple as that.
Raaaahhh!
What a waste, a sad waste.
Enough of killing.
Enough of misery and death.
I've had enough.
Uhh!
Why...
did you miss
my heart?
She's dead.
The ring is all I need.
I'll take it to her father as proof.
Mind giving me a ride just as far as the next town?
I'd appreciate it.
That reward money would rightfully be mine, you know.
But, hey, I'm generous.
I'll let you keep it just this one time.
Where is he taking her?
Away from here.
Away.
Fly. Come on!
You can make it.
Come on!
Fly away...
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here in this
resting place to bid farewell to our sister.
Into your gentle arms we commend her gracious spirit.
Take her to yourself and give her safe haven,
andthough she struggled in life,
now she knows your blessed peace.
For all who question will find answers,
and all who love
will find contentment, joy, and peace eternal.
For now we see as through a glass darkly,
but then we shall see clearly, face to face.
Mister.
Wait!
Mister, wait!
Um,
excuse me, sir, but I was wondering
if you knew my grandmother Leila.
Yes, it's you, isn't it?
My grandmother told me about you.
So, I'd be honored if you'd come to
our house. My dad would be so happy.
Please?
I appreciate your kindness.
Oh, come on. We don't live very far.
I just came here to keep a
promise to an old friend of mine.
She was afraid no one would mourn her death.
I'm glad she was so wrong.
Huh?
Oh.
I guess I see.
Anyway, thank you for coming, sir.
Good-bye.
GOOd-bye!
Well, that was nice.
You're not so bad after all.
You just dress bad.