[TAKUMI]
What're you looking at, yeah?
[NENE]
Oh! A flier for Herme's.
[TAKUMI]
Oh yeah?
Hey, that's the discount
department store, yeah?
Yep.
There's a really big sale
starting this morning!
[BUER]
Oh!
Can you buy the things
you want at a store like that?
[NENE]
Oh.
I highly doubt they
sell world peace there.
But I'd buy it if they did!
[BUER]
Mm-hmm!
That might be stupidest
thing I've ever heard
in my entire life.
Is there something you
want to buy, Cla-ring?
Not at the moment, no.
Well, is there
anything you need?
[CLARION]
Hmm...
Just equipment and backup.
All right!
Let's go look for some.
So? You ready?
I'm pretty sure you
know this by now,
but don't be stupid and
go anywhere dangerous, yeah?
[BUER]
Mm?
[BUER] Surely you must know
the very existence of a girl is,
in and of itself,
extremely dangerous.
'Tis a lethal weapon that--Ow!
Are you okay?
[PA 8A]
Herme's third anniversary sale
is now underway!
Prices are low, low,
and did I mention low?
Today we're starting a big
sales event for the latest
in disaster-prevention goods!
Hurry up, Mommy.
We're gonna miss the festival!
All right. Fine.
[gasps]
Billy! No running inside!
This place is amazing,
don't you think, Cla-ring?
Okay.
Why don't we start by
checking out the top floor?
Then we can work our way down.
This is gonna be so much fun!
[BUER chuckles]
I can almost smell it.
The swirling greed
of the vulgar masses.
'Tis a lethal weapon that--
[grunts]
[PRESENTER 8A] Because
today marks the beginning
of our brand new sale,
I'd like to introduce you to our
wonderful manager-for-a-day!
The chairman of
the CSGO, Mr. North!
Hello.
First and foremost, thank you
for being here today, folks!
Yes. I am the island's
government chair,
Mr. Janus North!
[CROWD applauds]
[NORTH] This is more than
just one department store's
special bargain sale!
It's a countermeasure
against the recent incident
of terrorism in Vulcan,
and the network outages
that have become
such a big problem
for our community!
Yes.
[CROWD chattering]
[NORTH]
Herme's is here to help.
From good food and
clean drinking water,
to fuel and backup power,
we have everything
you need and more!
[CROWD chattering]
[NORTH] And in the event
of a catastrophic disaster,
we offer these goods to
islanders free of charge!
[CROWD cheering]
I'm sincerely grateful
to Herme's department store
for helping the CSGO.
Cooperation between the
public and private sectors
will improve the lives
of all citizens of Cenancle!
[PRESENTER 8A]
And now, Mr. North,
as a way of showing our thanks,
a very special guest
would like to deliver you
a bouquet of the finest flowers!
Oh! It's me! Hooray!
[VLIND] I've been
waiting for this moment!
[NORTH]
What's this?
Chairman North!
Great misgivings have arisen
among the general populace
regarding your
extravagant private life,
palatial residence,
and dubious purchase
of a super deluxe
luxury custom limousine
that can't even fit in a
parking space here at Herme's.
Care to comment on the
growing discontent, sir?
I beg your pardon?
The sensible residents
of this island
don't want a diplomat
dressing in rags.
They want a refined leader.
You're dodging the
question, Chairman!
What did you say?!
Just who the hell
do you think you are?!
[VLIND] If you want
to know, I'll tell ya!
I'm Cenancle Island's
futuristic heartthrob journalist
who just got the scoop of a
lifetime that'll carry her
all the way to
international stardom!
But you can call me Vli--
I think you might be delusional.
Owie, owie, owie
[NENE]
Cla-ring,
can we please take that
beautiful elevator over there?
It lets you see outside.
No.
What's wrong? Do you
have trouble with heights?
No.
It's inadvisable from
a security standpoint.
I avoid the risk of snipers.
Tempered glass is
utterly powerless
against .50 caliber ammo.
[NENE]
Mm?
[elevator chimes]
[NORTH]
Who does that girl think she is?
Disrespecting me in
front of all those people...
[SECRETARY]
I apologize, sir.
A freelance journalist evidently
slipped into the mix.
Which floor would you like, sir?
The one with the yakisoba!
The 20th floor.
Right!
[NORTH]
It's a high-grade android!
Two of them!
[NORTH] Those darn
things are everywhere.
Because of them,
the media is always carrying on
about how robots
are stealing jobs
and how the economy is ruined.
[BUER] My fifth leg
is whispering to me!
An ominous creeping chaos looms!
Uh... I'm so sorry. I, uh...
[BUER] I feel it!
It seetheth! It surgeth!
'Tis a network disturbance!
[ALL]
Huh?
Wake up.
It's another network
disturbance, ma'am.
[VLIND]
Oh, who cares about that?
It's not even
newsworthy anymore.
But I bet I'd win an
award if I got the scoop
on what's causing it
to begin with.
[CAMERA PERSON]
The data transmission.
It stopped.
Well, don't just sit there.
Do something about it!
[CAMERA PERSON]
Like what?
[VLIND]
Huh? What the heck?
It's a fire!
That's a scoop, isn't it?
A scoop?
[CAMERA PERSON]
A hot one!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention.
A network disturbance is
currently occurring here
in Mercury.
I repeat, we have
a network disturbance.
I wonder if people
have any clue
as to the amount
of economic loss
caused by these
damn network outages.
Let's return to
headquarters, Mr. Chairman.
All right.
Why did we stop?
This is just perfect!
Where does this leave me
now that I've already given
this stupid department store
preferential treatment
for their contributions?
Please, sir.
You're right, but you
must stop carrying on.
Or I'll have to use my stun gun.
During a network disturbance,
a robot's no better than an
unplugged vending machine.
There's no need to worry.
They probably have
restrictions on their
recording devices, anyway.
Uh... 'Scuse me?
I still think you should show
a little bit more composure!
[NENE]
If it's a network disturbance,
it'll probably be over
in about 30 minutes.
[NORTH]
That's not good enough! Ugh!
[SECRETARY]
Mr. Chairman?
Don't you get it?
I'm headed straight for
an emergency situation
and there's no turning back.
Emergency number one?
Or emergency number two?
[NORTH chuckles]
Emergency number two.
[SECRETARY gasps]
[SECRETARY]
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
We have an emergency here!
Security, please respond!
[SECRETARY]
No luck.
Well, sir? How long do we have?
Ten minutes. No, five!
[SECRETARY]
Sir!
Please. Use these.
Come on.
I know it's not ideal, but it's
only me and the androids.
If worst comes to worst, sir...
[NENE]
Excuse me,
but there's something
you should know.
[NORTH]
Hm?
I'm not an android.
I'm a human being.
Please excuse my
manners, young miss!
I'm Janus North,
chairman of the CSGO.
It's a true pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
It's really nice
to meet you, too.
My name's Nene!
[SECRETARY]
Maintaining his public image
is only making it
harder for him.
He's about to break!
[NENE]
Are you okay?
[NORTH gasps, cries]
[SECRETARY]
Oh, sir!
Just try to breathe slowly.
[NORTH wheezes]
[SECRETARY] Please
hang in there, Mr. Chairman!
[NENE]
Cla-ring.
[whispering]
[NENE]
Pandora Device. Open!
Decode skill.
Elpis Series! Healing Space!
[NORTH]
My heart... My troubles...
It's all being healed!
[NORTH] My painful
memories are fading away.
[NORTH]
Nope! Not working!
[SECRETARY]
Mr. Chairman!
Are you all right, sir?
[NORTH]
I don't know.
Maybe it's not so bad.
Maybe it's just gas?
[SECRETARY]
Gas?
[NORTH] When I try relaxing,
it's actually not so painful.
[SECRETARY gasps]
Mr. Chairman!
Be patient until we get out!
Please, don't give up!
Cla-ring?
It's open.
Excellent idea, Cla-ring!
[NORTH]
T... T... Toilet!
[SECRETARY]
That was close.
[BUER] Ah!
Verily, now is a golden time!
Indeed!
It's kind of dark
in here, isn't it?
Hey, look. I could open this!
Nene, there's danger beyond!
[NENE]
Huh?
[NORTH]
You sure saved my skin, yes.
[SECRETARY]
We are incredibly grateful.
[NORTH]
I owe you big time.
[NENE]
Uh...
[NORTH]
Huh?
No!
[FIREFIGHTER 8A]
Where's our backup?
[FIREFIGHTER 8B]
I don't know!
[FIREFIGHTER 8A] The
chain-of-command must be all
screwed up thanks
to the network outage!
[FIREFIGHTER 8C] The sprinklers
and alarms didn't even go off?
What's going on here?
In breaking news,
a raging fire just broke out
at Herme's department store!
Panic reigns here
at the tragic scene.
Authorities are clueless
as to what might have caused
this fire in the first place!
Do you think it's possible
this was premeditated arson?
[FIREFIGHTER 8D] Are you
saying this was terrorism?
[VLIND]
Burn, baby! Burn!
[FIREFIGHTER 8D]
What do you think you're doing?
[VLIND]
Uh oh!
She just ran away!
Maybe she's involved!
Come back here!
[SECRETARY]
Sir, this is a dead end!
[NORTH] Great! They're already
done evacuating the building!
The alarm never even went off!
Careful, Cla-ring,
you might fall.
[CLARION] The stairs are
still intact on the level
right below us.
It does look like we
might be able to escape
if we can make it down there.
Damn. I wish I was 20 years
younger than I am.
Could you fly back then?
[NORTH yells]
[NORTH coughs]
Damn!
What the hell could be
giving off poisonous gas?
[coughing]
[SECRETARY] If we don't get
out of here, we'll suffocate!
[NENE]
Here. Use this.
Thank you, dear.
It's Nene, isn't it?
If we could find a rope, too,
that would be a big help!
You see anything?
Unable to see.
[NORTH]
Fine then.
You all stay here. I'll go.
Yes, sir.
But wait... You can't.
Don't worry about me.
I'll find us a way outta here.
I'm coming with you,
Mr. Chairman.
Nene.
Thanks, Cla-ring.
[NENE] There's no getting
through this sales floor,
is there?
[CLARION] It's over 300 degrees
Celsius beyond the firewall.
The lower floors are
approaching 400 degrees.
Temperatures are still rising.
But our durability will
allow for quick passage
through the flames.
I recommend we leave right now.
Cla-ring, hold on a second.
Those two people
are still inside.
I'm afraid that their chances
of survival are very low.
That's not true!
There's gotta be some way
we can all escape together!
Hey! Look!
That'll do the trick!
Cla-ring. Help me save them!
[NENE]
Pandora Device. Open!
Decode skill. Elpis Series!
Couturier!
[SECRETARY]
Chairman North.
The fire's spread
to the stairway.
[NORTH]
Perfect.
I can't afford to die now,
especially not in
a place like this!
[SECRETARY]
I don't exactly feel like dying
along with you, either.
[BOTH yell]
Damn it, there's
gotta be some other way
outta this hell hole!
I'm sorry.
But we had to act fast!
[NORTH]
What's this? Whoa!
Careful, sir.
You don't wanna
bite your tongue.
[NENE]
Cla-ring.
Will we make it through?
No problem.
But all this
audio noise is a drag
on the visualization processing.
[NENE]
Okay. I'll do what I can!
[NORTH]
Echolocation?
You mean they're
visualizing sound?
Without the proper equipment,
how is that even possible?
[SECRETARY 8A coughs]
I can't breathe.
[NENE]
Here, use this!
[SECRETARY] Aren't you
going to need some air, too?
We'll be fine for a while.
We have plenty of oxygen
stored inside of us.
Please help yourself!
Almost there, everyone.
[NORTH]
That's right!
There was a report of an
adepter moving to this island.
I wonder if it meant
these two girls.
[CLARION] Warning.
Obstacle detected, Nene.
Leave it to me!
[NORTH] Could they truly
be successful full cyborgs,
when there are still
so few of them worldwide?
That doesn't seem very likely.
[NORTH] Then again, stranger
things have happened.
If they are full cyborgs,
can they really straddle the
line between man and machine
this freely?
[NORTH]
Amazing!
I can't believe we actually
made it to the emergency stairs!
[NORTH]
You're incredible.
Who on earth are you two?
I'm Nene Nanakorobi,
and this is Cla-ring.
[CLARION]
It's Clarion.
And they're both adorable, too.
[BILLY coughing]
Oh no!
I recommend that
we leave immediately.
No, Cla-ring. We can't leave.
That child needs our help!
Sorry, but there's no time.
Yeah, but...
If we don't do something
to save him, he's going to die!
By necessity, our
actions are the outcome
of optimal decisions.
It's not your responsibility.
Nene?
Uh... Sorry.
It's just... The thing is...
We all need...
[NENE]
Daddy! Mommy!
[CLARION]
We have to get out of here now.
This building's
structural materials
won't last long in this fire.
There's also the danger
of combustible gas.
We're running out of time.
You go ahead
without me, Cla-ring.
Sorry. But I have to save him!
Billy!
Someone help me, please!
My son is trapped inside!
[RUBBERNECKER 8A]
Survivors!
[ALTMAN]
Chairman!
Thank goodness you're safe!
[NORTH]
Well...
It's all in a day's work,
I suppose.
But never mind me; where
are those two brave girls
we found inside who helped
us escape from the fire?
Have you seen them anywhere?
They were right behind us?
Did anyone else come out?
No, I'm afraid not.
Just you and the lady,
Mr. Chairman!
[NORTH]
You're kidding!
That can't be.
Because we all escaped together!
This is a disaster!
Poor Nene Nanakorobi!
And Cla-ring, too!
[ALTMAN]
Hm?
That can't be...
Are they inside?
[NENE]
Hang on!
You're going to
be all right now!
[NENE]
We gotta move fast!
[crashing noise]
Everybody please stand back!
It's not safe here!
[crashing noise]
The stairway...
[beeping noise]
[NENE]
The cylinder's running out!
[NENE] I need to force out
all of my internal oxygen.
That'll buy us some time.
[BILLY coughing]
We're all right.
I just gave you some good luck.
So we'll make it out for sure.
[NENE]
My oxygen levels are low.
But still!
I won't give up!
No matter what!
[NENE]
I have to survive.
I have to apologize for
being so mean to Cla-ring.
[CLARION] I still haven't
found anything I want, Nene.
[NENE]
Cla-ring. You came back.
Oh no... Your ear's burnt.
Are you gonna be okay?
Hey! See that?
Something's up there!
[ALTMAN gasps]
[NENE] But I told you
to get away from me.
[CLARION]
Nene's life is the top priority.
The child is not.
[NENE]
You're wrong.
[CLARION]
Then what do you want to do?
[NENE]
What do I want to do?
I want to save him.
[ALTMAN]
No! They're falling too fast!
[ALTMAN gasps]
[NENE]
Cla-ring.
We all have to make it
out of here in one piece!
[CLARION]
Agreed.
[VLIND]
Huh?
[VLIND screams]
[VLIND yelling]
What is this?
[CLARION]
Give him to the rescuers.
Make sure he survives.
Okay. Right. Sure thing.
[FIREFIGHTER 8A]
Over here!
There's a woman and her child
who need medical
attention right away!
Wait... Do you mean me?
Billy!
Mommy!
He's fine.
Not to worry, ma'am.
Oh! Thank goodness
you're not hurt!
Thank you for saving my son!
How can I ever repay you?
[CROWD 8B]
You're incredible!
[CAMERA PERSON]
Way to go!
You're a rockstar!
What?
[ALTMAN sighs]
Little Nene and
poor little Cla-ring.
They died trying
to save our lives.
Chairman?
Relax, those two
made it out alive.
[NORTH]
Hm?
Cla-ring?
Are you okay?
[CLARION] Yes, I am fine,
and the child is, too.
I'm so sorry.
I really am.
It is Clarion
who must apologize.
You definitely made the
right decision back there.
I promise you...
Next time, we'll get
you something you want.
You have my word on that,
all right, Cla-ring?
That sounds perfect.
[BUER] I am afraid thou canst
go no farther on that leg.
'Twould be wise to stop and
seek aid from a professional.
[CLARION] Negative.
Nene is the top priority.
[TAKUMI]
Sheesh!
No sooner did I say
don't go anywhere dangerous
than the two of you
go and do this, yeah!
[SUBORDINATE 7C]
Colonel Kurtz!
BUER has stabilized!
This is the result
of a single sneeze.
Well...
Let's make sure the CDF
doesn't find out about this.
Quick question, Cla-ring.
What kinda stuff did you want?
I could use some knives,
guns, smoke screens,
and electromagnetic
capture nets.
That sure is some
old-school equipment.
How about we get you
a Beam Rifle?
Or maybe even a Beam Saber!
I'll ask Takumi about those.
[NORTH]
Whoa!
What happened to my limousine?
[SECRETARY]
It's been crushed, sir.
[NORTH]
Who would do a thing like this?
[VLIND]
Hey, press corps!
One question at a time!
I'm just one reporter.
Albeit the greatest reporter
in the history of reporting,
Vli--
[SECRETARY]
Perhaps she did it, sir?
[NORTH]
Arrest her!