[NENE] Cla-ring, can you
do this with one arm?
No problem.
It's not even a handicap.
Together we can do anything.
Don't forget that, Nene.
Yeah!
[ALTMAN]
Can you open it?
[CDF OFFICER]
Before long, sir.
--[ALTMAN] Hurry.
--[CDF OFFICER] Right.
[ALTMAN] Something
doesn't feel right here.
[VLIND] What is
this place, anyway,
some kind of research facility?
[CAMERA PERSON] Whatever
it is, it's a huge scoop!
[VLIND] No! This
isn't the scoop--
it's just the
tip of the iceberg!
[gasping]
Uh-oh. We're caught.
This is it!
I'll put my life on
the line for a story!
'Cause I'm the world's
favorite reporter--
the one and only, Vli--
It's time for me to show you two
what true fear is all about.
I don't fear "fear."
Is that so?
You might just change your mind.
Dispose of them, Fear.
[CLARION grunts]
[FEAR grunts]
I fear you don't
amount to "fear."
No way.
Optical and pressure sensors
functioning normally, sir!
[SUBORDINATE 12A] No problem
with audio sensors, either!
[SUBORDINATE 12B] They're all
the real deal, Colonel!
It didn't have an ability
like this before.
What changed?
[NENE]
If Cla-ring is by my side,
I'm not scared of anything!
[KURTZ]
Unbelievable.
It's managing to fool every eye
in this base, all by itself.
Fear. Code 2-1-0.
[FEAR growls]
If he can't tell
which one is real,
then he'll simply
wipe them all out.
Now he won't stop until
the battle is over.
Two percent remaining until we
break through BUER's barriers!
Yes, at last.
[TAKUMI]
So close, yeah!
So close!
The barriers Uzal
built are so strong
even a master hacker
at a wizard rank
wouldn't stand a chance of
getting past them, yeah!
However!
I'll break through her walls,
just you wait and see!
[laughs]
This'll finish it, yeah!
[SUBORDINATE 12A]
Final barrier, penetrated!
[SUBORDINATE 9A] We have control
over BUER's mainframe, sir!
[BOTH]
Reveal yourself, BUER! Now!
[NENE gasps]
Oh no!
[CLARION growls]
[KURTZ]
I've waited so long.
Finally, this moment has come.
[KURTZ]
Who goes there?
[SHADOW VOICE] We are a
multi-national corporate complex
with a singular agenda.
An organization formed
to save all of mankind
from its impending destruction.
Our name is...
[SHADOW VOICE]
...Poseidon!
[KURTZ] And even they are
nothing more than fodder
for my dreams and ideals.
In the end, it'll all be mine!
Nice try.
Sahar Schehera,
the great genius,
I will inherit your life's
legacy and make you a true hero
to all of mankind.
[KURTZ] Once I obtain
this Super Weapon,
the World Peace we
desire will at last--
[BUER] I command you to stop
right there, Little Man!
I am BUER.
The philosopher of Hades,
endowed with five
limbs of the goat,
the head of the lion and eternal
knowledge of time and space.
But to you, I am BUER's
Central Nervous Unit!
Yes, I know. I'm about
to release you, BUER.
[BUER] Thou hadst best not.
Thou wilt regret it!
[TAKUMI] Well, what
are you waiting for?
Go on and unlock access.
Because when you do...
...BUER will finally
be mine, yeah!
Cla-ring! Your weapons!
[FEAR grunts]
[NENE]
Cla-ring!
[CLARION]
Right there.
[FEAR bellows]
[CLARION]
Nene. Don't be reckless.
Oh, thank goodness!
[gasps]
[NENE] Cla-ring!
[NENE]
I'm going to protect my friend!
I won't let you mess with her!
[NENE grunts]
Nene, I have a trump card.
Ten seconds. Buy me that time.
You got it!
[FEAR roars]
Even if it doesn't do much!
[CLARION]
Six, seven, eight...
[FEAR roars]
[NENE grunts, yelps]
Gertsecommas, no!
[CLARION]
Ten. Plasma Cat Punch!
[FEAR yells]
Oh, wow!
[NENE]
Cla-ring!
[NENE sighs]
[BUER] Halt! Thou
really wilt regret it!
Nay, verily!
No, thou mustn't! Nay, I say!
[BUER]
Nay! Nay...!
[KURTZ laughs]
Yes, BUER! Do it, now!
Purify the old world
of all iniquity!
The worthless ones.
The original sinners.
Use your fiendish power
to eradicate them all!
[PEOPLE gasping]
Say what?
[KURTZ whimpers]
Hey! Is that me?
And there's Cla-ring, too.
What's all this crap, yeah?!
Gotta hurry and
get rid of it, yeah!
[SYSTEM VOICE] KOM System
operational limit reached.
Executing forced termination.
Thank you for using the system.
Hey! Wait just a minute, yeah!
[KURTZ whimpers]
[BUER]
'Tis a horrible tragedy!
My super-secret stash
of hottie thigh images!
They have been unceremoniously
leaked all across the world!
Thigh images?
It's wrong. All wrong.
[BUER]
You son of a whore!
PC data, hello?!
Even one's parents must
keep their hands off
that type of thing!
[BUER]
I adore hottie thighs so much!
I relish in flat chests, too!
And I can't forget
the regular breasts!
Then, of course, there
are the buxom boobies.
Oh, how I love to
watch them jiggle!
[KURTZ] I don't understand
what's happening.
I thought I would
gain control of BUER
if I broke through
the system's barriers.
[BUER sobs]
What sayest thou?
All ye broke into was my
super-duper top-secret
collection of booty.
You idiot!
Not a single bit hath
reached the core!
[KURTZ growls]
[BUER] Ganging up
on me and hacking into
my meager bit of unadulterated,
if not creepy, happiness.
'Tis harsh. Far too harsh!
Shut up, you fool!
My plan was perfect.
Flawless.
I pretended to obey
the feeble-minded monkeys
of Poseidon for a
result like this?!
And I suffered all these fools?!
My time...
My dreams and ideals...
All wasted?
I refuse to accept this outcome!
[BUER]
'Tis over now! Gone.
Every last bit of it!
'Tis all over!
BUER seems mad.
[KURTZ growls]
[BUER]
I shall destroy everything!
Including myself!
[NENE gasps]
[BUNNY] If I had known how
difficult this was gonna be,
I would have gotten that girl to
unlock this dang thing, too!
[screams]
What the heck?
[gasps]
--[GIRLS whimpering]
--[BUNNY] I'm here!
[CHINA DRESS]
You came to rescue us!
[GYM UNIFORM]
We knew you would!
[TAKUMI sobs] In the end,
the American Empire and I
were doing Uzal's bidding
the whole freakin' time, yeah.
[UZAL]
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
Well, hello there!
[TAKUMI]
Uzal!
What the heck have
you been doing, yeah?!
[UZAL]
That can wait, my friend.
We need to focus on
Nene and Clarion.
Wait, what do you mean?
[NENE grunts]
Thank you.
[gasps]
Nene, please leave
while you can.
It's dangerous here.
You should come
with me, Cla-ring!
I cannot.
BUER has gone
completely berserk.
If I don't stop it, nobody will.
[NENE gasps] Then we'll do it
together, like last time!
[UZAL] I'm afraid this situation
is a little different.
Huh? It's Uzal!
[UZAL]
Hi, Nene. Been a while.
I just knew you were
alive somehow!
[UZAL] I'm sorry to push so much
trouble off on you, Nene.
[NENE gasps]
And please forgive me for doing
this from a bit of a distance.
Hey, Nene!
Oh, it's you!
Yeah, its me!
I thought you were in
your room this whole time
and here you are,
running around
doing who knows what
in this underground lair!
[NENE] I'm really sorry!
I didn't mean to deceive you
I just had to make sure
Cla-ring was okay!
[sighs]
Well, for now, let's just
focus on BUER, yeah?
What do you mean, the situation
is a little different this time?
When Nene and the others
stopped BUER before,
its rampage was a
defensive mechanism.
But right now,
it appears the rampage
has been integrated with
its Central Nervous Unit.
Wait, I'm confused.
How is that different?
Because this time
you could say BUER
is angry from the very
bottom of its heart.
It can no longer be
stopped from the outside.
[BUER] I shall reduce every last
trace of this island to ashes!
[TAKUMI] Well, when will
its battery run out, yeah?
[UZAL] There's a massive
amount of electrical power
stored up in there.
Cenancle Island will
probably be vaporized
--long before it stops running.
--[TAKUMI] What?!
[UZAL] It's partly
your fault, you know?
[TAKUMI]
Ugh...
Is there anything we
can do to stop it, Uzal?
[UZAL]
Technically, yes.
There is one way: the last
of the final measures.
It's Clarion.
Cla-ring?
[UZAL] Clarion is also a key
to make BUER self-destruct
from the inside.
[SUBORDINATE 9C]
Any luck?!
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
No, none!
I'm putting it
into play, men.
[SUBORDINATES]
Huh?!
Sir? You're sure?
She's the key? Cla-ring?
You trickster.
So the real storage key was the
little puppet all along, yeah?
But, Uzal...
I don't understand.
What will happen to
Cla-ring when it's over?
And what about BUER?
Don't forget, this is
Uzal we're talking about.
It'll probably destroy
the both of them
without leaving a
trace behind, yeah.
Do I have that right?
[UZAL]
You are correct.
[gasps]
No, you can't!
Not a chance!
I won't let you do this,
you hear me?
She's my friend!
Nene, this is the only way!
You be quiet, Takumi!
Right!
I'm the one who owns
Cla-ring now, not you!
I'll never let something
like that happen!
[UZAL chuckles]
Nene. At this rate,
the entire island is doomed.
That includes you and
all your friends, too.
I'm sorry,
but Clarion must stay.
[NENE]
But... you can't!
[TAKUMI]
Nene, please!
This may sound coldhearted,
but it's best to let things
play out this way.
I know you're upset,
but the puppet came here
prepared for this, yeah?
[NENE] Cla-ring, how can
you be okay with this?
If it's the only way
to keep you safe,
then it's worth it.
Please let me go, Nene.
I know that you want
to keep me safe,
but I won't be happy unless
you're right here by my side!
Look me in the eyes and
tell me you're okay with this.
You could die.
Do you realize that?
We'd never see
each other again...
Nene's safety
is the top priority.
[NENE]
I don't want this... at all!
I haven't taken you shopping
like I promised you I would.
Cla-ring!
[CLARION]
Nene, are you crying?
Of course I am!
--[TAKUMI sighs]
--[NENE sobs]
Actually, there is
another alternative.
[TAKUMI]
Huh?!
[UZAL] However,
it might turn out to be
an even more dangerous gamble.
Do you wanna give it a shot?
Whaddaya say, Nene?
[NENE whimpers]
[SUBORDINATE 12C]
Colonel, this is inadvisable!
The legs aren't ready.
They're only 80% complete!
I thought I told you,
the legs are just for show.
Why don't you understand that?
[NENE]
I'll do it.
[TAKUMI]
Nene, no!
It's fine.
As far as I can tell, this is
the best way for everyone
to have a happy ending!
[TAKUMI]
But this plan is total crap!
[UZAL] Yep, I figured
you'd be willing to help!
All right, Clarion.
Use the Pandora Device
so Nene can--
[CLARION]
I refuse.
[CLARION] Uzal. I demand that
the plan be retracted at once.
[UZAL]
Oh... Interesting.
She's never disobeyed
my orders before.
Don't worry, Cla-ring,
it'll be fine.
Plus, don't you remember?
This is us.
When you and I are together,
there's not a thing in
the world we can't do.
Nene.
Come on. Help me do this.
And I swear I'll
come back to you.
Pandora Device. Open!
[NENE]
Release skill. Storage Key!
[BUNNY]
You guys, hurry up!
[GIRLS]
Huh...?
[screaming]
All right, then. Wish me luck!
Here I go!
[TAKUMI]
Wait, Puppet!
I gotta get inside.
I don't know what the two
of you are up to right now,
but it's not going to work!
[NENE gasps]
[NENE screams]
[screams]
[gasps]
Cla-ring!
[KURTZ]
You leave me no choice!
I'll destroy you and BUER!
No ammo?
[CLARION]
Hurry, before it closes.
What?!
[KURTZ]
The leg!
Get ready, Nene,
it's almost time.
[NENE]
Right!
[KURTZ]
No, you don't!
[NENE] Hello.
Thank you very much, sir.
[KURTZ gasps]
I'm really close.
[gasps]
Nene!
[NENE]
That must be it.
[BUER sobs]
[NENE]
Hello again.
Listen to me, BUER, please.
You don't have to be angry.
[BUER]
Yes, I do! Of course I do!
They saw all those
naughty images!
Now I am ruined!
So what if they did?
There is no shame in
something like that.
[BUER]
'Tis a lie! A dirty lie!
It's all right.
BUER, to tell you the truth,
those images were great!
They were artistic, in a way.
[BUER gibbers]
Oh no! It's not gonna work!
Nene's in trouble!
[KURTZ] That's why I said
the legs were for show!
What?!
Nene!
[CLARION]
Nene...
[TAKUMI gasps]
[CLARION]
Nene... Nene...
What's wrong, Nene?
Answer me.
[ALTMAN]
Freeze!
This base is under our control!
If you think that
I'm afraid of the CDF,
you're dead wrong.
Colonel Ian Kurtz!
You're under arrest for
committing acts of terrorism
against this island.
Have you lost it, Captain?
I'm afraid that you have.
If your island's military
stirs up trouble--
We are no longer a
military force, Colonel.
As of yesterday, we're a newly
established judicial branch:
The Cenancle Police Department!
[KURTZ]
Hmph.
[ALTMAN] You've been stripped
of your military rank.
You're just a criminal now.
Well done, Altman.
You've got it all
figured out, haven't you?
How in the name of
everything holy did that young
whipper-snapper find out
that I was taking bribes?!
[KURTZ]
Well, you'll have to kill me!
[ALTMAN yells]
[KURTZ groans]
You're done here!
I'm locking you up and
throwing away the key!
[VLIND] A mysterious facility!
Mysterious robots!
And now what do we see,
but a big, mysterious sphere!
All the mysteries
will be revealed!
But don't worry,
my loyal viewers!
You can trust me to get
to the bottom of things.
Bringing it to you live, it's
your favorite TV idol, Vli--
[CLARION]
Nene, can you hear me?
Aren't we going to go
shopping together?
Nene.
Please just come back
and call me Cla-ring again.
[sighs]
[BUER] O, my sweet maiden
with the jet-black ears!
The request of this pure lass
hath soothed my rage
and quelled my fury.
As thanks for rescuing me from
the depths of utter despair,
I shall grant thee one request.
State now what you want.
My request is simple.
I want one thing:
Nene Nanakorobi!
Nene!
Huh...? Cla-ring?
Good morning!
[TAKUMI]
What will become of BUER, yeah?
[UZAL] I'll sink it
to the bottom of the sea,
so nobody can ever get to it.
Besides, upon
further reflection,
I think BUER could use
a little more time to figure
out its own sense of self.
But I suppose the first
phase of the experiment
was successful enough.
[TAKUMI] Experiment?
What experiment, yeah?
[chuckles]
Sorry, but that's
still a secret.
You make me so mad, yeah!
Hey, listen.
[TAKUMI gasps]
Thank you.
For protecting Elpis--
Nene and Clarion, that is.
Huh? Elpis... means "hope."
[gasps]
Those two were the true key
to BUER this whole time, yeah!
[BUNNY]
Hey!
I see you found all
your friends, Bunny!
Thanks to you!
I couldn't have
done it alone, Nene!
You rock!
[ALL gasp]
Another tremor?
[TAKUMI]
This is serious, yeah!
Here's Uzal's message, yeah!
You'd better hurry it up
and get out of there, girls!
[BUNNY]
You're alive?!
You should really listen to her!
Uzal's gonna completely seal
off this geofront, yeah!
Aaahh!
[screaming]
[NENE] Come on, you guys,
we've gotta hurry!
[BUNNY]
This is like déjà vu!
Let's go, people! Get out of
here as quickly as possible!
[KURTZ grunting]
Hey, stop! Don't move!
[KURTZ]
I won't surrender!
I haven't realized
my ideal world!
There's no way this is
the end of the line!
[KURTZ pants]
[KURTZ]
I see.
So you're Sahar Schehera?
[KURTZ screams]
We made it, you guys!
[BUER grunts]
So it seemeth.
BUER, it's you!
I retrieved him.
Ha-ha!
[BUER groans]
[NENE]
That's it.
That's how our incredibly
long and grueling day
came to a conclusion.
I guess that's the end!
[BUER chuckles lecherously]
[muffled yelling]
[NENE]
We'll see you later, friends!
Nene, things are still
kind of a mess in town, yeah!
Please be careful, okay?
Right!
So? You ready?
I know Nene pulled
off an amazing feat
and saved the island,
but she's still a
little unsteady, yeah?
[groans]
Jeez. How did we end up on
freaking housekeeping duty?
[TAKUMI]
Listen up, morons!
[GIRLS gasp]
[TAKUMI] You're mine now,
so you better work hard
or I'll kick you
to the curb, yeah?!
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
[AMY]
Shopping with Cla-ring?
And with tiny guy, too?
[BUER]
I am a demon king!
[ALTMAN]
Nene!
[NENE] Hello, Robert!
Are you helping people again?
Heh, heh.
It is my nature!
[VLIND] So many unbelievable,
mind-boggling events
happened here on
Cenancle Island!
And because of my unwavering
tenacity as a reporter,
we managed to get the
whole thing on camera!
Once again, reporting live,
it's the Universe's most
trusted future journalist.
The one, the only, Vli--
Can I tell you something?
I sure hope we find
something you want soon.
I already found it.
[NENE]
Huh?!
Well? Are you gonna tell me?
[CLARION]
It's, uh...
Yes, go on!
[BUER]
Hotness! [grunts]
It's a secret.
Come on! That isn't fair!
I will tell you, Nene,
but only if you
achieve world peace.
All right, then! It's a deal!
[NENE]
Let's go, Cla-ring.
From this moment forward, we'll
fight together for world peace.
One... two...
[NENE, CLARION]
Yeah!