[BUER screams]
[TAKUMI]
Just accept it, yeah!
I can't let something
inside my home
when I don't know what Uzal's
built into it, now can I?
Let's open you up and have
a look at your guts, yeah!
[BUER screams]
[TAKUMI]
What the heck?!
[CLARION]
All right, no more of that.
[TAKUMI]
What are you doing here, yeah?
Nobody can get in here, yeah!
Oh. Hacker mode.
I suppose that
explains it then, yeah!
But, why?
It's not as if I was
trying to do anything
to the puppet, yeah!
Sorry, but Cla-ring
says she doesn't want you
breaking BUER!
[BUER]
Wah!
I do thank you for
your kindness and concern,
humble-bosomed girls!
It is clear your feelings
for me runneth deep
and I am ready to
receive them in kind!
Uzal ordered me to keep
you out of Takumi's hands.
I must do whatever it takes.
Even kill you.
[BUER yells]
[TAKUMI]
Darn that Uzal.
That woman makes my blood boil!
Cla-ring?
Do you want to hold
hands for a little bit?
[MALE VOICE 4A] Application for
enrollment screening interview
confirmed. Next
applicant, please proceed.
I'm Nene Nanakorobi.
Thank you for interviewing me!
[FEMALE VOICE 4A] Please relax,
and just try to be yourself,
all right?
[NENE]
Okay!
[MALE VOICE 4A] Why exactly
do you want to study
at this school?
[NENE] I've dealt
with a lot in my life.
When I was young,
I got really sick.
And then I lost my
parents in an accident.
But even so, many people--
[FEMALE VOICE 4A] All right,
now for the last question.
What is your goal for the
future, Miss Nanakorobi?
To achieve world peace!
[FEMALE VOICE 4A]
Pardon?
That's my dream.
My life will be a success
if I make that happen.
[FEMALE VOICE 4A]
Understood.
[MALE VOICE 4A]
That concludes the interview.
Thank you so much for your time.
[MALE VOICE 4A]
Miss Nene Nanakarobi.
Congratulations
on your enrollment!
May this school
prove to be an asset
for all of your
future endeavors.
[computer beeps]
What is it?
Homework.
[TAKUMI]
Come on!
I wanna examine BUER right now!
I wanna open up that little
demonic five-legged freak show
and find out exactly
what Uzal was up to!
It's not fair, yeah!
Nene's the problem.
She's the one
standing in my way.
She waltzes right through
my beefed-up security wall
like it's nothing.
A formidable girl, yeah.
And it's impossible to separate
Nene from that stupid puppet!
I have to figure out a
way to distract them both
at the same time, yeah.
I need to think of something
that would engross her
more than the puppet.
But what?
Oh! Yeah!
[DRAGON roars]
[TAKUMI]
What do you think, yeah?
I tried remaking a retro game
using a modern
direct link engine!
[NENE]
Wow!
This is Monster Bash, isn't it?
You're darn right it is!
You should play it all day!
[NENE]
Come on. Let's go!
[TAKUMI laughs]
Now I can examine BUER!
Except this time,
they can't stop me!
[TAKUMI]
Well... That didn't take long.
[NENE] I guess I'm just
good at figuring out games.
[TAKUMI]
Look! I'm trying to help!
You can't just leave
this thing lying around!
Someone might steal it.
You should let me keep a
close eye on it for you, yeah!
[CLARION]
No chance.
[BUER] Darkness falls
over me once again!
I can't see!
Mommy, I'm frightened!
Please, help me;
there's a scary man
with an axe under my bed!
Now we don't have to worry!
What's the deal, yeah?
It's real hard to work
when you're both
staring at me like that!
You don't have to stand watch.
I won't try anything
with BUER, yeah!
No. That's not it.
I'm actually doing
a homework assignment.
[TAKUMI] The student
will observe professionals
while they work.
Then compose a report
with an emphasis
on what they felt while watching
the job being performed.
Well, my work isn't
really geared toward
that kind of thing at all, yeah!
How about I give you
a letter of introduction
to several businesses
I'm involved with instead?
Feel free to observe
any of them you like, yeah!
Thank you so much!
This is gonna be fun!
Don't you agree?
[TAKUMI] Are you keeping up
with the maintenance
on your prosthetic body?
There is no need to worry.
I will take
excellent care of her.
[TAKUMI]
All right then, yeah.
Have fun, and I'll
see you later, yeah!
[NENE]
See you later!
[TAKUMI] She really doesn't
know how to be suspicious
of people yet, yeah.
Easy. All too easy.
Doing schoolwork is weird.
You don't want to do it?
Oh, no. This is fun.
It's just...
Considering my goal
of world peace,
I wonder if it's
a wise use of time.
How do you mean?
I know learning
is a good thing.
But before I came here,
I was helping do research
that would benefit
the whole world.
Studying seems like
a selfish thing to do
when I could be working
towards the betterment
of all mankind.
There is a much
faster way to do things.
Is there something
you need to learn?
Of course there is.
There's so much.
[sighs]
But the best way
to learn is to watch.
And I suppose that's what
today is all about, isn't it?
Observing.
If there is something
that you need to learn,
then simply use
the Pandora Device.
[NENE]
Like I said,
I've helped out with
research in the past.
But I don't have any experience
with full or part time work.
What about you, Cla-ring?
Have you ever held a job before?
Yes. Right now.
Always being by Nene's
side is Clarion's job.
[NENE]
Uh...
For it to be a job, you
have to get paid, don't you?
[PROSERPINA]
Good morning, everyone!
I'm Proserpina.
I look forward to
working with you today!
Same here, Miss!
[VLIND] Since the
terrorism in Area Vulcan,
public order has
taken a major nosedive.
Network disturbances have
rendered the infrastructure
unstable here
on Cenancle Island.
But like the phoenix rising
from the ashes of despair,
I'm back!
Reporting live
from Cenancle Island,
I'm here to bring you
the unfettered truth,
no matter the cost!
[giggles]
When I get knocked down,
I pick myself back up.
It may be a tough job,
but somebody's gotta do it.
And so, I'll perform
my journalistic duty
even if it kills me.
[MALE STAFFER 4A]
It's time!
You got it!
I'm a super star!
I'm the best in the biz!
Guess who's back, world?
That's right, it's me, Vli--
[NENE]
Wow.
This is the first
place on Takumi's list.
A hardware manufacturer.
Hi.
We're here because
we would like to do
some workplace observation.
We can arrange that.
Before we get you processed,
welcome to Megatech.
They must be some
big shot's kids.
Those prosthetics aren't
cheap, that's for sure.
Someone paid a pretty penny.
It definitely shows.
Those two are just
as cute as they can be.
I'm sorry, I didn't call
to make an appointment.
But I do have a letter.
[gasps]
Welcome to our company,
Miss Nanakorobi.
We are honored to have you!
[MALE EMPLOYEE 4A] Which floor
would you like to see first,
Miss Nanakorobi?
Your wish is our command.
Oh, uh... I don't know.
[MALE EMPLOYEE 4B]
Might I make a suggestion then?
We have a top-secret
exoskeleton development lab
you might find interesting!
All right. Sounds fun!
No, no, don't be ridiculous!
Clearly, the young lady
would be far more interested
in seeing our
brand new line of--
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 4A]
Anything you wish to see, Miss,
anything at all,
just say the word!
Uh... Right.
[EMPLOYEES]
Thank you for coming to observe!
Please be sure to
give our sincere regards
to Ms. Korobase!
[NENE] Let's see if we can
be a little more discreet
at the next place.
What do you say, Cla-ring?
[EMPLOYEES] Welcome to our
company, Miss Nanakorobi.
We're honored to have you!
Please feel free to
make yourself at home
while you're with us!
I hope you'll have
a chance to see the lab
for our newest product: a
lightweight, recoilless handgun!
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 4C]
We have been hoping to get
Ms. Korobase to finance research
on vibratory components
that interact with gravity
for several years now.
[EMPLOYEES] Welcome to our
company, Miss Nanakorobi.
We're honored to have you!
Come see the
development of our new
actuator that links up
with the latest
cyborg operating systems!
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 4D]
Please put in a good word!
We would love for Ms. Korobase
to license her optronics patent
to our company!
[EMPLOYEES chattering]
[EMPLOYEES]
Hurrah! To Ms. Takumi Korobase!
[MALE EMPLOYEE 4F]
Our company is highly confident
that it can develop
high-resolution
auditory elements!
[MALE EMPLOYEE 4G]
This branch office deals with
humane weaponry,
primarily non-lethal ammo!
[MALE EMPLOYEE 4H] The cost
to develop new components
and floating micromachines
is quite high!
[MALE EMPLOYEE 4I]
We would very much love to make
some military connections!
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 4E]
Please ask Ms. Korobase for us!
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 4F]
To Ms. Korobase!
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE 4G]
Miss Nanakorobi!
[MALE EMPLOYEE 4J]
Thank you, Miss!
Your face is stuck, Nene.
Oh. Yeah.
[NENE sighs]
My face is finally
back to normal.
Did you get what you needed
for your homework assignment?
That wasn't exactly what
I was hoping for, Cla-ring.
I just wanted to
see regular people
doing normal, everyday work.
[BUER yelling]
Stop it, you devil!
Uzal said not to touch me!
You can scream all you like,
but no matter how loud you are,
Nene and the puppet won't
hear you, you little creep!
[BUER yells]
[PROSERPINA] The greatest!
The mightiest! Titan TV!
Wow, look at that. Neat.
Welcome, ladies and gents.
On today's episode of
"Proserpina's Corner
on Cenancle-Wide,"
we're coming to you
live from Vulcan Park!
As you can see,
the reconstruction event
is already underway!
Look at that; it's a TV host.
I've never seen one before!
I know!
[MALE DIRECTOR 4A]
Okay, we've gone to commercial!
I don't mind if
you watch me work.
Sounds like fun to me!
That's very kind of you.
[PROSERPINA]
Nene and Cla-ring, huh?
Clarion.
This job is fun,
but really hard.
And considering how hectic
it can be, the pay's not great.
[NENE]
Oh.
But the gig definitely
has its perks.
You get a lot of experience
and you have a chance
to rub elbows
with famous celebs.
And most important of all,
you get to create your own
professional opportunities.
[chuckles]
[VLIND] Gimme all your money,
you crazy kids!
Your giggles of excitement
won't put food on the table!
[BOY 4A laughs]
It's a monster!
[BOY 4B laughs]
Beat up the monster!
Well! If it isn't Janus North
of the Cenancle
Self-Governing Organization!
[VLIND]
Oh, come on!
You're gonna let some
wannabe idol from the sticks
have her own TV show?!
[NENE] Working a job
sure can be tough.
It's awesome to help others.
If the disaster
has hurt your wallet,
your whole family can visit
this tent for a hot meal,
free of charge.
So how does it taste, Miss?
It's very tasty, thank you!
Tasty?
This stuff is totally better
than my Mom's cooking,
that's all I know!
[CROWD laughing]
[NENE]
These volunteers...
They're giving up their time
to help others for no money.
[CLARION]
Yes, they are providing aid
unilaterally and freely.
Going by the standard
definition of performing labor
in exchange for money,
this is not a job.
But if you regard the entire
island as a single community,
then I suppose it's
plausible this volunteer work
might be considered
economic activity
that generates a mutual benefit.
Well, I doubt they would
use such scientific language
to describe it.
They volunteer 'cause
we're all in it together.
We're all connected
to the same community.
We're family.
We are connected? With cables?
Not with cables.
With our humanity.
[HOODLUM 4E grunts]
[PEOPLE yell]
[HOODLUM 4A]
C'mon! We told you to clear out!
[NENE]
Huh?
[MALE VOICE 4B]
Hey! Stop that!
Who told you people
you had permission
to throw your little
party here, huh?
[MALE VOICE 4B]
Don't do that!
[PEOPLE yelling]
[yelling continues]
Please!
Leave these people alone!
[HOODLUM 4B]
Beat it!
[HOODLUM 4A] You can't
be out here giving away
free meals to these people!
We've got businesses
we're trying to run, man!
That's right!
I don't even
know how you people
eat this disgusting crap!
[NENE]
Cla-ring!
[HOODLUM 4D]
What's with this kid?
[HOODLUM 4B] You got some
kinda problem with us?
Come and get some!
[NENE]
Cla-ring!
Check it out, dude.
These chicks are androids!
Get outta here, losers, before I
turn you both into scrap metal!
[HOODLUM 4B]
Ow! Hey, who did that?
Hey! Jerks!
Violence against young ladies?
That's despicable!
Take that!
Hey, man. That hurt!
Ow! This sucks!
[CROWD yelling]
Hey, what's the problem?
What in the world is
taking you guys so long?
[HOODLUM 4B]
Boss...
Things got out of hand
thanks to those stupid kids!
What should we do about 'em?
[BUNNY screams]
[HOODLUM 4B] You want us
to kick their butts?
[BUNNY]
Retreat, retreat!
Run away!
[HOODLUM 4A]
What? Are you kidding me?
We were just getting started!
[BUNNY]
I don't understand.
What is Sahar's
puppet doing here?!
If I let those thugs go
toe to toe with that monster,
they'd be dead meat,
and so would I!
[PROSERPINA] Don't you at least
have some emergency food?
Thankfully, most
of the ingredients
didn't get ruined.
But we're not
professional cooks.
Without preparation time,
there's no way we can
feed all these people.
Oh no.
[OLDER BROTHER 4A]
Come on, let's go home.
[YOUNGER SISTER 4A]
But we didn't get to eat.
What?
Come on. What do you say?
Will you help me out
again, Cla-ring?
My job is to assist you
in whatever you might need.
All right!
[NENE]
Thank you so much!
Pandora Device. Open!
[NENE]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
We are here to cook!
But there's no way
you'll be able
to prepare this much food
all by yourselves!
Don't worry about us.
Please, just let us help out!
[NENE]
Elpis Series. Decode!
Kitchen Drudge!
Wow! They're fast!
[PROSERPINA]
Whoa! So good!
[MALE VOLUNTEER 4A]
Well!
I can't believe
everything worked out!
Thanks for bringing in those
two cooks to save the day!
What? I didn't call them.
I assumed that
you guys did that!
[NENE] Thanks for
showing us around today!
It was a pleasure.
Do you know where
those two volunteers went?
[CLARION]
Yes, of course.
They told us they had
to leave on urgent business.
Too bad.
I was really hoping to have a
chance to tell them thank you.
That's all right.
People were happy today.
I'm sure their smiles
were thanks enough.
I sure hope so.
I wish I could've gotten
an interview, though.
Oh, right.
Did this help you with
your homework assignment?
Yes!
I learned some jobs
pay people with money
and others pay them with smiles.
Thank you so much for
making me smile today!
[NENE]
I learned something else, too.
In a community,
everyone is connected!
[SUBORDINATE 4A]
Colonel Kurtz.
[KURTZ]
Yes?
[SUBORDINATE 4A] The eviction
scheme at the seaside park
seems to have failed, sir.
It makes no difference.
We achieved our primary goal.
And then some.
The Self-Governance Organization
received the message
loud and clear.
But we cannot deviate
from the schedule
and waste any more time.
With every single
tick of the clock,
the fate of the whole island
hangs in the balance.
[BUER screams]
[TAKUMI giggling]
Now you're all mine, yeah!
[BUER screams]
[TAKUMI whimpering]
It appears you've foiled
my plans again, yeah!
Well, don't let that go to your
head, you stupid little puppet!
If I had my way,
I'd break you into
a million spare parts
and sell you on the
black market, yeah!
[TAKUMI]
Crap!
[NENE] Please don't try to do
anything to Cla-ring, okay?
Uh... Right.
You got it, yeah!
Do you like that
game, Nene? A lot?
Yeah, Monster Bash rocks!
There are quests and tons of
really cool equipment, as well!
It's hard, though, because if
you don't have the right item,
then you have to start
the quest all over again!
And eventually...
[CLARION] Next time,
remind me not to ask you.
[TAKUMI]
Yeah, yeah!
I want to investigate
BUER's secret, yeah!
[BUER]
Oh, maiden, whose inner thighs
give shape to a
beautiful triangle.
Fine, I shall tell thee the
secret of my fifth leg!
[CLARION] I was told to
destroy you if you talk.
[BUER screams]