[SUBORDINATE 9B]
All units. Insert stylets.
[SUBORDINATE 8A]
Commencing the 27th attempt
to physically connect to BUER.
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
Deploying attack barriers!
Anticipating maximum load!
[SUBORDINATE 9C]
Colonel Kurtz?
Connect now.
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
Connecting!
Unit 5, signal lost!
Unit 3 and unit
6, both lost!
We've got a major
network disturbance!
Sir, it's the exact
same thing as last time.
I won't let that slow us down.
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
Unit 4, maintaining connection!
[SUBORDINATE 9C]
Injecting micro-machines, sir!
[SUBORDINATE 9B] We've broken
through a barrier maze that
appears to be the outer shell
of BUER's main system!
[SUBORDINATE 9C] Assigning
highest priority to maintaining
the circuit.
Commencing penetration
of the next barrier!
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
We're winning, marginally.
We can keep going!
[KURTZ] We assumed this would
be the outcome, gentlemen.
Just make sure
we stay on schedule.
[SUBORDINATE 8A]
Yes, sir.
[KURTZ] Fortunately, Sahar
Schehera left behind BUER.
What is its eye looking at?
[SUBORDINATE 8A] We're
detecting a high heat source!
[alarms blaring]
[SUBORDINATE 9B] Shift
observed in the magnetic field!
[SUBORDINATE 9C] Heat source,
temperature rising!
[KURTZ]
This can't be!
Hold on...
You mean it's looking at us?
Get the classified storage
out of here right now!
Drop whatever you're doing!
There's a major risk the data
might undergo a whiteout!
We won't get another
chance like this, sir!
Do it.
[ALL gasp]
[SUBORDINATE 9C]
Look out!
[KURTZ] I didn't expect
undoing one layer of protection
to cause it to
heighten its security.
[WORKER 9A]
What the hell?
No matter what happens,
the CDF cannot
find out about this.
Sir.
At the very least,
I was able to observe BUER
in full effect.
This much power at such
a low percentage...
There's no doubt.
Sahar Schehera was a
supreme genius, indeed.
You know what they say...
The best kind of genius is one
that's already dead and gone.
And it's true.
We'll profit from
what's left behind.
We are the second
hand that ticks away
the order of the world.
All this we do for the
promise of world peace.
All right,
hold your breath, please.
Yes, sir. Will do.
Here, I'll take that.
[TOTO]
Hmm...
Perfect. There's no
clumping or anything.
Everything is okay.
You can talk now.
Hey, Cla-ring!
I'm glad we're
back together again!
I was told you're
just getting a basic
partial hair implant, Clarion.
And that I should let you
tune your mechanicals yourself.
Thank you.
I'm all done with settings.
Incredible. Wow.
The detail of your configuration
is simply amazing!
Do not look, no matter what.
Of course.
Seriously, though.
Yes. I hear you.
Well, Nene,
after we finish adjusting
your epidermal coating,
you'll be free to go.
[NENE]
'Kay!
I can't get over how
sparkly you look, Cla-ring.
That'll do it for today.
You can put your
clothes back on.
And don't forget
your petroid doll.
[BUER] I am no pet,
ministering angel!
I am the great
demon king BUE--Agh!
We are much obliged.
This turned out to
be quite the overhaul.
So please let us know if
anything feels off kilter.
Sorry.
I guess you weren't
expecting Clarion today.
Oh no, trust me, everything
was thoroughly explained.
Do what you think is best,
and don't ask
any questions, yeah!
[TOTO] Just promise me you
won't be so reckless next time,
all right?
Yes sir!
How frightening.
I can't believe
you found yourselves
right in the middle
of that horrific fire.
I hear the authorities
still don't have a clue
what started it.
Some people say arson.
Seems like bad things
are happening all the time.
Be careful, Nene.
Right!
You're free to go
for now, but don't forget,
you promised me you
would take it easy out there.
I appreciate all
of your help, sir.
I know we were told
it's not our concern.
But aren't you the least
bit curious who Clarion is?
Well... Who can say?
Plus, maybe all that matters
is that she's so adorable.
Yes, perhaps you're right.
[NENE]
It's so pretty out here.
I know!
Hey, Cla-ring, you wanna
go shopping tomorrow?
We can spend the
whole day looking
until we find
something you want!
You know, like uh...
New equipment. Or some backup!
But... I no longer need those.
Sorry. I didn't know that.
Well...
How about we buy
you some clothes?
You know what?
I just want you
to discover something
that really matters to you.
[CLARION] You mean something
like your world peace, Nene?
[NENE]
Yeah.
You always help me
whenever I need it,
so why can't I return the favor?
Let me help you now.
Let's figure out what
you want and go get it!
All right, then.
I'll give it some thought.
[NENE]
You promise?
[CLARION]
Yes, I promise.
I'm done at last!
I can't tell you how
relieved I am to be done
with my repairs and
all of my schoolwork!
Your ears look great, Cla-ring.
I'm so glad the
doctor fixed them.
Do you like 'em?
Oh, yes.
They're more than
satisfactory. Perfect.
When they first got singed,
I was so worried for you.
But as usual,
you were gallant.
Like a heroic cat prince
from an old timey fairy tale!
[CLARION]
A cat prince?
Nene?
[NENE]
Cla-ring...
In my whole life...
I've never had this much fun.
Or been so incredibly
happy before.
Hey, Cla-ring...
Let's stay like this.
For now, and forever and ever.
[BUER]
And now...
For the angel's baiser!
Mouth to mouth!
[BUER grunts]
[BUER cheers]
[TAKUMI groans]
The terrorism
and network outages
are destabilizing
currency, yeah.
What's more, the
American Imperial Army's
advisory group is putting
pressure on every issue!
I bet I know what
they're after, yeah.
[TAKUMI] I figured you were
going to show up eventually...
Uzal's puppet.
So this is about BUER, yeah?
[VLIND]
Ugh!
Somehow I managed to
survive all that uproar
with the fire.
But things got weird!
This isn't the idol
I wanted to be!
I thought I'd get
away from everything
and hide out for a while
in the refugee camp.
But as it turns out,
it's no longer there!
Is it possible my
information's out of date?
No, it couldn't be...
[rumbling]
What the heck?
Run for your lives!
[screaming]
[VLIND]
Huh? This is a major scoop!
What did I venture to this
island for if not to become
the most famous TV
personality in the world?
Now, I need to gather my team!
[VOICEMAIL] Hello. You have
reached your voicemail service.
Fine. I'll do this alone!
Without them!
That's right! I'm back again!
The world's most trusted
news reporter! Vli--
Where'd she go to?
It's not like her
to just disappear.
[MIC PERSON]
Hey, check it out.
It looks like she
called not too long ago.
[SOLDIER 9A]
Is this a delivery?
Hey! Are you listening?
What's the big deal?
It's probably just more
work machinery, right?
[SOLDIER 9A yells]
[OPERATOR 9A]
Intruder alert! Intruder alert!
Incursion by an
unidentified hostile force!
[OPERATOR 9A] All troops,
level one battle-stations!
Details about
hostile force unknown!
Should you make contact, switch
to information-sharing mode.
You're clear to engage.
Weapons free!
[OPERATOR 9A]
Intercept! Intercept!
Orders have been issued
for the unconditional
extermination of any trespassers
within this facility!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
The enemy force is
a large mobile weapon
with multiple
automated infantry!
Types unknown!
We can't stop them using the
equipment we have on hand!
[SOLDIER 9D]
Get down!
[SOLDIER 9E]
Gas masks on, now!
[COMMANDER 9A]
What the hell is this?
Put me through to
the colonel. Huh?!
[OPERATOR 9A]
Warning!
There's a possibility
this facility's system
is being hacked!
[SOLDIER 9D] They're currently
moving from S14E to N14F!
[OPERATOR 9A]
Attention all troops!
Prepare to engage!
[SOLDIER 9E] All right, men,
let's give 'em hell!
[SOLDIER 9F]
Don't let them pass!
[SOLDIER 9E]
What's that?
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[OPERATOR 9A]
Disengage now!
All troops,
fall back to shaft 2!
We're closing the barrier!
What in the hell
was that damn thing?
[SOLDIER 9G] I saw her.
With my own eyes.
She was riding on
the enemy's weapon.
A little girl with cat ears.
Wearing a maid's outfit!
She was terrifying, sir!
[UNIT LEADER 9A]
This is no time for jokes.
It's not a joke!
You gotta believe me!
Shinokaomi.
Code Yatsukahagi engage.
[MULTIPED TANK 9A]
Authentication, clear.
Entering Mode Yatsukahagi.
Footgear and crampons locked.
Moving main deck.
Releasing barrel.
[MULTIPED TANK 9A] All energy
lines directly connected.
Chamber interior
pressurizing normally.
Commencing rifling rotation.
[MULTIPED TANK 9A]
Ready to fire.
Go get some counseling, soldier.
[SOLDIER 9G]
It's the truth, I swear!
[UNIT LEADER 9A]
Calm down!
You and I both know
there's no way a little--
[SOLDIER 9G yells]
[UNIT LEADER 9A] Cat ears.
A maid outfit, too.
I guess he was telling
the truth, after all.
Damn.
So this is about BUER, yeah?
I request your cooperation.
[TAKUMI]
Cooperation, yeah?
Tell me this, you stupid puppet,
why should I have to cooperate
with the likes of you?
[TAKUMI]
A video?
[UZAL] I'm going to
say this to begin with.
You can consider this a warning.
[TAKUMI]
Wh--? Uzal?!
My name is Uzal Delilah
and I'm a genius scientist
as beautiful and elegant
as I am brilliant.
[TAKUMI]
And cocky, yeah!
[UZAL] Once it's been confirmed
that BUER is at risk
of going on a
devastating rampage,
I ordered that this video
be shown to someone
who meets a certain requirement.
[TAKUMI]
A certain requirement?
[UZAL]
I'll explain.
If BUER, my greatest creation,
is started in a way
that deviates from
proper procedure...
It will definitely go berserk.
System hacks and physical damage
will yield the
exact same result.
If pushed too far, it will
rampage until it self-destructs.
I must make this clear:
I don't intend to hand
BUER over to anyone.
I will say once more,
this is a warning.
The fact that someone is
actually watching this video
means a crisis of epic
proportions is about to unfold
here on Cenancle Island.
As we speak,
someone is attempting
to make a move on BUER.
I cannot force
you to take action.
You're free to do whatever you
want once you hear this warning.
But...
I do sincerely hope you'll
find it within yourself
to contribute to the
cause of lasting peace
on Cenancle Island.
Bye-bye for now!
Looks like things are as
screwed up as ever, yeah.
I already knew the
American Imperial Army
was swarming like ants
all over Uzal's roost!
But I ignored them
because I never thought
they'd actually succeed
in interfering, yeah.
What in the heck is this, yeah?
[CLARION] An image from
just after the fire broke out
at Herme's.
That's evidence that
a particle cannon beam
passed through the foundation
of Herme's from underground.
[TAKUMI] Then BUER has already
started to go berserk, yeah?
Which means what happened before
is about to happen again.
What specifically do you
mean by cooperation, yeah?
I request equipment
and backup, please.
So you want to
start a fight with
the American Imperial Army?
Sounds like big
trouble to me, yeah.
[CLARION]
Combat is not the objective.
I will reach BUER
as quickly as possible,
and take measures to stabilize
it by any means necessary.
[TAKUMI]
Tell me this much...
Is following the directive
to stabilize BUER
your primary objective?
Negative.
Nene Nanakorobi's safety.
Perfect answer, yeah!
Take this with you.
It's unstable, so I gave up on
my commercialization efforts.
But you could probably
find a way to make it work!
You'll have my cooperation.
But there's one condition and I
have to have your word, puppet!
[TAKUMI]
Don't kill anyone, yeah!
I know more or less
what Uzal was after
when she made you.
So I know it's
a tall order, yeah.
But this applies to more
than just this situation.
The rules are simple:
You won't kill anyone
and you won't abandon anyone.
Not under any circumstances.
The moment you violate that...
You lose any and all rights
to be by Nene's side
and you'll be banished
from her sight
for the rest of your days!
[TAKUMI]
Hear my prayers now.
All forces of good...
I humbly, humbly request...
That you send us grace...
That we might triumph...
And stave off evil.
I ask that the holy, ethereal
light of goodness and peace
might envelop all forces
of darkness and anger.
I ask, too,
that you might make pure
all impurity with the
divine wrath of grace
and righteousness.
[TAKUMI] I promised
I would cooperate, yeah.
But I never said
I'd heed the warning.
[TAKUMI]
BUER belongs to me now.
I won't let anybody
else have it, yeah.
[VLIND] I followed a suspicious,
borderline creepy, character
to this place because
I smelled a scoop!
And now, here I am,
running though this freaky
underground labyrinth
beneath the park!
[VLIND screaming]
Back off!
I'm the world's most
beloved reporter!
The name's Vli--!
[TAKUMI] We won't have to worry
about these soldiers anymore.
I have to admit...
You handled Shinokaomi
surprisingly well.
This block is
fully under control.
That should take care of
most of the bad guys, yeah!
I did it this time!
The world's favorite reporter
hit the journalism jackpot.
[TAKUMI] We'll let the
Gercomas clean up here...
We should continue on with
the elite exterminators, yeah!
[CLARION]
Understood.
[BUNNY laughs]
I've been waiting, Clarion!
I'm gonna finish
you off for good,
you stupid little freak!
What's the matter?
You don't know who I am?
Are you kidding me?
Come on, it's me, Bunny!
Stop ignoring me!
Take a good look
at these combat robots
I made, cause they're
about to kick your butt!
I didn't oversee Sahar's
base for nothing, you know!
All I have to do now
is lower my hand.
After I do that
they will all atta--
[sneezes]
That was an accident!
No, don't! I'm begging you!
Please stop this!
Didn't you hear me?
I said stand down!
[BUNNY yelling]
Why do things always have to go
so terribly wrong for me?
I only meant to threaten
and capture her, that's all.
[BUNNY]
It didn't do a thing?
Geez, talk about armor!
[BUNNY]
What's this?
An anti-optical
weapon smoke screen!
There's no way my robots
will be able to break through
a shield like that!
[BUNNY screaming]
[TAKUMI] What the heck
was all that, yeah?
Once we make it past this block,
we'll reach where
BUER is isolated, yeah?
Uzal's BUER is--
[TAKUMI]
Hey! What's going on, yeah?
[KURTZ]
So you dodged that attack.
It seems it wasn't the
multiped tank's abilities
that overpowered an
entire imperial army unit.
You seem too refined to be
Alliance or Holy Republic.
I like you.
We can play this
game if you want to.
Cla-ring...
It's time to wake up.
Where did she go?
You're in a good mood
today, Cla-ring!
My operating efficiency
increases significantly
when my ears are cleaned.
It's easier to work
when you're in a good mood.
And humming a tune makes it fun!
I know!
We should do some karaoke!
I think I'll pass.
[TAKUMI] I'm going to
get my hands on BUER
if it's the last
thing I do, yeah!
[UZAL]
Don't even try.
[TAKUMI]
Uzal?!
[UZAL] It's way too big to fit
in your little pocket, Takumi.
[TAKUMI] Where're you
transmitting from anyway?
[CLARION]
It's a recorded video.