[VLIND]
Cenancle Island.
Population,
approximately 42,000.
The surface and underside
of a high-tech island
that's forever changing,
day and night.
The twisted crimes that
take place within its folds,
and the one young star
who stands up for the truth.
[chuckles]
[phone rings]
Hello?
[SHOW PRODUCER 7A] This is Titan
TV's production department.
I'm calling in regards
to the offer we extended
the other day to make you a
regular host on Hyperion News.
[VLIND]
Victory!
You suck!
If you don't have your
own TV show,
you're nothing but a
big ole waste of space!
You're not even
a washed up has-been;
you're a "never was" loser!
I accept!
Can't wait to get started!
Please send my
agent the details!
[SHOW PRODUCER 7A]
This is wonderful news!
We were certainly hoping
to get you for this position,
Ms. Sandra Jarny.
[VLIND]
That's not me!
Of all people, Jarny
works for a rival company!
Listen up, I'm not
Sandra Jarny, okay? I'm Vli--
I hate this crap!
She just got full maintenance
at the hospital the other day,
and now she's
damaged again, yeah.
I mean, come on!
How beaten up does
she plan on getting
while she's here on the island?
She needs to stop it
with the good deeds!
First, she falls out of a tree
fetching a child's balloon.
Then she helps carry things,
and ends up being
crushed beneath them.
And last, she rescues
a cat from a freakin' sewer!
Apparently, Uzal reinforced her
frame and bio-safety components,
so it's not super serious
or anything like that.
But I can't stand it, yeah!
And then there's
the module Uzal added.
I hate to admit it,
but I don't understand
its contents at all, yeah!
[UZAL laughing]
[TAKUMI]
Knowing that idiot,
it's probably nothing
harmful to Nene,
but even so, it offends
every part of my being!
Well guess what, Uzal? Ya jerk!
Today's the day
I figure it out, yeah!
Oh. Hey, Cla-ring, what's up?
[NENE]
I see your hair's not behaving.
Leave it to me!
Silky, smooth, and straight.
[laughing]
[TAKUMI] The new Gertsecomma
model will make me
impossible to detect because
I installed a direct connection!
I just wanted to take a moment
to say thank you, Cla-ring.
I know I've been reckless,
but it's only because
you make me feel
like I can do anything.
Like I'm invincible
or something.
[CLARION]
Clarion's job is to help Nene do
what she wants to do.
[NENE]
Thanks! You're the greatest!
One other thing...
It's about when I transform.
[TAKUMI]
Transform?
But what--
What does that mean, yeah?
What do you want to know?
Well, it's just...
When you and I connect,
I'm wondering why everything
suddenly feels all light.
[CLARION]
That's not a transformation.
It's a response Uzal programmed
for when you
and I are connected.
She said the external aspects
were a matter of taste.
[NENE]
Taste?
[NENE] But after that, why's
there always a flash of light?
[CLARION]
Oh.
Now I know what you mean
when you say "transform."
That event is set to occur
when the optical
camouflage activates.
Hold on just a second!
Optical Camo on Nene's body?
[NENE] Optical
camouflage? That's weird.
[CLARION]
When the light shines,
it's examining your
current appearance.
[NENE] What about when
my clothes disappear?
[CLARION] They don't
actually disappear, Nene.
Optical camouflage
is essentially a tool
to render something invisible.
[NENE] But why do the
old clothes have to go away
before the new ones appear?
[CLARION] Curiously,
the software is set up
so they don't happen
at the same time.
The reason is unknown.
[NENE] After that,
the really bright light
starts shining again.
And then I'm done
changing clothes!
It's just an illusion.
You don't actually change.
[NENE] Can I use optical
camouflage to choose clothes
I like better?
[CLARION]
Unknown.
[NENE] I at least get to pick
a signature pose, right?
[CLARION]
Unknown.
[TAKUMI] A disguise via
optical camouflage?
That makes sense.
There have been multiple
times where she's changed
her outward appearance.
I have a message
I'm supposed to play
when this question comes up.
Yoo-hoo! Nene!
[NENE]
Oh! Hi, Uzal!
So, disguises and
poses are the marks
of all great heroes!
Please feel free
to use them at will!
Also, let's keep
this between us,
but I definitely swiped the
design for the optical camo
you're using from Takumi
and then modified it
to make it better!
[TAKUMI] You shouldn't steal
somebody's top-secret tech
and then use it for
your own stupid purposes!
That she-devil has always
been so selfish, yeah!
[NENE, CLARION]
Stare.
[TAKUMI gasps]
[LECTURER 7A] At the end
of the last century,
the impact of a giant
meteorite resulted in
a jumble of misinformation
and lead to the subsequent
Asian Conflict.
The former Japanese capital
of Tokyo was devastated,
and even now the
effects are still felt.
[BUER]
Woo-hoo!
[groans]
Thanks for waiting, Cla-ring.
Let's go.
More than anything else,
I'm learning how much
I still don't know.
Would you like to attend
an online school, too?
Pass.
And what about you, BUER?
[BUER] My inquiring
mind wisheth to know
what secrets a maiden
might keep in her--
[chokes]
[CLARION]
He'll pass.
[giggles]
You guys! Look, look!
I know it's still
under construction,
but isn't it wonderful?
[NENE]
Yeah!
[AMY'S GRANDMOTHER]
Now we can finally say goodbye
to living in that
puny little tent!
[AMY] Look, tiny guy, I can use
this to make you a house, too!
[BUER gasps]
[BUER]
I am BUER, the demon king!
Thou shalt not confine me
to such a dark dwelling!
[NENE]
Oh! Hello, Robert!
Well, well, if it isn't
Nene. Cla-ring, too.
It's Clarion.
I didn't know you
lived here, Robert.
[ALTMAN] I don't.
I just stopped by to help out.
Oh. That's very kind of you.
[laughing]
I guess it's just the way I am.
Hello, Captain!
[ALTMAN]
Men. At ease.
As you probably know,
this forced relocation
has the citizenry concerned.
Not to mention the
network disturbances.
And the recent rash
of robot thieves, to boot.
Stay focused and alert.
Sir!
[CHICKEN]
Lookee here...
Two high-grade androids
strolling down the street.
It'll be like takin'
candy from a baby.
This is why it's always
smart to keep an eye out
in the rich neighborhoods.
Those two walkin' scraps
of junk are worth more
than a freakin' luxury car.
That is so cute!
They're holding hands!
They're like sitting ducks.
Boss, can we
grab some grub after?
[COCCO clucking]
[CHICKEN]
Welcome back, CoCCo!
Nice recon work out there!
Are you guys ready or what?
According to our info,
there's about to be
another widespread
network disturbance!
The CDF doesn't have time
to bother with petty thieves,
but don't get sloppy
and leave behind any clues
that'll trace back to us!
Well? Let's do this!
[UNDERLINGS]
Yeah!
Oh, crap!
[UNDERLING 7B] The one with
the ears must be a guard!
[UNDERLING 7C]
Be careful!
[NENE]
Cla-ring! Watch out!
[BUER]
Petty criminals!
Meet them in battle!
[CLARION]
Unable to report.
Oh no.
[UNDERLING 7A]
It's not working! What do we do?
I think we're gonna
need some back up here!
Get her, Mr. Fried!
Take refuge, Nene.
Cla-ring!
[BUER]
Me too!
[grunting]
[shooting noise]
[CHICKEN] What the heck's
takin' you guys so long?
Let's hurry up
and get outta here!
[UNDERLING 7A]
Mr. Chicken?
[CHICKEN]
Huh?
[CHICKEN] It's not worth much
if you break it, little brother.
Right.
[CHICKEN]
Nice! It's airborne!
Aim your capture
nets, boys! Fire!
It's heavier than it looks.
At least it's ours now.
Whoa! I never seen one
armed like that before.
This one might be
more than we can handle.
[UNDERLING 7E]
We better hurry, Boss!
If the network disturbance ends,
the CDF will have
us dead to rights!
Damn.
I guess we better
get moving then.
Forget about the heavy one and
ditch the egg-shaped one, too.
But let's take the humanoid.
[UNDERLINGS]
Yes, sir!
[UNDERLING 7D] Can't you
move any faster than that?
[BUER]
Hark. Ye lot are lucky!
I shall let you go, for now!
Another disturbance!
This is terrible, yeah!
The worst!
What happened to Nene?
Her signal's gone!
Oh, good grief!
What do I do, yeah?
[TAKUMI]
Agh! Hey, wait, yeah!
What's the matter
with you, puppet?
I'd better look at
the log real quick!
[TAKUMI]
Nene was abducted by thieves?!
Who do they think they're
dealing with, yeah?
I won't stand
for this injustice!
Those scum of the earth losers
must be shielding Nene's signal.
But...
I bet they're using
an escape vehicle, yeah.
Island traffic
info search. Engage!
Analysis of surveillance
camera footage.
Narrow down candidates.
[TAKUMI]
I found it, yeah!
These thieving jerks
have been looting the island
ever since the
disturbances started.
It's no surprise they'd zero in
on Nene and Uzal's
little puppet,
given how much they're
worth on the black market.
My information quarantine
was absolutely flawless,
but I was foolish and
careless not to even consider
the possibility of
random petty thieves, yeah!
If Uzal ever finds out
I put Nene in danger
'cause of a stupid
mistake like this,
she'll make fun of me
for the rest of my life!
Wow, you sure are dumb!
[laughing]
[TAKUMI screams]
[siren blaring]
[TAKUMI] I'll take them
down before it's reported
to the CDF, yeah!
Attention, Gertsecommas!
Deploy with extermination
equipment now!
Hey! Time to stand down, puppet!
Rendezvous with my
forces immediately!
[TAKUMI]
Hey!
Get on, yeah!
[TAKUMI]
Let's fly like the wind, puppet!
[WOMAN 7A]
Aww, how cute.
[TAKUMI]
You're heavy, yeah.
[DAVID]
Check that out! So cool!
Cla-ring? Was that you?
[TAKUMI] Looks like
this must be the place.
Let's do recon until
my reinforcements arrive.
[TAKUMI] First, we'll figure
out where Nene is, yeah.
Then our plan will depend
on what we find once we get--
[TAKUMI]
I got cut off again, yeah!
[CHICKEN] Well, I never
thought you'd actually be able
to follow us.
Welcome to our hideout.
Hey, CoCCo. Good job, buddy.
Boys? Let's finish
what we started.
[CHICKEN] And this time,
try to make it quick, all right?
[BUER]
We shall rout you, fiends!
[UNDERLING 7B]
What's the deal?
It looks like we got company.
I think we'd better
get out there, guys!
[NENE]
What the--?
[rustling]
It's cramped in here!
I got it open!
What happened to me, anyway?
Where am I?
[NENE]
What is this place?
Um... Hello there, friends.
[NENE]
Hold on! Where is Cla-ring?
Damn.
If the CDF finds this place,
we're gonna have to
look for a new hideout.
Well...
That's fine;
this place sucked anyway.
Good riddance.
And besides, we're getting
a high quality catch
out of the deal!
Hurry up and nab
that cyborg, Fried,
but whatever you do,
don't break it!
Okay.
But bro, this one's quick!
Yeah, It might be fast,
but without a human being
telling it what to do,
that puppet's as
worthless as a pile of junk.
It might be able to defend
itself, but not for long!
Fly!
[clucks]
Good job, Fried!
Now, hurry and
take down its system!
[CLARION growls]
See?
In the end it's just
some rich person's toy.
[COCCO clucks]
[CLARION yelling]
No point in struggling.
[CLARION yells]
[CHICKEN]
Huh?
[FRIED groaning]
[UNDERLING 7D]
Mr. Fried!
[UNDERLING 7B]
Did you guys see that?
That friggin' android attacked
him without being ordered to!
It must have an illegal AI!
[CHICKEN]
Damn you!
You wrecked my brother's arm.
You're gonna pay for that,
you piece of junk!
Kill that bot! Destroy it!
[UNDERLING 7D]
Go get the guns!
[NENE]
Cla-ring!
[NENE laughing]
Yay! You're here, Cla-ring!
Hey! Stop!
The humanoid's awake!
Yeah, I can see that, dummy.
Why did you start it up?
I didn't start it!
What's goin' on here?
Oh, Cla-ring!
I'm so happy you
came to rescue me!
Thank you so much!
This place is dangerous.
Recommend evacuation now.
Right!
Let's go!
Wait, Cla-ring,
we can't leave just yet.
[NENE]
If we're leaving,
then I think the right thing to
do would be to take them, too.
But they can't move on their
own because they're empty.
[CLARION]
Empty?
[NENE]
Yes.
But even so, I can
still hear them saying
they want to go home.
You can hear them?
[NENE]
Yes, Cla-ring. I can.
So what do you say
we do a good deed?
[CLARION]
As you wish.
[NENE]
Pandora Device. Open!
[CHICKEN]
Set up in front of the door!
It's the only way in or out!
We've got 'em trapped, boys!
CoCCo. Do your thing!
[COCCO clucks]
[CHICKEN] If there's an illegal
AI with that type of ability
guarding it, that humanoid
must be worth a pretty penny!
[FRIED grunts]
Don't get down on
yourself, brother.
After we sell that bot,
we'll get you the
best arm money can buy.
[FRIED]
Thanks, bro.
Once CoCCo takes
out its sensors,
we'll storm the place,
and get what's ours!
Take out the one with the ears,
but whatever you do,
don't destroy the prize!
[CHICKEN]
Hm?
Hey, CoCCo! What's the matter?
[CHICKEN]
Huh?
[COCCO clucks]
[CHICKEN]
No, CoCCo, why?!
[UNDERLING 7E]
I can't see!
[UNDERLING 7A]
Who's there? What is this?
[UNDERLING 7D] Damn it!
Where'd they come from?
What's happening?
Which one of you idiots
turned our loot back on?
[UNDERLING 7B]
Ah! Keep away!
[UNDERLING 7C]
Ah! No! No, stop it!
[UNDERLING 7A]
Help! They're crushin' me!
[UNDERLING 7E]
Let me go!
[UNDERLING 7D]
I can't move!
[UNDERLING 7C]
There're just so many of them.
What do we do?
We already wiped these droids,
so why are they
powered up again?
We're all dead!
Cla-ring, Cla-ring.
[ANDROIDS]
Cla-ring. Cla-ring.
[CHICKEN]
What the hell?!
[UNDERLING 7A]
We're surrounded!
[UNDERLING 7D]
Put me down!
[UNDERLING 7B]
What is happening?
Decode skill, time.
Elpis Series!
Don't hurt her.
Or we'll make you
regret it, Chicken Man.
[NENE]
Puppeteer!
[UNDERLINGS screaming]
[CHICKEN grunting]
Don't do this, please!
We can work something out!
I beg you!
Do what you want with me,
but whatever you do,
you have to promise me
you won't hurt
my little brother!
[CHICKEN]
CoCCo!
[COCCO]
Cocco?
Yes. Thanks!
Sorry I made you
betray your friends.
You wanna go home now?
[COCCO clucks]
CoCCo. Hey.
He is all yours.
On one condition.
Well, two.
Stop stealing androids.
And don't do anymore
mean things to Cla-ring.
[COCCO clucks]
[CHICKEN] This is the
weirdest day of my life.
[NENE]
Let's go home, Cla-ring.
[CHICKEN]
Somebody wanna explain to me
what the hell
just happened here?
[NENE]
Let's all go home!
[NEWSCASTER 3A] And now
for some breaking news.
The CDF located the hideout
of a notorious island gang
that has been repeatedly
stealing high-grade robots
and arrested them all.
It's a big win
for the community.
The majority of the
robots were confiscated,
but the CDF says
many were likely sold
to locations off-island.
Those channels are
currently being pursued.
It's clear the
members of the gang
had been in a fight.
Many of them were
seriously injured.
[NENE]
That's weird. They're beaten up.
[TAKUMI]
Geez.
Do they have any idea
how much of a pain
in the you-know-what
that was to clean up?
[SUBORDINATE 7A]
Underwater visibility restored.
[SUBORDINATE 7B]
Switching to visual operation.
[SUBORDINATE 7C]
Modify the decoy AIs?
Every one of them, sir?
[KURTZ]
That's right.
Get started right away.
[SUBORDINATE 7C]
The majority of them meet
the uniform standard, sir.
But when there's
this many of them--
[KURTZ]
Do it.
After all,
time waits for no one.
I don't understand.
How did you know the
androids wanted to go home?
'Cause I heard all their
voices in my head saying,
"I wanna go home!"
It's possible that
was residual data
still left in their memory.
No way, it was the
cry of a robot's heart!
Impossible!
[NENE] Cla-ring.
Thanks for saving me!
[CLARION] Nene's safety
is a third-priority matter.
[NENE] You wanna know what
my top priority matter is?
Hugging you with all
of my might, Cla-ring!
Squeeze!
[TAKUMI] Glad to see
you two are so close, yeah!