[CLARION]
Nene. Nene.
Wake up. It's morning now.
[NENE yawns]
[NENE] Cla-ring, do you know
if your joints are waterproof?
Yes. They are sealed properly.
Please turn your
back this way, Nene.
Hey! You're tickling me!
What goes around comes around!
[CLARION]
Ah...
[BUER]
Dark. Cramped. Scared.
Time to go.
[BUER]
Hark!
This smooth sensation
is undoubtedly
a flat-chested maiden
nuzzling me against
her ever so tiny bosom!
Oh. Hi, Gercomas!
Where are you going?
Do you mind if Cla-ring
and I tag along?
[beeping]
No, that's okay,
we don't mind walking.
Thank you, though.
Besides you three guys,
do you know how many
Gercomas there are total?
Oh! Hello, Takumi!
Gertsecommas are
hazy on the concept
of the individual.
Don't waste your time.
They can't understand
vague questions like that!
Take a look at this, Nene!
It's a Gertsecomma
factory, yeah!
Wow!
[TAKUMI] One by one, each of
these menacing mechanisms
is slowly and methodically
assembled here
in this incredible plant.
[TAKUMI]
Pretty neat, yeah?
Their current production count
is 1,031, and that
number grows every day.
The Gertsecommas
are incredibly flexible!
They can change their
options by unitizing
and simplifying their machinery.
They're Takumi's supreme
masterpiece, yeah!
Except that the fundamental
design is Uzal's.
True. But I'm not impressed.
She always makes one-eyed,
egg shaped robots
'cause she thinks
they're super creepy.
Eyeballs are super creepy!
When she first saw the design,
Takumi was thrilled.
But then immediately
she looked annoyed.
It's true.
And then Takumi said--
[TAKUMI]
"Well, if you insist,
I suppose I could make your
stupid robot for you, yeah!"
[CLARION]
Did you not?
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up, yeah!
[NENE]
Takumi?
[TAKUMI]
Where are you going now, yeah?
To the park.
There's a little something
I'd like to try today.
Just watch out for any
nasty bot-nappers, yeah!
Right. I guess we'll
see you later then!
[KIDS yelling, chattering]
This spot should work.
[NENE]
Pandora Device. Open!
Now decode skill.
Elpis Series.
It's juggling time!
Wow...
Well, look at that.
She's really good.
[applause]
Oh my!
[NENE] I can't believe I can
actually do something like this.
It's amazing!
[cheering]
[NENE]
Everyone seems to love it!
[BUER] At water's edge,
a scant-chested maiden
stareth in melancholy
as a gentle breeze
underscores the
sounds of seagulls--
Do you consider that a failure?
It seemed to me everyone
enjoyed themselves.
A testament to
the Pandora Device.
Yeah, you're right.
They were so happy.
Nene.
Is this not a step
in the right direction
of the world peace
that you desire?
I don't know. It just
doesn't feel right to me.
No offense.
But in the end,
it's your power, not mine.
Clarion belongs to Nene.
[BUER]
Hot!
It seems sneaky to
use somebody else's power
for your own benefit.
Seems sneaky?
Do you mean to say
that it's unjust?
Yes.
Think about it this way.
Can you really accomplish
world peace by yourself?
[NENE]
Huh?
The power of others is unjust?
Power is only just if
it's yours to start with?
How do you measure
what is truly yours?
Or what you've
learned from others?
[NENE]
Yeah. Good point.
Technically, I guess
I'm not all mine either.
It's true.
I was made by other people.
My prosthetic limbs
were given to me.
Everything.
Cla-ring, you're right.
Maybe I'm a little
sneaky, as well.
[ANNA] Oh. Are you
already done for the day?
Well, that's too bad.
Maybe there'll be a
second performance later?
You're quite special.
Thank you, but...
I'm not special.
I was just practicing.
You're as modest
as you are talented.
I've seen some of the
best street performers
in the world and they
don't hold a candle to you.
Thanks for the compliment.
But the truth is,
it's not really me
that's good at juggling.
I beg to differ, young lady.
I never expected
that rehabilitation
would be so difficult.
[ANNA]
Truth be told,
I'm still getting used to the
idea of having the darned thing.
Sorry.
I just sprung that on you
rather suddenly, didn't I?
My name's Anna.
What's your name, dear?
Oh. Right.
Nene Nanakarobi.
This is my friend, Cla-ring.
Clarion.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I was quite surprised
to see a child like you
using a prosthetic
limb so skillfully.
I'm afraid I still
can't move mine very well!
I see. I'm very sorry.
No, please.
Watching you did my heart good.
And I wanted to
express my gratitude.
Thank you very much.
Oh, uh... You're welcome.
I want you to have this.
How come?
[ANNA] Children who try hard
should always be rewarded
for their efforts.
[ANNA]
Here.
Thanks a lot. That's very sweet.
Bye, Nene. Bye, Cla-ring.
Nice to meet you!
[NENE]
Children who try hard.
[VLIND groans]
Another round over here!
[ROBOT 5A]
Ma'am, you've had too much.
Shut your face!
[ROBOT 5A]
Two drinks is plenty, Miss.
Don't judge me, you
big heapin' pile of junk!
Robots are takin' over! Yeah!
Just today, I lost
another job to one of you
tin can freaks!
[ROBOT 5A]
Here you go.
It was a part-time costume gig.
And the icing on the cake,
they tell me if I want
to be a real reporter
then I gotta get cyberized!
The world's gone crazy!
I'll close out.
[ROBOT 5A]
Here.
[beeping noise]
[ROBOT 5A]
Your balance is insufficient.
Sign right here, please.
I'll need your ID code
as well, Ma'am.
Yeah.
Hold on...
A network disturbance?
What the--?
[ANNOUNCER 5A]
Attention ladies and gentlemen,
Cenancle Island is
currently experiencing
a large-scale
network disturbance.
We sincerely apologize
to all island residents
for the inconvenience.
We ask for your patience as
we work to resolve this issue.
This sucks.
It's no use, man;
it won't budge!
[KOTOBUKI] Hmph! Our job just
got a heck of a lot easier.
Goodness. What's the problem?
A network disturbance?
[gasps]
Oh no! Someone help!
[ANNA grunts]
All the info feeds...
They're down.
And I'm betting that
the trains are, too.
[CLARION] No repair time
estimate has been announced yet.
[BUER] My fifth leg
hath whispered unto me.
It seems the network disturbance
hath caused
something to go amiss
in the very core of Cenancle
Island's operating system.
But why would that happen?
[BUER] As with all
things in this world,
there is cause and effect.
You think?
[BUER]
Indeed!
For instance, in a certain city,
there was once a
major power outage.
The following year saw
a record-setting baby boom!
[TAKUMI]
Oh, crap!
This has never happened before!
It's not an EMP, and it's
not a virus either, yeah!
I hope Nene's okay out there!
That's right!
Uzal's puppet is with her,
so at least there's no danger
of anyone stealing her, yeah!
[ALTMAN]
You two.
Yes, sir?
[ALTMAN]
Code zero.
Hey, where is
your administrator?
Oh. Well...
I, uh...
Code Zero, please.
That means output your
model and affiliation now.
Is your auditory element
working properly?
Yes. I can hear you
just fine, sir.
[ALTMAN] I gotta say, your
natural responses are amazing.
I bet you're worth
a pretty penny.
The thing is...
I'm a human, not a robot.
A human? But that can't be.
Come on.
No, it's true.
I'm a full-bodied cyborg.
Gee whiz!
Boy, do I feel like a jerk!
Forgive me!
I didn't realize
what you were, Miss.
Oh.
Please don't worry;
I'm used to it by now.
[ALTMAN]
A full-bodied cyborg.
I've heard rumors
of these things before,
but this is definitely
not what I was expecting.
Thanks to the
network disturbance,
robots are going
into standby mode
so it's open season
for cyborg thieves.
I know it's none of my business,
but if I were you two,
I'd go straight home.
I understand, sir.
We were going to
wait for the next train.
But I guess it's down, too.
Why don't you
let me walk you home?
It'll make me feel better about
the way I behaved before.
Plus, this is a dangerous area.
[BUER] Sayeth the wolf
in sheep's clothing--
Hey...
Did either of you ladies
hear something just now?
We did not.
[ALTMAN] Nothing like
this has ever happened
on Cenancle Island before,
and I think the authorities
are pretty clueless
as to what caused it.
[BOY 5A]
Mommy, I'm tired!
Can we go home? Pretty please!
I wish we could, but
with the buses not running,
there's nothing I can do!
Sorry to ask,
but do you mind if we
take a little detour?
Of course! Go right ahead!
[laughing]
I can't help myself;
it's just my nature.
You know what I mean?
Well, in my opinion,
it's a wonderful thing!
Thanks for escorting
us home, sir!
It was really nice
to meet you, Miss!
See? It's my nature!
I just can't help myself!
Right!
We haven't even formally met.
Forgive my manners. I'm Robert.
What's your name?
I'm Nene Nanakorobi.
And this is my friend, Cla-ring.
Clarion.
[ALTMAN]
All right.
Nice to meet you,
Nene. Cla-ring.
[NENE] It's nice to
meet you too, Robert!
[CLARION]
Clarion.
[ALTMAN]
Sorry again! I can't help it.
Honestly, I didn't mean to
take us this far out of the way.
Whoops.
[NENE]
Oh, that's all right.
It was nice to
help others in need.
[OLD LADY 5A yelling]
These bots are like
sitting ducks out here!
[TSUKASA]
Oh yeah!
This is one of Pony's rarest,
high-end models.
We're gonna be
filthy rich, dude!
They took Mii!
Please! Help me get her back!
Are you all right, Ma'am?
You have to help!
My Mii is like family to me!
Nene! You look after her!
No! I'll go, too!
[NENE]
Cla-ring!
[ALTMAN]
What was that?
Dude... What the hell?
My freakin' loot vanished?
Me too.
Damn! What was that?
Check it out. A chick!
Whoa. She's fast!
She took the bags
right out of our hands!
Loot recovery complete.
Dude, that's not a
chick; that's a robot!
It sure is.
Come on, we should
steal that one, too!
[CLARION growls]
[TSUKASA] Okay, Bot, us
humans are in charge now.
You better do what we say.
[CLARION]
Enemy threat confirmed.
Switching to combat mode.
Hold it!
[ALTMAN]
You're not stealing a machine.
You're kidnapping
someone's family member.
Apologize to the lady
for what you've done,
and I might let you
walk away from this!
For real?
[KOTOBUKI] Save us the boring
lecture about right and wrong
and hand over the
damn robot right now,
or you'll be sorry, man!
[ALTMAN]
She's more than just a robot!
Look at her. She's a girl!
Oh, man.
This guy's crazy. Full-on!
What can you do?
And we just hate resorting
to violence so much!
Yes.
I couldn't agree more.
I was hoping we could settle
this peacefully, as well.
Uh oh.
Is this guy just really
strong or somethin'?
[NENE]
Claring! Robert!
You have impeccable
timing, girly bot!
[CLARION]
Nene!
[KOTOBUKI yells]
[ALTMAN]
Hey. You guys all right?
We're okay. Yes!
Mii! Thank you for
bringing her back to me!
Glad I could help, ma'am.
[laughing]
[ALTMAN]
Sorry to hold up the show,
but I gotta make sure these
guys get what they deserve.
[NENE]
It's okay.
We can make it home from here.
It's just not in my nature
to let bad guys get away.
Sorry for getting you and your
friend involved in this mess.
No! Please don't apologize!
World peace is built
on things like this!
[laughing]
World peace, huh?
That's great!
I'll do my best to live
up to your expectations!
Goodbye.
You're a good egg, Nene.
It's true. Cla-ring, too.
Clarion.
You know, Cla-ring...
I think we did a lot to
achieve world peace today!
What's wrong?
It's Anna!
What happened?
Are you all right?
This is awful.
She needs a doctor!
I'll call an ambulance!
There's no connection.
[CLARION] If there is
something that you want to do,
just use the Pandora Device.
Is it sneaky to use someone
else's power for good?
[NENE]
What?
[CLARION]
Or is it just?
You're right. Anna's hurt.
Cla-ring? Come on. Let's help!
[NENE]
Pandora Device. Open!
[NENE] Decode skill.
Elpis Series! Paramedic!
Don't worry, Anna,
you're in good hands now.
[NENE]
Accessing prosthetic limb!
Acquiring vital signs!
Reading clinical record!
I see it all!
Her medical history.
Her drug history.
I know how to deal with this!
This power may not be mine,
but at least I can do
something good with it!
She doesn't just
have a prosthetic limb.
She's also using artificial
internal organs.
Since she's not cyberized,
they're monitored
via the network.
That's why the
disturbance led to errors!
[NENE]
Pinpoint the symptoms!
If I take over
control of your system,
then it'll buy us time.
But we've got to get you
to a hospital right away!
Nene. We need a ride.
Luckily, we have one.
Show yourselves now,
Gertsecommas!
[NENE gasps]
They were concealed
using Takumi's
thermo-optical camouflage.
Thank goodness they're here!
We'll be there
in no time, Anna.
Hang in there!
[TOTO] Well...
There's no need to worry now.
But it's a good thing
you got here when you did.
Thank you so much, Nene.
You saved my life.
Of course.
I'm just glad you're okay now.
You weren't hurt lifting
me off the ground, were you?
Are you kidding?
I'm a full-bodied cyborg,
so it didn't faze me at all.
[ANNA gasps]
[ANNA]
My, my. A full-bodied cyborg.
I've heard rumors of your kind.
That's wonderful.
Good for you, Nene.
Uh... thank you?
[ANNOUNCER 5A]
Please be advised.
The network disturbance
has officially been resolved.
I repeat: The network
disturbance has officially be--
Good for you, Nene.
Anna praised me.
That's never happened before.
[NENE] Although...
I did have a little help.
[phone ringing]
Nene here.
[TAKUMI]
Nene! Are you okay?
Nothing's happened to you, yeah?
I'm fine.
No need to be worried!
[ALTMAN]
Pardon me, sir.
Captain Robert Altman reporting.
[ALTMAN]
Special Military Adviser Kurtz.
What is it can I do
to assist you, sir?
[KURTZ]
You're late.
It's 42 seconds past the
appointed time, Captain Altman.
[ALTMAN]
I apologize, sir.
The sudden network disturbance
resulted in disorder
all across the island,
as you know.
Life is time, Captain,
and nothing more.
Don't waste mine.
Making light of time is
something only savages do.
I will remember that, sir.
I am requisitioning
four of your force's
underwater duty robots, Captain.
Get them ready.
Four? But sir...
Is that necessary?
Forgive me.
Not to speak out of turn,
but we just gave you six.
[KURTZ]
They were lost.
And why do you need them?
I don't feel
inclined to explain.
You have your orders, Captain.
I want them by tomorrow.
[ALTMAN]
Yes, sir.
I will have them ready
for you before noon.
[KURTZ]
One other thing.
I want you to be sure to
carry out that other order
regarding Vulcan Harbor Park.
You can count on me, sir.
And remember: it's all
for the sake of world peace.
[ALTMAN]
Nene. Cla-ring.
There might be peace coming.
But I'm afraid it's
going to be much different
than you imagined.
We really need to play doctor,
'cause I am dying to see you
dressed up like a nurse!
That is pointless.
Just use the
Pandora Device, Nene.
Wait! Maybe I should
dress up like a nurse
and you can be my patient
and I'll take care of you!
I think she might
need to go to a hospital.
[NENE]
Robert! You know what?
You're what they call
a champion of justice!
[ALTMAN laughs]
It's my nature!
[NENE]
I respect you!
[CLARION]
Nene.
Takumi told you to stop
fixating on older men.