[ALTMAN]
Yes, ma'am.
I train every day,
so I have no issue
carrying heavy loads if need be.
[MECHA-PANT] I bet the elderly
community just breathed
a big sigh of relief.
[ALTMAN]
Heck, if I have to,
I'll carry an old person
and their stuff, too!
[laughing]
Huh?
[ALTMAN] The CDF is
here for the people,
and we'll do whatever it takes
to ensure peace on this island!
[laughing]
[MECHA-PANT]
There you have it.
An honest to goodness hero of
the community from the CDF!
Please. Let's tell
the whole truth here.
You and I both know the CDF,
just like the rest of this
island, would be nothing
but a puny little shrimp
if it weren't for its
deep political and economic
ties to a major power.
[MECHA-PANT] I'm Mecha-pant
and this is my sidekick--
The most trusted name in
journalism on Cenancle Island,
the one and only, Vli--
[STAFFER 6A]
Cut! Cut, cut!
You know what?
Get back in the costume!
[AMY sighs]
I can't wait to see
next week's show.
[meows]
[TAKUMI]
Okay. L1, rock!
[NENE]
Uh... Right!
[TAKUMI]
R1, paper!
[NENE]
Okay!
[TAKUMI]
L2! Scissors!
[NENE]
Right. Got it!
[TAKUMI]
R3, paper!
[NENE]
'Kay!
[TAKUMI]
Raise L2, and R3, yeah. Rock!
Uh... Okay!
[TAKUMI]
Raise R1, and L2, scissors!
And now raise L1,
but don't lower L3, yeah!
It's so... hard!
I can't do this anymore!
[TAKUMI]
Well, if you can't handle it,
then what's the point?
Who the heck is gonna
have a practical use
for a Hekatoncheir design
like this anyway, yeah?
[BUER]
Whoa! Hark!
I shall raise my fifth leg!
[BUER screams]
Nene. It's time
for us to go now.
Maintenance, yeah?
Indeed.
[AMY humming]
So how do I look, Grandma?
Dr. Toto won't be able
to resist you, my dear!
Wow, Boss, you look great!
That dress sure does flutter!
It's like the old saying goes,
"love makes a lady lovely!"
Grandma, stop!
[AMY'S GRANDMOTHER]
Good grief.
What in the world is all
this commotion about?
We have company, Granny.
These guys from the CDF
say they need to speak to us.
I don't care who they are.
If they want answers,
they'll have to talk to Granny!
No, wait. I can't
get involved with this.
We have places to be!
It's okay.
I can go to the hospital
by myself, Grandma!
You sure?
I'll be okay!
I won't get lost, and I won't
talk to any strangers, either!
If anything happens,
you call me right away!
[AMY]
'Kay, bye bye!
[giggling]
[LEAN meows]
[SAMANTHA]
All right. Change into this.
You can put your clothes
in there, young lady.
[NENE]
Yes, ma'am!
[BUER]
Ahoy!
Away we sail,
upon the unknown ocean!
We chart a course
into the vast sea
of a maiden's
lingering fragrance!
Look at that cute little doll.
[BUER] Lo, thou art
a ministering angel!
Sei molto bella!
Oh, you precocious thing.
Are you one of those petroids?
The newer models
are so well made.
I am no pet!
I am BUER, the demon king!
Tonight, let us speak to each
other of love everlasting.
Nene. I think it's about
time for us to go now.
[NENE]
'Kay!
[BUER] The moment for
maintenance of the adult variety
is upon us!
Girl on girl!
[muffled yelling]
Nene. Shall we go then?
Sure.
[BUER] Ah! Cramped and dark.
Cramped and dark.
Cramped and dark!
[TOTO] The stress
and strain on your frame
is within acceptable limits.
So there's nothing
to worry about there.
Does anything
feel uncomfortable?
No, Doctor. I'm fine.
Good, good.
And your senses haven't
seemed out of tune
with your body?
No. Not since I
came here to the island.
[SAMANTHA] Looks like
she's been in good shape
since she arrived
at Takumi's house.
Interesting.
[LEAN meows]
Stay here, Lean!
Animals aren't
allowed in the hospital.
I'll be done soon,
but you're gonna have to wait.
[LEAN meows]
Listen.
Don't, don't, don't,
don't, don't move!
Promise you'll stay right here.
[ANNOUNCER 5A] This notification
is for all island residents.
Please be advised a large-scale
network disturbance
has occurred.
[MALE CITIZEN 6A]
Hello? Hello?
Uh oh, it's another
network disturbance.
Great. Here we go again.
What a massive pain.
You shouldn't worry about it.
It's not really a problem!
In three, two, one.
[TOTO]
See?
The hospital's system is
set up to immediately switch
to hard-wired lines
as a safety measure.
Doctor?
Is it okay to continue
an exam like this
during a network disturbance?
Yes, of course!
It's more than okay.
The owner of this hospital
had the prudent idea
to install high-level
disaster countermeasures.
[TAKUMI] Naturally there's
plenty of emergency power.
Plus, a multi-layered
web of barriers
constantly guards
all connections between
the hospital and the
Island's network, yeah!
What's more, the
hospital's infrastructure
is primarily wired,
so we can continue
with medical treatment
even when fully isolated
from the outside network.
Wow!
The owner sounds like
a pretty incredible person!
[TOTO laughs]
[TOTO]
Incredible, indeed!
[TOTO] All right.
Clench as hard as you can.
[NENE grunting]
[TOTO]
Okay, very good.
What is this exam for, Doctor?
We're adjusting
things so you can exert
the exact level of
strength you intend to.
I'm using a collection
of data from average girls
your age as a reference point.
At the moment, the trouble is
there's a little bit too much
leeway in your base output.
So I have the ability to
exert superhuman strength?
[TOTO] Well, yes, but we're
adjusting it so that you won't.
Aside from being impractical,
that level of strength
could be dangerous.
On the other hand, applying
limiters isn't good, either.
[NENE laughs]
The brains of all living things,
both people and animals,
frequently issue
behavioral commands
that don't take
into account the body's
actual structural strength,
and then of course,
it quickly applies the brakes.
But if we were to release torque
every time that happens...
He just wants you
to be normal, dear.
You don't want your friends
to call you Gorilla Girl, right?
I don't know.
I think gorillas are cute.
Not that I've ever
seen a real one before.
[TOTO] As a result, we must
create appropriate safeguards.
[FEMALE VOICE 6A] Your
registration is now complete.
Please wait in the lobby.
[LEAN meows]
[AMY]
Lean!
Lean. I told you to wait. Gosh.
Stop it. Be quiet, Lean!
They'll hear you and
I'll get in big trouble!
Will you relax? Ah! Lean!
[AMY]
Come back here!
Dr. Toto is gonna
be so mad at me!
[AMY]
Lean!
[LEAN meows]
[AMY] That's a good
kitty cat. Hold still!
[cart rolling]
[LEAN meows]
[AMY]
Lean? Hello?
It's not scary anymore.
Come on out now!
[AMY]
Hello?
[BUER]
This box of terror is naught
compared to the
icy prison of Cocytus!
There's a tiny thing inside.
[BUER]
I am not tiny!
My name is BUER.
And I am a philosopher of Hades.
A philosopher?
[BUER]
Indeed.
What a weird petroid.
I wonder if someone
left it behind.
[BUER]
I am no one's possession!
But I thank thee sincerely
for liberating me, dainty lady.
You're very kind.
Oh. You're very welcome.
[BUER]
Muah!
I don't have time to pal
around with this tiny thingy!
Lean! He could be anywhere!
[BUER]
BUER!
I would have thee
call me that, dainty lady.
Now. Tell me, who is Lean?
Lean is a kitten.
I told him not to but he
followed me here anyway.
[BUER]
A-ha!
You see, pets aren't
allowed in the hospital.
It'll be a disaster
if one of the employees
finds him wandering around.
So I need to make sure
I get to him first!
[BUER]
Aye, I understand thy plight!
Thou can rely
upon my assistance!
[AMY]
Thanks a lot! But...
[BUER]
What is the matter?
[AMY] If he finds out I
brought Lean here with me,
Dr. Toto will never
forgive me for it!
[BUER] Thou needest not
be troubled by such things.
Thou shalt recover all
that thou holdest dear.
After all, little girls
are the only beings
who deserve to get everything
their hearts desire!
[crying]
[AMY]
Thank you very much.
[BUER]
No thanks necessary.
I do but speak the truth
to you, dainty lady.
Let us embark!
If there be a cat to
find in these chambers,
then verily, I shall not
fail in discovering it!
[KURTZ]
Give me a progress report, now.
[TECHNICIAN 6A] We've penetrated
the outermost logic
barrier layer, along
with layers two and three.
We're continuing our
attempts to access layer four.
[TECHNICIAN 6B]
AI support array one,
core temperature
up twenty points.
[TECHNICIAN 6C]
Array two connected.
Array three on standby.
[TECHNICIAN 6A] Sir. A
large-scale network disturbance
is occurring on the surface.
Not our problem.
Continue the work.
Well, BUER...
You're going to oppose me
to the bitter end?
[BUER]
Tell me, dainty lady...
Does this stray creature we
seek not have a tracking device?
[AMY]
Like the ones for pets?
You know, his collar
might have one, actually.
[BUER] And dost thou
know the ID number?
[AMY]
Hmm...
It's right here!
[BUER]
Ah!
[BUER yells]
Well?
[BUER] There has been
a network disturbance.
A great, penetrating
darkness is blinding my sight.
[AMY]
What do you mean?
[BUER]
I cannot help you.
[CLARION] We have a problem.
BUER is gone.
Whaddaya imagine
happened to him?
He has fled.
He hasn't made it very far.
There're no threats
on the premises.
Do you know where
we can find him, Cla-ring?
[CLARION]
This way.
[AMY crying]
Dr. Toto's never
gonna forgive me!
Oh, Lean! Where'd you go?
Why didn't you listen to me?
[BUER] Hmm...
I do find your tears touching.
But they do not suit a
dainty lady like yourself.
Entrust your hopes in me!
You're no help at all!
You said it yourself!
[BUER]
Nay!
[BUER laughing]
It seems the time hath come
for the philosopher
of Hades to rise up!
[BUER]
No matter how they might try,
none can evade the penetrating
force of my fifth leg!
Should an enemy of
thy cause approach,
fear not, for I will smite
them with my mighty hoof!
[yelling]
[BUER]
Small animal spotted!
[LEAN meows]
[AMY]
You found him. Awesome!
[LEAN meows]
[AMY]
Lean, come back!
Don't run away!
[LEAN meows]
[ANNA]
Hmm?
Oh, goodness me.
A kitty cat,
in a place like this?
[LEAN meows]
[AMY]
I lost track of Lean again!
[BUER] Grievest not,
dear dainty lady.
Truly, what hardship can
there be with BUER by thy side?
Wah!
[AMY] Thanks for
helping out, tiny guy.
Just as soon as we find Lean,
we'll go find your owner,
no matter how long it takes.
[BUER]
If you are willing,
I would not be averse
to frolicking by thy side
a while longer.
Why don't you wanna go back?
Do you get bullied at home?
[BUER]
Nay, I am not bullied!
[laughs nervously]
Nothing can bind me,
the demon king.
But 'tis nice to visit
the human world occasionally.
[laughs nervously]
[BUER] Hast thou come to this
establishment for treatment,
dainty lady?
Uh-huh!
This leg's only temporary.
I'm getting it switched
for a brand new one today.
[BUER]
A-ha!
[AMY] I can't wait to see
what my new leg looks like!
That's why I wore this dress!
'Cause Grandma thinks
it'll be a perfect match!
[BUER]
So sweet.
Her childlike innocence
alights inside my once dark
and bitter heart!
My dear dainty lady!
You look lovely!
That outfit brings
out thy life's glow!
[NENE]
Oh! There's BUER!
[BUER]
Ah! Sweet Maiden!
This reunion is an
inevitability of...
[BUER]
...fate.
Is she your owner,
tiny guy? Hello.
[BUER]
Sweet Maiden!
Do not forget to admire me as--
[ANNA] Well, well!
If it isn't Nene and Clarion!
[AMY]
Lean!
[ANNA] Oh!
Does this kitty belong to you?
[LEAN meows]
[ANNA] I was exploring
the hospital grounds
when I came across her cat.
[NENE] But I thought
you had been released?
[ANNA] The doctors were
concerned about the recurring
network disturbances.
So they asked me
to stay for a few days
in case there are issues.
[PA chimes]
[PA 6A] Paging Amy Gilliam.
Paging Amy Gilliam.
Please come to
examination room 3.
[NENE]
It's time for your checkup.
All right!
And don't worry, my dear.
We'll watch your cat for you.
[AMY]
Mm-hmm!
[NENE] Amy, you
shouldn't run like that
on the hospital grounds.
You might... fall down...
[NENE]
Aw, Amy!
Oh no! This is a total disaster!
I can't go see Dr. Toto
looking like this!
Why don't we borrow
a hospital robe for now
and get you covered up!
[cries]
I won't wear anything
but my special dress!
[AMY crying]
I usually keep a sewing
kit handy just in case,
but I doubt it can be fixed
in such a short amount of time.
[BUER]
There is another way.
Oh! Good call!
[NENE]
Okay, Amy.
You stay right here.
And remember, no peeking!
[CLARION gasps]
[NENE]
Pandora Device. Open!
Decode skill. Elpis Series.
[NENE]
Couturier!
[ANNA]
Care for some candy, dear?
[AMY]
Sure.
It's as good as new.
Wow!
[laughing]
[AMY]
Oh, wow! Wow, wow, wow!
Thank you for
saving the day, Nene!
[AMY]
Look, I'm all done!
[laughing]
[NENE] Oh. So you live at
that big camp in the park?
[AMY]
Yes!
Thanks for walking
me back, Nene.
That's sweet of you.
It's no problem.
You too, Cla-ring.
It's Clarion.
[BUER]
Hast not thou forgotten someone?
And thank you,
as well, tiny guy.
[BUER]
I am not "tiny guy." I'm BUER!
[NENE]
What is this?
[AMY]
This can't be...
Grandma...
[crying]
Grandma's gone and
everyone else is too!
Where did they go?
[NENE]
It'll be all right, Amy.
[phone ringing]
[AMY]
Grandma! Grandma, hey!
Yes, it's Amy! Where are you?
All right. Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Uh-huh, okay.
Yes, I understand. Bye, Grandma.
Is she okay?
[AMY]
Yeah.
She said some
officials from the CDF
paid them a visit and forced
everybody to clear the area.
[NENE]
Where are they now?
Uh... Here.
I know where that is, Amy!
We can take you there.
For real?
[LEAN hisses]
[NENE]
Come on, Cla-ring, let's go!
[AMY]
Let's go, Cla-ring!
I can't wait to tell Grandma the
story of how you fixed my dress!
[NENE]
Yeah! That'll be fun!
You better catch up, Cla-ring!
[AMY]
Catch up, Cla-ring!
[LEAN hisses]
Last one there's a rotten egg!
[BUER]
What an embrace!
A tower hath been erected on
the tropical island of my--
[NENE]
Huh?
What was BUER so
excited about back there?
Please don't pay
attention to that moron.
I wonder if that tower is real.
We should take a trip there!
We could watch the
sunset from the tiptop!
I think BUER had a different
kind of tower in mind.
[BUER]
I am BUER the demon king,
philosopher of Hades!
[AMY]
What are you, a lion?
[BUER] I'm endowed with
the head of the lion,
five limbs of the goat,
and eternal knowledge
of time and space!
[AMY] That tiny front leg
of yours is really cute!
[BUER]
It's not tiny!