[PASSENGER 1A]
Over there!
[PASSENGER 1B]
I see it!
[VLIND]
Camera! Sound!
Are we ready to go?
Time to start
the legend, people!
Hello there, my friends!
We're live outside
of Cenancle Island!
Not only is this
beautiful sanctuary
a first-class
luxury resort,
it's a city designed
with the latest
in cutting edge technology.
Keep your eyes
glued to that screen,
because in addition to
many famous corporations
and name brands
setting up shop here,
many of the globe's
most beloved celebrities
call this beautiful island
their home away from home!
Cut! Seriously,
who writes this crap?
I can't believe
we're already there.
I wonder what the heck
Clarion is up to.
[VLIND]
You know what I have?
Dreams!
First journalism! Then TV!
Then I become the
most famous movie star
in the history of the world!
[VLIND yells]
[CAMERA PERSON]
Why did you fall overboard?
That mic is really expensive!
[MIC PERSON] Should we
throw you a life preserver?
[UZAL]
Look at that.
[UZAL] That gaming system's
over twenty years old!
She plays it like she
knows what she's doing, too!
[UZAL]
Interesting.
Looks like she's a robot.
Hey! You there!
Code zero, please!
State your model number
and your owner's name!
[UZAL]
She didn't respond to the code,
which means she
might be an unauthorized
black-market android.
In that case, maybe
I'll snatch her up!
[UZAL]
I said, Code Zero!
Wait, do you mean me?
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
People make that mistake a lot!
You see, I'm not an android.
Don't feel bad!
It's not your fault!
I know I sort of look like one!
[UZAL]
Forgive me for my mistake.
I assume you're a
full-bodied cyborg then?
Yes! Wow!
How did you know?
What a relief.
Not many people
understand that right away.
Usually they think I'm
some sort of illegal robot.
I know it's misleading
'cause I'm wearing a swim suit.
It's just that it's been so
long since I've had the chance.
[UZAL]
A full-body cyborg!
Interesting!
Huh?
[UZAL]
No, that game of yours.
Monster Bash on
an early model DSD!
It really takes me
back to my childhood!
Wait...
You said "childhood,"
but this gaming system is old.
Real old.
Oops.
I'm so sorry!
[UZAL]
It's fine.
The truth is, I haven't
seen something as archaic
as a non-direct link
game in a long time.
[NENE] I got it from
my doctor, actually.
It's part of my rehabilitation.
[UZAL]
You don't say...
But enough about that.
[water splashes]
[NENE yells]
[UZAL]
Well, well. Look who's back.
What have you got for me?
An annoying journalist.
Uh... I'm alive.
[UZAL]
What about results?
Results?
You always say such
vague things, Uzal.
Specifically, I'm asking
whether you managed
to glean any useful info.
[CLARION]
No.
[NENE gasps]
Nothing to report yet.
Ah! Ah! She's so cute!
Wah!
Is she your daughter?
[UZAL] You're a lot
of fun, you know that?
[ANNOUNCER 1A]
Ladies and gentlemen.
The ship will soon
arrive at Cenancle Island.
All passengers please
prepare to disembark.
[UZAL]
Introduction time.
My name is Uzal Delilah.
I have a little business
I run here on Cenancle Island.
[NENE] It's a pleasure
to make your acquaintance.
I'm Nene Nanakorobi.
I've actually just moved
to the island today.
[UZAL]
Nice to meet you.
Wait, Nanakorobi?
Greetings, you may
call me Clarion.
I am Uzal's prized cyborg pet.
Anyone who touches these ears
will feel the wrath of my fists.
[NENE gasps]
Can I hug you now?
Pretty please!
[CLARION]
No, you may not!
[UZAL] Feel free to
hug her all you want.
[NENE]
Huh?
Now don't resist, Clarion.
[NENE]
Clarion!
[NENE laughing]
Yeah, she's a lot
heavier than she looks,
and much stronger, too.
You see, you and
Clarion are the same.
[NENE]
The same?
So she's a full-bodied
cyborg, too?
Oh, wow!
This is great!
I've never met anyone like me.
From now on, you and I
will be best friends!
Look at that cute little
prosthetic body of yours!
So adorable!
[UZAL] Don't you have
the ability to choose
your outward appearance, too?
Well, actually, this is the
outcome of a growth simulation.
And my face was given
to me by my mom and dad.
Filial reverence
is rare these days.
Guess the apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
[UZAL]
Go on, Nene.
Feel free to hug her as
much as your heart desires!
[NENE]
Hooray!
[UZAL]
Clarion, no resisting!
[CLARION yells]
Just not the ears!
By the way, Nene.
While you're here on the island,
is there anything specific
you're hoping to accomplish?
Oh. Well, yes.
As a matter of fact, I've come
here to live at my aunt's place.
[UZAL]
Ah.
Korobase.
I'm going to learn about
life in the real world
while trying to repay
my aunt for her kindness.
Let me change
the question a bit.
If you could get your
hands on a bunch of money,
I mean a whole heck of a lot,
and you could obtain
anything you wanted,
what would it be?
Well, let's see...
[UZAL]
Clarion excluded.
[NENE]
I know.
I've dreamed about this for
as long as I can remember.
It's tricky, though.
I'm not even sure this is
something money can buy.
And if it is,
then I feel pretty certain
it's going to be expensive.
[UZAL]
What is it?
Why, world peace, of course!
[laughing]
Well, well!
You really are
interesting, aren't you?
You should pick something else.
And then you should
let Clarion go.
[NENE] When I saw the world
for the first time as a cyborg,
I was amazed that it
still looked beautiful.
It was like I had stumbled upon
some incredible secret truth.
I'm sorry! It's hard
to put into words!
Don't apologize; it's a
perfectly realistic dream.
If you work hard, then
you can make it come true.
Right!
[ship horn blowing]
[UZAL] Well, you have
my contact information.
Once you get settled in,
come and visit us.
So does that mean
I'll get to see Clarion again?
Yes!
[UZAL]
Uh... I'm sorry.
Something urgent has come up.
I have to get going.
Oh, okay!
[UZAL]
Oops, I almost forgot.
Welcome to
Cenancle Island, Nene!
It was so nice to meet you!
Say hi to Takumi for me!
Right! Nice to
meet you too, Clarion!
Nanakorobi.
I can't believe
she is an authorized
first-generation full-body.
No wonder Korobase is so proud.
Huh?
Hold on, how in the world did
she know my aunt's first name?
Well, whatever.
[humming]
[NENE]
Hello, this is Nene.
I'm at the harbor.
No, I understand the address.
Yes. I'll be just fine!
[NENE]
So many firsts.
My first trip, my first home,
the first person I've
ever met who's like me.
I sure hope we can be friends.
[NENE]
Wow! What weather!
Dad, Mom...
I felt welcomed
for the first time.
And it was wonderful.
--[CROWD muttering]
--What? No...
That's the way my friends went.
Uzal! Clarion!
[NENE]
Dad! Mom!
[NENE whimpering]
They're in danger.
And they need my help!
I'm on my way!
[sirens wailing]
Clarion! Uzal!
[NENE]
It's them!
Huh?
Why are they going that way?
Run away from danger,
or charge right into it!
For world peace! Yeah! Woo!
Hey, surprise!
Guess who came back?
[BUNNY] What the hell is the
meaning of this, Sahar Schehera?
[UZAL]
You activated BUER, didn't you?
[BUNNY]
That's correct!
And let me guess:
it went berserk.
[BUNNY]
You knew it was defective!
Now the underground
facility's collapsed,
and the organization
is in shambles!
Because you started
it up on your own, moron.
What she said.
I gave you a dummy
activation key.
I kept the real one for myself.
What amazes me is
you actually believed
I wasn't gonna notice
your little rebellion.
[ALL growl]
How could you do this?
There's been significant
damage on the surface, too!
Demon!
You fiend, you!
Why did you make us
wear these outfits?
[UZAL] Isn't it your
fault for betraying me?
[ALL growl]
[BUNNY] Hand over the
real activation key now!
Seems our former
friend is upset.
I guess she's not too
keen on being buried alive.
Are you sure you don't
want to beg me to save you?
[BUNNY]
Ugh! You shut up!
[UZAL]
Do you think they're doing this
because I didn't
pay them enough?
[CLARION]
No, they just don't like you.
Well, it's mutual.
Clarion.
Pandora device, open now!
Pandora device is initiating.
Confirmed.
Release skill:
Elpis Series, Anti-Material,
Enhanced Strength,
Pincer Attack Defensive
and Close Quarters Combat.
[NENE panting]
Clarion! Clari!
Cla-ring!
Cla-ring?
Not my name.
[CHINA DRESS]
Surround her!
[GYM UNIFORM]
Pincer Attack!
[NENE]
Wow, she's amazing!
[CHINA DRESS] Is this one
of Sahar's puppets?
[GYM UNIFORM]
Let's demolish her.
[LEOTARD]
Rock drill cartridge!
[NENE gasps]
Clarion! Protect Nene!
Cla-ring, no!
You'd better come with me!
[NENE gasps]
Well! Good luck, Clario!
We're outta here!
Don't abbreviate it.
[BUNNY gasps]
[CHINA DRESS]
The transmission!
What's with this smoke screen?
[NENE]
I'm sorry!
I feel awful about
your arm, Cla-ring!
Don't worry about her.
She can't stand having
her arm ripped off
by an excavation robot
almost as much as
she can't stand nicknames.
She'll be just fine.
An arm or two really
isn't anything to fuss about.
I know it's prosthetic,
but that doesn't make it okay!
She lost it protecting you,
so I doubt she minds too much.
And while we're on the subject,
what are you doing here?
[NENE]
I completely forgot.
We have to leave right now.
The city is falling apart!
Well...
I'd love to, but in case you
forgot, we have company.
Oh. Right.
What are those things?
They're bad guys!
The worst of the worst!
[NENE yells]
This is a major
emergency, Nene.
If you're willing, I could
certainly use your help.
[NENE]
Sure!
Is there something
that I can do?
Why yes, there is.
I need you to let me
write a wee bit of data
into your body's storage system.
Sadly, there's no
time to explain why.
Yes, ma'am, whatever you say!
You shouldn't be so
trusting of strangers. Okay?
Huh?
I swear...
Are you ready, Cla-ring?
It's Clarion!
We're temporarily
giving Nene Nanakorobi
the authority to use the
Pandora Device, all right?
[CLARION]
Uh...!
Yeah. Okay.
[UZAL] I programmed you
to have that look,
but you're making
me wish I hadn't.
The Pandora? What is that?
[screams]
[UZAL] Just put your
fingers right in there!
You're joking, right?!
Thanks a lot, but I'm
not into that stuff!
[UZAL] I'm sorry, Nene, but
this is absolutely necessary.
Guide her hand, Clarion.
[NENE gasps]
[UZAL] You do have the ability
to connect via your F port?
[NENE]
Well, yes, but--
Wait a minute!
[UZAL]
Pandora Device, open!
Release skill.
Elpis Series. Advanced Firearms!
[NENE] Deep inside of me
where I can't touch.
Where there's supposed to be
nothing but wires and machinery.
There's something
new coming into me.
Behead! I meant to say behold!
This is the scene here in
Vulcan City on Cenancle Island.
The ground is rumbling,
and explosions are
occurring everywhere!
This report is coming
to you from right smack
in the middle of danger.
By me, Vli--
[VLIND screams]
Where's Sahar?
Get us out of here now!
I'm working on it!
[BUNNY]
There they are!
Yikes!
[CLARION]
Left!
I won't let you do anything
to Cla-ring! So there!
[SCHOOL UNIFORM]
What do we do?
[MAID OUTFIT] There isn't
a whole lot we can do
with these pieces of junk!
[GYM UNIFORM] I'm working on
rounding up the security robots!
[UZAL] Aw! Thank you so
much for protecting Clarion.
She has a present
she'd like to give you.
[NENE]
Huh?
Take it.
Thank you so much, Cla-ring!
[UZAL] Use that to
protect us from danger.
I can't do that!
I want to, but I don't know how.
I've never held a gun before,
much less shot at bad guys!
Oh my!
Well done, Nene!
[NENE]
Whoa, what's happening?
This isn't my standard base
cyborg operating system.
[UZAL]
Relax.
The app we just
installed in your system
is expanding and adjusting
within the framework of your OS.
It's done booting up now.
[NENE]
Uzal! What are these things?
[GYM UNIFORM] I rounded
up the security robots!
[BUNNY]
Kill them now!
[NENE growls]
[UZAL]
Just as I thought.
She's an adepter.
[UZAL] "Full cyborg" is a
cutting edge technology
that's currently in development.
After rigorous rehabilitation,
cyborgs finally become able
to achieve basic movement.
Most people are
incapable of adapting
to the prosthetics at all,
so it's likely to be some time
before the tech is widely used.
However, in a few
rare instances,
reports show that certain
people have not only adapted
to the prosthetic body,
but their physical abilities
are greater than
that of a human.
We call these
anomalies "adepters."
They are able to compensate
for the limitations
of prosthetic tech using
their own innate talent.
Information about
adepters is classified.
All we know is that
they're teenagers or younger.
[UZAL]
Just like little Nene here.
An application for skill-based
prosthetic body control.
It's what we put
inside you before.
More ammo.
It's temporary.
But the application
gave you the shooting skills
of a highly trained
military professional.
It's essentially a
behavioral supplement app
for humanoid robot use,
but you managed it quite well.
Huh? So that's
how I did that?
[UZAL]
Look out, more of them!
[NENE yells]
[NENE]
It's true.
Just like before,
it's as if they're
moving in slow motion.
I know what to do. Take 'em out!
Uzal... What happened?
There's a time limit to keep
it away from undesirables.
The development process
has been put on hold
since it violates a dozen
or more international laws.
[NENE]
Never mind that! Cla-ring!
I was so worried about you!
Whoa! You're all burnt up!
[UZAL]
Clarion's all right.
What about you? Are you okay?
[NENE]
I'm great! See for yourself!
Oh no! I forgot!
I need to contact
my aunt immediately!
That's strange.
I can't get through!
[UZAL]
Takumi is fine.
What?
[UZAL]
Takumi Korobase.
That's right.
I meant to ask you earlier
and it slipped my mind.
How do you know my aunt?
Believe it or not, we're
close friends, your aunt and I.
I'm so glad to hear that!
Now!
Let's get out of here right away
and find a safe place to hide!
Uzal, Nene is awake.
[NENE]
Hug time!
What happened to my clothes?
Oh, Cla-ring.
You naughty little thing.
You're a weirdo.
[UZAL]
You collapsed suddenly.
We brought you here so you
could recover your strength.
Wait, I collapsed?
What's the matter with me?
Nothing like that's
ever happened before.
Where are we?
[UZAL]
This is my lab.
[NENE]
It's like my old hospital ward.
I don't understand,
are you a doctor or something?
[UZAL]
Sort of.
Uzal, there's no time!
[NENE gasps]
Thanks for taking care of me.
But don't you think
maybe you should repair
Cla-ring's arm first?
[UZAL]
We'll take care of her.
But it'll have to wait.
[BUNNY]
Sahar!
Come out of there!
Sahar?
[UZAL sighs]
The bad guys
have found us again!
[BUNNY] If you won't
come out, we're coming in!
[NENE]
Oh no!
We're in a tight spot, Clario!
Go! Open the
Pandora Device, now!
Huh?
[UZAL] You know what
you have to do, right Nene?
Yes. But...
Are you sure
Cla-ring doesn't mind?
[BUNNY]
Keep going!
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am!
C'mon.
Don't do it for me;
do it for World Peace!
All right then. Here goes!
[NENE]
It's entering me again.
Huh? Something's
different this time.
[NENE gasps]
What is this outfit?
[UZAL] Optical camouflage
tech that's currently
under development.
Camouflage?
[UZAL] I integrated it
into your mainframe.
You did?
[UZAL]
Naturally.
You want to disguise
your true identity
when dealing with
something so top secret.
Ah! This isn't camouflage!
It makes me stand out more!
[UZAL] I have an arsenal
of weapons for you.
Use whichever you like!
[NENE gasps]
Cla-ring, you should stand back!
I understand, but I refuse.
[NENE]
Huh?
[crying]
Save us, Mistress Sahar!
Please!
We can't take it anymore!
[CHINA DRESS] BUER is
completely out of control!
[BUNNY]
It just keeps rampaging!
[LEOTARD] The stop code
won't work, either!
[GYM UNIFORM] At this rate,
it's going to bore right into
the base of the island!
We are so sorry, Mistress Sahar!
I don't like to be
called by that name.
Quit with the crying already.
I'll stop the machine, okay?
[NENE]
Sahar? Who's that? You?
[UZAL]
Nene.
[NENE]
Huh?
Earlier today,
I recall you telling me
that you wanted
to buy world peace.
[UZAL chuckles]
Well then, how about
we start by buying peace
for Cenancle Island?
[NENE]
Huh?
I'm so glad we get to work
together, aren't you, Cla-ring?
Don't you listen?
I told you not to call me that!
Aww!
But I really love that nickname.
It's so cute, Cla-ring!
Disconnect me, please.
[NENE] Hey, Cla-ring,
I have a question for you.
What is that big black
ball thingy underground?
[CLARION]
A boring machine.
[NENE]
Good grief!
I don't think I could
roll a ball that big.
[CLARION]
Boring, not bowling.