[NENE]
Whoa. So that's BUER?
This is not good.
Wait... Buy peace? For real?
The island's in danger.
If we don't save it,
no one will.
Well, what do you say?
Should we give it a shot?
Mmm... All right.
Thatta girl!
Of course, we wouldn't
be in this mess
if it weren't for those
morons over there.
Thanks to them,
my company's robot
is bringing the city
to the brink of collapse.
What robot?
[UZAL]
Its formal name is BUER.
It's a giant boring machine
my company created.
I've never seen a
bowling machine before.
[SCHOOL UNIFORM]
"Boring," not "bowling!"
[BUNNY] Besides, "boring
machine" doesn't even
begin to cover it--
[yells]
So we beat the machine,
and everything goes
back to normal, right?
Indeed!
You're our only hope, Nene.
No one can stop it but you!
[NENE] All right!
But are you sure I can do it?
Clearly, you'll
need Clarion's help,
but of course you can!
Okay.
[UZAL] Unless the two of you
join forces and work together,
I fear BUER will
sink this entire city!
[NENE gasps]
[NENE] Shouldn't we
repair her arm first?
[UZAL]
Yeah, good call.
[NENE gasps]
Cla-ring!
[NENE whimpering]
[UZAL]
Well, Nene, what do you say?
Will you team up with
Clarion and give her a hand?
A hand? Oh my!
Me fighting alongside
my new best friend?
Of course! With Clarion,
there's nothing I can't do!
You're incredibly brave.
And now for the plan.
[UZAL] I wish the
time limit on her using
the Pandora Device
could be longer.
What a letdown.
So sparkly!
Now that everyone's
on the same page,
it's time to
get down to business.
First, why don't you
take a look at this?
[NENE gasps]
[UZAL]
Clarion.
What's the situation with BUER?
[CLARION]
We have a precise location.
Three hundred fifty
meters below ground,
BUER is at the base of
subterranean shaft G11,
beneath Vulcan City.
[NENE]
Gosh, it's so far down!
[UZAL]
What you see here is BUER.
[NENE]
An eyeball?
[UZAL] Not very practical,
but definitely creepy.
[NENE]
Yes. It certainly is.
Is it recharging?
[UZAL]
Clarion.
Sum up the plan for
neutralizing BUER, please.
After BUER fires its cannon,
there's a cooling period
that lasts 180 seconds.
But the more it fires, the
greater the heat it generates,
which means the
cooling takes longer.
Cla-ring is the
coolest of all time!
That's too boring.
Lighten it up a little!
[CLARION]
As you wish.
[NENE]
How cute!
[CLARION] First, we press a
frontal assault to provoke BUER.
This should cause it to fire.
While the cannon is cooling,
we approach and shut it down.
--[UZAL] Hmm...
--[CHINA DRESS] This is nuts!
--[BUNNY] We're all gonna die!
--[GYM UNIFORM] I quit.
Shutting it down is easy.
You simply call the main console
and use the authentication
key, understood?
Where's the key, you ask?
Don't you worry!
It's right here.
[ALL]
What, those?
That's what I need
to do to disable BUER?
[UZAL] No, Clarion
will take care of that.
What I need for you to do
is to be her bodyguard.
Nene will cover
Clarion using this.
[UZAL]
Where were you?
[BUNNY]
Cut us some slack!
We dug our way to the vault
as fast as we could!
Whoa!
What is this, some kind of gun?
[UZAL]
It's a prototype.
But it should be a good piece
of backup for Clarion.
Is it real powerful?
[UZAL]
"Quick" is the word I'd use.
It's as fast as light.
[CLARION]
I'll use this.
Nene.
I certainly hope you don't take
what I'm about to say to you
the wrong way.
But this equipment is not meant
for a flesh-and-blood human.
[NENE]
Here we go.
We start our attack
in one minute.
Oh boy.
I'm so tense.
I've gotta calm down.
Hey, Cla-ring. Are you scared?
Hm? I know fear.
I'm not scared.
[UZAL] How about we
start by buying peace
for Cenancle Island?
Right.
Okay!
If I'm by your side,
then I'm not scared either!
Yay.
[VLIND]
Collapsing buildings!
A city in a state of chaos!
A major crisis saturated with
the choking stench of fire!
What exactly is happening
here on Cenancle Island?
The things you see
are not the whole truth!
And the whole truth is
not the things you see!
I said it twice
because it's so true!
What conspiracy lurks
at the bottom of this darkness?
Now, bringing it
all to you live!
It's me,
the pride of Titan TV!
The woman. The myth.
The legend of live reporting!
[yells]
Vli--!
[NENE]
Ten more seconds.
Three. Two. One.
Come on, ladies, let's go!
--We're gonna die!
--Sweet death!
[GIRLS yelling]
Well, here we go.
First, we press a frontal
assault to provoke the machine
into firing its particle cannon.
[CHINA DRESS]
You big piece of junk!
Good luck, everyone!
[GIRLS yelling]
They did it! It's working!
But won't they be in
danger if they're decoys?
[UZAL]
They'll be fine, Nene.
They just need to be
fast enough to dodge!
[UZAL]
Don't you worry!
[CLARION] BUER has switched
to emergency cooling mode.
Come on.
Let's do this.
All right!
That was for good luck.
Be careful, Cla-ring!
[CLARION] The defense mechanism
reacts indiscriminately
to anyone who approaches.
[CLARION]
You're up, Nene.
I got you.
[NENE]
Have no fear! I'm here!
[NENE yells]
With no rehearsal, she knocks
it right out of the park.
Nene sure is something else.
Hey! Why are you not done
digging out the lab yet?
[MAID OUTFIT]
I just now finished it!
[UZAL]
Well... So far, so good.
[NENE]
Ah!
She's amazing!
[UZAL]
Clarion! You're there!
We're all set! Good job, Nene!
[NENE sighs]
Thank you!
[UZAL] There's an emergency
terminal near the very top.
All you need to do
is activate that,
and it'll accept external input.
Okay...
[CLARION] This is the
main console? Weird...
[BUNNY]
What... is... that thing?
That's certainly
a rude question.
To be honest, I don't have time
to explain the details to you.
Clarion.
Hurry up and use
the key, please!
Use the key?
So I put these... on there?
[NENE gasps]
[NENE]
Look out!
Ha! Cla-ring!
[UZAL gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[NENE panting]
[UZAL]
Nene! Nene!
[NENE] She gave me good luck
so I'd always be safe.
[NENE] And I gave my
good luck to Cla-ring,
so she has to be okay.
Direct hit!
Save us!
[UZAL]
Oh boy.
Here comes the cavalry.
Your robot better pull this off,
or we're dead meat!
Uzal? Uh... What is this?
[UZAL]
It's called a Gertsecomma.
It's something like
a pet for Clarion.
[NENE]
All right.
But... Cla-ring is...
[UZAL]
Relax, Clarion's fine.
[NENE]
Huh?
[UZAL] Who do you think
is operating that machine
you're riding?
[NENE]
Then... Where is she?
[UZAL]
Right there.
Oh, no, she's trapped!
I'm impressed Clarion
managed to send backup
in such a tough situation.
Of course, it didn't
hurt matters any
that I set Nene's protection
as her number one priority.
Wait!
Look! Nene!
[UZAL]
Uh oh!
She's within BUER's
defensive zone!
Gertsecommas! Help her now!
Nene shouldn't have
that kind of agility.
[UZAL]
Oh, I see.
She's not dodging
the attacks per se;
she's taking advantage
of her skill
by anticipating BUER's
fire-control system.
What kind of talent is this?
Is she an adepter
like I thought before?
Or is she something
entirely different?
[NENE]
I can't get any closer!
Interesting!
Nene.
[CLARION]
Get on.
[NENE]
Cla-ring!
Huh? Oh. Like this, right?
Oh! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
I've got to
get to Cla-ring fast!
Here I come!
[NENE]
Whoa!
Support.
[NENE yells]
[NENE]
Cla-ring!
Are you okay?
Hold on!
I'll get you outta there!
[CLARION]
Listen.
I'm stuck and I can't move.
Leave me behind
and go stop BUER.
Huh? I can't!
Incorrect.
[grunts]
I have complete
faith in you, Nene.
Go now!
Do this for World Peace!
Cla-ring! I'll do my best!
[laughing]
Well, what do you know?
Clarion's starting to
learn to manage Nene.
Still, it's a really
big deal for her
to set her pride aside and rely
on somebody besides herself.
All right! I'll be back!
[NENE] For Cla-ring,
and for world peace!
[NENE] Get ready, BUER.
Here I come!
[NENE]
First things first,
I need to put the
glasses on the statue.
I can't do it! It's broken!
Oh, don't worry!
I've made plans
for this situation.
Relax. I have options for you!
[UZAL] Put them on
whichever you'd like!
[NENE]
Right!
[BUNNY] Why in the world
are you making her
go through all of
these shenanigans?
[UZAL]
'Cause it's fun!
[NENE]
Okay. Here goes nothing!
It's over now. I think.
[GIRLS cheering]
Just when I think
I've seen it all,
that Nene surprises
me yet again.
I wish I could savor
this moment and enjoy it.
[UZAL] But this
is no time for that.
I suppose things did
get a little out of hand.
But that's the way it goes.
Emergency evacuation
sequence, initiate.
Ready? Fire!
[NENE gasps]
[UZAL] Nene! Retrieve
the authentication key!
[NENE]
Uh... Right!
[UZAL] Also, I'm about to detach
BUER's Central Nervous Unit.
Now that you have the key,
I'd like for you to
retrieve that as well.
[NENE]
Central Nervous?
[UZAL]
After you're done,
go get Clarion and withdraw
immediately, understood?
[NENE]
Yes!
[BUER]
Mine name is BUER!
Art thou the one to rescue me
from this everlasting nightmare?
Oh, well...
Uh, yeah. I guess. I'm Nene.
[BUER] Splendid!
I do commend thee, Nene!
Do you happen to know what
the Central Nervous Unit is?
[BUER]
'Tis I, of course!
Huzzah!
Ah! It's moving? Oh no!
It's not supposed to move now!
[BUER] 'Tis but a return
to default mode.
Please, make it stop!
You're gonna crush Cla-ring!
[BUER]
'Tis required, for a reboot.
[NENE]
You have to help me!
[BUER]
I am a philosopher of Hades,
endowed with five
legs of the goat,
the head of the lion,
and eternal knowledge
of the infinity
of time and space.
To do so would be easy enough!
If I'm to help thee, thou must
show me thine underwear.
[NENE]
Sure!
[BUER]
Oh, yeah!
[NENE]
Cla-ring!
Oh no... No!
Cla-ring... Where are you?
Don't worry. I'm coming!
[CLARION]
Nene.
[NENE]
I'm here.
[CLARION] I used the
Gertsecommas as cushioning,
but now I can't move.
I'm exactly twelve
meters up from you.
Nene. Thank you.
[UZAL]
Excellent work, you two!
[CLARION]
I can walk on my own.
[NENE]
No! You need my help.
Well... Nice job.
Unlike those idiotic
lame-os behind me.
[GIRLS growl]
[BUER] Idiotic lame-os,
and traitors to boot.
I know not what to do
with these rogues.
Who is this half lion
half goat freak show?
[UZAL] We're escaping,
so if you wanna live,
you better tag along,
you losers.
[BUNNY]
You're the loser, loser!
[UZAL laughs] Then I assume
you winners have at least
secured an escape route?
Oh, save us!
I'm not ready to die!
Yeah. Same here!
That way.
[GYM UNIFORM]
Ah! The water's coming in!
[SCHOOL UNIFORM]
This place is finished!
[BUNNY] It's breaking
through the walls!
[CHINA DRESS]
We're all gonna die in here!
[UZAL]
Oh, calm down.
Unlike you, I'm not a big loser.
So I made sure this emergency
elevator was available.
[BUNNY]
Hooray!
[CHINA DRESS]
We're not gonna die now!
--[BUNNY] Hey! Squeeze in!
--[CHINA DRESS] Ow!
[ALL whining]
--[ALL yell]
--[thud]
--[buzzing noise]
--[UZAL] Oh.
[UZAL]
Uh oh, that's no good.
Over the limit.
[ALL laugh]
You fat fatty! Ha!
Tons of fun!
You cow!
[UZAL]
Fine, whatever.
Have it your way. Go without me.
[ALL]
Huh?
Hey... Wait!
Hold on just a sec!
What gives, Sahar?
You're not the
self-sacrificing type!
What kind of game
are you trying to play?
Sahar!
[UZAL]
Nene.
[NENE]
Uzal!
I'll be all right,
so whatever you do,
don't worry about me.
I'm sorry for running
you so ragged today.
[NENE]
That's all right.
You didn't get
your World Peace,
but we'll try again
next time, okay?
[NENE]
Okay, Uzal.
[UZAL] Unfortunately, I'm
afraid I don't have any peace
that I can sell you right now.
But there's something
else I can give you.
Clarion?
Go with Nene, please.
[UZAL]
Nene.
Look after her for me, will you?
[NENE gasps]
I'll make her happy!
What is she talking about?
Thanks, Nene.
[UZAL] One day you'll find
the peace you're looking for.
I truly believe that.
[NENE]
Don't be sad.
Uzal said she
would be all right.
[BUNNY]
Of course she'll be all right!
She lives any way
she darn well pleases!
She's not just gonna up and die!
[CHINA DRESS] She wouldn't
die if you killed her.
Stupid jerk.
[elevator dings]
Are we at the surface now?
We're okay, aren't we?
I don't know, but we better
get outta here and fast!
[CHINA DRESS] We can worry
about the details later!
[NENE]
Uh... What?
Hey! When we use
the Pandora device,
does it make you
feel awkward, too?
No, I am not programmed
for that emotion.
So it doesn't embarrass
you when I leap into the air
and grab onto you like this?
No, but it does
make me annoyed.
[NENE]
Aren't you excited?
Now we can finally
go see Aunt Takumi!
[CLARION]
Who is that?
[NENE]
She's my aunt, of course!
And I bet she's
really cool, too!
I mean, I hope she is.
I've never met her before.
[CLARION] Expectations tend
to yield disappointment.