[NENE]
First, I took the eagle emblem.
Then I obtained the
silver key from the sewer.
And afterwards,
I moved the model tank.
There.
[BUER] Girl, art thou
done with thy work?
Yes, sir!
I arranged the paintings
in the break room
per your instructions!
[BUER]
Mm?
Huh?
Wow, this is like a video game!
[BUER]
'Tis adventurous!
[NENE]
Here goes!
Cla-ring.
[growls]
I'm coming for you!
[yells]
[BUER grunts]
[gasps]
[BUER] Why would the sight of a
hatch make thee want to open it?
[NENE]
It just does!
[whirring]
[rattles]
[BUER]
Here we are.
[NENE]
Cla-ring.
[AMERICAN SOLDIER 11A gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[AMERICAN SOLDIERS gasping]
[NENE whimpers]
[NENE]
BUER, snap out of it, will ya?
Which way should I go?
[AMERICAN SOLDIER 11A]
There she is! Come on!
[gasps]
It's all the stolen robots!
Oh my...
[door opens]
[NENE gasps]
[KURTZ]
Carry out any decoys we have.
[NENE gasps]
This one's operational?
Greetings!
I'm Hanako Dosukoi.
Welcome to Herme's, sir.
We offer service with a smile...
[SECURITY CHIEF]
Excuse me, Colonel.
[KURTZ]
What is it?
We received a report
of an intruder
inside the facility, sir.
[NENE] If you're hungry,
visit our food court.
[KURTZ]
Intruder?
[SECURITY CHIEF]
Yes!
It was a suspicious android
dressed in a schoolgirls'
uniform, sir.
May I go ahead and conduct
a thorough search?
[KURTZ]
There's no need.
It's under control.
But sir--
[NENE continues chattering]
[KURTZ]
Dispose of this one.
The soldiers spotted it.
Apparently, it was
wandering around.
Are you sure about this?
It looks like a high
quality android.
Just do it.
We cannot let our country
find out what we're up to,
which means we have to
exercise extreme caution.
I'm sorry for
questioning you, Colonel!
[KURTZ] There are many
fools in this world.
Far too many.
Those who are superior
must control them.
[KURTZ]
Yes... It is up to us.
--[screams]
--So have a nice day!
[BUNNY groaning]
Hold on. Where am I?
Are you all right?
Wait a second.
Have we met somewhere before?
--Yeah, It's me!
--Oh, right!
You're Bunny!
My name isn't Bunny, jerk!
[NENE] What are you doing
in a place like this?
[BUNNY] I got tossed
out with the garbage.
[sighs] I suppose this
is the end of the line.
And I have to spend my final
moments with a freakin' android.
Actually, I'm a human.
People make that
mistake all the time.
Full cyborg? Oh, wow.
[BUNNY] Everything's
mechanized but the braincase.
It's only worked a
few times, worldwide.
[gasps]
Hold on. That means you've
been cyberized, right?
I have!
[BUNNY] I tried creating
a make shift terminal
with the parts available here.
If we can use this set-up to
access the base's system...
We'll be able to get outta here.
Unfortunately,
it was a rush job.
Relax, things'll
work out for us.
Huh?
I'm going to reach Cla-ring,
no matter what obstacles
are in my way!
[BUNNY]
I have to succeed, too.
My friends need me.
Ah. Let's get started!
[NENE]
Okay!
[BUNNY]
All right.
You only have to do one thing:
Get into the base's system,
and once you're inside,
release the lock on the hatch.
[NENE]
Understood.
Here we go!
[BUNNY]
So, can you hear me?
[NENE]
Yes! Loud and clear!
But it's totally weird because
I can't see myself, not one bit!
[BUNNY]
Well, you're in cyberspace.
If you don't configure yourself,
you can't perceive anything.
There's an avatar
there I created.
Activate it now.
[NENE]
I'm sorry. I don't see it.
Come on!
Anything will do, so just
hurry up and find an avatar!
If you remain in
a flat state for too long,
then your mind is
totally going to collapse!
[NENE] Oh, okay.
I'm working on it, now!
[BUNNY]
Hey! Are you all right?
[NENE]
Yeah, I'm fine.
The thing is, I can't
see anything around me.
[BUNNY] Well, that's
pretty typical, actually.
Humans can't perceive
the flow of data, Nene.
But don't worry, I promise
everything'll be all right.
Whatever you do, just don't
go outside the terrarium,
you understand me?
Wait, why not?
[BUNNY] Because you'll
lose track of yourself
in the sea of information,
and you won't be
able to get back.
See the arrow that
just showed up?
That's your navigator.
Follow it, Nene!
[NENE]
Okay!
[BUNNY] It'll lead you to
the base's configdata.
--It's so cute!
--[BUNNY] What're you doing?!
That's a military
barrier program!
Do not touch it!
[NENE]
Wow! There are so many!
[BUNNY] They're wandering
around all over the place,
so be careful!
[NENE]
Hey, Bunny?
Can I maybe go a
different way or something?
[BUNNY] You have to follow
the navigation route.
What you're doing is
like wearing a diving suit
and moving through the
dark depths of the ocean.
Do not go anywhere outside
the navigation route
or you're toast, you got it?!
[NENE]
Yes, ma'am!
Can she actually do this...?
It's got me feeling
really anxious...
[alarm sounds]
Hell's lid is opening, Nene!
Hop! Hop! Hop!
This is kinda fun since
it's like a video game.
But I don't think
I'm making much progress.
[BUNNY]
Whatever you do,
just don't go outside the
terrarium, you understand me?
[NENE] I wonder if there's
a way I can take a shortcut.
Ah! No! Help! [sobs]
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
This is bad! We're gonna die!
Please! Hurry up!
[BUNNY]
She's stopped!
What the heck is she doing?
[NENE] I'm there,
but I don't understand.
Just like back then.
[TECHNICIAN]
Can you hear me?
I need you to forget how
you moved your original body.
Try to focus on the parts
you never had before.
[NENE]
I don't get it.
[TECHNICIAN] Well, like wagging
your tail, for example.
[NENE] I hear you,
but I don't understand.
[TECHNICIAN]
Or flapping your wings, perhaps?
[NENE] I think it's best if I
think back to the beginning...
Not this beginning, but the
beginning of all beginnings.
When I was a little baby.
You know, like the first
time you figure out
you can move your own body.
[NENE]
I did it!
[NENE] Like seeing or hearing
something for the first time.
[NENE]
Lots of sparkling things.
So near and yet, so far away.
What is this?
So much is visible all at once,
yet I understand it all.
[BUER] Hmm? I sense
the maiden's presence!
[NENE]
I can feel Cla-ring...
Wait for me!
I'll come see you soon!
Even if she truly doesn't want
me to be worried about her,
if Cla-ring is in trouble,
then I want to share
in her troubles with her!
After all, she's the first
friend like me I've met
in the entire world!
[BUNNY]
We're gonna die!
I'm sorry, my friends!
I have failed you all...
[NENE]
Oh, that's right!
Wow! It reset!
She did it!
You got there in time!
You kick some
serious butt, Nene!
[BUNNY]
Hooray! Hooray!
[laughs]
[BUNNY]
Are you awake now?
[NENE]
Yes.
The emergency hatch opened, too.
Let's get out of here.
[NENE]
Oh, Bunny!
Didn't you hear what
I said earlier, Nene?
My name's not Bunny!
Oh, well. Not that
it really matters.
I'm super impressed with you.
I've never seen a terrarium as
incredible as that one before!
[BUNNY]
Huh? For real?
Well, you know, I do happen to
be one of the best engineers
on Cenancle Island!
Hands down!
[NENE]
Come on, Bunny. Let's go!
Or maybe I'm lucky.
Even I'm surprised
I pulled it off
using that big pile of garbage.
Hmm?
[BUNNY]
The cord's broken?
Then it was never even
connected to the network?
But if that's true, how did
she perceive the terrarium
and her avatar correctly?
That doesn't make sense.
How was she able to operate
the base's system?
Well, if we're going,
we better move now!
[BUNNY]
This girl...
What the heck is she anyway?
Hi. To all my loyal
and amazing fans,
I'm so sorry to have kept
you waiting like this!
What you're currently
looking at is a
super-duper-top-secrret facility
right underneath your feet,
just beneath the
harbor district!
They told you it was
a bedrock collapse.
But the real cause of the most
recent incident of terrorism
appears to stem from an ongoing
conspiracy somehow connected to
this dubious underground
lair in which I'm standing!
You have my word-- I will not
stop till the truth is out!
Coming to you live from
the depths of the island,
it's the world's most trusted
reporter, the one and only--
[yelps]
[CAMERA PERSON] Camera and audio
support have officially arrived!
[MIC PERSON]
I'm so sorry we're late.
[NENE]
Cla-ring, Here I come!
[yells] Awaken, you hidden
power that sleeps within me
yearning to be unleashed! Ahh...
Nene, let's use the door.
[laughs nervously]
I gotta go rescue all my friends
from their impending doom.
This is where we part.
[NENE]
Okay!
And I'm going to
go find Cla-ring!
Wait! Hold on!
[BUNNY]
Here.
[NENE]
Hey, that's Cla-ring's!
[BUNNY]
Yeah. I was looking after it.
I'll give it back
as soon as I find her.
[BUNNY]
Please do.
[NENE]
Thanks!
[BUNNY]
How do I tell her?
Can I tell her?
She gave up her
life to save mine.
She's already dead!
[BUNNY gasps]
Power transmission
system, all green!
Tactical diversion line!
Trending normal!
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
No changes currently detected
in BUER's behavior, Colonel.
[SUBORDINATE 9C]
Second barrier, penetrated.
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
Analyzing third barrier.
Two percent. Three percent!
EMP is confirmed!
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
Analysis: Units 22 and 25
are now unusable, sir!
[KURTZ] Don't use a debugger,
but overwrite the entire system.
Connect number 11 and
number 37 up to the bypass.
Deal with it that way.
BUER is stable, sir!
[gasps]
Keep going, men. Proceed
according to the timetable.
[SUBORDINATES]
Yes, sir!
If successful, this
operation will break through
all the protections!
And I will finally obtain BUER!
[TAKUMI]
A network disturbance...
Normally, this is where
I'd no longer be able
to interfere from
the outside, yeah.
But, I anticipated this outcome!
[TAKUMI] I set up a
direct connection, yeah!
Bring about great strength!
Bring about super power!
O hear me, you savage gods.
O three divine pillars
who created the land.
In accordance with the divine
laws of Heaven and Earth,
keeping time with
the open world,
let this come to be
without incident,
without any manner of
misfortune or adversity.
Now! I challenge you, Uzal!
[BUER grunts]
[SUBORDINATE 9C] The rate of
analysis is rising sharply, sir!
[SUBORDINATE 11B]
Barrier depth at 46%... 56%!
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
Third barrier, penetrated!
What's going on here?
Even if a genius did build it,
when confronted with our
considerable resources,
there's no way it's
not going to tire.
[BUER] Alas! At this rate,
my main body shall fail!
[BUER]
Fire! On!
[SUBORDINATE 9B] BUER's barrier
strength is recovering, sir!
Not bad, yeah.
Just what I'd expect from Uzal!
[SUBORDINATE 9B gasps]
[BUER]
What nerve!
[SUBORDINATE 9B] Sir! Successful
purge of BUER's barriers!
[SUBORDINATE 9C]
Colonel! BUER is reconstructing
its barrier method and deploying
multiple false entries!
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
Barrier method analyzed!
They're being vaccinated!
Trojans are deploying!
[SUBORDINATE 9C] Barrier code
switching to mob rule, sir!
Analysis has become
far more difficult!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
--Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
--[BUER groans]
[BUER] 'Tis getting
me nowhere and fast!
In that case, target
the meddler's pawns!
I shall blow every last one of
them off the face of the Earth!
[SUBORDINATE 9B] Detecting a
heat source alteration inside!
[SUBORDINATE 11B]
It's the particle cannon!
I won't let you!
KOM drive! Activate! Now!
Amenotorifune, full throttle!
I'll crush Uzal's BUER
if it's the last thing I do!
[BUER yells]
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
Aiming cancelled, Colonel.
[SUBORDINATE 11B] Stoppage of
firing sequence, confirmed, sir!
[SUBORDINATES gasping]
[BUER groans]
Nicely done...
[SUBORDINATE 9B]
Fourth barrier, penetrated!
[SUBORDINATE 11B]
Approximately one hour
until BUER is completely
under our control, Colonel!
It appears the plan will be
carried out without disruption.
Soon, we'll be in control
of the whole world
and no one can stop us.
The future is ours, gentlemen!
Hey, Cla-ring. Where are you?
It's me, Nene!
Colonel Kurtz, I am detecting
an intruder near BUER.
Let me see it on the monitor.
It's me, Cla-ring.
Where are you?
[KURTZ]
That's the one from earlier.
Time to find out
what's going on here.
Greetings, successor
of Sahar Schehera.
So, we meet again.
[NENE]
You're huge!
[KURTZ] You and the
cat-eared combat robot
wouldn't make me
think twice, normally.
But then, with Sahar,
appearances can be deceiving.
Cat ears? Do you know
where Cla-ring is, Mister?
Unfortunately, you're a
bit too late, my dear.
Sorry to disappoint.
BUER is already
in my possession.
Do you know what makes
BUER so valuable?
Its particle cannon!
A super-weapon that
surpasses nukes,
it can attack entire cities
without risk of
treaty violation.
The world is a
rotten place, indeed.
Impoverished nations
prey upon the weak.
It leads to nothing but
disorder and chaos.
I detest that more
than anything else.
Arrogance, envy, wrath,
depravity, greed,
gluttony, lust...
The fundamental
seeds of conflict
will never go away
while these thrive.
That is the great
weakness of mankind.
This is why the world
needs a single controller,
someone to rule over it all!
A group with supreme
military strength
to strangle this
growing depravity.
Order is the ideal beauty!
Poseidon is that entity.
And we will establish peace!
[NENE]
Huh?
[KURTZ] Stand with me, Sahar's
successor, and come to our side.
You have my word,
I'll use your technology
for the sake of World Peace.
We will rule the foolish masses
with true order born
out of pure fear.
You don't have to do something
scary like that, Mister.
That right?
[NENE]
After all, you can always just
purchase world peace
with money, right?
[chuckles]
[NENE] By the way, about
my good friend Cla-ring...
She's a cute little girl in a
dress with cat ears and--
Are you making fun of
me right now, droid?!
--Don't you realize fools
--[whimpers]
--like you who have no ideals
--and covet peace with money
--Ah, no. Sir, please, don't...
--are plunging the world further
--into chaos and disorder?!
--Ah, no. Sir, please, don't...
Yeah, but... Cla-ring!
I've had enough.
You're a waste of time.
You can send in all
the puppets you like,
but it won't matter in the end.
[gasps]
Wait a second.
That's Cla-ring's.
[KURTZ]
She fought hard,
but when it was over,
that's all that remained.
Please, take it.
[KURTZ] I can certainly
promise you this much.
You're going to
regret insulting me.
[KURTZ]
Goodbye.
[NENE whimpers]
[NENE gasps]
Nene. Are you all right?
Insane...
That was a direct hit
and it didn't even
--leave a single scratch?!
--Cla-ring!
--And somehow, the cat-eared bot
--We're together again!
--managed to revive itself
--Oh, thank goodness
--and evade our system.
--you're still alive, Cla-ring!
--I underestimated Sahar
--Nene, what are you doing here?
--yet again.
I'm here so I can
rescue you from danger!
Cla-ring. Cla-ring!
We should go now. And quickly.
It's not safe. You ready?
No, I can't leave yet.
What?
Tell me you're joking, Cla-ring.
Come on, we should go to
the hospital right away.
Sorry, I can't leave.
Incidents have been
occurring on the island
because there are
people going after BUER.
If Clarion does not stop
this once and for all,
Cenancle Island
will never be safe.
Oh, so that's it then.
In that case, I'll help you!
I cannot get you involved--
You know what?
I know I haven't lived
on this island for long,
but it feels like home to me.
[NENE]
I've met all sorts of people.
And I've made lots
of fun memories.
Every moment has been so
much more fun and rewarding
than when I was on
the hospital ward.
I like this island so much.
And I absolutely adore
everyone on it!
[gasps]
That's why I have to
protect it, Cla-ring!
Please, just let me help!
To be completely honest.
When I first saw that
note you left for me,
I was a little bit
shocked to say the least.
We were together all the time,
but you know,
I'm me, and you're you.
We're not the same being.
We're separate, and we
think different things,
and that's okay.
I want us to be
together. So badly.
Me, too. But see--
Yeah, I understand.
You're just concerned
for my well-being.
You did everything
you could by yourself
so I wouldn't get involved.
I'm so sorry I wasn't
able to see it, Cla-ring.
But this time, it's
my turn to help out.
I want to do my best for
your sake, all right?
Nene...
[NENE] To me, you're
the most special person
in the whole world.
[NENE]
You know what?
I just want you to
discover something
that really matters to you.
Something that matters.
[NENE]
Hm? What's that?
Oh, never mind.
--[KURTZ] Sahar's successor.
--All right.
It would be a shame to lose
your technical prowess.
But so be it.
Let's fight. Now.
Yeah!
[NENE]
If you and I are together,
then nothing can
stand in our way!
Nene, I have complete
faith in you.
[NENE]
Pandora Device...
...open!
--[SUBORDINATES gasping]
--She transformed.
But how?
So, you wanna make
a fool out of me?
With this vile and
deplorable behavior?
Forgive my lack of manners.
I've yet to introduce
my creation.
His name is Fear.
If you're wondering why
I chose that particular moniker,
allow me to give you
a proper demonstration.
Seize them, Fear.
Oh, Cla-ring. Are you hurt?
Were you scared?
[CLARION] It doesn't hurt,
and I'm not scared.
I will stop BUER and
protect you. End of story.
You are so strong!
I'll help you stop the bad guys.
Let's fight them together!
[CLARION]
All right.
[CLARION] We'll eliminate
the obstacles in our path
and stop BUER.
[NENE]
For the sake of peace, right?
[CLARION]
Right.
[NENE]
Let's go!
If you and I stick together,
we can do anything we want!
[CLARION] Nene, I have
complete faith in you.