[TA] In order to negate
the world's current destiny,
the Power of Order
will awaken and destroy
the Black Beast's
preliminary form.
[RACHEL] Thus proving
that she, the Master Unit,
desires something beyond
this bland repetition.
[TB] Perhaps. But the future
we desire is quite different.
We would see a world
of tranquility.
We will appraise this Continuum
Shift, altering it as needed,
until a perfect
world is birthed.
One immune to the
vagaries of chance.
[RACHEL] Speaking of immunity,
Yuuki Terumi has already
shrugged off your
threadbare leash, has he not?
[TC] Yuuki Terumi's
actions have all fallen
within the
expected parameters.
Any interference stemming from
the use of the Sealed Armagus
Isayoi will be dealt with as
a part of the Continuum Shift.
[TB] At this point, I believe
you, Rachel Alucard,
inspire more apprehension
than does he.
[TA] Do you intend to shirk
your duty as a spectator
and interfere yet again?
[RACHEL]
You wound me.
I am the rightful heir
to the Tsukuyomi.
Defending the Master Unit
is my raison d'être.
To say nothing of the fact
that the world you desire...
...seems so dull.
[RAGNA grunts]
Too slow.
[JIN] Finally, the truth has
made itself known to me.
Oh, yeah?
[JIN] All the evil
in this world...
You are the festering
root of it all, Brother.
Bastard! What the
hell're you on ab--?
[RAGNA groans]
[JIN]
You are chaos personified.
You spew out corruption onto the
Earth with your every breath.
But don't let it
worry you, Brother.
No one in this world is
going to lay a finger on you.
For the simple reason
that... you die here!
[RAGNA roars]
[RAGNA]
You bastard!
[JIN]
Aw! What's wrong, Brother?
You can fight much better
than that, can't you?
[RAGNA] You're
pissing me off, Jin!
[JIN]
No Shadow, No Echo.
Judgment.
Snowstorm!
[RAGNA screams]
[JIN laughs]
You're so weak, Brother!
The fun's going to be
over far too soon!
If I kick your ass,
will you shut up already?
[JIN laughs]
[MAKOTO]
It's Tager.
He's the one we were
gonna meet with?
[HAZAMA] You're a
peach, Lieutenant.
You brought her right to me.
Hunting her down across the
whole city would have been
a real pain in the ass. You get
a gold star. Now, run along.
[NOEL] What?
Keep your damn star.
I didn't bring her here for you.
Such a sassy Beastkin.
Here I thought you were
being a good little soldier
and doing me a solid.
After all, this whole
Continuum Shift was prepared
for Noel Vermillion. I can't
start the party without her!
Huh? What do you mean?
[HAZAMA] C'mon! Do I have
to explain everything?
Long story short--
it's been a lot of work.
But it's about to pay off.
I think it's time
that we yank the support
characters off the stage.
Starting with good
ol' Tsubaki Yayoi!
[NOEL gasps]
What did you do to her?
[HAZAMA] I don't appreciate
your tone, Lieutenant.
Don't forget, I am still
your superior officer.
[MAKOTO] You, my superior?
Don't make me laugh!
[HAZAMA]
Oh, it's like that, huh?
Y'know, I heard you refer
to this oversized schmuck
from Sector Seven by name.
I wonder! Has Lieutenant
Makoto been in contact
with known enemies
of the N.O.L.?
Oh, the humanity!
It brings a tear to my eye
just entertaining
the possibility!
We gotta split up
and run for it, okay?
We're splitting up?
Make a break for the left.
I'll cut to the right.
And I'll bring up the rear.
[MAKOTO] Wha--?
Makoto!
Bolverk! Come forth!
[HAZAMA] Woo-hoo!
Can you stand?
Go, before it's too late.
[NOEL gasps]
I got this.
I'm not leaving you!
Either we get out
of this together
or we don't get out at all!
Tsubaki needs both our help!
Good call, Noellers.
That's a lot to do by yourself.
[NOEL] Yeah!
If you're looking for a fight...
This is your lucky day!
Oh, no. How am I ever going
to survive two against one?
[TAGER groans]
My self-repairs
aren't done yet.
[KOKONOE] Don't try
anything stupid.
[TAGER] The situation's
escalating over here.
Yeah. That's why I'm rerouting
all your remaining energy
into getting the transfer
system back online.
[TAGER] Wait, what about
evac-ing these two?
Getting Lambda out
there is more important.
[TAGER]
Yes, but...
[KOKONOE] Look, I don't have
time to argue about this, Tager.
Wait, Kokonoe--!
Yeah, I know.
[MAKOTO grunts]
[MAKOTO]
Hah! Hah! Yah!
[HAZAMA]
Oh-ho-ho, c'mon!
Too slow!
[MAKOTO yells]
[NOEL]
Take that!
[HAZAMA]
Uh--!
[MAKOTO yells]
[HAZAMA]
Ya got me...
[MAKOTO]
Huh?
[NOEL]
What's that?
Ouroboros, bitch!
Ah!
[HAZAMA] Who said
you could touch me,
you mangy little half-breed?
[HAZAMA] I know you
wanna play, Twelve,
but we've got a busy day later.
You should take a nap.
[HAZAMA] Your turn.
Somebody thinks
they're a bad-ass, huh?
I could stomp your
head in right now,
but where's the fun in that?
Damn it!
What the hell?
How does Terumi keep
knowing when to strike?
Guess I'd better
assume that bastard's
got his eyes on us
all the time, more or less.
But even a snake has to blink.
I'll wait for his
focus to shift.
Question is, what's gonna
command that freak's attention?
[KOKONOE] This has Ragna the
Bloodedge written all over it.
[MAKOTO screams]
You don't look like
you're having any fun!
You gonna die?
Is that all you're good for?
Makoto...
[laughs]
Huh?
[HAZAMA] Look who
decided to join us!
[NOEL] Makoto!
Not another inch!
One more step and she's
got a date with gravity.
Man, if she falls
all the way down,
you can bet your ass
she's gonna be roadkill.
[NOEL]
Let her go this instant!
Do you want her to fall?
You need to think before
you open your mouth.
Strike one!
[MAKOTO wails]
Makoto!
[HAZAMA] Y'know, I betcha
beating her to a pulp
would have its charms, too!
[HAZAMA snickers]
Put her down!
[HAZAMA]
Shut your mouth, puppet!
I don't know where you get off
thinking you can boss me around!
[MAKOTO yells]
Stop squeezing her!
She's gonna die!
You don't listen!
If you tell me what to do
one more time, I'm going to
pulp her like an orange!
I'm so sorry, Captain Hazama.
Please don't hurt her.
I'm begging you.
"Don't hurt her"?
Do you have any idea
whose fault all of
this is? Answer me!
Whose fault it is?
Noel, he lies.
[HAZAMA]
Shut up, you!
[MAKOTO screams]
[NOEL gasps]
Well, gosh. Did I pet
the squirrel too hard?
[HAZAMA laughs]
That's Beastkin for ya!
A human would've had the
good sense to die by now!
[NOEL] Please, just...
just stop already.
Give it a rest. How could
you not know the score?
It's friggin' obvious who's to
blame for your friend's pain.
Obvious how?
It's you, all right?
You, Noel Vermillion!
You screwed the pooch for
everyone just by existing!
It was me?
[HAZAMA]
That's right.
Everything you touch
turns to crap, Lieutenant!
You wanna know why?
It's because you
shouldn't even be here!
Your existence ruins everything!
[NOEL]
I shouldn't be here?
Correct! If you hadn't been
there to steal her spot,
poor Tsubaki wouldn't
have turned into
a walking poster for
the Zero-Squadron!
You're such a good
friend! Way to go!
[NOEL gasps]
That girl, she never
had a chance.
Her life was gonna suck
either way, don't get me wrong,
but you sure as hell
didn't help any!
Don't talk that way
about Tsubaki!
Are you allergic to
the truth or something?
She's a cipher.
Nothing special about her.
But she could've had a little
bit of happiness in her life.
Too bad her bestie kicked
that plan in the nuts!
[NOEL]
That's not--!
Ha! Take a look at how
things should've been!
[HAZAMA] Look upon the truth
and despair, you mistake!
[NOEL] Nooo!
You saw, right?
You totally saw it!
You got a ringside seat to the
world as it should've been!
[HAZAMA] One without
any trace of you!
No. You're wrong.
I'm not a mistake.
[HAZAMA] No more BS, okay?
I'm just gonna say it!
The Azure Successor and the
Calamity Trigger are you!
You effed it up!
[gasps] I...!
[HAZAMA]
And now you know.
I think it's time we wrap
up the chit-chat, girls.
You still alive up there?
[MAKOTO shudders]
[HAZAMA] Let's put you
out of your misery.
[NOEL] Huh...?
Makoto... Makoto!
[NOEL gasps]
[HAZAMA]
Don't look so sad.
She probably hasn't
even hit the ground yet.
[NOEL]
You bastard...
You'll pay for
what you've done!
Look who finally grew a pair!
Feel that hate!
Let it crawl into your
heart and soul! Yes! Yes!
[NOEL]
You killed my friend!
I won't let you
get away with it!
Atta girl! Put one
right in my head!
Pull the Calamity Trigger!
[screams]
[NOEL] I'm gonna...
I'm gonna kill you!
Now! Quickly!
Tick-tock, Noel!
Pull the trigger already!
Do it, do it, do it!
[screams]
[NOEL] I hate you.
I hate you.
I hate you! I hate you,
hate you, hate you, hate you!
[HAZAMA cackles]
[HAZAMA] She finally disengaged
her freakin' Limiter! Yes!
Hate my guts!
Hate your own damn guts!
Hate the whole world! And
use that Eye! Use it to see
[HAZAMA] the world's despair!
Every beautiful bit of it!
I am a mistake.
The world is useless.
You are so right! It is!
When people look at you,
they see through the façade!
They fear the thing underneath!
[HAZAMA] What are you
gonna do, huh, Number 12?
Curl up and die?
Or unleash your all-encompassing
hatred upon them?
Come, Twelve! Join me!
Join me in the darkness!
[NOEL] This world...
I hate it.
With this, with this, I finally
have control over everything!
[laughs]
What is it?
[RAGNA] I'm gonna have to
kick your ass later, Jin!
[JIN] Damn it!
You again.
[JUBEI]
Jin, don't follow him!
Out of my way,
old one. Now.
Just get to that underground
Cauldron, y'hear?
You won't have to wait for long.
[JIN]
To the Cauldron, huh?
[JUBEI]
That's right!
[JIN]
Why should I obey you?
[JUBEI] If you're
really itchin' to finish
your fight with Ragna,
you'll do it.
What awaits me?
[JUBEI]
Y'got feet, kid.
It's up to the young folk now.
Change the world.
Look who showed up.
I thought you'd keep
me waiting for a while!
[RAGNA] Terumi! Where's Noel?
Tell me, dammit!
[HAZAMA "Noel"? Well, if you
mean Noel Vermillion...
Direct your eyes
to the center ring!
This sensation...
Son-of-a...!
[HAZAMA] Ooh! That was
pretty quick on the uptake!
Y'know, for you.
[RAGNA]
That's a Cauldron.
[HAZAMA]
No effin' duh!
Don't tell me
you're going t--!
Well, of course I did!
What the hell else was
I gonna do with her?
Terumi! You bastard!
[RAGNA grunts]
Stop the smelting
right now, dammit!
Can't we discuss this
like grown-ass men?
That's enough!
Just hang in there, Noel!
I'll get you out
as fast as I can!
Oh, no! Not the
fearsome Azure Grimoire!
Take me away, Ragna!
I give up!
Restriction 666 released!
Dimensional Interference Field
deployed! Blah, blah, blah!
[RAGNA and HAZAMA]
BlazBlue... activate!
What the hell? It stopped!
That's impossible!
[RACHEL] Hail the
conquering hero,
trussed up like a fowl
for the holiday feast.
[HAKUMEN] Hm?
[RACHEL] Not the most elegant
oubliette I've ever seen.
[HAKUMEN] Why have
you come here?
[RACHEL] Terumi has
taken Noel Vermillion.
[HAKUMEN] Hm...
[RACHEL] Meaning, Mr. Hero,
that your cue to
enter has sounded.
[HAKUMEN]
Once freed from this prison,
you know I will strike down
the Azure Successor.
Acceptable.
[HAKUMEN] You mean
to repeat the cycle.
I'd rather not.
However, the loss of the
Master Unit is not an option.
[HAKUMEN] In that case,
I will play my part.
Though doing your bidding
vexes me to no end.
You scoundrel. I am a fair sight
nicer to you than Kokonoe.
[HAKUMEN]
Hm. It doesn't matter.
This restraint circle is more
than even you can handle.
Is that so?
Multiple levels of
punitive restraints.
Nowhere near what I would
consider foolproof.
[HAKUMEN]
I will not thank you.
Nor would I accept it.
Now, then...
[BOTH] Mm?
Princess, are you all right?
Of course I am.
[RACHEL] Kokonoe. Dismantling
your barrier was no easy task!
[gasps]
[NAGO] Huh?
[RACHEL and NAGO struggle]
[RACHEL]
What's this... power?
[IMPERATOR]
You struggle in vain.
Your bonds are magical.
Magical?
[RACHEL] Don't tell
me you're...!
[IMPERATOR] I grow rather weary
of your tiny rebellions.
[RACHEL] You're in no position
to judge me, Imperator!
Huh! Spectators belong
in the audience,
not taking to the stage to
steer the plot as they will.
Forthwith, I shall lower
the curtain upon this farce.
My power. How are
you blocking it?
Wanna know?
Do you really?
I'd hold onto my ass
if I were you, Rags!
Feel good about
your odds right now?
[TRINITY] Fight, and you
will surely perish.
[RACHEL] Right now, this is a
fight you cannot hope to win.
Don't tell me...!
[HAZAMA] You should see the
look on your face, Ragna!
It's priceless!
It's like you're a kid again!
[RAGNA gasps]
Get ready, 'cause
here's a spoiler!
[HAZAMA] The one who created
the BlazBlue is yours truly.
[RAGNA gasps]
[IMPERATOR] Hazama,
please create the BlazBlue
for my entertainment.
[HAZAMA]
Like, right now?
[IMPERATOR] Episode 11,
"The Murakumo Awakens."
Are you done yet?
[HAZAMA] No!