[NOEL] "Mr. Kitten,
Mr. Kitten.
Napping in the sun.
When the nap is over.
Time for fun!"
Mmm.
That last line's
a little short.
[NOEL] Oh, no!
My poem! Come back!
[JIN] Huh?
Jin Kisaragi!
I didn't see you there!
This paper. Is it yours?
[NOEL] Y-Yes.
Thanks for grabbing it.
My name's Noel. It's such
a pleasure to meet you.
Noel? Ah!
The girl with the
unmatched ars
magus scores.
[NOEL] Mind if I
take that back now?
Sorry.
[NOEL]
"Mr. Kitten, Mr. Kitten,
napping in the sun,
when the nap is over,
time for fun?"
[NOEL] He didn't
read it, right?
I've never
been so embarrassed!
[NOEL] No!
[KOKONOE] You're a real
pain in the ass, Hakumen.
You know that?
I told you not
to get in my way,
but you didn't listen.
And for that,
you get the penalty box.
[HAKUMEN]
And I told you
that I am not
yours to command!
Wow. You shouldn't
be able to do that.
Maybe your Power of Order
is bending the rules for you.
Not that I give a crap.
That barrier I used is
self-repairing, buddy.
[HAKUMEN] You have
gone to great pains
to contain me, Grimalkin.
Tch. Much as I'd
love to toss your
self-righteous ass
back into the Boundary,
I still need your armor.
It is a Susanoo
Unit, after all.
[HAKUMEN] Huh.
There's no question
of your lineage, Beastkin.
You share your
mother's crude tongue.
Shut your hole.
[TA] It is good
of you to come.
[RACHEL] It has
been a long time.
Wouldn't you agree?
[TC] By your understanding
of time, it has been
19,792 hours, 41 minutes,
and 52 seconds.
[TB] For us, it's
been 283,875 hours,
18 minutes, and 24 seconds.
[TA] Why did you employ
the Tsukuyomi Unit?
[TB] Takemikazuchi would
have burned the city
and the irregularity
to ash, had you not acted.
[TC] By what logic
did you choose this?
It is enough
that I know.
[TB] Your refusal to
answer the query has been
duly acknowledged and logged.
You set Terumi free
from his prison
in the Boundary, did you not?
[TC] Yes.
[TA] The process
leading to the Day of Ruin
has already begun.
[RACHEL] If that is true,
you must long for
the world's destruction.
[TC] No.
[TA] We of the
Takamagahara only care
that the world
be in balance.
With the appearance
of the Azure Successor,
this reality veers
dangerously close
to a Continuum Shift event.
[TC] We will control
the event distortions
that are likely to
occur in the future
and target irregularities
for elimination.
Hm.
Fancy yourself
a god, then?
[TC] No.
[TA] The Takamagahara
was created by man.
As such, we cannot
ascend to divine status.
[TC] The Master Unit is subject
to the same limitations.
[TB] Both it, and the
distortions it ushers
into the world,
are unnecessary.
And you believe
Terumi will solve this?
Is he a cudgel you
can wield, I wonder?
[TB] The situation
is well in hand.
[TC] He poses
no discernable risk.
[TA] Should he chafe
against his leash,
we will reinitialize him.
[TB] You are a singular
being, Rachel Alucard.
Have you any interest
in returning to us?
My answer isn't
obvious to you?
[TA] We have delved past
the rhetorical nature
of your reply,
and discern that you
have no intention of returning.
[TB] That choice is illogical.
You observe the
grand sum of existence,
but you see nothing at all.
Ah! Son of a--!
[FLUFFY-KAKA]
We should play with him!
[CALI-KAKA] But Big
Sis Tao will scold us.
Good Guy! Time to eat!
[RAGNA] You don't
really think I'm gonna
eat this swill, do ya?
[TAOKAKA] Kaka cooking
is filled with the finest
ingredients we were
able to pounce on!
You're gonna
love it, Good Guy!
It's meow-tta sight!
Don't put that
in my mouth!
What the hell's
wrong with you?
Hey, y'know, that's
pretty damn good!
[NOEL sighs]
[MAKOTO] Shoulders
back, Lieutenant!
Ah! Ma'am! My apologies!
I was thinking
about something!
I didn't mean to
slouch on the bar!
Man. I got you
good, huh! Ta-da!
[MAKOTO] Great friend,
killer curves.
C'mon, Noellers! It's me!
M-Makoto?
[NOEL] Makoto!
I've missed you so much!
Look at this tail!
I should have known it
was you from the start!
[MAKOTO] I am more than
a big, fluffy backside!
[MAKOTO] Sounds like
you got yourself into
quite a pickle, Noellers.
Mhm. And I have no idea
what I'm supposed
to do next.
I'm really glad
you found me, Makoto.
I meant to ask you.
Where were you when
that stuff was happening?
Huh?
Y'know today!
When everything shook,
and the sky was all bright!
Oh. I didn't know...
the sky part.
[MAKOTO] So you missed it?
Oh, yeah. I was
down on a lower level.
Everybody in town's
freaked out about it.
Especially on
the top level,
where you could
actually see it happen.
They're saying that it
might've been Takemikazuchi!
Takemikazuchi?
It's a Nox Nyctores
they used back
in the Dark War.
But it was too strong,
so they locked
it away somewhere.
Wait, weren't you
the one who told me
all this back in the day?
It was probably Tsubaki
who told you about it.
I think we were
studying for our
first test of
the school year.
[MAKOTO] Okay, self.
"In order for mankind to
fight the Black Beast,
it fused magic with science,
creating what we now
know as 'ars magus.'"
[NOEL] You wrote a
paper on ars magus,
right, Tsubaki?
Uh-huh. I did it
in my spare time.
Help me, Noellers.
What's this Takemika-blah-blah
they're talking about?
[NOEL] Well, it's...
It's the most
famous Nox Nyctores.
They made it to use against the
Black Beast in the Dark War.
[TSUBAKI] But it was too
powerful to keep around,
so they sealed
it away afterwards.
An', the Black Beast
is the whole reason
those Nox Nyctores things
were made in the first place?
That's right. The Great
Mage Nine made them.
She was one of the Six Heroes
who won the war for humanity.
[TSUBAKI] Wielding these
weapons, they were able
to defeat the Black Beast.
Don't look so confused,
even grade-schoolers
know that.
Not all of us can be
brainiacs like you, okay?
I got let into
the Military Academy
'cause I'm good at sports.
All the more
reason for you to
buckle down when
we study together.
Yeah, yeah.
The three of us sure
spent a lot of time
in that library, didn't we?
Mhm.
Do you remember?
There was that one time,
when the Major showed up?
Hey, Noellers!
I heard you requested
a clerical post.
Huh?
Uh, yeah.
But you're so crazy-good
with ars magus.
I just thought that...
[footsteps]
[FEMALE] It's the
student council president!
Jin, it's you!
Hey, Tsubaki.
You been studying hard?
Uh-huh. With my
roommates here.
Hmmm.
Uh, Jin?
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
You're sure that
nothing's wrong, then?
Promise. Guess I'll
see you later, Tsubaki.
[TSUBAKI] Sure.
Something is
definitely up.
Maybe it's your
heart-rate every time
Kisaragi walks by.
[TSUBAKI] What?
Too late to deny it!
Right, Noellers?
Huh? I had no idea!
No! He's just a
friend of the family!
[NOEL]
Those were good times.
I wonder what
she's up to now?
[MAKOTO] Mmm.
[NOEL] What's wrong?
She's probably
on her way to
Kagutsuchi as we speak.
Really?
[MAKOTO] Yeah.
But if you want a happy
reunion, think again.
I'm gonna tell
you something
that's super top-secret,
even in the
Intelligence Department.
But you deserve
to know about it.
It's Kisaragi. He snuck
out of the hospital.
There's no sign of him.
[gasps]
But why'd he go? His
wounds looked really bad!
No way of knowing.
The brass thinks he
might've gone to the enemy.
He would never.
[NOEL] Something
about Ragna.
More crappy news
where that came from.
Hey, Noellers,
you never heard
where Tsubaki
got posted to, huh?
The Zero Squadron.
♪
[MAKOTO]
The Wings of Judgment.
You mean,
the enforcement unit?
Yeah, and she's on
a mission to track down
the Major and you,
[MAKOTO]
and kill you both.
[gasps]
[HAZAMA] Jin Kisaragi
and Noel Vermillion
need to be found,
and, well, assassinated.
Apparently, they're both
on the lam in Kagutsuchi.
[TSUBAKI] Uh, sir, what did
they do to merit assassination?
[HAZAMA] It's an
Imperial Command.
Or does the will
of the Imperator
mean nothing to you?
[TSUBAKI] No, sir.
Very good!
I'll tell you why, though,
so those pesky doubts don't
pop up during the mission.
[HAZAMA] It's all the fault
of Ragna the Bloodedge.
What did he do?
[HAZAMA] Major Kisaragi
and Lieutenant Vermillion
were in contact with him.
Now they've gone rogue,
and our branch office
there has gone dark.
You do the math.
All we know for sure,
Lieutenant, is that
they share some sort
of connection to Ragna.
But why?
Who can tell?
You're free to go,
Lieutenant.
Best of luck on your mission.
♪
[TSUBAKI]
Sealed Armagus Izayoi.
Never thought I'd use it.
Especially against them.
[gasps]
What am I doing?
[JIN laughing]
Wait, Brother.
I'm on my way.
I'll have my satisfaction.
[NAGO] He's seen
better days, Princess.
Even for a
hero such as he,
the burden may
be too severe.
You're gonna
help him, right?
Another player is about to
make their grand entrance.
[JUBEI] Long time, no see.
I've never met
you before, cat.
Don't be so familiar.
[JUBEI chuckles]
Course you haven't.
Folks call me Jubei.
[JIN] Jubei, huh?
So you fancy yourself
one of the Six Heroes, then?
[JUBEI] It doesn't much matter
what you call me, fella.
I'm here to
give you a message.
This world wants to be
steady more than anything.
Tilt things too far one way,
and something evens it out.
That something is
the Power of Order.
You speak in riddles.
[JUBEI] The worse the tilt,
the more it takes to fix it.
That much power
could bring about
the end of the world,
if a fella ain't careful.
Huh?
[JUBEI] The Power of Order
ain't good or evil, y'know.
Whoever's using it,
that's the key.
[JIN] Meaning?
[JUBEI] For now?
A whole lotta nothin'.
Listen, Jin. If the
day comes when you
find the grit to
square off against
what's inside you,
I'll be waiting!
[JUBEI] They
grow up so fast.
[NOEL] I-I need
to find the Major!
[MAKOTO] Any idea
where he could have gone?
[NOEL] He's after
Ragna the Bloodedge.
What? The
guy who's been
knocking down
our branches?
Mhm.
The Major was fine until
he got that
note about Ragna.
[MAKOTO] Aw, man!
I had him, too!
[NOEL] Why am
I such a dummy?
All I had to do
was stay by his side!
If only I'd waited, maybe
the Major would be okay!
If you really
wanna find Ragna,
try looking in
Kaka Village.
It's on the bottom
level of Kagutsuchi.
That far down?
[MAKOTO] If you should come
across Tsubaki out there,
call me right away.
I mean it, Noel.
Don't do anything foolish!
[NOEL] Makoto?
[MAKOTO] We'll talk
this out, the three of us,
and it'll be okay.
[NOEL] Yeah.
[LITCHI] Hm?
[NOEL breathing heavily]
[LITCHI] That uniform.
Ars magus! I feel it!
It's that way!
[LITCHI] You there! Stop!
[NOEL] Wait, what?
Who are you?
[LITCHI] Litchi Faye
Ling. I'm a doctor.
But, if you're a doctor,
why do you have a weapon?
What business does
the Praetorian Guard
have around here?
I'm just--I mean--
I'm looking for
someone, that's all!
He's got spiky white
hair and a red jacket!
I see.
I thought as much.
[NOEL] So you've
seen him then?
[LITCHI] Yes. And I'm
well-aware of the bounty
the N.O.L. has
placed on his head.
Ragna's under my care,
which means
I'll defend him to the end!
I don't wanna fight you!
I am a Praetorian Guard,
that is true,
but the reason
I'm looking for him
has nothing
to do with that!
[LITCHI] Tell me
about this reason.
It's because he saved
my life earlier today.
I just want to talk
to him for a bit.
But you're enemies.
Are we, though?
Officially, I guess
that's true, but it's like,
I know him from somewhere.
Trust me! It all
sounds crazy to me, too!
But if I don't see
Ragna the Bloodedge
my friends are gonna die!
[NOEL] I beg of you!
[RAGNA] No more food, dammit!
Good Guy's not
gonna get better if
he doesn't clean his bowl!
I'm full! What part
of that don't you get?
I ain't your
friggin' trashcan!
Tao? What are
you doing in here?
[TAOKAKA] Hey, Boobie Lady!
Tao thought you went
home for the night!
I fully intended to,
but then...
[RAGNA] The hell?
[NOEL] Hi again.
[NOEL] I was just
gonna leave you alone,
but then something came up!
Oh, goody.
Hold on!
Why's that uncovered?
[RAGNA] Uh.
Tao! Didn't I tell you
to keep an eye on him?
It's not Tao's fault!
Tao told him
not to do it,
but Good Guy took
the bandages off!
Your wounds are deep!
[LITCHI] It's going
to take time for them...
What the--?
[RAGNA] Uh. You were saying?
What the hell?
Quit staring.
It's creepin' me out.
[NOEL] Huh? No!
I wasn't staring!
Yeah! Sure you weren't!
[RACHEL] Hmm. I had
come to aid you, but...
it seems you are
doing quite well.
Who're you?
[TAOKAKA]
Me-ow! You smell good!
Oh, now you wanna help?
Wait, you're the...
girl from before.
Piling new scars
upon old. So pathetic.
And whose fault is
it that I got 'em, huh?
Ya left me in some
pint-sized vigilante's lap!
Tao likes it when her
house is super-exciting!
[FLUFFY-KAKA]
No fair, Big Sis Tao!
[CALI-KAKA] Yeah we
wanna play with him, too!
[FEISTY-KAKA] Playtime!
[SPOTTY-KAKA] Get him!
[RAGNA] What? Aw, son-of-a!
Ow! That hurts,
you little brats!
That's enough playtime
for tonight, kittens!
You seem to know a lot
about Ragna, little miss.
Why is that?
That's "Lady
Rachel" to you!
Yeah! She's a princess!
The object of your
searching all these
many years, has landed
in your very lap,
Litchi Faye Ling.
How'd you know that?
Who in the world
are you anyway?
I am merely an old
acquaintance of Kokonoe's.
I will leave the rest unsaid.
The Professor, huh?
Dammit. How'm I
supposed to heal
with everyone barging in?
C'mon! I can
see you staring!
Don't be mean.
I can't bandage you up
if I'm not even looking!
Whatever.
Just get it done!
[RAGNA groans]
Okay, okay. So, why'd you
have to see me again?
Major Jin Kisaragi.
What does he mean to you?
Aren't you nosy?
We're enemies.
That good enough for ya?
I know you
hate each other!
But there's more to it
than that. I can tell!
So you tell
me what's up.
Huh? How
would I know?
That's why
I'm asking you.
In case you forgot,
we ain't exactly on
the same team here.
[NOEL]
I just want to help.
You saw it, Noel.
[RAGNA] That Cauldron.
I'm gonna smash that
thing to pieces.
And, every last
branch of the N.O.L.
But most of all.
That bastard, Terumi.
That man. Terumi.
I know him as
Captain Hazama.
What has he done?
[RAGNA] What has he done?
Goddamn plenty!
An' none of it is
your friggin' business!
I don't get it.
You ain't running away?
No. Not this time.
[NOEL] I have a question
about Major Kisaragi, too.
And if I don't ask
while I have the chance,
I'm gonna regret it later.
[MALE NOL 4A] This dock is
off-limits to civilians!
Captain Hazama!
Colonel Relius!
[HAZAMA] Hmh.
Good save, young man.
The 13th Hierarchical
City of Kagutsuchi.
[HAZAMA] Indeed.
And now,
we wait for the rest
of the players
to stumble in.
[RAGNA] Hey! I'm not
a friggin' mummy!
[JIN] Wait for me, Brother.
'Cause I'll be there
to kill you soon enough!
[HAZAMA chuckles]
Despair, disappointment,
hatred, sorrow, heartbreak.
It's going to be an
all-you-can-eat buffet
of suffering,
and I'm going in hungry!
[laughs intensely]
[MAKOTO] You really
didn't know it was me
without my tail, Noellers?
[NOEL] I'm sorry,
Makoto! It was dark!
[TSUBAKI] Episode Five,
"The Pair of White Guns."
[NOEL] Hey! It's Tsubaki!
[MAKOTO] Noel!