[HAKUMEN] I am the white void.
I am the cold steel.
I am the just sword.
With blade in hand,
shall I reap the
sins of this world
and cleanse it in the
fires of destruction!
I am Hakumen!
The end has come!
Bring it, you son-of-a--!
♪
[HAKUMEN] What's wrong?
Your strength is
supposed to be unrivaled,
Ragna the Bloodedge.
Shut up, masked freak.
[RACHEL] It's ever the same.
It's your cue, Kokonoe.
[RAGNA] Damn it...
I haven't even scratched him.
What the hell?
[HAKUMEN] Before my blade your
powers are next to nothing.
I will end you, here and now,
and prevent a great calamity.
[HAKUMEN] Go, Dark One,
back to the
maelstrom of chaos!
[HAKUMEN]
Phenomenon intervention!
Damn you, Grimalkin!
[WOMAN] Tch.
Aw, quit your bitching.
Just, lemme haul
you in already.
Attaboy.
[HAKUMEN]
You will not interfere!
Wait, he can muscle
through an event disruption?
Son-of-a-bitch!
[WOMAN] You, with the hair!
Move your ass!
You have no chance
against this guy right now!
Who the hell are you?
I don't remember asking
for your opinion, lady!
[WOMAN] Get over it!
You need to run while
you still have legs!
[RAGNA] Running from
a fight ain't my style!
[HAKUMEN] Time to end this.
All right...
Bring it, freak!
[RAGNA bellows]
Restriction 666 released!
[RAGNA] Dimensional
Interference Field deployed!
BlazBlue activate!
Hope you're ready,
'cause I ain't
holdin' back anymore!
[HAZAMA] Looks like
the party's begun.
[JIN grimaces]
♪
[bellows]
[RACHEL] It's time...
Everything up until
now is known to me.
But beyond this...
[blast]
What's going on here?
[NOEL] I think I'm
getting closer, but--
I can't tell anymore.
This place...
Why does it...
[NOEL] look familiar?
What the--?
[HAKUMEN] Huh?
I've seen...
this room before.
[NOEL gasps]
[NOEL] Identifying.
Identifying. Identifying.
This is gonna be fun!
[RACHEL] We step beyond.
[yells]
Murakumo Unit
is now online.
Verifying new subject.
Subject identified
as identical.
[NU] State your name.
I am Boundary Interface
Prime Field Device.
Number 12.
State your name,
identical one.
[NOEL] You are an
Anti-Sankishin Core Unit.
[NU] Unit description.
Boundary Interface Prime
Field Device, Number 13.
Anti-Sankishin Core Unit.
Nu.
Your existence
is a paradox.
Recommendation: Self-destruct.
Negative, Nu.
Self-preservation prioritized.
Analyzing.
Twelve is an identical unit.
Proper course of
action... elimination.
[NU and NOEL] Confirmed.
[BOTH] Commencing
extermination of subject.
Bolverk! Come forth!
[NOEL whimpers]
[gasps]
[NOEL] What...
what's going on here?
This girl, why...
why am I fighting her?
It's like I'm
shooting out of reflex!
Continuing assault until
target is destroyed.
[NOEL] How is
she still standing?
No! Why won't
she go down?
Leave me alone!
[NU] Repair protocol
engaged. Arming petals.
[NOEL] Am... am I gonna die?
♪
[YOUNG RAGNA] Hey c'mere!
[YOUNG SAYA] Okay, brother.
♪
Finish her.
[shards falling to
the ground and clinking]
[NOEL] What?
But why?
[NOEL] Why? Why does
he seem so familiar?
[RAGNA] It's none
of your business
why I'm here, okay?
Now are you gonna get
your ass to safety or not?
[gasps]
[NU] Ragna.
[NU] Yay! It's Ragna!
You're so bad.
Leaving me all alone.
Last time
was Akitsu, right?
I don't give a damn.
[NU] Didja come to
kill me again, silly?
[RAGNA] Killing is for
people. You get broken.
Ragna... I love it
when you talk dirty.
[NU] Nu hates everyone,
y'know. But not you.
[NU] Uh!
You weren't much of
a gentleman last time,
stabbing Nu out of
the blue like that.
You just shoved
it right in!
Shut up.
Naughty boy.
You went to town on
Nu and you liked it.
[NU] Stabbing away at
defenseless little Nu that way.
Nu couldn't move,
or even speak.
She was completely
at your mercy.
Don't say that!
You were smiling.
[NU] Today's a whole
different story, Ragna.
See?
Nu can talk
this time around.
Her body's ready for you!
Oh, but maybe
you liked it better
when Nu was your plaything.
Shut your mouth,
you little freak!
[RAGNA] Talking like
that with her face.
It's disgusting!
Is it?
[NU] You act all grumpy,
but we're a lot alike.
You want to
destroy things, Ragna.
Nu, the world,
even yourself.
You want to smash
it all to pieces, huh?
Whaddya say?
We could, you know.
Just end the world
and be together forever.
[NU] You've been
so lonely, Ragna.
But those days would be over.
[RACHEL]
Her poisoned words are a
thorn that pierces your heart.
You're writhing in pain,
but every twitch
drives it deeper.
This agony is yours alone.
You've been set adrift
on the rapids of time.
Once again, the current hurries
you to a familiar doom.
[NU] Come here. Let's play.
[cries out]
[NOEL groans]
[giggles]
♪
[distant weapons clinking]
[RAGNA] Gauntlet!
[RAGNA] Hades!
[giggles]
What are you
waiting for, Ragna?
[RAGNA] What the hell?
Why do you look
at me with her face?
Damn you. Damn you!
[laughs]
[squelch]
[RAGNA groans]
You're insane.
[NU laughs]
Oh, Ragna!
Now we'll be
together. Always.
Thus, the bloody
denouement.
I practically know
it word-for-word now.
The actors are bound to
a plot that's e'er the same.
[NU] Oh, Ragna...
This feels really good, huh?
We're so connected right now.
Deeper.
Nu wants it deeper!
[chuckles]
Like hell are
we connected!
[NU] Hey...
Nu has a special
trick in mind, Ragna.
Check it out.
[NU] Watch!
Restriction 666 released!
And then I say,
"Dimensional Interference
Field Deployed!"
Murakumo Unit, activate.
Oh, yeah? Fine!
If this is how you
wanna play it,
the gloves
are coming off!
[RAGNA] Restriction
666 released!
Dimensional Interference
Field Deployed!
Blazblue!
[NU] We should
take it slow for now.
But later, you can
be as rough as you want.
You can destroy everything.
Nu likes it when
you're like that.
[NU] Come on. It's time.
[RACHEL] The two
of you will meld.
Into a beast that
will devour the world.
[RAGNA] Y'know what?
I hate the world anyway.
[RAGNA] I'm in.
Whatever catastrophic
bullshit you're planning,
mankind deserves it all.
Ragna!
Don't give up, Ragna! No!
Guess I dozed off, Saya.
Are you having a good day?
[YOUNG RAGNA]
What's with that face?
You get in a fight
with Jin again?
[inaudible dialogue]
Huh? What'd'ya say?
I can't, really
hear you right now.
I'm so sleepy I can't
keep my eyes open.
You can't give up.
[YOUNG RAGNA] Huh?
[NOEL] You can't
give up! Ragna!
[shrieks]
[NOEL grunts]
Huh?
Impossible.
'Bout effin' time!
[NOEL struggling]
How come... you gave up?
[NOEL] Dummy. Dummy, dummy,
dummy, dummy, dummy!
Dummy, dummy!
Dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy...
Shut up already--I get it!
What I meant to
say was, y'know...
Thank you.
For the save.
I really owe you one.
[NOEL begins sobbing]
Huh? Ow!
What the hell!
I just got stabbed!
Oh! I--! You're--!
I'm so sorry!
What do I do?
I'll go find a doctor
and bring them to you!
[NOEL] Just be patient!
I'll be right back!
Man, what is
the deal with her?
[RACHEL] It moves again.
[RACHEL] Thank
you for this respite
from my infernal
boredom, Ragna.
[RAGNA] Who the
hell is that girl?
Talk, Rabbit!
She is the new Eye.
[RAGNA] Wait...
She's what now?
The Azure Successor.
The Calamity Trigger.
[RACHEL] Unlike the copy
you so clumsily wield,
she will inherit
the true Azure.
The stagnant pool of time
has been undammed.
Even I do not
know where this new
current may take us,
but take us it shall.
In truth, I can
hardly wait.
I dunno what you're
going on about, Rabbit.
Cut the fluff-talk
and try it again.
[RAGNA] Huh?
[RACHEL] It awakens.
[RAGNA] Hey!
I wasn't done with
you yet, you know!
You're so powerful.
How could you be a copy?
[NOEL] Ragna! I'm back!
Damn if that girl don't
look exactly like you...
[RAGNA] Saya.
[giggles]
[RACHEL] The world has
begun to move forward.
[RACHEL] He concerns me,
and rightfully so.
But now, for the moment,
[RACHEL] you are the sole
possessor of my attention.
[RACHEL]
Nox Nyctores Gigant.
Take mikazuchi!
[JIN] Congratulations, Brother!
Your greatest wish came true!
Our story is an
anime, which means...
[RAGNA] Episode Three,
"The Observi--"
Jin, you bastard!
Shut up!
[JIN] Brother!