[HAZAMA] I'm getting
all of my ducks in a row,
believe you me,
but that damn Ragna
keeps ad-libbing
and skipping cues.
It's rushing the story
along faster than I'd like,
since the girls
aren't awake yet.
[HAZAMA] It's chaotic,
which I can dig,
but if I'm going
to send the world into
a truly abysmal tailspin,
I need more time.
Rome wasn't burned in a day.
[HAZAMA] Speaking of abysmal,
who's this hot mess?
[ARAKUNE] Who are you?
[ARAKUNE] Tell. Tell who
you are. Answer question.
Now, do it now.
Tell, tell, tell!
Messed with the power
of the Boundary, didja?
Guess you learned too late
that the Boundary bites back.
[ARAKUNE]
Azure, Azure, Azure!
I smell Azure!
[chuckles] If pudding and
nightmares had a baby,
I think it'd look
a lot like you.
[ARAKUNE growls]
Must! Must have it!
Give me the Azure!
[HAZAMA] Suck it, oil-slick.
[ARAKUNE yelling]
I like the cut of your jib,
you crazy bastard.
Send him up above.
They're gonna love him.
[ARAKUNE]
Azure, Azure, Azure!
[laughs]
Her readings are still
way below normal.
[KOKONOE] In this state,
she'd be a chew-toy
to that bastard.
[sighs]
[KOKONOE] I'll need performance
data to optimize her.
All right. As soon as
Tager gets back,
we're putting her
through a test-run.
Uh...
[KOKONOE] Dammit.
[KOKONOE] Why do I leave
that crap sitting around?
I don't even drink it.
[LAMBDA] Idea Engine engaged.
Area unknown.
[LAMBDA]
Area unknown. Area...
Area identified.
Location is the
13th Hierarchical City
of Kagutsuchi, Zone 2.
Hostile presence detected.
[ARAKUNE] Up here. Yes,
I smell more Azure up here.
Delicious, delicious Azure!
Danger Level, A.
Imminent harm.
[LAMBDA groans softly]
[ARAKUNE] I caught it!
I caught the foods!
I will chew it to pieces.
Take the tasty life
inside of it!
[LAMBDA] Damage, severe.
Escape not possible.
Not today, freakshow!
[ARAKUNE] Who? Who is the
thief who steals my food?
Your food, huh?
[ARAKUNE] Tasty. Tasty smell!
It's the Azure!
Azure, Azure, Azure,
Azure! Must have it!
[ARAKUNE] Aah!
Aaahhh!
[yells]
[ARAKUNE yells]
Pain, pain!
Will devour the Azure
another time, yes!
[RAGNA] Uh.
Hey you. That was
close. You okay?
[RAGNA gasps]
You again!
I'm gettin' real sick of this.
Subject identified.
Keeper of the Azure Grimoire.
♪
[RACHEL] You stand at the
brink of a momentous choice.
Will you visit
your wrath upon her?
[sighs]
[grunts]
[yells]
[KOKONOE] Huh?
[KOKONOE] Aah!
Lambda!
Oh, man.
What I do now
is hack my merry way
into Kagutsuchi's
surveillance system.
I'll find her and
have her back home
before the N.O.L.
even knows she was there.
Well, that's a
kick in the nuts.
Is the Izayoi still
doing its thing or what?
Okay. I'll just wire in
a little more juice.
Crap! Fried the
hardware! Aw, hell!
[KOKONOE] There is a way
I can find her without
hijacking the
surveillance cameras.
Shut down the Idea
Engine inside of her
and trace the particle stream.
But, if I do something
that extreme,
there's no way of knowing when
I'll have it up
and running again.
Shutting it down
might mean forever.
Damn it all! I can't
take that chance!
[KOKONOE] There's more
than one way to skin a...
well, y'know.
[RAGNA] So, is the Red Devil
gonna interrupt us again?
What are you doing here?
Did Kokonoe send you?
Ugh!
♪
[RAGNA] I didn't sign
on for this crap.
Damn things keep popping up,
and always with that face!
Hm.
Hey!
[squeaking]
What the--?
[KOKONOE] How's this for
thinking outside the box?
I hack into the
N.O.L. branch in Kagutsuchi,
and have their
system isolate data
that matches Lambda's
'til she pops up!
Who designed these
cyber-defenses, anyway?
They may as well have
laid out the damn
welcome mat for me!
Prepare to be boarded,
library scum!
Huh?
[KOKONOE] Dammit!
You're tellin' me
the whole mainframe is down?
[KOKONOE] Fix your
crap already, N.O.L!
Analyzing,
analyzing, analyzing.
[LAMBDA] Complete.
Subject is a male Tartar.
Phylum, Mollusca.
Class, Gastropoda.
It probably came from
that guy who tried to eat ya.
Word on the street is
that crazy bastard
has all sorts of creatures
living inside of him,
like a weird little
ecosystem or somethin'.
You're a real
fish outta water.
[LAMBDA] Reclassifying subject
as a fish out of water.
Confirmed.
Not quite. You're the
one that I meant.
Uh! Ugh...
Anyway, what do they call ya?
Requesting.
Can't do anything
without a thumbs-up
from Kokonoe, is that it?
Requesting same
data value. Your name.
You didn't say yours,
why should I?
Mm.
[exhales]
It's Ragna the
Bloodedge, okay?
R-A-G-N-A.
[LAMBDA] Rag...na.
Ragna.
You're not getting
lunch outta me.
All of their
hardware is crap.
Everything from
the security cameras
to the N.O.L. mainframe.
Guess I gotta
call in a favor.
[MAKOTO]
Feeling a little better?
[NOEL] Mhmmm.
Makoto, I can't just let
Tsubaki go on like this.
What do we do?
Before we do anything,
we have to get you
to a safe place.
[NOEL] Huh? What's wrong?
Did Captain Hazama
tell you to save me?
That guy's got
nothing to do with it.
Huh?
I've been sniffing around.
And you know what I dug up?
Hazama's past is blank.
No place of birth,
no age, absolutely nothing.
How come? What's he
got to hide, huh?
I don't trust that guy at all.
Something's snaky about him.
Mhm.
Yeah. You're right.
Anyway, Sector Seven's
Professor Kokonoe
is all set to take us in.
[NOEL] Wait, we're going
to Sector Seven? How come?
Because I'm...
Don't you fret!
I am gonna get this
all figured out.
For you and Tsubaki, both!
Noellers, you just
gotta trust me!
Uh.
I couldn't just
leave her there.
Right now, she's a damn
easy target. All the same.
I didn't sign on for
babysitting duty today.
She's one of
those things that...
[RAGNA]
I've been destroying.
[RAGNA] Hey!
Hm?
[RAGNA]
The hell are you doin'?
Vital signs failing.
Huh?
[TARTAR squeaking]
[RAGNA] You see that cut
there? It's killing him.
Usually they'd be able
to live through
getting dinged up.
But he can't bounce back
because he lost his host.
[RAGNA] Whether it's
fluids or nutrition,
he got something
from that bastard
that he's missing now.
Wait, did he just--?
[TARTAR squeaking]
If nothing else,
he's a fighter.
Here, you hold him.
[LAMBDA] Mmm.
Hm? Hey, wait up.
Don't just pick up
random plants.
I'm looking for aqualeaf.
Aqualeaf.
Referencing.
Referencing. Referencing.
[LAMBDA] Subject found.
Family, Aster-A-C.
Genus, Aquafolia.
Its rhizomes secrete
an analgesic substance.
[RAGNA] That's why we're
lookin' around for it.
When I trained with
my master back in the day,
we didn't have
medicine with us.
If we got sick,
the forest was our pharmacy.
Aqualeaf is delicate,
but the seithr's
pretty light around here,
so there should be
some in good condition.
Guess ya hit the jackpot.
[clears throat]
[TAGER] Tager here.
Go ahead, Kokonoe.
[KOKONOE] So, I kinda
sorta lost Lambda.
Bring her back,
would ya, Tager?
You know how important
that Idea Engine is to me.
Without it,
that bastard will never
get what's comin' to him.
[TAGER] Don't worry, Kokonoe.
I'll retrieve her for you.
[radio clicks]
[KOKONOE sighs]
Ew! I touched it.
Theory.
[RAGNA] Huh?
Subject is male.
Males are rare.
Therefore, he's worth saving.
You're asking why I helped?
[RAGNA] It's not like I had
some big reason to do it.
The way I look at it,
I just let something
that was alive keep on living.
All of us die someday.
End of story.
But that doesn't mean
you have to let it happen
like you don't
give a damn either way.
You fight it.
Tooth and nail. Y'know?
An' if you can't win
that fight by yourself,
it's all right if somebody
tags in an' lends a hand.
[RAGNA sighs]
Ragna, did someone help you?
[groans]
[RAGNA sighs]
[RAGNA] Yeah.
A couple of someones.
Wouldn't be here
today if they hadn't.
[groans]
Aqualeaf ain't gonna fix this.
[leaves rustle]
[RAGNA plays song]
[chuckles]
Wanna try?
[LAMBDA blowing air]
[leaf squeals]
[laughs]
[TARTAR squeaks]
You're blowin'
it too hard.
You gotta be more
gentle to play a song.
What is "gentle"?
Not in your
database, huh?
Okay then.
How do I make it
make sense to ya?
[LAMBDA] Huh?
You're a piece of work.
Negative.
I'm Lambda.
Hm? So Lambda's
your name, then?
[LAMBDA] Mhm.
[LAMBDA] Hm?
[gasps]
Huh?
I was cold.
[chuckles softly]
Tartar heart-rate,
dropping, dropping, dropping.
Zero pulse. Subject,
male tartar has ceased to
[LAMBDA] function as
a viable organism.
He is dead.
What do I do?
You don't gotta
do anything.
Mm-mmm.
[RAGNA] Then keep him
in your thoughts.
Until the day he ain't.
Let his memory live
in a corner of your soul.
If it fades away
over time, let it.
You'll have done right by him.
[LAMBDA] What is "soul"?
I don't know. It's this
thing you keep in your head.
Or maybe deep
inside your heart.
No one knows
where it lives,
but it's that spot that gets
all warm whenever you're happy
and gets chilly whenever
you're feelin' sad.
You were real gentle
with that little guy, Lambda.
[TAGER] Kokonoe I have
Lambda in my sights.
But she's not alone.
[KOKONOE]
Ragna the Bloodedge again?
[TAGER] Mm.
[KOKONOE] Like attracts
like, I guess.
Heya, Ragna. Guess who?
[gasps]
[RAGNA] Red Devil!
[KOKONOE] Thanks for keeping
an eye on Lambda for me.
[grunts]
What is she, Kokonoe?
I need you to tell me!
[KOKONOE] I took the body of
the 11th Prime Field Device
and stuck the soul
from the 13th in it.
Long story short,
she's a living weapon.
I'm gonna kick Terumi's
slimy ass with her.
Terumi is mine!
[KOKONOE] You're never
gonna beat him
with that dinky Azure.
Tager, you go back to
look for Noel Vermillion.
Hold on. Why the hell are
you guys looking for Noel?
[KOKONOE] We're not the one
you should be worried about.
Terumi's on the hunt, too.
If he finds her,
he's gonna smelt her.
We need to bring her in
for her own safety.
You're saying
he's gonna smelt her?
I talked a big talk
about mercy to that girl.
[RAGNA] "Let something that was
alive keep on living," I said.
Does she count, too?
Tch. Man, what a hypocrite.
This from the guy they
call the Grim Reaper.
[RAGNA] But, maybe it's not
too late to change my spots.
I'm gonna protect her.
[RAGNA] Do your worst, Terumi!
Time to wake up, milady.
There's so much for us to do.
[HAZAMA chuckles]
[ARAKUNE] Heya, folks!
It's me, the "before" version
of Arakune! I sound
relatively normal, right?
Episode 9 is "The Power
of Order." See ya!