Ready.
Instructions accepted.
[RAGNA] This crap again?
[LAMBDA] Activating battle
system. Deploying field.
[RAGNA grunts]
Readying arsenal.
Combat imminent.
What the hell?
♪
[RAGNA grunts]
[RAGNA yells]
What? No talking
this time?
That's fine by me!
[LAMBDA]
Countering blade attack.
Minimal damage taken.
Whatever.
Barrier solidified.
You're such a
pain in the ass!
Aw, hell!
This looks an awful
lot like a real fight.
[KOKONOE] Hey, not her
fault if Ragna can't hack it.
Don't go mucking up my data.
Copy that.
[SENA] Huh?
Hey, Luna. Did you hear
something strange just then?
[LUNA] Who knows?
Maybe they're doing
some construction.
[SENA] Or maybe
Mr. Ragna's in trouble.
[LUNA] Luna doesn't give
a crap about that pervert!
We're outta here.
[RAGNA] Well, that smarts.
Thanks for letting me heal
up from last time first.
Ah, whatever! Bring it!
[RAGNA] Hm?
What's wrong?
You change your mind?
It's too friggin'
late for that!
[KOKONOE] Hey! Lambda!
Annihilate that chump already.
That's an order!
Denied. Rag...na.
[KOKONOE] What? She has
bits of Nu-13's memories?
[KOKONOE] Tager! Get Lambda
outta there, A-SAP!
Do it!
Here comes!
Well, then. So much for
my not interfering.
[RAGNA yells]
[RAGNA] Dammit,
Red Devil! Put 'er down!
[TAGER] This fight
is over, Ragna.
But your efforts
were not in vain.
Kokonoe got
her data. Thank you.
Screw Kokonoe!
What're you shifty
bastards up to, huh?
Couldn't say. She hasn't
bothered to tell me.
I'm just the muscle.
[RAGNA scoffs]
Welcome to my shit list.
♪
So how did
pieces of Nu's memories
get into your head?
I wonder if it's a
side-effect of the Life Link?
[KOKONOE] Gonna have
to make some tweaks.
Huh?
Doesn't ring a bell.
Wish I could help you, mister.
Fresh produce,
right over here!
[MALE STREET VENDOR 6A]
Come give it a look!
[JIN grunts]
♪
[JIN] Damn it!
Why can't I track him down?
[MAN] At long last.
Jin Kisaragi.
Show yourself.
[MAN] I am Bang Shishigami!
This scar upon my face.
Is it not familiar?
[BANG] It's your handiwork!
Hm. We crossed
swords in Ikaruga.
Face me, villain.
I will avenge my
homeland's ruin!
[JIN laughs]
You can try!
[grimaces]
[BANG] Dragon of Destruction!
Honorable Death!
Aah!
[BANG] He fell quickly.
I hit him but once.
Of course.
He's already hurt.
[VILLAGERS chatter]
[NOEL] Just when he was
starting to be nicer to me.
[NOEL] I guess,
we're enemies after all.
Eh!
It's fine!
I need to track down
the Major and Tsubaki!
Miss Litchi? Then,
this is. Yes, of course!
Maybe the Major
stopped by a clinic
to get his wounds treated!
[NOEL] Um, excuse me!
Huh?
♪
It's pretty. They're
for New Year's, I guess.
I've got nothing to say
to you, Library girl!
[NOEL] I can't
waste time like this!
[distant fireworks explode]
[JIN shaky exhale]
Where am I?
[BANG] My home,
as fate would have it.
[gasps]
[JIN] What treachery is this?
[LITCHI] It's
pointless to struggle.
At the moment, you're
under a paralysis spell.
How am I not dead?
You could have your
vengeance at any moment.
I'm utterly defenseless.
[BANG] Trust me.
I would like nothing more
than to strike you down.
But there's
no honor to be had
in the killing
of a wounded foe.
For now, rest and heal up.
We shall have our duel
once you've regained
your strength.
[LITCHI] That means bed-rest,
and plenty of it,
whether you like it or not.
Mister Bang, could you
grab some clothes for him?
[BANG] For you,
Miss Litchi, anything.
[LITCHI] Bang is a good man.
"A bounty hunter of love
and justice" as he puts it.
What does a bounty
hunter know of justice?
Plenty. Enough to
spare the life
of his greatest foe.
[LITCHI] Not many people
would have done that.
And you are?
I'm Litchi Faye Ling.
I operate a clinic for
the people of Orient Town.
Cleavage aside, I am
one hell of a doctor.
I doubt that. Physical
treatment is so primitive.
Treating the patient
with ars magus
is much more expedient.
Your way's
dependent on seithr.
It is strong, but its
usage can have consequences.
You'd know that
better than most.
I'll leave your
medicine with Bang.
[birds chirping]
[JIN] I can move.
It wore off on its own?
[JIN pained breathing]
[BANG] Major.
[groans]
[BANG] Your breakfast is
waiting for you. Please, eat.
Whatcha need miss?
Sorry, sir. I'm not in
the market for produce.
In that case,
we got nothing to say.
I think you're wrong.
[TSUBAKI] See, I need info.
[TSUBAKI]
We've got lots to say.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
If you're looking
to spend that much,
I'll sing like a bird.
♪
[TRINITY] Under no circumstance
must you fight Yuuki Terumi.
With the Azure
Grimoire as it is.
you will surely perish.
[RAGNA scoffs]
Thanks for nothin'!
[birds chirping]
Was it wise of
you to free me?
There's nothing to stop me
from attacking you at will.
[laughs]
Such a devious attack
could never fell
Bang Shishigami.
Besides, neither of us
wants me to have to
feed you by hand,
now do we?
[JIN groans]
[BOYS laughing]
[BANG] This area
is very tranquil.
If you're of
a mind to see it,
I'd be more than happy
to show you around.
Do you mean it?
♪
[MALE CARPENTER 6A]
Heya, Boss!
Ho there! I applaud your
work-ethic, gentlemen!
That quake the other day
did a number on the roof!
Trust me, Boss.
We're not up here by choice!
[BOYS laughing]
[BANG] High stakes, eh?
[BOYS] Bang!
Hey, Mister Bang!
[BOY 6A] You're one of
those N.O.L. sleazeballs!
What are you doing here?
[JIN] Hm?
If you came here
to fight with Bang,
you gotta get
through me first!
[BOYS 6B, 6C, and 6D]
Yeah, me, too!
[BOY 6E] That goes
double for me!
[BANG laughs]
It's quite all right.
This man is my guest.
But, it was
bastards like this guy
who took Ikaruga
away! And my dad!
It's true. Our homeland
was annihilated,
and we lost a great many
loved ones along the way.
But if you smile,
then we didn't really lose.
Let's show our
guest here who's boss!
Yeah, you're right.
I'm gonna smile super big!
Perfect!
That's the spirit!
Now, Major, would you care
to join me for some tea?
[BOYS chatter]
[JIN] Telling those children
not to avenge their dead?
Such hypocrisy.
[BANG] Vengeance is
my lot as a warrior.
It's my duty, but the
people who live here,
they shouldn't have
to shoulder that kind of
hatred for the
rest of their days.
[JIN] The words of a fool.
Hm. Who can say?
[BANG] This, is where
I leave you, Major.
You are welcome to explore
the rest of it
at your leisure.
Wait. You're letting me go?
You're not a threat
at the moment,
injured as you are.
Young miss! I shall
leave my payment here!
[FEMALE TEA CLERK]
All right!
[JIN exhales heavily]
[TSUBAKI] Jin. It's me.
Huh?
[JIN gasps] Tsubaki!
[JIN] That uniform.
You don't mean to tell me.
[TSUBAKI] Yes, Jin.
I volunteered.
As a member of
the Yayoi family,
one of the Duodecim,
it's my right to
serve the Imperator.
But why, Tsubaki?
Why stain your hands
with the Wings of Justice?
[TSUBAKI] Jin, I--!
All right.
Major Jin Kisaragi,
you are charged
with several counts
of insubordination,
as well as having gone
AWOL from the hospital.
These are the
actions of a traitor.
A traitor?
[TSUBAKI]
Come back with me, Jin.
If we go now, then maybe
they'll show you some mercy.
It's still not too late!
[JIN] I can't.
Not yet, at least.
[TSUBAKI]
What are you thinking?
[JIN] There's something that...
I still have to do.
I see. And does
that "something"
have anything to do
with Ragna the Bloodedge?
Mm.
[RAGNA] Picks a fight,
and then runs away?
[chuckles]
Damn that Nu
for startin' crap!
Next time,
her ass is going down!
Her, and all of 'em
who're using that face!
[gasps]
Then, does that mean?
[grunts]
[RAGNA] Damn it all!
It doesn't matter!
Why do I even think
about crap like this?
[RAGNA grunts]
[TSUBAKI] What is this about?
[JIN] Look, it's got nothing
to do with you, Tsubaki.
Just go back to headquarters.
I won't.
The two of us are
leaving here together, Jin.
Even if... I have to
drag you there myself!
That's the Sealed
Armagus Izayoi!
Tsubaki!
[JIN] Do you have any
idea what you're wielding?
Well, of course.
Seems that you do.
[sighs]
We don't have much
time, so listen!
[gasps]
[TSUBAKI] Jin, I--
I've been given an
Imperial Command to kill you!
That's the last thing
in the world I want to do,
but... I'm carrying
out orders, that's all!
I must!
Put it down, Tsubaki!
Stop using the Izayoi!
[JIN]
It'll steal your light!
Just run, Jin!
[HAZAMA] Ooh.
What's wrong, Tsubaki?
Having trouble
sealing the deal?
Good thing I listened in!
Just to check, you haven't
forgotten that whole part
about Imperial Commands
being absolute, right?
[gasps]
Imperial...
commands are... absolute.
What have they
done to you?
Uh? What's wrong, Yukianesa?
[JIN] Why don't you obey?
[TSUBAKI] Now, you die.
[JIN groans]
[FEMALE TEA CLERK screams]
Wha--? Major!
♪
[TSUBAKI] Huh?
Jin? I--Oh, no!
Tsu...baki.
[groans]
[TSUBAKI] This...
...isn't real.
It can't be!
[BANG] Major, no!
[TC] Eradication of the
Power of Order observed.
[TB] His death might
lead to the world's end.
[TA] Losing the Power of Order
at this junction is ill-advised.
Proposing an event disruption.
[TC] Yes. Case 685.
Eliminating event distortion.
[BANG] Vengeance is
my lot as a warrior.
It's my duty, but the
people who live here,
they shouldn't have
to shoulder that kind of
hatred for the
rest of their days.
[JIN] The words of a fool.
Hm. Who can say?
[BANG] It's high time
we return to my home.
Young miss! I shall
leave my payment here!
[FEMALE TEA CLERK]
All right!
[panting]
[TSUBAKI] Pardon me.
If you have a pot going,
I'd love a cup of tea.
Is the tea not to
your liking, Madam Rachel?
The world has
chosen to err
on the side of
caution, it seems.
How dreadfully provincial.
Wouldn't you agree,
Valkenhayn?
[HAZAMA] Well, that happened.
Didn't know we were
playing with do-overs,
but I'll let it
slide this time.
Them saving his ass don't
make no never-mind to me!
Do you know why?
[HAZAMA] I've got
some tricks of my own
I still need to
shove up my sleeves.
[KOKONOE] Keep sleeping
for now, Lambda.
If I'm gonna beat
that grinning bastard,
I need your Idea Engine
working perfectly.
[JIN] Brother.
[gasps]
[JIN] Yukianesa.
What's wrong with you?
[BANG] It froze
Lord Tenjo solid.
And etched my defeat
into my face.
But a sword you cannot draw
is nothing more than a bauble.
Major, perhaps the fault
lies not within the blade.
How dare you?
[BANG] I know this is sudden,
and I am loath to send you out
into the night, but I think
you are in grave danger.
One of your own hunts
for you even now.
[JIN] I thought you wanted
a fight, bounty hunter.
'Til you've healed up,
there's no honor in it.
Besides...
[BANG] So long as your
sword refuses you,
it wouldn't be
much of a fight.
Now make haste.
[BANG SUBORDINATE 6A]
Boss, are you sure about this?
[BANG] Yes. He's free to go.
Once his wounds
are healed
and his doubts
have been swept away,
then we shall have
a duel for the ages.
His eyes, they had the look.
[BANG] The look of a
man about to do battle
with something enormous.
Like, my master's
that fateful day.
[JIN] The fault is mine?
About damn time.
[TSUBAKI] Jin, I'm really
glad that I didn't find you.
[NOEL] Tsubaki!
[gasps]
Noel!
[chuckles]
[BANG] Miss Litchi!
Would you please read
this letter I wrote you?
[LITCHI] Uh, "Episode Seven,
The Wings of Judgment"?
[BANG] Uh! I gave
you the wrong letter!
How can this be?