[bubbling lava]
[footsteps]
So the smelting
is already completed.
[grunts]
Loading, loading,
loading, loading.
All systems online,
Murakumo activating.
[NU] Ragna!
[NU] Come here to
kill me again, silly?
[RAGNA] Killing's for
people. You get broken.
Oh, Ragna I love it
when you talk dirty.
Come here. Let's play.
[laughs playfully]
[RAGNA] Dammit!
Ahhh!
Son of a--!
[stabbing]
[RAGNA cries out]
You're insane.
[NU laughs playfully]
Oh, Ragna!
Now we'll be
together. Always.
[HAZAMA] How many
times are you gonna
let that girl shish
kabob ya, Ragna?
[RACHEL] It's always the same.
We've run the scene to death,
and again, the curtain falls.
Sleep well,
Ragna the Bloodedge.
Our pantomime will continue.
[MALE NOL 1A] This is the
N.O.L. Ahkitsu Branch!
We're under attack!
It's the Grim Reaper!
He hit us out of nowhere!
We've taken heavy casualties!
If we don't get backup--
[blast]
♪
[sighs]
There's plenty of
seithr down here,
that's for damn sure.
[RAGNA] Dammit!
Underfoot again. Like dirt.
But dirt, I'm sure,
has better manners.
[RAGNA] Shut it!
[GII cries out]
My!
What the hell? Why're
you griefing me, Rabbit?
Don't be mean, Princess.
I'm a bat, not a baseball!
[RACHEL]
Your self-control is laudable.
Brute that you are,
I feared you might
have fallen prey
to that arm of yours.
Imagine my surprise.
I'm impressed.
You're a good boy, Ragna.
[RAGNA] Hey! I'm not
some mutt, y'know!
Kagutsuchi awaits you.
Huh?
Kagutsuchi?
Why the hell would I waste
my time with a place like that?
Course, the town's got a
Cauldron I need to destroy.
Hm?
Guess I'll give it a look.
Well if it ain't Little
Miss Blood Breath.
You spend your time
eavesdropping on a lady?
[HAZAMA] Uh huh.
When it comes to time,
I have got a crap ton.
I'm not gonna lie,
all this repeating
makes planning
ahead a real pain in the ass.
You would be wise
to do naught but watch.
Yeah, I bet
you're right, huh.
Unfortunately...
I have way too
many irons in
the ol' fire to
call it a day now!
[laughs]
♪
[knock]
[NOEL] Excuse me, sir.
Second Lieutenant
Noel Vermillion.
[JIN] Come in.
Major Kisaragi,
I bring this.
[JIN] The dispatch
bears an ars magus seal.
It's classified.
[JIN] It's him.
[gasps]
Finally,
Ragna the Bloodedge.
[JIN laughs]
Major, sir. What is it?
Thirteenth, huh?
Move.
[door slams]
[people chattering]
A lotta people here.
Huh?
[groans]
[RAGNA grunts]
[TAOKAKA] Om noms.
Tao needs om noms!
Taokaka Punch!
[yells]
[TAOKAKA] Meow-ch!
[TAOKAKA] Me... ow...
Of course. Kaka Clan.
Huh?
You don't have to
beat Tao up, mister.
[TAOKAKA] Just let her
waste away to nothin'.
[TAOKAKA]
Thanks for all the food!
[eating sounds]
You're a good guy,
treating Tao
to all these tasty things!
I totally got
hustled, didn't I?
[TAOKAKA] Nope! You
Tao-tally got hustled!
Oh, by the
way Good Guy,
do you know
where Rawrgna the
Something, Something
likes to hang out?
Huh?
I think you're talking ab--
[TAOKAKA] If Tao
uses her best mew-ves
on Rawrgna and catches him,
she'll get a bunch of money!
More than anyone ever!
[RAGNA] Wait,
she's a bounty hunter?
They're even giving
out posters of Rawrgna!
[TAOKAKA] Look!
[RAGNA] That's not
what I look like!
[TAOKAKA] If you see that
face, tell Tao right away!
You're a good guy, Good Guy,
so Tao will buy you om noms
with the reward meow-ney!
Cross my heart!
[RAGNA] Even if
I tell her my name,
I don't think she's gonna
put two and two together.
[TAOKAKA] No more...
Tao surrenders!
Now that the belly is full,
it's time to
catnap for a while!
Sleepy, huh?
You're meow-bsolutely
right, Good Guy!
Tao's gonna flop
down in a patch of sun
[TAOKAKA] and
catch some Zs! Meow!
Hey, what's
the matter?
[RAGNA] It's nothing.
Huh?
But there's still a bunch
of food in the bowl!
Tao calls dibs!
It's all me-ine!
[RAGNA panting]
Master... Check it out.
[JUBEI] Listen up, kid.
The power of the Azure
don't belong to nobody.
Don't forget. Ever.
I won't forget. Master.
[RACHEL] Your eyes
are filled with hatred.
With loved ones slain
and kin stolen away,
I daresay such
malice is your right.
But the world will turn,
as always it has.
No matter how you
may rail against it.
[footsteps]
So this is it. The 13th
Hierarchical City. Kagutsuchi.
[HAZAMA] Somebody looks
ready to buy some souvenirs.
"Noel Vermillion," wasn't it?
Sorry, Captain Hazama!
Please forgive me!
[HAZAMA] I suppose I could.
If you stop calling me Captain.
I come from the Intelligence
Department, after all.
We're casual.
Yes sir! Uh... I mean...
Just call me...
Mister Hazama.
[HAZAMA] All right, then!
Let's review the basics.
This whole mess
with Major Kisaragi
is being handled with the
highest level of
discretion, of course.
I mean, if folks
find out that the
Hero of Ikaruga
has gone rogue,
the N.O.L.'s gonna
take one on the chin
[HAZAMA] in the court
of public opinion.
[HAZAMA] So, if you
encounter the Major,
bag him and bring
him into headquarters
with a minimum of fuss.
Right!
Most secretaries
would give
their eye teeth to
beat up their boss.
Do bear in mind,
a Level D alert is
currently in effect here in
the fair city of Kagutsuchi.
It's because
Ragna the Bloodedge
has been spotted here
in town, right, sir?
He's been hitting N.O.L.
branches, one by one.
Right. Have your superiors
told you anything
about this Ragna chap?
Oh, uh... They said
to observe him only,
and not to make contact. Sir.
[HAZAMA]
Roger that, Lieutenant.
Why don't you go
check out the city,
since we got here so
far ahead of schedule.
We'll meet at the
Kagutsuchi Branch later on.
Sir! I'll get
on that right away!
[elevator doors close]
[sighs heavily]
You disobedient little minx.
[TAOKAKA] ♪ Meow, meow, meow.
Meow, meow, meow ♪
[singing continues]
[grunts]
--[RAGNA] Hey!
--[TAOKAKA] Huh?
Why the hell are
you followin' me?
[TAOKAKA] Tao's not
following you, Good Guy.
You just picked the
direction Te-aow wanted to go!
[grunts]
[TAOKAKA] Meow!
Huh?
Ooh...
You're playing
keep-away with Tao, huh?!
Whatcha got there, Good Guy?
Is it tasty food?
[RAGNA] Hey! Quit it!
[TAOKAKA] Meow!
Dammit! Let go
of my arm already!
[TAOKAKA] Whoa...
Tao's feelin' kinda mewsy!
You're getting on my
nerves, ya damn mooch!
--[TAOKAKA] Meow?
--[RAGNA] Lay off already!
Good Guy got grumpy
all of a sudden.
He should've eaten his food.
Maybe here I can get some
friggin' peace and quiet.
[exhales heavily]
Your self-control is laudable.
The power of the Azure
don't belong to nobody.
Yeah. You're a real
pain in the ass.
Aintcha?
[exhales]
[NOEL] Huh?
Saya, come here! Hey!
♪
[squelch]
[YOUNG RAGNA yells]
[RAGNA yells]
[RAGNA] Saya?
Huh?
What the--?
Who the hell are you?
[NOEL] What? Hold on!
You were having
a nightmare.
[NOEL] It must
have been horrible.
Let's see.
You're warm, but
you're not feverish.
[NOEL] Still,
you might want to have
an actual doctor
check you out.
[gasps]
Something's the
matter with your arm!
[RAGNA] Get offa me!
Wait, I--!
Aww. There he goes,
running off like always.
"Like always"?
We've never met before.
[footsteps]
[RAGNA] The hell's
wrong with this place?
I haven't seen anybody.
Did the N.O.L. clear
out when they heard
I was coming?
Or maybe it's...
A trap.
[MAN] Took you long enough.
[footsteps]
[MAN] We finally meet.
Brother.
Jin.
[JIN] I'm amazed
you didn't bleed out.
And that new arm,
it looks like an
improvement over the
one I took from you.
This one might not
come off so easily.
You bastard!
Why?
Yes, that strength!
You really are my brother!
I've got a bunch
of questions, Jin,
and you're gonna
answer 'em all!
But before that...!
I'm gonna beat
the shit outta you!
Let's kill each
other, Brother!
Augh!
[JIN chuckles]
Goodness! That was
really something!
So that's the power of the
Azure Grimoire you wield.
I'm glad you're
still alive.
I'm having too much fun
for it to be over yet!
Don't tell me you're
getting tired, Brother!
[RAGNA] I've had enough!
Huh?
[yells]
[JIN groans]
[JIN] What's the
matter, Brother?
Don't have the guts
to finish me off?
Look, dumbass, I didn't come
here today to end your life.
If you wanna die,
do it yourself.
Brother, even now
you're merciful.
[chuckles]
That's why you
can't protect anyone.
Because you're soft.
[chains clanking]
It looks so...
empty.
Maybe Ragna
the Bloodedge
dropped in for
a little bit.
Huh? Hm.
[NOEL gasps]
Major Kisaragi!
He's out cold.
Pardon the pun.
[chuckles]
Taking him back with us just
got a whole lot easier, huh?
[HAZAMA] Mission
accomplished, I guess.
Well let's be off!
Please, wait!
[NOEL] I--I'm gonna pursue
Ragna the Bloodedge!
Oh?
I thought that the brass
told you not to engage him.
[NOEL] It's true, sir.
They did, but given
what happened,
we can't just let him go!
[HAZAMA] Well... if it
means that much to you.
[NOEL] Mr. Hazama, please
take care of the Major!
[NOEL] It looked like
Ragna the Bloodedge
almost killed Major
Kisaragi back there.
Why was Captain Hazama
so calm about it?
Uh! Huh?
[blast]
What the hell?
[RAGNA] Wait! The
Azure Grimoire is afraid?
[MAN] It has
been a long time...
Dark One.
[RACHEL] You are right
in fearing him, Ragna.
Fear in the face
of absolute power.
Fear of your death.
In all of your duels,
[RACHEL] not once have
you emerged the victor.
Nice mask!
Who's under it?
[MAN] I am the white void.
Damn it!
[MAN] I am the cold steel.
I am the just sword.
With blade in hand,
shall I reap the
sins of this world
and cleanse it in the
fires of destruction!
[MAN] I am Hakumen!
The end has come!
[RAGNA] O Azure
Grimoire dwelling
within my right arm,
cancel the jinx
on fighting game
anime shows, would ya?
[RACHEL] Episode Two,
"The Azure Successor."