♪
This is the place.
I think.
♪
[sighs]
-[MIYAKO] Um, hi.
-Yeah?
I'm looking for the Nocturnal
Community Relations Division.
I'm Miyako Arata.
[GUARD]
Ah, so you're the new kid, huh?
Sakaki told me you'd be by.
Please come on in.
Follow that hallway to the end
and turn right.
Pass the elevator hall.
Make a turn at the corner
with the cafeteria,
then you should see it.
First door on the left.
This it?
Hi, I hope you weren't
waiting long.
That's strange.
No one's here.
Uh?
[MIYAKO screams]
[coughing]
[THEO]
Jeez. Didn't expect that.
Did I use the wrong stuff?
Let's see, sulfur, aluminum,
and goat gallstones.
Were my proportions off?
-Um, excuse me?
-[THEO] Huh?
Is this the Nocturnal Community
Relations Division or...
[THEO]
It is, but who are you?
Well, I'm supposed to be
starting here today, but---
[THEO] Oh yes!
You're the new kid!
I remember Reiji telling me
something about that earlier.
[gasps]
Nice to meet you.
I'm Theo Himeduka. I work here.
There's no need to be formal
around here, so please,
-call me Theo.
-If you say so.
I used to live in Britain,
so I'm used to first names.
Seriously, Theo?
You did it again, didn't you?
The smoke got all the way
to the cafeteria this time!
-Tell me you weren't using fire.
-[THEO growls]
The only one in the wrong here
is you, Kyouichi!
You jerk!
You used my photo to break up
with your latest skank again,
didn't you?
-Grow up!
-Oh. Secret's out.
Listen, it's so much easier
for them
to think I found someone else.
[THEO]
Not for me!
Every day there's some
angry hag on my doorstep
giving me the side-eye!
[KYOUICHI]
Lucky you!
[THEO] Quit making me
clean up your mess
after these shady trysts!
I swear. It happens again,
you'll regret it.
Wow, I'm an idiot.
Do you have a cold,
Miss Himeduka?
I thought you were
a man for a--
What? Of course I'm a man!
I told you to call me Theo!
-Theo!
-[MIYAKO] Okay.
[THEO groans]
It's really not that hard.
Hello. This is Sakaki.
What's up?
Yeah, Miyako's here.
The new recruit.
Should I send him in?
Understood.
It's no problem,
introductions can wait.
That's Sakaki Kyouichi.
-He loves women and drinking.
-Right.
-[THEO] Used to work as a host.
-Yeah.
[THEO] Now he's the
shift leader of the division.
Never know it by looking at him.
[MIYAKO]
Huh.
[KYOUICHI]
Thanks for that, Theo.
Feel free to ask us
about anything
you don't understand, all right?
Thank you so much.
I appreciate that.
-[bell ringing]
-[MIYAKO] Huh?
Well, it's 7:00.
About time for us
to get to work, then.
Change into the outfit
in that far-right locker.
We'll be going outside
for your first shift.
We spend most of our time
outside the office.
I'll give you a nametag
to wear inside later.
We work a different shift
than everyone else,
so you won't use it much.
Um, won't it be
getting dark soon?
What part of the job
requires going out at night?
-What were you told?
-[MIYAKO] Huh?
Oh, um, the job description said
"building relationships
with people of all ages
"in various fields
and social positions.
Also engaging in planning
and promotion."
[THEO]
That's right. This is Shinjuku,
where people from
several different countries
do many different jobs
in many different places.
[KYOUICHI] You might be
wondering what it is we do
to make this a better place
for them to live.
Well, figuring that out
is our job, basically.
At least, that's what
the paperwork says.
Is that helpful?
Have you ever seen a youkai
or an angel or a devil?
[MIYAKO]
Huh?
Is this a joke, or am I supposed
to answer that seriously?
I'll go ahead
and take that as a hard no.
But if you were assigned here,
it means you triggered
that little trick
that's hidden
in the employment exam.
[KYOUICHI] He's probably
the type who didn't notice it.
[THEO] Well then, we'll need
to do a rite of passage.
Huh? I don't know what
you're talking about.
[chuckles]
♪
What is this place?
Huh? Shinjuku Imperial Gardens.
You've never been?
Well, sure. I have but, um...
Wait, I don't think
they allow anyone
to go in at night, do they?
We have to come here a lot
as part of our job,
so we have a key.
There's hardly any light inside,
so be careful.
Sure, okay!
[MIYAKO] We work in the
Imperial Gardens after hours?
What did I sign up for?
That looks like a good spot.
I agree.
The rite of passage,
you ready?
Uh, hold on. I don't understand.
What is this thing
you keep talking about?
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
Even if you scream and pass out,
I'll take care of you.
It'll be easier to understand
if you experience the job
rather than us explaining it.
-Look over there.
-[MIYAKO] Huh?
[KYOUICHI] Notice the fairy?
Between those trees.
Uh... where?
It's there.
You probably can't see it
right now, though.
Same goes for youkai,
angels, and devils.
In fact you should assume
most of the occult creatures
you've seen in works
of fiction actually exist.
And, rookie,
that's the first lesson
on our agenda for tonight.
Okay. It's just kinda hard
to believe
this has anything
to do with work.
I understand.
But it's an
important discussion
pertaining to the job we do.
-Theo?
-Yup, that's right.
So, why are we spraying bushes?
It's the Spray of Ibn Ghazi,
a little helper for people
who can't see them normally.
It's made from the soil
of ancient tombs,
amaranth flowers,
and ground ivy.
Look. There, in front of you.
♪
[MIYAKO]
Huh?
Now tell me what do you see?
[MIYAKO]
I, uh, I see a light.
-Wait, it's changing.
-[FAIRY coughing]
What is happening?
It's a little girl?
And she has wings on her back.
Is that a fairy?
[FAIRY huffs]
[grunting]
[THEO]
That one was a pixie.
You can find them everywhere.
It's just hard to believe.
Well, you have to believe it
if you can see it.
Because, otherwise,
you'll just have to assume
that you're going insane.
[gasps]
♪
[hisses]
-[thudding footsteps]
-[MIYAKO] Huh?
[MIYAKO gasping]
What the hell is that?
You can see without
the spray already?
Means you've got
good instincts.
This big boy is a Cu Sith.
Don't worry, it's friendly.
[MIYAKO whimpering]
Neat, huh?
They all have
their own unique names.
And each falls under a certain
category of occult creature.
Angel, Devil,
Youkai, and Fairy.
That said, we have
a general term for them.
We refer to
the non-human creatures
we use in our work as...
"Anothers."
Wow, you don't seem
very scared.
[MIYAKO]
Well, no.
I'm more surprised.
If that's all you are,
then this rite of passage
was a big success.
Looks like we might have
actually got
a decent rookie this time.
Most are usually
passed out by now.
Or at least their legs
are too weak to stand.
But you're doing
all right, huh?
Yeah, but I'm still wondering
what our job is?
[KYOUICHI] Maintaining relations
with the Anothers.
And then, if they cause any
problems for civilians, well...
we're the ones who
take care of it, make sense?
As members of the Nocturnal
Community Relations Division,
we work primarily
as public servants.
Hmm? What's wrong?
Nothing. Just...
-I'm a little worried.
-Nothing to be worried about!
If you can stay calm at the
first time of seeing Anothers,
I'd say you're doing
pretty good!
He's got a good point.
Just do what you're told
and focus on the things
you feel good about.
We won't ask for much more
than that just yet.
Okay.
Miyako Arata.
We're the Shinjuku Ward
Nocturnal Community
Relations Division,
and we're glad to have you.
So here's what's on our list
of things to do tonight.
We're investigating
some loud noises
that have been
reported lately.
They seem to be coming from here
in the Imperial Gardens.
-Noises?
-Yeah.
Since there are
no events being held,
we don't know
where they'd be coming from.
We were patrolling around
this area last night.
That's where we found traces of
two different types of Anothers
at the site
of a damaged tree.
Analysis of both the physical
and circumstantial evidence
leads us to believe there's some
sort of territory struggle.
We believe it's between some
of the tengu and the angels.
Huh? So they fight each other?
-The Anothers, I mean.
-Oh yeah, for sure.
The Imperial Gardens have
a lot space and greenery,
so there are multiple types
of Anothers that live here.
Sometimes they fight.
[MIYAKO] Okay.
So how do we stop them?
-Put up a barrier.
-[MIYAKO] Huh?
Oh, you mean with,
like, talismans,
and salt and burning sage?
-More like that.
-[MIYAKO] Huh?
-[MIYAKO] Tape?
-[THEO] Yup.
It engages
the element of wind
and adjusts the area's
dimensional phase.
That creates a fairly
powerful barrier
which can block out
most noises.
Theo made it himself.
The other wards
are using it, too.
Hey, did you find out
about Sendagaya Gate?
[KYOUICHI] I spoke
to Shibuya's division earlier,
so I'm sure it's handled.
[MIYAKO]
Ah!
The Gardens run into
Shibuya Ward, don't they?
Here you go.
Newb.
We'll split up
into two groups
and make barriers with this.
-Sound good?
-Yeah.
[tape ripping]
Nice job.
I'll finish this one.
Can you go work
on that forest over there?
Just run the tape along
the trees on the left side.
[MIYAKO]
Roger that.
[sighs]
[MIYAKO] Can this really create
a strong enough barrier?
[leaves rustling]
[screeching]
[inaudible dialogue]
[TAROUBOU]
Oh, my winged beauty.
My beloved Adiel.
I feel so powerless having only
one place where I can meet you.
[ADIEL]
It doesn't matter to me
where we need
to meet, my Taroubou.
As long as you're safe.
I long for a life in the sky.
-The two of us together.
-As do I.
All I want is to fly
with you forever!
Then let's do it!
I know the others
will never accept us,
but who cares?
Really? I'm so happy!
[ADIEL gasps]
But no,
I could never leave
my dear sister behind.
[TAROUBOU inhales sharply]
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid
it's time for me to go.
[ADIEL]
So soon, my love?
I want to spend
my future with you.
Promise me you'll think
about it. Okay?
[gasps softly]
-[KYOUICHI] That's an angel.
-[MIYAKO] Uh...
And the other one
was a tengu.
It's rare
to see them together.
Rarer that they'd stand
so close.
That's fascinating.
I thought they were having
an argument at first.
[MIYAKO]
But then it quickly changed.
-[booming]
-[MIYAKO gasps]
[FOLCIEL]
There you are, Taroubou!
I am Adiel's sister, Folciel,
and I know very well
that you've been deceiving her!
I've come here tonight
to destroy you!
Wait, please.
You must've misunderstood!
You won't get away!
Hold it right there!
Father, what are you doing?
Stay right there, Taroubou!
How dare you accuse
the son of Yotsuya Fudoubou!
You should all know better!
Did you think I'd stay back
and allow you to kidnap him?
I know exactly
what you monsters are up to!
[grunting]
No way!
I hope they both
settle down on their own.
-Huh?
-[water sloshing]
He's taking Adiel!
No, you don't!
That's strange!
What are they trying to do?
Wait, Adiel!
We're coming for you!
Theo! They might be
leaving the park!
What? How is that possible?
[KYOUICHI]
Hell if I know!
[ringing]
[MAN A] Yes, this is
the Nocturnal Community
-Relations Division?
-[KYOUICHI] It's Sakaki!
The Anothers are leaving!
They're heading to the city.
We're gonna follow 'em!
Thanks for the update!
You guys be safe.
[keypad beeping]
-[panting]
-[phone ringing]
[MAN B over phone]
Yes?
[MAN A] This is Shinjuku
Nocturnal Community Relations.
I was just informed
some of our staff
are trailing some Anothers.
[MAN B]
And?
[MAN A]
They may be heading your way.
Just wanted to give you
a heads up.
[phone disconnects]
♪
[inhales sharply]
[TENGU grunt]
Adiel! Get away
from that tengu!
Sister, please,
you have to stop this!
Oh, so you refuse? Fine!
[ADIEL gasps]
[CROWD screaming]
Is this the noise
they were complaining about?
♪
[panting]
[THEO]
Wow, there are so many of them!
♪
[cell phone buzzing]
-This is Sakaki!
-[THEO] City Hall!
Get over here right away!
They're all fighting each other
in the People's Plaza!
Hurry it up!
♪
We're here.
How's it looking?
Dirty looks and small spats.
This could go on till morning.
-What is it?
-You might be wrong.
I don't think they're fighting
over territory.
I didn't say it was fact!
Angels and tengu don't get along
and I made a guess, so sue me!
What? Are you serious?
[MIYAKO] I guess that means
none of them know.
-[THEO] Know what?
-Those two.
I just saw them in the park.
Taroubou and Adiel.
They're in love with each other!
[BOTH]
Taroubou. Who?
The tengu who was
with the angel.
All right, hold on.
I'm not following you at all.
You just saw them
standing next to each other.
How do you know?
-Well, because I heard---
-[THEO] Run, you idiot!
[crash]
Arata! Are you okay?
That hurt.
But, yeah, I think I'm fine.
So I got a human involved.
I'm sorry.
And now you want
to fight us too?
[FUDOUBOU gasps]
[FOLCIEL]
Please forgive her.
She never meant to hurt the boy.
The angels
are attacking us, too?
You must understand,
we do not wish to fight you.
[KYOUICHI] They're not gonna
give up, are they?
[MIYAKO]
Huh?
You might want
to step back, Arata.
This next move is going
to hit them pretty hard.
[MIYAKO]
But why?
There's no need
to go easy on them!
Hold on. We--
You want a fight?
[MIYAKO]
Why?
♪
[MIYAKO]
Why is this happening?
-Now, Theo!
-On it!
[MIYAKO] No one is listening!
No one's being heard!
♪
[loud bang]
[ALL coughing]
Are you out of your mind?
What are you doing?
Listen! They were trying
to apologize!
Yotsuya Fudoubou and Folciel
both said they had
no intentions of hurting me!
Wait. Did you say...
You guys need to relax, too!
Adiel's not in any danger!
You're kidding me. No way!
So are you talking to them?
[MIYAKO]
Huh?
I'm just repeating
what they said
when they were right
in front of you.
Did you not hear them
or something?
We can't understand
their language!
Don't act surprised!
They're Anothers!
How the hell are we supposed
to know what they're saying?
It's no different than trying to
understand your dog or your cat!
[KYOUICHI]
Where did they find this kid?
[THEO]
Mnh-mnh.
So then, you can
understand our words?
Hello. Would you mind
telling me who you are?
Just an employee
of the Shinjuku
Ward Office, ma'am.
-[ADIEL] Sister!
-[MIYAKO gasps]
[FOLCIEL and FUDOUBOU]
Wait, What?
You want to elope?
[ALL ANOTHERS murmuring]
-[ANGEL A] An angel?
-[TENGU A] And a tengu?
[TENGU B]
This is unheard of!
[ANGEL B]
They're from different realms!
What's going on here?
Nothing's making any sense.
[groaning]
I can't believe
what I'm seeing.
My dear, sweet sister.
Uh, Miss,
from what I saw,
they made a wonderful couple.
And besides,
it's their romance, isn't it?
Let's leave it to them, okay?
[BOTH sigh]
What do you say
we put this thing to bed for now
and talk again
in a few days?
Yes, I agree.
What are they saying?
Is it over. Or...?
[MIYAKO]
Mm-hmm.
Sister, stop! You're hurting me!
-Ouch!
-[FOLCIEL] Quiet!
[TAROUBOU grunts]
You will never keep secrets
from me again!
I'm sorry, Father.
♪
[MIYAKO]
Taroubou?
Hello. What's your name?
Miyako. Miyako Arata.
I'll remember that
♪
So that's it.
I never did figure out
what was going on.
Huh.
What are you exactly?
Be honest.
I don't know.
I'm trying to figure that out.
[laughter]
[OLD MAN TENGU]
Excellently done, my friends!
[THEO gasps]
[THEO]
Something else is here?
And it looks to me like
your knack of languages
hasn't changed a bit, has it?
-Abe no Seimei.
-[MIYAKO] Uh...
Okay, what did
that thing just say?
Translate!
[MIYAKO]
Oh. He's calling me Abe.
-Hold on.
-[KYOUICHI] What's wrong?
-Are you okay?
-[MIYAKO groans]
Actually, I don't know.
I'm kinda dizzy.
Sorry.
So... question.
Who is Abe No Seimei?
[wind whistling]