[car engine revving]
[car doors opening]
♪
[KYOSHI moaning, growling]
[ARATA]
What are kyoshi exactly?
The walking dead.
Theo can give you details
when we get back.
So, there's a way out?
We're not trapped?
[KYOICHI]
Of course not!
-[ARATA] Okay.
-[ANOTHER chuckles]
Come on!
Who put this obnoxious
ritual here?
[AKANE]
Theo?
[THEO]
How's it going?
Hey. We're from Chiyoda Ward.
Senda told us you were in a bind
and might need backup.
[inaudible dialogue]
[FEMALE AGENT]
He sent us as reimbursement
for borrowing your new guy.
[THEO] That sounds like him.
I'm glad you're here.
Is it true?
You found a kyoshi ritual?
Yeah.
We've got stolen
izuna tails in Aichi,
hair from the family god,
some fairy dust,
and mermaid scales.
Oh, yeah, there's also
the centuries-old grave
and some dirt
from Toyama Park.
-I knew...
-[ALL gasp]
[THEO] ...right away it was
to create the...
[KYOSHI moaning]
Kyoshi?
-Theo! You're here?
-[THEO] Huh?
[THEO] Kyoichi!
Are you all right?
Yeah, no problem.
[THEO gasps]
There's an Another behind you.
Do you know what it is?
♪
[THEO]
Long black hair.
And the shiny,
golden eyes of a beast.
Is that the thief
we've been looking for?
The one who took Suzuka's hair?
Well, now, isn't this
a strange sight?
How rare it is to see you
with humans, Seimei.
I suppose it has been
a long time, hasn't it?
Things do change.
But enough of that.
I'm ready, Seimei.
For you to entertain me.
♪
[KYOSHI moaning, growling]
[MALE AGENT 1] Not good.
There's so many of them!
And we're sure they're kyoshi?
What do you think, Chief?
What should we do?
[FEMALE AGENT]
I'm not sure,
but we've
got to move on this.
Seal off all entrances
to the park.
Keep them in here
no matter what it takes.
What? Are you kidding me? Aah!
[ARATA whimpers]
Be careful!
These monsters will
literally eat you alive.
[ARATA]
Huh?
[THEO grunts]
It didn't work.
-[THEO] Let's go, guys!
-Right!
[ARATA gasping]
Hurry!
[KYOSHI wailing]
[grunting]
Hey! I thought--
[KYOSHI growling, moaning]
-We made it.
-[gasps]
Were you trying to kill me?
I wasn't going
to scream or anything.
The Kyoshi track down humans
by sensing the direction
of their breath.
Ah!
That's why you did it.
Can't get a signal down here.
-A barrier?
-Probably.
Why did it have to take so long
for me to figure it out?
So, um, tell me more
about the Kyoshi.
He said they're
the walking dead?
Yes, that's right.
They used to be human corpses.
And what that means for us
is normal people can see them.
They're artificial Anothers.
So, they were created?
[THEO] The difference between
these guys and zombies
is that their bodies
are still intact.
[ARATA] Why would anyone
make something like that?
[THEO] Well, in China,
they used the ritual
to send the recently deceased
away from their village.
They'd wander into the night,
never to be seen again.
[KYOICHI]
Judging by their clothes,
these bodies date back
to World War II.
[THEO]
My guess.
Someone had prepared the ritual
to be used during the War
and then abandoned it
when the War ended.
[KYOICHI] So, then, this Another
stole the remaining elements
needed to complete the ritual
using these bodies.
Every time!
When they're about
to lose a war,
countries always turn
to the occult for help,
and if it's not instant,
they walk away
and leave dangerous stuff
-just lying around!
-So, um,
how do we protect
ourselves from them?
Well, with sunlight.
[ARATA]
And since that's not an option?
You got a flamethrower
or shotgun?
[ARATA]
You know that I don't!
Why don't you try coming up
with a solution
yourself, Seimei?
-Huh? [screams]
-Why'd he come back?
Stay calm,
he's just toying with us.
Hold on! Why do you keep
calling me that name?
You mean Seimei?
Why? Does it bother you, Seimei?
That's not my name!
I already told you,
I'm not this damn Seimei!
He's snapped.
[ANOTHER]
You're not?
You're not Seimei? Is that true?
I see. I was so certain
that I had found him.
But since that's not
the case...
Yeah. I'm so glad
we cleared that up.
[ANOTHER]
...I'll just kill you.
I had prepared all of this
for my friend,
but I suppose
it'll have to go to waste.
I despise how much
you resemble him.
[ARATA whimpers]
[ANOTHER]
You must die.
[ARATA]
Well, shit.
I'm Seimei!
Yep! I was just messin'
with you, buddy!
Do you mean it? I'm so glad.
I've missed playing with you.
Wait! What?
Get back, you guys!
They're part human,
so force will work on them!
But it won't get us very far.
-Find the altar!
-What are you talking about?
Do you realize
how many kyoshi are out there?
Keeping that many bodies moving
requires something powerful.
The Chiyoda team above are
calling for reinforcements now,
but we've got to find a way
to protect ourselves
while we wait
for them to show up.
-[grunts]
-[KYOSHI moaning]
[ARATA]
Ow! Whoa!
[GROUP panting]
Wow. That was very impressive.
[KYOICHI]
What a creepy place.
This must be where they were
doing research on the Kyoshi.
[footfalls]
It looks like the string
is coming from that direction.
-A string?
-Yes.
It's what gives the kyoshi
the ability to move.
Huh?
[THEO] Since their
human bodies
are no longer alive,
they shouldn't be
functioning at all.
So, some kind of power
that comes from the altar
helps them move, correct?
That's right.
It's negative energy.
Also known as, "Yin."
I see it now.
These threads are connected
to the altar.
They then transfer
Yin energy to the kyoshi.
So, we should cut them.
Huh?
You can't.
Not without something enhanced
with a specific magic.
Hey, is that what I think it is?
[THEO] Yes.
It's the stolen hair
from the house god.
So, if we can't cut the threads,
we'll have to stop them
at the source. Right.
Wait, and that's the altar?
There are so many kyoshi.
We'll have to destroy
the whole thing!
Okay. Let's go.
[ANOTHER scoffs]
Do you think
it will be that easy?
Um, what's your
goal here, exactly
-[ANOTHER] Hmm?
-None of this makes sense to me.
I mean, why get us involved?
How are we a part of your plan?
If there was a giant machine
in front of you,
wouldn't you want to switch it
on just to see what it does?
-Huh?
-That's how I feel
when it comes
to surprising someone!
I wanted to see
the look on your face!
The humans up there would panic
if I were to try it,
but surprises are so much fun!
And that's all this is?
[ANOTHER]
Mm-hmm.
[ARATA] So he's basically
a child pulling a fire alarm.
He's having fun
fulfilling his curiosity.
What kind of Another
is this, anyway?
Come on. Who are you, really?
[ANOTHER]
I'm your friend, Coyote.
I'm glad we've finally
cleared that up.
Back then, you were calling me
a "black fox,"
which I've always thought
was extremely rude.
[whimpering]
[MALE AGENT 1]
I shouldn't even be doing this!
I'm just an admin guy!
Where are the cops?
It's game over, man!
[WOMAN] This could be
an opportunity for you.
Weren't you saying recently
that you wanted
a more advanced position?
[MALE AGENT 1]
I was wrong okay!
Okay that's it. We're done!
-[grunts]
-Nice work!
All that's left now
is the Shinjuku entrance.
[MALE AGENT 1] Holy crap!
Do we have to go through them?
[moans]
You see that?
There it is.
[ARATA]
Let's go.
[ALL gasp]
They're young girls.
If the threads are coming from
their mouths, then that means--
[COYOTE]
Surprise!
They're the altar!
-You found it!
-Huh?
You said you had
to destroy the altar
to stop the kyoshi.
What are you waiting for?
Go ahead and kill them!
So, tell me, Seimei.
What are you going to do?
Threads?
That's one way
to control kyoshi.
But I've heard there's several.
♪
Those threads supply
Yin energy to their bodies.
So, we just have to cut them.
[WOMAN]
Right, but with what?
This is from Suzu's shrine.
A knife. I think it'll work.
[WOMAN]
All right. Got it.
Get ready to break through!
-Right!
-Huh?
♪
How did they become the altar?
[KYOICHI] That uniform.
She's from the
Osen Girls' Academy?
[ARATA]
You know them?
[KYOICHI] No,
but they were on a list
of missing people.
Does this mean
he kidnapped them?
I'm not the one who took them
from their homes.
The only thing I did
was make the altar.
A friend of a friend
is a soul-hoarding demon.
He loves to collect young girls,
so I made him a little bargain.
A demon kidnapped the girls
and gave them to him.
He says they made a trade.
That makes sense. It's all
starting to come together.
[COYOTE] So, what are you
going to do, Seimei?
If you destroy the altar,
the kyoshi will stop moving.
But if you don't kill
these sweet, innocent girls,
the kyoshi will continue
killing people out there.
How sad.
And what if they go after you
and your friends next?
[scoffs] He's saying whatever
he can to piss me off.
[THEO gasps]
Disgusting!
Shit! There's too many of them!
Stay back!
Kanoichi!
[COYOTE]
Save a few and many will die.
Or save many by killing a few.
Now, what will it be?
You don't have much time left.
[breathing heavily]
Hey! Don't you dare try to play
negotiation games with me!
[COYOTE gasps]
I am not stupid enough
to fall for that!
Both options are awful,
and I don't have to pick either!
You're counting on the fact
that most people
would choose
the smaller sacrifice,
which means
it's the wrong answer.
I'm saving the girls
and all my colleagues,
and everyone's going home alive!
Don't try that crap again!
[laughs]
I've never seen anyone
threaten an Another before.
Nice. Well said.
Ah! So, that's your answer?
Let me know
if you change your mind.
-Sakaki!
-How are they so strong?
These are teenagers, right?
I'll ask you again, Seimei.
Are you willing to kill
these teenage girls?
-[crashing]
-[gasps]
[KYOSHI moaning, growling]
Or would you rather
let them kill your friends?
Stop it!
This has nothing
to do with them!
-Oh?
-If you're trying to upset me,
then just focus on me!
You really want
to see me surprised?
This is what it looks like!
Leave everyone else out of it!
What do you want from me?
To be honest with you,
I didn't mean for it
to go this far.
It's been a long time
since we've seen each other,
but you're acting
like a stranger
who doesn't even know me.
And you're refusing to say
my name for some reason.
What are you talking about?
So, I guess I just
kept going to see
if anything would
cause you to say it.
Oh! It's the name you gave me.
You're the only one
who called me that.
Please say my name
one more time,
and I'll promise
to save everyone.
What? A-a name?
You have got to be kidding me!
[ARATA] He's threatening me
with people's lives?
All for some validation?
He still thinks I'm Seimei.
[KYOICHI]
M-Miyako!
[ARATA]
Sakaki! Theo!
What is his name? Think!
-[growling]
-[AKANE gasps]
Akane, no!
[gunshot]
[BOTH gasp]
Looks like we made it here
just in time!
[MALE AGENT 3]
Everyone get back!
[moaning]
[steam hissing]
Are you okay?
We heard
Shinjuku needed backup
and rushed over.
[sirens wailing]
[moaning]
It's not stopping them?
The only way
we're gonna end this
is to cut off their life source.
Do you know where that would be?
Underground, probably.
I think the Shinjuku guys
were on their way down there.
But I haven't heard
from them in a while.
[ARATA] Come on, think.
What could it be?
[COYOTE]
I'm your friend, Coyote.
Back then you were calling me
a "black fox,"
which I've always thought
was extremely rude.
[ARATA] Didn't Grandpa say
something about that?
Seimei and black fox
sound familiar.
[YOUNG ARATA]
A yokai?
Yes, that's right.
Seimei commanded them.
He commanded many yokai
when he was still around.
I remember.
Okay.
It was just a story.
Seimei named his yokai friend
and refused to treat him
like a servant.
He named him after
a black fox he knew
who had deep, golden eyes.
The name was...
Kohaku!
[COYOTE gasps]
♪
A-ha! Thank you, Seimei!
Thank you for saying my name!
The one you picked out
just for me!
Huh?
♪
[KYOICHI groans]
[KYOICHI]
Is it over?
[MALE AGENT 1]
What's happening to them?
Someone must have found a way
to stop the Yin energy.
And we're still alive.
That's quite a relief.
[SENDA]
Good job!
Best part is everyone survived.
Extra special thanks
to Chiyoda Ward
for jumping in to help.
It was nothing.
You didn't have to bust out
the police helicopter.
I may not have power,
but I do have connections.
We're so grateful for your help
in getting Suzuka's hair back.
We couldn't have done it
without you.
Thank you very much.
But this means we're even
for the use of Miyako's skills.
[WOMAN] All right,
let's get out of here.
Hey! Don't run off so fast!
[chuckles awkwardly]
Well, looks like
we managed to keep it
from getting out of hand
for the most part.
Thank you, sir.
How do you know him?
[THEO]
He's a detective specializing
in Another incidents.
I heard you even found
the missing
high school girls down there.
Those Anothers, am I right?
Always up to no good.
Oh, by the way,
I'm free to handle the report
for this on my own,
if that's all right with you.
That's more than all right.
I'm pretty sure "four missing
high school girls
discovered in a creepy facility
from World War II"
is out of my wheelhouse.
And probably more than
any government employee
should handle.
Stop brown-nosing me.
Can I at least count on you
to help me put together
a convincing story?
I don't see why not.
-[MALE AGENT 2] Yokoyama, sir?
-What is it?
We finished making the calls.
The girls are safe.
They were picked up
in an ambulance.
[YOKOYAMA]
Good job.
Now we just have
to come up
with a way to explain this.
I guess we could always say
there was another gas leak.
But you just used that.
[YOKOYAMA]
Unexploded shell, then?
[MALE AGENT 2]
The Ichigaya crew will make
another complaint.
A detective specializing
in Anothers?
That's pretty cool.
[KYOICHI] It's better in theory
than in practice.
It's not like they can arrest
invisible Anothers
or put them on trial
or anything like that.
Mainly, their job is coming up
with a plausible story
that the victims
can understand.
More like offering
peace of mind.
Yeah. That's helpful.
Oh, hey, Arata.
I'm sure we're all dying
to know here.
What is that thing that's
floating behind you right now?
Oh, well.
He's the one who stole
all those missing items.
Seimei's friend, apparently.
He goes by Coyote, I think.
[SENDA]
You think?
Do I need
to introduce myself formally?
Because to be honest,
I'm not interested
in being called any other name
than the one you gave me.
However, most people
who are privileged
to serve me call me this:
Huehuecóyotl.
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
So... that's what
he just said.
Huehuecóyotl?
Huh?
[THEO]
Huehuecóyotl.
He was the god of music
and dance in the Aztec religion.
But he was also known
as a great trickster god,
causing fights between man
and their gods.
He created chaos and sowed seeds
of murder for his own amusement.
[ARATA]
Are you sure he was a god?
[THEO]
Yes! God of disaster!
If something like that
is haunting you,
you could be exiled
from this country!
Well, that's rather rude.
And I'm not some
murder connoisseur.
I dabble occasionally.
[ARATA]
Get off me!
How fascinating.
Being chosen by a chaos god.
-[ARATA shouting, indistinct]
-You okay?
He told us how he found
the missing girls.
He said he made a trade
with a demon.
A friend of his.
It's been over ten years now,
but I finally have a clue
about my sister.
As to where
she could possibly be.
I said get off of me!
I'm serious,
leave me alone!
Aw, you don't have
to be so cold, Seimei!
Yeah, about that.
My name is Arata Miyako!
Quit calling me Seimei!
♪
My name is Abe no Seimei.
You may only call me Seimei.
-Do you understand?
-Do you understand, Kohaku?
Yup! I got it! Arata!