[SENDA]
His whole team?
Well, that's unfortunate,
but I'm sure Kanoichi did
what he could.
After all, his plan
was good enough for you, right?
I'm sorry? No, I don't think
we can do that.
We sent Miyako there,
but Kanoichi told him
to stay out of it,
so that's that.
With all due respect, we've got
our own work to complete.
I can't just lend
my subordinates
to mop up your mess.
I understand they're in danger,
but I'm afraid
there's nothing we can do.
It's outside
of our jurisdiction.
Of course, if that area ended up
being turned over to us,
we may be able to help you out.
Best of luck.
[sighs]
[cell phone buzzing]
[THEO] The whole cocoon
operation was wiped out?
What happened?
[FAIRIES]
She's mad, she's mad,
she's really mad!
-You stupid human jerks!
-Ow!
Manari's angry!
Our offerings!
They are gone!
You people made the
Silkworm Princess super angry!
Now we'll all have to leave
our home because of you!
[FAIRIES]
You dummies!
What offerings
was she talking about?
Uh! Did you say "offerings"?
Is that why they looked so mad?
[ARATA]
Yeah, pretty sure.
Crap, this is serious!
Those cocoons were going
to be turned
into offerings for a god!
For a god?
[cell phone buzzing]
[SENDA]
I see.
Tell me, Arata,
have you ever heard of deities
known as Oshira-sama?
-[ARATA] Huh?
-They're silkworm gods.
I'd rather be stuck
dealing with demons.
Right, demons are dangerous,
but they can be exorcised.
Gods, on the other hand though.
They can be a real handful.
And when they get mad, they
start throwing around curses.
[ARATA]
Curses?
[THEO] I doubt we get off
with just a curse after this.
Worst case scenario,
they become tatarigami,
and then we're really screwed.
Gods can be appeased
with rituals.
We can usually pull one off
before things get too bad.
But the rituals can be hard
to carry out correctly,
and it's not like
we can just...
-[THEO] Don't tell me!
-Yeah.
Our friends from
City Hall need us.
They foolishly made
a god angry.
And only the Ears
of Sand can help.
Why the hell would
you agree to that?
It's on the verge
of becoming a tatarigami!
[SENDA sighs]
-[ARATA] Okay. I'll do it.
-Huh?
It'll be fine.
-Seriously?
-Honestly, I'm terrified,
but things will only
get worse unless I go.
If there's anything I can do,
anything at all, I'm in.
[THEO groans]
♪
Are you sure? No doubts?
None.
[SENDA] All right.
You pull this off,
and City Hall
will owe us a solid.
[ARATA]
Right!
[SATORU] Of course
the brood mother was nearby.
I got careless.
This Kekkaiseki
lets me kill Anothers
with my own hands.
You're no different
from any other bug,
just vermin to be crushed.
[chitters]
If you're actually trying
to talk to me, don't bother.
You're staying right there.
You've hurt people.
You've wrecked this place.
Now it will become your grave.
When will you accept
that you can't win?
This world belongs to us,
Another, not your kind!
Your time ended long ago,
and our era...
is now!
[shrieks]
Please don't!
You have to stop!
Whatever you came here to do,
you're too late.
[grunting]
-I told you to back off!
-You fool!
[ARATA]
Don't hurt her anymore!
"Hurt her?"
It's not a person. It's a thing.
A dangerous Another
that needs to die.
Don't interfere!
You're just looking
for an excuse to kill her!
Your hatred isn't helping here,
it's making things worse!
[SATORU]
I'm sick of this.
Then why don't you sit back
and let me do my job?
What. Your job?
[cell phone buzzing]
Who would be calling right now?
[KYOICHI]
Must be something important.
[SATORU]
Huh?
The Shinjuku Ward guys?
[buzzing continues]
Kanoichi here.
[on phone] Hey there, it's Senda
from the Shinjuku Ward Office.
Why would you call
on the emergency line?
[SENDA] Because you made this
an emergency.
You should take care
of your crew
and let my boys handle
the Another.
[SATORU] The Metro office
has jurisdiction over this,
so stay out.
You see, not any more.
-[SATORU] Since when?
-Just now,
when your bosses at City Hall
gave up their jurisdiction
over the stadium.
The Shinjuku Ward Nocturnal
Community Relations Division
will be running
the show from here.
Impossible.
Who authorized that?
[SENDA] The Tokyo Nocturnal
Special Ordinance Committee.
-Member Zero.
-Ah! The governor of Tokyo?
So you can stay as long
as you're willing to do
what we tell you.
But you're done making
our jobs harder, am I clear?
That arrogant fool.
Well, you gonna
make yourself useful?
Can you, even?
You need to let her
go immediately.
I'm going to negotiate.
[grunts softly]
Princess Manari.
Seimei? Hello.
Again we meet, after so long.
Have you something to say to me?
We've wronged you.
I'm here to apologize
on behalf of humankind.
[chuckles]
Am I to take solace
in these words?
Nothing you could say or do
could ever redeem your kind.
You lashed out in fear,
as humans always have,
and you doomed us all.
You've slaughtered
half of my children.
My precious little ones
are perishing in fire
before my eyes.
What a monstrous thing
you've done,
and for what?
This atrocity will be felt far
beyond the walls of this nest.
The young ones you've murdered
were to craft offerings
to the gods.
The cocoons you've burned were
to be spun into the finest silk.
Even if I had the number
of cocoons needed
to produce silk now,
there aren't enough
to spin it into thread.
There is no setting
this right, human.
The festival at Izumo is nigh,
and I have no offering.
For the sin of denying
the gods their silk,
they in turn shall deny us
the power of the sun.
And so, when winter falls
upon this land...
I'll die.
You've wronged me!
No, you've killed me!
Do you understand now?
Your kind words
are worth nothing.
I will have your lives!
For each of my children
who burns,
so shall one of yours!
You'll atone for this
through their deaths!
Humans, if I should fall,
my hatred will foul
the very earth itself.
My rage will poison
the very air you breathe!
That miasma is insane!
Is she becoming a tatarigami?
I'll do it. I'll...
I'll take you!
[MANARI gasps]
And spin the silk, too!
Manari, nobody has to die!
You want to take me
to the festival?
[ARATA]
Yes.
[cackling]
One human to do
the work of so many gods?
No, I can't do it alone.
But I don't have to.
[MANARI]
Your friends would spin my silk?
[scoffs]
♪
Should we fail
to arrive in time,
you must know the fate that
will befall this land, humans.
[ARATA]
We do.
Then I shall wait.
[MEN groaning]
[SHIMIZU]
Hey! Wake up! Hey!
[groans]
[coughing]
[KYOICHI]
You want us to spin the silk?
It makes sense,
but can we really get through
all these cocoons by dawn?
[THEO] Did you come up
with a plan, Arata?
Kind of.
Or at least an idea
for a plan, I think.
[THEO]
Uh. You think?
I'm going to go work on it.
You guys work on the thread!
[THEO]
Hey, hold on!
Remember,
we're on a tight deadline!
[ARATA]
Got it!
How the hell are you people
acting like this is normal?
Well, we should get to it.
Let's go!
♪
All right, Senda, I'm here.
[SENDA]
Thanks for coming.
I know it's a long drive
from Kudanshita.
Can we skip the pleasantries?
Right, take care
of the second floor stands.
♪
This is something else, right?
It seems like every agent
in Tokyo is here right now.
I'm holding the silk
of the gods in my hands.
[YAMASHIRO]
What time is dawn, again?
I think it was around 6:02.
[YAMASHIRO]
So, we've just got half an hour.
Done. Lights up.
Don't let your guards down
for a second.
It's still a dangerous Another!
[THEO] Seriously, what is he
still freaking out for?
Makes sense,
with his mindset.
His mindset is the reason we're
all here cleaning his mess.
♪
[rumbling]
It's moving!
Damn it, I thought
we had till dawn.
Talk about worthless.
Ears of Sand.
-[whooshing]
-Huh?
[AGENTS murmuring]
What's this? More of them?
♪
I brought some help!
We've got more hands now!
Oh, no way. You lunatic.
Did you really recruit
more Anothers to help us?
[ARATA]
Just trust me.
Okay, you guys! Let's do it!
-Hmm.
-Right.
-Team. Let's get to work!
-[ANOTHERS] Yeah!
[ANOTHERS chattering]
Hey!
This is madness.
You expect-- Huh?
If Arata says
his plan will work,
then we believe him.
Hey, thanks. Yuki?
-Huh?
-Meow.
[grunts softly]
I've got no issue.
The brass might want
an explanation.
Yeah, good point.
[TAROUBOU] I'm not obligated
to help you people.
I can't see why I should.
You're the ones who burned
Princess Manari's cocoons.
This is your problem.
The blame falls on us.
There's no denying it.
We screwed up.
But we can't undo it.
If the princess becomes
a tatarigami,
many Anothers
will lose their homes.
And I don't want that to happen.
I can't let all of you pay
for our mistakes!
I know I have no right
to ask you for help.
But I don't think that
there's any other way.
Please, Taroubou.
I'm begging you,
for everyone's sake!
Please help us, just this once!
[TENGU 1]
What do you guys think?
He's not wrong.
We're all in trouble
if the princess
can't get
to Izumo by dawn.
[TENGU 2]
Yeah, but I don't know.
Why bother?
Even if we help
them out this time,
they'll never learn
their lesson.
Maybe.
But if we don't help
the humans,
we risk giving up our home.
[TENGU 1]
You've got a point.
-[TAROUBOU] All right.
-[ARATA gasps]
♪
[TAROUBOU]
Get everyone ready to move out.
Seimei and I will be right back.
[ARATA screaming]
[TAROUBOU] You're going to need
all the help you can get.
Adiel can lend a hand too.
[ARATA]
Huh?
This is my way of repaying
your favor, Seimei.
Sorry, wrong name.
Arata Miyako.
Can I call on you again
when I'm in a bind?
Will you help me out?
Yeah. It's a promise.
Any time!
[SENDA]
Good thinking.
You got us a lot of manpower
on short notice.
[THEO]
Uh... Well, "Another" power.
And we're not
getting it for free.
We made a deal.
The tengu made sure
they're getting something
out of this, too.
[ARATA] I know you said
I shouldn't make deals
with Anothers,
but this just seemed like
too good an opportunity
to pass up.
My Ears. I know they can
get me in trouble
if I'm not careful
about how I use them.
I've learned that Anothers
have different ways
of thinking than we do,
and negotiating can be
as dangerous as fighting.
But at least I can hear
their reasoning,
even if I can't
really understand it.
And after talking with them,
I think that angels and tengu
might have a lot
in common with us.
[THEO]
And by "us," you mean humans?
[ARATA]
Right.
I think we can learn a lot
by communicating
with humanoid Anothers.
Thanks to the Ears of Sand,
I've gotten to hear
how they talk to each other.
They have names
just like we do.
I want to use this power to
help us understand each other
and stop us
from having to fight.
To make peace
between humans and Anothers,
I think that might be
my true calling.
[TAROUBOU]
Arata, come here a second!
[gasping, giggling]
♪
[THEO] Anothers and humans,
working side by side.
I never expected
to see that happen.
Do you people
still not understand
how dangerous that guy is?
Oh, we do.
We actually figured it out
around the time
an Aztec trickster god started
showing up to work with him.
But what can you do, right?
♪
[THEO] I'm starting to think
we might be able to learn
a thing or two from Arata.
He's done a lot, hasn't he?
Maybe so, but I still have
my reservations.
[THEO]
Oh? Yeah, such as?
In the end, humans
and Anothers are different.
We can't do our jobs
unless we respect that.
They're a powerful,
unpredictable force,
something we should fear.
I understand your view.
You did what
you thought was best.
That's fine.
But Arata,
he comes at these problems
from a whole different angle.
I could never have imagined what
we're seeing here right now,
and I really believe
he's the only one
who could've made it happen.
Okay. We're counting on you!
[inaudible dialogue]
♪
We got it all done somehow.
Yeah.
♪
[rustling]
Mediocre work.
I'm sorry for that.
[MANARI]
But I shall honor my word.
You've sinned against me.
You're callous
and eager to destroy.
I will always see humans
in this light.
I know.
Even so...
for your sake
I shall forgive their folly.
Seimei.
[rustling]
♪
Thanks,
and the name's Arata.
Farewell.
-[KOHAKU] Arata!
-Uh...
[screams]
[groaning]
Look at what I made!
Like it? Pretty, huh?
This silk is just fabulous,
don't you think?
Yeah, nice.
I'm glad you like it,
but, you know,
we all could have
died here, right?
That's fun! Anyway,
I'm heading off to Izumo.
-[YUKI] Me, too!
-[BOTH] Yay!
Wait, will they even allow
an Aztec god in there?
I promise I'll get you
some really nice souvenirs!
[YUKI]
The best!
[BOTH]
Bye!
Well, guess we should be
on our way, too.
Thank you
for everything, Taroubou.
[TENGU 1]
See ya!
Thank you so much,
you guys!
No problem!
Until next time, Arata.
♪
[SATORU]
It worked out.
But next time,
it could be different.
A lot of things just happened
to go right for you.
Don't think it will
always be like this.
If you come at the job
like this every time,
you're going to get hurt.
I don't think so,
because I'm not going it alone.
I've got the
Shinjuku Division with me.
And we're good at our jobs.
♪
[SATORU chuckles wryly]
Excellent work, Arata.
Here's a reward.
Great job today, truly.
[chuckles]
Of course, as we expected.
Uh... come on, you guys.
[SENDA]
That was a lot of work.
What do you say we cut loose?
[THEO]
Ooh, yes, let's go!
[KYOICHI] Considering
the time, you think
we should hit up the usual spot?
[SENDA] We should hit up
wherever we feel like.
Metro Division is picking up
the tab, so go nuts!
Oh, and hold onto the receipts.
We'll need to write up
an expense report.
In Kanoichi's name, of course.
[ARATA]
Got it!
[ALL laughing]
[PEOPLE chattering]