Abe no Seimei?
[GRANDPA MIYAKO] Yes. Known as
a powerful onmyoji
from the Heian Period.
And our family, the Miyako clan,
all bear his bloodline.
[YOUNG ARATA grumbles]
I have many stories
about how amazing he was.
Let's see, there was once--
[YOUNG ARATA] It's okay.
I'm gonna go play over there.
[GRANDPA MIYAKO]
Wait. Arata!
Arata!
[OLD TENGU]
No, Seimei!
-[YOUNG ARATA] Huh?
-Seimei!
I know a Seimei when I see one!
It's your blood!
It smells the same as his!
This must be a mistake. I--
-[barks]
-Aah!
[screams, gasps]
[THEO]
Mornin', sunshine.
Well, look who's awake.
Okay... I guess?
[KYOICHI] You collapsed at
the Citizen's Plaza last night.
It's understandable, I guess.
Sounds to me like
you had a busy night.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm head
of the Nocturnal Community
Relations Division.
My name's Senda.
Introducing our boss.
[ARATA]
Oh, it's nice to meet you, sir.
I was planning on making our
introductions tomorrow, but...
Arata Miyako, is it?
So, you've got Ears of Sand,
I've heard.
♪
[THEO]
So, basically,
it's when you can
miraculously understand
a random language
you've never heard before.
We call it
The Ears of Sand!
Does that sound like something
that's ever happened to you
when talking to
a foreign stranger?
-I don't think so.
-[THEO] Interesting.
So it doesn't happen
with human languages, then.
Yet you understand
the Anothers perfectly. Huh.
Looks like you've discovered
an exceptional new member.
Yeah, I know.
[ARATA] So, um, if you can't
understand the Anothers,
how have you been able to deal
with them for this long?
Facial expressions,
mannerisms, patterns.
Same way you might try
with a cat or a dog.
-Huh?
-This is a first.
I've never known anyone
in our line of work
who could hear them.
Unless, well,
I was going to say
maybe before our time,
but I don't think
there are any past records.
[SENDA] I wonder if it has
anything to do
with the way they call you
Abe no Seimei?
Got any idea
what that could mean?
My grandpa said
something about it.
And our family,
the Miyako clan,
all bear his bloodline.
None of us
ever took him seriously.
[SENDA]
Hmm.
Well, since your shift is over,
why don't you go home
and get a little rest?
Have a good night.
[ARATA sighs]
[THEO]
That was weird, wasn't it?
[KYOICHI] Yeah, what's the deal
with that kid?
[SENDA]
Abe no Seimei, huh?
Isn't the exam supposed
to weed out anyone
who had prior relationships
or experiences like that?
Huh?
You're here to investigate?
Well, and to bring a gift.
If we can find out your
connection to Abe no Seimei,
that could help us determine
whether or not
the Ears of Sand are real,
according to Senda, anyway.
[ARATA] Huh?
Okay. Sure.
[GIRL] What's this?
Arata has visitors?
[ARATA]
Oh, hi, Izumi.
New co-workers?
It's a pleasure
to meet Arata's friends.
My name's Izumi.
[ARATA] Her parents own
a great restaurant nearby.
And this is Sakaki.
We work together.
Excuse me, my name's Theo.
His superior. Pleasure.
Hmm?
Superior? Really?
That's right.
Theo's been with us
as long as Chief Senda.
[ARATA]
What? I had no idea!
[THEO] So, you have to do
whatever I say.
[KYOICHI]
Most people are surprised
the first time
he tells them that.
[IZUMI]
Hey, you're doing something
for the government
on the night shift, right?
[ARATA]
Yeah, why?
[IZUMI gasps]
Is it something kinky?
[ARATA]
Uh...
[ARATA] I think all my grandpa's
belongings are still in here.
I haven't opened it
in a really long time.
This brings back
so many memories.
I used to play in here
when my grandparents were alive.
When my family and I moved in
after they passed away,
I just kinda stopped.
[THEO]
Whoa, holy crap!
My parents said you can take
whatever you want.
That's amazing!
Okay, I'm gonna go
check upstairs.
[KYOICHI] I guess we should
at least take all the papers,
Sure. Uh...
♪
It's a cat?
[gasps]
Huh? It stood!
Arata!
[ARATA grunts]
You're back!
I missed you!
-You smell so good!
-[THEO] What's going on?
Uh, it's an Another,
who's obsessed with Arata.
[THEO] Huh?
[KYOICHI]
It has two tails.
A nekomata.
How could you
possibly know my name?
[YUKI]
Don't you remember?
We used to play together
all the time!
[ARATA]
A white cat.
With blue eyes.
-Yuki?
-Yes!
[YUKI] I'm so happy
to see you again, Arata!
[THEO]
Hello!
I could use some help up here!
Why is that nekomata
insanely huge?
Arata. You okay?
[ARATA]
Yeah.
[YUKI] What are you
doing here, Arata?
We came to get a few
of the old books
for a little research.
[YUKI]
You can't do that!
Your ancestors told me
to protect
everything in this storehouse.
And that's what I plan to do,
no matter what.
[ARATA]
Ancestors?
[YUKI] Your grandpa's
grandpa's grandpa.
It goes a very long way back.
Ages. He was my former owner.
You mean,
you've been here that long?
[YUKI]
I have.
But over the last century or so,
you've been the only one
that's been able to see me.
[ARATA]
Poor guy.
So, all this time,
Yuki's been in here alone.
Just protecting the storehouse.
♪
[ARATA sighs]
Why don't you come with us
and watch over the books
from there?
You've gotta be bored
of this place by now.
The grandparents that I remember
would've never wanted you
to spend an eternity
in a dark house like this.
[YUKI]
But...
[ARATA]
Please come.
I want you there.
That okay?
[YUKI]
Arata! I'm so happy!
I was... I was so...
so lonely...
in here all by myself.
I'm sorry, Yuki.
I wish I'd gotten
to you sooner somehow.
Being alone is hard.
♪
[YUKI]
This place is huge!
And there's so much light!
It's nothing like
the storehouse!
I was hoping you'd like it.
-[TAROBO] Hey, over here!
-[ARATA] Huh?
[TAROBO]
Other way. Up.
[ARATA]
Huh?
[TAROBO]
Arata Miyako, right?
[YUKI]
Hold on, you know him?
[ARATA]
Sure. Taro-- Uh?
Those bruises!
What happened?
Well, I got into a fight.
A big one.
Everybody's against my love
for an angel.
Father is always fighting
with her sisters.
To be honest, I'm not sure
what's going to happen now.
But you're different.
You believed in our love.
You rooted for us.
[laughs softly]
And why not?
I thought you two
made a nice couple.
That's nice to hear.
Means more than
you'll ever know.
So, uh... thanks
for your kindness.
Huh?
[YUKI]
You've made me happy, too!
I can finally talk to you.
I've always wished I could.
Yeah. Me, too.
♪
[inaudible]
[MAN] The Anothers are
pretty quiet tonight,
aren't they?
I wish it were
always like this.
Huh? What is that?
A bird?
Can't be, it's way too big.
Is there something
on top of it?
A person?
Good morning, how are you?
Hey there. Welcome back.
Looks like we have
everybody here now.
Which is great
because there's something
we need to deal
with immediately.
On the Shibuya Ward side of
the Shinjuku Imperial Gardens,
someone reported
spotting a kisha.
Hmm? A kisha?
[THEO]
This is what it looks like.
They're Chinese Anothers.
Monstrous birds
that bring disaster.
It's got ten necks
but only nine heads.
Some call it
a nine-headed bird.
Thing is, we've actually
been getting reports
of sightings for a while now.
In January,
it was seen in Kyoto.
February, it was Aichi,
and it just keeps
heading east from there.
It was in Aichi in February?
[SENDA]
Yep. The Izuna incident.
What are you guys
talking about? Izuna?
[THEO]
Hang on. Watch this first.
[MAN]
Do we really have to do this?
[THEO] An Izuna is a type
of weasel Another.
Its tail is made
of a metal so flexible
it's called, "living iron."
-[IZUNA squeaking]
-Many like to use it in rituals.
-[MAN] Is that them?
-[liquid splatters]
Huh?
[gasps]
It-it's blood!
[SENDA]
Is it making sense, Arata?
There was a time
when several Izuna were found
with their tails cut off
in the Aichi Prefecture.
That was the Izuna Incident.
But there's more
to it than that.
[ARATA]
Hmm? The same one as before?
Yeah, and it was seen
very recently.
Your assignment is
to head out to the gardens
and look for traces
of the kisha.
Shouldn't be
too difficult to track,
with one of its necks
bleeding constantly.
[ARATA]
Look at all that blood.
Mission accomplished.
Is this kisha that bad?
Honestly.
[KYOICHI] This blood
on the ground
will excite the Anothers.
If a kisha shows up,
it's only a matter of time
before our
Another troubles multiply.
[ARATA]
Yeah, that is bad.
All we can do is be careful
and collect overtime.
Overtime, and hope that it goes
away as soon as possible.
Couldn't we talk
to it directly?
[BOTH]
Huh?
Well, since I can understand it,
I could ask it to leave?
Maybe it doesn't know
it's causing a problem?
[THEO laughing]
Arata, you can't reason with it.
It's not a person.
[THEO] That's like trying
to explain to a typhoon
that residential areas
are inappropriate places
-to throw tantrums.
-But I--
It's a side effect
of the Ears of Sand.
You have the ability
to understand them,
and that boosts your confidence.
It tricks you into thinking
you can trust them.
What are you going to do when
you ask them politely to stop
and they agree,
in exchange for your life?
[KYOICHI] Human common sense
doesn't translate for them.
You know what would help?
If you researched
the scarier traits
of the Anothers.
Anothers aren't capable
of human common sense. Right.
[FAIRY 1] I guess this means
we can't fly for a while.
[FAIRY 2]
How can someone be so terrible?
[FAIRY 1]
You're right. We'll stay low.
[FAIRY 3] There's no way
we can fight them.
We could be attacked by a cat
or something down here.
Why can't you fly?
[PIXIES]
He found us!
-It's a human. What do we do?
-Let's run!
We'll have to run
if we can't fly!
[gasps]
I know him!
He's the lowest one in the ranks
at Shinjuku City Hall!
-He's the lowest?
-The lowest!
Hey! Listen, you guys!
[KYOICHI]
What's going on over there?
The fairies!
They're all upset about
not being able to fly
for some reason?
We need powder for our wings.
But some strange person
stole all the powder we had.
They were riding on
the back of a giant bird.
I say it was a fancy man
with long hair!
[FAIRY 2] No, it was a woman
with dark hair!
[FAIRY 1] They had the golden
shimmering eyes of a beast!
[ARATA] At least, that's how
the fairies explained it.
So, there was
an Another on a kisha?
That may be where
the problem lies.
Excuse me, guys.
Sorry to ask this of you
when you just got back,
but can you go
to the Kanoichi Bunko?
Why Kanoichi?
All they would tell me
is that they need
Arata's ears
as quickly as possible.
But whatever it is,
it results in them
owing us one.
I'll get you the paperwork.
[KYOICHI] Kanoichi Bunko
Publishing is said to have
basically anything
you'd like to learn
about various eastern magics.
They're an old clan of onmyoji,
and the entire family
is quite skilled
in the crafting
of magical tools.
So they've fused British magic
with Japanese items.
[THEO] Everything they make
is for dealing with Anothers.
Here, read this.
Oh. Thank you.
It sounds like
they were robbed.
Luckily, an Another close by
saw the whole thing
when it happened.
So, I'll bet they want
to use your Ears of Sand
to interpret its report.
[ARATA]
Huh.
Welcome.
My name's Akane Kanoichi.
I'm with the Chiyoda division.
I really appreciate you coming
so far out of your way
to help our branch
with this matter.
Please. You're always doing
so much for us.
[AKANE]
And you must be Arata Miyako,
-is that right?
-Oh, yes!
Everyone's been talking
about your gift.
Even all the way out here
in the Chiyoda ward.
Thank you
for coming here today.
You're welcome.
[door opens]
[ARATA]
Who's that?
Protector and goddess
of the Kanoichi.
[KYOICHI]
Is that a zashiki warashi?
[AKANE]
Yes, you're exactly right.
[THEO] How'd you get her
to agree to be your house god?
Zashiki warashi are supposed
to be impossible to bind.
Yes, I know. We are
very fortunate to have her.
She agreed to stay in accordance
with an ancient contract.
[THEO]
What contract?
[AKANE]
Once every ten years,
it is our duty to cut her hair.
We offer up a dagger made
with the Kanoichi's arts
as part of a barrier.
She told us she would like
to seal away something
beneath the items.
[KYOICHI]
So, you want Arata's help
with something involving
this ritual?
[AKANE] Yes. If we don't get
the stolen hair back,
the seal will be weakened.
-[GIRL] The oni.
-Huh?
The oni is coming.
-The bad oni.
-[ARATA] Huh?
-Oni?
-[gasps] You heard that?
You can understand me, mister?
Uh, yeah.
I'm Arata.
Arata Miyako.
And what's your name?
Hello, Suzuka.
That's a very cute name.
-Akane?
-Yes.
She wants you to know
her nickname.
She'd like us all
to call her Suzu.
You really can understand
what she's saying, can't you?
♪
Okay... Suzu.
[AKANE gasps]
[ARATA]
Now, Miss Suzu.
Can you tell me
who stole your hair?
-Do you know them?
-You can get it back?
[SUZUKA]
I don't think you should.
It was stolen by a beast
hiding in human form.
It's truly a beautiful
and cheerful dark creature.
But it's so... so scary.
[ARATA]
Sounds like it.
Do you know
why they took your hair?
[SUZUKA]
I don't know.
But they said
it would be over very soon.
[YUKI meows]
[meow]
She said it's a "beast
in human form."
-Wow.
-Oh, yeah.
That reminds me of what
the fairies were saying.
FEMALE NEWSREADER:
A theft has been reported
at a Shinjuku
imported goods store.
The police are treating
the situation like a burglary.
The case was reopened after...
Hey, look,
isn't that Koseido?
Have you heard of it?
Well, yeah.
It's technically
an imported goods store
but with the ability to get us
any magical stuff we need.
You know, like goat gallstones,
and mermaid scales,
and burning glass or...
or living iron...
and fairy wing powder, too.
-[ARATA] Uh, Theo?
-Huh...
[THEO]
Give me just a minute.
-Hello, good morning.
-Good morning!
Hey, how's the
dream team doing?
[THEO]
Morning.
You look exhausted.
[THEO] Yeah, I was just
checking on something.
Can you still work,
or do you need to be sent home?
Guys, I'm fine, okay!
Let's get to Hakoneyama.
[SENDA] Right.
Well, there've been
many strange fires
reported at the top
of that mountain.
Wouldn't that be
the fire department's job?
Every time the fire department
or police head out there,
they don't seem
to find anything.
And that means it's our job now.
[ARATA]
I recognize this place.
It's a pretty famous
occult spot, isn't it?
[KYOICHI] Yeah. It was
originally built by the Tokugawa
and was used as
a military base during the war.
I've heard there was also
a hospital built under it.
Well? Learn anything?
[THEO]
Some kind of seal or entrance.
Hold on.
Why is it shining like that?
-[THEO gasps]
-Idiot!
[THEO groans]
Why would you touch something
before you even know what it is?
[cell phone buzzing]
What? I'm pretty busy
right now.
[SENDA] Listen! I just got
a call from the police.
You were spot on, it turns out
it was a bunch of mermaid scales
that were stolen
from Koseido that night.
[gasps]
[THEO]
Dirt from an old grave.
Could it be?
[switch clicks]
[ARATA grunts]
Ow!
-[KYOICHI] Not sorry. You awake?
-Huh?
Yeah.
Where are we?
[KYOICHI]
Probably inside of Hakoneyama.
And judging by
how high that ceiling is,
I'm gonna guess
we're pretty far down.
-Know what else?
-What?
This is why you
never touch anything
without being completely
certain it's safe.
Got that, rookie?
[groans]
I'm so sorry.
-Huh?
-It's Seimei!
Good to see you!
It's been ages.
An Another?
What good timing you have.
The gift I brought for you
is almost finished.
What do you mean? A gift?
[doors opening]
Good, they're moving.
[ARATA]
What's moving?
People?
No. Not quite.
They're moving corpses.
Kyoshi!
[growls]
[ANOTHER] Did I choose the
perfect reunion gift or what?
I hope this brings you hours
of entertainment, Seimei.
[wind whistling]