[ARATA]
According to Kohaku,
Abe no Seimei was an onmyoji
from the Heian era.
He was known for his skills
in both astronomy and astrology.
Kohaku was one
of several different types
of familiars that he used,
and he was the one
who named him.
Supposedly.
So, according to our research,
I would say, yes.
The Miyakos and Abe no Seimei
are in fact related.
-[gasps]
-[SENDA gasps]
Totally called it.
[sighs]
[horn honking]
[KAMATA] The Miyako family
genealogy chart
appears to support
the theory as well.
So, then where did we get
the name Miyako?
It's so different.
They may have changed it
to avoid being found.
That seems to be
a common occurrence
in this business.
You can honestly say
you're sure?
Oh, absolutely.
It just so happens I met someone
who's a direct descendant
and borrowed their library.
They may or may not have left
these important documents
on their desk
when they took off,
and I may or may not have
picked them up
and simply forgotten
to put them back.
Sounds slightly unethical.
This is crazy.
And it looks to me
like your knack of languages
hasn't changed a bit, has it?
Abe no Seimei.
It makes me wonder.
[SENDA]
If it's true? Probably.
Since you're related,
you may have some
of Seimei's
especially strong power
in your genes.
Right.
Do you really
believe that, though?
-[door opens]
-[SENDA] Hmm?
Hey, Kamata.
Here's my sister's paperwork.
[gasps]
Thank you so much!
What's all that about?
Well, the way she'll have
to return to society
is a little odd.
So, we have a decision to make.
Do we wanna be official
and get the
missing persons case dismissed,
or do we wanna take
a more discreet route instead?
Kyoichi's sister
isn't the only one out there.
There are still several others.
And each one of them
went missing
because of an Another.
The question is, has she aged,
even though she still looks 17,
or has she actually remained 17
all these years?
That's where we come in.
You need people on the outside
investigating.
We're more than happy to do it.
Huh.
[SENDA] Be mindful that both
the situations presented
have advantages
and disadvantages.
Right.
[ARATA sighs]
♪
[IZUMI]
Wow! Yes.
That looks amazing
on you, Shiori!
Sure you're not just being nice?
Right?
It looks great.
[chuckles softly]
Okay, I'm convinced.
I'll get it.
[IZUMI]
Good call.
♪
[inaudible dialogue]
Sorry to drag you here.
-It's fine.
-For real, though.
I'm glad that Izumi was able
to help us out.
I have no idea what girls
are wearing these days.
To tell you the truth
neither does she.
You look happy.
How do you feel?
Pretty good.
And I owe this to her.
I was a mean brother.
-So, thank you.
-Huh?
Truly.
You and Theo
helped me out a lot.
What do you mean?
[KYOICHI] It's because of you
that I finally have her back.
I don't know where
any of this goes from here,
but for now...
Well, I'm just happy
I get to make up
for lost time, you know?
Don't forget, she'll be needing
winter clothes soon.
Hope you like shopping.
♪
Thanks for coming today, Izumi.
No problem.
Got a few things for myself.
How's your arm?
Oh, it's fine now.
What about you? You okay?
Huh?
Is your job dangerous?
Izumi.
[IZUMI]
I know, I know.
You can't say exactly
what you do for work,
-but, still.
-[ARATA sighs]
[IZUMI] I mean, are you involved
in a lot of cases like Shiori's?
I'm worried about you.
-[ARATA] Well, don't be.
-Huh?
No need.
My coworkers always
have my back.
I'm fine.
Hmm. Yeah, that's true.
They seem like they know
what they're doing.
They do.
[bird crowing]
[sighs in relief]
Hmm?
[ARATA sighs]
What's wrong, Arata?
Well...
she's scared,
but I guess that's normal.
[KOHAKU] Aren't you
a ray of sunshine today?
[gasps]
-You know why I'm upset!
-Do I?
Don't you think for a second
that I've forgotten about
what you did to Izumi!
What else could I do?
I was helping a friend.
So you do anything your friends
ask no matter what?
That's what friends do, right?
Kohaku?
Listen, um, about that friend,
let's pay them a visit today.
Huh?
[meows]
-[KOHAKU] Let's go.
-[ARATA] Huh?
Where are you two going?
-You're about to find out.
-Hey, wait!
[yells]
♪
[KOHAKU chuckles]
[ARATA] I really hope
you're not taking us
somewhere creepy and weird.
[YUKI] We haven't been
on a walk together
in such a long time, Arata.
I'm assuming if you invited me,
that means you like cats, right?
Sure, but Bastet's
a little scary when she's mad.
-Who's Bastet?
-A very talented cat.
She's a wonderful musician,
but her temper is quite short.
-[cheering in distance]
-[gasps]
Gorgeous. It feels so alive!
Where you going now?
♪
[sighs]
Great.
[KOHAKU]
I love this place so much.
The crowd, the giant stage,
the booming music,
it's all so magical.
You've been here before?
[KOHAKU]
Yes, several times.
You mean, you pay
for tickets to shows?
[KOHAKU]
Woo-hoo!
[ARATA] Guess I should've known
the answer to that one.
♪
[keyboard keys clacking]
[door opens]
[SENDA] I can't believe
you're still here.
You know, you're not required
to move into the place.
It's supposed to be
a harvest moon tonight, right?
I was thinking I might try
harvesting a mandragora.
[SENDA]
Okay, well just don't let
the general affairs
department see you.
If they find out
you're using the office
on a day we are closed,
that could become an issue.
Why are you here?
Well...
Bunkyo Ward
contacted me earlier.
They did? Really?
[SENDA]
Yeah, they wanted to gripe to me
about work on my day off.
I'm too old for that drama.
[THEO] Right. So what is it
they're upset about?
[SENDA]
Hmm. It's ridiculous.
You know about the Another
that's following
Arata around, right?
[THEO sighs deeply]
Yeah, that Coyote one
that he calls Kohaku?
[SENDA]
That's the one.
Turns out,
he's been wandering
around Bunkyo Ward.
They say it's causing
quite the uproar
with the local Anothers.
He's got them all
in a tizzy over it,
which is never good.
[THEO sighs in annoyance]
[THEO] Of course that's gonna
piss them off.
He's an Aztec god!
He's on a whole other level
than most Anothers,
and they're jealous.
[SENDA]
That's just the half of it.
They say Arata's
been seen with him.
Sounds to me like he's just
taking a walk, though.
[THEO] So now it's okay
to just go on evening strolls?
We have to find a way
to stop him somehow.
He can't parade around
with the god of disaster
and allow him to pop up
on anyone's doorstep
-whenever he wants! Sheesh!
-[cell phone vibrating]
[SENDA] Relax, we don't have to
jump on this right away.
Huh?
The least we can do is
let the guy enjoy his day off
without any lectures.
Hello?
Yes, this is Senda
from the Nocturnal Division.
How can I help?
Of course I remember you.
[YUKI and COYOTE laughing]
[SENDA]
You're saying Coyote
is in the Taito Ward now?
Right. I understand.
[laughter continues]
Guys, come on.
-[yelling excitedly]
-[laughing]
[KOHAKU]
Arata, get in here, it's fun.
-[BOTH laughing]
-[ARATA] No thank you.
You guys need to get down
from there.
♪
Huh?
[inaudible dialogue]
[YUKI]
Arata, I'm getting hungry.
[sighs]
It is getting pretty late.
How much farther
are we going, Kohaku?
We're headed east, but how far?
That, I don't know yet.
Things are so different now,
it's hard to tell.
Nothing here
looks like it used to.
[ARATA]
Uh... Huh?
[KOHAKU] We might be
able to get a better gauge
if we go up there.
[ARATA]
Why would we do that?
-[KOHAKU] Come with me, Arata.
-[ARATA] Where are you going?
[KOHAKU chuckles]
Where's your sense of adventure?
Wait. No. No, thank you.
Okay, this is how I die,
I guess.
Being dropped by an Aztec god
while holding a cat spirit.
-[YUKI] Arata, look.
-Huh?
Uh...
You've finally made an effort
to travel this way, have you?
You should know, every inch
of land beyond this point
belongs to my master
and you are not allowed
to proceed.
[caws]
[YUKI] We aren't trying
to proceed anywhere!
He forced us to come with him!
Don't drag us into this!
I don't want to hear it,
Fatty Catty!
Save it for the mice!
Did you call me fat?
I dare you to call me that
one more time!
Okay, sure, maybe I haven't been
exercising lately,
and Arata's furniture
is obscenely comfortable at home
and work, and I enjoy
premium brand food!
But you will not call me fatty!
You wish to fight?
Very well.
[caws]
[YUKI screeches]
Deja vu?
I feel like
I've already seen this.
Well, it does happen
every morning.
[screeching, cawing continues]
[YUKI/ANOTHER]
Back off!
I'm not your average
morning crow!
I am Yatagarasu!
And I was chosen to guide
Abe no Seimei
through the land
of Musashino!
Do you see these magnificent
velvety black wings?
Seimei loved the color so much
that he gave me a special name
that was inspired
by its beauty.
Clear your mind and ears
that you may celebrate
my nobility and dignity
by learning
my glorious name!
Kuro.
Is that a unique name?
No. It's pretty standard.
This name was a gift
from the great Seimei himself!
Wait just a cocka-doodle-do.
You understand me, human?
Yes. Every word.
Wha... Uh... Oh!
So then, you're Seimei?
I'm so sorry, please forgive me!
My eyesight is terrible
at night,
and no one had the courtesy
to tell me you'd returned!
I truly had no idea!
If I had known, it would have
been my pleasure
to welcome you
with open wings--
I'm not Seimei.
I'm Arata.
Arata Miyako.
Uh...
But I'm curious.
Are Seimei and I that alike?
Oh, well, to be honest,
you're asking a bird
whose eyes aren't
so sharp anymore.
Well, I am a cat,
and I can see just fine!
So this crow was a friend
of Seimei's, huh?
That's perfect.
We need a favor.
Can you lead us to his garden?
His garden? What for?
[KYOICHI]
Yes.
Yeah, that sounds great.
Thanks.
Did you get everything
they just said
on the phone typed out?
Yeah, I got enough.
I gotta say, we are dealing
with one strange human being.
He sympathizes with demons
and sides with Anothers
like a total weirdo.
Then takes nightly strolls
with disaster gods.
How does he sympathize
with demons?
Wow.
The disappearances are
confirmed kidnappings.
All by a devil called Azazel.
Which means we can officially
determine that the case
of the missing high-school girls
has been solved, right?
I hope it's that easy.
[SENDA] I understand
a case of this level
was an unfair task to handle
on your own while I was gone.
-I apologize.
-No worries.
But still, it must feel great,
to have your sister back.
All because of you.
It never would've happened
if you hadn't
recruited me that day.
[chuckles]
You, too, Arata.
Thank you for lending us
your Ears of Sand.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It was just very tough
to listen to.
The hysteria in
the young girls' screams.
Azazel sobbing,
drowning in his own despair.
I can't get it out of my head.
The sounds of their pain.
I feel bad for Azazel.
I can't help it.
He's the same one who kidnapped
your friend, right?
Yeah, but...
if you'd heard it,
I think you'd feel
the same way that I do.
The Ears of Sand.
I said they were
a double-edged sword,
and I was right.
[KYOICHI] Understanding
the Anothers means
he's able to sympathize
with them,
something we never could.
[THEO] I just hope they don't
get him killed him someday.
[KURO]
We're getting close!
We can take a right up ahead!
[YUKI]
You're too excited about this.
[KURO]
No one asked you, Fat Cat!
Don't you got a mouse to chase?
[YUKI]
Call me fat again, I dare you!
[KURO] I have been waiting
for Master Seimei
to come back
for way too long!
I'll be so overcome with joy
to guide him again
that I'll probably molt
when I see him!
Oh, yeah?
I never stopped serving him.
I protected his ancestors'
treasures for several lives!
-So, Seimei's here?
-Yes, he is.
I can't believe it's been
one thousand and twenty years!
Wait. Maybe twenty-one?
What difference does it make?
Are we there yet?
Where you were taking us?
Wait a minute.
What have you been doing
all this time?
Seimei's been gone
for quite a while.
I'm confused.
Where did you go?
Did you ever...
[KOHAKU]
Here we are.
[KURO] This is it.
I'd recognize it anywhere!
This is Master Seimei's garden!
[ARATA]
How did we get here?
[YUKI]
It's so beautiful!
[BOTH gasp]
♪
I ceased to exist.
[ARATA]
Huh?
[KOHAKU] You asked
where I was when you...
Pardon me, where I went
for all those years
when Master Seimei went away.
I simply didn't exist.
My name, you see.
♪
You are the one
who gave it to me,
and you're the only one
who knew it.
Therefore, without anyone
to call me by my name,
Kohaku did not exist.
It was only when you called me
by that name again, that I...
Well, now you've got me curious.
If you were to give me
a name, Arata,
do you know
what it would it be?
Think about it for a moment.
Huh?
A name only you would call me.
One that only you ever heard.
What would I name you?
♪
The funny thing about that is...
I wouldn't.
You'd still be Kohaku to me.
[KOHAKU gasps]
[ARATA]
And since "Kohaku" means amber,
it makes sense
with the color of your eyes.
Don't you think?
♪
Yes.
That's exactly right!
Thank you!
I'm going home now!
Huh?
Hey, wait! Kohaku!
Where are you going?
Wait!
Does that mean he's gone now?
Strange that he would
leave me here.
[YUKI]
Well, what are you gonna do now?
Guess we should go, too.
Wow. Look at the time.
It's well past midnight.
Now let's see.
The closest station is.
That would be Aoto Station.
But, unfortunately,
the last train leaves
at 11:57 on weekends.
[gasps]
You really are a guide!
Master Seimei is no fool,
and he would only
ever hire the best!
Crap! The last train
already left!
How much is a taxi
to Kagurazaka?
About 6,000,
not including night fees.
[gasps]
There you go guiding again!
I said Master Seimei
only hires the best,
and I take my job seriously!
I don't have that kind of cash.
Good morning.
How is everyone?
[KYOICHI]
Morning.
[sighs]
Six thousand yen.
What's all that?
[KYOICHI]
Reports, of course.
About what?
The rokurokubi at Yushima
in Bunkyo Ward went missing?
[KYOICHI] Plenty of damage
caused by the kappas
at Shinobazu Lake.
Lots of Tanuki rummaging through
the trash bags at Ueno Park.
In the Katsushika Ward,
okurijochin were witnessed
lighting up
all the streetlamps at night.
Wanna know why?
Because you thought
it was a great idea
to take old Coyote
out into the city.
Seeing the god of disaster tends
to freak out the Anothers.
They panic
and become destructive
while trying to hide.
[THEO]
The phone didn't stop ringing
the entire night.
So, have fun.
We're gonna pass
those babies on to you.
I'm going to bed.
Hold on, don't fall asleep yet!
I was the one who was dragged
around the city
and forced to pay
6,000 yen.
Holy crap.
What is the matter
with you guys?
This is all his fault.
I get why they call him
the god of disaster!
[KYOICHI]
What are you saying?
♪
[people chattering]