♪
[AZAZEL]
I hadn't realized back then,
that humans were fragile
and could die so easily.
But as long as I have a vessel,
you can be with me again.
You can smile at me again.
[THEO]
So there's some vile demon
that goes around
collecting women?
You're sure that's
what Huehuecóyotl said?
Yeah. An Another shrouded
in black sand.
That's probably the very one
that took your friend,
and the girls in Toyama Park.
Not to mention,
Kyoichi's sister.
And, speaking of Kyoichi,
you tried to use Arata
to get information on this
Another?
-Yeah.
-You're willing to negotiate
with Huehuecóyotl
and the Another?
But, he told me he wasn't
planning on negotiating!
He lied to your face!
The fact that he got
you involved proves
he is willing to do
whatever it takes.
[KYOICHI]
He's right.
If it means giving up an arm,
I'll do it.
-Wha-- ?
-And you didn't approach me,
because you knew
that I'd try to stop you.
You're not hard to read.
[KYOICHI] I've been searching
for her for seventeen years
and I finally found a clue.
I couldn't pass
this opportunity up,
no matter what the cost.
-[THEO] Idiot!
-[tires screech]
[THEO]
Then you should have come to me.
Right from the beginning.
I would have helped
in some other way,
without resorting
to manipulating Arata.
You moron!
[car whooshes by, honks]
I don't exactly feel
great hearing that I was used.
It makes me a little sick,
to be honest.
But I don't want an apology.
If you did apologize,
I know I'd forgive
you immediately,
since you've done
so much for me.
Instead, you owe me one.
[KYOICHI]
Got it.
[light clicks on]
[footsteps]
-[slaps]
-Now then.
Time to track down
the entrance to Hell.
We're starting with
zero clues, though.
Why do you say that?
We've got plenty of clues.
Just think about it.
[keys clicking]
[beeping]
These are all the cases
involving missing
teenage girls so far.
Now, we just have
to narrow it down.
How do we do that?
[THEO] That sand affects the
gravity of the space around it.
So for starters, if we put in
data on gravity fluctuations,
we'll have an idea of the range
in which the Another operates.
You can do that? Really?
Yeah, it's new.
I was curious about
the black sand, myself.
So I spent a lot of time
looking into it.
-You did?
-[computer beeps]
[THEO]
All right, that should help!
[KYOICHI] So, theoretically,
these are the paths
traveled by the black sand
Another? Hmm.
[ARATA] And there's one part
where it's concentrated.
Yeah.
I'm willing to bet
that this is where
its hideout is located.
[ARATA]
But that's still a big area.
Try deleting
the oldest incidents
from the collected data set.
[THEO]
Aye-aye.
[keys clicking]
So, uh, since we're looking
for a demon and all,
is there anything
demon's don't like?
[KYOICHI]
Where are you going with this?
You know.
Like how cats hate baths?
My cat won't step foot in water,
even though it's an Another.
Something they don't like.
'Kay.
If we're right about
it being a demon,
we can safely remove
areas near churches.
And any place with
a dense angel population.
Let's try it.
Just gotta search for
and apply that data.
There.
-First, areas around churches.
-[beeping]
[THEO]
Second, areas where angels live.
There're only four spots left!
Huh? Can you zoom in on this?
-[THEO] Sure.
-[beeping]
A school? Wait a second.
Don't tell me!
Each spot's near
an all-girls' high school!
[ARATA] When you think about it,
those are the perfect
locations for this thing,
aren't they?
[THEO]
Yeah. There's no better place
to find its preferred prey,
I guess.
[ARATA]
Sakaki.
Kohaku said this would all be
over tomorrow morning.
Right. There's little time.
Let's visit them all.
There's only four. It's doable.
-[THEO] Okay, let's go!
-[ARATA] Right!
♪
[no audible dialogue]
-Keep me updated.
-We're approved!
[THEO] This is the area with the
highest gravitational numbers.
[KYOICHI] Only an hour
and a half until dawn.
Let's split up to
find the entrance.
Wanna give me some spray?
On it.
Miyako. What's wrong?
[KOHAKU]
Oh, come on.
Even if you find
the entrance with that,
you still can't go in.
And plus, I thought I told you
to stay out of this
if you don't want to die.
Or have you changed your mind
and want to perish?
Either way, I'm impressed
you found this place.
Kohaku. I want you to take us
to Izumi right now!
Like I just said,
if I did that, you would die.
You can't say that for sure!
Just help us.
Oh! Well,
I admit, I never thought
about it that way,
but still, where is all of that
self-confidence coming from?
[ARATA]
Don't make fun of me!
Fine. You've actually
piqued my interest now.
I suppose it could be fun
to watch you try
and escape from that obnoxious
guard dog he's got.
-[ARATA] Then...
-Yes, yes, I'll take you there.
Do your best to
make your way out.
It won't be easy,
but it should be entertaining.
To me.
[energy bursting]
Now, it's time for us
to go to Hell.
[ARATA] What's with this place?
It's all doors.
Is this really Hell?
[KOHAKU]
No, Hell is up ahead.
Every one of these doors
is connected to a different
place in the world.
Naturally, one leads to Hell.
Come on, let's hurry.
Hey, Kohaku.
[KOHAKU]
What? Tired already?
[ARATA] No, but we've been
walking a while.
-Are we almost there?
-[KOHAKU] Almost.
Azazel is just up ahead.
Azazel? You mean the demon?
[BOTH]
Azazel?
Uh, you know that name?
Yeah, it's one
of the biggest there is!
He used to be an angel.
But he broke a taboo by falling
in love with a human girl
and turned into a devil.
That's exactly right.
He swore his eternal love
to her, but she passed away,
and now he's trying
to bring her back from the dead.
It's been years now.
[sighs softly]
Who's that? And where am I?
-[SHIORI] Shh!
-Huh?
Be quiet.
[gasps softly]
[IZUMI]
I can't move my left hand.
[energy shimmering]
Finally done.
All her limbs are ready to go.
-And now...
-[BOTH gasp]
[AZAZEL] Don't worry.
It won't fail this time.
Don't worry. It's okay.
Don't worry.
[gasping softly]
[THEO] So the one girl's leg
and the other's voice were...
[ARATA]
Yeah. Apparently, they're like
the parts needed
to bring her back to life.
But it's not
as simple as that,
because a lot of the parts
keep getting rejected.
That's why he kept looking.
That makes sense.
If he could have used anyone,
he would have stopped
after kidnapping
just a handful
of these girls.
Yeah, and what's more,
he didn't care about the ones
that didn't work
or were used already
and gave them to Kohaku.
Which explains
what those girls
were doing in Toyama Park
that night.
Huh?
Flowers?
Huh? Really?
Flowers in a weird place
like this?
Let me see. Is that wolfsbane?
[grunts]
Hold on just a minute!
Is this "guard dog" Cerberus?
Give me a break!
[KYOICHI]
What's wrong, Theo?
[THEO] Wolfsbane blooms
from Cerberus's drool!
This isn't exactly
its natural environment,
so if there's this much of it,
that means Cerberus
has to have been here recently!
-[liquid sloshing]
-[soft growling]
[KOHAKU]
What now?
Will you leave
before you're found?
Or keep pushing onward?
[CERBERUS]
This smell.
It's been so long
since I've had meat.
Where is it?
Meat. Meat!
Where is the meat?
Not just that.
There's the smell of Coyote
and sweet candy, too.
Is that thing Cerberus?
[roaring]
Yes. That's right.
Have fun running!
Have fun what?
[CERBERUS]
Is that you I smell, Coyote?
Oh, crap.
Found it!
Good thing I had this.
It loves sweets!
We can use it to distract it!
Book it!
[panting]
That was actually
a nice little distraction.
-However...
-[growling]
[KOHAKU] You're gonna
need more than that!
We won't last a second
if that thing catches up to us!
[KYOICHI]
We know!
-Great!
-[growling]
[AZAZEL]
Now it's all here.
The arms, the legs, the hair,
the body, everything.
I finally have the parts I need.
She'll be just as she once was.
-My lovely.
-[muffled gasp]
[IZUMI]
Hey!
-[IZUMI cries out]
-[thudding]
[AZAZEL]
All that's left are the eyes.
These are hers.
So I'll be taking them back.
[panting]
[growling]
Incredible! All three of you
are still alive!
[ARATA]
Shut up!
Huh?
Sakaki, over there!
[gasping]
The exit!
[roaring]
-[ARATA yells]
-[KYOICHI gasps]
[KYOICHI]
Theo!
[roaring]
-[exploding]
-That work?
-Not good!
-Theo!
I'll devour you all!
-[roaring]
-Run!
Huh?
You can't have this one.
He's mine, got it?
Now go.
[grumbles]
I guess you win again, huh?
[bubbling, oozing]
-That was close.
-You're so difficult!
I told you it would kill you
if you let it.
Next time, you had
better listen to me.
I can't always step in.
-Kohaku.
-[KOHAKU] Yes?
I honestly never thought the day
would come when I'd thank you.
But, thanks.
It's not like I care
about your little friends.
I just can't have
you dying on me.
[KYOICHI]
You okay?
[THEO] Sorry for screwing up
at the last second, guys.
[KYOICHI]
You're fine. Let's go.
[THEO]
Yeah.
[ARATA]
Izumi!
Izumi, are you all right?
She's fine. She's unconscious,
but she doesn't seem
to be in any danger.
Thank goodness!
Shiori!
-You son of a--
-[gun fires]
[bullet ricochets]
[MALE ANOTHER]
Don't interfere.
[ARATA]
I can't move!
Stay still for a few moments
and I will release you.
Of that, you have my word.
Translate.
He's holding us
so we don't interfere.
[energy shimmering]
[chuckles]
How I've missed you.
[FEMALE ANOTHER whimpers]
[anguished screaming]
[screaming continues]
Again!
You woke me up again!
This body isn't mine.
I hate it!
It feels disgusting.
It's horrifying!
[anguished screaming continues]
She's having
a nervous breakdown.
She says the body isn't right.
Those sounds are really words?
You're kidding me.
[KYOICHI]
Then, she's an Another?
[KOHAKU]
His methods are so ghastly.
Of course she's stopped
being human after such madness.
What's wrong?
Look, it's me, Azazel.
Won't you show me
that beautiful smile?
From when we first met?
[FEMALE ANOTHER screams]
[anguished scream]
You keep putting me
inside these things
over and over
and over again!
It feels wrong.
Disgusting!
[anguished screaming]
[screaming continues]
Why won't you let me sleep?
Release me from this nightmare!
[panicked screaming continues]
I don't know who you are.
-[bones cracking]
-[FEMALE ANOTHER cries out]
[exploding]
-[air whooshing]
-[dissolving]
[pained cry]
I have failed.
Why must something go wrong
at the last moment
every single time?
It's maddening!
[shudders]
What was the problem this time?
[cackling]
This is wonderful!
He's always so unemotional,
and now his face is filled
with tremendous despair!
[laughing]
-[AZAZEL] Why? Why?
-[energy shimmering]
As I promised...
[ALL gasp]
We can move again!
[KYOICHI]
Shiori!
Begone.
There's nothing here for you.
-Bastard!
-Wait!
Just stop for a second
and remember our goal!
To get everyone
out of here safely!
Not to defeat them!
Don't escalate things!
You've already
gotten Arata involved.
Fine.
[grass rustling]
Hey, sis.
Whose voice is that?
Sorry. I can't see.
I don't know what's going on.
Unless that's you, Kyo.
-You can tell?
-You called me sis.
You used to always
call me that.
I may not be able to see,
but I do know my brother.
And another thing,
your voice sounds like Dad's.
[soft sobbing]
I was right.
It is you, Kyo!
I hope you weren't too worried.
Or lonely, all by yourself.
Sorry about that.
[sobs softly]
I wish I could see your face,
after so long.
♪
Huh. These lights.
[SHIORI]
You've gotten so big, Kyo!
And look.
You've grown so handsome
since I last saw you.
-[KYOICHI] Shiori.
-I'm your big sister,
but somehow I've ended up
younger than you.
[KYOICHI] You're safe.
And that's all that matters.
[SHIORI]
Well, it matters a little to me!
Hey. I can move
my hand again, too.
[sighs]
What a relief.
-Huh?
-[IZUMI] Hmm?
I don't get what's going on.
Can you explain it to me, Arata?
[ARATA]
Sure.
[KOHAKU] Oh! That must've have
hurt him quite badly.
He's a pitiful sight.
-[footsteps]
-[KOHAKU] Uh?
Not yet. Not yet.
This is far from over.
Next time.
It'll work. Next time...
[chuckles]
At this rate,
he'll keep this up
for eternity.
Pay it no mind.
He'll continue forever
and despair forever.
A vicious cycle.
That cycle of despair
only serves as proof
of my prior conclusion.
That a happy marriage
to a human girl is impossible.
Grief will always prevail.
Wouldn't you agree, Azazel?
[crowd chattering]
[relieved sigh]
I found you.