[thudding footsteps]
[FEMALE FAIRY]
Over here! Hurry up!
Don't be such a wimp!
[ARATA]
Hold on.
[FEMALE FAIRY] We're going
to have to leave you behind!
You're so slow!
[ARATA]
Can't you slow down a bit?
Some of us don't have wings.
Oh, is that them?
Uh, hi. How are you?
I'm here from the Shinjuku Ward.
[ANOTHER grumbles]
[ARATA]
Haven't seen you before.
Where are you from?
What's your name?
My name. Good question.
Let me think. What's my name?
Sorry, I can't remember
who I am.
[KYOICHI] An Another
that suffers from amnesia?
Strange. Not sure
why you brought him here.
Well, I wanted your opinion
on his condition.
You can't just
bring them here, though.
I didn't think. Sorry.
I can't walk away
and leave it behind.
Though it's been shattered,
broken to pieces.
My beautiful home is gone,
now I have nothing.
Um, he's saying that the statue
where he's been living
has been destroyed,
but he still can't leave it.
Some Anothers require
a kind of home vessel
-to host their spirit.
-A vessel?
Oh, man,
that's gotta be rough,
losing your home,
then not being able
to remember who you are.
[THEO]
This is pointless!
-I'm getting absolutely nowhere!
-Here we go again.
Do you think this means
he wants to have a meeting?
All I can tell
from a piece this size
is that it's from
a very old statue.
And our equipment
isn't very much help.
I'll send a sample of it
to the university for analysis.
[SENDA]
That seems complicated.
I just wish we knew his name.
Fine. I hear what you're saying.
I'll go see if I can find out
his name and type.
[sighs]
I'd send Kyoichi with you,
but he's gotta go
help his sister.
Oh, uh, right.
Today's the big day.
She's finalizing
her post-graduation plans.
Huh? Nice. Congrats.
By the way, I'm a little behind
updating the database
with all this new information.
I'll do it. I'm the one
who brought him here.
Didn't mean to throw you off.
Sure you can handle that?
-[ARATA] Yep.
-That works for me.
Trust him. He'll be fine.
Uh...
Hey, If you're good, I'm good.
Good luck. You've got your work
cut out for you.
[ARATA]
Right. I won't let you down.
[knocking on door]
Huh? Are you okay?
[ANOTHER]
Hmm? Mm.
I'm not sure. Need food.
Oh! Of course you do.
Anything in particular
you'd like to eat?
In particular to eat?
What's in particular?
[ARATA] I mean, what's your
favorite thing to eat?
I do love honey.
Do you have honey?
But will that be enough?
-Yes. Please.
-I can do that!
♪
Here you go.
How do you like to eat it?
On bread or what?
[ANOTHER]
Hmm.
[ANOTHER grunting]
Uh, I'll do it.
Or not.
Wait!
You don't wanna do that!
-[ANOTHER] Oh!
-[bottle clinking]
-[muffled grunting]
-[ARATA] Aah!
Hang on!
I'll look for some napkins!
[sighs]
Rough night there, buddy?
Yeah, you could say that.
I forgot to tell you.
If he's the type of Another
that requires
some kind of vessel,
-that could get complicated.
-How so?
[THEO]
For one, without a vessel,
he has nowhere to go.
-Oh.
-But don't worry.
There is a solution.
He'll be fine if we give him
a place to stay.
-Where though?
-[THEO] You got this.
Uh... Huh?
[ARATA yells]
[sighs]
[ARATA]
It'll be fine.
I can take him home
just for today.
♪
Who's this guy?
Well?
Huh?
Oh. He, uh...
[YUKI]
He smells like a bear!
Why would you bring someone
in here who smells so bad?
Why does that
upset you so much?
He's spreading his divine aura
all over the place
and not even trying
to hide it!
[YUKI]
He can't stay here
unless you want me to go crazy!
Guys, this is all
just part of my job.
[YUKI] Fine, then I'll leave!
I'm outta here!
Wait for me, Yuki.
I'll come with you!
Hey, guys!
[groans]
[school bell rings]
[MALE TEACHER]
Hmm.
Tell me something, Mr. Sakaki.
What are your thoughts
on your little sister's
current post-graduation plans?
Uh! Um, Well, I,
I love my big sister,
and little sister,
and I honestly just
want her to be happy.
But I think she should...
He's a little nervous
today, sir.
I'm sorry.
Takes him a sec to warm up.
-Kyoichi?
-Uh, she's right.
Just a reminder, no need
to be nervous, just relax.
-[alarm rings]
-[ARATA groaning]
[moans]
[ANOTHER grunts softly]
[ARATA]
Uh...
Here's breakfast.
Try not to spill it
this time, 'kay?
[ANOTHER]
Hmm.
-[lid pops]
-Uh...
So, I was thinking
we could find you
a new place to live today?
[ANOTHER]
Hmm.
[ARATA]
I'll even throw this in. Deal?
Hell no! He smells!
You think that's enough
for us to take him in?
[FEMALE FAIRY]
Go insult someone else!
[MALE FAIRY]
Yeah, get out of here!
Then, what should I do?
[MALE FAIRY]
You can start by leaving!
♪
[ARATA snoring]
[alarm ringing]
[moaning]
♪
[ANOTHER]
Hmm?
[groans]
[inaudible dialogue]
♪
[inaudible dilaogue]
[alarm ringing]
[ARATA moans softly]
[ringing continues]
[ringing stops]
Hmm, hmm?
♪
[KYOICHI] Maybe it's just me,
but it seems like
that Another's doing
a lot better.
[THEO]
What about that one over there?
[gulping]
Are you gonna be
all right, Arata?
-You tired?
-Sure.
Been walking for days on end.
I didn't know it'd be like this.
Damn right. Believe me,
I know how you feel.
I'm sure you do.
I shouldn't complain.
Hunting for clues is my job,
and the wear and tear
is just part of the package.
With that, I'm off
to find this guy a home.
[ARATA]
Finished eating?
Why don't we check out places
in this neighborhood today?
♪
[ARATA]
A new home, huh?
But what kind of place
would be good for him?
Uh. Oh, no. He's gone!
Okay, there he is.
Thank goodness.
♪
[ANOTHER]
Hmm.
I like the atmosphere
of this one.
I believe it will be
a very worthy home for me.
Hold on! I think
we'd better keep looking!
-[KIO GONGEN] Hey!
-[ARATA gasps]
Who gave you permission
to set foot on my property?
Consider this an honor.
I've decided to make this place
you call yours
my temporary home.
Temporary home?
How dare you?
Though, I suppose
I should expect
this kind of entitled behavior
from a hunting god!
What did you say?
Listen! Let's take a step back!
Seimei! What are you doing here
with this trash?
Helping him.
He lost his vessel and memories,
and he's having a rough time!
[KIO GONGEN scoffs]
Not my problem, is it?
Get those bear fleas
out of here, Seimei!
And don't you dare come back!
[ANOTHER]
Hmm.
[sighs]
Let's go.
In general, shrines will already
be occupied by gods.
But there is such
a strong power here.
-Not easy to give up.
-You have to.
It's not worth starting
a battle over, is it?
If you can't find a vessel
that isn't occupied,
you leave me no choice
but to do battle
for my right to stay here.
Uh, please don't go in there.
I promise you'll regret it!
[groans]
Hey, kid, what's wrong?
Come on, wake up!
Please!
Oh. Hi.
Hi.
Rise and shine, sleeping beauty.
You owe this guy your thanks.
Pretty amazing that Another
brought you back to us.
You really need to take
better care of yourself.
I appreciate your work ethic,
but you're pushing way too hard.
I apologize.
There's more
to it than just that.
Arata's lifeforce is slowly
being siphoned from his body.
That's the reason he collapsed.
Does that have anything
to do with the fact
that this guy's starting
to regain his strength?
[warbling]
That surprised him,
which could only mean
that he didn't do it
on purpose.
Can he drain energy
just by being close?
No.
It's more likely
that he's absorbing
the energy humans are spending
whenever their curiosity
focuses on him.
-Where are you going?
-Leaving, of course.
Since I'm responsible
for draining your lifeforce,
the last thing I want to do
is remain here
and cause your death!
You still need a home!
And we haven't figured out
your name yet, either!
My pride is important to me.
Respect that. Please.
I will not steal the life
of an innocent man,
especially not when that man
has done so much for me.
But you'll make
my work more difficult!
I'm not done yet!
It's still my job
to figure out who you are!
That means
you're not allowed to leave!
Aren't you afraid
of what could happen?
[ARATA] We've been together
this whole time,
and I'm not dead.
[sighs]
That's true.
[THEO] Ya know, I'd apologize
for killing the moment,
except I have no idea
what's being said here.
[KYOICHI]
Translate, please.
Right, I keep forgetting.
Forgive me.
Interesting twist.
Theo? Your thoughts?
I just need his name.
Once we know that, everything
else will fall right into place.
I agree, then let's keep
moving forward.
I'll stay with the Another.
Maybe he'll say something that
will be a clue as to who he is.
For real? Did you forget
that you just collapsed?
[ARATA]
I'm fine.
At least we know
it's not because I'm sick.
Look, I know what I'm doing,
all right? I've got this.
Also, I realize I may have lost
some of my strength,
but that Another is feeling
a whole lot better
because of me.
I'd call that progress.
I'd call you
a very stubborn guy.
Excellent work.
[gasps]
What did you say?
[KYOICHI] Never hurts
to be supportive, Theo.
Besides, we hired him,
didn't we?
Can't fault him
for making us look good.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Just keep me updated, please.
I will!
[ANOTHER]
Hmm.
[beeps]
♪
[WOMAN]
Thank you! Have a nice day!
♪
What's the matter?
The number of people here.
I didn't realize
there were so many
and such
a wide variety of types.
That's especially true
in the Shinjuku prefecture.
What's more, I've never met
a human quite like you before.
You're unique.
It's a big world
out there, isn't it?
Is that triggering
a memory for you?
No, not really.
But it does feel like
something is trying
to break through the fog.
[ARATA]
That's great.
Be sure to tell me the second
you notice anything at all.
It could be important.
I'll be sure to do that,
but first I have a request.
I haven't eaten yet.
And after
all that chaos back there,
I'm feeling a bit hungry.
Surely you must
be getting hungry, too?
I'll make something for us
as soon as we get back
to my place.
Actually, I just bought
some really nice honey.
It's imported,
supposed to be delicious.
[ANOTHER]
I can't wait to try that!
♪
[ARATA]
Okay, moment of truth.
[grunts]
[sniffs]
Ah!
-What's wrong?
-N-n-nothing.
I'm fine.
That smells good.
See what you think.
Thank you very much!
♪
I, I think I might be familiar
with this particular honey.
-Huh?
-The rich beauty of its color,
like fine jewels.
It glitters in the light
like dew on leaves
changing color in autumn.
And the sweet scent tickles
the heart with joy.
I remember it well!
♪
[gasps]
-[birds chirping]
-[grass rustling]
♪
[bees buzzing]
[swallows audibly]
This is the one.
I have received many offerings
of this honey
from people in need of my help.
They would offer it
with their prayers
for things like peace
for their families
and healthy cattle
or for a fertile harvest.
Yes, of course!
This honey is from my homeland!
[ARATA]
The Ukraine?
[beeping]
[THEO]
Yep, that's it!
This says he's an Another
called Volos!
According to Slavic myths
from the region
that's now the Ukraine,
he's the god of forests
and hunting.
He's also said to protect cattle
in the form of a bear.
Which explains
why he never tried to kill you
when you were with him.
And that element of his story
helped me narrow down
his identity.
-How's it goin'?
-[GROUP] Uh...
Hey! We solved the mystery.
Oh!
Great, well, I guess
you won't be needing
this thing, then.
Needing what thing?
Well.
[ARATA]
What is this?
I thought maybe
he'd see something there
that triggered a memory.
But since you've
figured out who he is,
guess you don't need the help.
You can still go if you want.
It's over in Ueno.
[VOLOS gasps]
This is... This is it!
I have no doubt!
At last, I've found
a new vessel and a new body!
[ARATA]
Huh?
[VOLOS] Tell me,
what will happen
to this statue after this?
[ARATA]
Huh?
Let me see.
It's a traveling exhibit,
so it will either be sent back
to its home museum
or continue to travel the world
making appearances
like this one.
[VOLOS]
Traveling the world?
Seeing places I've never visited
or even heard of before?
I've seen many things lately,
just over the past few days.
And if I'm allowed
to continue on that journey,
I will consider myself
very lucky.
♪
[VOLOS] The gods need
human emotions to survive.
Like faith, gratitude, sadness,
along with their prayers.
I'd been forgotten,
and that caused my power
to be taken from me.
If not for you, I would have
spent eternity spiritually dead.
The passion and loyalty
of your heart
are what saved my soul.
Thank you for that.
It's nothing. But sure.
All part of the job, Volos.
Understood.
I hope you're proud
of this noble job.
I'm grateful.
♪
[VOLOS] I just realized that
you never told me your name.
-Uh?
-[VOLOS] What is it?
Arata. Arata Miyako.
Hmm. That's a good name.
[engine starts]
♪
And I am Volos,
god of the Rus!
Let the world's people know
that I, my name, and my power
have returned to rule
the forest once again!
Thank you, Arata Miyako!
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[YUKI]
Arata!
Uh. Huh?
Huh?
[screams, grunts]
[YUKI]
I'm here!
Hi, Yuki!
Glad you're back!
Missed you.
I'm so glad that bear-smelling
guy found a place to go.
I guess this means
you're back, too.
Wow. You look a bit weak.
That's what you get
when you take on those types.
[YUKI]
Are you okay, Arata?
[ARATA]
I'm just fine.
It's all part of the job,
you know?
Great. Let's go do
something fun now.
We could go look
at cherry blossoms?
No, I gotta head back
to the office.
[YUKI] Okay! Then I'll wait
for you at home!
Ready to go?
[KOHAKU]
But I just got here!
Hey! If you don't want
to see cherry blossoms,
why don't we go fishing?
[ARATA]
Some other time, sure.
[scoffs] You're no fun!
I've got an idea!
I'll just come with you to work
and be your assistant!
[ARATA]
Nope! No, you will not.
♪
[ARATA]
Yokai, angels, devils,
most of the occult creatures
you've read about, actually.
We have a name for them
for all the non-human creatures
we come across
in our line of work.
"Anothers."
-[rustles]
-Huh?
[ARATA] Our job is to maintain
relations with the Anothers.
That way, if they start
causing problems for civilians,
we know exactly
how to take care of it.
We are the Nocturnal Community
Relations Division
working at the
Shinjuku Ward Office.
And we take our jobs
very seriously.
♪
Uh?
Good morning, team!
♪