[alarm ringing]
[groans]
[YUKI]
Get up, Arata! Rise and shine!
[alarm continues]
-[ARATA grunts]
-[alarm stops]
Oh, hello. Good morning!
-Uh. You're here?
-That's right.
I thought it would be wise
to attempt to blend in
with the humans of this era.
What do you think
of this outfit I found?
Or would you prefer to see me
in something
a little bit more masculine?
I, uh... I don't care.
Wear what you want.
Are you going to explain
to me why you're here?
[COYOTE]
Should I not be?
[ARATA]
Well, it's my place.
I realize that.
Is there a reason you don't want
me floating around your home?
You allow that cat
to stay here.
Why not me?
I'm Arata's friend, thank you.
[ARATA sighs]
If I told you
I value my privacy,
would that make sense?
We never used
to keep secrets from each other.
Rude.
[ARATA]
Well, if you're not gonna leave,
why don't you tell me more
about this Seimei?
You want me to tell you
about the past?
That's such a typical thing
for a human to request.
Even more so to ask a friend
for stories about yourself.
It's not like that.
How would I know?
[chuckles]
I'll make an exception
if you forgot.
And it seems you have.
♪
[SEIMEI] You expect me
to believe you're from
a world underneath us?
Yes, I do.
Please, allow me to explain.
♪
We are standing
on this part of the world.
And I am from an area
over here.
You mean the world we live in
is round like that?
If so, wouldn't those
at the bottom fall off?
They're wondering
why you don't fall.
To them,
you're on the bottom side.
[chuckles]
I admit, that is fascinating.
You're a good storyteller.
[COYOTE]
Well, there's more.
Did you know that the stars
are in a different order
to those living
in other countries?
Does that mean
they get lost more often?
You had such a thirst
for knowledge those days.
Wait, that means someone
from the Heian period
knew earth was round
before we did.
Yes, that's true.
That someone insisted on
learning about the stars.
-Don't you remember?
-Oh, crap!
I gotta go! I'll be late!
[scampering footsteps]
Always in such a hurry.
[KYOICHI]
Okay, then.
Any news on
the old Coyote situation?
[ARATA]
Not really.
Then let's table
that case for now,
since no one seems
to be in danger.
[THEO]
Agreed.
Unless there's
a good enough reason,
you don't want to try
and tackle a god of calamity.
Let's not call him a god.
I'd say he's more like a NEET.
I can't imagine
what's happening in his mind.
[THEO] Don't try.
That would be like trying
to figure out
what motivates a typhoon.
You'd be wasting your time,
and you'd drive yourself mad.
[ARATA] A typhoon?
Yeah, I can see that.
[YUKI grunts]
The look on your face!
Cats are so funny!
[YUKI]
Shut up!
Well, we should still keep
an eye on him.
Yeah, definitely.
We might learn something
we'll need later.
Good morning.
-Morning. Good to see you.
-[door closes]
[KYOICHI]
How's it going, Senda?
[SENDA]
Great!
[sighs]
Hey, guys. Your reports?
I'm assuming you're about ready
to turn those in to me?
What reports?
[SENDA]
Don't mess with me right now.
Same report
we turn in every year.
You need to have them
in tomorrow.
[THEO] Wow, already?
Time flies, doesn't it?
The Shinjuku Ward Special Cases
Fixed-Point Observation
isn't new.
[THEO]
But it's such a pain in the ass!
[SENDA] I know.
I've done it. On time.
We're outside today,
so hurry up.
[THEO sighs]
Fine. I'm on it.
Where are we going?
[KYOICHI]
It's right over there.
♪
You mean Kabukicho?
Yep. They want reports
on six Anothers
who are apparently living here.
In case there are any issues.
It's pretty much become
a tradition for our section.
Let's see, number two
are the shojo.
Number three's Minerva's Owl.
Number four's a dryad.
Mezu is five.
Number six is Bultungin.
And Azukiarai is number seven.
Um, what happened
to number one?
We've got enough with these six
without digging
into whatever's going on
with that one.
[KYOICHI]
Exactly.
-Stay focused, Miyako.
-Right!
♪
[KYOICHI]
Let's get started, shall we?
[THEO]
Right behind you.
Smells like alcohol.
[SHOJO 1]
Come on! Keep drinking!
[SHOJO 2]
Hey, it's my second bottle!
[SHOJO 1] How 'bout
that catch we made, huh?
They sound angry.
What's going on with them?
What are you lookin' at?
You got a problem,
Neck Tie and Four Eyes?
-They're gorillas?
-Shojo.
A type of Monkey Another
originally from ancient China.
[growling, sniffing]
[SHOJO 1]
You smell like rookie meat.
[chuckling]
[SHOJO 2] All I can smell
are my sake burps
-So, uh, you guys cops?
-Not at all!
Shinjuku Ward civil servants!
This guy just answered
like he understood what we said!
I know! He must be
that Ears of Sand guy!
Uh...
He's just like
any other stupid human!
But maybe that could make
things more fun around here.
We've been drinking with the
same group since Gongen left,
and I'm getting bored.
[ARATA]
Who's Gongen?
[SHOJO 1]
All right, this one's for you.
-Oh. That's okay, please don't.
-[SHOJO 2] Why not?
Our sake's
not good enough for you?
[SHOJO 1]
Try it!
Throw it back!
You're gonna love it!
[chuckles nervously]
Just one.
[THEO]
Are you an idiot?
Uh? You didn't drink it.
Maybe next time.
I'm still working.
Work? Is that what
you do for money?
For more drinks?
[KYOICHI]
Don't ever put something
an Another gives you
close to your mouth!
Understood.
They were being nice, though.
Anothers don't really think
in the terms of "nice."
They were probably trying
to loosen you up
to make it easier for them
when they get hungry.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
[KYOICHI]
He means they'd eat you.
They've been there for a year
just hanging out with each other
and getting wasted.
Huh.
We don't know if
they're planning on leaving
or if they're there
permanently or what.
That's why we have to keep
checking in on them regularly.
[ARATA] If they've been
wasted for a year,
how'd they hear about
the Ears of Sand?
♪
Wow, this is amazing!
I got my wallet back!
Yeah, glad we could
help you out!
There's some paperwork
for you to sign
just so it's on file
that you picked it up.
[MAN]
Cool, cool!
Hey, Nakamura,
he's ready for you.
On it!
[KYOICHI]
Hello, Haguro.
-You got a minute?
-Huh?
[HAGURO]
Sakaki. Of course.
If you could just
sign here please.
All right. No problem!
They were here and here.
They moved
a little further than before,
but, other than that,
nothing else to report.
Sounds good to me.
This has helped us out
tremendously.
-Thank you.
-[HAGURO] No problem.
Need anything else,
I'll be in the blue box.
[KYOICHI] Are those your kids?
They're so big now!
Yeah. Every time I blink,
they've grown another inch.
They sure are a handful,
but I love 'em.
They have a good father.
They're very lucky.
♪
[ARATA]
So that policeman, Haguro.
-He can see the Anothers, too?
-[KYOICHI] He can.
But you're the only one
who can talk to them,
so you're not off the hook.
[ARATA chuckles]
-It's up here.
-[faint rustling]
Okay. What's that sound?
♪
Miyako. Go check it out.
[rustling gets louder]
♪
[ARATA screaming]
[panting]
What's with the naked guy?
He's an Another. Not human.
That's Azukiarai. Number seven.
I promise you he's harmless.
It's just a pain
to keep up with his location.
We always have
to figure out where he is.
But we've done that, so...
[THEO]
There's still four more left,
so let's keep moving.
Hold on a sec!
Why won't you tell me
what happened
to number one on the list?
There wasn't anything
written down.
They were around
before World War II.
They were a boss
in this area. I think.
[NAKAMURA]
Those guys that came by were
from the ward office, right?
-What did they want?
-[HAGURO] I didn't ask.
I trust they had their reasons.
Huh?
What the hell's that?
-Was it a loiterer?
-Huh?
Well, whatever it was,
it's gone.
Probably just
headlight reflections.
Must be an Another
if he can't see it.
That must mean...
[gasps]
[bicycle clatters]
Um... uh?
Uh, Haguro?
♪
[THEO] There's number three.
Minerva's Owl.
Whoa, it just moved!
♪
[THEO]
This says dryad, number four,
has no changes.
[KYOICHI]
Well, yeah, she's got roots.
She can't move.
[THEO]
And right over there should be
our number five, Mezu.
♪
Awesome.
Just one more left.
It should be somewhere
right around here.
Huh?
-Damn, I'm good.
-[ARATA] Huh?
[ARATA]
Looks like a stray dog.
[THEO]
Nope. That's a hyena.
What's a hyena doing
in Shinjuku?
[KYOICHI]
That would be Bultungin.
He came over here
with the US Army
after the war
and then never left.
[growls softly]
Well, what a surprise.
You're the Ears of Sand,
aren't you?
I don't know how you know that,
but I am.
Good, now you can warn
the others.
Be careful.
Trouble is coming.
[gasps]
-Right behind you.
-Huh?
[thudding footsteps]
Was that a...
It's carrying a police officer.
-Let's go!
-Right!
[THEO]
You know how you hear about
"mysterious disappearances?"
That's what we're witnessing
right now
unless we do something
to save that officer.
[KYOICHI]
Uh! It's Haguro!
[THEO]
They must've made eye contact.
That's all it takes.
[ARATA]
Where's it taking him?
[THEO]
To its territory.
Pay attention.
You have to follow
a certain set of steps to enter.
Sounds like a pain
to have to do that every time.
[KYOICHI] Welcome to the world
of Anothers.
♪
[THEO] Hold on. Kabukicho has
a Kio Inari shrine?
Shrines are supposed to be holy,
not a home base for an Another.
♪
I think I get it now.
That's him!
The first Another.
He's the one who disappeared.
[yawns]
[ARATA]
But what made him come back?
And more importantly,
how do we save Haguro?
The Another doesn't seem
to be very aggressive.
[KYOICHI] Not much we can do
with him sitting
right in front of us.
-[ARATA] What then?
-Hmm?
-[FAIRY 1] Look, that's him!
-[FAIRY 2] It definitely is!
Kio Gongen, I found him!
The Ears of Sand guy's
over here!
Seriously?
[growls]
Uh...
What happened?
Well, I know that
Another's name. So, that's done.
And, you're gonna
make us guess?
[ARATA]
It's, uh, Kio Gongen.
Wait, you mean
the actual god of this shrine?
[KIO GONGEN]
What a surprise.
I never thought
I'd see you again!
Hah! Hello, Seimei.
[ARATA]
I'm guessing this isn't going
to go away anytime soon.
[laughing]
Look how mad he is!
Sandy ears is upset!
[ARATA]
Cut it out!
So, tell me Seimei,
what have you come here
to ask of me?
The officer! He's a friend,
please let him go!
-You want him back?
-[ARATA] Please!
[KIO GONGEN]
I can't do that yet.
He needs to stay here
for a little longer.
Funny story.
I think I drank a little
too much and fell asleep.
But now that I'm awake,
we gotta throw a festival
to make up for lost time.
A festival?
To sacrifice him?
Please don't.
I'm not gonna eat him.
I just really want
a new drinkin' buddy,
for a hundred years or so.
-A hundred years?
-Fill us in!
What are you two
talking about?
Sorry. He wants
to keep Haguro here
so he can drink with him
for a hundred years.
Anothers are such drunks.
Please think of his family.
If you keep him for that long,
it'll hurt them
as if he had died.
He has two children
who need him!
Please let him go!
Hmm. Hmm!
I mean, is it
that big of a deal?
If I don't give him to you,
will you take him by force?
I accept your challenge, Seimei!
-Uh...
-What did you do?
-Why is he all pissed off now?
-I don't know!
[COYOTE]
I'm just in time!
-Are we having a drinking party?
-[chuckles]
[KIO GONGEN]
Well, well. I remember you.
Listen. You don't want this.
A festival? To do it right,
you need way more people.
[KIO GONGEN]
Hmm. I guess that's true.
So, why not have
a drinking contest
with the three of them instead?
If they win,
you give the man back,
and if they lose,
he stays with you.
-[KIO GONGEN laughs]
-Hey! I didn't agree to that!
You've always been the one
who fought for everyone
and didn't give up
until you saved them.
[ARATA]
Well...
So, why are you
abandoning this man?
Miyako! Remember us?
What are they saying?
Where to start.
Well, we're all having
a drinking contest with him
and if we win,
then he'll give us Haguro.
What? How? He's huge?
What makes you think
we could out-drink him?
[KYOICHI] I don't think
there will be an easier way.
Tell them we accept as long as
it's something humans can drink.
You're sure it's okay?
[KYOICHI]
That doesn't really matter.
We don't have a choice.
♪
[gulping]
[inhales sharply, gulps]
[groans]
[gulping]
I'm done!
[FAIRIES]
Here you go!
[gulping]
[belches]
That looks painful.
This is turning out
to be worse than I thought.
Sorry.
-[ARATA] Theo?
-[body thuds]
[KIO GONGEN]
Oh, no,
leaving the contest so soon?
What a pathetic loser!
[FAIRY 1]
You're the best, Mr. Gongen!
[FAIRY 2]
Win it all!
[COYOTE]
You're doing great, Arata!
Kohaku!
Why aren't you helping me?
If I help you, I'm gonna have
to help everyone else
or it wouldn't be fair.
What do I care? I'll take on
as many of you as you want!
Come here.
Call Senda and have him
send reinforcements.
I'll handle this, don't worry.
Now hurry up!
Um... I gotta pee.
Is that your fancy way
of saying you'll call for help?
Why not? Let's make it a party!
Bring anybody you'd like!
Um, okay, thanks
for your hospitality.
Be right back!
[KIO GONGEN] This one seems
like he's still got
some fight in him.
[gulps]
[panting
I'm impressed!
Not bad for a skinny one!
[KYOICHI] Crap.
I can't keep this up.
[breathing heavily]
I've been running
for twenty minutes.
[grunts in frustration]
[gulping]
[BOTH groan]
♪
Give me my next drink!
Come on!
[groaning]
[ARATA]
What the hell?
I'm never gonna get out of here!
[KYOICHI]
Quit making poo face at me!
You think you're so cool
because you drink a little bit
but guess what?
You suck at hosting
'cause my cup
does not runneth over!
Do you even know
what it's like
dealing with these
little bitches all day?
It's a big ol' pain
in the ass
because I don't have
anyone to back me up!
I saw.
[panting]
[yells]
[SHOJO grunts]
[SHOJO 1]
We're out of sake, guys!
[SHOJO 2] We'll have to get
some more tomorrow.
[SHOJO 1]
My buzz'll be gone by then!
[SHOJO 2] Maybe we should get
better quality sake!
[SHOJO 1] Not good enough
for you, Princess?
[SHOJO laughing]
Hey, what do you know?
It's that Ears of Sand guy!
[SHOJO 2] Ol' rookie meat
smells like good sake!
[gulping]
[belches]
[hiccups]
It doesn't matter
how long you stick it out.
It's still poison
to the human body.
[gagging]
Ki! What's up?
It's been forever!
[SHOJO 4]
Getting your wake-up drink on?
[SHOJO 3]
Great job not inviting us!
[SHOJO 1]
Are we not good enough for you?
What the hell
are you doing here?
-[SHOO 5] Where's the sake?
-[SHOO 2] Move, buzzards!
It's time for
papa monkey's medicine.
[gulping, slurping]
Aah!
You were not invited!
Why are you interrupting
my festival time?
Sounds like
somebody needs a nap.
Drink up, fatty.
Down the hatch!
Hurry up! You go grab Haguro.
I'll get Theo.
Right!
All right, I take it back!
Let's get ape-face-wasted!
Now that is what I call
a party worth crashing.
So then why am I
just floating up here?
Hey, there!
Got room for one more?
♪
[groans]
[panting]
[KYOICHI]
How are you feeling, Rookie?
[ARATA] Like I want to go home
and take a hot bath.
[THEO slurring] Reports-es.
Gotta write reports-es.
♪
[BULTINGIN] See? I told you
there was trouble.
[laughing]
♪
[KYOICHI]
Hurry it up!
Uh. I'm coming!
Lesson learned.
Anothers are a pain.
[THEO]
Too many reports-es!
[groans]