[YOKOYAMA]
So, your newbie hasn't quit yet?
That's pretty impressive.
[SENDA] Nope.
He's hangin' in there.
-[YOKOYAMA] That so?
-[SENDA] Yeah.
Look, think whatever you want
about me,
but I'm a good judge
of character.
[YOKOYAMA]
Sure you are.
That's why everyone younger
than Kyoichi's quit on you.
[SENDA]
Wait, I think I found it.
Yeah, right here.
What does that look like to you?
Honestly, I have no idea.
Is that our jurisdiction?
I think you should look into it.
The thing is, I'd love to.
But no. Every time I request
to investigate that scene,
I'm rejected for some reason.
And you think
you'll get approval
by getting us involved?
[chuckles, slurps]
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Great.
[THEO]
You're talking about the north
and south elevators
in City Hall?
That's right. We've officially
gotten clearance to investigate.
Well, It's about damn time.
-So, this is good?
-Huh? [sighs]
Really?
Did you just ask
that question out loud?
This is
The Parallel World Elevator!
Please tell me
you've at least heard of it.
I can't.
-Sorry.
-[sighs]
Wow, that's unfortunate.
You should consider it
a part of your job
to research what's happening
in the world of the occult.
Here, just do a search.
It'll pop up right away.
Okay, thanks.
[THEO] Someone posted about it
on our business page.
Basically, someone took the lift
to the Observation deck,
and when the door opened
they were in a different world.
We have a page?
-Yeah, and I designed it.
-Huh?
[THEO] This guy was posting
every time
something would happen
with this elevator
as it was happening.
And then one day
he just stopped
and couldn't be traced.
Rumors say it's because
he's mysteriously
gone missing.
Ever since his disappearance,
a few others have posted
about similar incidents
happening to them
on these same elevators.
Some of these
were obviously trolls
fabricating
to get attention,
but there are other accounts
where it's not as clear.
[SENDA] And there are more and
more alleged reports every day.
The police are finally taking
the case seriously
and actively looking
for the missing people.
Really?
So, then, why don't
we just let them
handle the investigation?
Because there could be more
to these disappearances
than the police
are equipped to deal with.
Watch.
-[THEO gasps]
-[ARATA] What the...
[SENDA] At first,
I thought it was because
she was in
the Parallel World Elevator
and this was the point
when she teleported.
[THEO gasps]
But she came back.
Same place.
[SENDA] With no visible injuries
or signs of struggle.
And for some reason,
she has no memory of any time
spent in the observatory.
We have similar reports from
several other visitors as well.
[THEO] Looks like
there are a group of people
who have gone missing
and a separate group
with lost memories.
[ARATA] Could that mean
there are two separate
Anothers at City Hall?
[THEO]
It's possible.
But I hope that's not the case.
Right. Kyoichi's on his way now
to meet the girl
we just watched.
Apparently, she's someone
he kinda knows.
[GIRL] I remember getting out
of the elevator
and walking
to the south observation deck,
and then
it was like I blinked
and was suddenly
on the north deck!
I mean,
talk about freaky, right?
Was there anything else
unusual about it?
Seriously?
Is teleporting from
one observation deck to another
and having no memory
of it not enough?
Have you been around
anyone else recently
who's experienced
something similar?
Um, something similar?
Well, my friend told me that
she got into the north elevator
and ended up
in some bizarre cloud land
with a woman holding a box.
You know, like all those stories
that came out?
Right. So your friend actually
remembered the full incident,
but you don't remember anything
between standing
on the two different decks?
Are you sure?
[GIRL]
Hmm? Yeah, I've got nothing.
Wait. Aoi.
Hmm? Yeah, what is it?
Why are you acting all serious?
[KYOICHI]
What happened?
Did you make up with him?
-[AOI] Hmm?
-Your maybe-ex-boyfriend.
Uh, no, Mr. Nosey-Pants.
But if we're done talking
about freaky elevators,
there's a girl at my work
that you have to meet.
Seriously.
I'll have a thing at my place
and invite you both!
[THEO]
So what did Aoi say?
Anything major?
[ARATA]
Who's Aoi?
[KYOICHI] She was a customer
when I was a host.
[ARATA] Oh.
That's cool, I guess.
[KYOICHI] She didn't say
anything to help clarify
how the disappearances
are happening,
but she did say something
that disturbed me a little.
She was engaged to a guy
she'd been with for a while,
but just the other day, he broke
up with her out of the blue.
She was devastated.
But when I met up with her,
she didn't seem bothered
by it at all.
You would never guess
she had been suffering.
[THEO] You don't think
she just got over it?
No.
It felt more like she'd
forgotten that it had happened.
So, do you think she lost
her memories of that guy
all together or just that
they had been engaged?
She remembered that
she had a boyfriend,
and she was aware
that they broke up,
but it was like
she completely forgot
how heartbroken she was
and that she was working
through a depression
only days ago.
Like the sadness was deleted.
Anyway, that's
a secondary issue.
We need to examine
the scene first.
What do you think, Theo?
[THEO] So far, I'm not finding
any signs of crests or spells
-that could've been used.
-[elevator chimes]
Which means it's highly unlikely
this was artificial.
What do you mean?
Like incorporating magic
to turn this elevator
into some kind of device.
I still don't get it.
Well, then, I'll give you
an example.
If someone's worshiping
an Another
and needs to give it
a sacrifice,
they could turn those doors
into a magical gate
in which to throw
their offerings.
Wait, what?
And if it looks like
an ordinary elevator,
victims would have no idea
until they were standing
right in front of the Another.
[gasping]
The data we've collected
makes it look like it happens
right as the victims
leave the elevator
and walk out onto
the observation deck.
So, I guess we're going up.
Theo, you head to the south deck
and check things out up there.
Arata and I will see
what happens on the north deck.
[THEO]
Roger that.
Just remember,
this was your call.
Don't end up
in a parallel world!
[chuckles]
I'm sure he thought
that was funny.
♪
[ARATA]
Nothing's showing up.
Same here.
Well, let's do this.
Right.
♪
[elevator rumbling]
So...
for both cases,
it's completely random, right?
Missing persons
and missing memories
could happen
on either elevator?
Yeah, and we don't know
how the outcome is determined.
Why would Anothers do this?
No clue.
But we'll try to find out.
Even if we can't comprehend
their logic.
[chimes]
All right. Let's go.
[BOTH]
Uh...
A parallel world.
Noted.
[FEMALE ANOTHER] You must have
what I'm looking for.
Though I can't be certain.
Give me what you have.
[ARATA whimpers]
Well, this is
pretty anticlimactic.
[static over phone]
Are you kidding me?
Okay, I'll try Arata, then.
-[static]
-Huh?
Guess there's
no cellphone service
in those parallel worlds!
God, I'm hilarious!
[laughing]
No, no, no, no, no!
[chimes]
Kyoichi!
Arata!
It was a joke.
Wasn't it?
[ANOTHER]
Everything you have,
give it to me.
Um, do you have any idea
what she's saying?
She just said, "Give it to me."
Give her what?
[ARATA]
I have no idea!
[gasps]
[ANOTHER]
No, that's not it.
That's not what I need!
Oh, no!
Did I make a mistake?
[ARATA]
A mistake?
[ANOTHER]
What do you have?
You've brought
absolutely nothing.
Then I don't understand
what you're doing here!
You must have made contact
with this human at the entrance
and then followed him here.
[ARATA]
What is she talking about?
Is that what she means?
[ANOTHER] How many times
is this going to happen?
You try to prioritize efficiency
and somehow end up
less accurate.
Efficiency?
-About what?
-[gasps]
You understood what I said?
But how?
You're a human, aren't you?
[ARATA]
Uh, yeah.
Wow!
I'm talking with a real human!
How wonderful!
Great, you must've been
sent up here
so we can talk about things.
What are we going to talk about?
Come on. This way!
-Wait!
-No!
Arata!
I've no further need of you.
[ARATA]
Kyoichi!
[THEO]
[KYOICHI sighs]
What happened?
Where's Arata?
-[KYOICHI] She took him.
-[THEO] Huh?
She's controlling that space.
We ended up in another world,
and I was sent back.
But why?
Damn it!
What happened to him?
Where did he go?
[ANOTHER giggles]
I got rid of him
because he was in the way.
[ARATA]
Huh?
Is he going to be all right?
I just sent him back outside.
It makes it easier for us
to talk, don't you think?
[ARATA] I'm sorry,
I just don't understand
what you're trying to do.
[ANOTHER]
I'm looking for something.
[ARATA]
You said that.
But what are you looking for?
[ANOTHER]
Things.
I'm gathering
all the precious things
that have escaped
from this box.
[ARATA]
Strange.
It doesn't seem like
she has anything to do
with the disappearances
and lost memories.
This device has been
extremely helpful.
It tells me exactly who has
what I'm looking for
and who does not.
Then it conveniently
delivers the ones
who have what
I need right to me.
It was great
until I changed the settings.
I increased the amount
of deliveries.
But then I had several people
sent to me
who only had something similar
to what I needed.
Similar?
Exactly what are you
looking for?
Loss.
The man you were with carries
a tremendous amount
of grief and heartbreak,
and those feelings
triggered the device.
Uh...
You see, even though
I am looking
for a sense of loss,
it's still slightly different
than what he had.
[ARATA]
I wonder what kind of loss
Kyoichi is suffering.
[THEO panting]
[KYOICHI]
Theo, any luck?
[THEO panting]
I tried several times...
but nothing worked.
Which means there has to be
some kind of criteria
that neither of us
can meet!
Shit!
I don't think we're going
to be able to get in there.
Hey!
Where are you going?
-Hey!
-[door slams]
[ANOTHER] This box
once held many things:
fear, sadness,
diseases, crimes.
It was practically overflowing
with tragic,
yet beautiful treasures.
Because of that,
I was told never to open it.
[BOTH gasp]
But I was so curious
I took a peek,
and that's when
they all burst out.
It was my mistake.
Therefore,
it's my responsibility
to put everything back in.
Some of these things,
like the loss of a loved one,
fell here in Asia.
Why are you looking
for something like that
in a City Hall elevator?
What's City Hall?
If you're referring
to a human building,
I don't know much about those.
The paths I create to where
you and I stand all originate
in whatever area
contains what I need.
Wait, those aren't
the only two elevators?
Are there more of them scattered
throughout the country?
[elevator chimes]
[ANOTHER]
Just a moment.
Here comes another visitor.
I hope this one's
not another mistake.
Oh, good.
This one is correct.
Give me your heartbreak
and your feelings of loss.
[heartbeat thumps]
Thank you.
Go. Continue on your path
as usual.
You were just leaving
for the day.
A simple transition.
When you wake up,
you'll be
exactly where you wish to be.
[people murmuring]
[groans]
[ANOTHER chuckles]
She actually brought me
quite a large amount.
So much that it may be time
for me to go.
I've almost recovered enough
of the heartbreak
that was lost here.
I think my next stop
will be Europe,
where I'll recover jealousy.
So, does that mean
you won't need
the City Hall elevators anymore?
[panting]
[THEO]
See what I mean?
I told you, it triggers as soon
as you step off the elevator.
Please try to calm down.
You're supposed to be
the leader.
[KYOICHI]
I just...
I just need to bring Arata back.
[THEO] Then let's get Reiji
on the phone
and come up with a plan.
Maybe he'll have a solution.
With the state you're in,
we're not going to get
anywhere on our own.
Hey, Reiji?
We've got a bit of a situation.
Hey!
Kyoichi, where are you going?
I'd almost forgotten
how wonderful it feels
to hold when it's full!
It may not look like much
but this box was
essentially supposed
-to be my dowry!
--[cell phone vibrating]
Isn't that amazing?
[ARATA]
Izumi?
I can still get
messages out here?
I said, "It doesn't make sense."
I should see what's inside."
It's my dowry, after all.
[THEO grunts]
[THEO]
That's it.
I can't do this.
I'm calling Reiji immediately.
We need help.
[KYOICHI]
I'll see if I can reach him.
[THEO]
Crap, that's right.
The barrier probably
blocks out voice.
[cell phone vibrating]
[THEO]
I've got messages!
But my phone calls
weren't going through!
That's how they were posting.
Yeah, you're right!
For some reason,
the text feature works
from the other worlds.
[beeping]
You're probably sure
you caught a glimpse of it...
[ARATA]
"She has nothing to do
with missing people
or missing memories."
[beeps]
What the hell's
he talking about?
Feelings of lost love?
But she is responsible
for the missing memories.
Huh?
That's why Aoi was
so weird that day.
The anguish of her breakup
had been taken from her.
♪
An Another
that steals emotions, huh?
♪
But I'm keeping that
to myself this time.
Excuse me?
They're never
falling out again.
When you take those feelings
away from people,
do you also take
their memories?
Memories?
I honestly don't know if I do.
Huh?
[KYOICHI]
Yeah, I think I believe that.
Even if she's causing
the memory loss,
I doubt she realizes it.
[THEO] She doesn't seem to care
if anyone sees her face
or knows where she is.
Otherwise, why would she choose
to leave my memories intact?
So then, if she's
just responsible
for the memory losses,
maybe there's a second Another?
Yes.
Question is where?
[SENDA] What do you mean
they never went missing?
[YOKOYAMA over phone]
We were able to identify
and reach out to that guy
who was posting
about the strange occurrences
on the elevator.
He said there was never
a missing person report filed.
He also said he had
no recollection
of ever going to City Hall,
much less making real-time posts
about strange occurrences.
Great. I'm glad to see this case
is heading nowhere.
Thanks.
The guy from the forums.
He was believed
to have gone missing
because he just suddenly
stopped posting.
But if he had actually forgotten
about that world
and what happened to him,
then of course he wouldn't post
about being there anymore.
It makes perfect sense.
This could mean no one
ever went missing at all.
Then all the people
who have lost their memories
or vanished
for various lengths of time,
that was because of you.
♪
What if I asked you to stop?
Is it as simple as that?
Asked me to stop what?
Using that elevator
to look for the items
that fell out of your box!
Why would I do that?
Because that's not the way
it's supposed to be used!
I've had no trouble
using it that way.
[ARATA]
Clearly. But when you do,
it affects the lives
of innocent people!
Why should I have to let go
of something that belongs to me
just because it makes
the humans uncomfortable?
[ARATA]
Huh?
[ANOTHER]
I can't place them above myself.
[THEO] What are you going to do
when you ask them politely
to stop and they agree...
in exchange for your life?
[KYOICHI]
You know what would help?
If you researched
the scarier traits
of the Anothers.
[ARATA] Just because I can hear
and talk to them
doesn't mean
we truly understand each other.
Anothers have no compassion
for humans.
I see.
I've got to go.
Oh, that's too bad.
♪
I hope to see you again.
I'll find a way for you
to come back
and visit any time
you would like, okay?
Before I go,
I've been meaning to ask,
what's your name?
[ANOTHER]
My name?
I'm not quite sure
how to answer that,
but some
have called me Pandora.
Pandora. With a box.
Like the myth of Pandora's Box?
[THEO] Still nothing
since his last text.
[cell phone vibrating]
[elevator chimes]
[THEO/KYOICHI]
Arata!
I'm back.
I'm okay.
Sure about that?
I've got you.
Did you make a bargain
with that Another?
You didn't accept any gifts,
did you?
[ARATA]
No, nothing like that happened.
[KYOICHI]
Arata.
Please forgive me.
I shouldn't have made you
go up there with me.
Don't say that!
Uh, I'm totally fine, see?
Both you and Arata
returned safe,
so I say that's a success.
Come on,
let's get our reports done
and call it a day.
I'm ready to get the heck
out of here.
[KYOICHI]
Agreed.
Let's pack up.
[THEO groans]
I'm passing out
as soon as I get home.
Have you seen Arata?
Maybe we should grab some food
before we go?
[THEO]
He should be here soon.
Oh, hey, how's it going?
You know, I'd ask you
the same thing,
but I'm pretty sure
I know the answer.
That report was something else.
One Another at the root
for both elevator cases, huh?
Sounds like you guys
had a long night.
Yeah, you could say that.
Having this skill
isn't so great.
The Ears of Sand may help
to understand the Anothers,
but that doesn't mean
I can stop them
from being destructive.
Well, luckily,
that's not our job.
We aren't expected
to eliminate the cause
once we've solved
the mystery.
Hmm?
[SENDA] The Another
is leaving City Hall,
you're back safe,
and we know enough
about this case to close it.
So that's what we're gonna do.
Time to move on.
♪
[SENDA]
Hey, Mr. Yokoyama!
Wanted to let you know
that the matter at City Hall
has been resolved.
Right, right.
No, I didn't forget.
I still owe you dinner...
[ARATA] There's one thing
I left out of our report.
Kyoichi's sense
of heartbreak and loss
is what brought us to Pandora
in the first place.
♪
She said his loss was too much
for her to take.
What happened to him?