[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
[DORIN]
Jinto! Hey! Jinto Lin!
[JINTO]
Huh?
[DORIN chuckles]
Dorin Ku!
Hey!
[BOTH chuckle]
Man, you look well.
Thanks a lot.
Where are the others?
I'm here alone, Jinto.
No one else can come.
Yeah?
[DORIN]
Don't think badly of them.
They're just surprised.
They all know you commuted
to an Abh school,
although nobody
knew your status.
[JINTO]
It's okay.
It's my fault as well,
for keeping it secret.
But would you have let
me hang out with you
if you knew I was a nobleman?
[DORIN] We wouldn't have
let you hang out with us
if we knew what a
lousy player you were.
You what?
[DORIN]
It's a first for everyone.
Hey, nobody knows how
to act around noblemen.
Yeah, me neither.
That new outfit looks
really good on you.
Hey, stop kidding.
Here.
[JINTO]
Oh, thanks.
Look.
That lady over there
has the hots for you.
I envy you.
Older gals like you!
[DORIN chuckles]
H-Huh?
Man! If only I could have
your face for a single day.
They only stare because I'm
wearing clothes of the Empire.
It's like watching
a dog using chopsticks.
[DORIN]
A dog?
No, it's much more than that.
Well, for someone from
the Land, that is.
Guess so.
Hey. I've only ever seen
Abhs on 3-D images.
So are they really
as cute as they say?
[JINTO]
I dunno.
I've never seen them
in person myself.
No, he won't return
even if he could.
The Empire won't give
him noble status.
Yes, he's being tricked himself.
And it serves him right!
[JINTO]
I know now how animals feel
when they're taken to a zoo.
I came here in turmoil.
[JINTO] And now that
I can read and write,
I'm off to the capital.
What's that? Not back
to your home planet?
No. I'm going to a school
that trains war secretaries.
[DORIN] Are you gonna
become a soldier?
I must.
Ten long years at
the Star Forces,
and then I succeed the title.
I guess noblemen have
a really tough life.
[JINTO] The higher your rank,
the greater your obligations.
It makes more sense than
the other way around.
[DORIN] So does that mean
you'll be aboard warships?
[JINTO] Yup. In fact, one will
pick me up at 1800 hours.
What? A warship's
gonna come here?
Well, why the heck d'you
think I'm dressed like this?
So, some Abh soldiers
will be here?
Um, I'm not really
sure if he's Abh,
but I do know he is an officer.
I guess it's 1800.
Is it? Then I should be
leaving right about now.
Uh, you won't stay a minute
and watch me get escorted away?
No, siree.
I'll just start to pity you,
and then I'll probably
start to cry.
Yeah right! You are truly the
cruelest villain of Delktoe.
Oh, what flattery!
Don't make me blush!
Oh, yeah.
So just what is the formal
name you use as a nobleman?
Prince Jinto of the
Count Lin Syun Rock Hyde.
I think.
You mean to tell me you don't
even know your own name?
It's just not me yet.
It still sounds like
someone else's name.
Really?
Well, Prince Jinto "something,"
I hope you never forget me,
"Dorin Ku," okay?
'Cause, it's sure a lot
easier to remember
than "Jinto something."
Hey, I won't forget you.
And you can skip the
"Prince somethings,"
but don't forget the
name "Jinto Lin."
Gotcha.
By the way, Prince Jinto of the
Count Lin Syun Rock Hyde,
here's a farewell present.
Why, this is from...
Memories from planet Delktoe.
Are you leaving now?
[DORIN]
Yeah.
This is mine?
[DORIN] Yeah. Hope you have
a splendid trip in Space.
Would be nice if you
got to travel alone
with a beautiful room attendant.
[JINTO]
Stop it.
I'd rather be with you
than any room attendant.
[DORIN]
Not me.
[JINTO] Hey, I'm admitting
to something important.
[DORIN]
So we'll talk next time.
[JINTO]
Yes. Next time, when I return.
[DORIN] I'll even hire
you at my company.
[JINTO]
Heh. I'm counting on it.
[DORIN] I'll advertise
that our company employs
a former Empire nobleman.
[JINTO]
I look forward to it.
[DORIN chuckles]
[JINTO]
Heh. Dorin.
[DORIN]
Hm?
[JINTO]
Goodbye.
[DORIN]
Bye.
[JINTO] I continued staring
until he disappeared
beyond the doors.
He never looked back.
[OLD LADY 1 screams]
[OLD LADY 1 speaking in Baronh]
[gasps]
That's blue hair.
[OLD LADY 1 speaking in Baronh]
[JINTO]
Stop him!
Oh, excuse me!
Whoa!
[BOY 3 speaking in Baronh]
[BOY 2 speaking in Baronh]
[yelping]
[BOY 5 speaking in Baronh]
[BOY 4 speaking in Baronh]
[BOY 2 speaking in Baronh]
[JINTO]
Hm?
Huh?
Are you Prince Jinto of the
Count Lin Syun Rock Hyde?
Uhh... Yes, I am.
Oh, but, uh, f-first of all,
thank you so much.
My patrol ship Gosroth
is awaiting you.
Come with me, please.
[JINTO]
Huh?
Uh... Hey, wait.
[JINTO]
Slow down.
But wait.
Wait.
[JINTO]
I asked you to wait!
You already seem know
my name, correct?
Yes, of course.
Why, you're the
Honorable Prince Jinto
of the Count Lin Syun Rock Hyde.
Uh, yes.
I'm the Jinto "something"
Lin "something" Rock Hyde
that you say.
I just felt, well, uneasy
that you know my name
but I don't know your name.
So I wondered, well, I-I
don't know Abh customs...
...but... but I...
Huh?
Lafiel, you shall say.
[JINTO] It was... as if she were
declaring a victory in war.
[LAFIEL]
In exchange for that,
I would like it if I could
simply call you Jinto.
Okay?
Uh, sure! Oh, yes, of course.
In fact, I'd rather
you call me that.
[chuckles]
[OLD LADY 1 speaking in Baronh]
Oh, right!
Lady!
Your bag.
Huh?
[OLD LADY 1 speaking in Baronh]
[JINTO]
Lady.
Jinto.
Come.
[JINTO]
Mh-hm.
[LAFIEL]
Jinto.
[JINTO]
Yes?
[LAFIEL] Back there, I saluted
you and you stepped backward.
What was that for?
Oh, that? It's a...
It's just a greeting
from my planet back home.
[LAFIEL]
Hmm.
Very strange. It seemed as
if you had blocked a punch.
Really?
Uh, any custom can look strange
to those who aren't
accustomed to it.
Yes, but, Jinto,
you are an Abh,
so you should learn the ways
of the kin of the stars.
Kin of the stars.
[JINTO] Known as the
product of genetic art,
they generally appear
beautiful and do not age.
They have a life-span of over
200 years and blue hair,
and their body is built
for the lifestyle in Space.
From their affinity
with the stars,
the "kin of the stars" is a name
they prefer for themselves.
I was only recognized
as one of them
through a law introduced
by the Empire.
[JINTO gasps]
[JINTO]
So this is the Gosroth ?
Is that supposed to be a joke?
[JINTO] Please don't forget
that I still know very little.
[LAFIEL]
This is the Calicke.
This spaceship is loaded
onto the Gosroth .
It seats 50 people, although
you're the only passenger today.
[JINTO]
I'm quite honored.
Hm?
So, uh, who'll pilot it?
Oh, ah.
Now, will this suit you?
Are you asking if
I like this ship?
If you'll sit up front here--
or if you'd prefer,
you can sit in the back.
Well, uh, are any of the
maids in the back pretty?
There aren't any beautiful
maids, but there's a cute pilot.
Then I guess I'll
sit here up front.
Is it really true that you
can monitor the entire ship
just by connecting
with that thing?
Yes.
This chip allows me to feel
exactly what the ship feels.
Are you sure that you find
all of this that interesting?
Well, sure!
After all, no one on Land has
the ability to see behind them.
Yes, but in my case,
I was born with it.
[JINTO gasps]
[JINTO] C-Can you read
this? At this speed?
[LAFIEL]
No.
[JINTO] Then what are
you doin' this for?
[LAFIEL] The analysis crystal
is checking the spaceship.
If it detects any
irregularities,
the problem area is displayed.
Wow. Huh...
It's strange that you can use
that thing to steer the ship.
What do you mean?
Well, just think.
Operating such a huge ship
with only your fingers,
it seems really absurd.
Do you think there
could be a better way?
Well, uh...
Well, for instance,
what would happen if
you suddenly got the urge
to grab for something?
[LAFIEL]
Grab what?
Nothing in particular. Just...
[LAFIEL] I forget all about my
left hand while I'm operating.
[JINTO]
Hm?
Is that true?
[LAFIEL]
There. We're done.
[JINTO]
Pretty simple, isn't it?
Yes. It's all done with this
analysis crystal right here.
[JINTO] Yeah, but what
if it makes a mistake?
Humans make mistakes.
So reassuring, thanks.
You sure do worry too much.
I mean, judging
from your remarks,
there's absolutely
no way our equipment
will break down so fast.
[chuckles]
Point taken.
[LAFIEL]
Control.
Roger. This is Harbor
No. 1 control center.
[LAFIEL]
This is spacecraft Calicke
from patrol ship Gosroth .
The command number
is 01-00-0-937684.
Request departure from Pier 2.
[CONTROLLER 1]
Roger.
Commencing depressurization
for Calicke of Gosroth .
So tell me what's
happening outside now.
Are you curious?
Yeah, well, since I don't
have your sensors.
I see. All right.
[CONTROLLER 1]
Depressurization complete.
[LAFIEL] Request to
open the gates of Pier 2.
[CONTROLLER 1]
Roger, Calicke of Gosroth .
[LAFIEL]
Open exit confirmed.
Request permission to depart.
[CONTROLLER 1]
Permission granted.
Calicke of Gosroth ,
do you require an
electromagnetic boost?
No. We will use our
low-heat propeller.
[CONTROLLER 1]
Roger.
Y'know, I kind of think
an electromagnetic boost
would be rather tough on you.
[JINTO]
Hm?
[CONTROLLER 1]
Calicke of Gosroth ,
we hope you have a
safe journey back.
Harbor No. 1 control
center, signing off.
Yes, thank you.
Calicke of Gosroth out.
[LAFIEL]
Take off.
[JINTO yells]
[JINTO]
It's flying.
Of course it's flying.
An Abh child can fly
a ship like this one.
Well, I-I'm sure that's true,
but you seem awfully
young yourself.
Are you saying
that I'm childish?
N-Not at all!
Your age is just difficult
to figure out, that's all.
And, well, anyway, it's
kinda rude to ask a girl.
I understand.
Actually, your guess
is quite accurate.
Recently, I turned 16.
Sixteen! Huh.
One year less than me.
[beeping]
What's that?
It is now safe for
us to accelerate.
Oh, I see.
[LAFIEL]
Can we accelerate?
[JINTO]
Go ahead.
How long will it take us?
[LAFIEL] Are you sure you can
withstand the acceleration?
I'm a Land person.
I can take it, so don't worry.
We'll get there in
six minutes. Let's go.
[JINTO yells]
[JINTO]
What's going on?
[LAFIEL] We're accelerating.
You said you'd be okay.
[JINTO] I-I didn't expect this!
I'm not okay at all!
[LAFIEL]
Shall I slow it down a bit?
[JINTO]
Yes! Please!
How can you stand it?
[LAFIEL] Our ancestors'
ships were not equipped
with gravity control devices,
so to live in high speed--
Lafiel! Slow down. Please.
Okay.
Jinto, I've got a
question for you.
Wh-What?
Why is it rude when you
ask a girl what her age is?
[JINTO]
Huh?!
It was a very strange beginning.
The beginning of our journey.
[LEXSHUE] I am Captain Lexshue
of this ship, Gosroth .
A-Abriel?
[LAFIEL]
I thought I told you earlier.
[LEXSHUE speaking in Baronh]
Tell me.
Please tell me if I'm
a "daughter of love"?