[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
[SPOOR]
I'm bored.
[SPOOR] I had always
dreamed of becoming a captain
and fighting against an enemy,
but while I was Captain,
there was no war,
and now that
there's finally a war,
I get these boring duties.
Am I unlucky or what?
Ah, commendable!
Yes, Rear Admiral Spoor!
Send most of
our mines right here!
We cannot allow it
to close again...
We must help the Futune!
[CREW 10]
There are enemy space-time orbs
coming from direction 010,
quantity about 300!
[KUFADIS] Looks to be the
enemy's main formation!
They're sending additional
forces toward us,
so we must take action!
Please stop making such a fuss
on my generally relaxed bridge.
[SPOOR] Make the calculations.
Do we have time?
Uh... Yes! Sure!
Let's maintain present route.
[SPOOR] We should arrive
at the enemy's battle line
any time now.
The enemy's strategy
is focused only on
stopping the Futune.
No threat to the main fleet.
[TRIFE] Agreed!
All vessels prepare to advance.
Lokale, annihilate the
front-line vessels to the right.
Wakapeil, wipe out
the vessels to the left.
Buledef and Kitil, follow me.
Now, if we don't start
getting aggressive,
Futune will steal the show!
[SPOOR]
It's taking too long.
We'll send half of
our fleet immediately
to destroy those ships.
Kufadis.
Captain?
[SPOOR]
I detest these little jobs.
Please inform each unit
of its respective target.
[KUFADIS]
Hmm.
Oh, and tell them not
to leave targets for us.
So are we going to
stand-by on reserve?
No, I want the targets
right over there!
[KUFADIS]
But they look like...
...oversized transport ships,
which are non-military
and pose no threat to us.
[SPOOR]
They could be backup war vessels
merely disguised as such.
They may be hoping to
pass through unharmed
and then pounce on us.
And so I would just like
to force their hand first.
Uh, right...
[CREW 10] Target orders
acknowledged from all units.
Very well.
Charge!
Let the main event
of fire dancing begin.
We are Futune,
the Goddess of Dance.
Let us step out and show them
what great dancers we are.
[KYUA]
Inspector.
We've located
two suspicious kids.
Where are you?
[KYUA] At the Limzale Inn,
but they're no longer here.
Ugh!
So they got away.
[KYUA] No, they were gone
by the time we arrived.
[ENTRYUA] So, you think
they were suspicious?
[KYUA] Yeah. Neither left
the room even once
during their stay.
Any witnesses?
[KYUA] The girl had black hair
and eyes and tanned skin.
She was apparently
very beautiful.
"Very." Uh-huh...
[MARCA] You think we're
just a bunch of dreamers,
don't you?
That there's no way
the Empire will recognize
our independence just
because we happen to have
you as our hostage, huh?
Oh, so you are aware of that.
What we are after
is a new spaceship.
And not independence?
No, for our independence.
Min is very eager to gain
independence right away.
But I believe we should just
approach it step-by-step.
Well, if you want
to get on a spaceship,
why don't you just
become citizens?
Our objective is not
just to ride spaceships,
but to finally acquire
one of our own
and that will make us
all free! Yeah!
You know that's impossible.
All interstellar
ships of the Empire
belong to Her Majesty
the Empress,
and not even the
top noblemen own their
own personal spaceships.
But we see numerous
ships of companies
and lords coming in and
out of the space harbor
all the time.
Those are all leased out
to the Empire merchant group
as a package which
includes the crew,
and the lessee has
control over the ship size
and contract term,
but the merchant group
has control over the crew.
Well, then, what's
going to become of
all our dreams?
[JINTO]
So then...
What are your plans?
This is our destination.
Was our destination.
That's my town which
we were gonna use
as a secret place
to confine both of you,
but I'm not sure it's
of any value now.
Think about it carefully.
Why do Abhs have
to be so arrogant
when they say things to us?
Don't let it bother
you too much.
You'll get way too stressed out.
I was trying to be helpful!
[MARCA]
Look over there!
Min, did you
purchase that thing?
No...
[LAFIEL]
Huh?
The United Mankind.
[UNDERTAKER gasps]
Are all of you
people citizens? Huh?
Why, I ask you the same thing!
My name is Lieutenant
Commander Alanga
of the United Mankind
Peace Corps,
Sufugnoff army division,
district military police.
[MIN] And I'm the owner
of that town over there.
You see, Lieutenant, my friends
and I were making our way
to my house for a party.
[ALANGA]
Then you must be Min Kulsup,
a member of the
Independence Party.
[MIN] Former member.
I quit three years ago.
[ALANGA]
But you are Min, aren't you?
[MIN]
That's right!
You are now under arrest.
Oh, yeah? What for?
[ALANGA] A large quantity of
weapons was found in your town.
Your Independence
Party is possibly
a hidden organization
that may take measures
and revolutionary actions
in sympathetic support
of the Empire.
[UNDERTAKER whimpers]
There's simply no
merit in resisting arrest.
They've misunderstood. Yikes.
Don't do it!
[GROUP yelling]
[MARCA]
Why'd you do that?
Well, run!
[ALANGA]
I'll get you!
Over that way!
[LAFIEL]
Well, hurry!
Thanks to you stinking Abhs,
I've become a
permanent fugitive!
Run now and complain later!
Come this way.
[UNDERTAKER whimpers]
Look there!
[GROUP]
Huh?
You just had to come!
[UNDERTAKER]
What the--?!
[LAFIEL]
Uh...
[MIN]
This way!
In!
Hurry!
[LAFIEL screams]
[JINTO screams]
[MIN]
Get out of the way!
Is everyone here?
Sure are!
Great! This way.
[JINTO gasps]
Oh, yeah...
[JINTO]
What is this?
It's a lava cave.
Well, what was that hole
we just dropped through?
That's an escape route
I made just in case
we had to use it someday...
You know, you guys have
made it really difficult!
Can you believe they now
think that I'm a collaborator?
With the Empire,
of all things! [yells]
[LAFIEL]
I'm sorry.
[MIN]
Huh?
I feel really terrible
about involving
all of you in this situation,
but we simply can't afford
to get caught ourselves.
[UNDERTAKER]
Long ago...
I once knew this guy, see,
who decided to jump into
a thorn bush.
Save the stories, okay?
[gasps]
[UNDERTAKER]
Hm? Hm?
Shh...!
Can you hear it?
They're here...
Turn out the light.
[UNDERTAKER] Naturally, the
guy was covered in scratches.
Who was?
[UNDERTAKER] The guy that
jumped into the thorn bush.
So, I went to
the hospital to see him,
and asked him
why he did it
and the guy replied...
"At the time, it seemed
like a good idea!"
[MARCA gasps]
[MIN] This path leads
to the main stream,
which has several outlets
taking you to the surface.
[LAFIEL] I want everybody
to go ahead of me.
What are you talking about?
Look, I can't afford to
cause you any further trouble...
I'll stop them
right here... go on.
I've never heard of
kidnappers being saved
by their own hostages before.
We better go now,
'cause nothing's gonna change
that girl's mind.
Hurry up. The enemy's close.
All right.
I hope that we
get to meet again.
See you later, girl.
[DASWANI]
Hmph...
Hey...
You're not trying to
get rid of me, are you?
Well, you're really not
much of a sharpshooter,
but having you is sure
better than nothing at all.
[JINTO] I hope they don't
use a fire cannon here.
We'd be buried alive.
[LAFIEL]
Don't worry.
After all, kin of the stars
aren't meant to die under soil.
[JINTO laughs]
[ENTRYUA]
I see they got here first.
[KYTE]
So what do you think?
Should we go underground
after them, too?
[ENTRYUA] Leave the game
of "underground tag"
to the army soldiers.
Oh, but Inspector...
You see, around here
we refer to the officers
of the Guzonyu local
police as "moles."
We can use the detailed
information they get
about this lava cave.
You mean...
So let's wait
for them at the exit.
[JINTO grunts]
[LAFIEL]
Run!
Wait here.
Uh-huh.
Now, take aim, but place
only one knee on the ground.
[JINTO]
Right.
[LAFIEL] When I give
you the sign to shoot,
swing your gun up and down.
[JINTO] I'm not sure about
shooting at an enemy
I can't see.
[LAFIEL] Hey, it wouldn't
make any difference.
[JINTO]
Thanks for your support.
[LAFIEL]
Now!
[SOLDIERS yell]
Look out!
[LAFIEL]
Further in!
[JINTO, LAFIEL yell]
[JINTO coughs]
Hurry!
Space-time orbs
661 breaking space-time!
Here they come.
There are six space-time orbs
of attack ships on route 45
with a distance of 16 units.
Are you certain?
Could they be mines?
[CREW 10]
No.
Weapons Officer, please tell me
how many of our mines are left.
Four on this ship,
four on Bogbyursh,
and five on Hasunbyursh, all
for a grand total of 13 mines.
I am capable of
adding up small figures.
Front-line vessels will now
commence launch of all mines.
Tear them to shreds!
Tell me, Kufadis.
What is it, Captain?
What would be the worst
crime an officer could commit?
I would think it's to
disobey one's superiors.
No, the worst crime
is to be a fool.
What kind of fool sends
only six attack vessels
to get rid of
three patrol ships?
I see.
I may not take
my job seriously,
but I'm not foolish enough
to sacrifice your lives
--without cause.
--[KUFADIS] Of course.
Furthermore, I can do
without fools on my bridge.
The Duchess Letopanyu
picks her own playmates.
But who is she
playing against?
Uh... I'll, uh... I'll try
to be a worthy playmate!
[SPOOR chuckles]
There's hope for your future.
[CREW 15] One minute
to space-time merge!
[CREW 10] No sign of
surrender yet from 661.
[SPOOR]
As I expected.
Senior Navigator, make
adjustments for our three ships
to enter space-time together.
[CREW 15]
Yes, Captain!
Inform all units to fire
their electromagnetic rifles
at once upon
merging with space-time!
Now. I do wonder what
we'll uncover in there.
My heart's pounding.
[CREW 15]
Ten seconds space-time merge!
Well, here we go.
[CREW 15]
Five, four, three, two, one...
Merge!
It looks like they're
surrendering to us!
We've received a
surrender signal by radio.
Inform all ships
that we must halt attack!
I'd ruin my name if I shot
at those who surrendered
so willingly.
Hasunbyursh has just shot,
so we now must use our rifles!
Detonate mines!
[SPOOR] Why couldn't they
tell us by inter-orb radio?
Did they think they
could get away?
[KUFADIS]
They're transport vessels.
[SPOOR] Even I have incorrect
hunches every once in a while.
[KAHYUL] A craft has
arrived from the Futune.
[TRIFE]
What's the situation?
[KAHYUL] They've imprisoned
a group of bureaucrats.
Why are there government
officials at a battle?
It would seem that
the United Mankind
has a custom of having
bureaucrats attend battles.
Their methods are totally
incomprehensible to me.
Well, in any case, I guess what
that means is we have won.
It's the obvious conclusion.
[TRIFE] It's too obvious
to get thrilled,
but order all fleets to assemble
for a big celebration.
[KAHYUL]
Right away.
And finally, I do have
one more job for the Futune.
[KUFADIS]
Detecting enemy fleet!
Direction 105, distance 0.12
light seconds,
speed 217 wesdash per second.
Fleet consisting
of about 20 vessels.
[CREW 14] Type of vessels
in enemy fleet confirmed.
They're believed to be 12
large-scale transport ships,
one patrol ship,
and six attack ships.
Ninety-eight percent
chance of our victory.
[KUFADIS] Shall we issue
a call to surrender?
[SPOOR]
There's no need.
They'll surrender
if they want to.
[CREW 10]
Message from enemy ship.
"We have 22 prisoners on board,
including the
Marquis of Sufugnoff.
Cease fire and
allow us to pass."
Oh, communications!
[CREW 10]
Yes, Captain!
Send this reply.
[CREW 10]
Yes, Captain.
And the message?
That I am the
Rear Admiral Spoor,
the commander of the
scouting fleet Futune.
You should be thankful for
the generosity shown by us.
I will allow you the
opportunity to surrender.
I will wait until we are
.08 light-seconds apart.
Should you miss this
opportunity to surrender,
we have an even sweeter destiny
in store for your spaceships.
As a bonus, you will
have the honor of dying
with Abh nobility as you
disintegrate into particles.
Notify all vessels!
[CREW 10]
Yes, Captain.
We will open fire
as soon as they come
within .08 light-seconds,
and by then,
you can promptly ignore
all surrender signals
from the enemy.
Shower them until there's
absolutely nothing left!
Wait one moment!
What is it, Senior Officer?
Firing at a surrendered
enemy will scar the honor
of the Empire and Star Forces.
You know,
you're right in suggesting
that it's not a pretty sight,
so we won't do it.
Yes.
Thanks for accepting
my suggestion.
So then, am I free to
decide on how to transport
the enemy prisoners?
Yes.
You govern as the
chief commander.
Very well.
How many people are
there in the enemy fleet?
[KUFADIS] Well, they have
12 large-scale ships,
so I'd guess 25,000?
So we can fit them on
one Talse transport ship?
One ship?
Well, it's not impossible...
Calculate this for me...
If there were 24,000
on the Talse,
and it had to sail through
Ordinary Space
right to the Capital,
how much time would it take?
Through Ordinary Space only?
Yes, that's right.
[KUFADIS]
Approximately 58,300 years.
I can't imagine the
prisoners being too happy
about such an extended holiday.
[KUFADIS]
I wouldn't think so.
[SPOOR] Then let's shorten
the travel time for them.
Well, there won't be any use
for space-time orb generators.
Nor is there a need for
stabilizers or crew members.
Omit gravitation.
Still seems heavy. Did you
factor in food and water?
[KUFADIS] I've included
a one-year supply,
and hydroponic farming
facilities to supply them
with basic food.
There's no need
for farm facilities.
Please delete that as well.
While we're cutting
out luxury items,
should we also delete food,
water, and air?
The prisoners would
die if we did something
so utterly stupid as that.
I can't dream of
something so brutal.
That'll make it a lot lighter.
Recalculate the travel time.
[KUFADIS] I don't think it makes
that much of a difference.
It's still about 49,100 years.
We should be proud we managed
to reduce the travel time
by almost 10,000 years.
[KUFADIS]
Yes, but...
[SPOOR] Communications
Officer, inform all units
that we will respect their
wish to surrender at any time,
and add that those surrendering
after the battle has begun
will unfortunately be
thoroughly obliged to travel
to the Capital through
Ordinary Space only.
To save travel time,
the ship will unload
space-time orb generators,
gravitational devices,
and stabilizers,
and there will be no crew.
The prisoners will be
given a one-year supply
of food and water.
Arrival time is estimated
at 49,000 years.
That should do.
[KUFADIS]
Please wait, Your Excellency.
Quiet, Senior Officer.
Any further suggestions from you
will be considered dissention.
A lady of chaos...
[SPOOR laughing]
Y'know, I kinda
like that title for me.
[JINTO] Well it looks like
they haven't given up.
[LAFIEL] On the bright side,
they've marked the route for us.
[JINTO]
Yeah.
Y'know, when I'm with you,
I don't get as worried,
and everything just
seems more hopeful.
[JINTO]
We have a problem.
What's wrong...?
They're closing in.
It's a dead end.
Jinto! Get down!
[JINTO] I never imagined I'd
experience being a corpse
while I'm still alive.
[LAFIEL]
Does it still hurt?
[JINTO]
It's just a scratch.
[LAFIEL] Oh, it's humiliating to
ride a ship with no exterior
area sensors or guhakes.
[JINTO] This is not a ship.
It's a coffin.
C-O-F-F-I-N.
[LAFIEL]
It's cramped in here.
I suddenly have the urge
to get away from you.
[JINTO]
Ouch! Be careful, I'm injured.
[LAFIEL] I thought
it was just a scratch.