[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
Listen, Baron.
I hope you realize that our
mission is serious and sacred.
So, should anything
happen to Jinto,
I will not forgive you.
[WAITRESS 1]
Your Highness.
Her Highness is tired
and needs her rest.
Please show her to her room.
[JINTO]
Hm?
[FORMER BARON]
I see you're awake, young man.
Who are you?
[FORMER BARON] When you ask
someone for his name,
you should introduce
yourself first.
I am called Prince Jinto of
the Count Lin Syun Rock Hyde.
You're a count?
I wouldn't have guessed.
But you hardly look like an Abh.
Neither do you.
[FORMER BARON]
Well, I'm the former Baron.
Atos-ryua Syun Atos
Febdash Sluf.
So that makes you
the present Baron's--
[FORMER BARON]
Yes, I am his father.
Then what's the big idea--?
[JINTO groans]
Now calm down and
rest, young man.
It seems my son
has done something,
but I don't know what he's done.
I am not in the mood for jokes!
I'm not kidding you.
[gasps]
Oh, yeah. Lafiel.
Please, tell me, was I brought
to this place alone,
or was there an Abh girl
brought here as well?
I must know!
Was there a girl?
You were the only one I saw.
This girl you're talking
about, young man,
is she your girlfriend?
[JINTO]
My clyuno is missing.
My son is likely the culprit.
I have to see your son at once,
so please take me to him!
That would be impossible.
Why impossible?
[FORMER BARON] Because I am
confined here by my son.
[JINTO]
Huh?
[LAFIEL]
Jinto. Jinto!
[MACHINE 2]
The clyuno you're calling
is presently not being worn.
Show me where I'm
located, right now.
And show me the location
of the Baron's room.
Now then, how about
the guest rooms?
Which ones are
presently being used?
Are any of them used
for confinement?
[MACHINE 2] I cannot
understand your question.
Tell me the names
of everyone here,
and also tell me their
respective locations.
[MACHINE 2]
I cannot do that
without the approval
of the master.
Do you wish to get approval?
Please note--
Oh, forget it!
[gasps]
What about the space harbor?
Is there another possible
route I can take
to get to the moored
communications spacecraft?
[MACHINE 2]
Yes, there is.
And has the route been closed?
[MACHINE 2]
It is not closed,
but you'll need an electric-wave
crest key to get through.
Has my electric-wave
crest been registered?
[MACHINE 2]
No, it hasn't.
Can I register it now?
[MACHINE 2]
I cannot do that
without the approval
of the master.
Do you wish to get an approval?
Please note, however, that the
master is presently resting.
Tell me, whose
crests are registered?
[MACHINE 2]
Our master and every vassal.
The names of the vassals are--
That's enough!
The Baron's father
lives here, am I right?
[MACHINE 2] Yes. The former
Baron resides on this spaceport.
[LAFIEL]
Is the electric-wave crest
of the Baron's
father registered?
[MACHINE 2]
No. It is not registered.
Why is that?
[MACHINE 2]
Orders from the master.
So tell me why the
Baron ordered this.
[MACHINE 2]
I cannot do that
without the approval
of the master.
Do you wish to get an approval?
Please note, however, that...
Just skip that and tell me
where the former
Baron now resides.
I would like meet with
the former Baron.
Please arrange an appointment.
[MACHINE 2]
I cannot do that
without the approval
of the master.
Do you wish to get an approval?
[LAFIEL]
I don't want approval!
Just tell me why should I need
permission from the Baron
just to meet with
the former Baron.
[MACHINE 2]
I do not have an answer.
Naturally.
Tell me, is there anyone else
with the former Baron?
[MACHINE 2]
Yes. One other person.
Tell me his name!
[MACHINE 2] The name
has not been registered.
[LAFIEL] That person's
not a vassal, right?
[MACHINE 2]
That's correct.
Would I need a valid
electric-wave crest
to get to the residence
of the former Baron?
[MACHINE 2] You will need a
general electric-wave crest key
and the approval of the master.
Do you wish--?
I think I know the rest.
[JINTO]
Confined?
[FORMER BARON]
That's right.
I'm given everything I need,
but I don't have the
freedom to go anywhere.
What other word than
"confine" is there
for the situation
I'm in right now?
[JINTO] But the Baron
is your son, isn't he?
That's precisely why, young man.
He is discontent,
because genetically,
I'm a person from Land.
He hides me away so that all
the vassals cannot see me.
Thus he keeps me confined here.
I'm even more confused.
He's got a severe
inferiority complex.
The history of the Baron Febdash
family is still very short.
Only three generations ago,
the family didn't even
have warrior status.
He's always been quite
upset about that fact.
Which, I believe,
was the reason why he
decided to confine me.
He can't stand the sight of
his father, a Land person.
Land person?
That sounds a lot
like my problem.
After being locked up
in here for a while,
I kept reflecting on where
I must have gone wrong
in bringing up my son.
I've had lots of time to think.
Oh, I could give you plenty
of advice on raising a child
if you would like.
Maybe later.
But first, I must
get out of here.
Take it easy, young
man--uh, I mean...
Your Excellency
Count Prince, sir.
But I haven't got any time.
[gasps]
[JINTO]
How long was I unconscious?
Well, it's been about five hours
since you were
brought here, sir.
Five hours?
[SEELNAY]
Your Highness!
Your name is Seelnay, correct?
Oh! I'm honored beyond
belief, Your Highness!
You remembered the name
of a lowly servant.
Uh, where're you going,
Your Highness?
To the spacecraft.
Oh! Uh...
I'm terribly sorry, but our
master asks that you stay away
from the communications
spacecraft.
Um... Um.
[SEELNAY]
Wait, please. Your Highness.
Please. Please!
Your Highness?
[SEELNAY yelps]
Your Highness!
No! You mustn't!
But our master asks
that you stay away
from the communications
spacecraft.
Why are you hesitating, Klowal?
[FEBDASH]
Your decision is correct.
There is nothing to fear.
You even spoke your mind to
a real Abh, the Princess.
There's no mistake
that the enemy
is the Four Nations Alliance.
Should they come here,
do you think they'd allow this
Baron territory to continue?
No, they wouldn't!
So then, why not negotiate
trading the princess
for the Baron
territory's safety?
At the negotiating table,
I won't refuse to
cooperate with them.
Yes, I'll convert
this Baron territory
into an important supply base
for the Four Nations Alliance.
Then they won't be able
to push me around.
However, what if ties with
the Empire are severed
and the enemies don't come?
Ah, yes. That would be
the best scenario.
I could build a
kingdom of my own!
I can become the sole
ruler of this small world
in both name and substance.
I don't need any more
than 50 vassals.
I can live on
cultivated meat alone.
Yes, I can live without
Semryush apple wine if I want.
As long as I can retain
this world that I reign
as the absolute ruler.
[FEBDASH] Also, a Kingdom
does require a successor.
The Princess will
birth a successor.
[beeping]
Yes, what is it?
[GRIEDA] This is Grieda
from housekeeping.
I'm terribly sorry to interrupt
you while you're resting,
but we have an intruder in the
communications spacecraft.
What shall we do?
What's that?
Seelnay, listen!
Yes?
I want you to take me
to Jinto this instant.
To Jinto?
Oh, right, your friend.
The Baron has confined him.
Confined? By our master?
You know where the
former Baron is, don't you?
[SEELNAY]
Yes... but... um...
Well, but our master
must approve access
to number three block.
You must take us
there right now.
That's impossible!
Where can I contact him?
From housekeeping,
but they too--
What?
Then let's take it over.
You and me both.
Y-Your Highness... and myself?
You've used one before?
It's very easy.
[screams]
We have no time.
[SEELNAY]
B-But...
Listen to me.
At the same time that
you're the Baron's vassal,
you also belong to the Empire.
Is it more important to you
to wash the Baron's back?
Is it more important to
pour the Baron's wine?
Or... will you assist our Star
Forces mission together with me?
Well, I...
I'll follow your orders,
Your Highness.
I am grateful to you.
[SEELNAY] Your words are
too kind. Uh! Your Highness!
What's wrong?
I have one little
request for you.
Go ahead.
If I act against my master,
I will not be able
to remain here.
Please include me as one of
your vassals, Your Highness.
But I have no
vassals serving me.
You're joking!
Well, sure.
Many vassals serve the
Clyuve Royal family.
My father hires the vassals,
but I'll put in a good
word about you to him.
Oh my! I am truly honored!
You can do without that.
I don't have to do what,
Your Highness?
[LAFIEL sighs]
Hey, hey.
I realize you're in a hurry,
but you must have at least
an hour or two to spare.
How about relaxing for
a while, Your Excellency?
Could you take it easy
with the "Your
Excellency" bit, dear sir?
I'm not too comfortable
with that term.
[FORMER BARON]
Well, it looks like you've got
several problems of
your own, young man.
Just the same, a count has
the rank of a feudal lord.
My own mother did pretty well
for someone from the Land,
but straight from
citizen to count?
I don't know if it's your
father or your mother,
but he or she did very well.
It's my father.
You know, my father wasn't
even a citizen of the Empire,
so he certainly
turned a lot of heads.
Could you tell me
more about him?
I'm very sorry, but I
really must be-- Hm?
Really?
Well, then, I must
respect your wishes.
[JINTO]
There's not one window
where I could get
out from, is there?
Of course there isn't.
Even if there was, this area is
surrounded with tall pastures,
so you won't see anything.
In outer space, it's more
practical not to have windows.
[gasps]
[JINTO]
This is awesome.
[FORMER BARON]
Wait a minute.
Where've you been all your life
to be impressed by such
a common device?
[JINTO] It wasn't the
device I was impressed with.
I was moved by this
fascinating scenery.
[FORMER BARON]
Oh, sorry about that.
Is this an example of
Abh illusionary art?
So you know about it, young man.
I truly believe that
nothing of their culture
reflects the pride of the
Abh more than this scenery.
One can keep his
dignity to himself.
There's no sense going
around telling everyone.
However, that unworthy son...
Rather than become
the highest mountain,
he chooses to avoid the
mountains and dig deep valleys,
satisfying himself
that he's situated
higher than valley pits.
[JINTO]
Uh... Your Excellency?
[FORMER BARON]
Oh, right.
You haven't got time for this,
have you, young man?
[JINTO] Are there no
communicators in here?
[FORMER BARON]
Well, there is,
but it's only connected
to housekeeping.
I doubt they'll transfer
you to that girl
you were talking about.
[JINTO] Then how about either
of us acting like we're sick?
[FORMER BARON] Me getting sick
just after you come here?
They'll get awfully suspicious.
[JINTO] Then let's say
that I'm prone to illness.
[FORMER BARON]
Hmm...
I wonder if my son
would even care
whether you were dead or alive.
[JINTO]
Please take me there anyway.
If I can get through...
If she finds out,
maybe she could...
[FORMER BARON]
What confidence you have in her.
She must be a special girl.
[JINTO] She's a...
Princess of the Empire.
[FORMER BARON]
You don't say!
[LAFIEL]
Stay right where you are.
Direct orders from Star Forces.
I demand that you connect
me to the former Baron.
That is strictly prohibited.
[LAFIEL] Forget about the
Baron's orders. Hurry up!
[gasps]
Don't move, Kuhaspia!
How dare you!
[BOTH scream]
Tell me what's
happening, Seelnay.
[SEELNAY]
Look, Alisa!
I'm a vassal of Her Highness.
[LAFIEL]
Hurry, now!
You're really serious,
aren't you, Your Highness?
Well, I wouldn't
shoot if I weren't.
[GRIEDA]
I understand.
[LAFIEL]
Hm?
[door opens]
What seems to be the
problem, Your Highness?
Well, you've come at
the right time, Baron.
You shall cooperate.
Why do you wait to protect me?
[VASSALS mumbling]
How dare you point your
guns at Her Royal Highness!
Seelnay! How dare you betray me!
Citizen Seelnay is
under my protection.
Oh. Your Highness.
I couldn not be more grateful
to you than I already am!
Your Highness,
you're overreacting.
Have I not welcomed
you with open arms?
[LAFIEL] In that case,
you shall let us go.
You're not allowed.
I will rescue Prince Jinto
with or without your help.
All I have to do is slice
this spaceport apart.
I am a genuine Abh nobleman.
I will not submit to threats,
so you can do what you will.
[VASSALS chattering]
Wait. We're sorry. Don't leave.
[KUHASPIA]
Hmph.
You always were the
Baron's favorite.
[KUHASPIA]
Hm.
[JINTO]
Huh?
Your Highness,
we're now connected.
Am I talking to the
former Febdash Baron?
[JINTO]
Lafiel?
Oh, it's you! Are you all right?
[JINTO]
Yeah, somehow.
And you, you're okay?
I'm okay.
Be careful, Jinto. The Baron
could be on his way there.
[JINTO]
Why? For what?
Jinto, sometimes your
naivete is so charming.
I think that he wants you dead.
What-What should I do?
We've got no weapons
around here anywhere.
[LAFIEL]
Is there any way out of there?
Lafiel, I'm at a complete
loss without you around.
[LAFIEL]
I thought so.
Not yet?
I'm trying.
[ALISA]
Oh...
What is it?
The controls have
been... taken over!
Did you hear that, Jinto?
It would seem that the
Baron simply has no time
to destroy you.
Well, what a shame.
[ALISA] I'm terribly
sorry, Your Highness.
I can't gain access
to number three block.
Try a sketch map.
[ALISA]
Okay.
Lafiel?
[LAFIEL]
Jinto!
Can you see the
ceiling from there?
Look straight at its center.
[JINTO]
Why, it's...
It's an exit!
Of course, the pier!
You do have your own
spacecraft, have you not?
[JINTO]
A pier? Way out here?
Long ago, this was an arrival
and departure hall for guests.
They've since gotten
rid of the elevator,
so that exit now opens
directly into space.
[LAFIEL] I'm going to take
our spacecraft there.
We'll depart as soon
as you get there.
[JINTO] The Baron has the
communications spacecraft.
That ship does not
belong to the Baron.
It's an official
Star Forces ship.
I'll be waiting.
[FORMER BARON]
Hmm...
Are you sure you
two aren't in love
with each other
just a little bit?
No. Not at all.
[FORMER BARON] But there
aren't many in the Empire
who can casually call
Her Highness by her name.
Well, uh... let's
say that's just a...
[FORMER BARON]
Uh-huh?
...a feat achieved through
ignorance and very good luck.
Well, that sounds like
a fascinating story.
[FORMER BARON laughing]
[JINTO] I still had no idea
that a genuine Princess,
who happened to
drop by this star,
was about to trigger a serious
incident, all on her own.
[ALISA]
A dispute has been started
on this Baronial spaceport.
[FEBDASH]
Can I really trust you women?
Question us?
[FEBDASH]
I-I see.
Yes, you can trust us.
[LAFIEL]
Well done, Baron.