[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
[LAFIEL]
Vassal Seelnay, Vassal Alisa,
and although I don't
know your names...
All the other Empire citizens
who cooperated with me...
I thank you very much.
I will return as soon as I can.
I ask that you wait
for me until then.
[FORMER BARON] You still
insist on going to Sufugnoff?
[LAFIEL]
It's my mission.
There is a chance
you could find yourself
in the midst of a battle
without any protection.
[LAFIEL]
I'm going.
I was taught that
when uncertain whether
to stop or go, I go.
[FORMER BARON]
Farewell, young man.
Come again when
you have some time.
Tell me the story of
how the Count Hyde family
was formed.
In return, I'll give you
a thorough explanation
on the know-how of the Abh.
Yes, sir. I'd like that.
If possible, before you
decide to have children.
Sure.
[JINTO]
And so we refueled our ship,
said our goodbyes
to the former Baron,
and finally left
the Febdash territory.
Then we headed for what
was likely a battlefield.
[LAFIEL]
Jinto.
The gates to Sufugnoff
now appear within range.
What's the situation?
[LAFIEL] There are a
number of space-time orbs.
I don't know if they're
enemies or allies.
And if they're enemies?
We'll force our way.
Of course.
In about seven hours,
we'll enter the Sufugnoff gates.
I hope they'll greet us with
a much warmer reception.
Possibly they'll greet us
with intense, hot firepower.
[LAFIEL]
Jinto. I've got some bad news.
[JINTO]
I figured.
You don't have
to tell me any more.
They're asking whether
or not we're allies.
From the Empire?
[LAFIEL] I don't know
whose signal it is.
But I do know it's
not the Empire's.
Can't we deceive them,
and just tell them that...
...that we're allies?
How can you even think
of such a foolish tactic?
I guess it's my upbringing
showing through...
[beeping]
--[JINTO] Huh?
--[LAFIEL] That's it!
Wh-What is?
It's an order to cease.
They say that unless
we come to a halt,
they will open fire on us.
You're not about
to stop now, are you?
[LAFIEL]
Do you want me to stop?
[JINTO]
No.
Then, here we go.
[JINTO yells]
Did we dodge 'em?
Please don't follow us!
--I'll elude them.
--[JINTO] Can we?
If the mines run out
of fuel, we can.
[JINTO]
What about our fuel?
Oh, please, God...
[beeping]
[JINTO]
There's more!
Who in the universe
ordered extra mines?
We just might be
able to beat them.
It seems that they're
almost out of fuel,
so they sent out more mines.
[JINTO]
All right! Oh, no...
No, we're okay!
We can make it!
[JINTO gasps]
[JINTO]
Huh?
They're coming, Lafiel!
Increase to battle speed!
[JINTO grunting]
I bet they'll just
keep on chasing us
right up to normal space!
[LAFIEL grunts]
Our acceleration
functions are much better
in normal space.
[JINTO grunting]
We made it!
The mines?
[LAFIEL]
They followed.
[JINTO chuckles]
[JINTO] They misjudged
where we'd come out.
Won't there be enemies in
this section of space, too?
I don't think so.
[JINTO]
But it is possible, right?
[LAFIEL] They're too
busy with other things.
Look over there.
You see, the enemies
in Plane Space
were not guarding
against the Star Forces
coming from afar...
They were blocking
access to Sufugnoff.
So then they're in
the midst of a battle, huh?
[LAFIEL]
Mm-hm.
[LAFIEL] Empire Star Forces,
please respond.
We come from the
patrol ship, Gosroth.
[LAFIEL] Empire Star Forces,
please come in.
Empire Star Forces,
[beep]
You have reached Sufugnoff base.
Please report now,
communications spacecraft.
[LAFIEL, JINTO sigh]
The Gosroth patrol ship
recently encountered
unidentified space-time
orbs in Area Itoum 533.
[LEXSHUE grunts]
[LAFIEL] Our ship has hereby
arrived at this nation
ahead of the Gosroth
with the ship's logbook
and a civilian.
Roger. Understood.
In accordance with military
confidentiality policies,
disclose no more.
Understood, Sufugnoff base.
Instructions, please.
[OFFICER 1] I regret to
inform you we cannot have
your spacecraft enter our base.
You're on your own.
Understood.
Sufugnoff base,
from here on, I will proceed
without any assistance.
I hope you win.
Yeah. It's a slim
possibility, a tough battle.
But... may the
Empire be victorious.
Does that mean
they're about to lose?
Yes, of course they are!
The troops posted in the
respective nations are limited.
One communications base is
not likely going to withstand
a full-fledged invasion!
[JINTO] Sorry.
That was a stupid question.
[LAFIEL]
It's okay.
I'm sorry, Jinto.
After all, I failed to get you
to your destination safely.
Hey, it's not your fault.
'Kay? Now, what about the enemy?
They're far.
But three vessels are
headed over this way.
They really have a thing
for the number three,
don't they?
What's with three? Huh?
What could that be?
An orbiting tower. [gasps]
[JINTO] It's been
destroyed by the enemy.
[LAFIEL]
What a lowly thing to do.
Orbiting towers are
not military bases.
Hey.
Is this spacecraft
capable of landing?
[LAFIEL]
Landing?
That's right.
If there's no orbiting towers,
we've got no choice but to land.
It might land.
It might land?
[LAFIEL]
Yes. It looks like it can.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me you weren't
even thinking of landing
until I asked?
Well...
Then what were you planning?
Thought I'd help
with the battle.
But... how?
This spacecraft is unarmed!
I wasn't thinking.
Yet...
There just might be
something we can do...
There are those three
enemy vessels on our tail...
You brainless jerk!
[LAFIEL]
Hmph!
I'll have to accept
whatever you say.
After all, I did
trivialize your life, Jinto.
[JINTO]
Your own life, too.
You people are able to
live a much longer life,
so why are you
in a hurry to die?
We are not in a hurry to die.
It certainly does look that way.
But the battle
has already begun.
Look, when a soldier
goes out to a battlefield,
there's only one thing to do.
[JINTO]
Then do as you wish!
But as for me,
I am not a soldier...
Please let me off
at this planet!
Well, fine then,
your presence is of
no practical use out here
in the battlefield anyway.
Yeah, neither is your presence.
[LAFIEL gasps]
I'm sorry.
You're right, of course.
I know it...
I am useless.
[JINTO]
I told you before.
You're a great help to me.
You see, I may be
useless right now,
but someday someone
might rely on me.
I'd like to live until then,
and I'd also like you
to live until then.
[LAFIEL]
Yeah.
[beeping]
Is it the base?
No...
It's from the
spaceship up ahead.
Enemies... Close?
Yes. Very.
They're saying they'll
open fire unless we halt.
I hoped they would say
something more humorous.
I wouldn't want to
be killed by people
who lacked a sense of humor.
Neither would I.
[BOTH chuckle]
Well, then,
we really should hurry
on down to that planet.
First, we'll have to elude them.
[JINTO grunts]
Are we safe now?
Even if they changed
direction now,
there's no way they'd
catch up with us.
We're entering the atmosphere.
Try and stay calm, okay?
Try and be gentle, 'kay?
[JINTO grunts]
What's that?
What's the matter?
Hey, don't worry.
I only disengaged
the main engine.
[JINTO]
What do you mean "only"?
We can't enter
the atmosphere--
not with tanks containing
anti-substance fuel.
We have to think
about the residents.
[JINTO]
But...
The communications
spacecraft is not designed
for landing on ground.
Landing is not any different
than an emergency escape, Jinto.
[JINTO yelling]
Are we really gonna be fine?
I'm just as scared as you.
It's my first time, too!
[JINTO grunts]
It's your first time?
I already said...
I've never been to the
Land world in my whole life!
[JINTO] But haven't you
trained in landings?
[LAFIEL]
I did train!
Which one scares you more?
Landing, or the
Land world itself?
Both scare me!
[yells]
Did we make it in one piece?
Yeah...
Jinto, let's hurry...
They may be watching
us from above.
[JINTO sighs]
Right.
[LAFIEL]
Open!
You shall hold this.
Uh... yeah.
All set?
All set.
[LAFIEL]
Prepare to nullify.
[JINTO gasps]
[MACHINE 4] Preparations
complete to nullify.
Goodbye.
Launch self-destruct.
[MACHINE 4]
Acknowledged.
Deleting all information
and recorded transactions
in accordance with
confidentiality regulations.
I pray for your safety.
Well, that sure
makes me feel better.
Now. Let's go.
[LAFIEL gasps, groans]
What's wrong?
[LAFIEL]
Uh... It's nothing.
[JINTO grunts]
[LAFIEL grunts]
[LAFIEL]
Jinto. Wait a minute.
What's the matter?
Jinto...
I think there's something
wrong with my eyes.
Oh, no. What is it?
[LAFIEL] To me, the stars
look like they're flickering.
[JINTO]
Huh?
[LAFIEL] I don't want
to become a burden.
Should I be going blind,
take this logbook with you,
and proceed without me, please.
[JINTO chuckles]
Lafiel...
I hate to punch holes in your
self-sacrificing spirit...
...but stars naturally
twinkle when looked at
from within the atmosphere.
[LAFIEL gasps]
Does it look the same to you?
[JINTO]
Mm-hm.
[LAFIEL]
Really?
Well, why would I want to
trick you in our situation?
Stunning.
[JINTO] You know, I'm
beginning to see real results
in the education
you've received.
[LAFIEL]
Shut up, Jinto.
[JINTO]
We slept overnight in a cave,
and when I woke up,
it was already evening.
[MACHINE 5] Let's give thanks
to the United Mankind
for liberating us
from the rule of the
Humankind Empire Abh.
[JINTO]
The area was very quiet.
No sign of war anywhere.
However...
[MACHINE 5] This is a message
from the United Mankind.
[MACHINE 5] The reason we
entered this Nation Sufugnoff
was to retaliate against
the reckless actions
taken by the
"Humankind Empire Abh."
[JINTO]
I knew it.
[MACHINE 5] While we were
investigating the Plane Space
around a newly discovered Sord,
a warship of the Empire
suddenly opened fire on us.
[JINTO]
That's a lie!
Ambassador, it is clear to me
that you are telling a lie.
A lie?
You have stated that a warship
of the Empire suddenly
appeared and opened fire,
but there aren't any in our
highly respectable Star Forces
that would challenge
anyone without just cause.
It seems obvious to me
that this case has
been an exception.
If it were such
an exceptional case,
the ship would not have lost.
[MACHINE 5] We were able
to drive this warship back.
However, we cannot
justify such an attack
without warning.
[MACHINE 5] We therefore have
occupied this Nation Sufugnoff
as a form of retaliation,
and to guarantee our safety
around this new Sord.
[JINTO] What if this is Gosroth
that they're talking about?
Ambassador.
I had such great expectations
you would bring me lies
that were served
with more taste.
So I'm quite disappointed.
It's too bad.
[MAKALI] We should investigate
this matter further
before jumping to conclusions.
I suggest that we form a
joint investigative committee
between the
"Humankind Empire Abh"
and the United Mankind,
and select supervising members
from the three neutral nations.
So then, are you also
lying to me?
You have formed an
alliance with each other,
and that makes you
far from being neutral.
[MAKALI]
Majesty!
Majesty.
Should you make
a declaration of war
against the United
Mankind nation,
in accordance with
the Nova Sicily Treaty,
the People's Sovereign
Union of the Planets
must declare war
against your own nation.
[RAMAJ]
I'm aware of that.
And I suppose it will
be the same for the
"Republic of Greater Alcont"
and the "Federation of Hania."
Okay, then...
Let's go to war.
[SANGALINI gasps]
Majesty...
Please think this matter over.
You must realize that
you will have to fight
against half of all humankind.
[RAMAJ] Have you forgotten,
Ambassador?
The other half belongs
to this Empire.
I'll tell you this
much for certain.
The Empire lacks the faith
in a higher being.
There is absolutely
no way you can win.
[RAMAJ]
Of course.
Our Empire does not
have such faith. However...
I never knew such faith
had anything to do
with the outcome of a battle...
It must be one
of your superstitions.
Thank you all for coming.
I do hope you have a
safe journey back home.
Your diplomatic privileges
will be nullified
in exactly 24 hours.
Finally, one more issue.
Should we win
this battle with you,
it will be the final war
for humankind.
An everlasting peace?
People have dreamed
of this thing for ages.
However, it has never
actually happened, Majesty.
That's because
there haven't been
any Abhs until now.
[JINTO] Above our heads,
far away in outer space,
a war had officially just begun.
You jerk.
Lafiel!
I'll be back as soon
as possible, so wait here.
[LAFIEL]
Mm-hm.
Besides, you, uh...
stand out too much.
[LAFIEL]
Huh?
Come on, don't overdo it.
You're the only one
I can trust within a radius
of 100 light-years.
[JINTO] It'd be nice if
she'd say something like that
just once.