[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
[LAFIEL]
Tell me.
Am I?
Tell me, am I a
"daughter of love"?
[LAFIEL]
Jinto, look ahead.
[JINTO]
What?
[gasps]
[JINTO]
Is that the Gosroth ?
That's right.
You see, it's much
bigger than this ship is.
[JINTO]
Hmm.
[gasps]
[JINTO]
Wow.
I-It's huge. Immense.
So you noticed.
Uh, well, it's just...
It's tough from a
distance out in Space.
See, you've got your
extra-sensory system,
which makes a difference.
Well, don't look that way.
Not with pity.
It's just one way we
humans are different.
Yes, you're right.
And, therefore, I'll allow you
extra time to observe it.
Thank you. You're
being very kind.
[LAFIEL]
The Gosroth is one of
the Empire's
superior spaceships.
It has a length of
12.82 Westage.
[JINTO]
Is that all?
[LAFIEL] It's smaller than
a front line battleship
or transport carrier, but you
won't find another vessel
with more battle power
within all the Empire,
or within all inhabited Space.
I'm sure you're right.
[sighs]
What's wrong, trainee?
Why don't you knock
off the horseplay?
I was showing His
Excellency the Prince
the difference between our
ship and patrol ships.
What are you talking about?
[JINTO, LAFIEL chuckle]
[LAFIEL]
We're here.
[JINTO]
Thank you.
[LAFIEL]
I'm just doing my job.
[JINTO]
Uh... Can I see you later?
[LAFIEL]
The residential area is limited.
It's possible we'll
bump into each other.
[JINTO]
Oh, well, see ya.
And thanks for bringing me here.
[LAFIEL]
I had fun.
[JINTO]
Glad to hear it.
[whistling]
[LEXSHUE]
We are very pleased
to welcome you aboard,
Your Excellency.
I am Captain Lexshue
of this ship, Gosroth .
[gasps]
[JINTO]
The Abhs do introduce themselves
when they see someone
for the first time.
I'm Prince Jinto of the
Count Lin Syun Rock Hyde.
I'll be depending on you
to get me to the Capital.
You are in good hands.
Let's prepare for launch!
All engines are stable.
The ship's pressure is normal.
Preparations are now complete.
Approved to pass through Sord
by the State of Count Vorash.
We must pass through
within six seconds
after 15:27 and
12 seconds, our time.
The ship is now prepared
for departure.
Excellent. Accelerate
six demons.
We're heading for Sord Vorak.
Changing course to 17-62-55.
Acknowledged.
The course direction
is now finalized!
[LEXSHUE speaking in Baronh]
[GYUMURYUA]
All the engines are now stable.
Three minutes till
we reach Sord.
Space-time shots!
[GYUMURYUA] Space-time
shot generator stable!
[LESHIKURIA]
Space-time shots confirmed.
[JINTO gasps]
So, we're about to
travel through Space
of a different
dimension, aren't we?
[LEXSHUE]
That is true.
But you won't notice
much difference
while in this spaceship.
There will be no vibration.
The only difference will be a
shift in color to a dull gray.
One minute till we reach Sord.
Start the countdown
from 15 seconds.
[LAIRIA]
Yes, captain.
Fifteen,
ourteen, thirteen,
twelve, eleven,
ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
Passing through.
[LEXSHUE]
Confirm position.
Did you know that we
are completely unaware
of our location where we exist?
Huh? What d'ya mean by that?
[LEXSHUE] When converting
from Space to Plane Space,
we can only assume our position
through theoretical
probabilities.
Are you aware of the term
"theoretical probabilities"?
Something like "random guess"?
That is quite accurate.
Sord frequently presents
incomplete spiral curves
on the side of the Plane Space,
but we have no idea as
to what part of that curve
we'll come out of.
[SARIUSH]
Finished confirming position.
On the right shore,
1, 17, and 90.
Acknowledged. Bring up
the plane image for me.
[LAIRIA] Positioned for
transfer at 28 degrees.
Please compute the route.
Our destination is
the Sord in Sufugnoff.
[LAIRIA]
Computation complete.
Acknowledged.
I'll just leave the rest to you,
Lairia. Stay on route.
Yes, captain.
I suspect the rest
of our operation
will bore Your Excellency,
even if it is your first time.
Um.
I'm having some trouble getting
used to that "Excellency" bit.
And why is that?
[JINTO] I've got no idea how
I should behave as a nobleman.
How to behave?
[JINTO]
Um, am I behaving strangely?
[SARIUSH]
Hm?
[LEXSHUE]
Strangely?
I mean, are feudal lords
expected to be arrogant?
Sometimes they are forgiven
for being arrogant.
However, they don't leave
a very good impression.
Is that right?
Then my behavior isn't
so strange after all.
Well, it's better than
being arrogant.
[JINTO]
Hmm.
You appear quite tired.
Not really.
I'll have someone show
you to your room.
How about the young trainee
who escorted you here earlier?
Oh, the trainee. Isn't
she also a noblewoman?
[LEXSHUE]
Um...
She's not.
That's strange.
She certainly seemed like
a genuine nobleperson.
[LAIRIA]
Don't you know who she is?
No. Who is she? Someone
I should've heard of?
No.
Given your distinct background,
I'm not surprised you
don't know of her.
Pilot trainee Abriel,
report to the bridge at once.
A-Abriel?
Princess of the
Clyuve Royal family.
She is the granddaughter of
Her Majesty Empress Ramaj.
She's royalty?
[JINTO] I had gotten quite
used to embarrassments
over the years.
But I had never faced
an embarrassment
as huge as the one
I'm facing now.
[LAFIEL] What's wrong, Jinto?
You're being awfully quiet.
And why are you
walking behind me?
Well, you see,
Imperial Princess...
[LAFIEL]
Huh?
[gasps]
I'm not an Imperial Princess,
though my grandmother
is the Empress.
I'm only royal, since
my father is a king.
P-Please forgive me,
Royal Princess.
[LAFIEL] If you insist
on harping on the fact
that I'm related to the Empress,
call me the granddaughter
of the Empress,
even though that's not used,
since "Your Highness
Imperial granddaughter"
doesn't sound right, does it?
[JINTO]
You're exactly right.
I mean, I agree, Your Highness.
Incidentally, when I was born,
I was also bestowed
with the title and domain
of Viscount Paryunu with my
father acting as guardian,
so on occasion,
I am also referred to
as Viscount Paryunu.
And even more recently,
I've been referred to
as pilot trainee Abriel.
However, I thought
I told you earlier
that you shall call me Lafiel.
Uh... Sure.
So your friends call you Lafiel?
[LAFIEL]
Not necessarily.
None of my friends refer
to me without a title.
[JINTO]
Then... why?
[LAFIEL] It was the first time
anyone asked me for my name.
It seems as a granddaughter
of an Empress,
I'm well known, and
everyone knows my name
and recognizes me.
Instantly, people call you
"the Royal Princess."
My best friends call
me "Your Highness."
I sort of envy the other
trainees at the institution
who call each other by name.
Sorry. I, uh...
It got even worse
when I began to notice
that others found it difficult
to relax when I was around.
I'm really very sorry.
[LAFIEL] There's nothing
to be sorry about.
I mean to say, you've done
nothing wrong, have you?
You may have erred in calling
me "Imperial Princess,"
but it wasn't out of spite.
I haven't been brought up
to tolerate
disrespectful references,
but I shall accept any
title if it is correct.
So call me "Royal Princess,"
"Viscount Paryunu,"
or whatever you wish to call me,
Your Excellency Count Prince.
No. I'll call you Lafiel.
[LAFIEL]
Don't get me wrong,
I'm not insisting that
you call me Lafiel.
Yes. Please.
I want to call you Lafiel,
and nothing else.
You don't have to.
You know that.
But I really do want to.
How about "Imperial
granddaughter"?
Oh, this is insane.
What do I have to say to have
you forgive me, Lafiel?
[giggles]
[JINTO]
Huh?
I can sort of relate to that.
Since I was actually the only
flesh-and-blood nobleman
at my school.
[LAFIEL]
This is your room here.
[JINTO]
I meant to ask you.
How come there are so many
paintings around here?
For decoration.
Wouldn't you agree that a
warship needs some charm?
But it doesn't seem to match.
I'm sure there are pictures more
appropriate for a spaceship.
Lafiel, what feeling do you
get when you see these?
What do you mean by that?
[JINTO] Well, you've never seen
real sunflowers, have you?
[LAFIEL]
Sure, I've seen sunflowers.
The capital does have
a botanical garden,
and our residence has
its own flower garden.
[JINTO]
I see. Then how about this one?
[LAFIEL] I'm sure I've never
seen anything like it.
[JINTO] So, what does
it look like to you?
[LAFIEL] Let's see.
Like a scenery in a dream.
[JINTO] Of a place that
doesn't really exist?
[LAFIEL]
No, not really.
I can tell we initially came
from places like this one.
[JINTO]
A home you've abandoned?
[LAFIEL]
Our home is now in Outer Space.
We are the only citizens
of the Cosmos,
and we're very proud of that.
[LAFIEL] How does that
picture look to you, Jinto?
Is that scenery common on Land?
[JINTO]
No.
A scenery like that one
is quite rare on Land.
[LAFIEL]
Then how does it look to you?
[JINTO]
Hmm...
Whenever I see a
blue sky like that,
I remember my mother who died.
[LAFIEL]
Hm?
I was once told
when I was little
that my mother had
gone to the skies.
Your mother?
But aren't you--? I thought you
were the son of a father.
Aren't you the son of His
Excellency Count Hyde?
[JINTO]
He's my father.
Hm.
Oh, I see!
You've heard of a spousal system
called marriage, haven't you?
I have! I see!
So what's it like for you
to live with two parents?
Were you sad when
your mother died?
Oh, yes.
I was devastated.
[LAFIEL]
Oh.
You must forgive me.
I should not have asked you
such a thoughtless question.
No. It's okay.
I don't quite remember her death
since it happened long time ago
when I was just a child.
Although, I do often remember
the parents who brought me up.
But that way,
you can't possibly have
any birth secrets, true?
What do you mean by that?
I'm not sure what you're saying.
[LAFIEL]
I had a birth secret.
I didn't know whether or
not I was a daughter of love.
Wouldn't that make you uneasy?
[JINTO]
A daughter of love?
What's that?
Don't you know?
Well, there was a great
deal of material
that wasn't taught in
the classes I attended.
Do you know how Abhs are born?
[JINTO]
Huh?
Well, I-I do know
that it's traditionally
not through conception
into a human body.
Oh, sometimes we do.
But to examine the genes...
[LAFIEL] First, the fertilized
egg is taken out of the body.
Often it's transferred
to an artificial uterus,
but some women transfer
it back inside them
for the unique experience.
[JINTO]
Oh. I see.
[LAFIEL] But it is true that
conception normally takes place
in an artificial uterus.
To our race,
it seems that every single
Abh has a birth secret.
Oh, I did study about it,
but the information was
completely out of whack.
[LAFIEL]
In what way?
[JINTO]
Huh?
Well, like cloning yourself
to make your own child,
or mix the genes of
a complete stranger,
or even combine the
genes of someone
of the same sex with your own.
In addition, the other
person may be a relative.
How can you even think
of such a thing, huh?
[LAFIEL]
We do all of those things.
We should be free to
do just as we want.
B-But...
Yet, the most natural
way to make a child
is to combine the
genes of yourself
with the genes of
the person you love.
I'm so relieved to
hear you say that.
To tell a person that
you want their genes
is a very highly regarded
way to express one's love.
[JINTO]
Hmm.
[LAFIEL] And children born as
a result of this disclosure--
[JINTO] I get it!
"The daughter of love," right?
[LAFIEL]
Right.
Or the "son of love"
if the child is a boy.
Then why don't you ask your
father who your mother is?
Just ask him directly.
Or is it that your
father has...?
[LAFIEL]
Hmm?
Oh, no, my father's
still alive and well.
He should be around
for another 200 years.
Is that what you were assuming?
Or did I misunderstand?
[JINTO]
No, you're right.
Why didn't you just ask him?
[LAFIEL]
I did ask him, in fact.
But my father would not tell me.
He'd say that a child's
personality becomes richer
when the child has
a birth secret.
[sighs]
[JINTO chuckles]
It's not funny.
[JINTO]
Sorry. Can't you check into it?
No, regulations dictate
that my genetic records
cannot be released until
I become an adult.
[JINTO]
Is that so?
My father was always teasing me.
[JINTO]
What?
I'd pester him daily about
the supplier of my genes.
One day, he said he'd
bring home the supplier.
And here's the other half.
Where you came from.
[meows]
[LAFIEL]
She was the cat we owned!
[laughing]
[JINTO] You didn't
believe that, did you?
What do you expect?
I was only eight years old!
I cried all night and day.
I grew sick with worry and fear.
[LAFIEL] I'd wonder if my
palms would start to swell
and become paws, or if
I'd start growing claws,
or if the shape of
my iris would change.
Holia was a great little cat,
but I didn't want her
to be half of my origin.
What I also couldn't
stand was thinking
what a weirdo my father was
to have his child with a cat.
[JINTO laughs]
--[LAFIEL] Hey!
--[thud]
Stop laughing!
I'm sorry.
But you really don't believe
that story anymore, do you?
No.
But I still remember
those worrisome days.
The main reason I
entered the forces
to become a pilot so quickly
was to get away from my father.
[JINTO]
Do you dislike your father?
I don't dislike him.
I love him, and I'm
very proud of him.
It's just that,
when we're together,
he can sometimes
be quite irritating.
[JINTO]
Hmm.
Hey, I noticed you've been
speaking in the past tense.
Did he ever tell
you who she was?
[LAFIEL]
Mh-hm.
And she's a woman
that I know very well.
I know now that I'm
a daughter of love.
[chuckles]
I'm glad for you.
[JINTO] At that time,
we had absolutely no idea
that a long, long war
was about to begin.
The United Mankind.
Now, go on. Get moving.
Lafiel.
Nothing?
Hold on.