[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
We are the Gosroth
communications spacecraft.
We are calling the Baron
Febdash Area Control.
[MUINISHU] This is the Baron
[LAFIEL]
Requesting to refuel.
Communications spacecraft
of a patrol ship?
Roger.
We welcome you, communications
spacecraft of Gosroth .
Please indicate where
you wish to refuel.
[LAFIEL] Since this is
a light-weight craft,
we request to refuel
at the pier.
[MUINISHU]
Roger.
So what amount
of fuel do you...?
[gasps]
[MUINISHU]
Your Highness!
[JINTO]
Huh?
They know her everywhere.
Can you lead us
over to the pier?
Of course, Your Highness!
Yes! Right away!
Baron Febdash Area Control,
I have important news for you.
[JINTO]
Hm.
[JINTO] We were unaware
of the death of Gosroth .
[JINTO] That may have been
a fortunate thing for us.
[JINTO] How long will
we be able to stay here?
[LAFIEL]
I'd say 30 minutes.
[JINTO]
That's it?
[LAFIEL] We must get to
Sufugnoff as soon as possible.
[JINTO]
I know that.
But how far ahead are we of the
enemy fleet in terms of time?
[LAFIEL] About 27 hours
in Sufugnoff time.
In that case, can't we...?
[gulps]
Uh, forget I mentioned it.
I'm grateful you
haven't forgotten.
[JINTO gasps]
Your Highness, we bid you
and your companion welcome.
I will escort you
to your quarters now.
I shall have you
do that, but...
I am presently a trainee
of the Star Forces.
I ask that you treat me as such.
Yes, we understand
what you say.
This way now. Please,
Your Highness.
It's always this formal?
Not at all!
[JINTO]
Huh?
Hey...
[JINTO]
Hm?
You may sit over
here in this chair.
Huh? Why over there?
That's because...
[JINTO]
I get it.
I'm just no more to them
than a suspicious
person from the Land.
Jinto. Why are you
waiting there? Come here.
Okay.
What can I get you to drink
that would please you most?
Perhaps later.
I would like you to tell me
where I can take
a shower instead.
[MUINISHU] We cannot allow
a princess to bear a shower.
We will show you to our
executive bath hall.
Please give us a moment.
We don't have a lot of time.
And Imperial family
members shower, too.
I didn't realize.
I haven't the authority
to respond to that.
What drink can I prepare
for you to enjoy?
[LAFIEL]
Hmm...
Hm?
[JINTO]
Huh?
Uh... I'll have a
lemonade, please.
A nice cold one.
I'll have a hot til nom.
And with a slice of lope in it.
You out lope in your til nom?
That's a strange combination.
Huh?
[gasps]
[MUINISHU]
Very well.
I shall bring you your
til nom right away.
Just one moment.
Gee, I wonder if they'll
bring my lemonade.
Seelnay! How-How could you?
I'm terribly sorry,
Your Highness!
What's the matter?
[SEELNAY] I spilt the drink
I just served you.
I-I don't know how I can
repay you for my failure.
I-I beg you to please
accept my apology.
Your failure? You mean this?
Oh my goodness gracious!
L-Let me clean your fingers
for you immediately, okay?
You needn't bother with that.
I'm not sure how much you know
about Abhs raised in palaces,
but I can wipe my own fingers.
[SEELNAY]
I realize that, but I...
[JINTO] But y'know,
I think it'd be really silly
to take this subject
any further.
Uh, yes, uh...
I don't feel
comfortable in here.
Maybe I'll wash up elsewhere.
I'm sorry for not
greeting Your Highness.
I know you as Lafiel of
the Clyuve Royal Family.
I am Viscountess Abriel
Nei Dobrusk Paryunu Lafiel.
I'm Baron Atosryua Syun
Atos Febdash Klowal.
The pleasure is all mine.
[LAFIEL] Mine as well, Baron.
This is His Excellency,
Prince of Count Lin
Syun Rock Hyde, Jinto.
[JINTO] Nice to meet you,
Your Excellency.
I'm very pleased to have you
as a guest, Your Excellency.
Your Highness, I beg you.
Please accept my apology
for a most grievous error.
Which is?
[FEBDASH] We've made
an unfortunate mistake.
We've just realized that
we lack the fuel you need.
That can't be! Your Controller
confirmed to me--
[FEBDASH]
I'm terribly sorry.
I've accelerated a
fuel-filled asteroid.
It should be here soon.
[LAFIEL]
How long will it be?
[FEBDASH] It shouldn't
be more than 12 hours.
Twelve hours?
Your Highness, please.
In the meantime, you may sit
back and relax in my palace.
Thanks for your offer,
but we can't.
I'm still on duty.
We'll fly out on our ship
to meet the asteroid.
But I understand that your
communications spacecraft
is in need of a check-up,
Your Highness.
[JINTO]
Hm?
A check-up, huh?
[FEBDASH]
Your Highness,
please accept my sincere
desire to welcome you.
[LAFIEL] I've already explained
our situation to the vassal.
I'm sure you've got things to
do other than welcoming us.
Don't you need to plan an
escape from this territory?
[FEBDASH]
I appreciate your concern.
However, we do not
have ships here.
There are no means of escape.
I see. Yet--
A vassal will show
you around the place.
I shall see you at
the dinner table.
That man was obviously
ignoring you.
I guess.
[LAFIEL] I can't trust
someone with that attitude.
To welcome me properly,
he should also make
you feel welcome.
You're right.
But it can't be helped.
You're a royal Princess, and I'm
some insignificant nobleman.
It's a trick.
I think he's lying about
the check-up of our ship.
It's as if he's deliberately
trying to hold us back here.
For what purpose?
[LAFIEL]
I don't know.
Aren't you perhaps becoming
a little too suspicious, Lafiel?
I seriously don't
like him at all!
In that case, let's think
this through logically.
Is there any benefit for him
to go to the trouble of lying
just to keep us back?
[LAFIEL]
Hmm...
You have that "I just might
think of something" look.
How 'bout this?
The Baron is keeping us back
so he can steal our
communications spacecraft
to get away from
the enemy fleet.
[LAFIEL]
That ship is double seated.
It only handles two people.
[JINTO]
It would be plenty if the Baron
was planning to escape alone.
[LAFIEL]
And leave his vassals behind?
You don't trust
the Baron at all,
but you do trust his
sense of righteousness?
Stop it! Just leave
his ethics out of it.
Nothing is worse than deserting
one's vassals and citizens.
The laws of the Empire against
that act are severe!
With the added crime of
stealing a spaceboat,
he'd have a better future
in a concentration camp
of the United Mankind,
rather than remaining
within the Empire.
I see. So a title is a duty.
Right. A title is a duty.
[JINTO] So you're
saying that the Baron
is not planning any
sort of conspiracy.
[LAFIEL]
I guess that would be true.
[JINTO] In that case,
let him welcome you.
I'll also do what I can.
[MUINISHU]
Your Highness.
A luxurious bath has been
prepared. Please follow me.
The others will escort
you, Your Excellency.
Huh? Uh, we can't take
a bath together, right?
[MUINISHU]
Hmm.
[JINTO]
Huh?
Why don't you just go ahead?
We haven't got much time.
[LAFIEL]
That's true.
Bye.
[LAFIEL]
Goodbye.
See you later.
[SEELNAY]
Let me wash your back for you.
[LAFIEL]
No.
[SEELNAY]
Let me wash your hair for you.
[LAFIEL]
No.
[SEELNAY] Please. Do not
hesitate to let us serve you.
I'm not hesitating, thanks.
Hm?
Are you all aware
that an enemy fleet
is heading toward Sufugnoff?
Yes.
[LAFIEL]
Aren't you afraid?
No. I'm sure our master
will handle everything.
The Baron? And how
will he handle things?
I don't know how exactly.
[LAFIEL]
Hmm...
The Baron is
certainly well trusted.
Of course he's well trusted!
If it weren't for his kindness,
I would not be where I am today.
What do you mean?
It had been a dream of mine
to become a citizen
of the Empire.
However...
The status of women
is extremely low,
and there's little
hope of being more
than a good wife and mother.
[LAFIEL]
I can't imagine it.
[SEELNAY] My master
saved me from that world.
And he even gave
me an education.
[LAFIEL]
Education?
[SEELNAY]
Yes.
I am normally in charge of
inspecting fuel equipment.
I received my education
in that field.
[LAFIEL] So serving in the bath
hall is not your main duty.
[SEELNAY]
No.
In fact, this is my first time
to serve at the bath hall.
I've never been called upon
to give the master a bath.
Are the other vassals called
upon to wash the Baron's back?
[SEELNAY]
Yes.
Oh, the master is
a very kind person.
[LAFIEL]
He certainly doesn't look it.
[LAFIEL] How many people are
there in this territory?
About... 50 people.
[LAFIEL]
How many of them are Abh?
[SEELNAY] There are two.
The master and his father.
[LAFIEL] It seems to me
like an awfully lonely life.
[SEELNAY] It's true that
it somewhat lacks
challenge and excitement,
but it's a worry-free lifestyle,
so I really have no complaints.
So I'm a convenient
piece of entertainment.
[gasps] Not at all!
[gasps]
And what is this?
Do you expect me to wear this?
Those were the
master's orders.
[LAFIEL] Where did you
put my military uniform?
It is presently being washed.
You treat guests well.
[VASSAL 2] Also, military
uniforms are considered savage
at the dinner table.
Savage? I only wear
military uniforms.
But...
Your Highness! Please.
Please.
[LAFIEL] I'll wear the dress
over my military uniform.
That should be okay, right?
A very warm welcome
to you, Your Highness.
Where's Jinto?
[FEBDASH]
Jinto?
Oh, you refer to
Prince of Count Hyde.
My father is entertaining
His Excellency.
[LAFIEL] Why is your father
not joining us for dinner?
My father doesn't like company.
[LAFIEL]
That seems strange.
Why send a guest to your father
who prefers to be alone?
Fellow sufferers do pity
one another, don't they?
What do you mean?
Never mind. Nothing.
I cannot ignore this.
I have orders to take Jinto,
Prince of Count Hyde,
to Sufugnoff.
[FEBDASH]
Pardon me, Your Highness.
You're not insinuating that
we'd do anything to harm
His Excellency, are you?
You're acting suspicious.
This saddens me.
In any case, please have a seat.
Allow me to resolve these
misunderstandings over dinner.
[LAFIEL] I do hope they
are misunderstandings.
What wine would you
like with your meal?
I'm on duty. Something
non-alcoholic, please.
As you wish. How about
some tule lashban?
[FEBDASH]
By the way,
I noticed that you address
that young man by his name.
Please feel free to do the same
with me and call me Klowal.
No thank you.
Why is that?
I don't want to call
you that, Baron.
[FEBDASH]
Please. Go right ahead.
Delicious!
I'm honored, Your Highness.
[LAFIEL]
I wasn't complimenting you.
I was referring to
whoever prepared this.
This was prepared by
hand, not machines.
Am I right?
Yes, very observant.
I'm not too fond of machines
preparing my meal.
[FEBDASH] But I sense
you are terribly upset
about something, Your Highness.
Very observant, Baron.
I am angry.
[FEBDASH] Is it about that
young man from the Land?
Jinto is an Abh noble.
[FEBDASH]
Yes, I recall.
[LAFIEL]
It's not only about Jinto.
Are you sure the
communications spacecraft
needs to be checked?
You've got no shortage of fuel.
I'm doubting you on
a number of issues.
Oh, yes, I have been lying
to you about those things.
We do have plenty of fuel,
and we are not checking
your spacecraft.
Then why did you lie?
You wouldn't have accepted
my invitation for dinner
no matter how much I
asked, Your Highness.
[LAFIEL] Of course not.
We're in a hurry.
So then, it only
proves that lying
was the correct thing to do.
Now that I know you've lied,
you will let me leave
here, will you not?
[FEBDASH] Your Highness,
in regard to you leaving...
Would you be able to delay
your departure a little,
for your sake and for mine?
For how long?
[FEBDASH] Until the next ship
from the Empire arrives.
In other words, until the safety
of our territory is guaranteed.
We don't know how
long it'd take.
[FEBDASH]
Exactly.
[LAFIEL] So you're trying to
hold us up until then?
[FEBDASH]
Yes.
[LAFIEL] What do you wish to
gain in keeping us from leaving?
Do you have some sort
of grudge against us?
[FEBDASH]
Not a chance.
As long as you're
here, Your Highness,
I will do everything to
make your stay enjoyable.
I couldn't even think of doing
anything to harm you.
Oh?
I am no longer sure if you
understand what you are doing.
Your actions are very serious.
[FEBDASH]
Of course I understand.
I am doing my best
to protect the territory.
[LAFIEL] What does confining
us to your spaceport
have anything to do with
the safety of your territory?
[FEBDASH] Nation Sufugnoff
is a large area.
The United Mankind
knows where it's situated.
However, our Baron territory
is much smaller,
with a short history.
There is a great possibility
they have never heard of our
Febdash Baron Territory.
However, what if they
observed a ship
pass through the
gates of Febdash?
If this territory had
not been recorded
on their information network,
it would be the deciding
factor for them to attack.
But we already passed through
the gates of Febdash, right?
How can you be certain
we weren't observed?
It's true you may
have been seen.
However, let us not give them
another chance to see your ship.
There's no sense giving the
enemy a second chance.
You do have a point.
So, therefore, Your Highness,
I understand your reluctance,
but could you please
remain at this spaceport
until the enemy has
left the vicinity
and you're safe once again?
You know that you're
obstructing the progress
of a communications
spacecraft.
Aren't you worried that
the Empire may take away
a territory which you
tried to protect?
I don't believe so.
I am very passionate to
protect the territory.
The higher courts of the Empire
will deem my actions proper.
[LAFIEL] Even if Sufugnoff
comes under attack
before we have a
chance to warn it?
[FEBDASH] That shouldn't
be a problem either.
There's a lot of traffic
surrounding Sufugnoff.
If not you, I'm sure someone
else will inform them
that an enemy fleet
is approaching.
In which case, there should be
nothing wrong with my actions.
I do trust that you will
indeed testify favorably
to the courts that I took
very, very good care of you,
Your Highness.
As a faithful Abriel.
How dare you.
[LAFIEL] Forget about me.
How is Jinto doing?
[FEBDASH] My father is looking
after Prince of Count Hyde.
[LAFIEL] You shall stop
with the games, Baron.
I hate being deceived.
[FEBDASH]
I understand.
Since that young man
doesn't deserve
to be treated as a nobleman,
he is receiving the appropriate
treatment for someone from Land.
How many times should
I say this? He's a nobleman.
I understand that you
have a peculiar opinion
toward the rank of citizens.
I've never seen such servile
citizens as your vassals.
They're like cats trained to do
tricks. It's painful to watch.
The relationship between
a lord and his vassals
is no one else's business,
Your Highness.
[LAFIEL]
You're right.
I'd like to know what you regard
as the appropriate treatment
for someone from Land.
[FEBDASH] It's nothing for you
to worry about, Your Highness.
[LAFIEL]
Another thing I noticed.
Are there no men at all
among your vassals?
[FEBDASH] No. I can't stand
having men from Land around me.
You've given me another
reason to dislike you.
[JINTO]
I hear that Abhs sometimes smile
in front of those they hate.
"The smile of an Abh."
It is so gruesome-looking
that they say it is much like
a poisonous flower
in all its glory.
I have yet to see Lafiel
make such an expression.
The Baron has him confined.
It's quite important
that you take me
to your son, immediately.
I'm not able to, young man.
And why is that?
[ALISA gasps]
[LAFIEL]
Stay exactly where you are!
I am going to rescue Jinto
with or without your assistance.
[screams]
It's an exit!
Why it doesn't belong
to the Baron at all.
It belongs to the
Star Forces ship.