[PLAKIA]
See that Fiel?
That's just the
remains of a star.
[DUBUS] Do you have to be
quite so negative, my dear?
It's actually the
source of a new star.
Everything that's needed
for the birth of a new life!
[PLAKIA]
I've been doing some thinking...
What do you say we go home?
[DUBUS]
But we've only just arrived!
We haven't even taken
in the scenery yet!
We should stay for at
least a couple more days
before we get back to work.
[PLAKIA]
That's not what I mean.
I was thinking maybe we
should go back to Lakfakalle.
Now where did that
come from all of a sudden?
Don't you love me anymore?
[PLAKIA]
Mm-mm.
You know I love you,
my precious Imperial Highness.
In fact, even though
I hate to admit it...
I love you more than
anyone else in the universe.
[DUBUS]
Then why?
[PLAKIA] It's been wonderful
spending all this time
alone with you, but
I miss our friends.
We could have just as
wonderful time back there
with them.
I want to go back
to the Star Forces.
If that's really
what you want to do...
Sometimes I wish
you weren't so easily
persuaded about things--
that you'd fight your corner
a bit more forcefully!
What do you want me to do?
Don't leave me!
I could even throw in
a few tears if you want,
just for effect...
That was almost convincing.
You know full well
I'd rather die
than actually let
someone see me cry.
Is that some of your
Abriel pride talking?
No, just regular human pride.
Speaking of being human,
did you hear what the
people of Lakuryuush
have been saying about us?
They've decided that we're
just artificial life forms,
and that we were
created to look, sound,
and act exactly like humans!
Come on, that can't
be the official opinion.
I'm afraid so. It's as
official as official can be!
You can find it written in any
of their school textbooks!
All we did was discover
these isolated human worlds
and conquer them for the Empire.
But from their perspective
they'd have you believe
it was some huge alien
invasion from outer space!
[DUBUS]
You know...
Sometimes I think
that your imagination
gets the better of you.
How do you know
what's in their school
textbooks anyway?
You mean you don't remember?
We had orders to
carry them all the way
from Lakuryuush to Gamuteesh.
Really? Are you sure?
Ah... that curriculum package!
Now I know what
you're talking about.
[PLAKIA]
That's right.
I think there's still
a back-up copy
in the ship's
information system.
[DUBUS] No, I deleted it.
It was part of our contract.
Incidentally, our contract
also stated that we weren't
allowed to make use
of the cargo we carried.
[PLAKIA]
Don't be such a spoilsport!
[DUBUS] Sticking to our contract
is an important Abh ethic.
[PLAKIA]
What a shame.
Then I guess you don't
want to hear about
all the other interesting
stuff I found?
[DUBUS]
Knowing you, you probably went
straight to the juicy bits
where they make us out
to be evil tyrants!
[PLAKIA] It's quite
amusing when they get
the wrong end of the stick.
It's only if their
criticisms hit home
that I get annoyed.
[DUBUS]
That's understandable.
[PLAKIA]
You see?
Besides, they praise the
Empire's distribution system,
saying that by
using it their trade
has progressed
in leaps and bounds.
Here's another
interesting little fact.
Do you know what they call
the territorial representative
of Lakuryuush?
[DUBUS]
No.
[PLAKIA] "The person
in charge of maintaining
the Abh Aggregate"!
[DUBUS]
What's that all about?
It looks like we're
not the first ones to arrive
in this sector of space...
Ah! You're not the only
curious one exploring this area.
They're only about
three light-seconds away.
That's very close.
We're near the Sord.
It wouldn't surprise me
if we saw another ship.
It's a strange orbit.
If they're going
to use the Sord,
you'd think they'd approach
it from a different angle
instead of circling
it like that.
Maybe they're doing some sort of
scientific research in the area.
[DUBUS] They seem to
have some sort of radiation
surrounding them, but I don't
think it's a defense shield.
Then maybe it's not a ship.
That's a possibility.
Whatever it is,
I'll bet that it's manmade.
Well if it's not
an active ship,
then maybe it's a
shipwreck or something.
There must be quite
a few floating around.
Let's ask the computer.
I would like to run a
search of your database
of survey reports to see if
you can identify this object.
[COMPUTER VOICE]
Object not identified.
--Hey, Plakia?
--[PLAKIA] Huh?
How about you
and I go and explore?
This little detour of ours
might not have been
such a bad idea.
[DUBUS] It looks to me
like an interplanetary
navigation ship--
one of the older models.
But surely the computer
should have been
able to identify it?
[PLAKIA] Not if the
surveys aren't complete.
[DUBUS] Do you think we
should try to go on board?
[PLAKIA] If I say no,
you'll go anyway, right?
Okay... I'll go with you.
[DUBUS] If we're so perfect for
each other, which we are,
why did you want to cut the
honeymoon short and go home?
[PLAKIA] I'm not sure we're
perfect for each other yet.
But I'm afraid we might
be getting that way.
I think I'll let you take
care of the preparations
for boarding, my precious
Imperial Highness.
[DUBUS] How many times
do I have to tell you?
I can just about put up with
you calling me by my title,
but cut out the slushy
precious bit, will you?
[PLAKIA]
Hurry up and get a move on.
[DUBUS] With that attitude
you could be an officer!
[PLAKIA] Over here,
my precious Imperial Highness.
Didn't I just tell you
about calling me precious?
[DUBUS]
Can you get it open?
[PLAKIA]
I expect so.
What do you mean?
Are you saying you
haven't tried it yet?
It might need some muscle power,
in which case that's your job.
Oh, really? Why's that?
As far as I remember,
this little detour
was all your idea,
so you should do the work,
Your Highness!
Okay. Your point is taken.
I just wanted to
make sure, that's all.
I think that the air's
safe to breathe in here.
It's been exposed
to radiation for so long
there'll be no
harmful bacteria left.
What a pleasant thought...
[DUBUS gasps]
[DUBUS] All right!
Time to start exploring!
Maybe now you
understand why I call you
"my precious Imperial Highness."
Uh...
Are you sure we
should be doing this?
Shouldn't we let
the experts handle it?
It could be dangerous.
After we've come this far?
It's exciting being the first
to discover something.
Look, you can go back
if you want to.
What? And leave you here
all by yourself? No way.
It's out of the question!
You've always trusted me before,
although sometimes I wonder why!
How come you trust me so easily?
What have I done to
earn that trust from you?
[PLAKIA]
Are you sure you want to know?
[DUBUS]
Maybe not.
You know something?
It's kind of a weird feeling,
but I think I've actually
been here before.
Really?
[PLAKIA gasps]
Look! Something's alive!
Maybe...
[PLAKIA]
Don't!
I'm beginning to wonder
if we should leave this
to people who know
what they're doing...
Are you frightened?
What if I was?
Being timid isn't normally
your style, Plakia.
There's a difference
between being cautious
and being timid.
[DUBUS] I can't stop now
or I'll lie awake
at night regretting it.
[PLAKIA]
You losing sleep?
I don't think so!
[DUBUS]
It's not working...
[PLAKIA gasps]
What's the matter?
I think we should get
out of here, Your Highness...
I see... so I'm not
precious anymore, am I?
[PLAKIA]
You fool!
Look!
It seems like the same
type of hatch as the one
we came through
to get in here.
If it is, then we should
be able to get it open.
[PLAKIA]
What are you doing?
If this leads outside,
we'll get sucked into space!
Hey, don't worry about it!
We'll be prepared.
What do you think they are?
[DUBUS] It could be some
sort of cargo, but I doubt it.
I've never seen
anything like it!
Hey, isn't that...
[DUBUS, PLAKIA grunt]
[PLAKIA gasps]
The Roomasel!
What in the hell?!
[grunts]
Apparently this shipwreck
isn't a wreck at all!
[PLAKIA] Our ship is
drifting off into space...
If we can't get it back,
we'll end up spending
the rest of our lives here!
If that means I can be with you,
that's not so bad.
I think I need to
correct you on something.
The one that's drifting
away isn't the Roomasel.
It's us.
[PLAKIA] Do you think
them suddenly changing
the course of their
orbit like that
is some sort of message for us?
[DUBUS] If their invitation
had been a bit more graceful,
I would have been
happy to accept it.
But we weren't invited!
We just came aboard the ship
like we were intruders!
Maybe they're only trying
to get us off the ship.
The power reactor,
the control room...
There's gotta be a
couple of ways for us
to get back there.
[PLAKIA]
This is quite an antique!
[DUBUS] It wouldn't surprise me
if it was hundreds of years old.
It's probably been
traveling across
the different star systems
for a long, long time.
Y'know, this looks
similar to the inside
of the Imperial Palace.
Are you sure?
How is it powered?
Nuclear fusion, perhaps?
I wish I'd been
able to figure out
how to get control
of the ship's reactor
so I could realign its orbit.
We'd have to be careful not
to cause a radiation leak.
Remember that we are
the Kin of the Stars,
so as long as there are
stars around, we'll be safe.
You've got an idea forming
in that head of yours,
--haven't you?
--[PLAKIA] Why do you say that?
I can see it written
all over your face!
I never knew that reading faces
was one of your many talents.
I have got an idea,
but it's fairly basic.
It's probably not
stylish enough for you.
I could force myself
to forget about style.
Have you figured out
the orbit we need yet?
We're lucky this
system doesn't have
a large number of planets.
It's difficult enough
altering the orbit
without having to factor in
other gravitational influences
to the calculations!
Oh, don't worry so much. It
could've been worse, you know.
[DUBUS] Except now you're
making us alter the orbit
with explosives.
I'm sorry if it offends
your sense of style.
Well, it might just work!
[DUBUS grunts]
That was the third one!
Are you sure?
Wasn't it timed to go off
a bit later than the others?
The longer this goes on,
the harder it's going to be
for us to reunite
with the Roomasel.
[DUBUS] I guess this
means our honeymoon
is well and truly
coming to an end!
[PLAKIA grunts]
You okay?
[PLAKIA]
Yes, I'm fine.
The fourth one...
Watch out!
[PLAKIA yells]
[DUBUS, PLAKIA yell]
Are you all right, my dear?
Yes...
So did we succeed?
[beeping]
[DUBUS]
The explosions pushed the ship
a bit too far over...
You mean we have
to recalculate the orbit?
[gags]
You didn't use your Kiseegu?
But what about
all the radiation?
I had to rely on the headband.
It would've been
too difficult without it.
[PLAKIA]
Where are you going?
I've gotta get this ship
on a better orbit
before it's too late.
How will you do that?
I figured I'd have
another go at your idea
and try more explosions.
I'm going to come with you.
[groans]
Once this is over, we're
going home to Lakfakalle.
[PLAKIA]
As long as I'm with you...
Now you stay here.
I'll be all right on my own.
Or don't you trust me?
It might be completely
stupid of me,
but I'll trust you.
If you didn't trust me,
that would be stupid.
If that's really what you want,
then of course I'll stay.
[DUBUS] You should try and get
close to the front of the ship.
As far as you can.
[PLAKIA]
Don't be too long,
otherwise I'll
leave without you.
[DUBUS]
I'll be back as soon as I can.
This type of
reunion wasn't exactly
what I had in mind...
[PLAKIA gasps]
Do you want to
go back that badly?
Dubus, are you okay?
[PLAKIA gasps]
[DUBUS]
Plakia!
Are you all right?
Dubus, you're here...
What happened?
[PLAKIA]
Don't go in!
My darling, I hear you.
You know there's nothing
I wouldn't do for you.
But I have to go in there.
I've got to.
[PLAKIA]
Stop it!
[DUBUS] What are you
afraid of? The truth?
[PLAKIA]
Let's just leave him alone.
[DUBUS]
I need to know, Plakia...
[PLAKIA]
Your Abriel pride again?
[DUBUS]
No, just good old human pride.
[PLAKIA] Do you have to
take the headband off?!
If you already know
who it is, Plakia,
then does it really
matter whether or not
I remove the headband?
[DUBUS] Well it would appear
that he's related to us.
[PLAKIA]
Why? Why did they come back?
They must have known
it was useless!
[DUBUS] They were probably
created with the specific
intention of coming back.
Coming back in a more advanced
form than our ancestors.
[PLAKIA]
Don't say that!
[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
That means...
those things we saw were...
But why?!
[DUBUS] I hope we can get
back to Lakfakalle safely.
[PLAKIA]
Why shouldn't we?
Once upon a time,
I thought the world
was based on common sense.
But if we keep coming
across situations like this,
I might have to
revise my opinion.
I wonder if they
managed to find
their way back home...
[DUBUS]
I expect so.
They simply came here
before having their wings
taken away.
[PLAKIA] I wonder if we'll
find our way back home.
[DUBUS] It's difficult
when you're on your own.
[PLAKIA] But we're not...
we have each other, right?
Of course we do, Plakia.
[DUBUS] I wish I had
some of your genes.
[PLAKIA chuckles]
I must admit I've heard
better compliments.
[DUBUS]
I'm sorry!
Oh, that's all right...
I still love you, my precious
Imperial Highness.
[PLAKIA] I still think
this place looks like
a burial ground.
No, it's the source of
a new star and a new life.
[DOCTOR]
The water's breaking...
[baby crying]
[DOCTOR]
Congratulations!
Is she really ours?
She doesn't look
anything like you!
anything like you either!
Aren't her ears a bit
small for an Abriel?
[DUBUS]
That doesn't matter...
I name her Lafiel.
Captain.
Trainee Pilot Lafiel
reporting for duty!
At your service!
[PLAKIA]
Thank you.
I'll let you handle the
Third Calike.
I want you to take the
Calike and immediately
make your way to the
Planet Delktoe Spaceport.
There you will rendezvous
with Prince Jinto,
Count Lin Syune Locke Hyde.
If you need to brush up
on any of the details,
it's all written down
for you in part 14
of the ship's report.
Understood, Captain!
And I want you to promise
that you'll behave yourself.
Yes. Of course, Captain!
[PLAKIA]
Lafiel?
[DUBUS]
That's right.
"Laf" is the Abh word for "gem"
and also tells us that she
is a brave Abriel princess.
"Fiel" means the source of life.
Every new star has a mist
surrounding it called a Fiel.
In that mist are all
the elements needed
to create and sustain new life.
[DUBUS] Now please don't
go and say anything
that might bring
bad luck to the baby!
[PLAKIA]
Of course not!
[DUBUS] Lafiel... you do like
it as a name, don't you?
[PLAKIA] Considering you
thought of it, it's not bad!
[DUBUS]
Praise indeed, coming from you!
There's one more thing...
Would you keep the fact
that you're the genetic mother
a secret from her?
[PLAKIA]
Why?
[DUBUS] I believe that
secrets help build a richer,
more interesting personality.
[PLAKIA] I'm not going
to interfere with how
you want to bring her up,
but I don't think I've
ever heard anything
so stupid before in my life!
[DUBUS] Really?
I thought it was a great idea!
[PLAKIA] Well, you're the one
she's going to hate for it,
so it's up to you, I guess.
Don't you pay any
attention to what
he tries to teach you,
and you'll be just fine,
Your Highness!
[DUBUS] I wonder what kind of
person she'll grow up to be.
[PLAKIA] Well, if you're
the one who's raising her,
with any luck
she'll turn out to be
the complete opposite of you
and be a nice gentle child!
[DUBUS] What do you mean,
the opposite?!
[PLAKIA]
Are you sure want to know?
[DUBUS]
Not really!
[DUBUS] I've often
wondered if people learn
how to behave from the
people around them...
[PLAKIA]
I'm sure if you remember that,
you'll be just fine
bringing her up.
As for what the people of
Lakuryuush might think...
Who cares?
At the end of the day
they're just people like us.
[DUBUS] And you used
to be so concerned about
what people thought!
[PLAKIA] My precious
Imperial Highness...
[DUBUS] That's the nickname
I'm going to hand down
to this child!