[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
Your Highness! Please wait!
Take this with you.
I'm sure His Excellency
will need a weapon, too.
But you will need a
weapon for yourself.
Oh, but I still have the gun
that Kuhaspia left
behind when she left.
All right then.
I have one more
favor to ask of you.
What a terrific honor!
Oh, Your Highness.
I need to speak to Jinto from
the communications spacecraft.
How can I?
[growls]
Can I really trust
any of you girls?
[MUINISHU] Trust? Are you
questioning our loyalty?
[FEBDASH]
Yes.
Yes, you can trust us, Master.
We will protect you, Master.
No matter what the cost.
That's-That's good.
You are my loyal
and true vassals.
Will you stick by me and make
the Princess your enemy?
Yes, we will stick by you,
and we'll make the
Princess our enemy.
[ALISA]
This is housekeeping calling
with a message to all vassals.
A dispute has begun on
this Baronial spaceport.
I repeat, a dispute has begun.
The reason is that our master,
His Excellency Baron Febdash,
has wrongfully kept the Princess
from proceeding on her mission.
The Princess wishes to leave
this territory immediately
with His Excellency
the Count Prince Hyde.
That is why she has
taken drastic action
against the Baron...
Analysis crystal!
[MACHINE 3]
Connection cannot be made
to the analysis-crystal network.
Why not?
[MACHINE 3] Input and output
with general communicators
cannot be made.
Please use an
equipment terminal.
Blast! They must've done it!
Activate the terminal! Now!
[ALISA]
So, my dear friends,
let's cooperate
with the Princess.
She has promised to hire
everyone who cooperates
as a vassal of the
Clyuve Royal family...
That's a lie!
Royal families don't accept
vassals that easily!
Muinishu! The terminal!
No luck! I can't connect.
You vile, loathsome traitors!
How much more will
you get in my way?
As for you, come with me.
We'll find a terminal.
Muinishu, you wait here
and follow my orders.
Sir, just wait one moment!
There's an intruder
in the ship again!
What?
[LAFIEL]
Jinto.
Jinto!
[MACHINE 4]
It is not being worn.
Not yet?
Hmm...
Then I'll refuel first.
[LAFIEL] With these, I can
refuel without any help.
Exactly like in training.
Oh, no! I can't refuel!
[LAFIEL]
Huh?
He just released
and destroyed
all of the anti-substance
fuel at once.
Well done, Baron.
[LAFIEL]
After I rescue Jinto...
...I plan to kill you.
You can count on it, Baron.
[SEELNAY]
Your Highness.
We were able to
deliver the clyuno
through the food delivery route.
You can communicate now!
[gasps] Lafiel!
Jinto.
Listen to me.
I can't dock the ship,
so I won't be
connecting to the exit.
What do you mean?
[LAFIEL] Well, if you have
pressure-proof space clothes,
there's no problem.
[sighs]
Why did you need even to ask?
No, we have nothing like that.
[LAFIEL] All right, then you'll
have to swim through a vacuum.
When the ship's positioned,
open the exit when
I give the sign.
I'll send down a rope.
Oh, sure, that'll help.
You don't seriously think
this plan of yours will work,
do you, young man?
You will join us though,
won't you?
Even if I say no,
you'll open the exit,
and I don't intend to wither
and die in this place.
Oh, no, the spacecraft
has slowed down
above the former
Baron's living quarters.
You mean they haven't
given up yet?
We'll leave this place.
You girls will pick up a weapon
and follow me immediately.
I'm sure you know this.
It's above our rank to
receive the Count Prince,
but to also receive Her
Highness the Princess?
My late mother would be
thrilled to hear of this.
[chuckling]
Jinto, all is ready on my side.
[JINTO]
Same here.
[LAFIEL]
Step away from below the exit.
I'm now shooting the rope down.
Okay.
[LAFIEL] Let me know once you've
grabbed hold of the rope.
I'll pull you up while
there's still air.
I hope so.
Ready?
I am.
Let's go.
Some work other than cleaning
would be delightful
for a change, right?
Turn it!
Right! Lafiel! Pull us up!
[inaudible]
[groaning]
Hi, Lafiel.
That looks good on you.
[LAFIEL]
Uh! Jinto!
[JINTO]
Huh?
Jinto. Are you okay?
As you can see.
That's good.
You're a very important
commodity to this pilot.
I would be inconvenienced
if you got hurt.
See?
Well, I guess
that goes to show
exactly how much Her
Highness is in love with me.
The air is getting thin here.
Yeah, you're right.
[FEBDASH]
Blast. I know exactly why, too.
Hey, traitors, you hear me?
[RURUNE]
Shut up!
[SEELNAY] Would you be quiet?
You're being rude.
[GRIEDA]
Yes, Master?
Grieda?
Well! You've got some
nerve to say "Master."
You betrayed me.
[GRIEDA]
I'm terribly sorry.
[FEBDASH]
Well, that's not important.
Have we lost pressure
in the retirement block?
[GRIEDA]
Yes, exactly that.
[FEBDASH] Have you taken
measures to deal with it?
[GRIEDA] Yes, Master--
I mean, Your Excellency.
We've closed off all
air circulation vents.
[FEBDASH] What about the
garbage disposal vents?
[GRIEDA]
Uh! I forgot about that.
[FEBDASH] We'll all be in
trouble if the air runs out,
won't we?
Take care of it immediately.
[GRIEDA]
But the garbage disposal vents
can't be closed automatically.
We can't do anything
about it from here.
You idiot!
Why don't you just start by
trying to send out space workers
to the retirement block
to restore the pressure?
If you're going to revolt,
at least think through
the logistics yourselves.
Where the hell are you
keeping your brains anyway?
[GRIEDA] You see, we're in
a state of confusion here.
No excuses!
You girls comb through
all the exits.
If you see Her Highness,
restrain her immediately,
you understand?
What will you be doing, Master?
I'm going outside.
This is a battle!
[SEELNAY] Just badmouth
the Princess one more time,
and I'll show you-- Ouch!
[SEELNAY, RURUNE grunting]
[RURUNE]
Let go of me! You traitor!
[GRIEDA]
Everyone, listen to me!
[BOTH]
What is it, Grieda?
I'm way too busy right now!
[GRIEDA]
We're even busier here!
No more games! And
turn that receiver off!
R-Right.
This is housekeeping.
The entire spaceport
is now depressurizing.
For right now, do not
use the garbage disposal.
Should you find any open vents
at all, close them immediately.
Depressurizing? No!
That's right.
It seems that Her Highness
opened and forgot to close
the exit on the roof of
the retirement block.
Why don't you face it?
Her precious Highness
simply doesn't care
what happens to us.
This proves it!
[GRIEDA]
Be quiet!
Seelnay.
You have a license for vacuum
operations, don't you?
Yes. It's mandatory.
What do... do you have in mind?
Well, quite obviously
we require you
to close the exit to the block.
[SEELNAY]
But I can't do it alone.
Everybody else, go with Seelnay.
She will be in charge.
But I'm just a simple waitress.
I'm not licensed
for vacuum work.
And I don't want to
work under Seelnay.
Get some specialized
technicians.
Grieda, what authority do you
have to order me to go and--?
Will you be quiet?!
Ugh!
This is no time for
your nonsense!
Hurry up before we all die!
Look, we're not used to this,
so it's going to
take extra time.
Hey, Grieda's right.
Come with me! If you don't
wanna die, that is.
Aren't you coming, too, Grieda?
No, because I'm the head
housekeeper of this area.
And so, I am needed here.
[JINTO] Lafiel, His
Excellency is on our side.
Your Highness.
It seems my unworthy son has
caused you great trouble.
I'd be so thankful if you could
provide some assistance
in teaching him a lesson
for his misbehavior.
I can't, unfortunately.
I'm now on my way
to destroy him.
Ah, but...
Don't you think that's a bit
too extreme, Your Highness?
Your son has made it impossible
to complete my mission.
He's blown up the fuel-filled
asteroids. All of them!
Jinto and I are stuck here
with no chance of escape.
Yes, that's a problem.
Is that all you feel about
this? Aren't you angry?
Of course I'm angry.
That is not true.
I'm tired, Lafiel.
I'll get mad later.
Jerk.
Now, now, Your Highness, please.
I might be able to do something
about the fuel supply.
But how?
Well, has my son destroyed
the anti-substance
fuel factories, too?
No. As far as I know,
they're untouched.
[FORMER BARON]
In that case,
you can use any fuel we
can find from the factories.
That's true, but the Baron
took over the control room.
Your plan won't work unless
we can override the controls.
The former Baron himself
designed the spaceport, Lafiel.
It'll be easy to override
the analysis crystal.
It'll be easy, will it?
In any case, let's attempt it.
And then, if all
goes as planned,
would you leave my son's life
with me, Your Highness?
The offer is conditional?
Is there a problem with that?
I really need to
discipline him myself
for the trouble he's caused.
All right, then.
However, if the Baron
dares to get in our way,
I deal with him.
We are agreed.
Okay now. Let's start.
[FEBDASH] I see Her
Highness is heading
for the number 11 factory.
[FEBDASH]
Control room, can you hear me?
[MUINISHU]
Yes, this is control room.
[FEBDASH]
Is our remote control connected
with the number 11 factory?
Well, actually, for some reason,
the functions of
the control room
are showing signs of
instability, Your Excellency.
The thing doesn't
react to any inputs.
How was Her Highness
able to pull this off?
[FEBDASH]
Father.
Your Highness. We may have
a small problem here.
What is it?
[FORMER BARON] My son is
patrolling in the Ponyu .
And is this Ponyu
armed with weapons?
Well, is it?
Yes, I think this is it.
The Segno 947 built in
the Dugteif shipyard.
It's equipped with
two specially-loaded
40 Lengarf cohesive beam guns.
Do you think that
we can control it?
Can't be done.
He's disconnected the
ship's analysis crystal
from the spaceport's
crystal network.
So, it would seem
that I might be forced
to destroy your son, after all.
I guess it can't be helped.
But I-I thought this spacecraft
was totally unarmed.
Yes, it is unarmed.
Well... uh...
You sure seem pretty confident.
Confident?
[FORMER BARON chuckles]
[FORMER BARON] This is typical
of how the Abh think.
Let me explain.
It's not as if Her
Highness believes
she can definitely win.
There's just no sense
thinking about
what will happen
after we're killed.
She's merely warning me,
in case we were to survive.
[LAFIEL]
Then, what did you think, Jinto?
Well, I, uh...
[FORMER BARON] His Excellency
misunderstood you.
That Your Highness
disregarded the possibility
that this ship may be destroyed.
Do you really think I'm a fool?
We've got a 10%
chance of winning.
Of course I know all about that.
[JINTO]
But you still choose to fight?
[LAFIEL]
What other choice do we have?
[FORMER BARON]
This is also typical of the Abh.
To fight with a 10% chance
rather than surrender.
To the Abh, this is the obvious
choice, without question.
[LAFIEL]
Is there a problem?
Not at all, Your Highness.
Genetics aside,
I am also an Abh.
I certainly know the
moment when I need to fight.
You, Jinto?
[JINTO]
I'm just a commodity, right?
So I don't have an opinion.
But thanks for asking for
it just the same, Lafiel.
Time to settle this thing once
and for all, Your Highness.
Goodbye, Father.
[LAFIEL]
He's near.
Yes, he is.
We're now within range.
Can you tell?
It's a hunch.
We can't detect light speed
weapons ahead of time,
so now it becomes
a battle of hunches.
[LAFIEL]
He's here!
You're only a young pilot
trainee, Your Highness.
You will not be
able to elude me.
[LAFIEL] This is no drill.
Remember, this is no drill.
I've got a split second
to make my move.
If I miss it, I don't
get a second chance.
Not yet. He's still too far.
A little more...
Okay!
Terminate main engine now!
Decelerate, full power!
[FEBDASH]
What?
What's she thinking?
[LAFIEL]
Yes!
Ignite main engine!
Pathetic!
Try to damage my ship by
propelling ventilation?
Hm?
What's this...?
[yells]
She added...
anti-substance to the fuel.
Nicely done, Your Highness.
[LAFIEL]
It's over.
[JINTO]
Did you... kill the Baron?
[LAFIEL]
I killed him.
[LAFIEL] Former Baron,
I'm sorry for your loss.
It's all right.
It was an Abh battle.
"Sorry for your loss"?
That's all you can say?
Why're you upset?
[JINTO]
You just killed somebody.
[LAFIEL]
Hm?
If I didn't kill him,
he would've killed us!
I know that, okay! Still--
[FORMER BARON]
That's enough, young man.
There's nothing for you
to be excited about.
You just didn't want
to see Her Highness
kill someone, am I right?
[LAFIEL] Is it true what
the former Baron just said?
Well, yeah, I guess so.
[LAFIEL]
Why is that?
Huh. Well, that's...
[LAFIEL] Just so it's clear,
we were in a battle.
Yeah, I realize that.
[LAFIEL] Is there a problem
with me winning in a battle?
No, not at all.
After all, just think if
we had lost the battle.
[LAFIEL]
Then what is it?
Well, that's hard to answer.
Anyway. Sorry.
And thank you. You protected
me, after all, right?
Accepted. You should
be grateful.
And I am. Thanks, Lafiel.
Well, now that
everything is settled,
I think I'll go and seize
my rightful territory.
My... pitiful son...
[JINTO]
Huh?
The former Baron was not crying,
but in his words was a
sense of deep sorrow.
[MACHINE 5] Let's give
thanks to the United Mankind
for liberating us from the rule
of the Humankind Empire Abh.
The reason we entered
this nation, Sufugnoff,
was to retaliate against
the reckless actions
taken by the
Humankind Empire Abh.
While we were investigating
the Plane Space
around a newly discovered Sord,
a warship of the Empire
suddenly opened fire on us.
That's a lie!