[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
[LAIRIA]
Captain.
[LEXSHUE]
What is it?
[LAIRIA] Please come
to the bridge at once.
[LAIRIA] I've located several
unidentified space-time shots.
[LEXSHUE]
I'll be right there.
Lairia, what's the status?
[LAIRIA] Direction: 78 degrees.
Distance: 1,539.17 gedrels.
Heading on an 18 degree
course toward Sufugnoff.
Sufugnoff, is that
our next stop-over?
It is. It's likely we
should arrive there first.
And the object's length?
[LAIRIA] We have located
120 space-time orbs
of approximately 90 zezabo.
The amount, in terms of fleets,
would equal the total
output of four vessels.
Lairia, do you know which
Sord they entered from?
[LAIRIA] I'm having Leshikuria
calculate that now.
I'm afraid I can only
narrow it down to 47.
Are any of them
currently in use?
[LESHIKURIA]
No.
Not only are they all closed,
but these are generally
neglected Sords.
Can you tell me if
any of those Sords
are within one light year
of inhabited planets?
[LESHIKURIA]
Not one.
Within five light years?
[gasps]
[LESHIKURIA]
There's just one.
Where?
4.1 light years from Keish gate
193 is the planet Vascotton 4.
That planet is occupied by...
...the United Mankind.
[LEXSHUE gasps]
The United Mankind...
[JINTO] It's been five days
since Gosroth took off.
About then, I was tackling the
regulations of living quarters
for my paymasters'
training school.
Hopeless!
[sighs]
It's totally impossible to
remember all of this stuff.
Ugh. There are 120 articles
just on lunch manners.
[sighs] Dorin was so right.
Well, Jinto, you
had been commuting
to an Abh school here, right?
[JINTO]
Well, actually,
the candidates at
the school I attended
were expected to become
citizens of the Empire.
There were no Abhs.
Not even beautiful Abh teachers?
[JINTO] The teachers were all
old men from the territory.
[DORIN]
Aw...
Gee, wouldn't it have made
more sense to go to school
with a bunch of Abh kids?
[JINTO] The Abhs have no
elementary education system.
[DORIN]
Really?
Then how do they learn
to read and write?
[JINTO]
Well, from what I understand,
their parents are the ones who
teach them to read and write.
But there was no way my own
father could find the time
to teach me as the Abhs do, what
with his busy schedule and all.
So I was sent to school to learn
the Abh language and basics.
And that took you a
whole seven years?
I'd always figured that you
were extremely intelligent,
but I guess I was
completely wrong.
[JINTO]
He's so right.
So, this is it.
What is it?
[LEXSHUE] It appears that
the Four Nations Alliance
want to start a war.
Don't you agree?
They've been making
unreasonable requests,
such as calling for the
independence of Nation Hyde,
with access to a corridor
within the territories
of the Empire for protection.
They're well aware
that the Empire
will not agree to that request.
And so?
And now, they're
prepared to fight,
and all they wanted was
an excuse to attack.
I see.
They must have put a great deal
of time and energy into this.
[LEXSHUE] They would've had
to check a number of the Sords
floating in Space to find
one that they could use.
And even then, they
would've had to bring
the Sord closer to them.
[LAIRIA]
And to do that,
they would also need
to wait a few years
for the Sord to close again.
Yet, it's nothing
short of a miracle
for them to have done this
in less than ten years.
Or a... nightmare.
[LAIRIA] There's no question
they were planning this
well before the formation
of Nation Hyde.
[LEXSHUE]
Right.
The problems relating
to Nation Hyde
just happened to
come up recently.
Moreover, the Nova Sicily
Treaty might have been formed
because these plans
were in place.
[LAIRIA]
One thing I can't understand...
Why bother telling
such obvious lies?
[LEXSHUE] The only people
they're fooling are themselves.
Fooling themselves?
Now I'm getting more confused.
I find myself having difficulty
relating to their
way of thinking.
They probably want to believe
their actions are right.
What a great honor.
We have been labeled
the evil incarnate.
Oh. But there's more, Laria.
Yes, I understand that
we are supposed to be
natural born invaders.
Take a look at a history book
written by the United Mankind.
It points out that all disasters
are caused by the Abhs.
[gasps]
Captain, some clusters
have changed.
[LEXSHUE]
Hm?
One space-time shot
split into ten.
The enemy is now
headed this way.
From their volumes,
the space-time shots
appear to be independent
attack vessels.
How long until these guests
enter the range of our mines?
They will be entering our
range at approximately 21:15.
Lairia. Second-level combat.
Stand by to upgrade
to first-level combat
at exactly 20:30.
[LAIRIA]
Yes, captain.
Gunnery Officer Sariush,
analyze strategy.
Yes, captain.
[LEXSHUE]
What are our chances of victory?
[beeping]
[gasps]
What's that?
[LEXSHUE]
This is the captain speaking.
Everyone, listen carefully.
An unidentified space-time shot,
78 degrees and a distance
of 1,540 gedrels,
is headed this way.
Its destination is assumed
to be the same as ours,
the nation Sufugnoff.
Now listen to me, everyone.
As it stands, it is certain we
will arrive in Sufugnoff first.
But the object doesn't seem
to be too happy about that,
so they're sending ten
attack-vessel space-time shots
after us.
We have yet to confirm
where they came from,
but they appear to be from the
fleet of the United Mankind.
All quarters, this has every
sign of becoming a battle!
What's going on?
[LEXSHUE]
This is not a drill.
I repeat: This is not a drill.
If the enemy proves
to be persistent,
we will enter into battle
at approximately 21:15.
In preparation, we will upgrade
to first-level combat
at exactly 20:30.
All crew currently off duty
are asked to rest up
and be ready by this time.
I will repeat this once more,
so commit this to memory,
my precious crew members.
This is not a practice drill.
Captain, over and out.
Entering a battle.
[JINTO gasps]
L-Lafiel.
[LAFIEL] I've been ordered
to take you to the bridge.
Can you join me?
[JINTO]
What in the world is going on?
Just what you heard.
I don't know any more
than what was announced.
It seems you've
happened to join us
just as a war is breaking out.
How fortunate.
[JINTO] Life is filled
with such unexpected,
fortunate occurrences.
It's when you're the happiest
that you should worry
about hitting a wall.
[JINTO] If possible,
I hope it's all over
before my appointment.
[LAFIEL]
That is not likely.
We prefer not to end a war
before there's a clear victor,
and in this case,
the enemy appears to
be the United Mankind.
It's unclear if it'll
be over before I die.
I hope you mean a natural death.
[LAFIEL]
Yes, 200 or 250 years.
In any case, until I die.
[JINTO] You sure have a knack
for cheering people up.
[JINTO]
Hm?
[LAFIEL]
I have brought His Excellency
the Count Prince with me.
Sorry for the inconvenience,
Your Excellency.
Pilot trainee Abriel,
please stay here
while I speak with
His Excellency.
Yes.
Your Excellency.
I'm sorry I cannot
offer you a seat.
[JINTO]
Huh?
Oh, it's quite all right.
I'll just remain
standing, thanks.
I'm sure you understand
what is happening
from the announcement.
Right. We're likely
headed for battle.
We have a 37% chance
of winning this battle.
That's assuming that the enemy
is fighting with their best,
but even if they were sending
a bunch of rookies
on outdated vessels,
our chances of winning
still won't reach 50%.
It's bad, isn't it?
Right. The best option
now would be to escape.
But, unfortunately, our
circumstances won't allow it.
Therefore, I must have you
disembark, Your Excellency.
[JINTO]
I understand.
[LEXSHUE]
This ship is equipped
with a communications
spacecraft.
Although it's small,
it has the ability to
travel in Plane Space.
Please go to Sufugnoff
ahead of us.
You'll need to refuel
once along the way,
but you should be
able to get there
before those space-time shots.
You can catch another ship
once you're in Sufugnoff.
There is a communications
fleet base there,
so you shouldn't have to
rely on luck to find a ship.
Pilot trainee Abriel
will escort you herself
to the Nation Sufugnoff,
Your Excellency.
[LAFIEL gasps]
Captain! I can't!
[JINTO]
Huh?
I haven't got my
pilot's license yet.
You've completed the course
to captain a vessel.
You'll automatically
receive your license
once we've completed
this journey.
All that's left is paperwork.
You are qualified, trainee.
I'd rather remain on this ship.
I will not debate
this with a trainee.
Am I not the captain
of this ship?
No, you don't understand!
I will spell it out!
I am an Abriel, see?
An Abriel cannot run
away from an enemy.
[gasps]
[LEXSHUE] Why don't you
quit your petty outbursts
and your boasting
until you've earned
a head band with wings.
Abriel Nei Dobrusk
Paryunu Lafiel.
What do you mean running
away from the enemy?
You don't serve for any battle
divisions on this ship.
You're nothing but
an extra body here.
But I gave you an order.
An extremely important order
to take the Count Prince,
who is a non-combatant,
away from the battlefield.
I've ordered you to
inform the Empire
that we are being approached by
what is likely an enemy fleet.
Evading my orders would
be a prime example
of running away from enemies.
Your ignorance is so great
that you fail to recognize
the meaning of running away.
If that's your way of thinking,
then Abriels are not worthy
of the Abh allegiance.
If you still wish to talk back,
I'll restrain you on
grounds of disobedience.
You can discuss this further
at the ex-emperor's meeting,
where you can be sure they'll
adhere strictly to the rules.
[LAFIEL]
It was a misunderstanding
on my part, Captain.
You are forgiven.
Prepare the communications
spacecraft at once.
I still have something
important to discuss
with the Count Prince.
Captain, I will commence
with the preparations.
[LEXSHUE]
Once you're ready for take-off,
just relay a message to me.
[LAFIEL]
Huh?
There's no reason
for you to return here.
Captain. As you wish.
Now, don't waste any time.
I'll see you in Lakfakalle,
my precious Imperial Highness.
[JINTO]
Huh?
Absolutely, Captain.
I'm sorry, Your Excellency,
but we are pressed for
both time and space.
Please take with you only the
personal effects that you need.
I intended to.
I will be able to get
the rest of my things
from you later at the Capital.
I must apologize sincerely
for not transporting you
to the Capital as
originally planned.
[JINTO]
Hey, it's okay.
Transportation setbacks were not
uncommon back in Vorash either.
Those kind words take
a load off my shoulders.
There's one other thing,
Your Excellency.
And what is that?
I have one other thing
I'd like you to take,
aside from your
personal effects.
[JINTO]
Yes?
Open weapons room.
Captain Lexshue Robel Palakia.
[LEXSHUE]
Please, keep one for yourself.
And give one to
pilot trainee Abriel.
She'll know how to use them.
But why in the world would
we need something like this?
You can never be too careful.
My hunch is that the objects
heading in this direction
are on their way to attack us.
There's no other reason
why they'd allocate
all that military
power to stop us.
I have this gut feeling that
they're simply acting on
an impulse to destroy,
and these weapons
will help to ensure your safety
once you leave the spaceship.
Which means that this ship may
have surrendered to the enemy
by the time we
arrive in Sufugnoff.
I deeply hope and pray it
will not be the case, but...
Um... Captain, uh...
Your primary
objective is to have
Her Royal Highness
escape, right?
Then wouldn't a skilled
royal guard be much better?
Oh, no, please don't
misinterpret me.
It's my duty to avoid
battles as much as possible
when I have any
non-combatants aboard.
If a battle cannot be avoided,
I must take measures to ensure
the non-combatant's safety.
This is a responsibility of
all Star Forces leaders.
It is also true that
pilot trainee Abriel
does not serve for any
battle divisions on board.
I'm sure I would've given
her the responsibility
of operating the spacecraft
even if she had come from an
unknown family, Your Excellency.
[JINTO]
Hmm...
I'm sorry. That was such
a thoughtless question.
I would be lying if
I said I wasn't glad
about the coincidence
that the Princess
also happened to be
a pilot trainee.
You've given this a lot
of thought. Captain?
[LEXSHUE] Although her social
status has no meaning
as a member of the military,
Her Highness could
become Empress.
She may even become a wise
and great Empress.
My ambition is that,
when the day comes,
she would reflect on her
days as a pilot trainee
and acknowledge she
was taught well.
I cannot possibly allow her
to die before she can bloom.
Yes, of course.
[LEXSHUE] Well, you should
be on your way now.
Please return to your room
and finish packing.
I regret that no one's
available to escort you,
but you do know your way to
the departure deck, don't you?
[JINTO]
I'll be just fine.
Oh, about the flag
of my family crest
you were going to hand me.
I'll leave it behind for now,
but I look forward to
receiving it one day
to commemorate my
time on this ship.
Your concern is very much that
of a nobleman, Your Excellency.
Oh, is that so? I'm glad.
[JINTO] Well, Captain,
I shall get going.
[LEXSHUE]
Your Excellency,
please, look out for
the Imperial Princess.
[JINTO] I can't imagine a
situation desperate enough
for Her Highness
to depend on me,
but should such a time come,
I will do everything I can.
[YUNSERYUA] The communications
spacecraft has left.
The young man and
woman are safely away.
I hope they don't encounter
any obstacles.
[LAIRIA]
I certainly hope not.
They both have quite
unique backgrounds.
I think they'll become quite
important people in the future.
Actually, they already are quite
important people right now.
[LEXSHUE chuckles]
You're right.
Bringing those two
children together
could become my most
significant accomplishment.
And yet, this accomplishment
depends solely on them
reaching the Capital safely
and without incident.
You're awfully worried about
those two, aren't you, Captain?
Is something wrong
with being worried?
Well, no.
The obvious thing is that the
crew and members on this ship
are in greater,
immediate danger.
I do regret having to
criticize my superior,
but we haven't got time right
now to worry about others.
It's an amazing discovery
for me to find
that you're actually
feeling regret.
Regret of criticizing
your superior.
Yet, you're absolutely right.
Right now I must carry out my
responsibilities toward my crew.
[JINTO] I kept thinking...
I've gotta say something.
[JINTO] There are only
two intelligent beings
flying through this
separate space.
One of them is stuck
in a deep depression
and the other is giving serious
thought on how to introduce
a brighter atmosphere
to this other space.
Uh...
Lafiel...
[YUNSERYUA]
Captain!
Captain, we are within
communications range
of the unidentified
space-time orbs.
We'll introduce ourselves,
and request that the ships
identify themselves immediately.
[YUNSERYUA]
Yes, captain.
Nothing yet?
Hold on.
[YUNSERYUA]
We have a response.
[gasps]
[YUNSERYUA]
Why this is...
This is no correspondence!
This is a challenge signal!
It's confirmed.
Hey. Say something, Lafiel.
I can't believe I am so useless
at such an important
time like this.
That's not true.
Commence battle!