♪ Opening Theme ♪
[Fuu] I can't believe those two.
I wonder what's keeping
those lazy lumps this time.
The least they could do
is get back here with
somethin' for me to eat.
[footsteps, door shaking]
Huh?
So they're back, huh?
Where the heck have you two--
Please help me.
Huh?
[Fuu] What are you--
Just hang in there, alright?
We go easy on the girl,
then she just turns around
and makes fools of us.
Hey, look.
What's that?
[Fuu] What are you doin'?
You can't just come in here.
[Suzukichi] Well it
looks like you did.
[Fuu] Well, I...
I was just passing through,
and the hut
looked abandoned, so...
[smashing]
Will you cut that out?
[crashing]
Who the heck are you guys?
A strange girl come by here?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't play dumb
with us, chickie.
[gun shot]
[Suzukichi] Listen,
little lady, if you lie to us,
you'll suffer
severe consequences.
I said I don't know anything.
Let's go.
Huh?
But we still haven't--
Don't worry.
[Kikumaru] Yeah, but--
So what's this
friggin' line all about?
Our Father who art in Heaven,
hallowed be thy name...
[Official 1] Next.
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Heh? What the hell's
this thing?
[Official 1] It's
a stepping picture.
You step on it
as a test, understand?
[Mugen] No.
Look, it's a test
to find out if you're
one of the underground
Christians hiding in this area.
So will you step
on the damned thing already?
No way.
Huh? What did you say?
Sorry, dude, but I got a thing
about bein' told what to do.
Don't cause a commotion.
Step on it and be through.
Nah, I ain't gonna do it.
Then don't step on it.
Well now that you told me
not to do it, I do wanna do it.
Stop screwin' around!
[Official 1]
Take these two away.
You boys want a piece of me?
By starting
this pointless squabble,
you've done nothing but reveal
just how vast your stupidity is.
Please refrain from
these moments of self-grandeur.
Run that by me again?
[crazed laughing]
[thick spanish accent]
Well, it appears as if it's
time for me to step in.
What the hell?
I have traveled
across the seven seas,
just so I could
right the wrongs in this land.
My reputation may proceed me,
for I am known
throughout the world
as the man who
represents God on Earth.
Please allow me the chance
to introduce myself.
I am Xavier the Third, the
grandson of Francisco Xavier!
[Official 1] So what?
[Official 2] This guy's
wanted across the country
for interfering
with stepping stone tests.
[Official 1] He is?
[Xavier Yo] Hyah.
Arrest that man!
If someone
is opposed to my work,
then they are also
opposed to the work of God.
And their punishment is death.
What the hell was that about?
I have no idea.
You okay down there?
[Yuri] Thank you.
Tell me what
I can do to repay you.
You don't have to do
anything at all.
I can relate.
I get chased and captured
by guys like that all the time.
I understand
what it feels like.
Oh.
Then again, I've got
a couple of bodyguard guys
who deal with
most of that stuff.
They're pretty much
just useless bums though.
You'd think that they
could be on time for once.
They went out
for supplies hours ago,
and they're
still not back yet.
Hey, my name's Fuu.
And I'm Yuri.
It's nice to meet you.
Um, is that yours?
Huh? Oh, this?
Someone told me once
that I shouldn't
show it around too much.
So where did you
get that skull?
Well I guess it's
kinda like an heirloom
that somebody left behind.
[Fuu] Does it mean something?
Look into its eyes
and see what happens.
What do you see in there?
[Fuu] It looks like an 'x'.
[Yuri] It's a cross.
The Cross of Golgotha.
It's a good luck charm
for Christians.
Huh?
The people on Ikitsuki Island
have been handing
those down for years.
It's a huge refuge for
the underground Christians.
Ikitsuki Island?
It's a little spot
in the Nagasaki province.
Listen, Yuri. Ya see...
Ya see, I'm looking
for this one samurai
who smells of sunflowers.
Huh? Well, I wonder
if it could be
Seizo Kasumi that
you're talking about.
You know who he is?
[Kikumaru] So you
thought you could
pull one over on us, didja?!
Tryin' to make
fools of us, huh?
Well, we'll see
who gets the last laugh.
[Suzukichi] Hey,
put that gun down.
We agreed not to kill her.
Stay back.
Oh, you want a fight, do ya?
If... you don't
get outta here right now,
I'll use my
Maiden Swordplay of Death--
Yo.
[Mugen] Wake up, dammit.
You're late!
[Mugen and Jin]
Huh?
[Mugen] You sure she wasn't
just makin' shit up?
[Fuu] I know when
someone's lying.
She said she knows the samurai
who smells of sunflowers!
[Jin] Well, regardless,
it's gotten late.
If we continue
to wander around aimlessly,
we'll only end up lost.
[Fuu] We can't stop now!
[Fuu] Excuse me, but you didn't
happen to see a woman
come into this
village, did you?
She was probably being chased by
some scuzzy guys with big guns.
[Sentry] I can assure you
that didn't happen, Miss.
If someone like that
had come through these gates,
the whole town would be
in an uproar over it by now.
You didn't just dream this
whole stupid thing up, didja?
It wasn't a dream.
[Sentry] Well,
it's getting late.
If you have no place else to
stay, you're all quite welcome
to spend the night at my house.
Well, might as well
take you up on that.
[Jin] It's a bit strange.
[Mugen] What?
[Jin] The security
in this village
seems to be very
tight for its size.
Nothin' to get worked up about.
Let's hope not.
[multiple footsteps]
[running footsteps]
[Jin] Hey, are you in there?
[voices cheering]
[People in the crowd]
Saint Xavier! Saint Xavier!
[Xavier Yo] Thank you!
Okay, everyone, please listen.
For many years, it was
believed that you could
gain entry into the
holy land of Heaven
simply by believing in God.
But alas, those days
exist no more.
Heaven has become overpopulated.
The land of salvation
is not infinite.
And it is no longer possible
for just anyone to get in.
But fear not, for I have
your key to the gates of Heaven,
and it is this gun!
You see, whether or not you're
able to enter the Promised Land
is dependent on
your ability to produce
the divine weapons
you see before you.
These words are
indeed righteous and true,
declared by my grandfather,
Francisco Xavier!
[Crowd cheering]
Huh...?
Look who we have here.
[Suzukichi]
So what do you think?
If these bad boys
were European imports,
they'd probably
cost you around twenty ryo.
But you're a first time buyer,
so I'll cut you a deal
and let you
have 'em for fifteen.
[Kuroihara] I gotta say, I like
the way that you do business.
Why don't you consider this
my first installment?
[Yuri] Why are you doing this?
Just what do you think
that you're gonna get out of it?
Money, and lots of it!
Let me tell you,
it's hard to find
a more profitable
venture than religion.
Simply mention God's name, and
you can get away with anything.
And by working with
the underground Christians,
my risk of exposure
is virtually zero.
You can't imagine
how grateful I am to God.
Take a good look around.
I have such
a fabulous collection.
Shotoku Taishi's dentures--
five thousand ryo.
The three arrows
of Motonari Mouri,
which comes complete with a
certificate of authenticity,
and it cost me
seven thousand ryo!
Sojun Ikkyu's folding screen-
twenty thousand ryo.
Nobunaga's sandals,
the very ones
Hideyoshi held
to his chest to warm up.
Now this one's unique,
for it's two famous people
in just one item,
and it cost thirty thousand ryo.
It's true.
No matter how much
money you make,
it's still never enough
to keep you satisfied.
Do you really think that
my love is just another thing
that you can buy?
[laughing] Why yes indeed, I do.
I don't know why poor people are
always resistant to this fact,
but you see, there is
absolutely nothing out there
money can't buy.
And I'm afraid
that truth applies
to someone's love as well.
Like it or not,
my feisty little peasant girl,
you're going
to become my wife.
I won't.
Young lady, do you want to meet
the same unfortunate fate
that your father met?
In my experience,
when money fails,
violence becomes
an excellent alternative.
Well, come on now.
Isn't it in moments like this
you are supposed
to turn the other cheek?
[Fuu] You got it, Momo?
It's up to you to get them
this message, okay?
[squeaking]
[Fuu] Yuri! Are you alright?
Oh, Fuu, what are you
doing in here?
[Xavier Yo] I will give you
until nightfall.
Perhaps tonight you
will be my bride.
Or perhaps tonight you
will breathe your last breath.
Whatever it is,
the choice is yours. [laughing]
I can't believe that I've gotten
you mixed up in all this.
[Fuu] No, no, that's not it.
I came here, 'cause there's
something I wanted to ask you.
I have to know about someone,
about the samurai who
smells of sunflowers.
[Mugen yells]
You mangy furball.
Hold on. I've seen
that furry mug before.
Hey.
[Mugen] Hey! Yo!
This is between
me and the rat.
I believe this flying
squirrel is Fuu's pet.
She's got a pet?
[Mugen] Well, it'da been nice,
if she'da told us
where the hell
we can find her!
[Yuri] Ikitsuki Island
was a wonderful place.
It was like a sanctuary
for us Christians.
Trying to escape from
years of persecution,
the underground
Christians began
to show up on
the island in droves.
My father and I
were among them.
As was Seizo, also known
as the samurai who
smelled of sunflowers.
Confusion rose from the chaos,
and people scattered
into the night.
We fled to where we are now.
After that night,
I never saw Seizo again.
So do you have any idea
where he is now?
I'm afraid I don't.
All of that happened
so many years ago.
I don't know if he's
still on the island,
or if he died that night.
[Kuroihara] The next
stepping stone test
will be in Shimonoseki.
Can I expect that to be
just as entertaining?
[Suzukichi] Well it seems
the bigger spectacle we make,
the more new believers
we create.
Give our best
to the governor, will you?
[Mugen] So, that whole act of
yours is just a sham, huh?
Hey, who in the hell
are you two guys?
Too slow.
We're looking for our companion.
Nuh-uh!
How 'bout you be nice
and show us where she's at?
[Fuu] So, were you and your
father still together when
you ended up in this area?
My father is...
...is dead now.
That Xavier man...
is the one who killed him.
[Yuri] My father was a gunsmith.
He found out that Xavier the
Third was secretly negotiating
with the lords within the area.
Xavier had him silenced...
forever.
Perhaps this is the fate
that we must endure.
I'm sorry.
[Yuri] I tried to escape
from this place,
just as soon
as I had the chance.
But I was captured.
I'm beginning to think
that this is all just
an enormous trial,
meant to test my faith.
[footsteps]
[Xavier Yo] So, have you
made your decision yet?
Hurry, the party
will be starting soon.
[Xavier Yo] Now, make your vows
before the eyes of God
and all those
standing before you
that you will be faithful to me
in sickness and infirmity.
[Fuu] She'll do no such thing!
She won't do it, ya big creep!
The devil's voice dwells
within this young girl!
Execute her at once and
save her soul while you can.
This poor child
is overcome by demons.
We must exorcise them at once.
[Crowd worrying]
Demons! Demons?
Please don't, I beg you.
[Fuu] No, Yuri, please,
please don't let this man
do this to you.
Do what your heart
tells you to do.
I'm not going
to go through with this.
to become your wife.
I'd rather die first!
What'd you say to me?
I asked you a question!
[Crowd gasping]
[Xavier Yo] You must be punished
for your betrayal against God.
Don't you dare.
[Xavier Yo] Foul demons, I'm
going to send the two of you
back to Hell where you belong.
Die, devils!
[man screaming]
Mugen! Jin!
Who are these intruders?
Hey, you're that whackjob
from the checkpoint.
You deceive these people
with your histrionics,
then racketeer these firearms.
The gig is over, Boss.
Those guys were watchin' us
make the whole deal.
They saw?
[Crowd worrying]
Racketeer?
What's he mean by illegal guns?
[Crowd worrying]
Is this true?
[Crowd worrying] He's not
a Christian, don't believe him.
It's a lie, they're just trying
to slander us! All of them!
[Crowd screaming]
Shoot that man!
[gunfire and screaming]
Missed me!
Oh, my God!
[Crowd gasping]
[Crowd] Look, he's Japanese!
That can't be right.
We can see
who you truly are now.
You're obviously
not the descendant
of Francisco Xavier, are you?
He's found a way to turn a
profit by exploiting all of you
under the pretense that
you're doing it for God.
[Crowd] Then he's not truly
a servant of our Lord? Oh no!
[accent gone] Now hold on,
everyone, please calm down.
So yes, it turns out
that I'm actually Japanese.
But wasn't I able
to save you all,
solely because
you believed in me?
So doesn't that mean that
no matter where I hail from,
I'm still your savior?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but a savior's supposed to
bear the cross
of those he saved.
Okay, yes, you're right.
I shouldn't have
said that. I'm sorry.
I repent for my sins.
I was wrong.
So please, forgive me.
[gun shot]
Just kidding!
[Xavier Yo] As if I'd
really repent to a bunch of
mindless morons.
I'm sick of it.
I'm sick of you people
and your "God, God, God."
You only turn to God when
you want something from Him.
Well if you love Him so much,
then allow me to send you all
straight to His doorstep.
[Xavier Yo] Amen.
[Yuri] You're going to
Ikitsuki Island, aren't you?
[Fuu] Yeah.
I'll pray for you.
Good luck. May you find
the samurai who
smells of sunflowers,
even if it isn't Seizo.
Thanks.
Hey, you know it might be nice
if you told us who this guy is.
It would be easier
to find him if we knew.
Alright then.
The truth of it is...
He's actually my father.
[Fuu] Well, goodbye Yuri.
Take care, Fuu.
[Fuu] Alright you two,
let's get goin'.
May the grace of God
be with you on your journey.
♪ End Theme ♪