♪ Opening Theme ♪
[birds cawing]
[Official] Vagrant Mugen.
Vagrant and ronin Jin.
These two will hereby
be executed by decapitation
and their heads put on display.
Are you ready to apologize?
Are you ready to grovel at my
feet and beg for forgiveness?
[Mugen]
If living means bowing down
to the likes of you bastards,
I'd rather die on my feet
with my head held high.
[gasps]
[Jin chuckles]
Well said. I agree with him.
Very well then. I'll grant
your wish and send you
straight to the afterlife.
[birds cawing]
[steel slicing through air]
[cars driving by]
[tape rewinding]
[distant bird call]
[Man 1]
Hey, where are my dumplings?
Aren't they ready yet?
Yes, Sir. Coming right up.
[Man 2] Hey, baby,
let's have some fun.
[Girl 1] Oh...
[Man 3] Come on.
Don't give me that frown.
[Girl 2] Stop it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[Man 4] So what kept you,
you idiot?
Please, forgive me.
[Man 1] Where are my dumplings?!
Coming!
I'm bored to death.
[Man 5] Yeah, me too.
Isn't there anything
fun to do around here?
Geez, what's with
these customers today?
[Kikuzo] Now, now, Fuu.
Just keep smiling.
--But they're--
--[Ogin] Careful, Fuu...
...That blond boy is the son
of the prefectural governor.
Check it out! Brand new.
[Man 6] Hey, nice!
Some blade, huh?
Can't wait to do a test cut.
What are you looking at?
Hey! I'm talking to you old man.
[water splashing,
frantic whimpering] It's hot!
[callous laughing]
[Man 6] You got him!
[grumbling]
You guys are a bunch of--
[muffled talking,
callous laughing]
[record scratching]
[Hayashi] Oh, please,
Governor. I beg you, Sir.
If I lose this construction
job, it will be the death
of my whole family.
Please, Sir. Please!
[clinking]
You dare give me this?
I, well, I just...
Your spare change!
[scattered clinking]
[Elder Shibui] You men!
Kill this insolent peasant
for me at once.
[Townsman] Don't. You might not
like it, but just let it go.
Look. See those samurai
closest to the governor?
They're his bodyguards.
They're famous fighters from
Edo. Considered topnotch,
even among the Yagyu.
They're in a different league.
Even the governor's samurai
wouldn't stand a chance
against those guys.
Understand?
[record scratching]
Uh. Good afternoon, Sir.
Water.
Water?
Yeah, water.
Well, um, we only serve
paying customers,
so you'll have to order
more than water.
If you're broke,
go somewhere else.
Hm?
Fifty dumplings. Is it a deal?
[Fuu] Huh?!
You feed me, and I'll take care
of those guys for you.
But, um...
But what?
Maybe for twenty.
Are you kidding me? I'm not
going one dumpling lower.
[Younger Shibui]
Hey, where's my tea?!
Yes, Sir. It's coming right up!
[gasping]
[water splashing]
What's with you?
Uh, I'm really sorry.
It was an accident--
[Younger Shibui]
I don't want to hear it.
All I want to know is how you're
going to make it up to me.
I, uh--
One finger or two? Well, I
suppose one ought to be enough.
[gasping]
--[Fuu] Hey, what are you doing?
--[Man 2] Come on, hold still...
--Cut it out! Let go of me!
--[Ryujiro] Master, let me
take care of this....
I wanted to give the new
blade a test cut anyway,
and she'll do just fine.
[Fuu whispering]
Somebody, help me.
Stop struggling or you'll
lose more than just a finger.
Well, now, what'll it be?
Your nose maybe,
or how 'bout an ear?
Or perhaps your little...
[record scratching]
[Elder Shibui] Hmmm. It isn't
much, but where you're going
that's all you'll need.
You know what they say?
It's only six mon
to cross the River Styx.
[laughing]
You bastard.
[Jin] Move it, will you?
You're blocking the road.
Is that so?
Who the hell are you?
Don't try to interfere.
[Jin] To serve your lord
and do his bidding,
is that honorable?
Of course it is.
Even if that lord
is an unimportant piece of shit?
--[Yagyu Bodyguard 1] Say what?
--Hey! You better watch
that mouth of yours.
[Jin] Cutting down a man
who's done nothing wrong.
Is that what you spent all those
years honing your skills for?
[Yagyu Bodyguard 3]
Why I ought a...
[Jin] In my opinion,
you're worthless.
[Yagyu Bodyguard 1] Screw you!
[Yagyu Bodyguard 2]
Say your prayers!
[record scratching]
One-One-One hundred dumplings!
Huh?
[gasping]
[Mugen] Well, boys, your lives
ain't worth squat, are they?
Excuse me?
[Mugen] Do the math. A hundred
dumplings for all you guys.
What's that work out to?
Five dumplings a pop?
His math's way off.
You're a gutsy little punk,
but if you don't
shut that big mouth,
you're gonna piss me off.
Watch your ass, or I'll try out
my new sword on you someday.
Why not right now?
[pained yelling]
[steel falling]
[shocked wailing]
Forget all that formal crap
about coming at me
one at a time.
I'll take all you bitches on!
Oh, yeah?
Get him!
[record scratching]
♪ hip hop music ♪
[yelling]
[record scratching]
[Mugen] Come on!
♪ samba drums ♪
[groaning]
[steel hitting the floor,
Fuu thinking] Oh, crap.
[Mugen] Come on. Bring it boys!
[Younger Shibui]
You some kind of moron?
You just don't get it.
You just don't get it
at all, do you pal?
[Mugen] Huh?
[Younger Shibui] My old man's
the governor around here,
so folks who
mess with me pay for it.
Big time.
Hell, fact is
they don't live long enough
to see the next sunrise.
You starting to get it?
This isn't the damn civil war.
In this day and age
acting like a loose cannon,
going around swinging a
sword is totally passé.
Huh? AHH!
Do you understand
what I just said?
[Mugen] Nope. Not at all.
Come on, why not?
It's common sense.
That's just the way
the world is today.
I don't give a rat's ass
about your common sense.
Huh?
Because I come from Ryukyu, pal.
[record scratching]
Huh?
Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait just a minute!
You want money? Is that it?
You can have as much
as you want, okay?
H-How 'bout it?
You?
I'll take these.
You... bastard!
Somebody stop that man!
You miserable,
good-for-nothing cowards!
[record scratching]
[Younger Shibui] Listen. My old
man has three Yagyu badasses
guarding him around the clock.
Huh?
[Younger Shibui
nervously laughing]
What's the matter? You scared?
You pee your pants?
[laughing]
[wailing]
I'm sorry!
Hey, gimme your hand.
Hm?
[Younger Shibui whimpering]
Listen up, morons!
Here's the deal. You guys
ain't worth bothering with.
You're gonna leave
and I'm gonna count to ten.
You've got that long
to get those badasses over here.
I'll count with his fingers
until you get back.
This is one.
[bone breaking]
[screaming]
And two.
[bone breaking,
Younger Shibui screaming]
[hectic yelping, running]
And three.
[Younger Shibui
wailing in pain]
And four.
How boring.
What the hell,
let's do them all.
No, wait. Hold on a minute...
[gasping]
Are you one of them?
A Yagyu swordsman?
You are in the middle
of something. Pardon me.
[Mugen] Hey! Are you one of
those so-called badasses?
[running footsteps]
[Mugen grunting]
You've got the wrong guy.
And don't bother
waiting for the Yagyus,
they're all gone.
[Mugen] They're gone?
I killed all three.
Better yet!
[Jin panting]
[surprised gasping, whimpering]
[Fuu gasps]
[water trickling]
Uh, Mr. Ryujiro?
[maniacal laughing]
[frantic screaming, yelling]
[laughing] Burn it all.
Burn it to the ground!
[frantic screaming, yelling]
I can't imagine
a more perfect setting.
Aren't you going to run?
[Mugen] Nah, but go ahead.
Don't stay on my account.
[Mugen shrieking]
Damn that's cold!
Huh?
[water dripping]
[splashing]
What in the hell
is going on here?
Don't you remember?
I remember a dream.
There was fire all around me.
It wasn't a dream.
Oh, yeah?
So you were in a bathtub
with your thing hanging out?
Now that was a dream.
[Elder Shibui]
Too bad it wasn't a dream.
My son burned to death
in that fire.
And now you're both
going to pay for that.
Fortunately, it wasn't long
ago this place was called
"the torture department store."
You're going to be
well taken care of
till your execution tomorrow.
Ahh!
[Jin groaning]
[grunting]
Ugh.
[choking]
[grunting]
[bell tolling far away]
[Kikuzo] Fuu.
Huh?
I guess this must be
awfully tough for you.
Nah. It's really no big deal.
Well since you have no family,
you'd be welcome
to come with us if you like.
No. I'll be okay.
This thing has forced me
to make up my mind.
[Ogin and Kikuzo together]
Huh?
[Jin] You're the
lowest of the low.
[Mugen] What did you say?
[Jin] Your stance
leaves you wide open,
and your moves are
totally inefficient.
All in all your
fighting style is a mess.
You son of a...
I swear, you are the most
undisciplined fighter
I've ever known.
Shut you damn mouth.
And the only one
I wasn't able to kill.
Mugen is the name, pal.
You got that?
[Jin] Mugen.
Right.
My name is Jin.
You should remember it.
[crickets chirping]
[Fuu] Please, sir.
Forget it.
The prisoners aren't allowed
to have any visitors.
Can't you bend the rules
for a minute?
Oh, please, sir.
Do it for me.
Pretty please?
No way.
[Fuu] I'm begging you.
I'll do anything.
Anything?
[Fuu] Uh...
You mean you'll...
[Fuu] I, uh...
You know... have se--
Anything but that.
What is this?
You said anything.
You lying little bitch.
Not with you Baldy. No way.
I'm not bald.
--This is a hairstyle.
--Hey, cut it out!
[Guard] Stop wiggling.
Take this.
Thanks for the help, Momo.
[happy squeaking]
[Fuu] Oh, wow.
From the looks of things,
they really put you two
through the ringer.
You're that chick.
The one from the tea house.
[Fuu laughing]
Well, don't you want
to know why I'm here?
[Mugen] No.
Okay. See ya.
[Mugen] Wait.
I was just kidding.
Listen. If you promise you'll
do me just one little favor,
I'll help you escape.
Do we have a deal?
You serious?
[Flunky] And?
She said she was going
to visit the prisoners.
[Flunky] Find her!
[All] Yes, Sir!
It's not working.
So, what's the deal
with this favor of yours?
There's someone
I want you to find.
A samurai who smells
of sunflowers.
--[Mugen] Sunflowers?
--[Guards] Find her!
--Hurry up.
--Look over there.
[metal clanking]
Oops!
[Mugen] What is it?
--The key broke in half.
--[Guards] She's over there!
--Uh-oh. Gotta go.
--[Guards] Hold it!
[running footsteps]
[Fuu shrieking]
Stupid chick.
What the hell she even
come here for anyway?
[Crowd 1] What's it say?
[Crowd 2] A public execution.
[Crowd 3] It says
at sunset today.
[Fuu thinking]
What am I gonna do?
[frantic grunting]
[Shopkeeper] Forget about it.
I can't sell this stuff
to an amateur like you.
[whimpering]
[sighing]
I must be
the biggest sucker in Edo.
Take them you little thief.
Really? Oh, thank you!
Thank you so much!
[Fuu] Gotta borrow this
for a minute.
[Man] Hey!
[guards murmuring]
You at peace with yourself?
Hell, every freakin' day
I have to ask myself,
"Will this day be the last day
I lie in the sun?"
[Official] Vagrant Mugen.
Vagrant and ronin Jin.
These two will hereby
be executed by decapitation
and their heads put on display.
[Elder Shibui]
Are you ready to apologize?
Are you ready to grovel at my
feet and beg for forgiveness?
[Mugen]
If living means bowing down
to the likes of you bastards,
I'd rather die on my feet
with my head held high.
[gasping]
[Jin chuckling]
Well said. I agree with him.
[Elder Shibui] Very well then.
I'll grant your wish
and send you straight
to the afterlife.
[birds cawing]
[spectators gasping, whispering]
What the--
[spectators excitedly murmuring]
Yo. We put our fight on hold
until we get out
of here, agreed?
You intend to
kill them all, don't you?
I swear, you really are
the lowest of the low.
[Elder Shibui] You fools!
Don't even think
about making it out
of here alive.
♪ hip hop music ♪
Oh, I need a light.
Anyone got a light?
[Hayashi] Hey, you.
Here take this.
[Guards] Come back here!
Hey! Don't let them get away!
After them!
Come on!
Where'd he go?
[battle cries]
[Guards] Hold it!
Stay right there.
[Elder Shibui] What are you
waiting for? Kill them!
Kill them both!
W-W-W-Wait. Wait a minute.
I-I-Is it money you're after?
I-I'll give you
as much as you want.
[Jin] May the saints
forgive you...
...because I won't.
[Elder Shibui gurgles]
[Guards] Huh?
Damn. These cockroaches
keep coming.
So annoying.
Hey, look.
Uh?
[Mugen] Is that the...?
[fire sizzles]
[explosions]
[screaming, panic]
[distant mayhem]
Okay, it's your turn now, pal.
Alright.
Just hold on you two.
You guys made me
a promise. Remember?
You haven't forgotten, have you?
No, I haven't,
but this comes first.
[Mugen] Yeah,
first on my list too.
Now wait a minute!
A promise is a promise.
And if you two end up
killing each other,
there won't be anyone
left to help me.
What good is your promise then?
[Fuu sighs]
Alright, we'll decide this
by tossing this coin.
If it's heads
you fight each other.
But if it comes up tails,
you forget about the fight
and you both come with me.
Are we clear on this?
[Mugen] Give me that.
[Fuu] Think you might have
tossed it a little too far?
[Jin] He doesn't know
the meaning of restraint.
[Mugen] Kiss my ass.
[Fuu] Where is it?
It should have landed by now,
but I don't see it.
[Fuu grunts]
[Angry Mob] There they are!
Don't let them escape!
[Angry Mob] After them!
This way! Go get them!
Shit.
Hey, look! I won!
[Fuu shrieks]
♪ hip hop music ♪
[record scratching]
♪ End Theme ♪