♪ Opening Theme ♪
I can't believe that
this hot bath feels so good.
It's like heaven.
[Mugen] Just sayin'.
Don't you think
it's a little bit fishy?
How do you mean?
Like, what the hell
are we wanderin' around for?
We're searching for
the samurai who smells
of sunflowers, as I recall.
That's exactly what I'm sayin'.
I mean, if you stop
and think about it,
we really don't know jack shit
about this
sunflower dude, do we?
That's true.
Yeah, remember that one time?
[tape rewinding]
Oh yeah, the smelly guy, I been
meanin' to ask you about that.
Huh?
Who is this samurai
who smells of sunflowers?
Well, he...
What the hell
is a sunflower anyway?
Wait a minute-
You don't know?
It's a flower.
So what do they smell like?
You have any other leads?
Like a picture
or somethin'?
What makes you think
he's around here?
Aah! Stop!
You ever notice
she gets all weasely
when we bring that stuff up?
Mmm.
And this latest shit,
now she expects us
to go all the way to Nagasaki.
[tape rewinding]
[Jouji] I'm sorry,
but there's only one thing
that I can tell you:
Nagasaki is where
you should to look.
I am sure you might be able
to find answers there.
Nagasaki.
So we're just supposed
to believe this idiot
and go all the way there?
[Jin] Still, the man was
the chief merchant
of the East India Company's
Japan branch.
I doubt his information
would be unreliable.
Are you sure?
What's the difference?
With no other leads,
we haven't got much choice.
That's exactly what I'm sayin'.
There's no way in hell
she doesn't know more
than she's lettin' on.
That little tramp
is hiding somethin' from us.
Mmm.
[Mugen] Okay then.
What are you doing?
While she's busy takin' a bath,
I'm gonna snoop around a little.
[Fuu humming]
[Mugen] Here we go.
[Jin] You shouldn't go through
other people's belongings.
Hey, chill out, will ya?
It's her own fault
for not tellin' us anything.
[Jin] What is it?
I can't read.
[Jin] Give me that.
I see.
It looks like a diary.
That's her diary?
Jackpot.
There' gotta be
some information
about that sunflower dude
in there somewhere.
Yeah.
Go on, read it to me, you mook.
The tenth of July, sunny-
[Fuu] It's been almost
a year now, since Mom died.
I had always told
myself that one day
I would set out on a journey,
only I never had the courage,
so in the meantime,
I've been working and living
at this nice old guy's teahouse.
But now I've decided it's time.
I don't want
to forget this journey,
and so I decided
that starting today,
I'm going to keep this diary,
until I find the samurai
who smells of sunflowers.
And there you have it! I've kept
my word and started my diary.
I have now filled out
the very first page.
I have to admit that
the teahouse burning down
helped motivate me,
because I didn't have any choice
but to start my trip.
Parenthesis smiley face.
And as weird as this may
sound, the fire was caused
by a couple of crazy guys.
The first one to
come into the teahouse
was a crude and vulgar
guy with wild hair.
[Mugen] She talkin' about me?
The second I saw him,
I thought he was a bad guy,
the kind who commits
all sorts of crimes,
the type of person I'd
never want to be friends with
in a million years.
[Mugen] Say what?
Of course, once I
talked to him--
[Mugen] Hmm?
--I realized I was
absolutely right.
[Mugen] Shut up
you little bitch.
[Jin] You're shouting
at a diary.
I'll admit that
I needed some help.
The stupid
governor's son had come in
and thought he could
do whatever he wanted.
But even so...
[tape fast-forwarding]
Once he got started,
he didn't know when to stop.
I mean, he totally
went overboard.
If I'd known he was
going to do that,
I'd have taken my chances
with the governor's son.
[Mugen] Why you little-
In the middle of all this,
another man appeared,
one with long hair and glasses.
[Mugen] She talkin'
'bout you now?
I actually thought he
was kind of attractive,
not like the first one.
[Mugen] Huh?
[tape fast-forwarding]
But once the new guy
got into it,
he refused to stop
fighting, too.
they don't seem at all alike,
but maybe deep down
they're two of a kind.
[Jin] How rude,
don't compare me--
[Mugen] --to a guy like him.
Anyway, one thing led to
another, and before I knew it,
I had set out on my journey
with these two attendants:
Mugen and Jin.
The end.
[rewinding]
July the eleventh, sunny-
Something lousy
happened because of
those two going
crazy yesterday.
A guy showed up saying something
about Mugen cutting his arm off.
Hey there.
[gasping]
I think you should
go back to sleep for a while.
[Fuu grunting]
And so all of a sudden,
I'm this guy's hostage, geez.
Well, I was a little
drunk at the time,
so I don't remember too much.
The end.
That's it? The end?
Very brief.
P.S. The aki manjuu we had
in Joshuu were yummy.
[rewinding]
July 14th, sunny then cloudy-
I had another rotten day today
because of those two.
It all started when they
ditched me and ran away.
Thanks to that, I ended up
in a whorehouse this time.
A pervert was about
to have his way with me,
but thanks to an old
fortuneteller's advice,
I was saved.
[rewinding]
I would beware of vases
if I were you.
[ceramic breaking]
Vase?
[screaming]
A vase. It's like a little vase.
Go away!
[ceramic breaking]
July 19th-
Out of the blue, I was
kidnapped and held prisoner.
This is ridiculous.
Don't you think my life
is a little too eventful?
You know, I have to
wonder sometimes...
Why do these things
keep happening to me,
even though I have
two bodyguards?
Those bozos are pretty useless
for the most part.
I'm really starting
to think that I may have
picked the wrong guys.
I first realized this
when we had to earn money
for the ferry boat
to cross the river.
[rewinding]
My name's Moronobu Hishikawa,
and I'm a struggling
young artist.
Pleased to meet you.
I thought he was kinda cute,
even if he was a bit of a poser.
Maybe that's where
I made my mistake.
I went ahead and modeled
for his ukiyo-e painting,
but now that I think
about it, I don't know
what I ever saw in that guy.
Still, he did say
nice things to me,
which is more than I can say
for those two jerks.
Yeah, that mess was definitely
all their fault, too.
[Mugen] Hey, don't blame
your screw-ups on us.
He said that he was going to get
on a ship and go to Holland,
but I wonder what ever
happened to him.
I wonder if he's
on that ship right now.
Or who knows, maybe he's even
arrived there already.
[rewinding]
[Manzo] He, meaning
Moronobu Hishikawa,
was caught even before
he had a chance to leave port,
and never made it to Holland.
The fact is, he still
resides in that area.
However, there was no way
she could have known that
the man she met that day
would be recognized
by future generations
as the father of
ukiyo-e painting
In this world of ours,
talent and character are often
discovered in
inverse proportions.
[Fuu] P.S. The fried
squid he treated us to
was totally delicious.
Somethin' just occurred to me
that I didn't think of before.
Like what?
Like what the hell were we
even doin' going to Edo anyway?
No idea.
Take a look already,
what'd she write?
Today was the first time in ages
I was able to eat all I wanted.
I'm so happy.
I figured I might have to go
without food again after this,
so I ate enough
to tide me over.
Is she an animal?
Some of the items on
yesterday's menu included
eel rice bowls, loach stew,
and Edo-style sushi.
They were all yummy.
You hear lots of people say,
"There's always
room for dessert,"
but in my case, I think it
should be something more like,
"There's always room
for free food."
I wonder if
everybody's like that?
[Mugen] Just you, Porky.
[Jin] Mmm.
I also got to see
kabuki and fireworks,
which was really neat.
The end.
Come on, wait a minute.
Isn't there anything about
that sunflower
samurai in there?
Hmm.
All that she's writin' about
so far about is food.
Oh, that reminds me,
we're leaving today
and going to Nagasaki.
I pretty much figure
it's a long shot,
but the reason I came to Edo
was because I'd heard rumors
that he was here.
It's not like I had any
hard evidence or anything.
You're kidding me.
[Mugen] That little Bitch.
She dragged us there
because of a stupid rumor?
I can't believe it.
I got taken
hostage again, geez.
Is there anyone in the
whole world who's been
taken hostage as much as me?
To top it off,
my wallet got stolen,
and I couldn't buy
anything to eat.
I dreamed about
mom last night.
It was the first time
that I thought about her
in a long time.
It seems strange, I know.
But so much has happened
to me on this journey
that I haven't had any
time to miss her.
So, I haven't felt this way
for a long time.
It's hard for me to
find the right words
to write about Shinsuke.
I just couldn't
bring myself to say
anything to his mother, either.
But once some time has passed,
and I've had a chance
to sort out my feelings,
I definitely want to sit down
and write her a long letter.
I want to tell her
all those things
that I wanted to say back
then, but couldn't.
[Manzo] It is difficult,
if not impossible
for anyone to predict
what the future holds.
Incidentally, this is
a prediction of the lives
of people in the future,
taken from "Mudaiki,"
a speculative work of fiction
by Edo dime novel author
Harumachi Koikawa.
As you can see here,
predicting the future
is something of
a tricky business.
A case in point, what the
hell were they thinking
with those dumbass hairstyles?
[rewinding]
[Fuu] We left Edo and
started out for Nagasaki.
Well, we tried to,
but we're still in Edo.
We can't make any headway at
all, 'cause we've got no money.
At least we managed
to get a meal,
thanks to the money we got
when we pawned Jin's glasses.
It was yummy.
But then, those two went
crawling away
after some older woman.
What scumbags.
Hey, don't get me wrong,
it's not like
I'm jealous or anything.
It's just that it makes
things a lot more difficult
when my bodyguards
don't carry out their duties.
Well, I guess
she was kinda sexy.
She did have
a nice set of hooters.
Is that the kinda
women they go for?
Aww, who cares.
I got hit on today, too.
Although admittedly the guy
didn't make a whole lotta sense.
[rewinding]
It takes time to crack a pearl.
That's alright, it just makes
that jewel a lot more desirable.
Hi there, Honey. Who am I?
I'm gonna be big. My name is...
Nagamitsu Sakon Shogen.
[sighing] I'm starting
to get the feeling that
I only attract weirdoes.
What's a girl to do?
In the end,
we picked up a little money
with a street performance,
and we were
able to leave Edo.
But with every passing day,
it feels like I'm losing sight
of what I'm really after.
We're supposed
to be looking for
the samurai who
smells of sunflowers.
But we always end up
spending all our time
scrounging up enough
money to survive.
I guess the point
I'm trying to make here is:
getting by in life sure is hard.
The end.
P.S. the pear was yummy.
[rewinding]
[Manzo] As a side note,
there's been a recent uproar
over rampant sexuality
in the country's youth.
However, keep in mind
that Japanese people
had a rather open-minded
view of sexuality,
And it was especially liberal
during the Edo Period.
They only became prudish
in the Meiji Era
after the influx of
Western culture.
So, to put this in perspective,
one could say
that they've merely
returned to the values
of the Edo Period.
And if you take the time
to delve into world history,
then you'll discover that
Japan's Edo Period can be placed
right alongside the civilization
of ancient Greece,
and that it was an era in
which gay love flourished,
and homosexuality was considered
a more noble pursuit
than heterosexuality.
Incidentally, please forgive my
extremely delayed introduction.
My name is Manzo the Saw.
I'm an officer with
the secret police,
and I fight night and day
in the name of peace.
[rewinding]
[Fuu] I got
taken prisoner again.
We finally left Edo and got as
far as the Kanto checkpoint,
when we got conned by a scalper.
It seems like I've been
scammed a lot
since I started
on this journey.
I don't know, am I too naïve?
Maybe I ought to be
more suspicious of people.
Am I a bad judge of character?
I had a lot
to think about today.
Of course the worst part of it
all is that jerk, Mugen.
I believed in him,
thinking he'd come back for us.
What kind of rescuer
ends up needing to be rescued?
Anyway, I finally decided
never to trust him again.
[Mugen] Yeah, well that
suits me just fine.
Go ahead and don't trust me.
See if I care.
By the way, I spent
a lot of time with Jin,
because that jerk,
Mugen, didn't come back.
Now that I think about it,
I guess that was
the first time I ever
spent any time alone with him.
[Mugen] Huh?
I thought to myself,
"We're finally going to have
a heart to heart conversation."
But Jin kept his mouth
shut the whole time.
It was like he'd
taken a vow of silence.
I'd always thought that
at times like that,
guys were supposed to open up
and tell you all sorts of stuff.
I tried to break the ice, but
all I could get out of him was
a "Hmm," or an "Aah."
What's his problem?
That's what I'd like to know.
Does he hate me or something?
Or is he just shy?
I mean, after all,
we've been on this journey
for quite a while now.
How long is it going
to take before
he finally gets around
to opening up to me?
It's kinda sad, really.
The end.
Jin, man-to-man, what do you
really think of her, anyway?
Hmm.
[sighing] This guy's hopeless.
[rewinding]
[Manzo] The 1950s,
San Francisco, California.
A time in which the youth of
the so-called Beat Generation
were profoundly
influenced by Zen.
And that influence, in turn,
was passed on to
the Hippies of the 1960s.
Also known as
the flower children,
they turned away
from civilized society,
tripped on psychedelic music,
expanded their minds
and searched for true freedom.
It is said that among the
Hippies, there were those
who approached Zen
as a counterculture,
chanted Buddhist mantras,
burned incense,
and practiced meditation.
Elsewhere, during
the Edo Period in Japan,
although they aren't searching
for anything in particular,
here we find three people
deep in meditation.
And if one were to ask why these
people are doing this, well...
I'm sorry, friend, but we
don't even have enough money
for a place to sleep.
We don't have anything
to give you for charity.
[Zuikou] Well, that's wonderful.
I'm glad to hear that.
Huh?
[Fuu] Starting today, we'll be
staying at this Zen temple
for a while.
The monk in charge of
the temple is giving us
free room and board
while we're here.
It's more than
we could have hoped for.
But in return, we have to follow
the strict rules of the temple.
I've been working hard since
the crack of dawn again today.
Boy am I beat.
Since the beginning,
man was born into
a state of freedom.
He was not born so that he might
submit to rules or to a master.
This thought has occurred to me.
My question is this:
the duties of a warrior...
Does this philosophy
not contradict them?
No, because freedom cannot
be forced into existence.
Nor can it be won
through painful struggle.
Freedom cannot
be bought or sold.
It has nothing to do
with one's social status.
One's profession
is of no consequence.
In order for you
to accept yourself as you are
and live with
your soul at peace,
you must simply
teach yourself to let it be.
Only then will you
discover freedom.
Those idiots.
A lot of terrible things
happened to me lately,
and it's all because of them.
I have to wonder at times.
Did I pick the right two men
to go with me on this journey?
Ya know?
[Zuikou] All encounters happen
but once in a lifetime.
There is no right or wrong.
If you have met these two men
and are traveling with them now,
then that is your destiny.
For better or worse,
whatever the outcome
of your journey may be.
[Mugen] Hey, Master Chrome Dome,
I'm lookin' to
make myself stronger, here.
You got any brilliant ideas?
I wanna beat
that freaky bastard.
Hey, you listenin' to me, baldy?
How the hell am I
supposed to beat this guy?
Come on!
Start talkin', cue ball.
[Zuikou] Katsu!
Ow!
Look at that moon,
it's so big tonight.
[Mugen] I'm headin' out
for a bit.
You haven't forgotten
your promise, have you?
Huh?
The samurai who smells
of sunflowers, remember?
Don't forget, you said
you'd help me find him.
I won't forget.
[Jin] One other thing.
Hmm?
I shall be the one
who gets to slay you.
[Fuu] Looking back now,
sure a lot
of crappy stuff has happened,
but I've experienced
all sorts of new things, too.
If Mugen and Jin hadn't wandered
into the teahouse that day,
then chances are, I'd still
be working there right now.
When I think of it that way,
maybe it's like
Father Zuikou says:
It was a once in a
lifetime chance encounter.
I have no idea what stands
between here and Nagasaki
or how much longer
it'll take us to get there.
I just hope
the three of us can keep
traveling together
to the very end.
I'm positive that those two are
thinking the exact same thing.
Yep, that's the path
I chose to take.
[Mugen] You don't make up
other people's minds for them.
Right?
[Jin] Hmm.
[Fuu] Just kidding.
I figured those two
might try and get a peek
at my diary without asking,
so I decided to make
all that stuff up.
Serves you right, you jerks.
You--
[Mugen screaming]
--you little bitch!
♪ End Theme ♪