♪ Opening Theme ♪
[Sailors] Pirates!
Pirates! They're
coming straight for us!
Starboard!
Hard to starboard, now!
[men screaming]
Please, don't do this.
Take whatever you want,
just please don't kill me.
[muffled protesting]
Let's rest.
Huh?
I can't walk anymore.
Here we are, totally lost,
because somebody
wanted to take a shortcut.
Aw, quit your bitchin'.
We ain't even close to lost.
Look at where we are,
and tell me we're not lost.
I can smell it from here.
We're right by the ocean.
The ocean?
[Mugen] Yeah,
it's right up there.
Really?
[seagulls cawing]
[yelling] It's the ocean!
[Fuu giggling]
It's cold.
I thought that you
couldn't walk anymore.
What a whiner.
Whatever.
Mugen?
It can't be.
[Koza] Mugen!
You're still alive.
Hey, what's wrong?
Who is she? You know her?
Aah!
♪ hip hop beat ♪
[men screaming]
[Ryu] Easy pickin's.
Take everything they got.
[Fuu] Will someone please
tell me what's going on?
[Nobu] Dammit
So then, they're tough guys.
[Koza] Hold on, stop.
These people are-
Mind your own damned business.
[laughing]
Well, I never
expected I'd see you again.
Back from the dead, Mugen?
I'd always figured that the next
time we'd meet would be in Hell.
Well, then let me do the honor
of sending you there
personally, Mukuro.
[laughing]
Aren't we lucky?
Who'd have thought
we'd ever come across you.
We haven't been jumping people
just for their money.
We've been looking
for the meanest,
toughest bastards
we could find.
[Mugen] What for?
[Mukuro] Well, I know you won't
object to this...
We're gonna pull off the biggest
damned heist you've ever seen.
Run with us on this one, and
you'll rake in a ton of cash.
Thanks, I'll pass.
What's wrong?
Don't tell me
you've gone soft.
I don't work for nobody but me.
I thought I told you
all that before.
Oh, so then, tell me what
you're doin' with these two.
I got no commitments to them.
I'm just protecting them,
'til they get to Nagasaki,
that's all.
[Mukuro] You're protecting them?
You're kiddin' right?
Now that's funny.
That's a good one.
Hey, do you two have any idea
what kind of past this guy has?
Are you the least bit aware
of the number of lives
this guy's taken?
And now he says
he's protectin' people.
That's real amusin'.
[laughing]
That's better.
That's the Mugen
that I remember.
Is it all comin'
back to you now, buddy?
[Fuu] Mugen?
Hey, wait up.
Don't leave.
[Fuu] Really?
That nasty Mukuro guy's
your older brother?
But you don't
look anything like him.
How weird.
My name is Koza.
We grew up on the same island,
me and my brother and Mugen.
Back when we were just kids...
[Fuu] An island?
[Koza] Yeah, down in
the Ryukyu Islands,
one of the little ones...
where they send criminals
when they're exiled.
It was...
what I imagine Hell to be like.
[Koza] Everyone on that island,
except for the children,
has some kind of criminal past.
Me and Mukuro and Mugen
were born and raised there.
And that life
was the only world we knew.
So, he said that you guys
are going to Nagasaki.
Oh, yeah that's right.
We sure are.
We're looking for a samurai
who smells of sunflowers.
[Koza] Sunflowers?
Do you know him?
No, I'm afraid not.
But to get back on the road
that takes you to Nagasaki,
your best bet is gonna be
taking a boat
straight over to Ise.
[Fuu] A boat?
I'll go and see
if I can find one.
A boat, huh?
We're not taking a boat.
All it's gonna do is sink,
and we'll all end up dead.
I think if Mugen's with you,
that you'll be okay.
Huh?
You mean Mugen knows
how to work a boat?
Of course.
You mean he's never
mentioned it to you before?
[Koza] But...
This means that...
that he's leaving again.
[Fuu] Are you alright?
[Koza] I'm fine.
I just thought.
That I might be able
to be with Mugen again.
Just like the old days.
[Fuu] But, it didn't look
like Mugen and your brother
were on very good terms.
[Koza] I wish that
my brother was dead.
Well, I guess I can understand
with a brother like that.
But if you really
hate him that much,
you know don't
have to stay with him.
You're wrong.
[Koza] I know that I wouldn't be
able to survive on my own.
[Fuu] What the heck is up
with this village?
There's not
a single person anywhere.
[birds cawing]
[Mukuro] Don't tell me that
you've forgotten about it.
About the darkness you've got
in that soul of yours.
Now's your chance,
if you've got any last words.
Yeah, can you speed it up?
Well, now.
[Mugen] I don't give a rat's ass
about going to Hell.
Guess I feel like I'm
already there, anyway.
What really rubs me the
wrong way is the thought of
being killed by
you ugly bastards.
I've lived my whole life without
taking help from nobody.
And I'll be damned if
I'm gonna let you guys
help me into my grave.
[Koza gasping]
Son of a bitch.
Shoot him. Shoot him!
[Officer] What a fool.
Did he really think
he was gonna save himself
by jumping off this cliff?
[Murkuro] You got it?
First one to pull his reigns
before we hit the cliff loses.
If I win, then you
gotta work with me.
You got it?
--[Murkuro] Hyah!
--[Mugen] Ha!
[chuckling]
You bastard.
[Murkuro] Now do you remember?
In the end, my friend,
you and me are just
a couple of cursed men.
There will never be
a place for us to run to.
[Jin] They killed
everyone in the village
except for the young men.
No one was spared. Not even
the women and children.
My guess is that the men were
forced to fight each other.
And the survivors are the ones
who make up that gang.
I think that we'd be better
off staying away from Mukuro.
We should probably
leave here in the morning.
[Fuu] Mugen.
[Mugen] I'm gonna take the job.
But you can't take it.
What about us
going to Nagasaki?
Well, either way,
we're gonna need the cash.
We can manage.
Clearly, he tried to provoke
you, and you fell for it.
I changed my mind.
That's all there is to it.
As you wish.
Don't think you guys
are gonna change my mind.
[Fuu] Mugen!
Will you wait.
Mugen!
[Murkuro] I knew you'd come.
Alright then.
I got one condition.
Hmm? What's that?
Once this job's done, I never
have to see your ugly ass again.
Got it?
[Murkuro] Alright, listen up.
Our target's a shogunate
transport ship carrying
60,000 ryo in gold coins.
The ship has already
set sail and is currently
en route from Osaka to Edo.
And tonight, it's gonna dock
right here in our harbor.
They're stoppin' here
to let their sailors rest
and to load up on
some fresh food and water.
And that's when
we're gonna hit 'em.
[Mugen] Hang on a minute.
Just where in the hell are you
getting' this information from?
I got a connection
that's workin' from
inside the transport ship.
This mole's
a member of my gang.
Here's how it'll go.
Ken and Ryu will take out
the shipyard guys and carry
the barrels of supplies
onto the ship.
Inside one of those barrels
will be a surprise:
me.
I'll use a gunpowder bomb
to stir up a commotion.
While I'm doin' that,
the rest of you sneak up
with a pirate ship and
ambush from the side,
after that,
it's business as usual.
We board the ship, show no
mercy, and take everything.
The 60,000 ryo
and their lives.
And when we're done
stealing the gold,
we'll blow that ship sky high.
You realize that this is a
government transport ship?
[Murkuro] I'm aware of that.
It's gonna be crawling with
top-notch security guards.
But we don't have
enough guys for this.
That's why tonight's
our only shot.
It's gonna be rainin' tonight,
and there won't
be any moonlight.
We'll use the darkness
and be on that ship
before they know what hit 'em.
But it's clear outside.
You sure it's gonna rain?
Oh yeah, it'll rain.
How do you know?
I can smell it...
in the wind.
[Murkuro laughing]
Now that we have that settled,
let's put this plan into action.
The wind is really
picking up outside.
You think Mugen will be okay?
He has made his choice.
I know, but still.
[footsteps]
[Koza] Mugen.
Do you remember...
that time you and me laid down
and looked at the stars?
Do you remember what you said?
You said that if you were
looking down from up there,
nobody'd look any bigger than
a grain of sand down here.
Ain't ringin' any bells.
[Koza] If we had been
born someplace else,
someplace other than
that island,
I wonder what kind of people
we'd have turned out to be.
Are you happy now, Mugen?
[Mugen] Hmm?
I dunno. Can't say
I've given that much thought.
[Koza] I think Fuu
is really lucky.
[Mugen] You think so?
[Koza] Yeah.
Because, because she gets
to be with you, Mugen.
Mugen.
I wanna be with you, too.
Like she is.
I wanna get out of this place.
I wanna run away.
With you.
Sorry, but I'm the wrong guy
for that job.
[Mugen] Later.
♪ funk beat ♪
We brought you your water
and supplies, Sir.
Very well, I think I'll
just inspect the cargo.
Yes, Sir.
Something wrong?
Well, considering
the weather, Sir...
If we don't get these on board
soon, they're gonna get soaked.
I see your point.
[Shiren] Alright,
load them onto the ship.
[Mukuro] You got it. I'm takin'
em all out, even our own men.
We'll rendezvous with Shiren
when the job's done.
What about Mugen?
Time to go.
Where the hell'd
that come from?
[Mukuro] Sorry 'bout that.
My finger slipped.
Who're you?
You bastard.
Relax boys, I'll make sure
the next one
hits ya right between the eyes.
[Mukuro] Now don't
make me jumpy.
[explosion]
Alright, let's go.
♪ hip hop music ♪
What the hell happened?
[door sliding open]
[Shiren] These lowlife scum have
no respect for authority.
Teach 'em a lesson, men!
[Mugen] Thought he was supposed
to blow these guys up.
[Koza] You have to save Mugen.
Hurry up. He's gonna die.
What're you talking about?
[Jin] So it was a trap.
[men yelling]
Mukuro, you son of a bitch.
You played me, didn't ya?
Holy shit.
[Mugen] Damn you.
You bastard!
Mukuro!
[Koza] The
pirate ship's on fire!
[Fuu] What?
Who's on that ship?
Mugen!
[Fuu] Mugen!
♪ End Theme ♪