♪ Opening Theme ♪
[Mugen] Let me get
behind you, huh?
You're gettin' sloppy letting
your guard down like that.
[stomachs gurgling]
[Mugen groans]
What are you two doing?
Morning workout. We're done.
[Fuu] I swear.
What is it with you two?
Why do you have to attack each
other at the drop of a hat
for no good reason? You'd
think that two grown men
would have something better
to do. Jeez, you two owe me
your lives, remember?
If it weren't for me,
you'd both be history right now.
So I'm not gonna let you two
break your promise to me, got
it? Until we find the samurai
who smells of sunflowers, you
guys are absolutely forbidden
to fight one another. Is that
clear? I have absolutely
no idea why you men feel
it's necessary to use up
all that energy workin' up a
sweat doing all that pointless
physical exercise when we're
almost starving to death.
Not to mention, I haven't had
a bath for ages and ages.
My good looks
are gonna be ruined.
People are gonna think
I'm some old hag or...
What in the--?
What are you guys up to?
It's creepy.
[Mugen] If you ask me, I'd say
you've got a lot on the ball.
Right?
[Jin] Right.
[Fuu] I'm not sure I like this.
[Mugen] Yeah, I gotta admit,
you're the bomb.
Babe like you'll do fine
on your own.
Right?
[Jin] Right.
[Fuu] What the hell
does that mean?
[Mugen] What we mean is...
Huh?
Sayonara, sweetheart.
[hurried footsteps fading away]
Hey, wait!
[Fuu whining]
You've gotta be kidding me.
[birds chirping, water lapping]
[Shop Owner]
Welcome. Have a seat.
[Mugen] Think I'll sit here.
[Shop Owner] Sir,
there are plenty of other, uh...
Excuse me, Sir, but perhaps
you don't understand.
These guys are made men.
If you know what I mean, Sir.
You mean... yakuza?
♪ hip hop music ♪
[Shop Owner whimpers]
Yakuza. Ain't they the
dudes that need to get
their boss's permission
before they take a dump?
What the hell did you say?
Don't you know who we are? We're
the Nagatomi Gang, you fool.
So you got lots of dough. Why
not spread it around a little?
[Ngatomi 1 screaming]
Ow, my hand!
[Nagatomi 2] You bastard!
[Mugen] Chill out, dudes.
I'm hungry,
and I'm in a bad mood.
Could cost you
a whole lot more than one hand.
A real comedian.
Try laughin' when you're dead.
[grunting fearfully]
You're history you little punk.
[Rikiei] Hold it.
But... why, Boss?
Hm?
How'd you like me to
treat you to something
a lot better than this stuff?
You're strong,
and you got a lot of guts.
I like you.
Huh? But Boss...
You don't get it. Not one of
you is a match for this man.
Guess some of them crab thingies
wouldn't be too shabby.
[smirking]
Come with me.
[men talking, jeering]
[Dice Roller] Place your bets.
Place your bets.
[Gamblers]
Chou! Han! Chou! Chou!
Place your bets.
[Gambler] Han!
Han.
Gotta be chou. Come on.
[Gamblers] There it is.
Come on baby. Wait for it...
[Dice Roller]
Play. Two, five. Han!
[men cheering, protesting]
[Diagoro moans]
[Ishimatsu] Guess it's
not your night.
You lost a bundle, Pops.
It's time to pay up.
What's up dude?
I haven't seen any crabs yet.
Relax. I own this place.
I'll get you whatever you want.
[men talking, laughing]
Final call. Place your bets.
[Gamblers]
Han! Han. Give me chou.
Gonna be chou this time.
Hmm?
[Gamblers jeering]
[Rikiei] I know something else
that's a sure thing too.
Huh?
Before long, a man's
status and title won't
mean anything in this country.
All that'll matter is
who has the most power.
[Dice Roller] Play!
Six, six. Chou!
[Gamblers grumbling, protesting]
My intuition's
never been wrong yet.
Hm.
[wind chime tinkling softly]
[Osuzu] Alright, Sosuke. Who was
the founder of Confucianism?
Daydreaming again?
Oh, I, um... What was it again?
For goodness sake,
Sosuke, you were the one
who asked me
to tutor you, remember?
[Nagatomi 2] You bastard! You
think you're real funny, huh?
The fact that I'm here means
that you're in serious trouble.
Please don't take my store.
It's all I have left.
I'm begging you.
Oh, yeah! What the hell
were you gambling for
if you couldn't
cover your marker?
The game was fixed.
I know it was.
You shouldn't slander other
people's reputations like that.
If you have proof
you were cheated,
would you show it to me?
[door sliding open]
[Osuzu] Father?
Go back inside, now.
When someone can't pay us,
they have to give us something
of equal value instead.
[door sliding shut]
[Shop Owner] Welcome, Sir.
What can I get for you?
[Jin] Well, actually,
the thing is...
Mister, don't tell me
you're broke.
Oh, no, not again!
No offense, but I've
already dealt with
one penniless vagrant today.
He caused quite
a commotion you know.
Any idea where I
might find some work?
Ah, you're a sword for hire.
Well, I'd say you arrived
here at just the right time.
For many years, this town's been
controlled by yakuza called
the Kawara Gang. Been that way
as long as I can remember.
The Kawaras are alright. They do
as much for this town as anyone.
And their boss
is so kindhearted
he's called
"Heitaro the Buddha."
This has always been
a peaceful town.
But then about six months ago,
those thugs called
the Nagatomi Gang showed up.
And since then,
everything's changed.
[Daigoro] Please, Mr. Heitaro,
isn't there something
you can do? If not,
they'll take over my business.
I'll lose my shop.
I'll lose everything.
Raise your head,
Daigoro, and listen to me.
You and I have known each other
for a long time.
And Osuzu there is taking
excellent care of my son.
Naturally, I'll help you
in any way I can.
However, since you've
no proof to substantiate
your allegations,
there's nothing I can do.
[Kawara Gang 1]
But Boss, Daigoro wasn't
the only one it's happened to.
Almost every gambler in town's
been swindled by those goons.
[Kawara Gang 2]
We could lose everything to
the Nagatomi Gang.
Even our women!
[Kawara Gang 1]
At this rate it won't be long
before they gain control
of our entire territory.
[Kawara Gang 2] Boss!
[Kawara Gang 1] Boss!
[Rikiei] The weak
get eaten by the strong.
I've risen to where I am now by
devouring every weakling
that crossed my path.
One after the other.
Everything around here that's
worth calling a town
already belongs to me.
And now this one will too.
[shell crunching]
Tough little bastard.
[crunching, chomping]
You are an interesting guy.
How'd you like
to join forces with me?
Huh?
If we combine my expertise
and money with your courage
and raw power, no one could
stop us. So how 'bout it?
Wanna take over
the country with me?
That game with the dice
was rigged, wasn't it?
What's that?!
Take over the country my ass.
You're even phonier
than your dice.
[Shop Owner] And that's the way
it stands. At least for now.
I figure it's got
nothing to do with me,
regardless of how it turns out.
I have no money.
Well, if you're looking for
a way to earn some quick cash,
the Nagatomi Gang's always
looking for bodyguards.
Seems like they
never have enough.
Speak of the devil.
They're here.
That's the Nagatomi Gang
right now.
[Shop Owner] Good afternoon.
[Sosuke] Give me that IOU.
Hand it over!
[Nagatomi 3] Well, well,
what do we have here?
Why, it's little Kawara Jr.
You've got an IOU
from Osuzu's father.
Now hand it over!
[Sosuke] If you didn't
cheat him out of his money,
he wouldn't owe you
anything, you bastards!
[Nagatomi 3]
What's your problem kid?
[Nagatomi 4] Get lost kid.
Come back when you grow up.
[Sosuke] Give it back!
[Sosuke gasping, groaning]
You better run along home. Your
mama's waitin' for you boy.
[Sosuke grunting painfully]
[Jin] You there. Boy.
Huh?
I believe you have
need of a bodyguard.
Watch and I'll
show you my skill.
Say what?
You third-rate samurai.
[Sosuke] Give me that.
Give me the IOU.
Give it!
Here! Take the damn thing.
And I hope you choke on it.
[Nagatomi 3] You'll pay
for this you bastard.
[Shop Owner moaning]
[Fuu] Oh, I just can't
believe those two.
How could they run off
like that and abandon me?
Fine, see if I care.
I don't need them.
I'll look for the
sunflower samurai by myself.
[stomach grumbling]
I sure am hungry.
[Fortune Teller] You there.
Huh?
[Fortune Teller] You seem
to be searching for something.
Yes, you're
absolutely right. I am.
Ah, you are
searching for two men.
Hm? For two men? Hmm...
Oh, you mean those two.
[clinking]
Uh, this is all I have left.
Could you tell me where to look?
Well, I'll give you a hint.
I would beware
of vases if I were you.
Vases?
[Nagatomi 2] Hey, Ishimatsu!
[Ishimatsu] What? You look like
you've seen a ghost.
You say he was a bodyguard?
[Nagatomi 2] Yes, Sir. And a
damn strong one, let me tell ya.
He was so fast, I didn't
even see him draw his sword.
[Ishimatsu] So he beat you,
and you ran back here
crying like babies.
Y-Y-Yes, Sir.
[Mugen laughing]
Sounds like fun.
Leave it to me.
I'll take care of him for you.
Is that so? Well that's
mighty fine of you.
[Ishimatsu] Hold on, Sir.
If it's muscle you need,
that's what I'm here for.
[Rikiei] That man isn't merely
hired muscle, Ishimatsu.
He's my partner.
[Rikiei] Hey.
[Ishimatsu] This gang doesn't
need two men doing the same job.
The one who survives
will protect this gang.
Come on!
♪ electronic music ♪
Come on, bring it dude.
Give me your best shot.
[Ishimatsu laughing]
[Mugen chuckling] Pretty sweet.
[Rikiei] That's enough.
Huh?
Ishimatsu, get over to
that cabinetmaker's place
and grab his daughter.
What? But Boss, one of the
younger guys could do that--
Have you forgotten
how to follow an order?
Thanks a lot, Sir.
Without your help I--
Huh?
Hey, wait up! Hold on!
I'm sure my father will agree
to hire you as a bodyguard.
Please say you will.
Why is it you carry a sword?
Huh?
[Jin] That isn't a toy.
If they'd cut you down, they'd
have been within their rights.
Never carry a weapon unless
you're willing
and able to use it.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
[crying] You think you
can make fun of me 'cause
I'm just a kid, don't you?
But one day... One day I'll...
[clay shattering]
[Townsman 1] Oh, no!
[Fuu] I'm so sorry.
[Townsman 1] This is terrible.
Just terrible.
I sure hope you can pay for it.
Huh?
I said I hope you got enough
money to pay for this vase.
Vase? What's it worth?
A hundred ryo.
How much?
Listen lady, you shouldn't
go around breaking things
if you can't afford
to pay for them.
[Townsman 2] How much
do you need? A hundred ryo?
Uh, yeah.
Then you're in luck. I have
a job that you're perfect for.
You do?
[Townsman 1 chuckling]
Huh? What do you...?
Hey wait! Wait!
[Osuzu] No!
Osuzu!
Stop it! Let go!
We won't eat her old man.
We're not monsters, you know?
But she'll be working off your
debt until it's paid in full,
so you won't be
seeing her for a while.
Please, let her go. I'll pay
you back as soon as possib--
Hey, it's out of my hands.
You'll need to take it up
with the Kawara Gang.
This was about your family, but
now it's a lot more complicated.
You have only yourself to blame.
Because your friends hired
a tough bodyguard
who took back your IOU.
[Heitaro] Ishimatsu.
Hmm?
Mr. Heitaro, you used to be
my boss, but not anymore.
Address me respectfully
or not at all.
Now let's go.
[yelling]
That hurt.
[door sliding shut]
What's going on?
You're going to work until
you've earned that hundred ryo.
[Fuu] Wait a minute. Do you
mean to tell me that this is a--
A brothel, of course.
What did you think it was?
You're kidding me.
[Sosuke] Dad, listen to this.
[Heitaro] Is this the bodyguard
I've been hearing about?
Huh?
[Heitaro] Where's the IOU?
You little fool.
Osuzu's going to be forced
to work in a brothel.
She was taken there
a few minutes ago.
No way.
[Heitaro] You must have known
what would happen.
An eye for an eye.
That's the way the Nagatomis
handle everything.
Which is why, for all our sakes,
I've chosen not to
confront them.
Boss, we can't stand it anymore.
Let's raid their headquarters.
That's exactly
what they want us to do.
Anger breeds more anger,
destroying those around it.
And once it's begun,
it's a never-ending cycle.
And that is why
I'm afraid I must ask your guest
to leave now. The Kawara Gang
has no need for a bodyguard.
They're walking all over us.
Doesn't it bother you?
And what about Osuzu?
You can't just leave her there.
You're always saying things like
"anger breeds more anger,"
or "don't spill blood
unless it's necessary."
Well that might have worked
when there was peace, Dad,
but not now. Not anymore.
Those days are over!
Let's go.
If the Kawaras won't hire you
as a bodyguard, then I will.
I forbid it.
[Sosuke] I'm going after
all those Nagatomi bastards!
[Heitaro] I will not allow it.
Wait, Sosuke!
Hey, there. You're
new here too, aren't you?
Yes. How did you know?
I can see how sad you are,
and that's how I feel too.
Oh, come on now. Cheer up.
We'll help each other
and hope for the best.
Hope's a wonderful thing,
but I've none left.
I'll be helping my father pay
his debts by working here,
but still...
[men talking, women laughing]
[Sosuke] Damn, their security's
really tight.
Both our faces are known.
Getting in there can
be quite difficult indeed.
I got it.
You ask me, now's
not the time to be
chasing cathouse skirts around.
[Rikiei] What's your rush?
Rest assured the Kawaras'
bodyguard will be here.
That's why I baited
the hook so carefully.
Why go to all this
trouble for one guy?
It'd be quicker to just storm
the place and trash them all.
That's how we'd do it
back in the old days.
Now we remove the enemy's claws
and start him working for us.
Think about it.
If we start a war with
these guys, the people in town,
our customers, might be too
scared to do business with us.
And if the government
notices, they could make
a whole lot of trouble for us.
So when I make my move against
the Kawaras, I'll do it legally,
not by fighting in the streets.
I don't like waiting around.
Then don't just sit there.
Why don't you go
get laid or something?
[Sosuke with disguised voice]
We were wondering if
your establishment
had any jobs available.
Can't help you pal.
[Nagatomi 2]
That's one huge broad.
May we go in?
Yeah, through
that door over there.
[men talking, women giggling]
[Sosuke with normal voice] You
look pretty good in that outfit.
[Jin] It's quite uncomfortable.
[Rikiei] Pick whichever one
you want. On me.
[Nagatomi 2] Hey, you!
Yeah, you, the tall one.
Play something for us
on that shamisen.
[extremely bad playing]
Huh?
[smirking]
♪ hip hop music ♪
Cross dressers.
I mean, double crossers!
It's him. It's the
Kawara bodyguard!
Cool!
Hurry, Osuzu!
What the...?
Look who's here.
Tell me why you're here.
Why I'm here? Why are you here?
[Fuu] Hey! What the hell
do you think you're doing?
What about the promise you made
not to kill each other?
Guess no matter
how hard we try...
...fate's gonna keep
throwing us back together.
♪ End Theme ♪