♪♪♪
Don't give up on me now,
I'm just starting to have fun.
You bastard.
Shit.
I think it's about time
you learned how we felt
when we were forced
to live in disgrace.
I'm gonna take my time
and enjoy myself
while I destroy your life.
That's fair, isn't it?
I think I deserve that much.
'Cause in case you've forgotten,
you destroyed ours.
[Mugen screaming]
[Old Man] Who's there?
[Fuu] Um...uh... I'm looking
for Seizo Kasumi.
Is that you?
I'm afraid not.
This is no place for
a young lady like you
to be wandering
around by herself.
You should go home.
[Fuu] Please, Sir.
I came here to see someone.
I've traveled a long way,
and I've gone through
so much to find him.
I wouldn't have
believed it... could it be?
Wait here a moment.
[Mugen screaming]
[Umanosuke] Careful now.
I'd never forgive myself
if I allowed you
to die so easily.
Because there's a lesson
that I want you to learn.
I feel I have a responsibility
to teach you how it
feels to be disgraced.
And then to have
to go on living.
[Mugen] What a load of crap.
Huh?
You dumb dickhead, when it
comes to livin' with disgrace,
I wrote the book.
There ain't a damn thing a loser
like you could ever teach me.
You want me to have
a taste of how you feel?
Then quit talkin' like a pussy.
When you point
a sword at someone,
either you kill them
or they kill you.
There ain't no in between.
Now I'm tired of
all your pissin' and moanin',
so why don't you
shut up and get over it!
[Umanosuke] Ah,
now that was dirty.
Keeping that little dagger
hidden away like that
wasn't fair, was it?
I don't know.
See, I've always thought
of it as my ace in the hole.
[Seizo] Is there someone here?
[Old Man] Yes, Seizo, it is I.
There is a young girl outside.
She says that she has traveled
a great distance to see you.
What would you have me do?
If you like, I could
tell her to come back later.
No, don't. It's alright.
If she wants to see me,
send her in.
Forgive me for not
standing to greet you.
Please tell me your name.
I'm afraid my eyes
can't see very much these days.
[Fuu] Ever since I was
a very young girl,
my mother and I
lived by ourselves.
As long as I can remember,
I've been told that my father
had died a long time ago.
But now I know
that wasn't true.
He was alive the whole time,
and he had abandoned
Mother and me.
My mother finally told me
the truth as she lay dying.
Even now, when people
ask me about my father,
I say I don't have one.
I tell them, "I don't even
consider myself his daughter.
If I met him now,
I wouldn't accept any excuses.
I won't forgive him
as long as I live."
And why should I?
He knows nothing of what
my mother and I went through...
How we both suffered
when mother was sick.
Or the way she died.
That's why I swore
when I met him,
I would make sure
he understood.
I swore I'd finally
belt him one, no matter what.
I had it all planned.
This isn't fair.
I can't do anything to you now,
not if you're like this.
Fuu.
I don't think
we'll see each other again.
Goodbye.
[Young Fuu] Dear God,
please hear my prayer.
Once is all I ask.
When I grow up, please let me
meet my father someday.
[Old Man] The moment I saw you,
I said to myself,
"This is Seizo's daughter."
You should know that
he's thought about you
and your mother a great deal.
As long as I've known him,
he has always been-
Who- Who are you?
--[Fuu] Wait!
--[Old Man] Don't.
Let go!
[Kariya] Seizo Kasumi,
I presume.
I am Guard Captain
Kagetoki Kariya.
I have come here under order
of the shogun to take your life.
Well then, do what you have to.
I'm as good as dead already.
[Kariya] Do you have any
last words before you die?
[Seizo] Fuu, I have no right
to ask forgiveness.
I don't deserve it.
But you should know...
Not a single day has passed
when I have not thought
of you and your mother.
Please forgive me.
Damn it! Come out and fight.
I have fulfilled my first order.
I must now eliminate Kasumi's
family members and retainers.
No please don't.
Well that hurt like
a son of a bitch, didn't it?
I've had enough of this shit.
[Umanosuke laughing maniacally]
So, you wanna play
hide and seek, huh?
Ready or not, here I come!
I'm comin' ta getcha!
Found ya.
Bastard!
This is where you die.
You're pissin' me off!
Mugen.
I'm grateful you
selected this location.
You've chosen well.
If you are truly
the daughter of a samurai,
you may choose
to take your own life.
[gunshot]
You... son of a bitch.
Jin.
[Kariya] You have
my compliments.
You've somehow managed
to avoid a fatal blow.
In your current
condition however,
you can't possibly defeat me.
Why are you here?
Are you trying to throw away
the life you so narrowly
managed to keep?
As I recall, you once said,
"There are no lords
worth risking your life for."
That's right.
For my entire life,
I've chosen to fight
for no one but myself.
My dedication and
my study of the sword
was for no one but myself.
Until now.
[Mariya] This is the last lesson
I have to teach you.
It is the only means
in which to kill your opponent
when you have
no hope of victory.
It is not likely
you will survive,
but it is possible that
you will take him with you.
You leave an opening
in your defense,
which allows him to strike.
When that happens,
it creates a brief opening
for you to deliver your blow.
Your chances of surviving the
encounter are virtually zero.
If at all possible,
do not ever use this technique.
I swear, I always
get stuck with it.
[Mugen wheezing]
You... bastard...
Jin!
I can't believe you opened
yourself up for my attack.
Mugen!
[Mugen] What?
You guys again.
I can't move my body.
Looks like I finally bought it.
It's been sweet.
[Fuu] Mugen!
Mugen!
Mugen, you're alive.
Aw shit, it's only you.
I thought you were the angel
of death for a minute there.
[Fuu] It seems like
all I do is cry.
And here I was trying to
make it on my own. [sobbing]
You dumb broad.
What about the
sunflower samurai?
D'you finally meet him?
You did, huh?
A promise is a promise.
And you and I have
some unfinished business
to take care of.
You're right for once.
We really suck.
You got that right.
[Old Man] It's important that
you know the truth.
Seizo wanted to bring you
and your mother with him.
But he needed to
separate himself to keep
the shogunate's Christian hounds
from coming after you as well.
That is why your father
came here by himself.
In my memories
I can picture my father.
He was such a big man
and incredibly strong.
But then when I met him,
he wasn't anything like that.
He seemed so small
and frail lying there.
But still,
even before he spoke...
I sensed that he was my father.
Are you awake?
I guess.
[Jin] I could be wrong, but
this doesn't seem like Hell.
[Mugen] This is so weird.
Up until now,
whenever I met somebody
who was tougher than me,
I couldn't rest
until I killed the guy.
For some reason, I dunno,
I just don't feel like
killin' you at all.
[Jin] I, too, feel as if
I finally found
what I've been
searching for all this time.
I have been alone
my entire life.
You two are my first friends.
Hey, you guys are awake.
You certainly got enough sleep.
You've been out
for almost an entire week.
[Jin] We have?
I could eat a horse.
Can you get us some food?
[loud burp]
Catch ya later.
Until we meet again.
[Fuu] Uh, guys, there's
something I haven't told you...
Huh?
Such as...?
You remember back
when we started this trip
we made a little bet.
We'll decide this
by tossing this coin.
If it's heads,
you fight each other.
But if it's tails,
you forget about the fight
and you both come with me.
Are we clear on this?
Tails!
The thing is,
it actually came up heads!
[Mugen] Say what?
[Jin] You're kidding me.
[Fuu] That's all.
The whole thing was a trick.
Why'd we even
make this trip, you remember?
Later guys, see ya round.
♪ End Theme ♪