♪ Opening Theme ♪
[Uhori] When one reflects
on the past,
regardless of culture,
it is during periods
of idleness that
fashion is cultivated and born.
Yes, even the
threadbare casual style
was born here
in the Edo period.
And designs resembling
what is currently known
as "street fashion"
had already arrived
on the scene.
[clock chiming]
[faraway dog barking]
[Fuu] Hmmm.
Right. I think I'll try cheese
mochi and cod roe in mine.
[Shopkeep] Comin' right up.
[Jin] Okonomiyaki isn't
the same as monjayaki.
For crying out loud,
loosen up a little.
So, what are
you guys gonna order?
Seafood style, with oysters.
[Shopkeep] You got it.
How 'bout you?
[Mugen] Hmm.
Same as this guy.
Comin' right up.
Whenever we go out,
you always get the same thing
as either Jin or me,
but you can order whatever
you want off the menu, you know.
[Mugen] I don't got much choice.
It's all written
right there on the menu.
I have a little trouble
understandin' it okay?
Now let me get this straight,
are you saying you can't read?
This one here is "no".
So's this one
and this one, too.
So you see,
I can read just fine.
[Fuu] What's this one, then?
"No" I guess.
[Jin] It's "me".
Damn, you little bitch,
that was a trick question.
Are you serious?
You can only read
one letter, that's it?
One's more than enough
as far as I'm concerned.
You know, now that
I think about it,
since I've known you, I've
never seen you read anything.
I get by just fine
without bein' able to read.
Don't you think
it's amazing that
in all the time we've
been traveling together,
we never noticed
that he can't read?
[Jin] Hmph.
Oh yeah, real funny,
keep laughing.
And besides,
you don't gotta be able to read
in order to kill people.
[bottle crashing]
[Bundai]
What the hell kinda crap
are you spoutin'
over here, boy?
It's okay for a fool
to stay a fool, huh?
Don't give me any
of that pathetic garbage.
Listen, every single word
contains its own soul.
If you don't know the letters
that communicate that soul,
you're the one
who loses out.
When you're illiterate,
you're automatically
branded as an idiot.
Don't that piss you off, boy?
Well, don't it?
Are you okay
with being an idiot?
Answer the question!
[snoring]
Guess he passed out.
[record scratching]
[Fuu] Let's see,
how much do we owe?
We can't pay that!
[Mugen] Put it on
my friend here's tab, okay?
[Shopkeep] Come again.
[Fuu] Yeah, but what if-
[Mugen] Don't sweat it.
Call it a disturbance fee.
[Jin] Let's go.
[Fuu] Sorry, Mister.
C'mon, Mister,
up and at 'em. Let's go.
Time for you to settle up.
Altogether it comes
to thirteen shu.
What the hell's goin' on?
[Old Woman 1]
I'm getting sick and tired
of painting this wall
over and over.
It seems like they
get cockier every day.
Ah... I beg your pardon, ladies,
but do you know the
person who painted this?
Of course we don't!
If we did, we would've had 'em
arrested a long time ago!
[Uhori] I see.
[Jin] I'm sorry, but there's
someone in Mihara to whom
I am indebted, and I'd like to
stop by and pay my respects.
Huh?
Mihara's quite a ways
away from here, isn't it?
Who'd be worth
going that far to see?
An old girlfriend, maybe?
For anyone who aspires
to the martial arts,
Mihara is a town
which cannot be passed by.
Gojuu Hall is the finest dojo
in which to study
general weapons mastery.
Under the tutelage of
Master Jyunosuke Niwa, I once-
Fine, go have fun.
And as long as you're there,
make sure you ask him
if he knows anything
about the
sunflower samurai. Okay?
Mugen, tell me the truth.
You really wanna learn
how to read, don't you?
[Mugen] Just drop it, okay.
Hey, come on, I'm serious.
I can teach you how.
Let's see. That's a "sa". That's
an "n". And that's "jou".
"Sanjou" means
"was here." Got it?
[Bundai] That's the bastard...
who stiffed me with his bill.
Hmm.
I wonder what "4649" means.
I get it! "Yoroshiku" --
"nice to meet you"! You see?
Huh?
[Guys talking, laughing]
Jest who the hell are you?
[Member 2] What do you think
you're doing, hanging out here?
[Member 1] I hate to
break this to ya, pal,
but this is our turf
you're loitering on.
Listen, Pops,
I think we're gonna collect
a little relaxation fee
from you.
He's tellin' you
to hand over your money.
[both]
No, stay away!
This is a place
for those who strive
to master the martial arts.
This is not a place
for the likes of you
to be loitering about.
[Member 2] Uh, sorry,
Mister, but the thing is,
this is where we hang out.
Where might I find Master Niwa?
Niwa?
Daw, geez, if you're
talkin' about the bosses,
I think they're both
in town right now.
What?
[squeaking]
[Fuu] Darn that Mugen.
How does he manage
to disappear into thin air?
[Guys shouting]
I'm the boss, jerkoff.
No way, I'm the boss.
Huh? You pig,
is that how you show respect
towards your elder brother?
Yeah right, you were only born
one stinkin' minute before me,
so don't go pullin' that
older brother crap.
You think some freakin'
nimrod who can't even keep
junior and senior
ranking straight
is cut out to be the boss, huh?
You think this is some
procession of feudal lords?
Thinking like that is so lame.
Just lookin' at that hideous
face of yours pisses me off.
For once I agree, you took
the words right of my mouth.
What do they mean? Both of
their faces are identical.
Huh? Who was it that said that?
♪ funk music ♪
[Momo hissing]
[both]
Hottie...
Stop copyin' what I say.
You're the one who's copyin' me!
Those big brown eyes are so hot!
You're wrong again, you putz,
it's that sexy
little mouth of hers.
Oh? Goodness.
That voice is so sweet
like silver bells.
Idiot.
It's the way her nose
is turned up just a little bit,
like a cute little honey bunny.
Take it easy.
This one's mine, Bro.
[Jin] It's been a long time.
Tatsunoshin. Kazunosuke.
Can't be!
Jin, is it you?
You know these two?
[Mugen] That hurt!
Who the hell
do you think you are?
My name is Bundai.
This is a school.
While you're here,
address me as Sensei!
Oh, so you're a teacher, huh?
Yeah, you could keep trying
to solve your problems by force,
like you do now.
But the world
will keep on turning.
You can't build a castle if
all you've got is carpenters.
What you need is a wood plane.
Even if you've got the wood
plane, if it isn't kept sharp,
you'll get hurt.
First you sharpen your plane,
'cause when you start,
that's the first tool you use.
Now take your seat boy.
Startin' right now,
I'm gonna teach you how to read.
Huh?
I'd think that it would
piss you off to have
your companions always
mock you like that!
[Fuu laughing]
Are you kidding me?
You can't read?
[Fuu and Jin laughing]
Alright, dammit, you're on!
[Jin] Why do you quarrel
with one another?
As brothers, would you
not be better served
by helping each other
and mastering the path
your father laid down for you?
Hey, what do you
expect? Nobody follows
in their father's
footsteps these days.
It's not cool.
When someone offs themselves,
they screw over
the ones left behind.
Besides, the way
he dresses scares people.
Come back and say that
again after you wash
that butt-ugly face of yours.
You got somethin' to say?
You want some of this, pinhead?
[sighing] That's enough.
As the true heirs of Gojuu Hall,
settle this with swords.
[both]
We don't know how.
[Jin sighing]
Alright then, what would
you substitute for swords,
so that you two
can settle this?
I guess, uh...
Yeah, definitely that.
[Jin] Graffiti.
[Kazunosuke] Hey, it's not
what you think, bro.
It might look like
ordinary graffiti to you,
but we devoted our lives to it.
See, it's really
no different from the way
the old man
devoted himself to the sword.
It's called tagging,
and we do it because
it proves that we're alive,
and we make a difference.
[Tatsunoshin] No, that ain't it.
We try to push the limits and
tag the most dangerous places...
places nobody else ever
tagged before, you know?
The only time
we is really alive
is when we
experience that thrill.
They're saying pretty much
the same thing.
Here's an idea,
maybe you should duel each other
doing this graffiti thing.
[both]
How do we do that?
You could say
that whoever writes
in the most dangerous place
without getting caught
is the winner.
And the prize would be...
Oh, goodness boys,
whatever shall I do.
[both] Bro, please, you gotta do
this. You gotta be the judge.
What's this one?
Hmm, that's "re".
You dumbass!
This one right here is "ne".
The way you can always tell
that it's "ne" is that
it's got this loop on the end,
not the one with a swoop!
The one that's got
the swoop is the "re".
How many times do I
gotta explain it to ya?
This sucks!
What's wrong with
my little kindergartner?
Are you givin' up that easy?
Well? Are ya wussin' out?
They look the same, all these
damned letters piss me off!
If you got any complaints,
I listen to 'em
after you pass these drills.
[Fuu] This is kinda unusual
for you isn't it,
acting as a mediator
all of a sudden.
I mean, this is just
a simple squabble
between brothers, isn't it?
Their father was a man
I'm indebted to.
He once asked
something of me--
[Jyunosuke] There is now nothing
more that I can teach you,
my student.
Return to your master,
and walk your path
with your head held high.
[Jin] Yessir.
I've a favor to ask of you.
If anything should
ever happen to me,
I'd like you to look
after my sons.
[children laughing]
[Tatsunoshin] C'mon Kazu.
[Kazunosuke] Wait up, Tatsu.
You're it!
[Bonze] Well, this is
a pleasant surprise.
I don't suppose
you remember who I am?
It has been
far too many years, Priest.
I see that you've grown
into a fine young man.
Not at all.
Those are beautiful
flowers you've placed there.
Just some wild
chrysanthemums I found.
The thought is more important
than the flowers themselves.
I'm sure that as we speak,
Master Niwa is smiling
from beyond the grave.
[Jin] What happened to him?
[Bonze] Of all the earthly
emotions of men,
jealousy may be
the most powerful.
There was no dojo in the area
that surpassed Gojuu Hall.
The masters of the other dojos
curried favor
with the local lord
and made false accusations
against Master Niwa.
He was ordered to either
close his doors and take down
his sign or
cut off his own arm.
And so, in order to leave
the dojo to his sons,
Master Niwa felt
he had no other choice
than to commit ritual suicide.
But his sons proved they were
unworthy of this sacrifice,
for they were unable
to appreciate
their father's strength
and learn from his example.
And their behavior
forever dishonors his memory.
[clock chiming]
[labored breathing]
[Mugen] Be, Ne, No, Me, A, O!
All answers are correct!
Hell yeah.
What else did you expect?
Now use those letters
to write your story.
Write it bigger than
anybody else. Got it?
Bet 'cher ass.
Hey, where the heck
have you been?
[Mugen] Eh, here and there.
Geez, Mugen, we've got
a serious situation going on.
There are these two guys,
vying for my attention.
They're fighting over me now.
[Mugen] Yeah,
sounds rough alright.
Um, uh... Oh! I think they
called it "shagging".
What it is is a life or death
struggle using letters.
D'you say letters?
♪ drum beat ♪
[Police whistle]
[Police] Stop! Police!
Dammit.
Police!
Stop in the name of the law!
What the hell is this?
[Priest] This is horrible!
Somebody help!
[screaming hysterically]
[Uhori] The reds.
The blues. How lovely!
[Tatsunoshin] Haha,
I beat your ass.
[Kazunosuke] In your dreams!
[Tatsunoshin] No,
in your dreams!
We'll never settle it this way.
You probably already
thought of this,
but is there any place
you haven't put graffiti?
[Tatsunoshin] I guess uh,
[Kazunosuke] Yeah, there's one.
[both]
Hiroshima Castle.
♪ rap music ♪
[Police] Hold it!
[Police] Come along peacefully.
You know, I don't get it.
Why do you suppose
they picked Hiroshima Castle?
They're getting revenge
in their own way.
Revenge against the lord
that their father
was never able to get.
It's wrong,
they should be ashamed.
You can say that again.
What's wrong with them?
The kids these days
have no respect--
Dammit, you're writing it wrong!
This is magnificent.
Just what I've
been searching for.
[Kazunosuke] Who
the hell is that?
[Tatsunoshin] Come back here!
[Mugen] I'm number one!
So you guys,
who finally won the duel?
Neither of us won.
Some other guy beat us to it.
We got beat by
some mystery tagger.
It's a great big world
out there,
and there's always gonna
be somebody better than you.
What's important is that
you learned that lesson.
Then I guess
nobody wins me either.
[both]
Let us cop a quick feel.
[Fuu] Hey, no!
[squeaking]
Hehe! Woah... Dude,
she's so cute.
[both giggling]
Oh, awesome, look at her
cute little eyes.
She's so soft.
What's up with that?
[Uhori] I recognize your talent
for what it is.
Am I to assume that
you handsome young men
are the taggers that
have this town in a tizzy?
[Tatsunoshin]
That all depends...
[Kazunosuke] Who are you people?
[Uhori] Oh, how delightful!
My darlings, I'm going
to make you famous.
You boys have the potential
to become designers
who will breathe fresh air
into this stagnant industry.
I can feel it in my bones.
[Fuu] So, who are you?
[Uhori] Only the
textiles merchant who
is known to all in Ura-Edo.
I am Uhori, of the Ando store.
A pleasure.
Huh?
[Bundai] Nothin' doin'.
There's something you two need
to take care of, first.
Your grammar stinks. You've
been writin' everything wrong.
[both]
Aww, teach.
[Bundai] You're gonna hit
the books first!
Ya got it?
[Tatsunoshin] You serious?
[Uhori] Come back!
[record scratching]
[Fuu screaming]
What is it? What's wrong?
This one, too.
And this one over here.
What the heck's going on?
[Fuu] Hey you jerk!
You wanna explain this?
[Mugen] You gotta write your
name on your stuff, you know?
And that symbol there?
Mugen. It means infinite.
I made it myself.
Don't tell me,
that man yesterday...
[Uhori] Later, when the two
young men traveled to Edo,
they blew a breath of fresh air
into the fashion world.
Their stunning designs
spread from Ura-Edo Avenue
all across the country.
People call these two
gorgeous young men
"The Embodiment of Graffiti."
♪ End Theme ♪