♪ Opening Theme ♪
[cricket chirping]
[footsteps approaching]
[Ryujiro] Like they say,
you gotta fight fire with fire.
But Oniwakamaru is awaiting
execution. He's dangerous,
and if he's let out, there's
no telling what he might do.
[shrieking]
[Ryujiro] My missing arm
is whispering to me.
It's whispering, "You gotta
kill those bastards for me."
[metal clanking]
[door creaking open]
Good to see you, Oniwakamaru.
I admire that
fierce face of yours.
A face more beastly
than that of an animal.
You and I are two of a kind,
Oniwakamaru.
Fact is, we're so alike
we could be brothers.
So let's go take 'em out.
You and me.
Let's annihilate all
the people who tormented you.
[cricket chirping]
[bird cawing]
[Fuu] Alright,
is everybody ready?
Remember, no holding back.
Pull out everything you've got.
Even your secret stash.
One, two...
Are you kidding? That's it?!
Hey, dude, you sure
you're not holding out on us?
Look who's talking.
What's with the acorns?
Alright, that's enough.
You two made me a promise.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
Until we find the samurai
who smells of sunflowers,
you two are not allowed
to kill each other.
Oh, yeah, the smelly guy.
I've been meaning
to ask you about that.
Huh?
Who is this samurai
who smells of sunflowers?
Well, he--
What the hell
is a sunflower anyway?
Wait a minute.
You don't know?
It's a flower.
So what do they
smell like?
Do you have
any other leads?
A picture
or somethin'?
What makes you think
he's around here?
Oh, stop!
[stomach grumbling]
For right now,
let's get something to eat.
[bird cawing]
[Fuu] Ta-da! Yakimanjuu.
A Joushuu specialty.
The question is:
how many do we each get
if we split these
between the three of us?
[Mugen] I'll kill you two
and eat them all myself.
Hey! What's with you anyway?
[bird cawing]
[Fuu yelling]
Hey, come back here!
--[Mugen] That damn thief
--[Fuu] Come back here.
--just jacked my grub.
--Give me back my manjuu.
It's called a filcher bird,
and now you know why.
[Farmer 1] What are you saying?
You mean to tell me
that those missing people
were attacked by
some kind of ogre?
[Farmer 2] Yeah. At least
that's what the rumors say.
Good heavens,
what a horrible story.
Wait a minute.
You're a samurai, aren't you?
So, you're the one
who can kill that ogre for us.
Yeah, that's right.
What? Oh, no. Not me.
I couldn't possibly.
[Inuyama screaming] You mustn't
sneak up on me like that.
[laughing] I guess there are
cowardly samurais after all.
Now listen.
If those rumors are true,
then right now
those people are--
[Mugen]
Probably being eaten alive.
Hey, my dumplings.
[Mugen]
I heard you guys talking.
An evil ogre, huh?
You want me to kill it for you?
[awed exclaiming]
[Farmer 1]
That sure was amazing.
You're a real expert, sonny.
Bet you were a student at some
big name dojo. Am I right?
Yeah. Something like that.
[Fuu] So! What's this
ogre killing business?
You think you're
some kind of legendary hero?
Listen, you're going to keep
that promise you
made me, understand?
Now calm down.
Don't get angry.
Come join us. Have a seat.
I hate to say it, but I've
got to admit, I'm jealous.
Of self-confident people,
I mean.
You see, a guy like me
is samurai in name only.
That's good.
What kind of water is this?
Wow. A real drinker, huh?
[Fuu moaning]
Guess not.
Young man, you don't plan to go
through the
mountains today, do you?
Yeah. So what?
I wouldn't if I were you,
not at this hour.
The sun's about to go down.
Perhaps, but we have
no money to pay for lodging.
I see. Well in that case, I know
the perfect place for you.
There's a small, unoccupied
shack near the hot springs
just up the road where
you can stay free of charge.
So why not spend the night there
and start your journey
tomorrow morning?
[wood creaking,
Fuu snoring softly]
[Mugen] Look at the dumb broad.
She's out cold.
Let's strip her and dump her.
That innkeeper back there...
Eh?
Forget it.
It's probably nothing.
Huh?
[wood creaking]
[quiet clacking]
[Ryujiro] Good work.
You followed
my instructions perfectly.
Of course, Sir.
Well I'll be running along now.
[Ryujiro] Oh, I forgot
to mention one thing...
...Just to be safe,
I'm afraid, I gotta kill you.
[gasping]
Thanks very much.
That sure helped a lot.
[Mugen] Who said
I did it for free?
Huh?
What do you want?
What do you got?
[wood creaking]
Later. I gotta go
take care of something.
[Jin] That woman, huh?
Why'd you invite me?
My goodness,
what a silly question.
When a woman invites
a man to her home
and they're all by themselves,
there aren't that many things
they can do, are there?
Damn lady,
you move quick, don't you?
[Hotaru] I'm not interested
in playing the coy maiden.
Let's enjoy ourselves tonight.
Nights are like the lives of
human beings, all too brief.
[wood creaking, Fuu snoring]
Hey there.
[gasping]
I think you should
go back to sleep for a while.
[Fuu grunts]
[sloshing water,
crickets chirping]
[Inuyama] Evening.
Isn't this a nice surprise?
[Jin] You're the man
from the teahouse.
[Inuyama]
Beautiful, aren't they?
Do you know why
fireflies glow like that?
It's a form of communication.
Signals sent by the males and
females to attract one another.
However, they say
that every once in a while
a male will try
to attract another male.
Time to go.
[Inuyama] Oh, that reminds me.
I realize now
that I have heard of him.
You know, the sunflower samurai
that the young lady spoke of?
[Saruhashi] Ryujiro Sasaki!
Kanto region police.
Ryujiro Sasaki,
you're under arrest for arson,
malicious destruction,
and the cold-blooded murder
of a treasury employee.
Now come along quietly.
Well, now.
And here I thought I got away.
Be careful, Oniwaka. They want
to pick on you like the others.
[gasping]
Who the hell is that?
It doesn't matter who he is.
We'll take him down too.
Right now. You big, ugly freak.
[gasping]
[fearful gasping]
[screaming]
[laughing]
Stay away.
Stay away you damn monster!
[screaming]
[dying wail]
[Oniwakamaru] Don't be afraid.
Huh?
[Oniwakamaru] Everyone is afraid
of my face. They say it is ugly.
They hate me.
They call me a monster.
But if I do like this,
they cannot see my face.
[wood creaking]
No. Don't look at me.
You're not scary,
but you do seem
to have an awfully sad
look in your eye.
[crowd yelling, jeering]
[Oniwakamaru]
They called me a monster.
I thought they were
going to kill me.
I... I got angry.
I couldn't control myself.
I... I killed many people.
I am all alone.
A firefly.
[wood creaking]
It's all set.
I sent him his invitation.
Okay, Oniwaka,
let's get ready for the party.
[surprised grunting]
[Hotaru gasping]
[spitting]
What the hell did you just
force me to swallow you bitch?
[Hotaru chuckling]
Do you feel anything yet?
It was a one-night mushroom.
Ordinarily,
it's harmless enough,
but combined with sake
it's a deadly poison.
[gasping]
Who the hell you workin' for?
Better start talking quick
'cause I might just
slice you up by mistake.
A one-armed man
gave me the mushrooms
and told me what to do.
He's got the antidote and
something else
you want even more.
What?
That girl
you were traveling with.
I wonder what he'll do to her.
Shit.
[Jin] How much farther?
[Inuyama] We're almost there.
[breathing heavily]
Damn it.
[Inuyama sighing]
I neglected to mention this
earlier, but I am an assassin.
Yes, I already know that.
I'd like you to know
I've enjoyed your company
and bear you no ill will.
For me, killing is merely a
business. It's nothing personal.
[breathing heavily]
Son of a...
Huh?
Who hired you?
Well, it's getting late. Perhaps
we should get started, huh?
♪ hip hop music ♪
[laughing] My, oh my,
the rumors were true.
You're quite good.
It's been a while since I faced
a master swordsman like you.
Guess I'll be doing
some ogre slaying after all.
[Mugen] You bastard.
[Fuu] Mugen!
[Ryujiro] So you finally turned
up, huh? I figured you would.
Now I'm gonna make you pay
for cuttin' off my arm.
Say what?
You know what I'm talking about.
You're the one. And don't try
telling me you don't remember.
Sorry dude, but who are you?
[Ryujiro inhaling] Bastard!
Ah, I see. I've got to admit,
you're much better
than I expected.
In fact, if we were in a dojo,
I might not be able to beat you.
However...
Is there something wrong?
It isn't the same
as fighting in a dojo is it?
[Oniwakamaru yelling]
[Mugen] This sucks.
My arms are like wet noodles.
Mugen.
[Ryujiro] What's wrong?
The poison you swallowed
finally starting to kick in?
You wanna live?
Got the antidote right here.
Know why they're called
one-night mushrooms?
Because before you die,
you spend the whole night
in unbearable agony.
So by this time tomorrow,
you won't be around anymore.
[Ryujiro laughing]
[Mugen yelling]
[Oniwakamaru panting]
I am ugly.
Don't look at me. AAARGH!
[Mugen] Huh?
Mugen!
[Oniwakamaru crying]
[Ryujiro] Not yet, Oniwaka.
Don't kill him just yet.
That son of a bitch
is gonna die nice and slow.
[Inuyama] I haven't
enjoyed myself this much
in quite some time.
Nevertheless, I'd like to be
as efficient as possible, which
means never working overtime.
It's been fun, but I'm going to
end this now if you don't mind.
[cloth tearing]
How do you like that?
Can't breathe, can you?
But I won't let you die yet. You
haven't suffered nearly enough.
Now you're gonna
suffer some more.
[Fuu grunting, Ryujiro yelling]
Now it's your turn bitch.
[Fuu gasping]
Even better...
I'll make him suffer more
by killing you first.
And you call yourself
a human being?
Huh?
[Ryujiro laughing]
Whatever gave you that idea?
Young lady, I gave up
my humanity long, long ago.
I like to watch human suffering.
Now that's what I call fun.
I'm really a very generous man.
I want to share my suffering
with everyone else.
I'd say that's fair,
wouldn't you?
So, now you know why
you're gonna die.
[gagging]
Oniwaka... what are you...
[choking]
[bones breaking]
[Oniwakamaru roaring]
No, don't!
Don't do it!
[crickets churping]
Oh, dear.
[Inuyama sighing]
[Inuyama] What an odd
turn of events.
It appears that my client
has just been dispatched.
[Jin] What?
In other words,
now I have absolutely
no reason to kill you.
Clearly there's no point
in killing someone
if I'm not going to make
any money by doing so.
Well, I'm off.
[Inuyama] I expect that
someday, somewhere,
you and I will meet again.
In fact, I'm sure we will.
[Fuu] Why? Why did you
protect me? Tell me why.
You were the only one not
afraid to look at my face.
Now I am not alone anymore.
♪ End Theme ♪