♪ Opening Theme ♪
[Man 1] Mr. Yamane.
So this is where
you've been hiding then, huh?
You know,
I can't believe this'll be
Yamane the Ogre's last day.
We're gonna miss ya.
I'll just be
another old man tomorrow.
Guess the rest of my days
will be spent waiting to die.
[Man 1] You're leaving behind
quite a legacy, though.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but in the thirty years
that you've been here, you
haven't let a single person
slip through that
checkpoint, have you?
Do you intend to keep
sitting on your butt all day?
Now go on and get back
to your post, before I-
[Man 1] There,
that's the scary look.
I'll see ya later.
[Old Yamane] I've gone from
a young soldier to an old man
in the thirty years I've spent
guarding the Hakone checkpoint.
But even here,
at what's known as
the toughest border
crossing around,
there was one day
when things went awry.
I still remember
as if it were yesterday.
It's the only instance that was
not recorded in my log book.
On that one day, everyone
was allowed to come and go
through here as they pleased.
Thieves and criminals alike.
People shouted
at the top of their lungs,
beat drums, and danced.
On that one day, people
completely let themselves go.
But, that day was over
thirty years ago.
[film skipping,
record scratching]
[Mugen] A travel permit?
What the hell's that?
[Fuu] You never heard
of a travel permit?
I'm surprised you got
into Edo without one.
[Fuu] They won't let you
through the checkpoint
without a travel permit.
You have one, right, Jin?
I did, of course.
But...
But?
I lost it.
Losers.
[Mugen] Hey, don't sweat it.
If they stop us
at the checkpoint,
we'll just take 'em all out.
The punishment for breaking
a checkpoint is death.
And Hakone is rather
well known for being
a particularly difficult
crossing point,
especially for
women leaving Edo.
Huh?
What do we do then?
[Scalper] Hey there,
friend. If you're looking
for travel permits,
I got 'em right here.
That's right, if it's
travel permits you need,
gem 'em right here.
You've got permits?
You mean for the checkpoint?
That's right.
Really?
And if you buy 'em right now,
I'll throw in
these good luck charms.
One helluva deal.
[record scratching]
Arrest them!
Huh?
[Fuu] Hey, what's going on?
[Mugen] What's your problem,
man? We got permits!
These documents here
are blatant forgeries.
Did you think you'd be able
to get through the Hakone
checkpoint with these?
That scalper is so goin' down.
Take 'em away.
[Old Yamane]
That was the first time
that I ever laid eyes on them.
I was just
a lowly footman back then,
still wet behind the ears
as a government official.
I remember that
look in his eyes.
He was like a stray dog that
had long ago broken his leash.
Aah!
Let's go. All of your clothes
have to come off.
Do we have to do this?
Isn't being arrested bad enough?
[Official] How do we
know you're not hiding
contraband somewhere in there?
You think you can just-
[Official] You know in addition
to a strip search,
we can also perform
a more detailed inspection.
[Kinugasa] When you get a
moment, take a look over there
at the new company
you'll be keeping.
[Young Yamane]
That's Kinugasa,
the top official here
at the checkpoint.
He's your textbook
government lap dog,
totally rotten to the core.
But, because his parents
have a lot of clout in Edo,
no one dares
complain about him.
That was cold, dude.
With that attitude,
I'm gonna have a hard time
wanting to play nice and
pretend I didn't see you.
What, you kiddin' me?
Hold on a second,
what's going on?
[Kinugasa] Hey, which one of you
guys has a bounty on your head?
Come on, speak up.
[Young Yamane]
Once in a while this happens.
Someone we've caught
sneaking through
will end up having
a criminal record.
If it was a violent crime, we're
not supposed to execute him,
but instead escort him
back to the place
that issued the warrant.
That's why we're
always supposed to do
a thorough
background check before
we publicly execute anyone.
But my boss...
He enjoys killing
people far too much
to be bothered
by something as trivial as that.
Whoa, bingo.
Aww, dammit,
we killed this guy already.
Now what the hell
am I gonna do, huh?
Man, this really blows.
I gotta find some way
to make this look good.
Excuse me, Sir?
Whatever it is,
you should ask me later,
cause I'm pissed off right now.
I've got an idea.
Huh?
[whispering]
That's not bad. That could work.
Bring me those two guys,
along with that bird
who came in with 'em.
[record scratching]
[Kinugasa] So you happen
to be given some forgeries,
and not knowing
they were fakes,
you tried to pass
through the checkpoint.
Public execution
for this offense
might be a little too drastic.
That said, I just may be willing
to spare your lives this time.
But, there is
one small condition.
[Kinugasa] I want this head
delivered before the day is up.
[record scratching]
You got it? These two
stay here as hostages.
If you complete your task
and make it back by sunset,
and if I'm feeling generous,
I just might let you three
pass through the checkpoint.
But if you're not back in time,
then both of your little friends
here are as good as dead.
You're totally clear on this...
You're not confused
by anything he just said?
Yeah, sure. No problem.
Back before sundown, okay?
[Mugen] Hey, what's this stuff
about tengu in the mountains?
Supposedly,
they're grotesque people
too horrible to even look at.
They're able to strike
as fast as lightning.
There's not a person alive
who's seen them
and lived to talk
about it later.
No one goes anywhere
near that mountain these days.
Not even postmen
and foot soldiers will go.
[Mugen] See ya.
[yelling] You're sure
you're clear on this?
[Kinugasa] Hey,
what are you waitin' for?
Watch him.
I don't want him takin' off.
Um.
You don't think
he would run away, do you?
[Jin] Hmm.
♪ funk beat ♪
They're tailin' me.
The hell are you, Buddy?
Oh, are you referring to me?
I'm just out for
a little jog today,
trying to keep myself healthy.
Son of a bitch.
[Mugen yelling] Don't
confuse me like that.
[Young Yamane]
Being assigned to follow him
wasn't part of my plan.
I guess it goes to show
that even stupid officials
are smart enough to know
when to cover their ass.
[steel clicking]
♪ funk beat ♪
This time I know
they're tailin' me.
[Mugen thinking] Alright,
you tengu bastards.
Just try and catch me.
Huh?
Where am I?
[Fuu] Hey, you don't think that
he got lost or anything, do you?
[Jin] Hmm.
What in the hell is this?
[Mugen screaming, crashing]
[strange laughing]
[Mugen] That really hurt a lot.
[laughing continues]
You don't think he got captured
by the tengu, do you?
[Jin] Hmm.
[breathing heavily]
[Young Yamane]
Where... did he go?
[distant drums beating]
[drums getting louder]
[Young Yamane thinking]
Tengu.
No, they're...
they're warrior priests.
So that's who
the tengu really are.
The warrior priests
are relics of the past,
when there was
famine and uprisings.
Everyone thought that
since we'd been at peace
they'd disappeared into
the shadows of history.
I can't believe
they still exist.
[men roaring]
Hear me.
There are two kinds of dogs
that exist in this world.
There are stray dogs and those
who choose to be lap dogs.
Never knowing where
their next meal will come from,
stray dogs wander alone in the
rain in exchange for freedom.
Lap dogs are kept on
a short leash,
and for one measly bone a day,
content with defeat.
Now tell me
what kind of dog are you?
[men roaring]
[Aohabu] That's right.
Ignorant, overindulgent samurai
lead our country today.
The only thing that
is of interest to them
is the path to achieve power
and the ability to maintain it.
At their heels,
always doing what they're told,
never questioning their masters,
are their lap dogs.
And so, we refuse
to recognize this government.
We will pry this country
out of the hands of those
who have stained it:
the greedy, sword waving fools,
good for nothing but murder.
[uproar]
The battle that we face today
will be the last
that will ever need
to be fought.
Through careful cultivation,
the grass that we have planted
in our fields has
grown plentiful,
and with this grass,
we will erase all hatred.
But be warned!
There are those who will try
to stop our revolution,
and to those people,
we will show no mercy.
Anyone who chooses to attack us
had better be prepared
to pay with their lives.
[uproar]
Once again,
we have captured one
of their lap dogs, today.
[cheering]
[Aohabu] You don't look like one
of the shogunates pets, though.
Who are you?
What's the matter?
You one of those
spineless cowards who can't talk
when he doesn't have
a sword by his side?
[Mugen] I didn't understand
a freakin' word
of that shit you're spewing.
Well, at least you've got
some spunk if nothing else.
[Mugen] But there's one thing
that I do understand.
I don't care how many
damned dogs you got,
it don't amount to jack
if they ain't tough enough
to bark when they're out alone.
[booing]
Well, now.
You're sure an interesting
puppy, aren't you?
Perhaps I'll do you
a favor and provide you
with a shortcut
on your path to hell.
Alright.
Tomorrow.
We're gonna have one hell
of an execution with this guy.
[cheering, drums beating]
We'll make sure that you get
buried with that head tomorrow,
so try to rest
peacefully until then.
[door closing, locking]
[Young Yamane] Everything in me
says that I should run away.
And yet...
I can't define it, but there's
something about that guy.
I can't get
the stray dog out of my mind.
[Young Yamane whispering]
Hey!
You alive? Hey!
[pow]
[crashing]
[Fuu] You don't think he's been
caught and now he's wrapped up
and bound in
a straw mat, do you?
[Jin] Hmm.
[Guard] We'll execute
the both of ya tomorrow.
So do me a favor, will ya?
Try to keep yourself
out of trouble.
[door closing, lock latching]
Uh, haven't I
seen you someplace?
Yeah, I'm an official
from the Hakone checkpoint.
[Mugen] What the hell
you doin' here?
[Young Yamane] Well, I been
following ya this whole time
to make sure you didn't escape.
[Mugen smirking]
Keep up the good work.
Yeah, tell me about it.
[Mugen] Who are
these guys anyway?
[Young Yamane] I think
they're warrior priests
from another time.
[Mugen] Warrior priests?
[Young Yamane] Yeah.
Back in the old days,
the priests within a temple
would take up arms
and fight for their people.
But now that we're
supposedly at peace,
nobody has much use
for them anymore.
These guys, however,
don't seem to realize that.
Apparently, they've decided
they can fix the whole country.
[Mugen] What a bunch
of stupid morons.
Without a doubt.
[limbs cracking]
Huh?
You're pretty
flexible there ain't ya?
[Young Yamane]
Just a little trick I can do.
[limbs cracking]
[Young Yamane]
I'll need to borrow this.
[Mugen] Huh?
Hey, what do you think
you're doin' with that?
Hey!
Sorry, but it'll be
your head or ours.
Nanmaida.
--[Young Yamane] Fire! Fire!
--[Guard 2] Hmm?
[Young Yamane]
We're gonna be burned alive!
[Guard 2] Huh? He's serious!
[lock unlatching]
[men screaming]
What's going on?
[Guard 3] There's a fire
in the storage room.
If we don't do something quick,
it's gonna spread!
What?
[men] There's a fire!
Fire! Fire!
[men yelling]
Guess the idea of
waiting for tomorrow
didn't sit well with ya.
That's alright,
we can be accommodating.
We'll reschedule the execution
and kill you both now.
Yo, hit the deck.
[men roaring]
[Aohabu] What the-
[Guard 5]
Dammit, where are they?
[Aohabu] Find them!
[Guard 6] Do you see them?
[men] No! The field!
The field is on fire!
Our crops!
Our revolution!
You bastards.
Take a look at what's
happening to our grass.
Do you realize what you've done?
[voice getting pitchy] Our
holy grass has been destroyed
by your recklessness.
And now you'll pay for it.
[clock tolling]
Sunset will be over any moment.
So, he ran away.
He wouldn't do that.
Hey, just wait
a little bit, maybe...
maybe he's just over
the horizon. Right?
[Kinugasa] Know what I think?
I think it's time for you
to say your prayers.
Look! Someone's coming.
[Fuu] Mugen. I knew it.
I knew you'd come.
Who are you?
Oh, are you referring to me?
I'm just out for
a little jog today,
trying to keep myself healthy.
[Fuu grumbling]
So, without further ado,
it's execution time.
Aww, come on.
If you come back
to haunt someone,
you may want to consider
haunting your friend.
[uncontrolably laughing]
[Old Yamane] Yes, on that
night, everyone cut loose
and loved one another.
The gates of the checkpoint
were thrown open, and
everyone became equals:
government officials, thieves,
even garden variety bullfrogs.
All of us danced until dawn.
A revolution did
indeed take place.
But just for that one night.
[record scratching]
[Fuu] So what do you think
happened back there anyway?
[Jin] We should be grateful that
in the confusion we were able
to cross the checkpoint.
[Fuu] Can you believe Mugen?
Not only did he not
come back by sundown,
but it's morning
and he still hasn't shown up.
[crazed laughing]
Man, what a great party!
But all our work,
just went up in smoke!
It's all good buddy,
it's all good.
Yeah.
[Fuu screaming] You jackass!
[Old Yamane] Everyone danced,
like they were caught
in a trance. Then,
like the morning mist,
the whole affair vanished and
was just as quickly forgotten.
But I still remember
that proud stray dog.
And sometimes,
I wonder if he remembers too.
Does he recall
that summer of love?
That night he ran and danced
deep within that
electric purple haze?
[film skipping,
record scratching]
Gotcha.
♪ End Theme ♪