♪ Opening Theme ♪
[crowd cheers]
[Manzou]
It's well known that
many Japanese baseball players
are enjoying successful careers
in the American
Major Leagues today.
However, even among
the most avid fans,
few are aware of
the following episode
which occurred in Japan during
the early days of baseball.
The following story is a tale
of men whose souls burn bright
with a passion for the sport.
[Manzou] My original reason
for coming to visit this place
was to investigate reports that
several of the locals had made.
A foreign ship had been
spotted just offshore.
Oh, and pardon the
belated introduction.
I'm known as Manzou the Saw.
I'm a member of
the secret police,
just transferred to
this area recently.
Huh?
Oh for Pete's sake!
[Fuu] Let's see. How much
farther do you think it is?
We came this way along
the Nagasaki highway, so...
We'll reach Saga soon
and Ikitsuki Island
shortly after that.
[Shopkeep]
Here you are!
[Fuu] Huh?
I'm sorry, there's
been a mistake.
We didn't order all this.
[Mugen] Don't worry about it.
I ordered for us.
How exactly do you
plan to pay for this?
Don't worry about it.
Do you have a secret
stash we don't know about?
I said not to worry.
Ah!
[Jin] Delicious.
[Fuu] Ah!
Hey wait for me you guys.
[Fuu]
Oh, that was so good.
I can't remember the last
time we ate like this.
Nor I, but I'm curious to know
exactly how you plan
to pay for this bill.
Like this.
Huh?
We got a runner!
[Shopkeep 2]
Hey! Come back here, dammit!
[Shopkeep 3]
Don't let him get away!
No way!
Son of a... That guy's fast!
[Kagemaru] Huh...?
[Mugen] Ow!
[Mugen]
Who threw this?!
[Kagemaru] Right here.
[Mugen] Arr... You!
[Mugen yells]
[Shopkeeps yell]
You're pretty good, Kid.
How 'bout it?
Feel like playin' some ball?
Ball?
[Kagemaru] Tell ya what,
there's a ball game
scheduled for tomorrow.
If you play in it,
I'd be willing to pay these
fellas what you owe 'em.
Or if you'd rather, you can work
your butts off here for a month
to pay it off yourselves.
You got us into this.
It's up to you to get us out.
If you had any brains, you guys
woulda made a break for it, too.
How were we supposed to know?
We can't waste a month here.
You're going to have to play.
So tell me,
what the hell is this ball
you keep talkin' about?
It's called baseball.
It's a sport from
across the sea.
Basically I throw
this little ball,
and you try to hit it
with this stick here.
It's called a bat.
You mean you talkin' about
a stupid stick game?
It's more than a game.
It's a battle.
And our country's future
is ridin' on the outcome.
Say what?
That's right.
You see this whole
crazy business
got started about a week ago.
[women yell]
♪ Stars and Stripes Forever ♪
Who the devil's in charge here?
Hello, where can we find
the person in charge?
[Machidoshiyori]
I suppose you're lookin'
for the Town Consul.
That would be me.
[Doubleday]
Allow me to introduce
Commodore Joey Cartright,
the commander of the
U.S. East Indies fleet.
I am Abner Doubleday,
his interpreter.
We're here for one reason:
to establish trade between this
country and the United States.
Well, demand whatever
you want. I can't help you.
An official edict
has been issued
that foreign ships
should be driven off.
It's out of my hands.
Huh? Fuck them!
I think you may have
misunderstood us.
We did not come all this way
just to make a request.
This is an order.
Make no mistake about it.
Unless of course your village
would prefer to go
to war against us.
Huh...?
[Cartright]
Whoa. A baseball.
Son of a gun, this is amazing.
Baseball on a tiny island
in the far east?
Incredible.
The sport of gentlemen comes
to the country of savages.
[laughter]
Alright, you're on.
Huh...?
[Kagemaru]
In this peaceful country,
there's no need for either of us
to throw our lives away in war.
What?
So how 'bout a baseball game?
So now you understand
how we got stuck
playin' a game against
those damned Yankees.
I don't get it.
What are they crazy?
I mean why would those Americans
wanna come all this way
just to do something like that?
What a bunch of troublemakers.
Don't you have
any other players?
[Kagemaru]
Well I did, but...
Alright, listen up.
This is gonna be one
seriously tough game.
And understand that
if we don't win,
there'll be no tomorrow
for any of us.
Have I made myself
clear, ya sons of--
Hey!
Look, if it's that tough,
I think I'll pass.
Seriously, count me out.
Sorry, but I've got
a few errands to run.
Hey, come back here!
So, they ran away, ending
our first and last practice.
Tell me the truth.
Are these Yankees really
the bad-asses you say they are?
You better believe it.
Well, in that case, I'll do it.
Great, give it your best shot.
[Kagemaru]
What are you talkin' about?
We don't need just one player.
If we wanna win,
we need all three of yas.
♪ marching music ♪
[Manzou] So they came all
the way to this little port
thinking they could
catch us by surprise.
[Subordinate]
What do you plan on doing?
I think we should report
this to Edo at once, Sir.
Hold your horses.
Before we do, I plan to
sneak aboard that ship.
But Sir, you can't.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
I'll cleverly disguise
myself as an American
and then slip onboard.
Yes, Sir.
[Fuu] You said your name
was Kagemaru, right?
I'm curious to know
how you learned about
this baseball stuff.
I'm a secret agent.
For generations I worked
for a certain feudal domain.
You're kidding.
So you were a ninja?
[Kagemaru] 'Fraid so.
You see, Kyushu has always
had a lotta dealings
with foreign countries.
So we been doing our research
on those countries
for generations.
But then the national isolation
policy went into effect
and our domain was
pretty much crushed.
[Fuu] Hmm...
[Manzou] And so they learned
the rules of the game.
In a single night, they
were given a crash course
in the art of baseball.
At this point, things
get rather boring,
so I'll skip the details.
Huh? Freeze!
Howdy.
[Soldier 1]
Who are you?
Who? Who-ho-ho.
[Soldier 2]
Who are you?
Oh, I'm an American.
Yankee Doodle.
Shut up!
[Manzou yells]
[Ichiemon]
Here it is,
the matchup of the
century is underway.
The national prestige of America
and Japan is on the line!
My name is Ichiemon,
announcing the play-by-play
for today's game.
Question: aren't we
a few players short?
That won't be a problem.
Don't worry about it.
[Soldier 1] Hey look.
They even let dogs
play baseball here?
Fantastic! That's the
mystical orient for ya.
[laughter]
What'd you just say?
Everyone here is
a full-fledged player.
I can't find dogs
in the rulebook.
It doesn't say they can't play.
Okay!
[Ichiemon]
It's the first pitch. Play ball!
Doubleday is on the mound,
and he lets it rip.
Bunt!
[Americans yell]
[coughing]
[Doubleday]
Ninja baseball...
[Ichiemon] The next
batter to step to the plate
is Jin.
Holy cow, he's using
a "gedan" sword stance.
Can he successfully apply
this technique to baseball?
He connects!
It's a shot to center field.
That was great, Jin! Heh, ha!
[Ichiemon]
Now Mugen steps to the plate
with no outs and runners
on first and second.
And this batter is using
a two-sword technique.
The pitcher goes into his
stretch, and--what's this?
They've decided to
intentionally walk him.
Huh?
Wow!
[splash]
[Mugen yells]
[Umpire]
You're out!
[Mugen] Huh?
[Ichiemon] Mugen makes a
critical base running error
and passes the runner
in front of him. He's out!
Geez!
[Ichiemon]
The next batter is Fuu,
the only female on the team.
Bring it on.
[Umpire] Strike.
Strike.
Strike 3, you're out!
Aww...
Three pitches and
she's out on strikes.
The next batter up is the
village consul, at age 80,
he's far and away the
oldest player on the team.
[Machidoshiyori yells]
[Fuu] Hey, Mister!
It's alright.
Step over my corpse and move
on to a brighter tomorrow.
You can't!
[ding]
[Ichiemon]
The next batter steps up.
The dog...?
[Fuu] Oh come on, there's no way
an animal can hit the ball.
Don't worry about it,
he won't have to hit the ball.
[Fuu] Huh?
[Umpire]
Ball. Ball. Ball.
[Ichiemon] The pitcher can't
seem to find the strike zone.
Exactly.
It's because the animal's strike
zone is incredibly small.
All he has to do is stand there
with the bat in his mouth
and he'll get walked.
[Ichiemon]
And here comes the fourth pitch.
[dog yelps]
Huh?
[Kagemaru]
He's runnin' away!
[Fuu] Momo!
[Kagemaru] Damn. What do
you expect from an animal?
[Manzou] Hmm...
What's going on here?
Why's a ball game being
held in secret like this?
Huh?
Who are you?
Maybe I'm a baseball
fan just passing by.
Although to be honest,
that's not the truth.
We're short on players,
so grab a bat.
Huh?!
[Ichiemon] A pinch hitter
has entered the game.
Looks like a baseball
fan who was passing by.
What's this?!
His first at-bat and
he's calling a homerun.
Who is this player?
Where did he come from?
[Kagemaru] Bunt.
Mm-Hmm.
[Ichiemon]
And Doubleday delivers.
[Manzou yells]
[Umpire] Strike.
[Kagemaru grunts]
[Kagemaru] Moron.
Wrong. Didn't you
understand me? I said bunt.
Bunt.
Mm-Hmm...
--[Ichiemon] And here comes
-- Bunt.
--the second pitch.
[Umpire] Strike 2.
Stupid son of a--
Moron. Dumbass. Bunt, dammit.
Bunt!
Or you're dead.
Mm-Hmm...
[Ichiemon]
The count's 0 and 2,
and the pitcher
goes into his windup,
trying to put him away.
Ahhh!
No!
[Ichiemon]
The Japanese team is hot today,
while the American
players take a time-out
for a conference on the mound.
Son of a bitch.
Freakin' Japs.
It's time for us to teach these
savages how we do things.
Take an eye for an eye.
Show 'em the American way.
All the way.
[Umpire]
Play ball!
Ball.
A-Ahh!
[Umpire] Ball.
Bastards.
So they gonna play dirty, huh?
[Kagemaru] Ahh!
Ahhhh!
[Soldier 4]
Here it comes.
[Manzou yells]
[Soldier 4] Amen.
[Manzou]
Hey, I'm still alive.
[Manzou yells]
Manzou is dead,
but freedom will never die.
[ding]
Cheaters.
Hey umpire!
Paid him off.
[Ichiemon] The pitcher sets,
and here comes the pitch to Jin.
Ha!
[Ichiemon]
Holy cow he's fast.
He's going for an inside
the park homerun!
Huh?
What the--?
[Jin groans]
I... am ashamed.
[ding]
[Umpire]
You're out!
That's three.
Side's retired. Batter up.
[wind blows]
[Mugen]
You stay outta this.
[Kagemaru]
Hold on. I ain't dead yet.
They're not gonna stop me
from takin' the mound,
and I ain't comin' down until
they're out or my arm falls off.
[Ichiemon]
It's the bottom of the inning,
and the American team
is coming up to bat,
but the Japanese team has
been decimated by injuries.
They're down to a pitcher
and a first baseman.
What in the world
do they hope to do?
[Mugen yells]
[Umpire]
You're out!
God damn...
[Ichiemon] The next batter
is Commodore Joey Cartright.
[Fuu]
Get out of the way! Watch out!
Come on.
[Kagemaru groans]
[Kagemaru]
I die with no regrets.
[Umpire]
You're out!
[ding]
[Ichiemon] Things have
really gotten serious
here in the bottom
of the inning.
The Japanese team now has
only one player remaining.
How in the world does he intend
to keep fighting when
it's nine against one?
[Doubleday laughs]
It's not even a contest,
this game's in the bag.
'Gainst a bunch of pansy
ass girls like you,
one of me is more than enough!
Mugen goes into his
windup for the pitch. Uh...
Huh? What in the
world is he doing?
What the hell?
That's a balk! A balk!
What?
Ball. Ball. Ball.
Ball four.
[Ichiemon]
His plan has gone to pieces.
Not only does the pitcher
have no control,
at this point he seems to be
having difficulty standing.
Alright then. Guess I'll
try throwing it normally.
Yah!
[tree falls]
That was unbelievable.
No human being could
possibly hit a pitch like that.
[crack]
[Umpire]
Take ya base.
Yah!
God help us.
This isn't baseball anymore.
This is madness.
[Ichiemon] Amazing, the American
team's roster is decimated.
They're down to
one last player.
This game has been reduced
to a one-on-one battle.
It's man against man.
I'm not going to lose to you.
I won't let that
happen no matter what.
America cannot afford
to lose this game.
[Doubleday and Mugen yell]
Ahhh...!
[Ichiemon]
I can't believe it!
Both of the players are down!
How on Earth do we
decide the outcome?
Will this go down in the record
books as an incomplete game?
[Mugen grunts]
Jesus.
Friggin' kamikaze...
Listen up, ya damn Yankees.
Now I wanna see
a little hustle.
Go back to your own country!
[Ichiemon]
He's back on his feet,
and the American team
has no players left.
It's a forfeit. The game
is over! The game is over!
[Manzou] And so,
the game came to an end
after one short inning.
And the Americans went
home with less pride
and a profound fear
of Japanese people.
It was years before they once
again returned to these shores.
In fact, not until the arrival
of Commodore Perry in 1853.
♪ End Theme ♪
[Manzou] And so, as he
stood looking out to sea,
he had no idea that he had
inadvertently
saved this country.
His thoughts were turned
to the distant shores
and the strange land beyond,
to which the dark
ships were returning.
My thoughts ain't turnin'
anywhere. Quit makin' stuff up.
Where the hell did you come
from anyway? Shut your piehole!
[Manzou] Okay.