♪ Opening Theme ♪
[Mugen] I never met
anyone like him before.
I know he's still alive.
Something in my gut tells me.
[Fuu] There's gotta be
an easier road we could take
than this one.
I mean, this is ridiculous.
It's not like we're making the
Kumano pilgrimage or anything.
Isn't there some kinda shortcut
that'll get us
to the West faster?
I'm not familiar with the West.
Hey Jin, what's up with that?
[Mugen] It's the same no
matter which road we take.
Besides, it makes sense
to mix in with the crowd.
That way if any idiots are
after us, they won't spot us.
Why are they after you?
Are you criminals or something?
Yeah I guess you could say
I've been a criminal
since I was born,
but I'm thinkin'
maybe it's because
I'm so damn good-lookin'.
[girls giggling]
What an idiot.
He's a total idiot.
[Jin] Hmm.
So ladies, whattya say
the three of us go over there
where the grass
is nice and tall?
Huh?
And just what exactly
do you have in mind?
All sorts of things.
He's nothing but a pervert.
[Jin] Mmm.
[Girl 2] But you know what?
We have to be careful,
there's a monster around.
Everyone says so.
A monster?
[Girl 1] What did they say
it was? A Tengu? A Kappa?
[Girl 2] No, a crow monster,
remember? With lots of legs.
[Mugen] Aw, don't let
that kinda talk scare ya.
Those rumors always
get started when somebody
sees a dog or a bear
or something like that.
The rumor gets
bigger and spreads
from one person to the next.
It gets so distorted that before
you know it, it's a monster.
Gotcha!
[Mugen growling,
Girls screaming]
[Girl 2] What are
you doing? Cut it out.
[Girls punching]
Get off me!
Stupid jerk!
[Girl 1] Sleezeball!
[Girl 2] Pervert.
[Mugen groaning]
Man
Still horny, but at least
he's got food.
[Guys rapping] ♪ Huh, that
monster's gotta be Yoshitsune. ♪
Yo!
♪ On the peaks in the show,
he's a spooky mofo, ♪
♪ Everything's gone a-loony, ♪
♪ cause the mountain's
haunted by Yoshitsune. ♪
♪ It's gotta be the ghost ♪
--[Jin] Yoshitsune.
--[Guys] Yeah boy.
Who's that?
Who do they mean?
♪ He's fat, he's fly,
he's tall as the sky, ♪
♪ always grabs his rocks
when the bitches walk by. ♪
Yo!
♪ He's an ice cold sake, killed
a thousand mighty men, hyah! ♪
That wasn't him.
♪ He's so fast,
comin' up on your ass, ♪
♪ Gonna knock you in the air, ♪
♪ cause you jumpin'
everywhere in your face. ♪
Sayin'
Huh?
♪ The dude's so handsome all the
bitches wanna pants him. ♪
Huh?
Seems they have
their rumors mixed up.
Ha!
♪ There's no need
to bust a tumor, ♪
♪ cause it's nothin'
but a rumor. ♪
Word.
So, what is it that's
in these mountains?
Just a bunch of rumors,
that's all it is.
[Mugen] I gotta go,
gotta take a leak.
Huh?
Alrighty then.
Looks like we're not dealin'
with a Tengu or a Kappa here.
[Fuu] Hey, are you sure
this is a shortcut?
C'mon, where'd you get the
brilliant idea to come this way?
[Mugen] I got a feelin'
there really is
somethin' living out here.
There's somethin'
in these mountains.
Huh?
Any idiot can see things
are living out here,
so what's your point, anyway?
Well I'm kinda curious,
aren't you?
Mmm.
I admit this ghost of Yoshitsune
business has my interest piqued.
That's just great.
I knew it all along.
What is it you knew?
I knew from the very start
that you two would
be totally incapable
of following the
scent of sunflowers.
What?
You're only interested
in one thing,
and that's being with
a cute girl like me.
You're not the least
bit interested
in trying to find the
sunflower samurai anymore.
I hate it when people get the
wrong impression about me.
Huh?
You think I've lost interest
in finding your samurai?
I hate to break this to ya...
I never was interested!
Oh, and as for wantin' to be
with a cute girl like you, well,
just how dumb do I look?
So, you think you're cute, huh?
[spitting]
Yeah right, I don't think so.
Then why have you
stayed with me all this time?
It was just pure chance,
that's all.
Stop this, it's unseemly.
Tall, dark, and four-eyed here's
thinkin' the same thing.
Sorry, but hangin' around a girl
who's got no sex appeal at all
ain't my idea of a good time.
Now you've gone too far.
Yeah, that's right,
Jin, you tell 'im.
The four-eyed thing...
take that back.
Wait a minute!
So what's the big deal, uh?
A samurai who
smells of sunflowers?
What's up with that?
Why would you ever wanna
find a pansy like that anyway?
[Fuu] No, he's not
like that at all.
Alright then, what is he like?
Well, he's kinda like...
See what I mean?
You don't know
a damned thing about him.
Don't tell me that you don't
even know what he looks like.
[Mugen] Maybe you feel like
tellin' us why you're so
desperate to find this guy when
you don't even know for sure
if he's alive or dead.
The guy's alive.
Or at least until
I get ahold of him.
The jerk's gotta be alive.
So you want revenge?
What's it matter to you?
I'm guessin' this guy
had his way with you,
then threw you out like trash.
Now you want
a little payback, right?
[Fuu] Oh, okay.
Now I get it.
It's all clear to me now.
You know what?
You two were never anything
more to me than hired muscle,
you got it?
So I'm trading you up
for a tougher model!
Gimme a break!
I ain't gonna let some loudmouth
little girl like you fire me.
I quit.
Hold on.
That's fine with me,
because your services
are no longer required.
[Fuu] Goodbye.
Yeah, well
good riddance. See ya.
Hold on.
[Fuu] You're nothing but
a big dumb coward!
You closet pervert half-wit!
[steel against steel]
Those two are-
Let 'em fight. See if I care.
[Fuu yelling]
[steel against steel]
[squeaking]
Momo!
Momo come down! Wait!
Where are you going, Momo?
You can't leave me too.
[screaming]
[rushing water]
Whatcha doin' Momo?
No, don't!
Get back! Stay away!
[laughing]
I can't believe it.
I didn't kill
that bastard before I left.
Crap.
And this would have been the
perfect chance for me to do it.
♪ funk music ♪
Bastard.
What's the big idea?
Son of a--
Do you work for
the Matsumae domain?
Huh? Where the hell is that?
And who the hell are you?
Hey you!
Come back here.
Say you're sorry, dammit!
I can't...
...hold on.
[Fuu screaming]
As I suspected,
I see that your skills
have improved, Yukimaru.
So even you chose
to come after me for revenge.
When Ogura was unable
to carry out his plan,
he took his own life.
[Yukimaru] But you
must understand,
I'm not like
those others from the dojo.
There's no point
in avenging our master's death.
With the dojo gone now,
all everyone talks about is you.
I'm sick of it.
[Jin] You wish to make
a name for yourself?
Exactly what you did, right?
When you killed our master.
Why is it that
you keep running away?
I've no desire to kill you.
Yeah right.
You're not good enough.
The fact is,
you aren't worth killing.
Killing you is meaningless.
All it would do
is tarnish my sword.
I'm not the same
little boy I used to be.
I'm afraid your time is over.
[Jin] What's the matter?
Why don't we finish this...
...and go to hell together?
You can say that
you killed me if you like.
[Jin] I might as well
be dead already.
[Fuu] This is bad.
I'm gonna die.
I'm actually...
...gonna die.
Please.
Help me.
Somebody, please help me.
[squeaking]
Why you!
[Fuu] Momo.
I, uh...
You were carried here
by the river.
[Fuu] Was I really?
[Okuru] My appearance must seem
somewhat strange to you.
[Fuu] Uh, no.
It's not that, it's just...
[stomach grumbling]
Is it okay?
Mmm.
[Fuu] If you're sure
you don't mind!
[Fuu] Oh, this is so good!
A woman with a healthy
appetite is beautiful.
[Fuu] You've uh... you've done
so much to help me.
But I have no way
to repay you.
Hey Momo, come over here.
What's with you?
I think it's probably
because I have these.
These are sunflower seeds.
[Momo squeaking]
Geez, I see where
your loyalties are.
[Fuu] Well, thank you
for everything.
[gasping]
Ow, that hurts.
Huh? What're you...
[Okuru] These medicinal herbs
will help your wounds.
If you leave them on for
a while, it'll feel better.
[Fuu] Thank you.
[Okuru] The forest can be
dangerous at night,
feel free to sleep here.
Uh, my name is Fuu.
What about you?
What's your name?
You can call me Okuru.
[Fuu] Is this where you live?
[Okuru] For the time being.
I'm on a journey.
[Fuu] Have you
been traveling alone?
[Okuru] Yes.
[Fuu] I'm all alone, too.
Those two jerks are gone now.
[Okuru] Two jerks?
[Fuu] Yeah, up until today,
I had a couple
of useless bodyguards
who were traveling with me.
Well, I guess
it doesn't matter now.
Now I don't have anyone
in the whole world.
It doesn't matter if I wind up
dead in a ditch somewhere.
But for some reason, I always
hated the thought of drowning.
I mean your body bloats up
to twice its size, right?
Forget that!
I want my corpse
to be beautiful.
[Okuru] In my village,
ever person living there
was taken by the Roaming God.
It's a disease.
Killed every
single one of them.
Wiped out the entire village.
I had gone away on a journey,
so I was the only survivor.
I had a family, a wife
and newborn daughter.
They were both taken
by the gods.
I'm sorry.
Death leaves
no beautiful corpses.
None.
Good riddance to those two.
Screw 'em both.
That little bitch.
[Fuu] Where will you
go from here?
[Okuru] I've been
working my way west.
[Fuu] West, huh?
[Okuru] I can't stick
around here much longer.
[Fuu] I've been traveling
in the same direction.
West to Nagasaki.
You see,
I'm looking for a samurai
who smells of sunflowers.
Okuru,
I was thinking,
could I travel with you?
When you're done
sneakin' around, come on out.
I'll take you guys on
whenever you're ready.
[Policeman] We're
police officers with
the Matsumae domain
magistrate's office.
Come along peacefully, Okuru.
Huh?
[Policeman] Give yourself up!
♪ End Theme ♪