♪ Opening Theme ♪
[DJ screaming: Come on, y'all!]
♪ slow hip hop beat ♪
[Minstrel Singing]
As we return to our story
the hours, minutes,
and seconds have unfolded,
and disappeared,
never to be seen again.
We join our three travelers:
Mugen, Jin, and Fuu,
ever determined, relentless,
and hell-bent on success,
as they continue
their long journey
to distant Nagasaki.
After what seems
an interminable stay,
they set out from Edo.
Shortly after that, they passed
through the Kanto checkpoint,
and moved onward
through Suruga,
until they had passed Hamamatsu.
[record skipping]
They traveled beyond Ise, and
in spite of various digressions,
which no doubt
hampered their progress,
the three persevered
traveling ever westward,
to the point where
we join them now.
The road has not
been an easy one.
It has been long, with twists
and turns too numerous to count.
They have overcome many
trials and tribulations,
until at long last they
have arrived in the region
known as Old Capital.
And now, dear friends,
we invite you to join us,
as we travel from
what has been to what shall be.
We traverse
the spider web thin tightrope,
which separates
fact from fiction,
and leads us back
to the three travelers.
Samurai Champloo,
now begins the Kansai chapter.
It promises to be an interesting
journey. We hope you enjoy it.
[frantic breathing]
[Mugen, eating]
These freshwater fish
taste better than I thought.
[Fuu, eating]
There's a book called
"Master of the River" that says
they taste really bad, though.
[Mugen] I guess they do
have a lot of bones.
Jin, for cryin' out loud,
give it up, will ya?
C'mon, why don't you
just come have lunch with us?
You can eat some of my catch.
I'll never be able
to eat them all anyway.
Aw, don't worry about him.
He's just bein' a big baby,
cause he got skunked.
Yeah, but still.
C'mon, you heard what he said,
right before we started fishin'.
"Fishing is a life and death
struggle between man and fish,
forget this and
you'll most certainly get hurt."
He really said that. [laughing]
He can't even catch fish that're
swimmin' right in front of him.
We shouldn't laugh,
it's not nice.
[Mugen and Fuu laughing]
Do you think we
might've overdone it a bit?
Who cares?
Well yeah, but...
Whatever you do,
just don't look him in the eye.
[both]
Oh, whoa!
[Fuu] Where did these come from?
[Jin] They were at
the bottom of the pond.
[Mugen] We hit pot, Jack.
[Fuu] It's jackpot.
[Mugen] All I know now's
we're filthy bitch.
[Fuu] Filthy rich!
[Jin] I hope you're
doing that deliberately.
But whether you are or not...
[all three]
Banzai!
[Fuu] The big city. Real food!
Oh yeah, I'm really stuffed.
I can't remember the last time
I felt so good.
Half woman, half pig.
[Jin] Yeah.
[Fuu] ♪ I'm so full.
I'm so full. I'm so full, ♪
♪ and it's no bull. ♪
♪ It's no bull.
It's no bull and I'm so full. ♪
♪ But it doesn't hurt,
it doesn't hurt. ♪
♪ Cause now I'm
ready for dessert. ♪
Hey you guys, where you going?
[Guards] Hey, no women allowed.
[Fuu] What do you mean?
How come?
[Guard] This is the
red light district.
Let go, you buck-tooth freaks.
Let go of me!
I'm gonna get you,
you traitors.
You jerks!
[Akame] You are
most welcome here.
Please, gentlemen,
if you would kindly follow me.
[Mugen] Word on the
street's that this is
the best place in town.
Is that true?
[Akame] Our girls have
the looks and skills
to match any geisha in Edo,
and that's a fact.
We have nothing but
the finest girls.
You'll see for yourself. There's
not a bad one in the bunch,
and our prices
are most reasonable.
Nothing to complain about there.
Here we are, gentlemen.
Please, make yourselves at home.
I shall arrange
for food and courtesans,
suitable to men
of your stature.
[Fuu] What a couple of creeps.
How could they even think of
goin' to the red light district
when they've got me around?
It sure is tough
being a girl, isn't it?
Hey, Momo, are you
a boy or a girl?
[Momo squeaking]
I'm so hungry.
[Courtesans]
Welcome good sirs.
Hello, my name is Takigawa.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance. I'm Seyama.
Good evening.
My name is Yatsuha.
It is an honor and a pleasure.
[Mugen] Oh yeah. Ha ha! Sweet.
I think I'll take
this girl right here.
The rest of you
can accommodate my friend.
[girls sighing]
[Akame] Well, Sir?
[Ginsa] Who are they?
[Akame] We're unsure
of their identities,
but they seem to be
a pair of ronin.
[Ginsa] And they arrived
in the city today?
[Akame] So it would seem.
These are coins we had
planned to release in Kaga
in three days.
So, why are they
already circulating?
Did you fail
in your duties, Kakizou?
Yes, Sir. I can offer
no excuse for my failure.
I am preparing a full report.
Now!
[Henchman 1] Yes, Sir...
Bring him up!
[mechanical sounds]
[Ginsa] Who is this?
[Kakizou] His name
is Hankichi Otowa.
He tried to escape from
the underground foundry
the other day.
We were finally able to capture
him just outside Ryugakubo.
He had nothing on him
at the time.
[Kakizou] However...
However?
[Kakizou] As an extra
precaution,
we tortured him
viciously for hours,
but he never said a word.
It's possible he's been trained
to withstand torture.
I can't believe it.
Then we've been infiltrated by
the shogunate secret police.
This is serious Kakinoji!
[Ginsa] Akame.
Sir?
Who else started here around
the same time as this laborer?
Around the same time, Sir?
Let me see...
[Kakizou] It was
nearly a year ago when
he started working
at the foundry.
There were four or five others
who started underground then.
A year ago... Yatsuha's the
only one who started working
above ground at that time.
I can't believe Yatsuha
would do that.
Whether you believe it
or not really makes
no difference in the end,
doubts are like bothersome flies
that must all be crushed.
That is rule #1.
Yes, Sir.
For the sake of our great cause,
it is imperative
to be thorough
in everything we do.
I mean everything.
[Ginsa] I'll leave the disposal
of those two ronin
to you, Kakizou.
Turn them into fish food,
so as not to raise
any unnecessary suspicions.
[Kakizou] Apparently a fat girl
was accompanying the two men,
but she's no longer with them.
[Ginsa] Her too, then.
Track her down
and eliminate her.
[Kakizou] Yes, Sir.
Leave no traces whatsoever,
is that clear?
Don't fail me.
Not good.
[Mugen] Heh?
Hey, whatcha doin', Baby?
[Yatsuha, sweetly]
Oh! Nothing you need
to concern yourself with.
Maybe I didn't tell ya,
I don't like bein' teased.
So, whattya say we get this
little party started, huh?
After all, I put down
good money for this.
Yes, of course.
[vase shattering]
I'm sorry about the head,
but I'm afraid
my situation has changed.
[Yatsuha] It looks like
my partner has been captured.
Now I'm probably
in danger, too.
So that means I have
to go back to Edo now
and come up with a new plan.
[sighing] Boy,
this is so irritating.
I've worked undercover
for a whole year and now this.
Gotta go! See ya 'round,
lover boy.
But you never know,
maybe we'll meet again.
[Mugen] Son of a bitch.
That hurt like hell.
[groaning]
I think maybe I could learn
to like this rough stuff.
Yeah, it wasn't foreplay.
[Mugen] I'm not lettin' you
get away again.
Oh, good grief.
♪ hip hop music ♪
Alrighty. Let's get
down to business here.
Hey! Look, there's
a naked woman over there!
Huh?
[Yatsuha, breathless] Man...
this guy's incredible.
Still.
[Mugen, hoarse] Gotta
admit, you tough chicks
really turn me on.
[Yatsuha] Listen,
how would you like
to try something
really amazing?
[Mugen agreeing eagerly]
Alright, why don't
we go next door?
What're you doing?
Who are you?
First tell me
who the hell you are.
Oh, would you look at that,
this room's too crowded.
There's no way
we could have any real fun
with these guys in here.
Sons of bitches!
[Mugen] I want my nookie!
Talk to me Hankichi.
Say something.
Are you alive?
[Hankichi straining]
Yatsuha, is that you?
Sorry Yatsuha,
but I couldn't outrun them.
This is no ordinary
group of counterfeiters
we're dealing with.
You mean that with your speed
you couldn't outrun them?
Tell me who they are.
[Hankichi] I think they are
remnants of the Negoro.
The Negoro? You sure?
The ones from
the Warring States period?
I can't believe
they're still around.
We don't have
nearly enough men.
Yatsuha, go to
our master for reinforcements.
[groaning]
It's gonna be alright, don't
worry, I'll take care of it.
I'll come up with something.
[Hankichi] I'm sorry.
[Mugen] You ready now?
[Sweetly] Oh I just remembered;
we can't have any fun in here.
Hey, I know, as I recall,
there's a great spot that's
much better than this
right below us.
Huh? [Yatsuha screaming]
♪ hip hop music ♪
Are you positive that
this is all of them?
Yes, Sir.
The other one bit off his own
tongue and then killed himself.
Oh, I see.
[Ginsa] Hold him.
[Henchman 1] Yes, Sir.
[man struggling, gagging]
[Ginsa] I'll have you sing
a little for me...
about who sent you.
[man screaming]
[Yatsuha screaming]
What the hell was that?
Whassup?
Yo, what's goin' on down here?
It looks like our timing was
a little too good for once.
[Ginsa] Who the hell
are you two?
So you're the
big boss around here.
I finally see your face.
You're a spy from the East.
[Yatsuha] Ginsa Momochi! Your
operation has been exposed.
The counterfeiting
of koban coins is one of the
most serious of all crimes.
Hmm?
Oof.
This counterfeiting foundry
is irrefutable proof.
Now surrender yourself
and come along peacefully.
[Ginsa laughing]
Just what the hell's so funny?
Who is it that knows
about these crimes of mine?
Just you two, right?
Right now you are facing
over twenty descendants
of the Tsuda clan of Negoro.
More than twenty
dedicated warriors
whose skills are unmatched.
Considering the fact that
you're outnumbered here
by the likes of us,
what can a couple of
policemen from the city
hope to accomplish?
Okay, you got us
outnumbered. However...
--[Yatsuha] Hey...
--[Mugen] Hmm?
If you take out all these guys,
I promise I'll rock your world.
Forget about it.
You keep saying that,
but you never deliver nothin'--
[Yatsuha whispering]
You're on.
Get them!
♪ funk music ♪
[Henchman 3] Excuse me, Miss.
We're looking for a girl.
She's about your age,
but she's really fat.
You haven't seen her,
have you?
[Fuu] Nope.
[Henchman 3]
Sorry to bother you.
Let's check over there.
[Henchman 4] Yes, Sir.
[Jin] Who's out there?
[Kakizou] Answer me this:
Where did you obtain
those coins you have?
[Jin] As I suspected,
that money has a history.
But I owe you no answer.
My back.
[Girl] Mmm, Master Jin.
Can't be. How could you-
[growling]
[yelling] Who are you?!
The daughter of shogunate
secret police ninja
Jinpachi of Iga, Yatsuha.
Now I see...
You're Jinpachi's daughter.
So a relative of the same clan
of ninja mercenaries
that brought us down before
thwarts the Tsuda clan again.
Well, no matter.
[Yatsuha] Thank you.
For the past year,
we've been working undercover
and secretly
investigating these guys.
We were finally able
to arrest them.
We owe it all to you.
[Mugen] Forget it.
That guy was a scum bag.
No thanks necessary.
That is so long as you
intend on keeping your promise.
Look! A naked woman!
Huh?
[Hankichi] Here we go.
Are you sure he's
gonna be okay?
I feel bad
just leavin' him here.
It appeared that he had
some traveling companions.
They'll come lookin'
for him sooner or later.
C'mon, we better get going.
It's a long way to Edo.
I just hope the crows
don't eat him first.
He'll be fine. He's not
as delicate as he looks.
After all, that's
the man I'm gonna marry.
Huh?
I guess I fell
in love with him.
So long. Once both our journeys
are over, I'll come find you.
[Hankichi] A-Are you serious?
I'm so hungry!
My back.
♪ End Theme ♪