♪ Opening Theme ♪
[Narrator] Long ago,
the stars that glittered
in the night sky
were a vital set of guideposts
used by travelers everywhere.
People believed these heavenly
bodies would shine forever,
that they were immortal.
And so, because of this belief,
whenever meteors or comets
would fall from the skies
without warning,
they were feared
as sinister omens.
It was believed that if
someone actually saw a star
while it was falling, terrible
luck lay in store for them.
This belief lasted
for many centuries.
It was not until the
beginning of the Edo Period
that the shogunate appointed
the first official astronomer,
a scholar named
Shunkai Shibukawa.
Of course, at this time,
the world was still
thought to be flat.
Look, a shooting star.
I wish that very soon,
we find the samurai who
smells of sunflowers,
and that all of us make
it to Nagasaki safely,
and that we come across
a whole lot of food
so we can totally
stuff ourselves.
Huh?
Isn't that a...
It's a matsutake
mushroom, isn't it?
Huh?
Geez, don't you know anything?
Some people call 'em
"jewels of the mountains."
You can get a whole
lot of money for 'em.
Gah! What are you doing?
Come on, spit it out.
Mushrooms spread themselves
through spores,
so if you come across one,
you should be able to find...
Ahh! Not you too!
--Found another one.
--Me too.
Ah, no!
[Fuu yells]
Man, did I gorge myself.
[Mugen coughs and burps]
I'm afraid I have a heart burn.
Gone. Gone. Gone.
Gone. All gone.
They ate every last one of 'em.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I read something in
the horoscope section
of the newspaper.
It said I should be especially
wary of mushrooms today.
[Jin] Huh?
You couldn't have told us
that before we ate 'em?
[rumbling]
Ahh!
[Mugen yells]
[Fuu screams]
[Mugen]
Oh, this sucks.
[Jin]
Anyone hurt?
Where are we?
Jin...
Mugen?
Your hands are cold.
What's wrong with you guys?
They're like icicles.
[screaming]
[yelling]
Huh...?
[Fuu]
This is incredible.
What is this place?
[Jin] Seems as if they're
trying to excavate something.
[Mugen] Hey!
[men gasp]
Y-You shouldn't scare
people like that.
Nearly gave me a heart attack.
Sorry 'bout that.
[men sigh]
Be careful next time.
[biwa strum]
[Shige] ♪ There were
men on top of horses, ♪
♪ and horses on top of men. ♪
♪ Piled one atop the other. ♪
♪ The valley was laid
open before the men. ♪
♪ It's depth was
great and wide. ♪
♪ But the number of
soldiers that died that day ♪
♪ would fill its tomblike
walls from side to side. ♪
♪ Corpses stacked up to
build a mountain of death, ♪
♪ and it gushed rivers
of dead men's blood! ♪
The Tale of Heike, volume 7,
"Descent into Kurikara."
[biwa strum]
The end.
Well, what have we here?
How is it that wayward travelers
have happened upon us?
Yeah, um, what are you doing?
Focus my good visitor.
Move your eyes to this area.
Were you aware that these holes
represent the moon
and the stars?
Stay focused.
Now were you also aware
that the sound that
rings out from the biwa
is the sound of
the stars themselves?
Power comes from
strumming this biwa.
Do it right
and you can call the stars
straight down from the sky.
Great, another freak.
Who the hell're you?
Why yes, of course.
How very rude of me.
But travelers, please
don't forget that
you are the ones
who are guests here.
Correct me if I'm
wrong, dear visitors,
but doesn't it come off as
just a little bit presumptuous
that you assume the three of
you can just wander in here
and demand to know
what my name is?
But I'll let that go.
Perhaps I'm being
overly sensitive.
I would hate for someone
that I hardly know
to think ill of me
for any reason.
[Fuu]
What're you talking about?
You may address me as Shige.
Heike blood flows in my veins.
I have taken it upon myself
to excavate the
Heike's buried treasure
hidden long ago
in this very spot.
[Fuu]
Buried treasure...?
In this place?
[Shige]
Absence of proof
does not always mean
proof of absence.
It's an old expression,
perhaps you've heard it before.
I must admit that it
would be unfair of me
to demand that you simply
take my word for it.
Just read this.
Take a look.
This genealogy proves that I am
a descendant of the Heike clan.
And with this proof,
I have every right to claim
this buried treasure
for myself.
It is rather common
knowledge that
the Heike treasure is buried
here, in the land of Kyushu.
Its precise location
is indicated right here.
Invisible ink?
Well I don't buy it.
Yes, of course.
You still don't think treasure
could possibly be buried here.
Surely you don't mean to
insinuate that you believe
everything that I've told you
is nothing but a lie, do you?
Young lady, it's that kind of
cynicism and lack of trust
that serves to accentuate
the differences between
our two generations.
[Fuu grumbles]
This guy gives me the willies.
Come on.
[Shige] How typical.
Your generation only sees
people from one perspective.
You've made up your mind
and have chosen to deny
anything that suggests
you might be wrong.
How unfortunate.
Well, correct me if I'm wrong,
but doesn't one need money
to keep oneself fed?
It was five years ago
that we started this search.
And now, just as we are about
to discover the treasure,
we are unexpectedly visited
by three travelers.
Surely fate had
something to do with this.
Perhaps you would
care to assist us.
We happen to be short-handed.
Depends on the pay.
I promise you ten percent of
the treasure once it is found.
That's enough gold for
the three of you to fund
the restoration of an entire
nation if you wanted.
Say what?
Ten percent would be
a very large sum of money.
Are you kidding?
We don't have time
to mess around here,
we've gotta get to Nagasaki!
You'll need it all the more
if you're going to Nagasaki.
You can't fight a battle
on an empty stomach.
He who does not work
does not deserve to eat.
Well, I guess you got a deal.
Right.
No way!
Please, allow these
two to show you the way.
Sabini, Fuupa,
I leave them to you.
Yes. As you wish.
[Fuu] Geez. Why does
this always happen to us?
We're only doing this for
a little while. You got it?
[Shige] There's no need
to be in such a hurry.
Make yourselves at home.
After all, there is no escape.
[Fuu] I don't know what you guys
think, but that Shige is fishy.
Well at least while
we're staying here,
we're saving ourselves the
cost of food and lodging.
I say if we find that treasure
first we just grab it and run.
And somethin' about that
map didn't seem right.
[stomach growl]
Hey, can't we get some
grub around here?
[Fuupa] Um, well...
You guys do have food, right?
[Sabini]
We got this. Hey!
Hold on, share will ya?
Ah! Ug, what is this?
It's wasabi.
[Mugen gags]
[Narrator]
There are some theories
that suggest that
life on Earth
sprang from organisms carried
here by fallen meteors.
These chunks of rock
have traveled from the far
depths of outer space.
And no one can deny
the possibility
that unknown viruses
or organisms
may have been lurking
somewhere within them.
[Shige] This is Penta,
a self-professed psychic.
It was he who
divined the location
of the buried treasure.
Explosives were then
planted in the bedrock
that had long ago buried
the bounty beneath it.
This treasure does exist!
[explosion]
[Mugen grunts]
Dammit. What does that bastard
think I am, a freakin' mule?
[Fuu] You've got nobody
to blame but yourselves.
[Fuupa] Hang in there
just a little while longer.
Look at the dowsing
rod over there.
It's picked something
up in the bedrock.
Hold on. Somethin'
strange is goin' on.
I coulda sworn that guy's
arm was cut off before.
Did I just imagine it?
[crashing sound]
[Mugen grunts]
[Fuu] How many days
have we been here now?
[Jin] It feels like
just a few days,
but it could be several months.
The truth is you lose
all track of time
when you start
workin' down here.
But when we finally get to lay
our hands on that treasure,
it'll make the five years we
spent in this hole worth it.
Cause we'll finally knock
that corrupt bastard,
Genji, off his throne.
Genji?
What kind of jackass leader
moves the capital to Kamakura?
I'll tell ya,
Yoritomo's a son of a bitch.
Kamakura?
Hello?
Uh, we're in the
Tokugawa Era now.
[Sabini] Hey, what do you
say we take a little break.
[Fuupa] Yeah.
You really gotta admit,
the people here are
a little bit strange.
I mean, how can anyone
exist on nothing but wasabi?
It is odd.
But I recall wasabi
having certain
preservative elements to it.
Hmm?
Hold on.
I coulda sworn
those two guys were...
Are they... rotting?
Impossible.
That's why they always
eat so much wasabi.
[Fuu gasps]
What do you think?
Is this not the most
perfect place to forget
the troubles of
the world outside?
Alright, come clean.
Who are you people?
[Shige] My word.
Such a philosophical question
for someone of your age to ask.
I've pondered this myself.
Who am I, indeed.
I can only hope that someday
I'll be able to find the
answer to that question.
[Henta] Sorry, Sir, but
we're running out of manpower.
Well, I have no choice.
I must go summon some
reinforcements. Excuse me.
[Mugen groans]
I'm completely spent.
[coughing]
I have a heart burn again.
Wait a sec. Maybe I was wrong.
Maybe those weren't
matsutake mushrooms
that they ate after all.
Somethin's not right.
Are you guys also...
[coughing]
Huh? What's her problem?
[Jin] You know, something
has been bothering me.
[Mugen] Huh?
[Jin] Did that Heike family
tree seem suspicious to you?
Not really, but if you wanna
take a look at it, it's in here.
Why don't we take
a look at it then.
[Mugen] I can't make any
sense out of this damned thing.
[Jin] Hmm...
[stomach growl]
Man, don't they got anything
else to eat around here?
Guess I got no choice.
[Fuu gasps]
[Fuu screams]
Help me!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to
pull your arm off. I'm sorry.
[Fuu breathes heavily]
[Fuu screams]
Too bad.
Sorry you discovered our secret.
But now that you have,
I'm afraid I have no choice
but to kill you, too.
[Mugen] So that's how
it's gonna be, huh?
Wish you woulda said
somethin' earlier,
cause I got no problem
takin' all you ugly dudes on.
[Mugen]
Aww, come on, you done already?
What the--
No way. Why aren't you dead?
What the hell's up
with these dudes?
Ah! Ah! Hey! Get off me!
I'm afraid these men
are already dead,
which would make
killing them impossible.
Aww, don't fight it.
Once they kill you, I'll bring
you back to life as well.
[Mugen]
Get off me you freak!
That sure was a
close call, wasn't it?
My head was hanging
by a mere flap of skin.
[Jin]
What's this? Can't be.
Don't resist. Come join us
and help us take back what
that Genji scum stole from us.
[Mugen screams]
What are you talking about?
The Heike and the Genji
have been dead forever.
Don't you know that we're
living in the Edo Era now?
What did you say?
Don't you see?
You think you've been
digging here five years,
but it's really 500.
You guys are so screwed up
you don't even realize
you died hundreds of years ago.
[Shige laughs]
You stupid little girl.
How dare you come here and start
babbling this nonsense to me!
[Jin]
Just a minute.
You should probably see this.
Look at the family line here.
Huh?
The two names aren't connected.
But then that means...
You guys are totally unrelated.
I'm afraid you're
not a descendant
of the Heike after all.
Liar!
They aren't connected... at all.
[Mugen]
You got no Heike blood in ya.
[Fuu]
That's a bummer.
How can this be?
I've been digging
for so long now.
After everything
I've been through.
After all my hard work.
All of it was for nothing?
This can't be happening.
Nooo!
Uh...
Wait a minute,
what am I thinking?
Just because I'm not
related doesn't mean
we can't keep
digging for treasure.
We shouldn't get too
hung up on bloodlines.
We don't have a drop of
blood in our bodies anyway.
Why don't we just continue
on like we have been?
Let bygones be bygones.
Forgive and forget.
You don't wanna do that, huh?
You sure? Uh...
[biwa strum]
That's all!
Look, it's a mushroom!
♪ End Theme ♪