♪ Opening Theme ♪
It isn't my eyes that see them.
[clang]
[Sara] To be honest, I'd hoped
this day would never come.
I wished our journey
could have lasted forever.
But I guess that's
too much to ask.
Who are you?
[Jin yells]
Ah!
[Fuu sighs]
Maybe we could rest for a bit?
Huh?
You never know, Jin
might decide to come back.
The only way he's comin' back
is if he gets kicked in the nuts
for tryin' to make
a move on that chick.
Can't you ever say
anything intelligent?
When you start, I'll start.
C'mon.
We can't find the sunflower dude
with you sittin' on your ass.
[Villager 1] We need help!
There's been an accident!
[Mugen] Hmm?
[Villager 1]
It's the bridge.
The rope bridge outside
the village, it's collapsed.
[Villager 2]
The bridge collapsed?
[Villager 3]
Was anyone on it?
[Villager 1]
I don't know. Let's go check.
[Mugen]
Isn't that the way Jin went?
You don't think they...?
[Villager 1]
You guys find anything?
[Villager 4]
Have you looked over there?
[Fuu gasps]
Those are Sara's!
Someone was on the bridge?
No one could have survived
a fall from that height.
You think she--
[Villager 6]
We found someone!
[Sara inhales]
Hey, she's still alive.
[Villager 7]
I can't believe she survived.
[Fuu] Sara...
Jin! What happened to Jin?
There should be
someone else. A man.
[Villager 8] Sorry. The only
person we found here was her.
[Villagers] Hey, don't go
down there. It's dangerous.
[Fuu] Mugen!
Shut up!
[Fuu]
What do we do?
You think he could have made it?
[Mugen] Even if he did,
the moron can't see
a damned thing
without these, right?
Those are for show.
[Mugen] Huh?
[Kisaburou] Don't worry.
We'll get her back on her feet.
[Fuu]
Oh, thank you for everything.
Fortunately, her injuries
don't look too serious.
You guys are welcome to stay
here as long as you'd like.
[Fuu]
We appreciate it. Thank you.
Hey, Mugen!
Come back here!
[Sara groans]
You're awake.
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't asked
him to come with me,
this wouldn't have happened.
I could say the same thing.
It's not your fault.
If only, I hadn't
been so insistent
that he go along with you.
[Sara]
Tell me, Fuu.
After all of this, are you
still going to Nagasaki?
Well yeah, of course.
Right.
Mugen! Sara woke up
and seems okay.
Oh.
[Fuu]
Take over for me, will ya?
I'm gonna see if
maybe I can find Jin.
[door closes]
[footsteps]
Found these in the river.
I think they're yours.
Tools of the trade, huh?
[Sara]
I'll be waiting by the river.
[door opens]
[Hissing]
I've nothing against
you personally.
This path is the only
path I can choose.
If I don't do this, my son dies.
Well show me what you got then.
I wanna see if you really
had what it took to kill him.
[Sara yells]
Nice.
Guess I don't have to
go easy on ya, do I?
Get back, bitch.
[Mugen grunts]
Damn she's fast.
[Sara yells]
[Mugen] Shit.
Go easy on her...
what was I thinkin'?
I've banged swords with a whole
lotta people in my life, lady,
but you're in
a league of your own.
I've never fought
anyone like you before.
But your ass is still mine.
[clang]
What's that?
[Mugen yells]
Mugen!
What's going on here?
What are you guys doing?
[Mugen]
Tell me. Who the hell are you?
What I can't see, I can sense.
What?
Inside of you looms a simmering
storm of hatred and rage.
But perhaps what I'm
actually sensing is sadness.
[Mugen groans]
It's as if you've never
once been loved by anyone.
It's as if you're just like me.
You trying to say you
can sense my moves
before they even happen?
What a load of crap!
Will you stop it?
Please just stop it!
Mugen!
Get away!
Get back!
[Fuu] No!
Don't. Don't kill him.
[Fuu sobs]
Get back here, bitch.
I'm not finished with you yet.
[coughing]
[Matagi] Well, look
who's awake, sleepyhead.
Excuse me, who are you?
You can't tell by lookin'?
I'm the man who saved your life.
You what?
You know, you may be the
first guest I've had here.
Stay as long as you like.
Thank you, but
I'm afraid I can't.
[Jin winces]
[Matagi]
Now don't you be in a rush.
Takes time for a body
to build up its strength.
Are you hungry?
I'm in your debt.
Well forget it.
[Matagi laughs]
I'm just messin' with ya.
I'll leave it over here.
If you want some then
you can get it yourself.
[door closes]
[Jin groans]
[Jin] Huh?
[Matagi laughs]
I can't believe
you fell for that.
[Jin] Why--
Why are you tormenting me?
I wanted to see how far you
could make it if you had to.
Relax. I'm just playin' around.
Guess I'll get ya
somethin' to eat now.
So, let's see if
there's a fish out here
that wants to be your dinner.
Yow!
[Fuu]
C'mon, hold still.
[Mugen] Forget it.
It's just a scratch.
It'll heal itself.
Fine then.
Oh...
So, you're strong enough
to come outside, huh?
To catch a fish,
you gotta think like one.
See like one.
See like a... fish?
[Matagi]
They go with the flow.
Fish use the water
surrounding their bodies
to sense what'll happen next.
If you move against the flow of
the water, the fish feels it,
darts away at the last minute.
But, if you don't
fight the current
and flow with it instead...
[Matagi] Whoopsie.
But, some fish get away anyway!
[Matagi laughs]
[Fuu] You know what?
Let's call it quits.
Huh?
[Fuu] It's just...
If I lost you,
I don't know what I'd do.
[Mugen] That blind chick,
she was pretty intense,
but I didn't get the feeling
that she wanted to kill me.
Still, that bitch just
might be able to take me.
[Jin grunts]
Thank you very much
for your help.
You're leavin'?
Too bad. I was hopin' to
jack you around some more.
[Jin] Sorry.
Here's a souvenir for ya.
[Jin]
Your teachings are wise.
I will take them to heart.
My teachings?
[Jin] Give a man a fish
and you feed him for a day;
teach him how to fish and
you feed him for a lifetime.
I'm sure you know this
old Chinese proverb.
Haven't a clue what
you're talkin' about.
I ain't no damned teacher.
You never told me
what your name is.
Musashi Miyamoto.
[Jin gasps]
[Matagi] Gotcha again!
That guy's been dead forever.
It's Johnny, if you
really gotta know.
Johnny?
[Matagi laughs]
[Matagi]
Come back again sometime.
[Kids chatter and laugh]
[Pinwheel Vendor]
You lost your composure.
Did you become attached to them?
Perhaps I need to remind you.
It's not just your life
you're gambling with.
Did you forget that
your son's fate
rests in your hands as well?
No.
[Sara gasps]
[Pinwheel Vendor]
Something wrong?
No.
[Pinwheel Vendor] I want
the job finished by tomorrow.
Ahh! G-G-Ghost!
Huh?
You hungry?
[Fuu] Geez...
I think you're dead and
the first thing you ask
is if I'm hungry.
Even a ghost would have
come up with a more
thoughtful line than that.
It's cleanin' up after his ass
that keeps getting us hurt.
What are you talking about?
He knows what I'm sayin'.
He went off with that chick,
even though he knew
she wanted to kill us.
What happened to her?
I dunno, but she's
one serious badass.
I know.
Jin.
It would seem that
for whatever reason,
someone has been
investigating us.
She had obviously been ordered
to befriend and accompany us.
[Mugen]
She said somethin' about
her kid's life
bein' on the line.
She did? Well, if that's true,
then someone's
forcing her to do this.
But who could that be?
[Mugen] Take your pick.
We've dined and dashed,
snuck through a checkpoint,
and oh yeah, killed people.
But I hardly think the
people we've offended
could've hired an
assassin of her caliber.
[Mugen]
Gotta point there.
I guess you're right.
[Mugen] Well, regardless
of who sent her,
if that bitch is
trying to kill us,
chances are we're
gonna see her again.
That woman...
...can sense our moves
before we make them.
Kinda figured that.
Just like a fish.
[Mugen] Huh?
[Jin] Fish use the water
surrounding their bodies
to sense what will happen next.
You can't fight the current.
You have to flow with it.
If you do that, you
might just catch the fish.
[Mugen]
Where'd you hear that?
From the old man
who saved my life.
Huh?
[thunder rumbles]
If you really feel this
is what you gotta do, then...
...I'll do what I gotta do.
[Sara] After all of this,
are you still going to Nagasaki?
Right.
[Fuu gasps]
Mugen.
Shit.
[Mugen grunts]
[Mugen breathes heavily]
[Jin] You can't
fight the current,
you have to flow with it.
If you do that,
you might just catch her.
[thunder rumbles]
[slicing sound]
Why'd you do it?
Why'd you pull back?
You know that you had me cold!
I realized something.
My son's been dead
for a long time now.
This whole time,
they've just been using me.
[Mugen]
Then fight them.
I cannot.
The government hired me.
I just want you to live, Mugen.
Dammit!
♪ End Theme ♪