♪ Opening Theme ♪
♪ hip hop music ♪
Son of a--
Do you work for
the Matsumae domain?
Huh?
[Mugen]
Where the hell is that?
And who the hell are you?
[Jin] You can say that
you killed me if you like.
I might as well
be dead already.
[Fuu] You see, I'm looking for
a samurai who
smells of sunflowers.
Okuru,
I was thinking,
could I travel with you?
[Head Officer]
We're police officers with
the Matsumae domain
magistrate's office.
Come along peacefully, Okuru.
Huh?
[Officer 2] Give yourself up!
[Mugen] You guys ain't
no average street punks.
[Officer 3] Hold it.
[Mugen] Listen fellas,
I gotta feelin'
you're making
a big mistake here.
What makes you so sure
I'm the guy you're lookin' for?
[Head Officer] We're after a man
by the name of Okuru.
He's a criminal who has fled
all the way from Matsumae.
We were told that
he's wearing strange clothes
and is hiding somewhere
in these mountains.
Then we're both
lookin' for the same guy.
What's that?
What'd this Okuru guy
do anyway that makes you
wanna find him so badly?
[Head Officer] This man
isn't Okuru, let's go!
Move out!
[Mugen] Hey,
come back here, dammit!
You weren't takin' off
without apologizing, were ya?
I cannot let you come with me.
I'm sorry.
But why not?
It's because I've killed
soldiers of the domain
and I'm on the run.
If you were to come with me,
you'd be a fugitive, too.
It doesn't matter.
There are these two guys
I've been traveling with
up until now.
They've done a lot
worse things than that.
If you have friends nearby,
then you should
be traveling with them.
Those cold-hearted jerks
are no friends of mine.
[Okuru] Once you have
traveled with someone,
they become like brothers.
So you are never alone
in this world.
[Fuu] Okuru...
Are you always
going to travel alone?
[Okuru] I'm never alone;
my wife and daughter
are always with me.
Now go to sleep.
[Officer 4] We don't know why.
He was probably driven mad
by the disease.
I heard that he killed
everyone in his village,
and when the domain soldiers
went in to capture him,
he killed them, too.
The man even killed
his own wife and daughter.
If we leave him running loose,
there's no telling
what he might do.
You're sayin' he's insane?
Funny, he didn't look
like a nutjob to me.
I'll just have
to take him down, then.
What's that?
[Mugen] You better warn
all your little buddies
to stay outta my way
if they don't wanna get hurt.
[squeaking]
I have no more seeds for you.
♪ hip hop music ♪
So, you made it.
[Officer 4] Yes, Sir.
And that man back at the river?
It's as we thought, Sir.
He doesn't appear to be Okuru.
He's much too young, and he
said he was from the Ryukyus.
[Head Officer] If he
interferes again,
you are to consider him
an accomplice and kill him.
Understood?
[Officer 4] Yes, Sir.
Amazing.
Seems like we've got every
crazy person in the country
running around these mountains.
[Officer 5] Lord Tamato,
we found the remains of
a fire along the riverbank
and shavings from
arrows being carved.
Okuru is an archer, Sir.
There's no doubt about it,
Okuru is here in this forest.
Reinforcements will be arriving
soon from Matsumae.
We must use this opportunity
to take Okuru's head.
♪ Japanese folk music ♪
[Mugen] Hey, you want those guys
to find you or somethin'?
Sounds familiar.
Kinda reminds me
of a tune I heard,
back when I was a little kid.
[Okuru] Where are you from?
[Mugen] Ryukyus, islands
way to the south.
[Okuru] I'm from the far north.
[Mugen] Funny how that works,
ain't it?
We're from places that
are nowhere near each other,
but I'm familiar with
the music you're playin'.
Lemme guess,
you must be Okuru.
[Mugen] You know, they were
right on your tail,
those guys from Matsumae domain
or wherever it was.
You made a whole buttload
of trouble for me.
Those idiots thought
I was you.
[Okuru] And did
they buy you off?
Screw that noise.
See, all I'm lookin' for
is a worthy opponent.
They said you lost your mind
because of some disease.
But from what I can see,
you don't look that way at all.
You know, those guys are sayin'
you even killed
your own wife and kid.
Hey, Momo?
Okuru?
[screaming]
[Jin] Hey.
Jin.
What happened here?
[Fuu] Just now, I saw an ogre
or a demon or something
on that cliff there.
It was carrying a sword.
Hey, wait a minute.
Where'd you come from,
and what are you doing here?
[Jin] First tell me
why you're here.
[Fuu] None of your business.
Something tells me
you didn't come back
because you suddenly
felt sorry for me.
The truth of the matter is
that I thought
you might have drowned.
Huh?
[Jin] This was floating
in the river.
[Fuu] So you were gonna keep it
as a memento of me or something?
[Jin] More of an offering
for your corpse.
I appreciate the thought.
What happened to your arm?
Don't tell me that jerk
actually cut you this time.
[Jin] It's just a scratch I got
when I jumped off a waterfall.
[Fuu] You jumped
off a waterfall?
I'm amazed you even survived.
[Both]
What about Mugen?
Haven't seen him.
I see.
Oh, I know. Don't go anywhere,
I've got an idea.
There are some medicinal herbs.
Pretty sure I saw
some over here.
[Okuru] It was people
from the domain
who brought the disease
to my village.
While I was away,
the village was transformed
into a mountain of corpses.
It was a terrible sight.
That is how my village
was really destroyed.
It doesn't matter
whether you believe me or not.
Your eyes kinda
remind me of somethin'.
It's a look I've seen before.
Like the half open eyes of a
head that's been chopped off...
Still a little moist
and you can't quite tell
where they're lookin'.
So I've gotta wonder.
Are you alive or dead?
[Fuu] Jin! What are you doing?
What is it?
Did you honestly think
you could fool me?
The people revere
these mountains here.
Have you any idea why?
They say you will
be reborn here.
Death and rebirth. Everyone
comes here in search of this.
These mountains have
that kind of power.
What about you?
You looking to get
a second chance?
[Jin] Yukimaru.
[Yukimaru] You won't truly be
dead until I perform the job
with my own two hands.
You're still extremely young.
I am an old man of nearly forty.
I have lived past my days.
Perhaps it is time
to put an end
to my ceaseless flight.
You're pretty spry
for an old man.
Why do you keep
running from me?
You're sure you want this?
Even if you
hadn't betrayed me...
or turned your back.
I will never, ever
let you get away.
[Mugen] What's the matter?
Outta arrows already?
[sound fading away]
[paced breathing]
[heart beating]
[Yukimaru]
When I said
I only wanted to make
a name for myself,
I was lying.
I only wanted one thing:
to be you.
[Jin] Yukimaru.
What the hell
are those idiots doin'?
Who was he, Jin?
Was he someone you knew
from before?
Yukimaru was like
a little brother to me.
That's ancient history now.
[Officer 7]
We found him, it's Okuru!
[Officer 8]
Get the others, hurry!
[hurried footsteps]
Okuru.
Did they say Okuru just now?
Yes.
Hey, come back.
[Head Officer] Can you hear me?
There's nowhere to run.
Don't make this harder than
it has to be. Give yourself up.
Just stay out of this,
you bastards.
Son of a-
Persistent little peckers,
aren't they?
[Jin] Do you know this Okuru
that they're after?
[Fuu] I have to help him.
I owe him my life.
You have a strong
sense of duty.
Without duty this world
would be a dark place.
You should get out of here.
It's me they want, and I'm tired
of running from these men.
[Mugen] What?
I have to face them.
There's some matters
that need to be settled.
Perhaps what you said to me
earlier was true after all.
Maybe that day,
back in my village,
I became one of the dead.
Go on.
[Mugen] Hey, wait a minute.
Oh no!
Which way do we go?
Momo!
Where did Okuru go?
[squeaking]
This way.
[Head Officer]
Okuru. We meet at last.
After all this time,
I can finally bring your head
back home with me.
You know nothing...
...about what happened to us.
[Okuru] That official didn't
make the slightest effort
to try to save
even a single person.
He was afraid the disease
would spread further.
So he simply burned
the village to the ground.
No matter. It's still
my duty to bring you in.
Those are my orders.
Okuru's down there.
[Mugen] You bastards!
Keep your hands off him.
This guy's mine!
Hey, what're you...
You- You monster!
I'll make you pay
for what you've done.
[Mugen] I never met anyone
like him before.
I know he's still alive.
Something in my gut tells me.
Right. Ghost of
Yoshitsune my butt.
I bet the rumors were
just a bunch of stories
about those two.
Geez, what a load of garbage.
[Mugen] So tell me...
Why don't you let us in
on the real reason
you're lookin' for
the sunflower samurai.
Is it revenge?
[Fuu] That's right. Revenge for
my mom. Or something like that.
Whatever the reason. Wars
aren't won on an empty stomach.
[Mugen] You got that right.
[Fuu] Huh?
Hey, hold on!
Where are you going?
[Mugen] Where the hell is
this Nagasaki place anyway?
You hear anything
about the food there?
[Jin] They've got something
called "castella"
that was brought over
from Europe.
Huh?
[Mugen] C'mon, Girlie,
move your ass.
♪ End Theme ♪