♪ Opening Theme ♪
[men laughing, talking]
Gentlemen, place your bets.
[Gambler] Alright.
[Dealer] It's one! It's two!
This is everything we've got,
understand? So be careful.
Bet the three.
Not three. Five.
[Mugen] You'll do anything to
get on my nerves, won't you?
[Jin] Hey, that's my line.
[Mugen] Bastard.
Someday I'll make you
cry like a little bitch.
"Little bitch"? Do people
actually say things like that?
I've never heard it before.
[Mugen] Say what?
This isn't the time. Calm down.
[Dealer] Let's play.
[men groaning]
No way. We actually won.
Oh yeah!
I thought I saw an animal...
Nah, must have imagined it.
[Soba Vender]
What can I get you?
Tempura noodles please.
Shippoku noodles.
I'll have double shrimp tempura.
[Soba Vendor]
You got it. Coming right up.
Our first food in three days.
And we won't just be smelling
it. We'll be able to eat it too.
Hey! Watch it.
[Shinsuke] That's what you get
for not paying attention.
Man, what a jerk.
[Soba Vender]
Thanks for waiting.
Three bowls comes to fifty mon.
Here we go.
Excellent.
[Soba Vendor] Hey,
you gotta pay up first.
Sure. No problem at all.
Huh? What the...?
What's wrong?
[Fuu] What?
Come on. Pay the man.
[Fuu] I can't believe it.
Our money. That guy stole it.
Say what?
♪ hip hop music ♪
Where'd that dirtbag go?
Hm?
Don't move.
What is it? What's wrong?
My mistake.
[men chuckling]
[Young Man 1] Bastard!
[Young Man 2]
What's your problem?
Wrong guy.
[Fuu] Jeez, what's the big idea
beating up innocent people?
Huh. Piece of cake.
You dimwit.
Huh?
Holdin' on to your wallet
and looking around
like a scared rabbit.
It's like wearing
a sign that says
"I'm carrying
something valuable."
Like this.
[Juukichi] I'm sorry, Boss.
I swear, you're the
dumbest guy I've ever known.
Now look.
Whenever you're carrying
something this valuable around,
you've gotta act like what
you've got isn't worth anything.
Hey, you!
Excuse me.
You better watch it, buddy.
Anyway, when you've
got something... Huh?
It's gone.
What is?
[Kogoro yelling] Arrrgh!
That little punk lifted it.
[Kogoro] You idiots. Don't
just stand there. Go after him.
[Juukichi, Daikichi] Yes, Sir.
We only had it
'cause we gambled.
Come on, you guys,
just give it up, will ya?
I ain't givin' up nothing.
It's hard to fight
on an empty stomach.
[Juukichi] I couldn't
find him anywhere.
[Daikichi] Me either, Boss.
There's no sign of him.
You morons! Are you guys trying
to ruin my reputation? [yelling]
If the boss
finds out about this,
cutting off all my fingers
won't make up for it.
[Shinsuke gasping]
I don't believe it!
[crickets chirping]
[hurried footsteps]
Hey! Where the hell are you,
you little punk?
Get your ass out here!
Hey, does a young guy live here?
[O-hatsu] You people...
You barge into a stranger's home
without even asking.
Have you ever heard of
something called manners?
Besides, there are no young men
here. I have no son.
I'll have to ask you to leave.
[coughing profusely]
Our apologies.
[door sliding shut]
[Fuu] Any luck?
[Jin] He's not here.
[Mugen] Must have
been a bogus tip.
[Fuu] Oh.
[Mugen] We're gonna go take
another look around the place.
Huh?
You can keep watch over there.
What? You mean all by myself?!
Yes.
Good luck.
Wait a second!
[sighing]
[women flirting, men talking]
Hey, this is the genuine
article. Shinsuke are you nuts?
What the hell are you doing
with stuff like this?
I need the dough.
Huh?
Well, tell you what...
For a seventy percent cut,
I'll fence it for you.
Huh? Seventy percent?! No way!
Whatever you do with it
will be illegal you know.
Besides, how would a rookie
like you know where to go
or have the funds
for something like this, huh?
Yeah, all right.
Come back tomorrow.
I'll have all the details
worked out by then.
[owl hooting, crickets chirping]
[wind chime ringing]
[crickets chirping,
distant bird call]
[door sliding open]
Shinsuke!
[Shinsuke]
What are you still doing up?
It's so late. Were you
out working all night?
[Shinsuke] Something like that.
If this new job works out
it'll make me a lot of money.
Then I'll be able
to buy you better medicine.
Listen, two men were
here about an hour ago.
They were looking for you.
Huh?
Why, Shinsuke?
Who were those men?
How should I know?
Then why were they trying
to find y-- [coughing]
Hush! Now don't overexert
yourself. Go to sleep.
Shinsuke, you aren't
doing anything...?
Doing what?
You aren't doing anything that
would make you ashamed to
look people in the eye, are you?
'Course not. Me? I would never
do anything like that.
Look, you don't have
to worry about me.
You just worry
about your health.
[Mugen] Hey!
See him?
[Fuu] Nope! Uh-uh.
Nobody showed up.
Huh?
Welp, that's that.
There was a stable
a little ways back.
[Jin] We'll spend
the night there.
[O-hatsu] Who are you?
[Fuu] Oh! Uh, I'm sorry!
That's alright. So, are you
Shinsuke's girlfriend?
Huh? Oh, well, I, ah...
[O-hatsu] I see.
I know what happens when
a boy reaches a certain age.
Uh...
MMMmmm! It's so good!
[laughing, coughing]
[O-hatsu] I've never seen
anyone so ecstatic
about eating
dried sweet potatoes.
Hmm? Oh, sorry.
[O-hatsu]  If you like them that
much, please, eat all you want.
Thank you, ma'am!
You know, I'm still amazed
that Shinsuke found
such a nice girlfriend.
Oh, that. Actually--
You see,
his father left long ago,
and I've never been
in good health,
and that's made life
difficult for him.
At his age, his parents should
be taking care of him,
not the other way around.
Well, enough of that.
I'm glad he's doing things
normal for a boy his age.
I was wondering.
Has he talked to you
about what he's planning to do?
Huh? A-About what?
[O-hatsu] Oh, n-nevermind.
I-It's just that, well,
something seems
to be bothering him.
He hasn't been himself lately.
[Shinsuke] I give her the
medicine everyday, doctor.
Just the way you told me to,
but she doesn't ever
seem to get better.
[Doctor] I never said
it would cure her.
Considering her condition, about
the best you could hope for
is that it'll help her regain
some of her strength.
There's nothing else
I could do for her.
You can't afford to get anything
that would be more effective,
I'm afraid.
There are better medicines
available of course,
korean ginseng for example,
but it costs nearly
a hundred times as much
as the medicine
she's taking now.
Do you understand?
[Shinsuke breathing harshly]
I'm sorry, but I am
running a business here.
[people talking]
[Kogoro] Hey you!
Is your name Hikoichi?
Huh? What do you want?
There's a little something
I'm looking for.
What makes you think I got it?
[Kogoro] I happen
to know it's too big
for a small-time fence
like you to handle.
Yeah?
Stop playin' dumb.
I know who you
met with yesterday.
Your pal the pickpocket.
Huh? Who's that?
[menacing laughter]
Huh? Wh-Whaddya doin'?
[Kogoro laughing]
In a little while you're gonna
tell us everything you know.
I told ya, I don't
know the guy. Honest.
[screaming]
Ahhhh! No! Stop! Put it out!
You see? You're a lot
more talkative now.
Hey you!
Hmm?
Look at me.
You remember who I am?
Why, should I?
I'm the girl whose
purse you stole, you jerk.
You aren't going
anywhere, buddy.
Let go.
Ha! The hell I will.
Damn you.
[Juukichi] Hey there.
[Kogoro] You're a hard man to
find. You've been a naughty boy.
You should return
what doesn't belong to you.
[Fuu] Who the heck are you guys?
Be careful missy,
just stay out of my way
and don't even think about
screaming for help.
--[screaming] Help me somebody!
--Huh? You crazy bitch.
[Fuu screaming]
Somebody help me!
Boss!
[Kogoro] You son of a--
[Daikichi] Why you little...!
[distant whistle blowing]
What's going on?
The heat! We're outta here.
[whistle blowing]
[people gasping]
[Policeman 2]
What's going on here?
You! What's this all about?
[Shinsuke] Damn it.
Back off.
Don't come any closer.
If you do I'll cut her throat,
I swear I will!
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
[crowd talking excitedly]
Drop the knife
and give yourself up!
Kiss my ass! I'm warning you,
one step closer and she dies.
You got that?
You hear me out there?
All of you back off right now
or this girl is gonna bite it!
Oh, you're bleeding--
You keep quiet.
Yeah, but--
It's no big deal. Move!
[crowd talking]
What do you want us
to do now boss?
Should we storm the place
and grab the guy?
You nuts. Use your head
for once, dimwit.
There are too many cops around.
If we tried to get the stuff
back they'd spot us for sure.
Does it hurt much?
Nah, it's nuthin' all right?
That look on your face says
otherwise. Let me take a look.
You don't get it, do ya?
I'll kill you if I have to.
You understand what I'm sayin'?
By the way I met
your mother yesterday.
Huh?
I imagine it would
break her heart
if she knew you were a thief.
Didya' ...tell her
I'm a pickpocket?
Of course not, how could I?
I wouldn't want to make
a good mom like that
worry about her son.
Don't talk like you know
what I'm going through.
But I do.
You should be grateful
that your mother's alive.
[Shinsuke] Where are
your parents anyways?
[Fuu] My father hasn't
been around for a long time,
and my mother died a year ago.
When she was alive I used to
disobey her all the time.
Make her worry about me
all the time.
All the things I really
wanted to tell her,
that I wanted to ask her,
and now...
now I'll never be able to.
What I need is money.
Huh?
So I tried to find a job, but
none of the legitimate places
would hire a stupid kid like me.
The only people who say money
doesn't matter are the ones who
have more money
than they'll ever need.
Without money, you can't even
buy good medicine.
The kind that heals the sick.
And that's the ugly truth
of how the world works.
[Policeman 1, outside]
Listen, you criminal!
This is your final warning.
If you don't come out and
surrender to the authorities
before sundown, we'll come in
and take you by force.
You got that?
So what's the deal?
Well you see,
there's a girl who's being
held hostage in there.
There she is!
[Mugen] That little...!
Guess that explains why
we haven't seen her all day.
Look.
Huh?
Stay away! Back off!
[Mugen] Aha! Found you,
you pickpocken' bastard!
Stay back.
You can't go in there.
I've been lookin'
for this guy all day!
Give me a break will ya!
You'd better
surrender right now.
You've got
nowhere left to run to.
Forget about it.
I can't let myself be arrested.
Not now.
Then I'll distract them
while you run away.
Huh?
Once I've got
everybody's attention
you should be
able to sneak out.
[Shinshuke] You'd do that?
[Kogoro] Not if I can help it.
This time you're not
gonna get away [chuckling]
We don't have time
to mess around.
Now hand over the stuff
that you stole from me.
Outta the way!
What the hell? Who is that guy?
What an idiot.
Huh?
[hurried footsteps,
Mugen growling]
Well we meet again.
Whoever you are, get the hell
out of here. Get movin'!
Hold on! Let the boy go, Mugen.
Huh?
Police! Clear the way!
[Daikichi] What now, boss?
Enough of this!
Kill everyone! Kill 'em all!
[Shinsuke] Here. Take it!
[Kogoro] Ow!
Police! Clear the way!
Clear the way! Police!
[mayhem]
Now I'm gettin' pissed off.
[Fuu] That way!
[howling]
The opium is mine again! Ah!
[Shinsuke] Hey.
If I ever see you again,
I promise I'll repay you
for what you did today.
Until that day,
don't forget me!
♪ hip hop music ♪
Same to you!
Don't forget me either.
After him!
He's getting away! [whistling]
[whispering] Go, go!
[Policemen] There he is!
Stop in the name of the law!
Hold it. You're under arrest.
Back off! Stay away!
Stay away!
[sound fading]
[wind blowing]
♪ solo piano ♪
[door sliding open]
[O-hatsu] Oh, it's you.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing. Nothing at all.
He isn't here.
He hasn't come home.
Did something happen to him?
You worry too much. I came by
to say hi, that's all.
Well, I'll see you later.
[O-hatsu] He isn't ever
coming back, is he?
He isn't, is he?
[Fuu gasping]
[O-hatsu] It's all right.
Deep down, I knew
that something like this
would happen someday.
He did things
he shouldn't have done.
Things he knew were bad.
And now he's paid the price.
And that's why he-- why he's--
[Fuu] You're wrong!
He was-- Shinsuke was--
[wind blowing]
♪ End Theme ♪