♪ Opening Theme ♪
[Fuu] It's been too hard
to say goodbye,
so I'm going the rest
of the way alone.
I want you to know that
I really enjoyed the talk
we had around the
campfire last night.
Before I knew it,
I found myself wishing
that this journey
could go on forever.
But then all of a sudden,
I got scared.
When I thought of the
three of us splitting up,
I started to panic.
Maybe I've been relying on you
guys too much this whole time.
I wasn't sure if I'd be
able to make it on my own
once this journey was over.
So I started giving
it a lot of thought.
And I decided that
I needed to make
this last leg
of the trip alone.
On the north cape, there's
a house alone by itself.
You should go there
and look for him.
You should go quickly;
there's not much time.
Thank you.
Thank you!
[Kariya] And now, although it
pains me to say this,
I have to insist that
you two die right here.
[Mugen] You're takin'
us on by yourself?
You sure got a big
pair on ya, pal.
Come. I hope that you
don't disappoint me.
[Umanosuke] I want him to know
exactly how we feel.
Wh-What are you talking about?
I'm saying...
You're standing in your grave.
Well, this'll be fun!
[yelling]
[Kariya] Interesting.
You utilize erratic movements
that prevent anyone
from predicting them.
Huh?
[Kariya] But you must learn to
make use of your intellect
in the martial arts.
By relying solely upon
instinct and reflex,
you involuntarily reveal
your limitations to your enemy.
[Mugen] Quit talkin' to me like
you're all hot shit!
[Mugen yelling]
[Kariya] I would
very much like to see
your Muju Shin Kenjutsu style.
Show me the student able
to take down Enshiro Mariya.
How is it that you
know about that?
I see.
You're with the shogunate.
[Fuu gasping]
[forceful wind]
[footsteps]
[punch]
Bastard.
[Mugen] You're toast.
[glasses breaking]
[Mugen] Aww, shit.
[Denkibou laughing maniacally]
Mu-gen.
Who the hell wants me now?
[Denkibou] Mugen. [laugh]
Guess what, we got the girl.
Come to the church,
the one on the island.
Bye bye.
Say what? Can't ya see
we're kinda busy here?
If you don't hurry up,
bad things might happen to her.
I can't promise that he's not
carving her into little pieces
right now!
Don't piss me off!
Go.
Huh?
Go on.
I'll handle this.
No, you go!
[Fuu] You know, I don't
really wanna think about
stuff like that right now.
If you did, then that
jerk Mugen would...
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
Take care of Fuu.
[Kariya] Please decide which
of you is going to fight me.
Well just don't
let him kill ya.
You and me got
unfinished business.
Go!
[Boatman] Yes, Sir.
[Kariya] I hope
we can finally fight
without any distractions now.
How do you know the Mugu style?
[Kariya] Fate is
a fascinating thing.
If you hadn't killed Mariya,
the Muju style would
be something that
I alone am the master of.
So then, you're Kagetoki Kariya.
[Jin] You want to turn
Muju Shin Kenjutsu
into a band of assassins?
You're asking me to walk
a path of darkness.
No I am not.
But this is the
only choice I have.
[Mariya] There's no dishonor
in serving Master Kariya.
In fact, it's the same as
serving the shogunate itself.
[Jin] You're wrong.
If you do this, it'll no
longer be a martial art.
[Mariya] The period of the
Warring States is over.
This country is at peace now.
There is no need for our
style of martial arts,
one that teaches how to kill.
Martial arts schools
are in decline.
We must accept that.
Please, Jin, endure this.
So then, you were the--
[Kariya] Indeed I was.
[Mariya] You're ordering me
to kill my own pupil?
But he's the one I am planning
to pass my dojo onto.
You cannot ask me to do this.
[Kariya]
As you may have realized,
I was the one who
put him up to it.
Your skills have
grown well, Jin.
Master.
[Mariya screaming]
[Kariya] Regardless of the past,
there's no escaping that
it's your destiny
to die by my hand.
Since it is destined,
let's begin this.
I'd like to see what the
Hand of God is all about.
Gladly.
I've been sitting idle
now for far longer
than I would have liked.
[Boatman yelling]
I shouldn't do it.
I really shouldn't.
What's this... you again?
He made me promise that
I wouldn't do anything to you
until I got to the church.
But it's so hard.
I wanna kill 'im so bad.
And there he is,
right there under my nose
and it's driving me crazy!
I don't think
I can stop myself.
I can't. I just can't wait.
[screaming]
For what?
For what purpose
would a man like you
stoop to becoming
the shogunate's dog?
[Kariya] Hmph. You really think
that a man can live by
his sword skills alone
in this day and age?
So then, you're saying
that you have a lord
worth risking your life for?
You know as well as I that
the only thing any lord values
is self-preservation.
Honor means nothing to them.
There are no lords out there
worth laying down one's life.
[Kariya] You're right.
However, I am far from
being any man's puppet.
They think they have used me,
but it is I who have used them.
The age of the samurai will most
likely be coming to an end soon.
And although I
hate to admit this,
it's become painfully apparent
I was born into the wrong era.
As were you.
What'sa matter? That Ryukyu
style of yours not workin'?
Doesn't work so well
in tight spots, does it?
[Kariya] You're
an excellent swordsman.
It's been quite some time since
I've enjoyed myself this much.
Your skills are almost
on par with my own.
It will be by a razor thin
margin, but you will lose.
[Jin thinking]
His speed is amazing.
And I can't find a single
opening in his defense.
There's just one move
that will end this.
[panting]
[Voice] A samurai who
smells of sunflowers?
Sunflowers don't have a scent.
So wouldn't that mean that this
samurai you're searching for
doesn't even exist?
[Fuu] No, you're wrong.
I know you're wrong!
[Umanosuke] Just hang in there
a tiny bit longer.
You'll be put out of
your misery soon enough.
[Fuu] You do realize that
you guys are just
wasting your time with this.
Mugen's the worst.
The last thing he'd care
about is saving a hostage.
[Umanosuke] Oh really?
You don't say.
Well, if that's true
then I may as well kill
the hostage right now.
[Umanosuke] I guess I don't
have to kill you.
There's always the option
of leaving you only half dead...
[Fuu grunting]
Just so long as you're
still a little bit alive.
[Fuu grunting]
[unsteady footsteps]
Mugen.
[Mugen, tired] Sorry, Buddy.
Time to give her back now.
[Umanosuke] Oh I'm so happy now.
We finally meet at last.
So who the hell are you people?
[Umanosuke]
Don't play dumb with me.
Huh?
If you have forgotten us, fine,
but the three of us
will remember you
until the end of our
miserable lives.
Allow me to help.
Perhaps this will
jog your memory.
Before we met, my brothers
and I were well known
around the Satsuma area.
But that all changed.
We happened to be in
charge of a raw sugar ship.
Maybe you remember that night,
when you and Mukuro robbed it.
My oldest brother ended up
like this thanks to you.
When we returned to Satsuma,
they blamed us for the raid
and drove us out of town.
And that wiped out our chances
of working for the government.
The only thing that
keeps us going now
is the desire to hunt
you down and kill you,
you worthless piece of shit.
Y'know about that
ugly brother of yours...
Huh?!
[Mugen] I just sent his ass
to the bottom of the ocean.
You bastard!
You don't get it, do you?
Whether this little
girl lives or dies
doesn't mean a damn thing
to either one of us.
[Mugen] Shut up.
Look, I'll put down my sword,
but in return, you gotta
let go of the girl.
Well do it then.
But Mugen.
[Mugen] Get outta here.
You gotta go meet
your sunflower dude.
I'm gonna take care of this guy.
[Fuu] But Mugen,
I can't leave you.
[Mugen] Don't gimme that crap.
Listen to me.
I'm gonna be pissed off if we
came all this way for nothin'.
Get lost.
I can't. What if they--
I ain't gonna die.
Have some faith in me, will ya?
Oh Mugen.
[Mugen] Beat it.
Go on!
[screaming] I said go!
[Umanosuke]
You almost made me cry.
Are you really gonna throw
your life away for some girl?
Very well, but I think
I should tell you
that I intend to
kill you slowly.
[Mugen grunting]
Oopsie! Did I cut a little
too deeply that time?
Don't give up on me now,
I'm just starting to have fun.
[wheezing] You bastard.
♪ End Theme ♪