♪ Opening Theme ♪
[record scratching]
♪ One, two, three ♪
[Fuu] What the hell
do you think you're doing?
What about the promise you made
not to kill each other?
[Mugen] Guess no matter
how hard we try...
...fate's gonna keep
throwing us back together.
[men yelling]
[women screaming]
[Fuu] Wait a minute. Hey!
Hey!
Osuzu, let's get you
out of here. Hurry!
Come on. What are you
waiting for?
Sosuke...
I'm sorry.
[chain clattering]
[Rikiei laughing]
Bastard! How dare you
do this to her.
What are you gonna
do about it boy?
Damn you.
That's enough.
[Rikiei] How predictable.
I knew you two would
show up sooner or later.
What's up with this shit?
You guys can't kill him. I'm
the one that's gonna kill him.
Get the hell out of my way.
[pained screaming]
Hey, he's one of ours.
Are you nuts?
[men wailing]
Hold it.
It's too dangerous.
That woman's counting on you,
and you can't help her
if you're dead.
I know!
Get back here you asshole!
[Ishimatsu] You oughta get
rid of him right away, Boss.
The man's a lunatic.
Enemy or ally,
he kills whoever
gets in his way.
[Rikiei] He served his purpose.
Huh?
Seeing his strength in action
has inspired our men
to set higher goals
for themselves.
[Ishimatsu] But-- But, Boss...
[Jin] The only way you'll be
able to rescue her is by
crushing the Nagatomi Gang.
Their boss pays for
their loyalty,
but not enough to make
them willing to risk
their lives for him. And once
he's out of the picture,
they won't be a gang anymore.
Just a bunch of frightened,
disorganized thugs.
That possibility by itself makes
our endeavor a worthy one.
[Sosuke crying]
[Hostess] Damn,
what a terrible day.
If business doesn't
pick up soon, we'll go broke.
You girls had better
start making some money.
Do you understand?
Let's find a way
out of here, huh?
It's pointless.
Huh?
Because... I can't leave.
But why?
Because my father's in debt.
I have to pay it back
by working here.
Yeah, but you don't want this.
I don't get it. Why should this
debt be your responsibility?
You had nothing to do with it.
Because we are family.
You've got a family too,
don't you?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to hurt your feelings.
Uh-uh.
[Fuu] Sometimes families
can be a real pain, huh?
What the hell do you want?
Drawing your sword
is no longer necessary.
At this point,
your presence will suffice.
The hell with that!
Did you forget why I'm here?
To kick ass and
win your fights for you.
Listen, there are two kinds
of people who inhabit the world.
The rulers and the followers,
who at times upset the natural
order of things by
disposing of their rulers.
But not this ruler. With
you under my command,
they wouldn't dare, which
preserves the natural order.
So the power you're talking
about is the power to control
other people.
Is that what you're saying?
Yes. What's your point?
My point is that's all
a bunch of bullshit.
I don't want to rule
or have anyone rule me.
Where are you going?
If you stay you can have
whatever you want and
do whatever you want.
You can't walk away
from an offer like that.
[Mugen] I don't believe in
anyone but me and what I can do.
See ya.
You arrogant bastard.
You think you can
treat me like garbage
and just walk away--
[Mugen] If you send someone
after me, do me a favor:
send the toughest
mofo you can find.
So what's up?
You want a piece of me too?
I'm the same. I have faith
in myself and my sword,
nothing else.
Hm?
When I left Boss Kawara's
gang I thought to myself,
by using my skills and my
strength, I can get whatever
I want out of life. But the
world doesn't work that way.
There are times when you
have to agree with people,
even when you think they're
wrong. Or do something,
even though
you think it's crazy.
[Mugen] What a load
of horse piss.
What's that?
Hey, you can make
all the excuses you want,
but you're the one who decided
how to live your life.
[Nagatomi 4] Come on,
do something sexy damn it.
[Nagatomi 3] Yeah, why don't
you give us a peek of those
fine looking legs of yours?
[creepy laughing]
[Fuu] Jeez, what' your problem?
You girls better stop
acting so high and mighty.
You two are whores now.
You got that?
Now get the hell over here
and attract some customers.
Hey, let her go.
Quiet!
Hate your old man,
not me. He got you in here.
No.
Woo, that really turns me on.
[dirty chuckling]
[Nagatomi 4] You know,
I might buy some of you myself.
[more chuckling]
[hurried footsteps]
Maybe--
[sudden impact]
Hey, what the hell
do you think you're doing?
Blood. It's blood.
It's a raid!
We're under attack!
Oh, Sosuke.
[door sliding open]
Ishimatsu, you bastard!
How dare you show
your face around here.
You don't give a damn
how rude you are, do you?
What is it?
It concerns your successor.
He stabbed
one of our young men.
Huh?
[Ishimatsu] Our men weren't
prepared to defend themselves.
They were going about their
business with no intention
of spilling a drop of blood.
How will you make amends
for the man that was killed?
An arm, even two,
won't be nearly enough.
I'll handle this personally.
[Kawara Gang 1] Boss.
[Kawara Gang 2]
You gotta let us go with you.
[Kawara Gang 3] Please, Boss.
I'll be fine.
[Kawara Gang 2] Boss.
What have you done, Sosuke?
I'm responsible for his actions.
In that case,
I have a proposal to make.
I believe that bloodshed is
unnecessary to resolve this.
So let's settle things
in the yakuza way by gambling.
If you win, I'll return
your son, but in exchange,
I take control
of your territory.
You'll lose almost everything,
but it's better than
losing your son, now isn't it?
[Heitaro] Very well.
[Sosuke] Huh?
If I win, you will spare my son.
If I lose, one death will atone
for the other and I will never
see my son alive again.
[Heitaro] On one condition.
[Rikiei] What's that?
In the interest of fairness,
my gang will provide
the dice roller for the game.
The Nagatomi Gang
will provide the dice.
You're sure?
He knows what it means
to be yakuza.
Outlaws must always be prepared
to pay the ultimate price.
I'm looking forward to our game.
[thundering]
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
You promised you
wouldn't kill each other.
That little bitch.
[Rikiei chuckling]
That dumb bastard.
Soon his territory
will be mine legally.
I don't understand.
All I need to do is lose,
which I'll prearrange.
Give him back his son
and take his territory.
Yeah, but what about
the dice roller?
We agreed to use theirs.
Not to worry. Their dice
roller's gonna be a no show.
[Kawara Gang 1]
It doesn't make any sense, Boss.
You lose even if you win.
[Kawara Gang 2] It's to
their advantage either way.
[Heitaro] Nevertheless,
atonement must be made.
But Boss, if you lose
then Sosuke will have to die.
Please, Boss.
Don't do this.
[Fuu] A big wager?
[Prostitute] Yeah, I heard a
couple of guys talking about it.
They said the
Nagatomis and Kawaras
are putting their
gangs on the line.
What do you think will happen
to us if the Kawaras win?
Why? You think they're
gonna let us go free?
Don't be so naïve.
There's gonna be a gang war?
[Prostitute] You got it honey.
[Jin] For yesterday, Old Man.
[Shop Owner] You don't want
to catch a cold, do you?
Thank you.
Where do you think you're going?
[Heitaro] In the yakuza,
confrontation is
part of our lives.
Over the years I've killed
countless men toward whom
I've harbored no ill will.
The price I've paid is the loss
of precious friends and family.
Yes, I've seen more than
enough blood in my time.
So now this gang exists
for one reason.
For the sake of the young men
who are its members.
In the end,
we're simply outlaws.
Human beings who can't get by
in respectable human society.
There have always
been people cast aside
by the rest of the world.
Many years ago I realized people
like that have difficult lives.
They need looking after
by someone responsible like me.
But when Ishimatsu
joined up with the Nagatomis,
I thought to myself,
"Perhaps this is the right time.
Perhaps I should make
the decision to step down."
I admit that with skills such
as yours you might very well
be able to kill Rikiei. But
that would solve nothing.
It would just lead
to a new round of reprisals.
So please let me handle this
matter in my own way, alright?
This is for Sosuke.
[women chatting charmingly]
[Osuzu] Hey, Fuu,
what are you doing?
[Fuu] Can't you tell?
Instead of attracting customers,
I'm scaring them away.
If we don't get any
customers, we'll be fired
and we can leave, right?
Oh?
Don't give me that "oh"
stuff. You do it too.
[Guest] Wow,
what a perfect face!
Huh?
You're just what
I was looking for.
I want you to look at me
like that and then tell me
I'm a naughty boy.
You gotta be kidding, right?
[Guest] That's the look.
Just like that.
Yeah, you're my kind of girl.
He he he he!
[squeak]
Uh?
[Guest yowling]
That hurts!
Let go you little--
The vase.
Go away!
[shattering]
[men and women murmuring]
Sir, is everything--?
[Nagatomi 3] She ran away!
One, two, one, two...
Excuse me. Where's
the gambling house?
Two, one, two, one, two, one...
Here.
Well, get in.
I am called Oryu. I was asked
to come here today to act
as your witness.
It is an honor to serve you.
Where is the
bodyguard you hired?
He quit the gang.
I imagine he's
left town by now.
Both parties please
present your wagers.
[Oryu] There will be one throw,
and I ask that
there be no delays.
[door slamming, women shrieking]
Where's the girl?
She, um... She ran away.
Ran away?
Freakin' moron.
I approve.
Boss Kawara,
your dice roller please.
[Nagatomi 2] Doesn't look
like he's arrived yet.
He's quite late. I wonder
what could be keeping him.
Where's the dice roller?
Damn it. Of all
the nights to be late.
One, two, one, two, whoa.
Hi, there.
This the gambling house?
She's here!
Hurry up, will ya?
Come on. This way.
Here she is.
[Stylist] Hurry up
and get changed.
[Stylist] There isn't
a second to lose.
[Fuu] What the hell do
you think you're--aah!
Since your roller isn't here,
I suppose we'll have to
call in one of our substitutes.
Wait. Not quite yet.
Just one more minute.
[Kawara Gang 1] Boss,
the dice roller's here.
Huh?
What's that?
[awe and whispering]
Uh?
What are you doing here?
[smacking sound, Fuu gasping]
[Fuu thinking]
It's like a little vase.
Let's play!
What do we do?
Now I leave me fate
in the hands of the heavens.
What do you think, Boss?
[Oryu] Very well.
You may begin.
[Fuu] Are both parties
ready now?
Looks that way to me.
In they go.
Now, place your bets gentlemen.
[swallowing]
Han.
Hmm.
Chou.
Play!
[Oryu] Two, five. Han.
The Nagatomi Gang is recognized
as the winner of this match.
I concede defeat.
[Heitaro] As an outlaw,
I am honor-bound
to complete this
business. But know this:
What I lost, I never wanted
to win in the first place.
[Rikiei] What?
[Heitaro] I will not force my
adopted children to suffer
under the likes of you.
Nor will I surrender
my territory to you.
[Rikiei growling]
What is this?
I agreed to give you
a life to atone for the
life that was taken.
[Heitaro] I atone
for that life with my own.
[sudden impact]
Father, no!
Father!
[Rikiei laughing]
How pathetic. What a useless
display of outdated melodrama.
All this for nothing.
Nothing?
My dad gave his life
to honor the code
of the yakuza to the end.
[Sosuke] But you're not yakuza!
You're nothing but thugs!
I like being a thug.
Enjoy your territory kid,
'cause it won't be yours long.
[Rikiei] You fool. You threw
your life away for nothing.
Careful now. Hold it right there
mister hotshot bodyguard.
Don't even think about it.
[door exploding open,
man screaming]
Huh?
You're back.
What are you doing here?
[Mugen] I noticed nobody
was coming after me.
So I came after
you guys instead.
[Rikiei] Don't you care
if this kid lives or dies?
Nah, can't really say I do.
♪ samba drums ♪
Shit.
Hm?
Ishimatsu, where you going?
You gotta get back in there
and kill those guys.
[sudden impact]
You never trusted me
because I used to be
a member of the Kawara Gang.
The other guys either.
You never trusted anyone.
The only thing you ever really
had faith in was money.
Ishimatsu.
I finally saw him
for what he was.
[Sosuke] This was my father's.
[Jin] He asked me
to give it to you.
Ishimatsu, will you
come back to us someday?
[Ishimatsu] Sosuke.
I'm certain it's what
my father would have done.
Thanks for the offer,
but I want to keep honoring
the outlaw code.
I don't want to turn into
one of those thugs
you were talking about.
Once I've atoned for what
I've done, I'll be happy
to take you up on that offer.
We need to settle things.
Huh?
[Osuzu] Thanks so much
for all your help.
[Fuu] Oh, forget it.
I'm really happy for you, Osuzu.
Goodbye.
[Sosuke] Hey, bodyguard!
Come back here
one of these days.
[Jin] Yeah.
But we gotta find the
Sunflower Samurai first, okay?
[Mugen] Problem is,
I don't really know
how to hold back, you know?
I understand.
[wind blowing]
[steel falling]
♪ End Theme ♪