♪ Opening Theme ♪
♪ biwa melody ♪
[Biwa Minstrel] Betwixt the
time of then and now,
the three wandering
companions once again
set out upon their quest:
The journey in search
of the samurai who
smells of sunflowers.
Mugen, Jin, and Fuu
follow the path that fate
hath laid down for them.
O'er glistening rivers,
passed crashing waves,
till at long last,
the weary travelers reach Edo.
[cicadas chirping,
people chattering]
[footsteps]
[record scratching]
[Fuu] Look at that.
We just got to Edo, and our
luck's looking up already.
[Mugen] Whoa, it's all
you can eat for free?
[Fuu] Not only that,
we're gonna win this thing.
The three of us are
always half starved anyways,
so this must be in our destiny.
If it's free,
then we don't need to win.
Alright, then.
Who's next in line?
Huh?
The registration fee
is one shu.
No way. I thought it was free.
If we had money,
we wouldn't be here.
Well, I could take something
worth that amount, I suppose.
If you win,
you get the whole pot.
[Mugen] Got no choice.
[Fuu] Fine, whatever. Let's get
this thing started, okay?
How 'bout your
samurai friend over here?
I'm sorry,
but I can't simply hand over
the embodiment
of a warrior's soul to-- Hey.
Relax. Once we win,
you'll get them right back.
Hold on a minute.
Think of it as handing them
over for safe keeping.
Ain't no way in the world
we can lose as hungry as we are.
Uh?
[Fuu] Okay, let's go
stuff our faces.
[record scratching]
[Announcer] And they're off!
The munching has commenced.
It's the annual
big eater contest.
The games of
gastronomic gobbling.
Once again, big eaters
from all over the city
have come out in full force.
The rules are extremely simple.
The contestant
who eats the most wins
and takes home
all the entry fees.
Our contestants are eating
eel rice bowls made
with plenty of that
main ingredient
that Edo kitchens
are famous for.
And of course, I, Ichieimon,
Edo's number one gossip,
will be your announcer.
With me today
is Buddhist priest, Ingen,
known for his catchphrase,
"To hell with vegetarianism!"
Thank you. It's an honor.
[Announcer] The contestants
are now underway.
The one to watch out for this
year would have to be Izumi,
the winner from
the year before last.
She's been training hard
and looks to be in top form.
Wouldn't you say, Father Ingen?
Yes, but her specialty
has always been sweets.
We don't know how long
she can keep this up.
Bring me another.
[Announcer] And there he goes.
The odds
on favored to win today.
--[Contestant] Another!
--The man whose stomach
--knows no bounds,
Sonosuke, from Mujina.
I'd expect nothing less
from last year's champion.
--[Contestants] Another!
--When a contestant's ready
to give up,
we ask that the eater
--[Contestants] Another!
--stop chewing and put
their hands together
in the traditional
gesture of surrender.
Would you look at that?
We already have a contestant
throwing in the towel.
We're barely underway
and the man's given up.
Why in the world
did this bespectacled man
even bother to come today?
That's enough.
I am ashamed.
Please win my swords for me.
[record scratching]
[Announcer] The contestants
are dropping like flies.
This is a game
of survival of the fullest.
Who will be
the last one eating?
You must not consider stopping.
My swords are on the line.
Now swallow, damn it.
[all sounds fading
except white noise]
[crashing]
[Announcer] Holy cow!
Another one bites the dust.
[sounds back] We're down to
the final three contestants.
Sonosuke, the man with
the bottomless stomach.
Izumi, the queen of sweets.
And a newcomer to the contest,
a mysterious giant of a man.
Wait a minute, I missed one.
There's one more. We have one
more contestant I overlooked.
And what's more, she seems
to be a petite, young girl.
All four of them have begun
their twenty-second bowl.
Twenty-two
was last year's record.
What's this? Have the
queen of sweets chopsticks
stopped moving?
An official has gone over
for verification.
Could she possibly be...?
He's giving the signal.
She's done for the day.
[Sonosuke thinking] It can't be.
How could I lose?
I won't accept defeat.
I refuse to accept defeat.
[Sonosuke groaning]
[Announcer]
This is unbelievable!
Last year's champion, Sonosuke,
is down for the count.
Bring me another. Another!
Another!
Eh? This girl's stomach
is a cosmos unto itself.
It's connected to
the void of the universe.
[buzzing]
[Announcer] The unthinkable
has finally occurred.
These two newcomers are locked
in a one-on-one battle.
What's more, they've done
what no eater has done before
and broken the
twenty-seven bowl barrier.
We have finally gotten
the personal data
on these two contestants.
Hmm... The young girl's name
is Fuu. Age fifteen.
And the name of the large man
is... Wait, I can't read this.
This is unprecedented
in the history of gluttony.
Unless my eyes deceive me,
these two have
picked up their pace even more.
The cooks are having trouble
keeping up with them.
Shut the hell up, will ya?
[Announcer] How much food
can a human being eat?
One has to ask, "Where have we
been? Where are we going?"
Their forms are likened
to the gods themselves.
This is truly awe inspiring.
[Ingen] It may very well
be that what we are
witnessing here
today is a birth.
The birth of the next stage
of human stomach evolution.
[buzzing]
Stupid fly.
[Announcer]
It's over! She's given up!
--[Fuu] Huh?
--She's made the signal
of defeat. It's over!
Here in this culinary colosseum,
this holy war of the stomach,
our winner is the
large mystery man.
I win! Yay!
[record scratching]
This can't be happening.
Why the hell did you
put your hands together?
You were winning.
There was a fly in my face.
[Mugen] Who the hell
are you anyway?
[Fuu] Get off my case.
[Jin] My swords.
[Jouji, thick accent] Hi,
everybody! How is you this day?
Huh?
Those swords are mine.
Fat face little girl
you put up good fight.
You are girl ninja?
That's ridiculous.
Of course I'm not a ninja.
[Jouji] No? you should have
said so in first place.
Do I look like a ninja?
Why would I even need
to point that out?
Hey, Fuu. Is it just
me, or does this guy
talk kind of weird?
Oh, I'd say he's
talking pretty weird.
[Mugen] Do his eyes
look blue to you?
[Fuu] They are! They're blue!
[laughing] Eyes not blue.
[Mugen] And check out
the red hair.
[Fuu] Yeah, it is red.
Allow me to introduce.
I am Jouji.
I am Japanese,
born and raised.
Do you not believe
I speak truth?
[Jin] It doesn't matter,
but those swords
you're carrying are my life.
I'd appreciate you
giving them back.
No vay.
[Mugen] Didn't give it
much thought.
[Jin] I don't
expect them for free.
[Jouji] Then you vork for them?
[Jin] What's that?
[Jouji] I vant to
do Edo sightseeing.
You be tour guide. I vill
give swords back as tanks.
Sorry. Forget about it.
You're shit out of luck.
We don't know
nothing about Edo--
We'll take you
wherever you want.
Hey. Hold on a minute.
If you've got time for that,
what about the sunflower--
A few years back I used to be
known as the Edo Tour Map.
Freakin' liar.
[record scratching]
♪ hip hop music ♪
[Policeman 1] We need your help.
We've received reports
that a European
is wandering around
in disguise.
Have you seen
anybody like that?
Huh? A real European?
I'm not sure.
I don't think so.
I haven't seen anybody
like that around here.
[record scratching]
[Jouji] So, this is
famous Kaminari Man, ya?
No. Actually this is--
Kaminari Man.
Impressive. Ooh-ya!
Come on.
Help me out here, will you?
Wow. Kaminari Man.
I never knew that.
That one's man number one,
and that one's man number two.
[Fuu] Wow.
[record scratching]
He-He-He-Here you are, Sir.
Oh, so now we eat
the Edo-style sushi, ya? Argh!
Are you always so loud?
Can't believe
they're eating again.
What the hell are
their stomachs made of?
[Jouji] Ah, that burns.
This is wabisabi, ya?
[Jin] No, actually it's called--
[Mugen] Forget about it.
It ain't worth it.
[record scratching]
A European? You're serious?
You really think he was here?
[Policeman 1] We got a tip that
there was a man
in the big eater competition
who fit that description.
[Announcer] Hm... Well, there
was a large man about this tall
who talked kind of funny.
Is that who you mean?
That's the one.
[Jouji] Yay!
Hammertoe! Yay, yay!
[Mugen] I swear. I can't believe
how much you two can eat.
[Fuu] You gotta be kidding. I
always have room for free food.
[Jin] It's nighttime already.
You must have seen
more than enough of Edo now.
No, ve not finished yet.
I vant to see more.
This is really good.
[Policeman 1] Listen up you
peasants. I want your attention.
We've received report
there may be a European
somewhere in this restaurant.
You lowlife scum
better not be hiding this man.
Harboring him makes
you an accomplice. That clear?
Huh?
[Mugen] When someone talks to me
like that, it sort of puts me
in a harboring kind of mood.
[Policeman 2] What's that?
[Policeman 1] What the hell
did you just say to me?
You get in our way
and you're gonna regret it.
Hey, you got some guts.
Some other time I might
respect you for that.
But right now,
I'm gonna ask you not to resist.
[Policeman 2] If I were you,
I'd apologize.
When someone talks to me like
that, it kind of pisses me off
and I want to resist even more.
Hey, give me that sword
on your back, will ya?
I no give me.
[Mugen] Huh?
This ain't no time
to be stingy, asshole.
That's the European
we've been looking for.
Get them! Arrest them all!
♪ hip hop music ♪
Let's go.
Huh?
Son of a bitch.
Where could they go?
Why do you always feel it's
necessary to stir things up?
Can't help myself. Guys like
that just put a bug up my ass.
Yeah? And what
happens if we can't
stay in Edo because of this?
Then we wouldn't be able to look
for the sunflower samurai. Ooh.
[record scratching]
[Jouji] Oh, traditional
Japanese beauty.
So this is
Ms. Beauty's house, ya?
Tell me, are all
Europeans idiots?
You do realize that
people are after you, right?
This is no time
to take in a play.
This is last. Me promise you.
Huh?
After we go see,
your katana swords I give back.
[Fuu moaning]
We've no choice.
Now hold on.
[kabuki music]
[cheering]
[Audience 1] Nakamuraya!
[Audience 2] Norieimon!
A radiant beauty.
You do know that's not a...
[gasping painfully]
This is person I love.
I go to see.
What do you mean "go see"?
Hey, hold on!
You think he knows
what he's doing?
[record scratching]
Is true? You are a man?
Huh?
Yeah, that's definitely
gotta be a guy.
You mean you
really didn't know?
No. Cannot be.
Hey, don't take it out on him.
Stop it. He didn't do anything.
Is good because...
...like man better.
Huh?
And you are just my type.
My kind of man.
[Jouji] I ask you favor.
Vill you listen to my story?
I lie to you when I tell you
before I am Japanese.
I am really from
far country called Holland.
♪ slow funk beat ♪
[Jouji] The Bible says, "Thou
shalt not lie with mankind."
In my country,
they treat me like a deviant.
Because of this,
I was very depressed.
And then, one day
I discovered a book.
The book of
Saikaku Ihara of Japan.
"The Great Mirror
of Manly Love."
I read this book,
and it was very shocking.
[Saikaku Ihara] The path of
sexuality is not something
that causes chaotic,
carnal desires to gush forth.
Just as with calligraphy,
the tea ceremony,
and flower arranging,
it is a means by which
a moment in one's life
may be transformed
into an aesthetic
time and space.
It is in no way a vulgar thing.
On the contrary, it is
a relationship built on
the highest standards
of rectitude and respect,
which are also found in bushido,
but even more profoundly.
Bushido was built around the
solidarity and cohesiveness
of a male group which had
expelled all women.
They pledged loyalty
to their brothers,
prepared to lay
down their lives,
and spilled their red blood in
the act of ritual suicide.
In this respect,
the philosophy of bushido
has much in common with
the path of male love.
[Jouji] Japan is the greatest
wonderful culture of manly love!
When I first read this, I think
Japan is like no other country.
It is like heaven on earth.
Well, if it isn't the European
and the insolent fools
who sheltered him.
Now come along quietly.
[Jouji] I do not understand.
Why do you arrest me?
I do not anything wrong.
[Policeman 1] Here in our land
of the rising sun,
even if dogs and cats
and worms are allowed,
there's no law that says
we have to accept foreigners.
No! The Europeans
are everywhere!
♪ hip hop music ♪
Huh?
You're all just
a bunch of monsters.
You better surrender
peacefully or else.
Screw you!
Get that bastard.
Kill him if you want.
[Jouji] Mugen! I keep my promise
to give back sword now.
Here, Jin.
Mugen.
Yeah, I know.
Wow. Is sword fight.
Real samurai.
[crowd cheering,
kabuki music playing]
What's going on? Are those guys
the next act or something?
[Jouji] Oh samurai...
[Policeman 1] Alright,
hold it right there.
[Tanaka] Hold it.
Hold it. Hold it!
I have here and official order.
Look what's on it. The scarlet
shield of the Shogunate!
[Tanaka] Let me inform you
of this man's true identity.
This is the chief merchant of
the Dutch East India Company's
Japan branch.
Governor-General Isaac Titsingh.
We beg your forgiveness for
our reprehensible insolence.
Any idea what's going on?
It appears our friend
the foreigner has official
dispensation from
the Shogunate.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Sukeemon Tanaka.
Official representative
assigned by the Shogunate.
I've been sent here
to act as interpreter.
[Jouji] I guess
it was just dream.
I hoped could live in
this country as a Japanese,
but I suppose is
not possible yet.
[Fuu] Hey, cheer up.
[Jouji] But some day will come
when this country
will accept people like me.
I am sure one day things
will change and people here
will not be so tight-assed.
Like anybody's gonna be able to
relax their ass with you around.
[Jouji] I want to
show you my gratitude.
[Mugen] Forget it. It's not like
we did anything for it.
[Jin] If you'll excuse us.
[Mugen] See ya!
[Fuu] Hey, wait a minute.
There's something
I wanted to ask you.
[Jouji] What is it?
Have you ever heard of a samurai
who smells of sunflowers?
I've been looking
all over for him.
No, I have not heard of this.
However, it was we Dutchmen who
first bring sunflower here
to this beautiful
country of yours.
Perhaps if you give me
more clue to go on than that.
Oh yeah, right.
I'm not really sure
if it's a clue or not,
but I have something
that belongs to him.
[whispering] You must not
show this to anyone.
[Fuu] Huh?
[Jouji] It is very dangerous
thing in this country.
Do not let anyone see it.
[Fuu] Why not?
[Jouji] I am sorry, but there's
only one thing that I can
tell you. Nagasaki is
where you should to look.
I'm sure you might be able
to find answers there.
Nagasaki.
[Fuu] Hey, wait.
[Mugen] So, what are we
supposed to do now?
[Fuu] Isn't it obvious?
[Mugen] Huh?
Hey!
[Jin] Is it?
[record scratching]
[Mugen] What, seriously?
[Jin] I wasn't told of this.
[record scratching]
♪ End Theme ♪