[ZAPP]
Tch!
'Course the package
is guarded by a horde
of homicidal hemorrhoids.
What the hell do we do?!
They don't have eyes!
My vision powers won't
even work on them!
[ZAPP] Well, not with that
pessimistic attitude,
ya half-empty glass of pubes!
Positive thinking's
not gonna save us!
[DEMONS roaring]
Distraction!
[LEO screams]
[LEO]
Michella?
[MENUHYUT]
You must choose.
Which one of you two
will bear witness?
Please, don't.
Don't do it, Michella!
You've already suffered enough!
If you must, then
take my sight from me!
[MENUHYUT]
And so it shall be.
No!
[LEO]
Michella!
[gasps]
[sirens wailing]
[LUCIANA]
Oh?
Finally awake, huh?
[LEO]
Doctor Estevez?
[LUCIANA] So I heard you
tried to head-butt an ogre
and knocked yourself out.
[LEO]
Eh?
Real heroic.
I'll kill him.
This one counts as
a killable offense.
Wait. That's right.
While I'm here...
[LUCIANA]
Hm?
Hmm...
I really can't say that
I would recommend it.
I mean, sure, we perform
plenty of arcane,
thaumaturgic procedures
from the other side,
but we try not to
use them on humans
'cause when they go wrong,
they go disastrously wrong.
We're talking stitches
turning inside out,
malignant tumors
becoming sentient,
and even the random mutation
of previously healthy
friends and family.
So attempting an operation
that would allow your
sister to walk again,
and one that would restore
her sight, to boot,
well, that would require
some highly volatile magic.
[LEO] Right, so I'm guessing
that goes for my eyes, too?
[LUCIANA]
Huh?
[LUCIANA CLONE 1]
Ahh!
[LEO]
Uh. Hey.
[LUCIANA CLONE 4]
Huh?
[LUCIANA]
The All-seeing Eyes of the Gods.
This is the first time I've seen
them outside of a textbook.
Textbook?
How much have you
studied the history
of the All-seeing
Eyes of the Gods?
Are the stories true?
Does someone else
always have their sight
taken from them in exchange?
Well, I'm no expert, but--
[DIRECTOR]
Fortunately, I am.
And of all the
incidents reported
through 53 volumes
of literature,
that has always been the case.
Tell me, Leonardo,
are you trying to find a
way to reverse the effects
on your sister's eyes?
Well, yeah, of course I am!
That's the entire reason I even
moved to Hellsalem's Lot
in the first place.
[DIRECTOR]
That's understandable.
Although, in all of the
passages documenting
those who came to possess the
All-seeing Eyes of the Gods,
there isn't a single
mention of reversal.
And I sincerely doubt
that they can be removed
by any known medical procedure.
If I had to surmise,
such an action would be
a unilateral breach of contract
with a divine being.
The price of which,
would surely be exorbitant.
[LEO]
Damn it. Nothing but dead ends.
[MICHELLA humming]
[LEO]
Eh? What is that?
[MICHELLA]
A drawing of you.
[LEO]
Huh? Then who is that?
[MICHELLA]
It's me.
Oh, so you get to be a princess,
but I'm just a dumb turtle?
[MICHELLA] Ha! That's not
all you are! Look closer.
You're a brave and
heroic tortoise knight.
See, you protect the princess
from the evil ghosts.
But you still made me a turtle.
So? Turtles are good.
Turtles are slow.
Like in every story ever.
[chuckles]
[LEO] I'm sorry. I was
never any kind of knight.
[KLAUS] If a man can
acknowledge the adversity
in the path before him,
and yet he still struggles
toward the light,
then his spirit can't be broken!
[LEO] I tried, Klaus,
but I don't see any light.
Not right now.
[LEO screams]
When did we get a
doormat made of pubes?
[LEO] Quit comparing me
to objects made from pubes!
I demand you treat
me with respect!
Okay, okay.
Sorry, Professor Pubes.
Adding "professor" doesn't
make it any less insulting!
[ZAPP] Yeah, ya gonna teach me
some manners, Duke of Pubes?
[LEO] Hell yes, I am! I'll
teach you a lesson, all right!
[LEO screaming]
Real smart strategy
there, General Pubes.
[LEO]
Someone help! Get him off me!
[ZAPP laughs]
[ZAPP] Ah, your screams
are music to my ears!
[LEO screaming]
[STARPHASE clears throat]
Hey, you two. How 'bout
giving it a rest?
[LEO, ZAPP whimper]
How can such a calm,
friendly smile
be so utterly terrifying?
'Cause the nicer he acts,
the closer he is
to losing his shit
and killing everyone he sees.
[STARPHASE] Oh, thanks,
Klaus. Read my mind.
Please try not to push
yourself too hard.
Not like I have
much of a choice.
If one more major
earthshaker gets summoned,
it could wipe out
the entire city.
We've gotta trace
this source code
if we're gonna find the
programming goons behind it.
--[beep]
--[KLAUS] Hm?
Oh, it's from Gilbert.
[STARPHASE] Damn, his niece
is quite the looker.
[KLAUS] He says he'll be
back by tomorrow evening.
Man, that guy is
dedicated to his job.
He should stick
around and relax.
Who cares if the
wedding's already over?
All set, Mr. Starphase.
The program's ready to go.
[STARPHASE]
Well.
All right, then. Time to unleash
some hell on these fools.
And troll hunting
season is open.
Commence operation!
[STARPHASE chuckles]
[STARPHASE] Just you wait,
you heinous little shits.
I've got your half-assed
code by the tail
and it's gonna lead my
frigid fingers of death
right to your throat.
Go ahead and laugh it up
while you still can,
'cause I'm gonna fill
your windpipes with ice.
[explosion]
[STARPHASE]
What the hell?
[ALL gasp]
[ZAPP]
Heh?
Ah, ya can't be
freakin' serious.
It's Doctor Planario!
[KLAUS]
Are you certain?
He was imprisoned!
I saw it. A full year ago!
I'm guessin' they overlooked
some of his tissue,
'cause that's him.
Prepare for crisis response!
If we let him evolve
any further than he has,
there'll be no stopping him.
This time, we eradicate
every last molecule.
Well then, I'm gonna run
down to the corner store.
[sighs]
[gasps]
[JOSH]
Ah, crap, my wallet.
[BIG GUY A]
Hm? Do I know you, asshole?
[PLANARIO]
Even if I'm defeated,
my next regeneration
will surely-- Ah!
[STARPHASE]
Pack it up!
I did the hard work for ya,
now make sure you incarcerate
or incinerate him this time!
[GARRETT]
Copy that.
Make sure you don't shatter him!
It'll leave tissue behind!
Well, that was efficient.
Something's wrong, Klaus.
I can't reach Anila.
The lines are down.
[BIG GUY A] Huh? Now who
the hell are you people?
[ZAPP]
Tch.
[KLAUS] Are you all right, Josh?
What happened here?
[JOSH]
Th-The entrance changed.
[LEO] What? How is that
not an elevator anymore?
Remain calm.
We'll figure this out.
That's not the only
office entrance.
Everyone split up and
search for the elevator.
[KLAUS]
Hm? You okay, Steven?
Huh? Yeah.
[ZAPP]
This way, jack ass.
[KLAUS]
I'll contact Yurian, as well.
You just wait down here
and rest until he arrives.
Sure, thanks.
[STARPHASE]
What the hell is going on here?
There's something on your head.
I can't get 'em off.
[STARPHASE] I take it you
didn't have any luck.
Nope.
[ZAPP grunting]
[STARPHASE]
How'd it go?
[ZED] Not good. It led
to a subway platform.
Same with my door.
It revealed an equipment room
I've never seen before.
[YURIAN] Hey, sorry
to keep you waiting.
Heard you guys are
in need of a locksmith.
Yurian! You made it.
Thanks for coming.
[chuckles]
[YURIAN]
Hm.
Well, this is pretty serious.
You're at DEFCON Level 2.
[STARPHASE]
What?
[YURIAN] Even worse, security's
completely battened down
from the inside.
Is anybody still in there?
[STARPHASE]
Anila might be.
[YURIAN]
Could she be doing anything
that would trigger the alarm?
[STARPHASE]
Nothing I can think of.
She's just been
crunching our algorithm.
[YURIAN]
Okay, then.
Whatever caused it,
our access is completely
restricted from out here,
both physically and magically.
[LEO]
Uh.
It's Chain!
Oh, goddammit.
She doesn't know
about the lockout!
[phone ringing]
Hello. Go for Cha--
Chain, no!
[BOTH] Big Dipper
Style Blood Technique!
Crimson Orb-weaver!
[KLAUS]
Do you feel all right, Chain?
[CHAIN]
Yeah, but... I saw them.
[STARPHASE]
Huh?
The office. The place is
filled with giant bugs.
They looked like--I don't know--
almost like crane flies, but
they were three feet long!
Well that's gross.
Ugh.
But y'know, it's just a bunch
of stupid bugs, right?
Even if there's a billion
of them in there,
it's not like an insect can
hack our defense system
and crank up the DEFCON level.
[ZED] That would require
a level of intelligence.
[STARPHASE] But if we
assume just one of them
infiltrated the office
and spawned thousands
within the last two hours,
we can't really rule
out the possibility
they're evolving at an
inconceivably accelerated rate.
Well, this just topped
the urgency list.
Yurian, how much time will
it take to hack the system
and override this lockout?
Give me three hours and
I should have it sorted out.
Then hop to.
Our top priority is recovering
that code trace data.
We've gotta stop that summons.
There's only a few
days before they--
[LEO whimpers]
[STARPHASE]
What's wrong, Leo?
You know that earthshaker thing?
Well, uh, they've
already summoned it.
What the hell?
That is way too fast!
Bastards must've figured
out how to shorten
the minimum incantation time!
Yeah, it could be that.
But personally, I'm not
seein' a damn thing.
[STARPHASE]
Shit!
If his fingertips touch the
ground, we're all dead!
[phone ringing]
[K.K.]
What's up, Dr. Starphase?
Greetings from above.
I'm in position, so relax.
Wait. You're what, K.K?
[K.K.] Why do you sound
like there's a turd
in your underwear?
Were you not listening to me?
I just told you that I'm
here to save the day.
So maybe try to muster up
a little gratitude?
[STARPHASE]
Whoa! What're you doing?
[K.K.] Ew, that is one alarming
infestation in there.
I mean, it looks like an apiary.
Anyhow, I'm gonna blast
a shock round in there
and paint the walls
with some bug guts.
Don't you dare!
I'm running code to
save the world in there
and Anila might
not've gotten out!
You are just one more
thunder fart in this shit storm
I don't need!
[K.K.]
Tch.
Did you just click your tongue?
Oh, did I disappoint
you, you lunatic?
[phone beeping]
[INSECT] Nice do meed you,
gen... tlemen.
[KLAUS]
Who is this? Identify yourself.
[INSECT]
We do nod...
...have a name.
We only became aware of
our existence when you did.
But in the amount of
time that's transpired,
we now function on the
same level as humanity,
and will soon surpass you.
[KLAUS]
And what is your objective here?
[INSECT] Oh, my objective?
It's really quite simple.
I intend to borrow this office
until my evolution crescendos
and I've become a god.
[KLAUS]
I'm afraid that's unacceptable.
It's imperative we
return to the office
and we have no time to waste.
[INSECT laughs]
[PEDESTRIANS screaming]
[INSECT] You seem to have
misunderstood my words.
I am not requesting your
acquiescence in the matter.
The number of options
available to you are zero.
[LEO]
Whoa, there's a web of light.
[YURIAN] That's really bad.
They've gone to DEFCON 1!
[thud]
[ALL gasp]
[STARPHASE]
It's hopeless.
Nobody can get past
that level of security.
Leonardo, you said you can
see a web of light, correct?
[LEO]
Uh, yeah?
I need to assess this situation.
Can you hack my eyes
so I can see it?
[LEO]
Oh, of course!
[KLAUS]
Hm. There it is.
[ZAPP] Hey, Chief.
What exactly are you planning?
[KLAUS]
Throughout history,
anytime a warrior was
locked out of a fortress,
they snuck in through
the top floor.
[KLAUS] What happens if
my Blood Battle Technique
reaches its activation limit
and the blood returns
to its natural state?
One drop on that web and
it'll blow you sky high.
Okay, I'm glad I asked.
I'll need to infuse my blood to
hold its state all the way up.
What?
Sorry, Chief, but have you
lost your goddamn mind?
Your technique requires
a whole other insane
level of concentration
than our burning
or freezing types.
I'm well aware.
It's a good thing
I have discipline.
[PEDESTRIANS screaming]
[LEO] Klaus will always
refuse to give up.
I don't even think he knows how.
Now, K.K., commence
with the operation.
[K.K.] Get a tight grip
on those blood daggers.
[INSECT laughs]
[INSECT]
How pathetic.
Are they really unaware of how
robust their own security is?
Bullets are about as effective
as tossing pebbles at a tank.
Now that I think about
it, this isn't right.
[gasps]
Damn, it was a diversion.
[ALL gasp]
[YURIAN] All right, perfect!
I've got an opening now!
[KLAUS]
Yurian.
What's the likelihood of
deactivating the barrier?
It's impossible!
I only need a moment.
If you can crack it open
for just a few seconds,
I can force my way in.
It's gonna work, but holy
crap this keyhole's small.
[gasps]
Brain Grid Blood
Battle Technique.
Form 32!
Stechende Blitzattacke!
[VILLAINS laughing]
[RICHTER]
Here comes the touchdown!
[VILLAIN A]
Only about 20 feet left
before he reaches the ground!
[VILLAIN B] Richter, dude,
you're a freakin' genius!
This catastrophe's gonna get you
your very own Wikipedia page!
[CARL]
Uh!
Oh, dammit! I've
really gotta piss!
You're gonna miss it, dumb ass!
Tie a rubber band
around it, man!
We're almost there!
Hell yeah!
Here it comes!
Let's get a countdown goin'!
[VILLAIN B]
Oh, yeah! Good idea!
[RICHTER] We're not there yet,
idiots! Wait for Carl!
Hey! Shake a leg, Carl, c'mon!
[VILLAIN A] Forget his baby girl
bladder, let's go already!
[VILLAIN B] Ha-ha! Screw it!
Let's start the count!
[VILLAINS] Ten! Nine!
Eight! Seven! Six! Five!
Four! Three! Two! One!
Esmerelda. Blood Freeze Blitz!
Viento del Cero Absoluto!
[STARPHASE] Summons
interception, complete.
[LEO] And that is how the
most consequential lockout
in the history of the
world came to a close.
Steven looked like he
was about to collapse
right there on the street,
but he still stuck around
to finish the post work.
Once done, he left early to
finally catch up on his sleep.
Our defense system underwent
a major overhaul,
which temporarily
closed down the office.
What up, Viv?
[VIVIAN]
Come on in, guys!
[ALL yelp]
[BOTH]
Hm?
[LEO]
And during that downtime,
we lost the one place where
we could get away from work.
I won't give up.
[LEO]
And that's a promise, Michella.
[ZED]
When you encounter loneliness,
it leaves you helpless
and confused,
and the despair of it
never stops gnawing at you.
But take heart, friends.
Because if you can find
despair in this world,
then it's a certainty that hope
is there to be found as well.