[PARAMEDIC A]
BP's at 90 over 60!
Pulse is 140 and erratic!
[PARAMEDIC B]
Is he cognizant?
They're all packed!
Every single ER in the city
has turned us away!
Well, shit.
[LEO] Zapp! Say something!
Please, Zapp!
Shut up!
Or I'll stick you with
a syringe of Demerol!
[PILOT A]
What the hell?
[PARAMEDIC B]
Huh?
Something wrong?
Aim your eyes
toward one o'clock.
What the--? Where the
hell'd that come from?
[KLAUS] The intersection between
two worlds. Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society of super
humans toiling in the shadows
to preserve the fractured
balance between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[PARAMEDIC B] Well, that
looks like a hospital.
[COPILOT A] Yeah,
but I've never seen it before.
And it was not there when
we flew past this spot
15 minutes ago.
Hey, look!
[PILOT A] They've already got
an admin team ready to greet us.
What do we do here?
[ZAPP]
Why do I feel so sleepy?
[LEO screams]
[ZAPP]
Look at the pretty pasture.
[PARAMEDIC B]
Take us down!
What?!
[PARAMEDIC B]
Zap Renfro. Age 24.
Fractured femur and
multiple compound fractures
sustained in a head-on collision
with a heavily-armored vehicle.
We stopped the bleeding
and he's stable.
You guys take it from here!
Now I know how it feels
to be abandoned.
[LUCIANA]
How unprofessional.
I don't think they
liked you very much.
[LEO]
Mm...
Not to be rude, but you're
not a doctor, are you?
I certainly am.
Wait, what? You're not
even old enough to drive!
[LUCIANA]
And your point is?
[LEO]
Eh...
[ZAPP]
All those moments will be lost.
[LEO] Okay, this place
is weirdin' me out!
I do not wanna deal with
this crap on my own!
Uh, hey, Steven?
Wait. Is that what
I think it is?
[LEO] All I know is that it's
supposed to be a hospital.
Well, that, and it's
staffed by toddlers.
[STARPHASE]
Klaus.
[KLAUS]
Yes. It's finally returned.
Uh. Wait, you know this place?
[STARPHASE] We've both been
in this building once before.
Three years ago, during the
night of the Great Collapse.
[LEO]
Huh?!
[STARPHASE]
Seventeen hours since this fog
started ripping
the city to hell,
and it doesn't
look like the chaos
is gonna let up anytime soon.
Christ.
Hm?
Pretty sure that
guide's lost its use.
In case you haven't noticed,
most of the buildings aren't
where they were yesterday.
I'm using it to identify
the buildings floating past.
It's helping me to
assess the destruction.
That was the GE building
we drove beneath earlier.
Are you really trying to
pinpoint every building we pass?
You're treating the apocalypse
like a tourist trap.
[STARPHASE] Speaking of, we
should be thinking big picture.
Suppose the entire world's
shrouded in this fog.
If that's the case, then what?
I have no idea.
Whatever this is, I'm not sure
if our monster fighting days
have prepared us for it.
We're talking about
someone or something
that can rearrange New York
like it was made of Lego blocks.
I doubt our techniques are
gonna be enough to stop it.
Stop the jeep!
[BABY crying]
[KLAUS]
Steven.
Let's try to avoid any premature
and distraught
conclusions, shall we?
We need to stay
focused on surviving.
And we'll gather intel as we go.
But the first thing
we need to do...
[KLAUS] ...is find a safe
place to take this child.
Sounds good.
[KLAUS] That appears to be
Bradbury General Hospital.
[STARPHASE] All that's left
is the central building.
Hold it!
We have an infant.
It needs shelter and food.
[ANNOUNCEMENT A]
Paging Dr. Gunther. Dr. Gunther.
[GUNTHER]
Well, now.
I'm pretty sure I would remember
admitting a man your size.
[KLAUS]
We've only just walked in.
[GUNTHER] Really? From that
maelstrom of surreality?
[KLAUS] Yes. And we
found this poor child.
[GUNTHER] So, can you update me
on what's happening out there?
Well, honestly...
[GUNTHER] Still beyond
description then, huh?
[STARPHASE]
Exactly.
[GUNTHER] Well, I guess
that describes it plenty.
[NURSE A]
Doctor.
It seems the pain is keeping
Mr. Phillips from sleeping.
Five cc's morphine.
[NURSE A]
Right.
[GUNTHER] And don't forget
the laxative and antiemetic.
[NURSE A]
Yes, sir.
[GUNTHER] It's been
like this 18 hours now.
Not exactly easy
on a man my age.
Huh?
Hey, wake up, Luciana!
Go lie down on a sofa
in the waiting room
if you need some sleep.
[LUCIANA]
Uh?
Oh. Doctor!
I'm sorry. Did I
really fall asleep?
[GUNTHER]
Sure did. While standing up.
[LUCIANA]
Wow, oh my God.
Well, I do feel more alert
so I guess it helped some.
[KLAUS] That was some
rather impressive repose.
I've seen others fall asleep
on their feet before,
but never so gracefully.
Well, hello, big guy.
Aren't you a smooth talker?
If you caught me any other day,
I'd offer you a physical exam.
On the house, of course.
Pleased to meet you.
Klaus Von Reinhertz.
[LUCIANA] Luciana Estevez.
Welcome to our humble hospital.
[GUARD A] Stop right there!
That's far enough, buddy!
[gasps]
[gunfire]
Keep moving!
Get further back inside!
Wait. Hey! You two!
[STARPHASE]
We're all right.
You keep 'em safe in
there. Back in a jiff.
[KLAUS gasps]
[STARPHASE]
Huh.
So this guy, do ya think
he speaks English?
We know a total
of nine languages,
so we can work our
way down the list.
You okay there, Klaus?
That almost sounded like you
were tryin' to crack a joke.
Yeah, well, I suppose
I am a little bit anxious.
[KLAUS]
Steven. That's a Blood Breed.
[laughs]
I'm just out trying to enjoy
a stroll with my dog,
but of course, my shitty luck.
You two are fang
hunters, aren't you?
[sighs]
It's a special day here, guys,
can we not take a break from
the boring old routine?
[KLAUS]
Are your people behind this?
My people? I'm afraid not.
Can't claim authorship
of something
that's always been there.
This mist is a world that
exists right next to your own.
It's just that sometimes
the two realities collide.
All of your legendary monsters,
your vanishing aircraft,
all of the inexplicable, ancient
artifacts, now explained.
You know it's
January 1st, right?
New Year's Day, fellas.
Today's a celebration. It's
the start of a brand new era.
Which is why--
[ZAMEDLE'S DOG barking]
[ZAMEDLE laughs]
[ZAMEDLE] My bad. You know
how I like my monologues.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[ZAMEDLE'S DOG barks]
[ZAMEDLE]
Anyhow, I've got nothing to do
with this natural disaster,
so I'd like to feed my pup now.
So then, would you
kindly step aside?
I'll apply my Brain Grid
Blood Battle Technique!
[STARPHASE]
Esmerelda Blood Freeze!
[KLAUS]
You will not pass us.
[chuckles]
My goodness. I have
never been this scared.
I'm utterly terrified.
You brutes have
frightened me so much
I've dropped the leash
of my beloved dog!
[ZAMEDLE]
Look away from me, and you die.
[yells]
Lanza del Cero Absoluto!
[ZAMEDLE laughs]
[ZAMEDLE]
Nicely done, fang hunter.
[KLAUS yells]
[yells]
[ZAMEDLE]
You're not bad,
but you're fighting a
battle you cannot win.
The same way no one
can stop this fog
from devouring New York.
[bang]
[whimpering]
[LUCIANA screams]
He's regenerating too fast.
[KLAUS]
Go, Steven.
I'm not leaving, Klaus!
You try to take him on your own,
he'll feast on the
whole hospital!
We deal with the dog afterward.
It's a two man fight,
and I'm not gonna let
you martyr yourself!
[KLAUS]
I can still see the light.
[STARPHASE]
Huh?
[KLAUS]
We always stand a half-step
between the light and surrender,
but I know which
direction I'm taking.
Forward. Toward the light.
Even if that half-step takes me
through hell to get there.
[STARPHASE] Good lord, man.
You and your speeches.
I've got one minute
and 40 seconds in me.
Exterminate that beast in there
and get back to me by then.
[STARPHASE]
Hm.
That's a good number.
Not too modest or too arrogant.
Perfectly sums up your
whole personality.
Too bad, though.
Wish I could witness
the 100 seconds
you're about to unleash on him.
Three.
Two.
One!
What stopped it?
Heh.
Looks like some wet blankets
went and pooped on the party.
Never would've guessed
this dimension
had such powerful casters in it.
[SAILOR A]
Huh? What the hell?
[grunts]
[KLAUS]
And then we suddenly woke up,
only to find ourselves
surrounded by Hellsalem's Lot,
as it currently stands.
[STARPHASE]
Since that day,
I can't even tell
you how many times
we've searched
for this hospital,
but we couldn't find a
trace anywhere we looked.
[LEO]
Whoa.
--[horn blaring]
--[tires screeching]
[bang]
[LEO] Holy crap,
that's a serious pileup!
[GUNTHER] On the double!
Act swiftly and calmly!
[LEO]
Whoa. Look at 'em go!
[GUNTHER]
Ah, so we meet again.
Oh!
Dr. Gunther!
I'm glad to see you're alive.
[LUCIANA] Wounds sustained
to neck, back, and abdomen.
Red tag him and
send him to Trauma 2!
[GUNTHER] We'll have this
wrapped up in no time.
Just wait here
if you don't mind.
[LUCIANA] Yellow tag for
that one! Curtain 4, got it?
Oh, hey! Set him up for
the next available cat scan!
[KLAUS]
Hm?
[LUCIANA squeals]
[LUCIANA whimpers]
Wait, that couldn't be...
[ZAPP] Get the hell away
from me, you brat!
And hey!
Gimme back my damn
pants! Perverts!
[LEO]
You're okay!
[STARPHASE]
All right, Leo.
Ya told us there was barely
anything left of him
and that he was on
the brink of death.
[LUCIANA]
And that's true.
But I put him back together
and on the path
to a full recovery.
In truth, though,
I almost regret it.
Hm?
[yelping]
Dr. Estevez. Wait just
one moment, please.
[LUCIANA CLONE 4] Break's over!
We've got patients in need!
[LUCIANA]
Long time, Mr. Reinherz.
And a lot has transpired.
[KLAUS]
I'd appreciate an explanation.
What exactly happened?
To the hospital, and you.
[DIRECTOR] I'd be happy
to answer that for you.
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
I'm the director of the
hospital, Magra de Grana.
[DIRECTOR] The day the
Great Collapse occurred,
there was a comparable
amount of chaos and panic
on our side as well.
I was rushing about, giving
treatment to those in need,
when suddenly...
[DIRECTOR]
Huh?
[DIRECTOR] I discovered her
in the midst of the wreckage,
barely clinging to life.
[LUCIANA]
I consent.
Hurry, dammit!
[DIRECTOR]
The ability to divide herself
and administer multiple
treatments simultaneously,
despite the fact she would
no longer be a human.
She chose this existence
because it was the only way
to save those around her.
A truly admirable decision.
I deeply apologize for
our failure to protect you.
[LUCIANA] Oh, stop that.
Please, Mr. Reinherz.
None of us were equipped
for the events of that day.
That's all there is to it.
[LUCIANA] Although, the 247
patients that were here with us?
It's not over for them.
[STARPHASE]
Huh? What do you mean by that?
[KLAUS]
Hm? What is this?
[LUCIANA]
An organic life support system,
kind of like a cocoon.
[STARPHASE]
What for?
[LUCIANA] The monster that
attacked the ward infected them
with some type of spores
that've continued to extract
their vitality to this day.
But that changed 13 hours ago.
And that's why
we resurfaced here.
Their nutrition is no
longer being harvested.
So that son of a bitch
is sure to come to collect.
[gasps]
[LUCIANA]
He's here!
[LUCIANA CLONE 1]
Is that it?
The freakin' beast
hyper-evolved on us!
[LUCIANA CLONE 3]
It's disgusting!
[LUCIANA CLONE 4]
Bad dog! Bad!
[LUCIANA]
I've got a favor to ask.
For the sake of our
patients' wellbeing,
I would appreciate
it if you could--
Yeah, whatever.
So, you stickin' around
on this side for long?
'Cause I'm starved enough
to eat an entire buffet.
[growls]
What's wrong? You gettin' mad?
You gonna attack me, doc?
[DIRECTOR]
This is a facility for healing.
Our only objective is treatment,
not the opposite.
Ugh, really?
I guess that works
out for all of us,
since I got my spores
in yer patients.
So ya probably don't wanna risk
nothin' bad happenin' t' me.
[ZAMEDLE'S DOG laughs]
[ZAPP]
Hey, ya big ugly bitch!
For such a large guy, ya sure do
a lot of little dog yappin'.
Now maybe ya
think you're special
'cause you're up on two legs,
but I got news for you, pal.
That trick is called
begging, so you-- Ah!
And that's called shut up!
[LUCIANA]
Phardem Triga!
[grunts]
What?! You jerk!
You really think
you're gonna get away
with treatin' me like this?
[LUCIANA]
Treating you?
That's pretty rich
coming from the creep
who's been sucking the
life out of my patients.
Well, uh.
[LUCIANA] You've got a long life
as a test subject ahead of you.
[LUCIANA gasps]
How could anyone treat
a dog this poorly?
You're heartless.
Now die.
[ZAMEDLE]
Well hello, fang hunter.
[DIRECTOR]
Dr. Estevez! This way!
[ZAMEDLE]
Still haven't learned, huh?
Fight all you want,
but you're just gonna pass out
from blood loss again!
And this time, you'll die!
[gasps]
[ZAMEDLE]
There's the other one!
[STARPHASE]
Not too shabby, Klaus.
You held out for 133 seconds.
[phone rings]
[KLAUS]
Zamedle...
...Lolow Zeaze...
Shut up!
[KLAUS]
...Nazamsandriga!
Brain Grid Blood Battle
Technique. Form 9.9.9!
[screams]
Ewiges Gefängnis!
Ow!
Doctor Estevez. Thank you.
You have my gratitude for--
These past three years,
we've both done
well for ourselves.
[LEO]
I'm givin' you MVP, Zapp.
I mean, we never would've
been here to save the day
if it weren't for
you and that truck.
Where the hell's that
roided-out, rat-terrier?
I'll rip him limb from limb!
[LEO]
Uh, that already happened.
Somebody beat me to it?
[CHAIN]
No expectations.
No excess.
No pointless involvement.
One can live a
largely peaceful life
if they stick to
those three rules.
But no matter how hard you try,
things don't always
work out that way.
Holy crap, people are idiots.