[BLACK] Talk about
a blast from the past.
It's good to see you, man.
[LEO] Yeah, you oughta come
back and visit sometime.
[BLACK]
Ha. That's a nice thought.
But I'm not sure if I'm ready
for Hellsalem's Lot yet.
That city's inextricably linked
with White in my mind, y'know?
Yeah, sure. I get that.
Even so, it'd be nice
to catch up in person.
[BLACK chuckles]
Uh?
You know how it goes.
We'd probably just end up
talking about our sisters
the whole time.
You've got a point.
[laughs]
[BLACK] Speaking of,
how's Michella been doing?
Oh, well, so-so, I guess.
[BLACK]
C'mon, Leo.
You really need to actually
call her every once in a while.
Well, catch ya later!
[LEO]
Whoa, hang on!
[groans]
[LEO]
Thanks for the guilt, Black.
[MICHELLA]
Hello?
Uh, hey, Michella.
[MICHELLA]
Oh my God! Leo?
I can't believe I'm
finally hearing from you!
Are you really that busy, there?
You can't even find
the time to call?
Uh, sorry. Things have just
been a little hectic since I--
[MICHELLA] Forget it,
this is actually good timing.
Listen, I'm sorry to
spring this on you,
but I've got something
to tell you.
[LEO]
Huh? Sure, what's up?
You ready? Brace yourself.
Yeah?
[MICHELLA]
So I'm, uh...
Yeah?
[MICHELLA]
Well, I'm getting married.
Yeah?
[LEO]
Huh?!
[MICHELLA]
What kind of reaction is that?
I know the news is surprising,
but it's not shocking.
You're acting like
I murdered someone
and I'm asking you
to bury the body.
Seriously, you're
hurting my feelings.
[LEO] No, no! No,
really, it's just that--
I just mean-- I just
mean that just--
[MICHELLA] Whatever.
We'll talk about it soon.
Surprise part two.
I'm actually on my way to
Hellsalem's Lot right now
to visit you.
Huh?!
[MICHELLA] Well, you are the
only person in our family
that still hasn't met my fiancé.
[LEO]
Wait, you're coming?
Anyway, I've got some
other calls to make,
but I'll see you in three days.
[LEO]
Huh?!
[MICHELLA] Two PM sharp at
the New Asterisk Hotel.
And you better be
there, Leo! Bye!
[LEO]
Hey, wait! Michella!
You don't say.
Hmm.
[STARPHASE] Well, this makes
for a delicate situation.
I know.
Hey, Steven.
We're on the same page.
Here's the thing, kid,
there's a strong likelihood
that you and your sister's
eyes are connected somehow.
If something were
to befall Michella,
we have no idea what might
happen to your eyes in turn.
Reason enough for us
to protect her.
She's under our watch.
[chuckles]
[LEO] Thank you, guys,
that's awesome!
[ZAPP]
Why?
Why'd I get stuck on
babysitter duty again?
Stupid, helpless,
unwiped asshole...
Oh, drop it.
Anyone with one eye can see that
you obviously care about him.
So quit with the posturing.
Didn't ask for your opinion,
but I will ask why you're here.
Well, I wanna see
Leo's little sister,
and witness the
heartfelt reunion.
Cool, then there's no
reason for me to be here.
Stay put, slacker.
I'm on call today so I might
need to duck out at any minute.
[K.K.] Aww, it's adorable
how anxious he is.
He can't even sit still.
He stood up again!
[K.K. squeals]
[K.K.] Oh, God, my stomach
is filled with butterflies.
You're not watching
a soap opera, y'know.
Christ, try not to get
any estrogen on me.
[K.K.] Oh, it's like I'm
pregnant with Mothra.
So what the hell's your
excuse, Black Lagoon?
Nobody asked you to be here.
Oh, don't mind me.
I just don't feel comfortable
with you standing
guard on your own.
[ZAPP]
Huh?!
Well, to be more specific,
I'm not worried about Leo
so much as I thought
someone might need
to protect his sister from you.
Oh, you think you're
better than me, crab cakes?
Why don't ya go eat a net
full of dicks, blow fish!
No, I'm okay here,
but thank you for confirming
the validity of my concern.
Uh.
[ZAPP]
What? Patrick? And Neyka?
Did the entire agency turn out
to watch this sappy shit?
Uh. Huh?!
Oh, you can't be serious!
And they brought that hot,
nerdy doctor with them?
[ZAPP] I don't get it, what the
hell is the big draw here?
We're a world-saving
secret society!
Don't these friggin' people
have anything better to do
with their day?
[elevator dings]
Thanks so much, sir.
Michella.
Is that a big brother I hear?
Feel free to say hello.
[MICHELLA] Hey, c'mon,
don't suffocate me.
That's not what
Tortoise Knights do.
Are you ever gonna stop
calling me that?
[MICHELLA laughs]
Sorry.
Have you lost some weight?
[LEO] Maybe, I dunno.
Not like I own a scale.
I worry about you, Leo.
You've never taken very
good care of yourself
when it comes to your diet.
[LEO]
I'm fine, I promise.
Are you making sure
to get enough sleep?
Yeah, except for last night.
Well, sure.
That makes two of us.
[K.K.]
Aww!
It's so beautiful!
The bond between siblings
is such a wonderful thing!
Gotta say I feel sorry
for your actual kids.
So if you were on your way here,
what would you have done
if I hadn't called?
I mean, you don't
have my address.
[clears throat]
[MICHELLA] Oh, sorry,
got a little caught up.
I forgot to introduce you.
Leo Watch, meet Toby
McLachlan, my fiancé.
It's a pleasure to
finally meet you, Leo.
I know we've never met before,
but it feels like I've
known you for years.
Michella talks about you
just about every day.
She has so much pride in you.
According to her, you're
the kindest, strongest,
most reliable man alive.
To be honest, I couldn't help
but feel a little jealous.
Wow, no, I wish I was like that.
[TOBY]
Well, sure, I gotta say...
You certainly don't
look anything like
I was expecting you to.
Uh.
[TOBY clears throat]
Uh, no offense.
I believe every word
she's told me about you.
You do, huh?
Well, yeah, you said it.
So there's no doubt
that it's true.
[MICHELLA]
Ha!
He's really funny, right?
He's always saying all sorts
of silly jokes like that.
Wait, what silly joke?
I was being entirely
earnest there.
[MICHELLA laughing]
Oh, boy, see what I'm
talking about, Leo?
[MICHELLA laughs]
Doesn't look like trouble's
gonna suddenly rear its head.
I feel like we're safe to let
Zapp handle it from here.
Sure.
[MICHELLA]
What sounds good to you?
I figured we could just
get a bottle of red.
[LEO] And of course, I'm the
only one who can see this.
[MICHELLA]
Why'd we stop?
I gotta use the restroom.
[GAMIMOZU] Excuse me there,
young Leonardo Watch.
You can see me, correct?
If not, you would be
woefully inadequate
to possess the All-seeing
Eyes of the Gods.
[LEO]
So I guess he knows.
Who the hell are you?
Is that Toby guy
even still alive?
You beter not have done anything
messed up to my sister!
[laughs]
[GAMIMOZU] From top to bottom,
I'm Doctor Gamimozu.
Yes, Toby McLachlan
is still alive.
And no, I haven't even laid
a finger on your sister.
And what do you want from us?
[GAMIMOZU] I've been studying
the various prosthetic limbs
of the Gods scattered
throughout the world.
Not to mention
experimenting with them.
First time seeing one
outside your own head, right?
Feel free to take a closer look.
It's over 150 years old now.
You... You know the truth.
Tell me everything you
know about these eyes!
And start with why the hell
my sister had to be involved!
[GAMIMOZU]
Ohh. Your anger does make sense.
Bestowing the eyes upon such an
average human like yourself,
Riga El's actions were
cruel to say the least.
[LEO]
Riga?
[GAMIMOZU]
Riga El Menuhyut.
Personal ophthalmological
engineer to the divine.
I believe that you've already
made his acquaintance.
[GAMIMOZU] I've heard the
story from your dear sister.
I believe he asked you to choose
which of you two would
bear witness, right?
And that, my boy, is precisely
what your calling entails.
Ever since the dawn of mankind,
the All-seeing Eyes of the Gods
have been routinely dispersed
amongst your species to
monitor all significant events.
Essentially, these eyes--well,
it wouldn't be inaccurate
to describe them as the world's
most successful hidden cameras,
since they've spied on every
critical moment in history.
The emergence of Hellsalem's
Lot is easily mankind's--no,
it's easily Earth's most
significant occurrence,
eclipsing every last thing
that came before it.
To be chosen as its
official observer?
Good lord, man, I envy
how fortunate you are!
[LEO]
Did you say I'm fortunate?
Is that some sick joke?
If you ever say that
in front of Michella,
I'll kick your ass
out your mouth!
[GAMIMOZU] Oh, I'm sorry,
were you saying something?
And get this,
nobody told Danny so the putz
went ahead and ordered it!
Oh, the poor dumbass.
[BOTH laugh]
[GAMIMOZU chuckes]
[GAMIMOZU] That's the brilliant
beauty of these eyes.
Every eyeball in this
place is under my control,
and they only see
what I want them to.
I have to say, this new
model is truly exquisite.
Tell me, Leonardo,
you're absolutely ravenous
for vengeance, aren't you?
Provide me with one of your eyes
and we might be able
to strike a deal.
In fact, cooperating
with my research
is the best chance you have at
restoring your sister's vision.
Hey, Leo.
So your sister's fine
and everything's cool
and there's really no
reason for me to be here.
Right?
I, uh, actually...
[ZAPP]
See, the thing is,
Miranda dropped by my place
and found Nyala there
and now they've turned my
apartment into a warzone.
Aw, shit, this looks bad.
Anyway, I gotta go, so
you're gonna be fine, right?
[LEO]
Please don't leave!
Heh? Is there somethin' wrong?
Uh. No, I--
It's just that I, uh--
Dude, you'll conceivably
be fine on your own.
[LEO]
Yeah, but still--
Christ, ya look like you're
about to shit your pants.
Calm down, I'm leavin'
the fish here for ya.
And seriously, man,
you gotta be able to
protect your own family.
I mean, you are a member
of Libra after all.
Okay, good luck. Don't die!
[GAMIMOZU]
This Libra he mentioned...
Don't tell me you're a fang
hunter. You are, aren't you?
You snuck into their ranks
using your eyes' powers.
Impressively done.
[clock chimes]
[GAMIMOZU]
Oh, my.
This bathroom break has
turned worrisomely long.
So then, it's time that we
get back to your sister.
[MICHELLA] The castle's
haunted and full of ghosts.
[LEO] They look like they're
some pretty scary dudes.
Yep, and anytime
the mighty warrior
goes in the castle
to fight them,
the ghosts hide themselves
by turning invisible
and trick the warrior.
[LEO] So how does he
even fight them, then?
[MICHELLA]
Hmm...
Huh, good question.
What?! You haven't
thought that up yet?!
[giggles]
There he is. My brave
Tortoise Knight.
Sorry, that took a while.
[LEO] She knows that
something's wrong.
[MICHELLA]
But I'll see you in three days.
[LEO]
Huh?!
[MICHELLA] Two PM sharp
at the New Asterisk Hotel.
[LEO] That would explain
why she's been more assertive
than usual.
There's no one else she can turn
to, so she came to me for help.
All alone, with an unknown
creature at her back.
[phone rings]
[GAMIMOZU]
Hmm?
Hey, what's up, Steven?
Sorry to interrupt, Leo.
Nice, a direct head shot!
[gasps]
[STARPHASE] We've got a
rampaging Blood Breed.
Right. Yeah. I understand.
I'm sorry, Sis.
A little emergency
just sprang up
and I need to go
take care of it.
Huh?
I'll head straight back
as soon as it's handled!
[TOBY] I do hope that you'll be
able to make it back by tonight.
We don't have much time and
there's plenty to discuss.
There's the matter of her eyes,
and our wedding, of course.
Not to mention our
plans for afterward.
And really, that's just
scratching the surface.
[MICHELLA] Okay, guys. You
trying to keep secrets from me?
No, not at all.
I deeply love your sister, Leo.
And I want to help her.
Right, I'll try
not to take long.
[LEO] That was pretty
messed up in there.
What the hell was that?
You don't give a shit about
helping her. Screw you!
[GAMIMOZU] I didn't choose
those words to toy with you.
In fact, that was
Toby's natural response.
The perfect simulacrum requires
the perfect source material.
He genuinely is a fine,
upstanding gentleman.
Your sister really
knows how to pick 'em.
So where are we rushing
off to? I'm dying to know.
[LEO]
Shit, this is bad.
I've gotta shake him somehow.
Leo! Over here!
[LEO groans]
[DANIEL]
Crap!
[POLICESUIT A] You need to
step back, Lieutenant!
It's too dangerous!
Shut your hole!
Just keep him surrounded!
If he gets past us,
I'm docking your pay!
[STARPHASE]
Lieutenant Law.
[DANIEL]
About time.
What's the situation?
[DANIEL]
Take a look for yourself.
It's an absolute shit show.
Our sniper detail managed
to blow his head off
with a series of
explosive rounds,
but that didn't
exactly stop him.
It just made things worse.
[gasps]
[DANIEL]
What the hell is it doing now?
He can't seem to
regenerate his head.
Then the good news is he's
not an Elder-class, at least.
Although... that
doesn't help us much.
He has all of the powers
of a Blood Breed,
but he's rampaging
like a wild beast.
This is bad.
[gasps]
Get back some! We'll buy you
some time while you work.
We'll do what we can.
Back us up with firepower.
[K.K.]
Ew.
Damn, that thing's ugly.
[GAMIMOZU]
How fascinating.
It's been quite some time
since I've seen a Blood Breed.
But a rabid, crazed one like
this is a rather rare anomaly.
[LEO]
Dammit.
I've gotta help them,
but I can't let him
see what I'm doing.
So what...? What do I do?
[STARPHASE]
Esmerelda Blood Freeze!
Escudo del Cero Absoluto!
[GAMIMOZU]
Huh? Something wrong?
You're just frozen there
gripping your phone.
You were about to do
something, weren't you?
I mean, you do have some
role to fulfill here, correct?
[STARPHASE] Doesn't even
matter if he's corrupted,
we can't hold a Blood
Breed for ten seconds.
[KLAUS]
Leo, hurry.
[STARPHASE]
He shed his exterior! Dammit!
We can't let him
become a Zhen Tai Dan!
Well, boys, he's all yours.
[ZED] Big Dipper
Style Blood Technique.
Blade number Five!
Blade One!
Kagutsuchi Homuramaru!
Shinatobe Piercing Dragon Spear!
[ZAPP]
Seven Hells!
[ZED]
Heavenly Winged Bellows!
What are you
waiting for, dick bag?
Hurry the hell up already!
[screaming]
[BLOOD BREED roars]
[KLAUS] Ardamachael Zi--
Zirlahia Or Salzmailoros!
I hereby seal you!
[KLAUS]
Ewiges Gefängnis!
[roars]
[GAMIMOZU]
So that's your trick!
Ha-ha! Well done, Leonardo!
A remarkable feat!
Using the power of your eyes
to uncover their true names?
No wonder Libra considers you
to be such a valuable asset.
This is splendid!
Your access alone can
take me to the next level.
That settles it!
Leonardo. I believe the time
has come for me to possess you.
[LEO] Back when I first
moved to this city,
I used to have such dark
and depressing thoughts.
But these days,
I can't even remember
what those thoughts were.
Michella, I think
I'm about to--