[RIEL chuckles]
[RIEL]
Hm? Hm.
[RIEL gasps]
[LEO]
Hey! Enough, Sonic, cut it out!
This is pretty rare for him.
He never warms up to people
as quickly as he has with you.
[RIEL]
That's because he's smart.
It's better to be apprehensive
than to get eaten.
And evasion's the sole survival
tactic of sonic speed monkeys.
But he can tell I'm no threat.
Even a monkey can see
I'm pathetically weak.
No, I'm pretty sure he
just likes you, Riel!
No reason to get all
self-deprecating, dude!
[RIEL, LEO]
Huh?
[RIEL, LEO scream]
[PUNK A]
Oh, that all you got?
Quit lyin' to me, ya little
shit, cough up the rest!
Or I'll pull it outta yer lungs!
What? No! That's really
all the cash I have.
Empty. Empty. That's it!
[LEO screams]
[NUZRUBA]
Don't dodge me!
Why wouldn't I?
Listen, ya brat!
Nuzruba was tryin' to be a nice
guy and make sure ya didn't die
by only usin' his
pinky finger on ya.
So ya could at least
let me hit ya!
Oh, right! I'm sorry.
You are so kind!
You dumb ass! Your pinky finger
is an arm! And a giant one!
All the times I've mugged you,
you should know to
talk nicer to me, Leo.
Clear somethin' up for me.
Humas die when their heads get
popped off their necks, right?
[LEO] "Hello, Michella.
How've you been lately?
I'll never get to actually
write you this letter
because I'm being
choked to death."
[KLAUS] The intersection between
two worlds. Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society of super
humans toiling in the shadows
to preserve the fractured
balance between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[LEO]
Holy crap. That one hurt.
[LEO] C'mon. Don't
let this upset you, Leo.
I should really be
used to it by now.
Can't let each
mugging get me down.
Back on your feet! Carpe diem!
[SONIC grunts]
[LEO]
What the hell? Did that happen?
I mean, did I really just get
struck on the back of the head
by an object falling
out of the sky?
What're the odds?
One in a billion?
Right after getting
beaten and robbed?
That's more like
one in a trillion.
Whatever it is, it's
too much for one day.
[LI GADO]
Ah! It shattered!
The Hyber Grag Gigaramd
Womegabalson shattered!
Way too much insane
crap for one day!
[LI GADO] Uh, hi. Sorry for
panicking on you there.
[LEO]
Huh?
[LI GADO]
Hm.
There's a slight protuberance
on the crown of your skull,
but the injury isn't
anything serious.
You'll live, my micro
gigantic young man.
My name's Li Gado,
a mechanized physician.
I'm a hyper doctor specializing
in the battle against pathogens
with ultra-weaponry.
Um, not over there.
That's the wrong spot.
I'm over here on
this mobile platform.
[LI GADO]
Hm? Something wrong?
[LEO]
Y'know.
I've seen some crazy things in
this city, but congratulations,
you officially take the cake.
Ridiculous. How the hell did
I let you talk me into this?
[KLAUS] Please, Warden Alice,
try to speak quietly.
[ALICE]
Christ, I know!
I think I deserve the
right to vent, though.
[KLAUS] Well, what can I say?
The man reveres cubism.
It just felt wrong to let him
miss this visiting Cezanne.
[ALICE] His taste in art
is beside the point.
He's a double-S class prisoner
under constant Dreadnought
level supervision.
Allowing him to visit
a goddamn museum
completely contradicts that.
[KLAUS] Trust me, Warden,
I understand your concern.
That is why we took
the proper precautions.
I even had them clear
the building for the day.
[ALICE] That's all very well and
good for the public at large,
but still, it doesn't
do anything for me.
This little fieldtrip
interferes with my duties.
And that's what pisses me off.
I am terribly sorry for that.
This outing, perhaps you can
just consider it a reward
in light of his good behavior.
[chuckles]
[RIEL]
I just left him there.
My friend was being
assaulted and I ran.
I mean, sure,
Nuzruba's broken nearly
every bone in my body
with a single punch before,
but I shouldn't have left Leo.
[RIEL]
If only I weren't so frail...
If I was bigger and stronger,
I'd never have to deal
with all this terrible stuff.
[GEMNEMO]
Yeah, you've got a point.
[RIEL]
Huh?
[GEMNEMO]
You speak the truth, my friend.
[RIEL]
Sorry. Who're you?
[LEO]
Bacterial terrorism?
Sure, I know about that stuff.
You're talking about
terrorist attacks
using biological weapons, right?
[LI GADO]
No, no, you have it backward.
The bacterium is the terrorist.
He goes by the name Gemnemo.
He's a fully cognizant and
aggressively active being.
A super-dangerous
microbe, in fact.
[LEO]
Hmm.
This is really silly.
But then again, here I am.
Having a perfectly
fluent conversation
with a tech-savvy flea.
[LI GADO]
What flea?
Oh, you mean this!
It's just an exosuit to shield
me from your atmosphere.
Heh?! Whoa, hang on.
Are you saying
you're even smaller?
[LI GADO] Much smaller.
I'm a microbe, too, after all.
But the only thing we
should be discussing
is how I can promptly find
Gemnemo and arrest him.
Not only is he a
sociopathic genius,
he's the first bacterium
to master sorcerology.
And according to
our latest intel,
he's developed a
hyper-augmented method
for accelerated
cytological division.
Huh.
[LI GADO]
If we don't apprehend him,
it'll result in catastrophe.
However, there is still hope.
The ultra-gigantic
doomsday weapon,
the Hyber Grag Gigaramd
Womegabalson, can stop him,
so it must be repaired.
You mean, the thing that
slammed into my head,
and then shattered like
a cheap, shoddy toy?
[doorbell rings]
[LEO]
Oh, Ms. Landlady.
Sorry to bother you, Leonardo.
Do you have a moment?
Patricia's gone and managed
to get herself stuck
down there again.
I really hate to ask,
but do you think your monkey
could help me rescue her?
In return for the favor,
I'll give you more time
on last month's rent.
We're on it! Okay,
Sonic. Duty calls.
[LI GADO]
Hey, are you certain about this?
It looks like a maze
between these buildings.
Won't he just get lost?
This isn't the first time we've
retrieved stuff from down there.
It's no sweat with
me navigating.
[LI GADO]
How exactly does that work? Hm?
Take a left there. Good.
Now start heading down.
That's it. Just keep
on moving down.
[meowing]
[LANDLADY A]
Thank you so much.
[LEO]
No problem at all,
and thank you again
for the extension!
[LI GADO]
So that's your trick.
You were able to guide him
with those eyes of yours.
That's it, right?
[LEO]
Mmm. Yeah.
[ZAPP]
Huh?
Hey, uh, you. I know you.
Oh. Yeah, you work with Leo.
[ZAPP]
Hm?
Look at you!
You've been bulkin'
up the old guns
since the last time I saw you.
Um, I have?
Now that I've said
somethin' nice.
[ZAPP chuckles]
How 'bout you do me
a friendly solid
and let me borrow 20 bucks?
I'll get Leo to pay you back
the next time you guys hang out.
[RIEL]
Well, I--
C'mon. Help me out! Please?
[ZAPP screams]
[GEMNEMO]
You speak the truth, my friend.
Power's the only thing that
matters in this world.
So many people get trampled
into the ground, and for what?
Just so the powerful
can pile them up
and stand on their broken
backs to enjoy a better view.
And for someone as frail as you?
There's really no
hope for crawling out
from beneath that
helpless mound.
And climbing up
is nothing more
than a dream within a dream.
Tell me, friend. You long
to see it, don't you?
Go on, be honest, now.
This is just between us.
You'd like to see it, right?
For just once in your
miserable, little life,
don't you want to enjoy
the view from the top?
[footsteps]
[RIEL]
Hm?
Well, look who it is.
Y'know it's rude to just cower
instead of sayin' hello, right?
[NUZRUBA laughs]
[RIEL screams]
[ALL gasping]
[LI GADO]
I've finally finished it!
[LI GADO] The viral aggression
surgical strike cannon.
The Fuldra Radrict
Huvaserganon 7000-AR!
I can neutralize 99%
of the Gemnemo threat
with this beauty here!
Oh! Feast your eyes upon
the mighty spear of justice!
That's gonna save the world?
It looks like it came out
of a Gundam model kit.
[LI GADO]
It's not a toy!
It is built from the refuse
of my first weapon, though,
so unpredictability is a factor.
I've put in a request
with my headquarters,
but my regular gear, the
Grag Gigaramd Vedabalson,
is apparently still
undergoing its own repairs.
Then what's your plan here?
You've got a weapon but you
don't know if it'll work?
[LI GADO] The two of us will
just have to do the best we can.
[grumbles]
It's all up to you and me!
About that.
What makes you so certain
I'm getting mixed up in this?
[LI GADO]
Are you deaf?
I told you the fate of your
world hangs in the balance here!
Right.
[LI GADO] What's with the
dismissive, patronizing tone?
Well, basically,
you act like this thing's
a doomsday weapon,
but it already lost in
the battle against my head
and it barely left a bump on me.
So your fate-of-the-world talk
feels a bit disproportionate.
[LI GADO]
Unbelievable!
That right there is the
problem with you giants!
You only worry about
things bigger than you!
Wait, giant?
Well that's the only time in my
life anyone's called me that.
It's usually "little dude,"
or "runt," or "pipsqueak."
And then they rub my
head or push me down.
[LI GADO] That's the exact
behavior I'm talking about!
Strength doesn't determine
the outcome of every fight!
So don't you go and judge
everything by the same metric!
[STARPHASE] So, you thought
it best to bring him here?
[LEO] Yeah. You haven't
heard any news, have you?
Y'know, about any threats to
the city? Apocalypse type stuff?
Well, yeah, of course.
Apocalyptic threats are like
the everyday background
music to this city.
Hm.
It's not all that relevant,
but I just got word that
Zapp was hospitalized.
[LEO]
Huh?
He got in a fight and someone
tossed him into traffic.
[LEO]
How does that even happen?
[STARPHASE sighs]
Nothing that guy does
makes any sense to me.
So then, this, uh,
hyper-augmented method
for accelerated cytological
division you were mentioning.
Can you explain that to me?
[LI GADO]
In the broadest of terms,
it's a method for enlarging and
strengthening living tissue.
He first performs the procedure
on a target microbe,
which is implanted in a subject,
where it then proceeds
to rapidly multiply.
Knowing Gemnemo, though,
he's out for more than the
amplification of muscle mass.
I'd wager it results in
the unbridled evolution
of the full physical structure,
skeleton and all.
[NUZRUBA screams]
Please! I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me!
Not so quickly, Nuzruba.
I've only broken one
measly pinky, after all.
Me, on the other hand,
my body was a web of
compound fractures!
Consider this a greatest
hits of your abuse.
I want you to feel
every ounce of pain
that you've inflicted
on anyone in your life!
[NUZRUBA screams]
[GEMNEMO]
How's the view?
You've got a whole new
perspective, don't you?
It must be intoxicating to see
the world through new eyes.
The power's irresistible,
isn't it?
[GEMNEMO laughing]
Police, hold it! Hands
where I can see 'em! Huh?
Shit, that's just barbaric.
[RIEL] What I've done?
You call this barbaric?
Freeze, dammit!
[RIEL] If you could've only seen
what these monsters did to me
because that... was much worse.
[yells]
[RIEL roars]
[BRODY] Well, I'm feeling
artistically fulfilled.
That Cezanne was lovely, huh?
[growls]
[BRODY] Oh, don't give
me that stupefied look.
Prisoners are capable of
appreciating something
other than pornography, y'know.
[ALICE]
Tch.
This interest in painting,
do the two of you
often discuss art?
[BRODY] Well, only about the
stuff we do and don't like.
Nothing too complex.
This guy's not much for
debating theory and technique.
Yet you give him the materials,
he's actually quite skilled.
[KLAUS] Really?
I was completely unaware.
I'll have some art supplies
sent over for you.
You mean it? That's awesome!
[BRODY] Roll up a leaf green
Crayon and slip it in the pack,
if ya get my drift.
[HUMMER chuckles]
[BRODY]
Calm down, I'm joking.
[KLAUS]
Hm?
Whoa!
That was rad!
[bang]
[BOTH scream]
[HUMMER]
Exocrimson!
That's a catch and release!
[BRODY laughs]
Never thought I'd see the
day it's rainin' policesuits.
Weird, the weather
looks so nice.
[gasps]
[phone ringing]
[KLAUS]
It's me.
We have an emergency situation
on New Third Avenue.
An unidentified giant humanoid.
It's currently
engaging a swat team.
Alert all personnel
as a precaution.
DEFCON level 2. Prepare
for crisis mobilization!
[HUMMER]
Hm.
Hey, y'know, Klaus, seems like
we should give them a hand.
[KLAUS]
Warden?
Permission granted.
Put it down ASAP.
Understood.
Yee-hee-hee!
[KLAUS] Ah. By the way, Steven.
Leave a message for Gilbert.
Just to err on the
side of caution.
Tell him to please cancel
my schedule for tonight.
Exocrimson.
[STARPHASE]
It's 13 feet tall?
Near-human types tend
to get pretty big,
but that's still pretty
goddamn enormous.
[LEO]
Huh?!
Is that Riel?
Hang on. You know that thing?
[LEO] Well, I think so,
but not like that.
He normally weighs
less than I do.
[LI GADO]
Jackpot!
[LEO]
Ow!
[LI GADO] That's what
we've been looking for!
I'm sorry to tell you this, Leo,
but I am at least 80% positive
that your friend is now
a pathogenic terrorist.
Gemnemo's exposed him
to his procedure.
Huh?
[LI GADO]
His cellular tissue is splitting
at a hyper accelerated rate.
Just as muscles torn by exertion
create even thicker muscle,
and broken bones are even
stronger once they mend.
This process is being endlessly
repeated within him,
resulting in unchecked
explosive bodybuilding!
[LEO] Right. So, um, what
are you trying to tell us?
[LI GADO] Physically confronting
him is the worst thing
one can possibly do.
It'll only increase
his savagery.
Brain Grid. Blood Battle
Technique. Form 1-1-7!
[KLAUS]
Unzerbrechlich Kreuzschild!
[BRODY grunts]
[STARPHASE]
Klaus!
Delicacy might be required
with this target!
Avoid undue engagement!
[KLAUS]
Just confirmed that.
I'm going to attempt
to restrain it.
[RIEL roars]
Let's try Brain Grid Blood
Battle Technique. Formation 39.
[KLAUS]
Keilbarrikade!
Warden Alice!
Take Hummer and the others
and move far away from here.
What the hell're you gonna do?!
[KLAUS] I'll stay right here
and contain the damage.
Steven.
I've never seen anything close
to this kind of power before.
Do you have any
further information?
I could use some input.
[KLAUS]
What? My God.
Look out, Klaus!
I'm comin' for ya!
[HUMMER]
Hundred Crack Fist of the Me!
[BEYONDER B]
Look!
[SONIC gibbering]
[KLAUS]
My apologies, Sonic.
I'm afraid I never learned
to speak monkey.
Can you translate, Zapp?
[SONIC gibbers]
[ZAPP]
Yeah, he says he wants a banana
for not flingin' his shit.
[LEO] Guess I know why Chain
calls you "monkey brain" now.