[LEO]
Hello, Michella. How are you?
I'm finally doing well.
[LEO] I'm still scrapin'
by in this city.
Crazy to think how long
I've been here now.
[LEO] This place is as crowded
and messy as it's always been.
A noisy city where
abnormal is normal.
[LEO] And today,
it's just more of the same.
[LEO] Ugh. Well, that's
a depressing amount.
[CROWD yelling]
[LEO]
Huh?
[LEO screaming]
[NEW DEMONBEAST]
What's up?
I'm Leonardo Watch.
My friends call me Leo.
No one calls you that!
That's my name! I'm Leo Watch!
But who cares, 'cause I'm
plummeting out of the sky!
In a matter of seconds,
I'll be dead!
[LEO] I'm so-- Oh, God.
Thank you, Zapp! I love you!
[ZAPP]
Don't make things weird, Leo.
Now what ya got me playing
a spider-like,
web-slingin' man for?
[LEO] All I know is I got
kidnapped and knocked out
and woke up falling out of the
sky with this thing on my head!
What the hell?
That's a real cute test-tube-
bug-hat ya got on, Leo.
So fashionable!
[ZAPP laughing]
[MAN A screams]
[LEO]
Huh?
[MAN A]
Aww, so cute!
[roars]
[BOTH groan]
Hello, boys and girls!
It's your King of Depravity!
F.E.M.T! Femt!
[ALIGURA laughing]
Have you desperately missed me,
my unhygienic, uncultured,
unmotivated livestock?
Sorry, I've been busy
playing poker lately.
But I'm bored with that now.
So I did a little proactive
multitasking this morning
and whipped up a new synthesized
batch of demonbeasts.
They crumble and die six hours,
six minutes, and six seconds
after they hatch,
but they know how to make
that short life count.
Oh, how they indulge!
And heads up, they
are not picky eaters.
As quickly and large as they
grow, their metabolism demands
a ceaseless consumption
of victuals.
Long story short, they're big,
mean, and hungry,
so you might wanna run.
Well, that should cover it,
so you all have fun out there!
One for nonsense.
Nonsense for all!
[LEO groans]
I know, but please!
Just let me cling to you!
No one's questioning
your masculinity!
[ZAPP screaming]
Aw, shit, it cracked!
What the hell do we do now?
By the way,
I intend to spend the evening
binge-watching BBC Earth,
so I'd really appreciate it
if you could wrap it up
by then, thanks!
But if you fail to do so,
and these lovely puppies
of mine continue to grow.
Well, it would be
pretty damn funny
if they devour 90% of
the Earth's population!
[LEO]
Your sense of humor sucks!
[ZAPP, LEO gasp]
[LEO]
Oh. Oh, crap.
[STARPHASE]
Stand back, you two!
[chuckles]
[LIBRA MEMBERS shouting]
[shouting continues]
[K.K.]
What the hell?
Thanks a load for stepping
on my line, there!
I couldn't hear
my own attack name!
[KLAUS]
Uh, sorry, K.K.
Why are you apologizing?
We didn't have any choice.
No choice?
You gonna act like that wasn't
some dick measuring contest?
[phone ringing]
[STARPHASE]
Huh?
Hey, it's Chain.
Thought you might wanna know
there's a supersized demonbeast
heading right for you.
[STARPHASE]
Come again?
[CHAIN]
In ten seconds, you'll--
[gasps]
[roars]
[DEMONS roaring]
[STARPHASE]
Looks like we're boxed in.
[ZAPP yelling]
So what's the plan, Klaus.
[KLAUS] My Brain Grid
Blood Battle Technique.
Wait. Really?
Remain behind me.
Everyone, line up single file!
[ZAPP]
Don't tell me what to do.
Apply Form 1-1-7.
[KLAUS]
Unzerbrechlich... Kreuzschild!
[ALL]
Uhh...
Hm?
[ZAPP whimpers]
[KLAUS]
Uhh...
[DEMONS whimpering]
[LEO] Yep, Michella.
Today, this city almost...
I mean. I'm great today,
nothing to worry about.
[sighs]
[LEO]
Huh?
[LEO screams]
[MISS NIGHTENGALE] Hellsalem's
Lot is honored to receive
U.S. Presidential
envoy Franz Ackerman.
Here to further expand the
bridge between our two worlds.
Welcome to your new home,
Mr. Ambassador.
The induction ceremony is to be
held tonight at Federal Hall,
beginning at 7 p.m.
[LEO]
X!
X-Station! Double X!
Double X! Double--!
Ugh. Selfish jerk.
I'm sorry, Michella.
I should've sent you the money
instead of buying this.
But... I had to do it!
Hard Dive 4 ! This game...
I needed it.
This series literally
changed my life.
And it's the first new
release in four years.
Now let it begin.
Junk food, check!
Soda, check!
Always-unmade bed, check!
I'm ready.
[LEO]
Ah, crap.
Ah, double crap!
My hand! Calm yourself, dammit!
[phone ringing]
[LEO]
What do you want, Zapp?
[ZAPP] Where are ya,
ya scruffy nutsack?
[LEO]
What? I'm at home.
[ZAPP] You're gonna let me
talk you to like that?
Grow some dignity,
you gutless eunuch!
Hey! It's my day off and
I don't need your crap!
[ZAPP]
Great, you got 30 seconds.
Open your north facing
window, right now!
[explosion]
Heads up! Catch, scrotum face!
[LEO grunting]
[groaning]
[LEO]
Eh?
[ACKERMAN]
Are you a huma?
[LEO] Why did that asshole
toss a box of horror
into my house on my one day off?
[ZAPP] You know I can
still hear you, right?
That's how phones work, genius.
Shut up! And quit
calling me mean names!
[ZAPP] Whatever, just hurry
and get that box to the office.
[LEO]
Huh?
[ZAPP]
I'm kinda tied up
with some blood-thirsty,
trigger-happy lunatics.
[LEO]
Huh?
Well, they're after that box,
but hey, we're distracting.
Oh, right, that reminds me,
don't look inside.
[click]
[sighs]
[LEO]
It's a little late for that. Eh?
Ohh...
[LEO] Excuse me, why is
your head inside this box,
United States Ambassador,
Franz Ackerman?
[STARPHASE]
Y'know.
I think I'm gonna have
to categorize this
as one of the more surreal jobs
we've been hired
to handle, Klaus.
[KLAUS]
I'll agree with that assessment.
[RACHEL]
It happened so fast.
A nightmare. No, it--
It made even less sense
than a nightmare.
[STARPHASE]
Not to go out on a limb here,
but I bet it's the work
of Headless Duke Durer.
[KLAUS]
Hm.
[MALE AIDE A]
Durer?
You mean the one from
D's Elegant Exhibition Room?
Every time the government
tries to block public
access to the site,
it just pops back up.
Live cameras streaming
a feed of hundreds
of disembodied, live heads.
And you think they plan to
install Franz in this exhibit?
Good God.
This isn't exactly the
most fruitful beginning
for diplomatic relations
between two worlds.
It could even mean war.
[STARPHASE]
Slow down, now.
That's precisely what we're here
to prevent. Just trust us, okay?
I offer you my solemn promise.
We will return
Mr. Ackerman's head.
He will be whole
for the ceremony.
[ACKERMAN] So you know me.
Even recognize me by my face.
Well, uh, yeah.
[ACKERMAN] That heavily
booth-tanned gentleman
from earlier didn't seem
to know who I am.
Yeah, sorry 'bout that.
I'd be surprised if Zapp could
identify the president himself.
[LEO] Of course he
looked inside the box
before unloading it on me!
Pardon me, son,
but do you have a cellphone
I could borrow, please?
[LEO]
Huh?
[ACKERMAN]
I'd like to inform my colleagues
as to where my head is located.
[LEO]
Right, makes sense.
My... My apartment... And my...
X-Station! Double-X!
No! Oh, God, why?!
[ACKERMAN] Do you want them
to find us? Stop yelling, son.
[LEO]
I just lost everything.
[ACKERMAN]
But you still have your life.
This is serious, son.
The enemy has
infiltrated our cabinet.
[LEO]
So what do we do?
My phone just went up in flames
so there's no calling for help.
[ACKERMAN]
They could easily triangulate
and track your phone's signal,
so I would've asked
you to destroy it.
[LEO cries]
[ACKERMAN I'm afraid there's no
other alternative, Leonardo.
I need you to deliver me
to my colleagues.
Once you do, the government will
reimburse you for your losses.
What do ya say?
Yeah, fine, I'll do it.
[GARRETT]
Hoo, boy.
They blew this place to hell.
I see. Acknowledged.
Garret succesfully arrived at
the coordinates we tracked.
However, the location's been
destroyed in an explosion.
[GRAHAM]
Hm.
And you're positive
that's the address
the envoy was calling from?
[ANILA]
Yes. No question about it.
No answer.
Leonardo.
Are you serious?!
You're tellin' me he's dead
'cause I tossed him the package?
That poor, sweet, dumb,
fuzz-encrusted turd.
His death was as boring
and pointless as his life.
I'm sending you to hell!
Why does life have
to be so cruel?
Why are you so quick to
assume that he's dead?
Let's finish the task at hand
and go search for him.
[ZAPP]
Ahh...
Right. I know.
It's a shit storm.
The Gargambino Family.
The Snakebite Clan.
[EXECUTIONER A yells]
[CHAIN] The Screaming Reverse
Executioners Society.
And the trade show
for unidentified
outlaw organizations.
[STARPHASE]
Yeah, it's bad.
The bounty he's offered?
Durer's got every goon in this
city out headhunting for them.
[CHAIN]
Yep.
Find that head!
Bring me every 20 inch
duralumin case ya see!
[PUNK A]
Word is, some kid's got the box.
[PUNK BOSS A] I don't care
if it's a freakin' baby!
You shoot 'em on
sight and take it!
[COWORKER A]
Hey, Leo!
Wha'cha doin', ya nut?
Sneakin' through alleyways
with a giant alloy briefcase!
[LEO] God, he's so loud!
And so specific!
Hey, wait a sec.
I just remembered.
Ya got Saturdays off, right?
Switch shifts with me, will ya?
[LEO]
Eh?
[COWORKER A] I picked up this
chick last night, and man,
she has gots to have it!
Well? You're not busy, r-- Ah!
[PUNK BOSS A]
Quit runnin', huma!
There you are.
Just keep on running, okay?
Outta the way, ya twiggy broad!
Prognosis.
[PUNK BOSS A coughs]
[CHAIN]
Sudden Massive Heart Attack.
[SONIC screeching]
You're telling me
there's danger that way?
[LEO]
Mr. Brigade!
[LEO crying]
Hey, Starphase.
I've secured the subject.
Huh?
You need the package
delivered to the hall
no later than 7 o'clock?
Of course. I'm on it.
Leo, we've gotta get
to Federal Hall ASAP.
What?!
[LEO yelps]
Ah! Mr. Brigade!
Hey! This way, Leonardo!
[LEO]
But he's--
He's okay!
That ultra-high-test
coat he's wearing
just arrived in the mail today,
and it's the latest model.
Lucky bastard!
[groans]
How the hell is
getting shot lucky?
Keep running! C'mon, Leo!
[ALLY A screams]
Uh, holy shit.
[K.K.]
Leo!
I recommend ducking!
[S.R.E.M.A.S. yelling]
[ACKERMAN chuckles]
[ACKERMAN]
To be fully honest,
you didn't exactly strike
me as a good fit at first,
but I was wrong.
[LEO]
Huh?
[ACKERMAN] I mean, for here.
In Hellsalem's Lot.
Did you already live here
before the Collapse?
[LEO] No, I didn't.
I chose to live in this.
[ACKERMAN]
So, you're a thrill seeker?
[LEO]
No.
[ACKERMAN] Were you running
away from something?
[LEO]
No.
[ACKERMAN]
Then what brought you here?
Sensitive subject?
Never mind me.
What's it like outside?
[ACKERMAN]
Outside?
Oh... Still nothing but
fear and raw nerves.
But what else is there to expect
when the world's greatest
city is cracked open
by a void teeming
with alien life?
The general public
are living each day
like it's their last on earth.
It's an absolute joke.
Zero faith in the greatest
nation in history.
[LEO] You gonna set 'em straight
with stern uplifting speeches?
[ACKERMAN chuckles]
[ACKERMAN]
Not that easy.
[LEO]
I can see it!
[LEO chuckles]
We're almost there!
Eh?!
Get down, Leo!
[HUMMER]
Ya jerks better not kill Leo!
You'll feel real bad
about it later in life!
Huh?
Deldro? You see where
Leo ran off to?
[BRODY]
Nope.
[LEO screaming]
Heh?
[screams]
[LEO]
It's hopeless!
We're stuck in some kind
of nightmare loop!
[ACKERMAN] Leonardo, get back
on your feet and start running!
[LEO]
I can't anymore!
[ACKERMAN]
Don't cry, run!
You're welcome to
whine all you want,
but only after you've lost.
[LEO]
Are you for real?
How can you not wanna
give up right now?
You're just a head!
[ACKERMAN] Not giving up,
even if you want to,
is a politician's job.
To willingly surrender, when
there's still a glimmer of hope,
is selfish and senseless!
Look around you and think.
Is there nothing
left you can do?
[ACKERMAN] Focus on the
most important outcome
and fight for it!
[LEO yelling]
[LEO] Just a few more blocks
between us and Federal Hall!
I'm chargin' right
through this shit!
[ACKERMAN]
Hold on! Let's be cautious!
There's no time for that!
[SOLDIERS grunting]
Impressively done,
Master Leonardo.
[LEO]
Uh.
[DURER'S SUBORDINATE A]
Nice of you to join us.
So glad to see you're safe
and sound, Leonardo.
Bring the head to me
if you want this to end.
[ACKERMAN]
Hm? That voice.
Wait. Rachel? How could
you act this foolish?
You believe you can broker
a peaceful coexistence
with these monsters,
and you're calling me foolish?
[ACKERMAN]
How dare you.
[DURER'S SUBORDINATE A chuckles]
[DURER'S SUBORDINATE A] Man,
I get a kick out of you humans.
You like to call us monsters,
but come on, look at you.
I at least get along
with my own kind.
[LEO]
Hey, uh...
[DURER'S SUBORDINATE A]
Hm?
Could you please explain
to me what you're doing?
[DURER'S SUBORDINATE A]
Uhh...
No. I'm not talking to you.
The question was
for Klaus and Steven.
It's not what it
looks like, Leonardo.
We were just being
mindful, that's all.
Trying to minimize the
inevitable burst of chaos.
[DURER'S SUBORDINATE A] Oh, you
were being mindful? Ha, ha.
Only thing you're
minimizing here
is the severity
of your situation.
Y'know what, Miss Washington?
Sorry about this,
but I've just decided to remove
every one of your heads.
[ALL gasp]
[yells]
[whimpers]
I'll give you some
credit for ambition,
but did you really think
we wouldn't prepare
for a double cross?
[yells]
Well, it's been fun,
but I'm afraid there's no
more time to play charades.
[ACKERMAN] Our great nation
is beside itself.
How thrilling it is
to have a new world
born within our borders.
Although the boundless
possibilities within this city--
[LEO]
Oh. Hang on.
Ackerman said they
were gonna pay for me
to get a new apartment.
[STARPHASE]
You can't be serious, Leo.
You're a member of Libra
and you want the government
to know where you live?
Are you suicidal?
[LEO]
Huh?
We managed to carry out our
mission without any losses.
That's the only
compensation we need.
[LEO]
Uh, no, I did lose my home.
You could always stay
at the office again.
I've already placed the order
for your new cellphone.
You'll rebuild the
rest in due time.
[LEO]
But what about my...?
My...?
X--! X--!
I saw this movie the other day.
The heroes went and got
shawarma at the end.
We should totally go
and do that, Deldro.
Sure, why not?
[KLAUS] The intersection between
two worlds. Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society of super
humans toiling in the shadows
to preserve the fractured
balance between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[LEO]
This is my story,
and the story of the
people in my life.
And how they've given me hope.
[STARPHASE] Those first three
years after the Great Collapse,
no one knew what to expect.
These days though,
we consider the unexpected
to be this city's BGM.
But that's just another sign
of people's endurance
and capacity to change.
Except Klaus. You
never change, do you?