[GILBERT] Two containers of
nemesis coffee beans.
Three kilos of Xestaro
pasta 1.8, in six packs.
Three bundles of eyeball onions.
One bale of ogrehorn carrots.
Eighteen servings of
condensed liver.
[GILBERT]
Well, that's everything.
A pleasure doing
business with you.
Thank you, sir.
How should I stack these?
Anything that needs
to go up top?
Oh. Please, allow me
to handle-- Uh!
...that.
[KLAUS] The intersection between
two worlds. Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society of super
humans toiling in the shadows
to preserve the fractured
balance between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[ZAPP] Yeah, I'm callin'
bullshit, dude.
No way that's a skyfish.
Looks like you just got some bug
guts smeared on your lens.
I was there, Zapp!
I watched it slam into
Gilbert with my own eyes!
I do apologize for
alarming you so.
Although, there's no
cause for concern.
As you can see, I'm perfectly--
[GILBERT groans]
[LEO]
Heh?
[LEO, ZAPP]
Uh?
[GILBERT groaning]
[phone ringing]
[GILBERT]
Yes?
[CATHERINE]
Gilbert Franke Altstein.
It has been far too long,
my old friend.
[GILBERT]
My, what a lovely surprise.
Hello, Head Maid
Catherine Bates.
To what do I owe this rarity?
I wish this was a social
call, but it's business.
I was informed you sustained
some rather grave injuries.
[GILBERT]
Oh, how odd.
Wherever would you
hear such a thing?
[chuckles]
Pretense will not
deter this discussion.
Despite his protective
and reticent nature,
Master Klaus cannot
keep secrets from me.
[GILBERT] You personally
rang him over this matter?
[CATHERINE] As head maid
of the Reinherz Family,
that is my devoir.
[GILBERT]
Yes, but, madam--
[CATHERINE]
In light of your health,
I've dispatched additional
aide to provide you relief.
[GILBERT] Most unnecessary.
An imperious judgment, madam.
[PHILIP]
There it is. Hellsalem's Lot.
[PHILIP screams]
[PHILIP]
I'm ready to serve!
I'm from the Reinherz
Family Special Butler Corps!
My name is Philip Lenore!
I'm honored to serve you!
[LEO]
Holy crap, this dude is loud.
Is he always gonna
yell like that?
[GILBERT]
Mr. Lenore has been appointed
to provide supplementary,
interim aid.
A thoughtful gesture, but I will
maintain the primary role--
[GILBERT groans]
[PHILIP]
Are you all right?
[GILBERT]
Perfectly fine. Merely resting.
Please, Mister Altstein!
You need to convalesce.
Allow me to execute the full
purview of your duties.
Please, give me the chance to
prove myself as a combat butler.
Huh? Did he say combat?
What, like you fight?
When necessary, yes.
[PHILIP gasps]
[KLAUS]
Hey, Gilb--
Hm?
[gasps]
[STARPHASE]
He drank his tea?
And he actually liked it?!
You're positive Gilbert
didn't make it for him?
This new guy must
really know his stuff.
Count me impressed.
[ZAPP]
Oh, the freaking pain!
[LEO]
Calm down, Zapp!
My arm! My arm!
What the hell?!
[CHAIN] I'm sorry! He looked
so weak I couldn't help it!
Seriously?
I've called for a doctor.
This should suffice
until they arrive.
[LEO]
Ohh...
[GILBERT chuckles]
[GILBERT]
So he's performing admirably.
Well, that's reassuring to hear.
I should've known not to fret
over Head Maid Bates acumen.
You can drop the seething
decorum around us.
You've got every
reason to freak out.
That asshole's clearly
angling to steal your job.
[GILBERT chuckles]
[GILBERT] I would never
be so paranoid. Ha!
[LEO] I've gotta say, Gilbert's
a pretty remarkable guy.
No matter how crazy
things get around here,
he always takes
everything in stride.
And he seems to get along
with every person he meets.
The thing about him though,
it's almost like he
doesn't have a presence.
He's always just standing
there in the background.
Sometimes, I don't
even notice him.
He just blends in like
heavily bandaged wallpaper.
[LEO] So, um, the Eternal
Hollow's further down that way.
Trust me, you don't wanna
go anywhere near there.
If you're gonna use mass
transit, keep an eye out
for the destinations
marked with red letters.
For those spots
your survival rate
goes down by 30%, so avoid 'em.
I have to give this
city its proper due.
It far exceeds my imagination.
I'm surprised you've managed
to survive this long.
Yeah, but, hey,
it's not like every
block of this city
is a den of rabid demons.
There are still plenty of normal
folks who live here, too.
[door opens]
Hey, Leo! What's up?
[LEO]
How's it goin', Vivian?
[VIVIAN]
Not too bad.
[LEO]
Ya see? Just your average diner.
Normal as you can get.
Uh. Sure.
[VIVIAN] Who's this?
Another friend from work?
[PHILIP] Yes, I have the
honor of serving as Li--
[LEO screams]
Yeah? "Li" what?
The live show begins!
Who's feeelin' blue?!
The blues, yeah!
Bah-da-bah-blues!
[VIVIAN]
I guess Leo's finally cracked
under the insanity of
living in this city.
Broke his damn brain in two.
[LEO] You do know I
can hear you, right?
[PHILIP] Hey, uh, did I commit
a faux-pas back there?
Saying the name Libra
out loud like that?
Libra's got its fair
share of enemies,
and most other people
are just leery of us.
We're a secret society.
So, y'know, it's safest
to just keep it a secret.
Yeah, that makes sense.
[BEYONDER A]
Watch it!
[PHILIP]
Pardon me, sir.
[BEYONDER A]
Yeah, what d'ya want?
[PHILIP] I want you to return
the wallet you just stole.
[BEYONDER A] Huh?
'Fraid you're mixed-up, pal.
Here, lemme set you straight!
[BEYONDER A] Ah! All right!
You win! I'll give it back!
[LEO] Thanks for that.
I guess I owe you one.
[PHILIP] Think nothing of it.
All a part of the profession.
But with this level
of lawlessness,
I worry about your safety here.
Not to mention your finances.
[LEO]
Nah. I've got a system for that.
I spread out the cash I've got.
The wallet's just a ruse.
I only keep small
change in there.
[PHILIP] Then you just expect
it to be stolen from you?
Yep.
The smallest bit of trouble
here can spiral into chaos.
It's best to shrug it off.
[PHILIP]
Hmm...
Caught you, Mister Altstein.
Thought you could
sneak in some work
when no one was looking, huh?
[GILBERT chuckles]
[PHILIP]
Please return to your bed, sir.
So what was that?
[GILBERT]
Oh. Amazing, isn't it?
It's a sequencer for authoring
my own symphonic compositions.
Oh, come clean.
You don't have to keep
everything under wraps.
That's the command uplink
system for Libra, isn't it?
[GILBERT] This is one duty I
cannot allow you to supersede.
And why not?
I'm more than capable
of learning!
I don't doubt your aptitude.
It is too perilous.
Uh! But--
If you were to
learn the details
of Libra's inner workings,
the contents of your brain
would be valued
somewhere in the millions.
You would live in
constant pursuit
from all manner of lifeforms.
And I would avoid them,
as you have!
[GILBERT] This is not
the reality you know.
You're simply unprepared.
There's little you could
do to stop them.
I'm not strong enough...
Is that it?
[GILBERT]
Indubitably.
[PHILIP]
Hm.
There's a major flaw
in your reasoning.
Explain you.
How have you lasted this long?!
And how can you allow Leo
to freely travel on his own?
If you think so lowly of me,
then why don't you just
tell me to leave?!
[gasps]
[PHILIP]
Please forgive me.
[GILBERT]
There's nothing to forgive.
Such unflinching candor
can prove to be a virtue.
However, standing your ground
and embracing confrontation
isn't the only
means of survival.
You've had the chance to spend
some time with Leonardo.
So I'm certain that
you've already witnessed
that truth for yourself.
[PHILIP]
Dammit.
Whoa, man, careful
with the glassware.
[PHILIP]
Oh, um, terribly sorry.
[BARTENDER A]
You're one gloomy Gus, huh?
[BARTENDER A giggles]
Well, whatever's on your mind,
you can unload it
on me if you need to.
[BARTENDER A giggles]
[PHILIP]
For as long as I can remember,
I've idolized Gilbert
Franke Altstein,
the legendary combat butler.
By the time I was employed to
serve the Reinherz family,
he had already left the estate
to accompany their
third-oldest son, Klaus,
with his esoteric endeavors
in Hellsalem's Lot.
"There are those in
need of protection,
and if I am one of the
few capable of performing
such a deed, I will then
be the first to volunteer."
Those words of his, they
exemplify the man's nobility.
I truly believed I was the
one who could assist him,
but in reality...
[BEYONDER A]
You got 'im!
[BEYONDER B]
'Course I did.
Hang tight a sec.
Just gonna take a quick,
little peek inside his brain.
Won't take no time at
all to whip up a list
of his friends and family for
you to hunt down and murder.
[BEYONDER A]
Ha-ha! Hell, yeah!
[BEYONDER A laughing]
[BEYONDER B]
Whoa. Hang on, what the hell?
This guy's involved
with freakin' Libra!
[BEYONDER A]
He what?
[BEYONDER B] I'm out! No way
I'm messin' with that shit!
[BEYONDER A]
Hey, not so fast!
[BEYONDER B]
What're ya thinkin'?
[BEYONDER A]
Oh, I'll tell ya.
I'm thinkin' we just won
the goddamn lottery.
[laughs]
[LEO]
Dammit, Zapp!
Give me back my burger,
you prehensile dick!
You can have it back
after I've digested it.
Damn, these Jack Cheese
Rockets are so good!
[PHILIP]
Good morning, gentlemen.
[ZAPP]
Huh?
--[LEO] Morning!
--[ZAPP] What's crackin', P?
[LEO]
Stop it! Give it back!
[ZED]
Hey, good morning, Philip.
Hm?
[gasps]
[GILBERT]
It's evident something is amiss.
If you've been compromised
by means of duress,
please signal by touching your
face with your left hand.
[gasps]
[GILBERT] It's always a shock
to see a brain extraction.
I'm sure you're aware,
but you've fallen victim
to a dire procedure.
Now, as to the matter
of your brain,
do you know where it is?
No, goodness me.
That complicates things.
Well then, please seat
yourself before the console.
[GILBERT]
Try not to fret.
Take your time and read
every word on the monitors.
[BEYONDER C]
Holy shit!
[BEYONDER D]
Fellas, we just struck payday!
Only reason Libra's
got the power they do
is 'cause nobody knows
nothin' about 'em.
But once we got eyes
on the big picture...
[BEYONDER F] ...we can
frame it and sell it
or burn it to smithereens!
This brain was a smart buy!
[BEYONDERS laughing]
[BEYONDERS]
Huh?
[GILBERT] Interference is a
common issue with brain control.
They'll fall for it.
Now then, Master Leonardo.
Would you kindly
track down his brain
with your All-seeing
Eyes of the Gods?
Uh, sure.
[KLAUS] Got a lock.
I'll reclaim the brain.
[GILBERT] I would ask of you
to remain behind, young sir.
Mentally accouter your feet
with his symbolic shoes.
To bear the dark onus
of burdening his master,
not to mention exposing
him to grave danger.
That is a shameful regret
that will follow him
for the rest of his life.
Not to worry, though.
I will swiftly and safely
recover his brain.
I assure you.
That is an absolute certainty.
[LEO]
Hey, there's not enough room!
So damn stoic, Gilbert.
He's right.
Nothin' wrong with askin' your
ass-kickin' friends for help.
'Cause that's what we do.
[GILBERT laughs]
[GILBERT] You'll have
to excuse me, gentlemen.
I was planning to call upon you
once I had properly
warmed up the car.
[BEYONDER D]
It's still down!
[BEYONDER C] What do we do?
They're probably on to us.
[BEYONDER E]
Want me to waste the brain?
[BEYONDER F]
You dumbass!
We still got a data treasure
trove stored in there!
[BEYONDER BOSS A]
Everyone calm down.
Brain extraction remote
signals are untraceable.
They ain't ever gonna find us.
[BEYONDER C]
You sure, boss?
[PHILIP]
So this is how I die.
A disembodied brain in a bottle
shot by frantic monsters.
Not exactly the most
dignified death.
[BEYONDER D]
Huh? Hey!
[BEYONDER C]
Who the hell's the kid?
[BEYONDER D]
Hey, you! Get out of our face!
[BEYONDERS gasp]
[GILBERT] Greetings, my fine,
enterprising thugs.
As things stand, you currently
have three options open to you.
The first, release the brain
from your possession
and abscond into the night.
The second, you can
attempt to fight us
and still lose possession
of the brain.
This option will lead to
a surfeit of casualties
on your end.
And the third, you
can foolishly panic
and destroy the brain.
This option will result in
the comprehensive massacre
of your crew.
There will be no exceptions.
We will find every last one
of you, and eviscerate you.
So which will it be?
As a reasonable man, I would
recommend option number one.
[BEYONDERS laughing]
I can practically taste the
smoke you're blowin' up my ass.
Sounds like you got some a'that
sundown dementia, gramps.
[ALL laugh]
[GILBERT]
So option one is off the table?
You reprobate fools.
Just remember....
...I tried to warn you.
Don't bother begging
for your lives.
For the crime you've committed,
I will see that you atone
in a baptismal geyser
of your own entrials and blood.
I assure you this
is not a threat.
It is an absolute certainty.
[LEO] Hey! Over there!
They're in that factory!
Can't breathe!
[BEYONDER D]
Huh?
It's up there! Second floor!
Sorry, man!
[GILBERT]
No, think nothing of it.
[BEYONDER BOSS A]
Holy crap!
[LEO, SONIC scream]
[ALL yelping]
[GILBERT]
This will be somewhat bumpy.
Please buckle up and hold tight.
[ALL]
Huh?
I'm takin' you to hell with me!
[LEO]
Gilbert, no!
[BEYONDER BOSS A]
Heh. And that's how it's done.
[GILBERT] Don't gloat,
you bush-league imbecile.
It takes more than a sword
through my head to kill me.
The most damage you've
inflicted upon me
is the pain of having to
purchase new bandages.
[GILBERT]
You'll have time to regret
challenging a Regeneratore...
...when you're
putrefying in hell!
[LEO sighs]
You hang in there,
Philip. Almost done.
[SONIC gibbers]
[ZAPP]
Ugh, man, I am starving.
[gasps]
[PHILIP]
If you had simply told us
you possessed
regenerative abilities,
then none of this
would've happened
in the first place,
Mr. Altstein.
[GILBERT]
I'm sorry for my furtiveness.
Although, this ability only
activates within my body
in the event of a fatal injury.
When it comes to any other
trauma or affliction,
I'm just a normal,
frail old man.
[PHILIP]
Uh-huh.
I must say,
despite my decrepitude,
I am quite fond of this body.
[PHILIP]
Oh?
[GILBERT] How else could I
remain by Master Klaus' side?
Attending to his needs
for many years to come.
[GILBERT chuckles]
[PHILIP sighs]
[GILBERT]
Hm?
I'm speechless. It's been
an eye-opening experience.
Literally.
I've got a lot to learn.
I can see that now.
[GILBERT]
Listen, Philip.
Sir?
Cheer up, lad.
At least you have a face
that's fit for this city now.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
[GILBERT]
So what do you say?
Would you care to formally
take a permanent position
with us at Libra?
[PHILIP gasps]
[PHILIP] Oh, no! No, no,
no, no, no! No, sir!
[LEO] Kinda have to wonder why
Klaus even needs a butler.
I mean, just look how happy
he is doing the dishes.
[STARPHASE] Although the
All-seeing Eyes of the Gods
provide him with absolute
power in matters of sight,
there's something tormenting
him he can't see.
Not that it's anything
to worry about.
I'm sure he'll find
someone out there
who can show him what it is.