[DIRECTOR A]
Stand by on camera.
We're going live the
second we arrive.
Mic check, mic check.
One-two, one-two.
All set.
[PILOT A] We've reached the
location. Entering visual range.
[ALL gasp]
It's a full-on giant!
An enormous unknown creature
has appeared on the East Rim!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[REPORTER A]
The neighborhood's residents
are desperately fleeing
in utter panic!
[LEO]
Riel.
[KLAUS] The intersection between
two worlds. Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society of super
humans toiling in the shadows
to preserve the fractured
balance between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[ALL]
Cheers, ladies!
[rumbling]
[ALL sigh]
I'm officially
plastered. Oh, boy.
Your turn, Emilina.
Last letter was "H."
[groans]
[EMILINA]
Help me, dear God.
He got his first.
My son got his first.
The deputy chief's tie
made me wanna vomit.
You all saw it, right?
Son of a bitch is so epicurean.
Nell'Echezeaux. Ornellaia.
Amontillado Musa. Santa
Neige Rela. And La Granja.
Granja?
Ha. Ha. Ha!
Actually, it ends with an "a,"
so that's playin' dirty.
Yohann, why?
He's always been my sweet,
obedient little boy.
Damn you, evil puberty!
Leave my boy alone!
Who? What? You mean?
Oh! Your son?
[ALL]
Huh?
[MI-YEON]
What?
[ALL]
Uhh...
[CITIZENS screaming]
[MI-YEON]
No, not again!
I hate this stupid game!
One more round.
You lose one more
and the bill's on you!
It's not fair!
You are awful people!
Okay. Let's go again!
[MI-YEON whines]
[ALL]
Cheers, ladies!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[CITIZENS cheering]
Whoa! Awesome!
Smash some more crap!
Let's see some destruction!
[REPORTER A gasps]
[REPORTER A]
Is that...?
Count Gigagigafutmassif!
The world's largest
sentient being!
He's stepping in
to protect the city!
Our champion has arrived!
[CITIZENS cheering]
[ALL gasp]
[BEYONDER E]
He's runnin' away!
[BEYONDER F]
Are you serious?
[BEYONDER G]
What the hell?
Frickin' coward!
Why'd I bet on him?
[RIEL] Where am I?
I can't hear anything.
The last thing I can
clearly remember
was getting shot
at by the police.
And then I got angry.
Really angry.
[GEMNEMO] You are truly
amazing, you know that?
You're like a high-tension bow
that's been drawn
to its very limit.
Your repressed fury
and my procedure
are a synergistic match
made in heaven.
I never dreamt the results
would be so sublime.
Go ahead. You deserve
to soak it in.
You can finally savor
the view from the top.
[RIEL yelps]
You meant the literal top?
[GEMNEMO]
Beautiful sight, isn't it?
You've got every
fool in this city
running to keep their
distance from you.
All the crass arrogant brutes
who've trampled on you
throughout your life now
tremble beneath you.
The power is yours now.
You tower over every last
thing on this planet.
With just a single step,
you could pulp hundreds of them
into a flood of humbled juice.
[RIEL]
No.
Whatever this is you've
done to me, I don't want it.
Your "view from
the top" is horrible.
I can't see anyone!
I can't even hear them!
The only thing you've
given me is loneliness!
[GEMNEMO] What you're
describing is tranquility.
C'mon, you've heard
the old saying,
"it's lonely at the top."
That's because you're the
only one special enough
to even see this view.
[RIEL]
Make me normal again.
[GEMNEMO]
Absolutely not.
It's the miracle to
end all miracles
that you've grown so large.
And the fact that I selected
you just confirms my genius.
I'm not letting up until I've
seen how far we can take this.
The anticipation
is driving me wild.
Ha, ha!
You've abandoned the world
of your former height,
so you might as
well say goodbye.
But it's a good thing, buddy!
Remember how it treated you?
So you just toss out those
thoughts of turning back.
Forget the whimper,
you're going out with a bang!
Holy crap!
[BEYONDER H]
Whoa! Sorry, my bad.
[LEO] Yeah, you should be sorry!
Learn to be more careful!
Huh?
Ha! You gotta be joking!
How the hell can
someone break their arm
just from catchin' a baseball?
[BEYONDERS laughing]
Apologize!
Wha--?
Knocking the ball over
here was an accident,
so I'm willing to
let that one slide.
But laughing at his injury?
Now that one pisses me off!
What're ya gonna do if I don't
apologize, ya little shit?
[RIEL] Leo didn't think twice
about standing up for me,
while I was too spineless
to even consider it.
He's one of the best
friends I've ever had.
And then I left him.
He was getting attacked
and I just ran.
Bailing on him like that,
it's inexcusable.
I'll never forgive myself
as long as I live.
And now this.
I'm so sorry, Leo.
How could I be such a fool?
I'll probably never
see you again,
but I hope that you're doing
all right down there.
[RIEL]
Help me. Please, Leo. Help me.
[GILBERT]
Owl 1 to ground team.
We are in position and
awaiting instructions.
Well? Are you getting through?
[STARPHASE grumbles]
[phone ringing]
[CHAIN laughing]
[CHAIN growls]
Shut up! Stupid glowing meat!
[OPERATOR A]
The number you have dialed
is currently out of service.
[STARPHASE]
No luck.
Ground team to Owl 1.
We're going with Plan B.
I repeat, we're going with
Plan B. Now creating diversion.
[GILBERT] Copy that. Owl 1
beginning to approach target.
All right then,
Esmerelda Blood Freeze.
[KLAUS] Brain Grid Blood Battle
Technique. Form 1-1-1.
[STARPHASE]
Lanza del Cero Absoluto!
[yells]
[KLAUS]
Kreuzvernichterlanze!
[RIEL]
Huh? What was that?
[GEMNEMO]
How cute.
Some hopeful idiots think
they still have a chance
of stopping you.
Big Dipper Style Blood
Technique. Blade number Five!
Exocrimson!
[GEMNEMO] Now I'm just annoyed.
Stomp on them already!
Huh? You hear me? Get to it!
[RIEL]
No.
[GEMNEMO] Ugh. Can't you at
least try to have some fun here?
[RIEL] My size doesn't
even matter to them.
Even against a monster like me,
they refuse to give in to fear.
I'm not moving a muscle!
No way in hell!
[GEMNEMO]
What?
[GILBERT]
Approach accomplished.
No sign that we've
been detected.
You guys ready?
I'll go ahead and
link our visual input.
[LI GADO]
Whoa! I'm looking at me!
So I'm seeing what
the monkey sees?
Your eyes are incredible.
You're like a broadcast station.
We need to move fast.
I've never pulled a stunt
this labor-intensive before,
so I don't know how quickly
it'll take to reach my limit.
[LI GADO]
Hm? Your limit?
[LEO]
Doing this generates heat.
Too much strain and my eyes
start roasting in my sockets.
[LI GADO] Then we'll do this
as quickly as possible.
[LI GADO]
Okay, in you go!
[SONIC screaming]
[LI GADO] Perfect.
He's safely entered the beast.
[K.K.]
It's just standing there.
Who knows how long
we're gonna be waiting?
[GEMNEMO] This is beginning
to get tedious.
There's really no point in
acting all sanctimonious now.
[RIEL]
Just shut the hell up!
[GEMNEMO]
Huh?
[LI GADO] Gemnemo's a textbook
megalomaniacal control freak.
There's no doubt he's inside
where he can continue
to manipulate Riel.
Oh! Go up to the left
and then right!
Got it.
[LI GADO]
If he's in there like I suspect,
he'll be positioned
somewhere on the brainstem.
[K.K.] Feels like he's been
standing there forever.
Think he'll ever move?
You should probably
keep further back.
You've at least got the luxury
of attacking from a distance.
[K.K.] As big as that thing is,
anywhere is close to it.
[LI GADO]
These sonic speed monkeys
are impressive creatures.
He's so nimble and fast,
I can hardly keep track
of his movements.
[LI GADO]
Hm?
Hm? Hey! Are you all right?
[LEO]
Yeah.
Is the visual feed still intact?
[LI GADO]
Sure. It looks fine.
But your eyes.
Don't worry about me.
Just keep going!
[GEMNEMO]
I'm done with you.
[RIEL gasps]
[GEMNEMO]
I only wanted to observe,
but you've forced my hand.
[RIEL]
Wait, what are you doing?
[GEMNEMO] I tried asking nicely,
but from here on out,
your will is inconsequential.
Ha-ha!
Once I've tapped into
your motor center,
I can control your body
like a marionette.
[RIEL]
No, stop!
[screams]
[GILBERT]
Master Leonardo!
[LI GADO] Hang on, Leo!
I know that stench!
Your eyes are frying,
aren't they?
Dammit, quit thinking about me!
Just stay focused!
[RIEL]
Stop it!
I'm begging you!
[GEMNEMO]
Shut your hole!
I'm letting you
keep your senses,
so the sounds and sensation
of the millions you crush?
You'll get to enjoy every
last scream, you loser!
[RIEL screams]
[GEMNEMO] How does that feel?
Your nerves are mine!
[GEMNEMO]
Injecting anti-rejection agent.
Activating motor
neuron emulator.
[GEMNEMO]
System takeover complete
in four, three, two, one.
[LI GADO]
Did he get him?
[gasps]
Run, Sonic!
[SONIC screaming]
[LEO]
Gilbert, hurry! Down that way!
[STARPHASE]
What's on your mind, Zapp?
Well, I was just mullin'
things over here.
We just got hit with a
potential world-ending crisis,
like some super
real shit, right?
And yet, we send in the kid
who looks like a
mugshot of a nut sack?
I mean, sure, his partner over
here's got a little more brains.
But he's still a freakin' monkey
who spends hours on end
tryin' to lick his own junk.
So this just feels like a real
shit show of an operation to me.
[LEO]
Really?! So what? You jealous?
[ZAPP]
In your dreams, scrotum-scalp!
Quit callin' me that!
Look, all I'm sayin',
we got a team member
who specializes
in stealth, don't we?
[CHAIN grunts]
[LI GADO]
Now that you mention it,
if Sonic had come across
any obstruction, well,
that would've been
it for all of us.
Exactly!
That's precisely the damn point
I'm tryin' to make here!
Our master of
clandestine affairs,
able to pass through walls
and slip through the
cracks of reality itself,
was nowhere to be found!
I'm-I'm sorry, okay?
Saying you're sorry
doesn't rewrite history!
[KLAUS]
All right, Zapp, calm down.
Why should I?!
She completely bailed on
us at a critical moment!
It's only right that we get
some kind of explanation!
Be that as it may,
she doesn't deserve this
public persecution.
She already feels guilty
enough as it is.
Aww, is she-bitch
wracked with remorse?
Not good enough!
I'm not gonna be satisfied
until I get an answer!
[CHAIN]
All right, I'll tell you.
[ZAPP]
A freakin' girl's night out?
With the rest of the
Werewolf Bureau?
Les Hallis apparently
had to close down
for the rest of the week.
They drank the
restaurant entirely dry.
[ZAPP]
Huh?
[STARPHASE] They managed to just
about empty the wine cellar
in a single night.
[ZAPP]
Are you some kind of monster?
No, really, you are, aren't you?
I'm so embarrassed right now.
[ZAPP]
As you should be!
Maybe practice a little
self-control from time to time!
Do you realize that our job
entails saving the world
at a moment's notice?
Yeah. How 'bout you
take your own advice?
Huh?
Let's examine the facts at hand.
You tried to strong arm
cash out of a stranger
and wound up in the ICU.
[CHAIN]
Huh?
Asshole!
Shh! Shh!
I'm failing to see how exactly
Chain inconvenienced you,
considering you were in the
hospital the entire time.
And with the three different
harassment complaints
the nurses filed on you, there's
a paper trail to prove it.
[ZAPP gasps]
[thud]
[LEO]
Ow!
[ZAPP laughing]
Oh, you, joker, you!
However do you come up with
all these funny stories?
--[LEO] Please, stop!
--[ZAPP laughing]
[LEO] It's been five
days now since Riel
tumbled into the Eternal Hollow.
At the moment he fell,
everyone braced
themselves for the impact.
But that giant hole,
it just swallowed him up
without a sound.
[LI GADO] And that's all there
is to it. Problem solved!
[LEO grumbles]
[LEO] Li Gado's convinced his
procedure-reversal program
successfully reverted Riel.
[LEO] But still, I'm really
not sure what to think.
Actually, I'm just
not sure how I feel.
[LEO]
It's just...
If Riel is actually alive
at the bottom of that hole,
I can't help but
worry about him.
[LEO]
And how lonely he must feel.
[LEO, RIEL laughing]
[grunting]
Hey, Leo, good to see ya.
What the hell?!
[LEO]
Oh! That's it!
Let's talk to Dr. Li Gado.
I bet he can help.
[RIEL]
I'm okay, Leo.
[LEO]
Huh?
After the havoc I
managed to cause,
I'm wholly comfortable accepting
this as my true height.
[LEO]
Are you sure?
Believe me.
The view from down here?
It really puts the
world in perspective.
Hey, y'know what, Riel?
I think you've grown.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I guess I have.
[LEO]
Ah! Riel!
[RIEL laughs]
[KLAUS]
Hmm.
Hey, Steven. Has Zapp
been in yet today?
He's at Central Hospital.
Not again.
Doesn't sound like a pretty
sight when they found him.
His face was swollen
three times its size
and there were five sets
of handprints on him.
[LI GADO] And that's all there
is to it. Problem solved!
[LEO grumbles]
[K.K.] Children know not
their parents' hearts,
and parents know not
their children's.
And there's a good chance
they might not mesh.
In the end, there's
one thing for certain.
Nobody is ever loved the
way they truly want to be.
It's tough having kids.