[phone ringing]
[VELVED] Well, well, well!
Hello, General Gahnen.
I had a funny feeling you'd
be calling me about now.
[GAHNEN]
Cut the horse shit!
Is this intel about the werewolf
squad incursion authentic?
[VELVED laughs]
[VELVED] The rumors have
been lighting up the Alternet
for a whole three minutes
now, so it must be true.
It's also highly likely
the intel was leaked
by the werewolves themselves.
[GAHNEN]
Why the hell would they do that?
[VELVED] No reason for
them to keep it a secret.
And, of course, they want you
to know they're coming for you.
It's more fun for them that way.
[VELVED laughs]
[VELVED] I'd back against
a wall if I were you.
They're probably
already in your room.
[KLAUS] The intersection between
two worlds. Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society of super
humans toiling in the shadows
to preserve the fractured
balance between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[DELIMID] So, the five of you
managed to let loose
a total of 94 rounds...
and every one of them missed?!
That takes some real talent!
Wow! Thanks for saying so!
We'll do even better
on the next job!
Yeah, sorry about that.
[DELIMID growls]
Well, hey.
If you're not happy,
you handle the next one.
[DELIMID]
What was that?!
Killing is unnecessary
for a show of force.
Scare tactics work just fine.
[OLGA]
I...
...need a drink.
[growls]
[OGAMU] Now, now,
take a breath, Delimid.
Espionage has been the only
focus of our agency so far,
and it should remain that way.
If you want my feelings on this,
despite their natural skills,
I don't believe these ladies
were intended to be assassins.
Yeah!
Precisely stated, Chief!
Suck it, Delimid!
[DELIMID]
That's uncalled for!
See ya, Chain!
[OLGA]
Good work today!
Right back at ya!
[JANET]
Great job!
[MI-YEON]
Hey, Chain!
Chain, hang on!
Hey, Chain! Will you
please wait a second?
[yelping]
[CHAIN] Still haven't made
your mind up yet, have you?
About your token, I mean.
Isn't that what you wanna ask?
[MI-YEON]
Well, yeah.
[CHAIN]
You need to make a decision.
It's pretty damn important.
[MI-YEON] Trust me, I know.
It's just that--
I guess I'm still kinda
figuring out who I am, y'know?
It's super hard to pin
down one single thing
I care about so much that
it ties me to reality.
I mean, for Emelina,
it's gotta be her kid, right?
For Olga, I'm guessing
it's alcohol.
And then Janet,
well, it's probably--
Gonna stop you right there.
It's against the rules
to pry like that.
Our tokens are crucial,
and they can even be
fatal if they're misused.
So...
Sorry, kid, no way in hell
I'm gonna tell you mine.
[MI-YEON]
Aww.
[CHAIN]
Bye, now.
Oh, come one, Chain,
please help me out here!
[LEO]
Come on!
How is it possible that you
forget every single time?
[NEJ chuckles]
[LEO] Don't give me that
"heh-heh-heh" crap!
I've been waiting here
for a full five hours!
I'm lucky I noticed
you happen to pass by.
No telling how long
I would've been here.
[NEJ chuckles]
"Heh-heh-heh!" Stop laughing!
Look, just get a
cellphone, all right?
[NEJ] But, Leo...
I can't buy a cellphone.
If I had that kinda money,
I'd just-- I would buy...
I'd buy burgers!
[LEO] You don't think I know
that?! You have zero willpower!
All right, that's it!
No burgers for you tomorrow!
[NEJ screams]
[LEO] Take the day
to learn consideration
and how to be on time!
[NEJ]
Bur-- Bu. Bu. Bu. Bu. Bu.
Burgers!
No, please. Burgers!
Bu. Bu. Burger.
Ha-Hamburger. Eat. Eat.
A hamburger. Uh?
Huh?
[CHAIN laughs]
[CHAIN] You there, the fat
little mushroom fellow.
Are you a friend of
Leonardo Watch's?
Yeah! I am!
Bur-Leo-ger ham-Watch-burger
is my bestest friend
in the whole wide world!
That's a terrible mnemonic
device for remembering his name,
but whatever works, I guess.
Life can be difficult
for the forgetful.
A string of missed opportunities
and inscrutable tribulations.
I wonder what's takin'
bur-Leo-ger so long.
[CHAIN]
Hey!
[NEJ]
Huh?
Holy crap, your memory
is nonexistent.
Write the stuff you need
to remember in that pad
and carry it with you.
Right, I will! Brilliant!
Hey, who are you, by the way?
Uh?
For the time being,
you may refer to me as
the spirit of hamburgers.
[NEJ]
Huh?!
Would you like fries with that?
[CHAIN] Well, that had a
terrifying effect on him.
Maybe I should've chosen
a different identity.
[phone ringing]
Chain here.
[STARPHASE] Hey, good work
today. You off the clock?
Yep.
It went off without a hitch.
I doubt the general will
try to move forward
with his Blood Breed soldier
program after this.
Pretty sure he got the message.
Well, let's hope so.
Hang on a sec. Schedule's
pretty clear today.
Why don't you head on home
and get some rest?
[CHAIN]
Sounds good to me.
[CHAIN humming]
[sighs]
[CHAIN] Aw, dammit.
Did I just pop a button?
Whatever. Forget it.
I've gotta... brush my teeth...
[door opens]
Hey. Any new developm--?
I'm guessing you got bad news.
Yeah.
[VELVED] The so-called
invisible werewolves.
They currently exist everywhere,
and yet they exist nowhere.
That is the state
of their being.
[GAHNEN]
Enough with the riddles!
I'm asking how the hell
they were able to bypass
my mansion's panoptic
security system!
Five of them, just
appearing like ghosts.
[VELVED] Fifty experienced
guards, infrared alarms,
thermal sensors, motion
detectors, etcetera, etcetera.
[VELVED sighs]
[VELVED] Sorry to tell you,
but that's child's play to them.
[GAHNEN]
How is that possible?!
[VELVED] Although they're
referred to as "invisible,"
their stealth far exceeds
optical parameters.
Their shape, weight,
temperature, physicality, odor,
hell, even their very causality,
they can diminish every single
aspect of their existence
to an infinitesimal degree.
In other words, they can
alter reality to only exist
where and when they want to.
But don't you worry.
There are very few
of them in the world
and their powers
are not boundless.
Once they return to
their human form,
you can kill them
like any other person.
You're certain of that?
[VELVED laughs]
[VELVED]
One hundred percent, General.
You won't even need
a silver bullet.
[ZAPP groaning]
[ZAPP grunts]
[CHAIN] Hey, Gilbert,
got you a little gift.
[GILBERT] Mm. A most impressive
vase. Lovely choice.
You do have a rather exquisite
eye for appurtenances, Chain.
I can pick out a vase,
just don't ask me to arrange
the flowers, though.
But ya got no problems
rearranging my face, she-bitch!
Usin' me like you're in some
80's skateboard movie.
My face is not a half-pipe!
How 'bout I pull a
Rocky training montage
on those huge
speedbags of yours?
[growls]
[ZAPP whimpers]
File that under
sexual harassment.
Hey!
[ZED] Your quick wit just
swerved and crashing
into a vat of
inappropriate behavior.
[chuckles]
Nice to see the team dynamic
is as strong as ever.
Stop sneakin' around
and listening
to what people say, Gilbert!
[phone rings]
Yes, this is Chain.
Sounds urgent.
[DELIMID] These images were
captured three hours ago.
It's one of the country's
eight missile bases,
and it's currently on
standby to launch.
The target is unknown.
But the intel we've received
from various sources
cites "BB virus warheads."
"BB"? As in Blood Breed?
[DELIMID]
Let's try to avoid conjecture.
Although, given the
country's attempts
to manufacture vampire soldiers,
we can't rule out
the possibility.
Um, Delimid?
Yes, Emilina?
I'm 99% certain this is a trap.
And I agree.
But we still can't risk not
doing anything about it either.
Especially since we're the only
ones who can do something.
This is the floorplan
of the base.
The missile control mainframe
is housed in the central room
with four backups
surrounding it.
If even one of the
hubs goes down,
the system will
immediately crosscheck
with the other terminals
and reboot itself.
So your only option
is to take down
the four backups simultaneously.
The central system will
then be left vulnerable
for you to disable it.
One question.
How are we getting in?
[JANET] There don't appear
to be any infiltration routes.
No, there is one.
[DELIMID]
They're not expecting
high altitude
freefall infiltration.
[gasps]
[PILOT A] Failure to
prevent missile launch!
Plan B is now in effect!
Disable the warhead and
redirect it to the ocean!
[SUBORDINATE A] The control
subsystems are malfunctioning!
[GAHNEN]
Is it them?
[AIDE A]
They're incredible.
If we weren't anticipating
their interference,
all of this would look just
like a normal malfunction.
[SUBORDINATE A] Subsystems down!
One through four have gone dark.
The main system
is fully exposed!
[STAFF A] Wait, they're in
the middle of an operation!
[STAFF B] We can't allow
you to go in there!
[DELIMID]
Hm? What is this, Klaus?
[OGAMU]
Is something wrong, my lad?
You tell me.
[KLAUS] Do you recognize
this woman, Chief?
[OGAMU]
Hmm... Let's take a look.
The woman you see,
that's Velved Rheinkeimer.
[DELIMID]
Uh! Are you serious?
[OGAMU] Well, she has certainly
changed her appearance
since her time spent with
the Werewolf Bureau.
[KLAUS]
Makes sense.
Plastic surgery is a
fugitive's best friend.
Dammit!
I knew we should've killed her
when we had the chance.
[KLAUS] So she's still aiming
to take down the werewolves?
I don't see how she
possibly could.
Due to the level of injuries she
sustained in our last battle,
she no longer possesses the
ears, eyes, or nose it takes
to even detect another werewolf.
There it is. Motive.
This photo, it was taken
just under two weeks ago now.
[STARPHASE] Our intel shows she
closed a transaction on that day
with a dangerous
entity who resides
in the recesses of
Hellsalem's Lot.
The merchant in question...
was Zeodra the Heretic.
Among the 13 Kings, he's proven
to be the most mercurial.
Tottering between
madness and lucidity,
his senses are
constantly bombarded
with the deluge of light,
sound, and vibration
flooding through all
of Hellsalem's Lot.
If she gained even a tincture of
Zeodra's ubiquitary sensitivity,
Velved Rheinkeimer will
find the werewolves.
[VELVED] Hi there, sweetie,
how've you been?
Long time no see, huh?
[VELVED] To think of how long
we worked with one another.
You could've at least written.
I know that voice. It can't be!
Rheinkeimer?
[VELVED laughs]
How the hell are you
alive, you bitch?
[VELVED] I would be
a little more delicate
with my choice of
words if I were you.
I'm literally clutching
your lives in my hands.
[EMILINA]
But how?
Our existence is diluted
beyond perception!
[VELVED] Oh, diminish yourselves
as much as you want.
No matter how many
times you divide it,
one will never become zero.
There will always be
a scant trace of you.
Unless you go so far as to
wipe out your existence,
I have the means to find you.
You're an even bigger
monster than before.
What kind of deal did you make?!
[VELVED]
Shut up!
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
I spent way too much for
you to ruin this for me!
You all chose this
fate for yourselves.
If you had only gone
along with my plan,
we would all be billionaires
and the closest of friends.
But I digress.
Only thing left to do is
get my hands on Chain.
I'm not gonna pretend like
I ever cared much
for the young lady.
She clearly thought she was
better than everyone else.
[EMILINA] Just get the
hell out of here, Chain.
[VELVED]
Wow, you mean that?
And just turn her back
on the ticking console?
Once the system's restored,
that bomb goes boom.
[VELVED laughs]
[CHAIN laughs]
[CHAIN] An invisible werewolf
falling defenseless prey
to something that can be seen?
Don't make me laugh.
[CHAIN]
Nope. No way. Nu-uh.
So you want me to prove how
much better I am than you?
Let's head for the
horizon of causality.
Try to catch me if you can!
Existence Dilute!
Don't do it.
[VELVED] 1st Sensitivity.
2nd Sensitivity.
3rd Sensitivity!
Where the hell are you?
Dammit. Time to go deeper.
4th Sensitivity!
Where are you?!
Dammit, you bitch,
where the hell are you?
Still no sign. How much did that
crazy mongrel dilute herself?
[gasps]
[VELVED]
Now I've got you!
She dissolved even further.
Don't tell me...
Did she stick her tail out
just to rub it in my face?
[VELVED]
Nobody mocks me!
13th Sensitivity!
[EMILINA]
Chain. You gotta stop!
Any further and you
won't make it back.
Please, don't. It'll be like
you never even existed!
[VELVED yells]
[VELVED] What the hell? Is this
the only thing left of her?
[VELVED screams]
[EMILINA] Casper 1 to HQ.
Plan B achieved.
Repeat. Plan B achieved.
Team status.
Casper 4 is missing.
Requesting Emergency
Salvage Protocol.
[groaning]
[GILBERT]
Good morning, Zapp.
I don't really see what's
so good about it.
[GILBERT] Would you care for
me to brew a pot of coffee?
[ZAPP]
Sure. Brew two pots.
[LEO] I can't believe
you're late again!
I told you to figure out
a way to fix this!
[NEJ chuckles]
[STARPHASE]
Token? What the hell is that?
I'm not following
you at all here.
You don't have to understand.
Just follow the
directions, okay?
That token expresses
Chain's most ardent need
for her existence.
It's her strongest tie
to this reality,
and her 100%, fail-safe,
pure reason to return.
Wait, this is her reason?
Hold on, what am I
doing here again?
[DELIMID grunting]
Ohh. That's right.
[STARPHASE] Better get
this over with quickly.
Just do it exactly as written.
Um, hello, there, Chain!
I've come to visit you!
[CHAIN grunting]
Um. Okay.
[CHAIN screaming]
[LEO screams]
[LEO]
You got here before me?!
And I'm running
15 minutes early!
[ZAPP]
Whoa, hey, Steven.
What the hell
happened to you, man?
Y'know, Zapp,
just don't even ask.
Actually, great question,
please do ask.
[ZAPP]
So, which is it?
[STARPHASE] I only went over
to Chain's apartment
and did as I was told, and this?
This is the result! So you
explain to me what happened!
[ZAPP]
Heh?
[GILBERT]
"Quarrels should be avoided."
And that most certainly
applies to this city.
The direct approach is likely
to lead to your own defeat.
That is why I always
choose to make a point
of hanging several steps back.
And it can appear
intimidating as well.