[MICHELLA]
Oh, c'mon. Enough, Leo.
Leo.
We're right on the edge
of Hellsalem's Lot.
Why are you taking
pictures of your sister?
Wait. Didn't this...
already happen?
[MICHELLA]
You okay?
[gasps]
Michella!
[MENUHYUT]
You must choose.
[MENUHYUT] Which one of
you two will bear witness?
Don't do it!
If you must, then
take my sight from me!
[CITIZENS screaming]
[LEO]
Uh.
Eh?
[ANNOUNCEMENT A] Count
Gigagigafutmassif is on the move
through the city!
All citizens!
It is your responsibility
to avoid his path!
I repeat!
Count Gigagigafutmassif is
on the move through the city!
All citizens!
It is your responsibility
to avoid his path!
[KLAUS] The intersection between
two worlds. Hellsalem's Lot.
Libra, a secret society of super
humans toiling in the shadows
to preserve the fractured
balance between worlds.
These are the records
of our covert missions.
[PUNK A laughs]
[PUNK A]
So friggin' awesome.
That alone's worth the scratch
we spent on the tourism package.
[PUNK B] Says here he's the
biggest sentient lifeform
in the world, boss.
Oh! Excuse me.
Nah.
Don't think I wanna
excuse you, twerp.
Uh. Sorry, I--
[PUNK A] Step over here
a minute, shit bag.
[LEO]
Please!
Hey! Chain!
[LEO]
What?!
[thudding]
[sighs]
[STARPHASE]
Oh. Morning, Mrs. Veded.
[VEDED] Well, morning might
be a bit of a stretch, sir.
Are you all rested up for
your dinner party tonight?
Yeah. How're all the
arrangements goin' for that?
[VEDED] Everything's
already taken care of.
You are the best.
I wouldn't even wanna
throw this party
without your specialty
roast beef.
[phone ringing]
Relax. I've got it.
This is Steven.
[ELLEN yawns]
[ELLEN] Hi, Steven. You're
sure up bright and early.
It's already 11 o'clock, Ellen.
You sound like you're some
kinda decadent empress.
Lounging in bed while her
servants feed her grapes.
[ELLEN chuckles]
[ELLEN] Are you adequately
stocked up on wine for tonight?
Well, it's just an
intimate soiree,
so I'm sure we'll be all right.
But if you're offering
to bring a bottle,
I won't discourage you.
We can always share
it some other time
if we don't get to it tonight.
[phone rings]
[STARPHASE]
Hello.
[LARRY]
Steven, my man.
Your pad has a pretty
good-sized terrace, right?
You got a grill out there?
[STARPHASE] Wouldn't be
a terrace without one.
[LARRY]
Hell yeah!
I'm bringing some
primo cuts and spices.
You're gonna love 'em. Ciao.
[STARPHASE]
What's up?
[VEDED chuckles]
Nothing.
I'm just glad to see you
in such a good mood.
You've been so tense.
I know you've been
under a lot of stress,
so you deserve some fun.
You could tell that?
[gasps]
[STARPHASE]
No. I mean.
Your intuition's spot-on.
I'm just known around my office
for being a bit
difficult to read.
So you kinda threw me
for a loop, there.
Sorry.
[chuckles]
Oh, Zapp!
Christ, c'mon, Tracy.
Is knocking too much to ask?
This is my bedroom, you bitch!
There better not be
stains on those sheets!
[chuckles]
That talking tea--
[TRACY] Snap out of it,
you callous dumb ass!
She's gone! Mizaria's gone!
The old lady I buy
cigarettes from?
My cat! My precious
Oriental Shorthair, you jerk!
Oh, please, no!
I can't go on living if
something's happened to her!
She's the one thing
in this world I love!
[SHARON]
Oh my God, quit whining!
It's just a stupid cat.
Besides, she's probably
churning around
in some demonbeast's
belly by now.
Might as well put
up missing fliers
with a picture of
a turd on them.
[TRACY growls]
Um. What're you--?
[TRACY chanting]
Oh, shit! How did I forget?
Her entire family are members...
This bed's like a
thousand feet long.
Man, you must hav'ta special
order these sheets, huh?
[SHARON]
I'm sorry!
What?
[SHARON screams]
[ZAPP]
Huh?
Scumbag! Get out there
and find my cat!
Unless you want your prick
to wind up like Sharon's tits!
[ZAPP]
Holy shit! Hey, stop!
You've got 13 hours to find
Mizaria and safely return her
if you want that spell removed!
[ZAPP] What are you,
the freaking devil?!
Find my cat or I'll pop your
dick like a balloon animal!
[LEO groans]
[SONIC gibbering]
Thanks a bunch for
the backup there.
Not that I blame you.
Oh, crap.
Those creeps made off
with the allowance
I saved up for Michella.
Damn it.
[LEO]
Yeah, yeah.
You wanna know why I let
those guys get away
with hitting me like that.
Yeah, sure, I know.
I could've easily gotten away.
All I would've had to do
is hijack their vision
with these eyes of mine.
[LEO] Look, it's hard
for me to explain.
But using these eyes just
to save my own ass?
I don't know, it feel
kinda wrong to me.
[BEYONDER A]
Huh...
Might be that one there.
[meows]
[ZAPP]
Oh, thank you, God, that's her!
Here, kitty, kitty,
kitty, kitty.
Wait, kitty?
[snarling]
[grunts]
[ZAPP] Hey, why'd it
get all dark and warm?
Are you high or just stupid?
Acting like that,
you were practically
begging Nego to eat you.
[doorbell rings]
Here we go.
Steven! Darling!
[ELLEN chuckles]
How are you?
More composed than when
you called me this morning.
This is Christopher.
Hello.
How's it goin'?
[LARRY] And I thought
I was showin' up early.
Larry! You made it!
I'm hoping you've got
a big ass fridge.
[STARPHASE]
Damn, Larry,
you brought a whole
meat locker with ya.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot to check if
we have any charcoal.
Dammit.
Heh! You start without us?
Well, maybe one or two.
[CHARLIE] Crippling symptoms
of working too hard.
The only known cure is for us
to drink you under
the table tonight.
[STARPHASE chuckles]
[STARPHASE] I better go hang an
IV for tomorrow, in that case.
Come on in. Make
yourselves at home.
[LARRY]
You do that,
but don't be surprised if I fill
your IV bag with Opus One.
[STARPHASE]
Hey, Veded.
Thank you, but I can
take it from here.
You can head on home.
You're sure?
[GUESTS chattering]
Thanks for all your help.
Well, if you're certain.
Now then.
[STARPHASE]
All right, everyone. Shall we?
[GUESTS cheering]
Huh? A weapon?
So, you've finally come
to your senses, have you?
A dinky little squirt like you,
it's just crazy to be walkin'
around this city unarmed.
Now what's a good fit for you?
[chuckles]
Wha'cha think?
She cuts a ten
foot diameter hole
in the fabric of space itself!
[PATRICK sighs]
[PATRICK]
Huh? That one?
That's nothin' but a stun baton.
Can't even kill your
opponent with that thing.
That's fine by me. I'll take it.
[PATRICK]
Hmm...
[PUNK A laughs]
[PUNK A]
Let's do some shots!
--[WAITRESS A] Watch it, creep!
--[LEO] There he is.
[PUNKS laughing]
[LEO]
Hey!
I-I want my wallet!
Piss off.
I don't won'chur whiny,
ugly-ass face ruinin' my night.
That money is for
my blind sister.
I'm asking you to
do the right thing--
Do I really strike you as
the type to give a shit
about anyone's sister?
Blind or not.
Real scary. I'm pissin'
my pants here.
[LEO] It won't kill you,
but it'll hurt like hell.
The shock'll just knock you out
and keep you still for a bit.
[PUNK A]
You sure it won't kill me?
What if I've got a pacemaker
or just some kind of
weak heart condition?
'Cause that would make
you a murderer.
[chuckles]
[PUNK A]
Here. Ya left this.
[LEO screams]
All right, Hellsalem's
Lot's a joke.
One thousand years
of domination my ass.
Cleveland's tougher than this.
[PUNKS laughing]
[PUNK B]
Ahh...
Well. Hello, beautiful.
Ya just get here?
No way in hell I
could've overlooked
a gorgeous fox like you.
Don't think I've
seen you before.
Wait, are you from outside?
Ya got me.
Thought I'd get a firsthand look
at this big ol' scary city.
Gotta say I'm disappointed
with how tame it is.
I mean, if a sexy girl like
you feels safe enough
to go out drinkin' on her own.
Well, it can't be too
dangerous then, right?
[CHAIN] Actually, that's
where you'd be wrong.
I always find a big,
strong man to protect me.
[chuckles]
Well, that's one thing
we're good for.
Well, here's to meeting new
people. Have a drink on me.
[CHAIN]
Thank you.
[PUNK A laughs]
A gal after my own heart!
[CHAIN]
I won't lie, I do like to drink.
How about a game?
If you can drink
more than I do,
you can do anything
you want with me.
Anything.
You're on!
Hey, outsider.
Do you really think
you can outdrink her?
Or are ya bluffin'?
What the hell is it to you?
[DEMON B]
I got a hundred on Chain!
[DEMON C]
I'll go 50!
[MAN A]
Two hundred!
[THE PROFESSOR]
Three thousand on the outsider.
[BAR PATRONS shouting]
[ZAPP howling]
[ZAPP howls]
[CROWD cheering]
[PUNK A] What the hell
kinda booze is this?
Don't tell me these freaks
drink this shit every night.
Man, it's like I can
hear my own blood
screaming through my veins.
[CROWD cheering]
[PUNK A] Shut your mouths,
you goddamn morons!
Every noise is like an atomic
explosion in my skull!
[PUNK A] I'm starting to
suspect she's hustlin' me.
[GUESTS cheer]
Well, Jim and I were first
introduced at the theater.
Porno?
Oh, you're so gauche.
[GUEST D] It was fully made to
order by the Maxium Milligan.
Seriously?
[GUEST F] Have you tried this
Vavradugo-based quiche yet?
[GUEST G] These recipes of
Cynthia's are delectable.
[LARRY]
You out, Charlie?
[CHARLIE]
Yep.
Hang on. You guys runnin'
low on beer? I got it.
Thank you, oh gracious host!
Here. See?
[STARPHASE]
Is this some kinda party game?
[ELLEN]
Sorry, but the party's over.
Although you, Steven Alan
Starphase, member of Libra,
are invited to leave with us.
If you refuse, we'll
just have to kill you
and take your brain.
Well, and your flesh and bones.
A little postmortem doggy bag.
[STARPHASE] Hmm, sorry, I'm
afraid you've got the wrong guy.
Furthermore, Ellen.
I thought I'd
introduced you to Larry
for the very first
time this evening.
But if you already
knew each other,
well, now, that would've been...
...really fucking rude.
[gasps]
[STARPHASE]
You're unbelievable.
Easiest thing to do would've
been to riddle me with holes
without a word.
So you were ordered
to take me alive, huh?
Who the hell is your boss?
'Cause they gave you an
incredibly foolish mission.
Do you really expect
us to tell you that?
[STARPHASE] 'Course not.
I just wish I could thank them.
I won't have to ruin any of
my furniture with your blood.
Also, it would've
been heartbreaking
to watch Veded's roast beef get
wasted by haphazard bullets.
This tough guy act you're going
for is laughable right now.
Make any sudden movements
and you're dead.
Our employer can make
do with your corpse.
Sudden movements?
What? Like to attack you?
[chuckles]
I took care of that before you
even walked through the door.
[STARPHASE]
Esmerelda Blood Freeze.
Aguja del Cero Absoluto.
Feels like you've
got icy needles
running through your
veins, doesn't it?
When? How long have you known?
When did you--?
Well, I did have my suspicions.
But you had me fooled
until a minute ago.
You guys played it
off well. Really.
The biogenic guns
were a smart move
for getting past the
building security,
but you should've bought
them before you met me.
Larry, your center of mass
has shifted to the left
since I last saw
you ten days ago.
And Ellen.
That sharp,
sweet-smelling grease
specific to biological weapons?
You tried to conceal it
with too much perfume,
which is very unlike you.
You should've used a different
brand than your regular.
That being said.
I regret to inform you that you
will now be dragged screaming
into the bottomless
abyss of darkness.
[ELLEN]
Who is that? Is it Libra?
Not even close.
Our leader would never allow
the unspeakable things
that you're about to endure.
These guys are my
own private squad.
They operate in secret under
my independent command.
[ELLEN gasping]
Sorry to put you
through the trouble.
What a mess.
That's exactly what
we're here for.
[STARPHASE] I've gotta take a
walk and get some fresh air.
We won't be very long.
Everything will be cleared.
[CROWD chattering]
[PUNK A grunting]
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD]
Chain! Chain! Chain!
She's some kinda monster.
[PUNK B]
You okay, boss?
[PUNK B growls]
[PUNKS gasp]
Thanks for showing a
lady a good time, guys.
It's been a blast.
--What the hell?
--Hey, wait a second!
--That's my money, you bitch!
--Get back here, you!
[BARTENDER A]
A pity you lost,
but that does leave you
gentlemen to settle the bill.
Torakichi, you're
gonna have to cover it.
The thing is,
Boss, with what?
You mean she cleaned
you out too?
Well, I guess she screwed all
of us. Sorry 'bout that, pal.
[BARTENDER A]
What?
Don't you "what" us!
You saw the shit she
pulled! Smug bastard!
[PUNK B screams]
[BARTENDER A] Our policy is
clearly posted on the door.
If you drink in our
establishment
with no means of paying,
then we'll simply have to find
another method of payment.
[ZAPP]
Oh, thank God! Leo!
Holy crap, what is the
matter with you, Zapp?
A cat! You've gotta
find a cat for me!
Use your super god eyes
and hunt it down, please!
What now?
[ZAPP screams]
Tracy thinks I lost
her stupid cat!
She cast a Banalcadeth spell
on Lieutenant Freedom Magnum
and I've only got
about 30 minutes
before she assassinates him!
[LEO]
Right then.
All I got from that was that
you don't have much time.
Regardless, even with
my All-Seeing Eyes,
I can't track a cat
I've never seen before.
Sorry, dude!
[ZAPP wailing]
[PASSERBY A]
Huh?
Watch where yer walkin',
ya freakin' twerp!
Ah! I'm sorry, sir!
Idiot!
Didn't I tell ya we gotta keep
close to the sides now?
--[clattering]
--[PUNK B screams]
[meowing]
Uh. Hi, kitty.
--[CAT hisses]
--[PUNK A screams]
[PUNK B]
Boss, no!
Back off, flea bag!
Lay one more paw on the boss
and I'll bite your face off!
[VEDED] Calm down, you two.
Fighting never solves anything.
Hi, I'm Ellen. Pleased
to meet you, Steven.
Name's Larry. How's it hangin'?
[STARPHASE]
Yeah.
I get it. I dropped my
guard for some fun.
[brakes squeal]
[door opens]
[VEDED]
Mr. Starphase?
[STARPHASE]
Veded?
What're you doing out here, sir?
Don't tell me the
party's already over.
Well, uh, yeah.
[GAMIEL]
Hey, Mom!
[VEDED]
Oh, this is my son, Gamiel,
and my daughter, Emilida.
[GAMIEL]
Nice to meet you.
And you as well.
Huh? Now that is one cute cat.
[EMILIDA chuckles]
We just found her on the street.
[LEO]
Don't give up yet!
Crawl on your hands and knees
and beg her to remove
the curse if you have to!
I can't!
The only thing that'll quench
her fury is dick blood!
She's out of her freakin' mind!
[GAMIEL, EMILIDA chuckle]
[PUNK B yelps]
They seem like
they're great kids.
[VEDED] They manage to
put me through my paces.
[EMILIDA]
Hey, no biting!
[PUNK B screams]
[STARPHASE]
Hey, Veded.
Yes, sir?
Thank you. For everything.
[VEDED]
Huh?
[chuckles]
[ZAPP]
Die! Why can't she just die?!
[ZAPP screams]
[LEO]
Oh. Hey, it's Steven.
[ZAPP]
How could she does this to me?!
Look at that.
Heh. It's like everyone I know
is out on the town tonight.
[ZAPP] The more life people
get under their belts,
the more they wish
they could forget.
Most of those memories
involve women in my case.
But to live without experiencing
anything worth forgetting?
Now that right there,
that is called regret.