[TESSA] I know I haven't come
to visit in a very long time.
So I thought I'd make it
a point to stop by today.
After all, things are only
going to get rougher.
[sighs]
[LEONARD]
Teletha.
[gasps]
I'm surprised.
Didn't think I'd see you.
I'm surprised, too.
Seeing you here.
I wasn't sure if you even
remembered mom and dad.
We're all bound by memory.
I was also hoping that maybe
I could persuade you to join me.
Ah.
Come now. I think it's time you
stopped being so stubborn.
You're not a child.
Enough.
[TESSA] Save your breath.
Because brother or not,
you're now my enemy!
Very well. I can see you've
already made up your mind.
That's right. A long time ago.
I suppose I'll let it
go for today. Fowler?
[FOWLER]
Yes, Master Leonard?
Time to go.
[FOWLER]
As you wish, sir.
Farewell, Teletha,
and to him as well.
[SOUSUKE]
Captain, are you all right?
[TESSA]
I'm fine. Time to withdraw.
[SOUSUKE]
Roger that.
This is Gebo Nine.
Now descending to Point Golf.
Urzu Seven, prepare for docking.
Urzu Seven, roger that.
[TESSA]
I'm sorry for the trouble,
and with school about to start.
It's fine.
Ah.
[LEONARD] Mr. Kurama.
What brings you here?
I was in the area.
Thought I'd come see you.
[LEONARD]
How fortunate.
Rumor has it that you were
meeting with Mithril's witch.
[LEONARD]
My little sister?
[KURAMA] Apparently that
white AS was there as well.
Why didn't you neutralize it?
That certainly would've
made things easier, from here.
Because it most likely would
have ended in a draw.
I imagine they were ready
for any move we might make.
[KURAMA]
What about that Belial of yours?
Thought it was the best.
The unit's still
being fine-tuned,
we were a little short on time.
[KURAMA chuckles]
I wonder,
is loyalty to our organization
the thing you're short on,
Leonard Testarossa?
Maybe, time will tell.
[KURAMA]
I don't plan on holding back.
I'll hunt them down,
whatever it takes.
Both Sousuke Sagara,
as well as this Chidori girl.
Do what you need to do.
[KURAMA] Both Gauron and
Gates played around too much.
I will not.
Also, your predicted Zero Hour,
is only 58 hours away.
Predicted? It was foreseen.
That doesn't matter.
I will continue to follow
the plan of operation.
Also. You better stay
out of my way from now on.
He's quite unpleasant.
[LEONARD]
He's the serious type.
But in that respect, I find
him more than reliable.
[KYOKO] Okay, the results of
the ballot count are in!
The numbers are clear, so
therefore, without futher ado,
the next student council
president will be Yui Morikawa!
[students cheer]
[KYOKO]
That's everything!
Which means your
final significant duty
has now been completed!
Hayashimizu, excellent work.
Thank you for your kind words,
Ms. Kagurazaka.
It looks like I can now
graduate without any
concerns for the
future of this school.
Of course. With your
successor chosen,
you can retire in peace.
We'll be in very good hands.
And now you're on
your way in politics,
making your mark on history!
[chuckles]
I doubt it, madam.
Although. I certainly did
enjoy myself playing the role.
[ERI]
Oh really?
Pardon. With the
election results in,
should I post them on the
board in the morning, ma'am?
[ERI]
Yes, please do.
Well, everyone, that brings
our meeting to a close.
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am!
Great work! Way to go, Kaname!
Thanks, Kyoko. And I'd like to
thank you for being a part
of the election
committee as well.
No sweat! I did it as a
favor to you, but I had fun!
[KANAME chuckles]
Uh! Wait, Kyoko,
aren't you late for work?
[gasps] I forgot! Uh-oh.
I better get going!
[KANAME]
Take care!
[KYOKO]
See ya!
Best of luck.
Our student council duties are
finally coming to an end.
You achieved much during
your tenure. I thank you.
[KANAME] Thank you
for all you've done!
I was never really cut out
to be vice-president, though.
Sagara. I appreciate
your service, too.
Thanks, your Excellency!
"Your Excellency"?
No. I won't be president
for much longer.
Once I'm out of office,
how will you address me?
As "Your Former Excellency",
of course.
[HAYASHIMIZU chuckles]
You honor me, Sagara.
But why don't we try something
shorter, and less flashy.
[SOUSUKE]
Understood, sir.
You guys make a
pretty good team.
Oh, I meant to ask you.
Are you ready for your
college entrance exams?
I have a feeling
I'll be fine.
Provided I don't get maimed
by a car wreck on my way
to the testing center.
How confident.
And here I am, scared to death
that I won't get into college.
Even if I spend the entirety
of the year studying for it!
Is that so? Because I've heard
that as far as science and
math are concerned, your grades
are consistently perfect.
[gasps]
[SOUSKE grunts]
Look, that's good!
So be proud! One should know
and value their own aptitudes.
[KANAME]
Yes! That's true.
[KANAME giggles]
Well, time to get going.
Shall we, Sousuke?
Sure. I'll come.
Hold on, Sagara. I'd like to
speak with you for a moment.
All right?
[HAYASHIMIZU]
It's been what,
nine months since you
transferred here?
[SOUSUKE]
Yes, sir.
[HAYASHIMIZU]
Much has transpired.
Strange incidents.
Dangerous ones.
[SOUSUKE]
Yes.
I doubt you can keep
it up much longer.
What do you mean,
"keep it up"?
The life you lead.
It's not a problem with you.
You've caused your
fair share of disturbances,
but with a little
more learning,
I'm certain you'll become
more or less "normal".
I'm afraid, she's the problem.
Chidori? How so?
I looked into that hijacking,
as well as the multitude
of startling incidents
that followed in its wake.
It's her. She's been at
the center of all of it.
And the same thing
happens each time.
You're nowhere to be found,
and a mysterious
armed group appears.
I've refrained from prying.
But, I fear it's only
a matter of time
before someone
else makes a fuss.
[SOUSUKE]
Well, I...
[HAYASHIMIZU]
I'll be graduating soon,
which means I won't be
around to keep defending your
mutual situation the
way I have been.
[SOUSUKE]
I... I like it here.
I feel the same. Everyone here
has been affable so far.
But if something
bad were to happen,
they will be frightened,
as well as anxious.
Then, they'll become cruel.
You're saying that
we should leave?
I didn't go that far.
It solves nothing.
But still, it's something
you and she should discuss
sooner than later.
[SOUSUKE]
Hm.
[HAYASHIMIZU chuckles]
[HAYASHIMIZU] And besides,
this is merely a school.
It's simply a way station.
It is?
[HAYASHIMIZU]
Although it's easy to forget,
life will go on from here.
Decades and decades of it.
[knocking]
[HAYASHIMIZU] Oh, my.
That ends our conversation.
I'm keeping
someone waiting, myself.
[KANAME]
And then, out of nowhere,
Shiori's boyfriend says
that he wants to break up!
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[KANAME] Things started getting
ugly from there, and somehow,
I got stuck calling her
boyfriend for her.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[KANAME] Then when he
told me the situation,
I knew that it was all just a
terrible misunderstanding.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[KANAME growls]
What is your problem?
Are you sad your job with
the student council is over,
or is something else
making you mopey?
No, I just...
It's nothing.
Don't give me "it's nothing".
Please, forget about it.
[KANAME grunts]
Boo.
[WOMAN A] And I said,
"Why are you shopping there?
The prices are so high!"
Listen.
[KANAME]
Hm?
[SOUSUKE]
Let's hold hands.
Huh?
So, no?
Look. I would, but I...
It's just...
[SOUSUKE]
Right. I see.
[gasps]
[KANAME]
Um. It's just I... don't know...
Yeah, me too.
It's sudden. Strange.
You're right.
Is it too strange?
[KANAME grunts]
Well?
So hey, uh, you want
something to eat?
You're sure?
Uh, well, yeah.
I have enough ingredients.
We could... maybe have
a job celebration party.
Our own party?
[KANAME] Mm-hm.
Sounds fun, right? So why not?
[elevator beeps]
[KANAME]
Sorry. I'll have it right open.
Hey, perhaps we
should let go, for now.
'Kay.
[KANAME chuckles]
In we go.
[SOUSUKE]
Yeah.
[gasps]
[KANAME shouts]
It's you!
[KANAME]
What's the matter, Sousuke?
Why'd you--
[gasps]
Greetings, Kaname Chidori.
Don't move. Raise both
of your hands slowly,
and then stand up.
If you don't obey--
[LEONARD] Let me guess,
you'll gun me down?
The same old
diplomatic approach.
Give it a rest.
I'd find it crass, saying the
same thing to you.
[SOUSUKE]
What do you mean?
Let me show you.
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[LEONARD] The smallest AS model
in the world, the Alastor.
A gun like that, you'd be
at quite the disadvantage.
[SOUSUKE]
We'll see.
[KANAME gasps]
[gasps]
Now. Are you done?
I came tonight because
I wanted to talk.
[SOUSUKE]
Bastard.
I don't really care
why you've come here.
You can march yourself
right out of my apartment.
But I'm here to talk to you.
That's not my concern!
Get out!
Now hold on. It's a
rather simple matter.
No need to get so worked up.
Could you gather your things
and come to my place?
What'd you say?
You'll be treated with
the utmost courtesy.
I assure you. You'll be safe,
and free, for the most part.
Huh? I don't know what
you're talking about!
[LEONARD] Really? I thought I
explained it pretty clearly.
Are you making fun of me?
I'm not. Perhaps I'll
phrase it this way.
My organization is finally
taking things seriously.
What're you trying to say?
[LEONARD]
Mithril has done far too well.
Amalgam, my organization,
keeps losing to you guys.
And it's beginning to
become a problem.
That's right, and we're going
to keep making things difficult.
[LEONARD] What I'm trying
to tell you is simple:
You've gone too far. Now our
policies have changed.
We will crush Mithril, and take
the Whispereds by force.
[KANAME]
By force? You mean me?
[LEONARD]
That's right.
Amalgam has already started
to contemplate securing you,
even if it means having to
get rough. Do you understand?
So, you're saying--?
[SOUSUKE] You'd turn this
town into a sea of fire?
[gasps]
As things stand, yes...
Now then, with that in mind,
do you understand why I
came to you tonight?
[KANAME] To persuade
me before it happens?
Yes. I hoped my love
might sway you.
You've got some nerve!
[KANAME]
Hold on, Sousuke!
Huh? What for?
Do it.
That's quite kind of you,
but I just so happen to enjoy
my current life, the way it is.
But mostly. I would never
go anywhere with you,
you twisted creep!
I hate you! Loathe you!
Despise you!
[LEONARD chuckles]
So cold. Could it be you're
still upset with me?
Didn't you hear me?
[LEONARD]
But you said you'd forgive me.
[KANAME]
Get lost!
I'll say this in closing,
and listen well.
You are exceptionally gifted.
Yet you allow ordinary
people to boss you around.
It's a waste of your gift.
Stop talking.
You must've noticed
the difference by now.
Those around you are hopelessly
stupid when held in comparison.
Leave! Right now!
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Fine. I will then.
Consider yourself warned.
Oh! Also, Sousuke Sagara.
Yeah, what?
[LEONARD] A cusory investigation
has revealed that you have
racked up over a hundred
confimed kills in your career.
[KANAME, SOUSUKE gasp]
[LEONARD] Yet here you stand,
leading this kind of life.
Isn't that a little unfair?
[SOUSUKE breathes heavily]
Just saying. Goodbye.
[KANAME whimpers]
[SOUSUKE]
Chidori.
[KANAME gasps]
[KANAME]
Hm. I'm sorry.
Who cares what a
guy like that says?
He can't be trusted.
[SOUSUKE]
Yeah.
[KALININ]
Understood, Sergeant Sagara.
Try to hold out until morning.
We'll send a helicopter
out to meet you.
[SOUSUKE] But Lieutenant
Commander Kalinin,
tomorrow could be too late.
There's no telling when
they might attack!
All the more reason we can no
longer use normal channels.
Further communication should
be kept to an absolute minimum.
[SOUSUKE] Understood, sir.
Urzu Seven, signing off.
I knew this day would come, and
I knew it wasn't very far off.
But I never expected this.
[exhales]
It was only a matter of time.
Yes.
[KALININ] Shall we dispatch the
helicopter in the usual way?
No. We'll send the
Arbalest along with it.
The Arbalest?
Are you sure about that?
[TESSA]
For safety's sake.
An M9 should be sufficient
for a security detail.
Without Sergeant
Sagara as its pilot,
the Arbalest is no
different from an M9.
So we might as well
have it available to him.
Understood.
Sergeant Sagara was under
the impression that Amalgam
was starting to get serious.
Have they lost their composure?
Hard to say.
But perhaps, they've grown
quite annoyed with us.
I sincerely hope
that's all it is.
[SHINOHARA]
Captain.
I've made contact with
Tactical HQ in Sydney.
Admiral Boorda's on the line.
[TESSA]
Put him on.
Tessa? What is it?
Greetings, Admiral Boorda.
I thought you should know.
Leonard has made contact
with Kaname Chidori.
[BOORDA]
Is she all right?
Yes, Sergeant Sagara
has her secured.
However, according to Leonard,
things are changing.
There's been a shift
in Amalgam's policies.
Elaborate.
[TESSA]
They'll be more aggressive.
We need to remain alert.
You're right. There were a
few disquieting developments.
Something odd is going on with
Intelligence, and I haven't been
able to contact Lord
Mallory since yesterday.
Is your location secure, sir?
Should you evacuate?
[BOORDA]
Good point.
We'll relocate operations
to our backup HQ.
Merely for the sake of caution,
in case of emergency.
[TESSA] Admiral? I'm having
trouble hearing you.
Tessa? This feed is awful,
we're losing signal strength.
Please, evacuate! Quickly!
Something feels wrong.
[BOORDA] Hurry it up,
this has never happened--
Uncle, please! Get out!
[BOORDA]
Reconnect me!
[MALE STAFF A]
Line A. Line D. Line V.
All lines have gone silent, sir!
[FEMALE STAFF A] It's possible
that there was an EMP attack.
What the hell's going on?
There's no time for
theories here. Signal evacua--!
[MALE PILOT A]
Bombing successful.
Commence Zero Hour.
Repeat. Bombing successful.
[SHINOHARA] All standard
lines seem to be down.
No response from
Tactical Headquarters.
[MALE STAFF C]
Warning radar, weather radar,
most of our sensors are offline!
Trying to determine the cause.
[TESSA] Could this be the
result of an EMP strike?
[SHINOHARA]
It's similar,
but this seems to be an
ongoing phenomenon.
It's inconceivable that such
a pulse could be man-made.
What do you think?
The only thing left to us is to
remain vigilant. Your thoughts?
[TESSA]
Mr. Kalinin?
Yes. I am of the same opinion.
[TESSA] Sound the alarm.
Yellow One.
Yes, ma'am. Initiating alert
level Yellow One immediately.
[MALE STAFFD]
All hands alert! Yellow One!
The base has come under some
kind of electro-magnetic attack.
All personnel, stand on alert
at your designated posts.
This is not a drill.
Remain vigilant, and stand by.
[MALE STAFF D]
All hands alert! Yellow One!
[KURZ] An attack?
So where's it coming from?
Who knows? We're on standby.
[MALE STAFF D]
All personnel...
Well, damn!
What's this? Are you scared?
[KURZ] No, just blown away by
that uniform. I said da-yum!
[KURZ groans]
[MAO] Now that I'm
a Second Lieutenant,
I thought I'd get
used to wearing it.
Now quit staring and come on!
[KURZ groans]
[SOUSUKE] Urzu Seven to
Merida Island HQ. Respond.
This is Urzu Seven.
Merida Island, do you copy?
Damn! It's going
on six hours now.
[KANAME grunts]
What time is it?
Just after six.
So did you get any sleep?
Yeah. What about you?
Yeah, plenty.
Liar. You haven't slept!
I understand why we can't
stay at the apartment,
but how long do you plan for us
to drive around in this thing?
Just try to be patient
until we rendezvous
with Mithril's chopper.
[KANAME]
When will it come?
I don't know.
Huh?
I haven't been able to
contact HQ since last night.
Wraith either.
It seems the communication
network's been disrupted.
[KANAME]
Same with my phone.
The phones are a mess,
but satellite connections
are especially bad.
Tough luck. If you took
refuge at the Merida base,
we could ensure your safety.
Take refuge at the base?
[SOUSUKE]
That's right.
[SOUSUKE] Eat some. This might
turn into a long haul.
You really are a fan
of these things.
Do we have some
tea or anything?
[SOUSUKE]
Make do with water.
[gasps]
Hey! Great...
Sousuke? We will get to
come back, won't we?
Perhaps.
[gasps]
What?
Nothing.
The enemy's become more
fixated on your abilities
than we anticipated.
What, you mean the whole
"being a Whispered" thing?
But, those powers
are so vague. Jeez.
Less than you might think.
Hayashimizu remarked
on it yesterday.
Your perfect scores on
math and science tests.
That's not a normal thing.
But even if that's true, they're
just standard high school exams!
You're right, but one day you
might find yourself solving
the toughest equations
in the world.
[gasps]
I'll just keep it hidden, then.
[SOUSUKE] The time for that
is gone. Amalgam knows now.
[KANAME]
Well, what should I do?
Mithril has Tessa,
or rather, the Captain.
Her power is much like yours.
I'm sure you would
be welcome there.
[KANAME]
Who, me?
But, I'm nothing compared
to how amazing Tessa is.
Plus, I wouldn't be any
help during a war.
[SOUSUKE]
A war.
You're right. There's no way
we can fully count on Mithril
to be the answer
to our problems.
So your concerns are justified.
Then I still have school
to keep going to,
and I would miss all
of my friends there.
And yes, I realize I'm in no
position to talk like that.
Sorry.
[SOUSUKE] I'm well
aware of how important
your life here is
to you. Same here.
We've been living
it together. But now...
[SOUSUKE]
Chidori.
[KANAME]
Hm?
[SOUSUKE]
Maybe we should just...
No, never mind.
'Kay.
[radio chirps]
[SANTOS] Gebo Nine to
Urzu Seven. Can you hear me?
I'm currently holding at an
altitude of 3,000 meters
above Kawasaki.
[SOUSUKE]
It's the helicopter!
[KANAME sighs]
[SOUSUKE]
Urzu Seven to Gebo Nine,
you're garbled, but I hear you.
[SANTOS] Urzu Seven, confirmed.
What is your current position?
[SOUSUKE] Gebo Nine, Urzu Seven
is currently on standby at
LZ Echo. I have Kaname Chidori.
[SANTOS] Gebo Nine, roger.
That's good.
Looks like we're at a range
where a signal will reach.
[SOUSUKE] Gebo Nine.
I'm unclear on the situation.
What's happening?
[SANTOS] It's wide-scale
radio interference.
Tactical HQ in Sydney
got knocked out.
Some of our other bases appear
to be under attack as well.
[SOUSUKE] What? Any word
on Merida Island?
[SANTOS] I don't know.
I'm at least going to
pick the two of you up,
so secure the landing zone.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Roger that.
Current conditions at the LZ--
[gasps]
Get down right now.
Huh?
Bad guys.
[KANAME gasps]
[SOUSUKE] Gebo Nine.
This is Urzu Seven.
We're being surrounded.
Taking a quick head count.
At least five of
those Alastor types.
And at least, eight armed
enemy combatants.
I'll attempt to flee.
[SANTOS ]
Gebo Nine, roger.
Do what you can
to get through this.
Five minutes or so.
I can try. Now wish us luck.
Sousuke?
I'm so sorry. We're in
for a long five minutes.
[SOUSUKE]
Next time: "Damage Control."