♪
Good to go. Now lift her up.
[RILEY grunts]
[KAEW grunts]
Keep it going, a little higher.
[NAMI grunts]
[groans]
[grunts]
[KAEW sighs]
[NAMI chuckles]
Nice. The whole mech's
been overhauled.
Good work. Sure was a chore.
Now it should be
as good as new.
[KAEW] Yeah, but...
what about that paint job?
[NAMI]
Huh?
[LEMON]
I agree.
We could stand to make
it a little flashier, huh?
[NAMI sighs]
[SOUSUKE]
I had the same thought.
[LEMON]
Hm?
[LEMON] Doesn't exactly
look intimidating.
That was not my objective.
These were the colors of
the last mech I piloted.
[LEMON]
Huh?
Doesn't really matter,
but I'd like to call this
mech "Al the Second."
Seriously?
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Is that weird?
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
And the winner is Stick Man!
[ASCH] We're up. You done
with those adjustments?
Just about!
[NAMI]
Finished.
'Kay. Well. Be careful.
[RILEY] Hmph. It's all
up to you, Sousuke.
Not a problem.
[KAEW grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
For our next bout,
in the melee weapons category.
First we have Crossbow!
Operated by Sohsky Seagull.
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Versus Vanguard!
Operated by John C. Bogle.
Fight!
[ANNOUNCER]
The winner is Crossbow!
[NAMI] That was amazing
Sousuke, way to go!
[KAEW chuckles]
Wow, you're the real deal.
[RILEY chuckles]
Mm-hm!
Yeah, but you might wanna
drag your next fight out a bit,
just to put on a show.
What? That's nonsense!
All he needs to do
is keep winning.
Yes, I agree.
It's enough to win.
[LEMON chuckles]
--[KAEW] So..!
--[NAMI] Anyway.
[ASCH]
Let's talk about that axe dodge.
[SOUSUKE]
I just did my best to react.
[NAMI]
How are you so good at this?
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
Fight!
[grunts]
[ANNOUNCER]
The winner is Crossbow!
Fight!
[ANNOUNCER]
The winner is Crossbow!
[inaudible]
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
The winner is Crossbow!
He did it.
[NAMI giggles]
He's won every
match he's fought!
[ASCH]
Damn, who is this guy?
To be honest, I don't care.
He's our ticket to
the big leagues.
You're knockin' 'em dead.
Negative, none of them died.
You're so weird.
Oh, yeah?
[NAMI giggles]
But seriously.
How have you not even
broken a sweat yet?
Guess my body
must be used to it.
Uh...
[LEMON] A properly trained
soldier makes his entire AS
an extension of his body.
Or so I read. You agree?
[NAMI]
Where'd that come from?
I've been studying up on it.
That quote you gave,
it's the motto of the
SAS Assault Cavalry team.
And what is the SAS?
[SOUSUKE] A commonwealth
special forces unit.
I don't suppose
you were one of them.
[SOUSUKE] No, but my
superior officer was.
I wonder if he'd agree
with what I'm doing.
Say what?
No. Forget it.
[LEMON sighs] All right.
Fine, be all mysterious.
[NAMI grunts]
[SOUSUKE]
Something wrong?
I dunno. I can't really
explain why I think this.
But are you nervous
about something?
Negative, I just--
Well, maybe a bit.
[NAMI]
How come?
Cause I'm starting to
feel comfortable here.
It defies reason.
You're "comfortable"?
[SOUSUKE]
When I'm with you.
[NAMI gasps] Not sure what
that's s'posed to mean.
But there are worse things
than being comfortable,
aren't there?
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[NAMI gasps]
Here. It's your cut from today.
Thank you.
Of course. You kicked butt.
[ASCH] No doubt about it.
Someone's in love.
[SOUSUKE]
Who is? With whom?
[ASCH] Obviously, I mean Nami.
She's into you, man.
Oh yeah. Well, of
course she is.
[ASCH laughs]
Didn't take you for
a player till now.
Well, by this city's standards,
my skills as a pilot
are extremely high.
So since Nami's a team owner,
it follows that she'd
hold me in high esteem.
[ASCH]
Uh... Good grief, kid.
Look, that really isn't what
I was tryin' to get at.
He means that she
likes you romantically.
And she's a picky girl,
so that's a rare thing.
Lots'a guys ask her out.
She turned 'em all down.
You would know.
I mean, seeing as how you
were one of 'em, right, Kaew?
[KAEW]
Hey! That's private!
Whenever she shows up
and you're not around,
guess what the first thing
out of her mouth is?
"Where's Sousuke?"
She ain't subtle.
She's blunt as hell!
So blunt it's suspicious.
[ALL laugh]
That girl's on the hunt.
[laughing continues]
[ASCH]
So what about you?
Regarding what?
[ASCH]
Well she likes you. Ya like her?
[SOUSUKE sighs]
Chidori.
[KAEW]
Huh?
Nothing.
That's a serious expression.
What, did you leave a girl
back home or somethin'?
[SOUSUKE]
The opposite.
[RILEY]
Huh?
What's that s'posed to mean?
[door opens]
--[KAEW] Uh-oh.
--[NAMI] All right, boys.
Lunch breaks over,
we're burning daylight.
Let's get back to work.
[ASCH]
You got it.
Sousuke. Here.
What's this?
[NAMI]
A shopping list I wrote.
Go and buy that stuff
with Lemon, 'kay?
[LEMON chuckles nervously]
[SOUSUKE] These are all
specialized AS parts.
You can't get these
at the average shop.
I see.
You haven't been down to
the market yet, have you?
[SOUSUKE]
Market?
[PEDESTRIANS chattering]
[SOUSUKE]
Reminds me of Akihabara.
Thought that was
Tokyo's Hentai Town.
No. Electronics town.
[LEMON]
If you say so.
[SOUSUKE] Huh? They're selling
BMD chips for 400 these days?
Is that expensive?
[SOUSUKE] No. They were
2,000 a year ago.
[LEMON] Wow. That's a
serious mark down.
Just goes to show how
common ASes have become.
Which is odd in itself.
The increase in AS use,
it's happening almost too fast.
Or maybe I'm just
overthinking all this.
Yeah, that's my guess.
[SOUSUKE]
That's brutally honest.
Well, I'm an artist.
And good art doesn't try
to spare people's feelings.
You're really an artist?
[LEMON]
Yeah, and in a way at least,
I feel like you are too.
[SOUSUKE]
Huh?
Sure, I felt that way
after watching you fight.
It's graceful. It doesn't
feel like rote skill.
There's art to it.
[SOUSUKE]
You think?
[LEMON]
I've watched all your matches.
And the way you fight
evokes something.
You're clearly not just
in it to make ends meet.
You're fighting for
something greater.
It's like your eyes are always
set on some distant goal.
Or... maybe I'm just
overthinking now.
I'm new to this stuff,
but that's the vibe I get.
Am I wrong?
I'm not really sure.
That said...
[LEMON]
That said?
When it comes to means of self-
expression, this is all I have.
What, you mean fighting?
[SOUSUKE]
Affirmative.
I wish I had some kind
of peaceful talent.
Like music, or drawing,
or photography.
But in truth,
fighting's all I'm good at.
Hey now, let's not
jump to conclusions.
You'll never know what
else you're good at
till you try it out.
For example...
I'm listening.
[LEMON] Hmm... You could
be a ladies' man!
But why would I do that?
[BOTH gasp]
[OFFICER A]
Hands in the air!
[LEMON yelps]
[OFFICER A] Get down on
your knees. Nice and slow.
[LEMON]
Uh, officer?
I uh, think there must've
been some kind of mista--
Get down, quickly!
You said to do it
slowly a second ago,
now I'm just confused.
[LEMON grunts]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
I got a report that a couple
of no-good foreigners were
stealin' from some
of the businesses
here in our fine market.
Hm. Looks like our informant
was reliable, too.
Wow. You seem pretty certain.
When that Rick guy got
murdered, you said there was
no way you could prove anything.
Lemon, let it go.
[LEMON]
You've gotta be kidding.
I have rights, damn it!
I wanna see a lawyer right now!
I'm gonna suggest that
you watch your mouth.
[SOUSUKE]
And who are you?
[POLICE CHIEF]
Heh. I'm the police chief.
And that's all you need to know.
Thank you, that's
easy to remember.
Huh? You've got some brass, kid.
But if you come at me with that
insolent attitude in my city--
Well, you can guess
how that'll go.
Eh, Sousuke Sagara?
Scarface. You come with me.
Sousuke.
I'll be fine.
[SOUSUKE]
A tooth?
[footsteps]
[door opens]
[POLICE CHIEF]
Robbery, assault,
attempted murder, extortion,
perjury, illegal immigration,
obstruction of police duties,
and possession of an illegal
weapon to top it off.
Is there anything else
you'd like me to add?
[SOUSUKE]
What am I adding to?
The list of charges
against you.
Then how about assaulting
a police chief?
Uncuff me and
I'll do it right now.
[POLICE CHIEF chuckles]
You don't seem to
understand your situation.
This room isn't just
an interrogation cell.
It's also a courtroom.
I'm your prosecutor,
judge, and jury.
Hell, I'll even be the man
who carries out your sentence.
You must be pretty
understaffed here.
[POLICE CHIEF]
Hmph.
What is it that you want?
I doubt you came here just
to tell me my prison term.
You're a sharp one.
As I'm sure you've guessed,
this is about the arena.
I hear that you're
on a winning streak.
Yeah, what about it?
[POLICE CHIEF] You're winning
more than you have a right to.
A lot of businessmen are
involved in these competitions.
It's big money.
And I mean really big.
So we have a certain, uh...
Well, why don't we
call it a system?
You're saying my
victories have cost
the wrong people money.
[POLICE CHIEF] That's right.
You really are a sharp kid.
So you can see
where this is going.
I want you to take part
in this system of ours.
I see. You're
rigging the matches.
Who's to say?
But as things stand, you're
lookin' at 50 years in jail.
[SOUSUKE] Fifty years would
be a problem. I'll cooperate.
I'm glad to hear it.
[SOUSUKE] But I also want a
place where I can really fight.
Say what?
[SOUSUKE]
Not like the arena.
Take me somewhere that
I can fight for my life,
with far more money in play.
I know it exists.
[POLICE CHIEF]
Heh.
Where'd you hear that?
[SOUSUKE] It's how things
work in this field.
Do you know the details
of what's involved?
Of course. These live-ammo
fights are illegal.
So they can only be
watched by VIPs.
I hear these deathmatches
are quite the spectacle,
so they take place on
the city's outskirts.
I was also told the
payout's a lot higher.
About half the pilots
who compete end up dead
within a matter of months.
Were you aware of
that little fact?
That sounds about right.
[POLICE CHIEF laughs]
Why do you want in on this?
The money.
[POLICE CHIEF]
Anything else?
Got a taste for blood.
[POLICE CHIEF]
Huh?
Well, in that case,
I'll make arrangements.
I think we can find
a place for you.
But until it's done, I'll keep
your friend in custody.
[NAMI]
Sousuke!
What happened to you two?
And where's Lemon?
He's still in their custody.
I saw the police chief
and got released.
By the chief? Wow.
I'm surprised he helped you.
I'll explain later. Let's go.
[NAMI] Rigged matches?
Guess it figures.
You don't seem surprised.
[NAMI sighs]
[NAMI]
Not really.
I've heard plenty
of rumors about it.
And you'd have to be an
idiot to expect sportsmanship
in a city like this.
But doesn't it seem weird
that he let you go so easily?
[SOUSUKE]
No, I asked to join something.
[NAMI]
What was that?
The deathmatches.
[NAMI]
Deathmatches?
You do understand that
isn't just a name, right?
[SOUSUKE]
Real fights with live ammo.
It might be illegal,
but... it's good money.
[NAMI] You wanna take my machine
to go get yourself killed in?
Gah! What are you thinking?!
The only kind of people who
do those battles are idiots
who've gotten themselves
neck-deep into debt.
We aren't like that!
We're doing just fine.
We've almost gotten into Class
A, isn't that enough for you?
At least tell me the real
reason you're doing this.
Well, I...
You can't say.
You know, I thought you and I
had at least gotten to
be friends by this point.
Was I wrong?
I don't wanna die out
here without knowing
what any of this was about.
[gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
You're right. Thanks, Nami.
I'll explain everything, okay?
Take a seat.
[SOUSUKE] Joining the
deathmatches was my goal
from the start.
To get close to the dark
side of this sport,
I first needed to gain a
reputation in the main arena.
'Kay, but why was
that your goal?
Because the deathmatches
are organized
by a group called Amalgam.
Amalgam. Who're they?
They're a secret organization.
They make a profit by
manufacturing conflict
around the world.
The terrorist attacks
of the past few years?
Amalgam was behind
almost all of them.
Wait. You can't be--
[SOUSUKE] There was once
a secret mercenary force
dedicated to fighting
against them.
I'm a survivor from that force.
What do you mean by that?
You're saying it was destroyed?
Amalgam attacked us
three months ago.
Our forces were wiped out.
You're kidding me.
[SOUSUKE]
Amalgam works from the shadows,
which makes it very difficult
to find them on my own.
The only clue
I have in this city
is the illegal deathmatches.
We've defeated Amalgam ASes
several times in the past,
and we ID'd the recovered
bodies of their operators.
A good number of them
competed here in this city.
Like they had fought
in the arena?
[SOUSUKE]
Of that much, I'm certain.
But before we could
learn any more,
my group got
destroyed by Amalgam.
Are you for real?
[SOUSUKE]
Affirmative.
Well, I guess that
would explain why
you're such a good AS pilot.
So then, it sounds like these
guys are really bad news.
That's accurate.
And my mission is
to get close to them.
But I can't do that
without your assistance.
[NAMI]
To hell with that!
You can fight your
war by yourself!
It has nothing to do with me!
Wait!
Please, listen!
No, you're fired.
Don't show up here again.
[sighs]
I guess that figures.
[MAID gasps]
[doorbell rings]
[SOUSUKE]
Nami?
What are you doing?
Being cautious.
Look. There's something
I wanna ask, at least.
What's that?
You're in a bind, am I right?
Yes.
[NAMI] And you can't
get out without help?
[SOUSUKE]
Affirmative.
[NAMI sighs]
All right, fine.
I'll go along with your plan.
For now, anyway.
Are you sure?
[NAMI] Well, it's our best shot
at getting Lemon out of jail.
And you did say there'd be
good money in it, right?
Yes. That's true.
Okay, but don't get
your hopes up just yet.
There's no telling if Asch and
the others are gonna agree.
If the crew says no,
then that's the end of it.
[SOUSUKE]
Understood.
[OFFICER C]
He hasn't made a run for it yet.
Guess he's not
all talk after all.
Oh, he was serious. But
keep an eye on him anyway.
--[OFFICER C] Yes, sir.
--[phone rings]
Huh?
What is it now?
Oh, uh. Shit.
Uh, my apologies, sir.
No. Never. I wouldn't
even dream of it, sir.
Yes, of course. I won't
allow him to escape.
Please, sir, you can
rest assured that--
Rest assured?
No, I actually can't.
You had better take
Sousuke Sagara seriously.
[POLICE CHIEF] Yes, I'm fully
aware of that, Mr. Kurama.
[grumbles]
Is that a fact?
[POLICE CHIEF]
Yes, sir. You have nothing--
I just knew that punk
would come after us.
♪
[SOUSUKE]
Next time: "Giant Killing."