[SOUSUKE]
You can see the whole school
from the top of this building.
Right. Sounds good.
So about that AS of yours.
How long can it keep jamming?
[SOUSUKE]
For up to two minutes.
And it has to be still
to keep the signal up.
[KANAME] But if the signal
covers the whole school...
[SOUSUKE]
Yes.
That should stop them from
detonating the bombs.
[KANAME] Yeah. So we need
to evacuate everyone,
and save Kyoko, in the
span of two minutes.
[SOUSUKE] How do we determine
what frequency to jam?
[KANAME]
I'll write an algorithm for it.
[SOUSUKE]
In the Arbalest's programming?
You can do that?
[KANAME] It's written
in BAda, right? I can do it.
[SOUSUKE]
How long do you need?
[KANAME]
One hour.
[SOUSUKE]
I'll buy us some time.
[sirens blaring]
[phone buzzes]
We're setting up
a trace right now.
[KURAMA] Have you
made a decision yet?
[SOUSUKE]
I can't agree to your terms.
[KURAMA]
You can't, huh?
So you don't mind if
we kill your friends?
If you want to murder
a bunch of schoolchildren,
that's none of my concern.
[KANAME]
Wha--
[KURAMA] I could kill a few
now to see if that's true.
Do what you want. But I've
been ordered to kill the girl
before letting her
fall into your hands.
Heh. All right, so what
are your demands?
[SOUSUKE]
My safety guaranteed.
You don't get it, do you?
I think I'll just set off
my first bomb right now.
[SOUSUKE]
Then negotiations have failed.
[phone clicks]
[KANAME gasps]
Hey!
Everything's fine.
But you--
--[phone buzzes]
--[KANAME gasps]
[KURAMA sighs] What matters
to me is that I can
secure the girl.
I'm aware.
[KURAMA] That AS of yours
is a threat, though.
For us to deal,
I need you to prove that
it's been neutralized.
[SOUSUKE] Then at eleven
hundred hours I'll have it moved
to the abandoned factory in
Sengawa's second district.
It'll be on standby, hatch open.
[KURAMA]
We'll be watching.
[SOUSUKE]
Of course.
Next, I'll send the girl to
Sengawa Station alone.
While you're picking her up,
I'll disappear,
and you won't follow.
[KANAME gasps]
[KURAMA] Fine. But if things
don't go exactly to plan,
I'll blow up the school
and everyone in it.
As I've already informed you,
that doesn't amount to a threat.
Al. Cancel stealth mode.
[AL]
Roger.
[KANAME]
Wait. What're you thinking?
[SOUSUKE] It's not safe here.
We're leaving.
That isn't what I meant.
Why'd you basically
just offer to surrender?
[SOUSUKE]
Tactical deception. I lied.
It should buy us time.
[KURAMA chcukles]
The punk's got some balls.
[phone buzzes]
[SOUSUKE] It's Sagara.
I need a favor.
[KANAME]
I'm finished.
Right, it's time for
me to get moving, then.
And me? What now?
[SOUSUKE] Take cover somewhere.
I'll find you once it's done.
C'mon, there has to be some
way I can help you out.
[SOUSUKE]
You've done plenty already.
[KANAME sighs]
[SOUSUKE] If I don't
come back... read this.
You'll find contacts and
a Mithril safehouse.
But why wouldn't you
be able to make it?
[SOUSUKE]
You know what I mean.
But Sousuke...
[KANAME gasps]
I'll see you soon.
Take care of yourself.
[SOUSUKE]
Al. Stay on alert, mode four.
[AL]
Roger... Sergeant?
[SOUSUKE grunts]
What is it?
[AL] I'd like to request that
you refrain from leaving me.
Why would you ask that?
[AL]
Because I've had a premonition.
[SOUSUKE]
Of what?
[AL] I feel that you and
I will soon part ways.
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Just remain on alert,
like I instructed.
[HENCHMAN B grunts]
Thirty minutes to go. Should we
send men to the station?
There's no point.
The girl won't be there.
So then.
He's planning something. When he
pulls the trigger, so do I.
[KANAME] Don't get in the way.
Just stay here... and be quiet.
[KANAME]
Did I just see...?
[KANAME grunts]
[bell rings]
[HAYASHIMIZU]
This is the student council.
A serious accident has just
occurred on the fourth floor
of the north building.
It was, of course,
caused by Sagara.
[STUDENTS groan]
Due to this accident,
some poison gas may have
leaked into the air vents.
Students and staff are
to evacuate at once.
Poison gas? There's no way.
[KURAMA sighs]
Well, that's the end of that.
[KURAMA gasps]
[HENCHMAN A gasps]
[KURAMA] It's not working.
What's going on here?
We've been hit by a
powerful jamming signal.
Let me see what the source is.
[HENCHMAN A gasps]
[KURAMA grunts]
Run for it!
That damn Sagara's
gone and done it again!
[MALE STUDENT C]
We're all gonna die!
As quick as expected.
[HENCHMAN A]
We're still being jammed, sir!
It's coming from--
[KURAMA grunts]
[gasps]
That mech. How'd it get there?
Contact all units and have
them attack the Arm Slave
at point delta.
What are you waiting for?
Does that include the Venoms?
Of course it does.
Call back all three!
[AL] Warning:. Enemy infantry
detected at close range.
Twelve in total.
I am taking fire.
[SOUSUKE] How much longer
can you jam the signal?
[AL]
Ninety seconds remaining.
[SOUSUKE]
Kyoko!
[KYOKO whimpers]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
I'll get you out.
These strange men
came out of nowhere.
What about Kaname?
Where is she?
She's fine. No need to worry.
--[explosions]
--[BOTH grunt]
[KYOKO]
What's going on?
Doesn't matter.
[KYOKO]
You sure?
I'll bypass the detonator.
Don't move.
[AL] Jamming signal will
fail within 20 seconds.
[SOUSUKE] I know I have to cut
one of these cables, but...
...which one?
[AL]
Ten seconds left.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
[AL] Jamming suspended.
Changing position.
What is all this?
[SOUSUKE]
Don't move yet.
Please, just tell me
what's happening.
I don't want to die out
here without knowing
what any of this was about.
How'd you find me?
What are you?
[KURAMA]
He's a hitman.
No sudden movements.
You got that, Sagara?
This girl your friend?
Then surely, you've told her how
you're not actually a student.
Stop this.
See, an employer of his forged
his paperwork so he could
infiltrate this school.
All for Kaname Chidori.
That's not true, is it?
[SOUSUKE grunts]
It wasn't just--
[TEACHER] Miss Tokiwa?
Are you up here? Please answer!
We have to evacuate the school.
Please come out...
Must be a teacher.
[Teacher]
What are you doing?
Look. You're not authorized
to be on school gr--
[KURAMA]
Where is Kaname Chidori hiding?
Don't worry Miss Tokiwa,
you'll be okay.
I'll talk some sense
into these guys.
I won't let anyone hurt you!
[KYOKO gasps]
Who're you?
Wait...
[TEACHER chuckles]
[HENCHMEN, KURAMA grunt]
[SOUSUKE]
Close your eyes, Kyoko!
[ALL grunting]
Damn.
[sighs]
So you're Wraith.
Wasn't expecting a woman.
Where have you been
this whole time?
[WRAITH sighs]
Was gonna ask you that.
I've been trying to
track you down.
Huh...
[headset beeps]
[AL]
Three enemy AS's approaching.
Should I prepare to intercept?
[SOUSUKE]
Pick me up.
[AL]
Roger.
[WRAITH]
What do you plan to do now?
I'll fight them.
[KYOKO whimpers]
[SOUSUKE]
Kyoko.
I really did have fun here.
Thank you.
--[radar beeps]
--[AL] Missiles detected.
Impact in two, one...
[STUDENTS scream]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Damn it!
[WRAITH]
Sergeant! Sergeant Sagara!
[SOUSUKE]
Huh?
[gasps]
[KYOKO groans]
I'll try to keep her stable.
Hurry up and go!
Sergeant. What're you doing?
The enemy's coming!
[breathes heavily]
[grunts]
[pants]
[CROWD gasps]
[KANAME pants]
[radio beeps]
[KURAMA]
What do you want?
[LEONARD] Seems you're
having a tough time.
[KURAMA] Nice of you to notice.
We didn't find the girl, either.
I'm about to give up.
[LEONARD]
No need for that.
Take Sagara hostage,
and she will appear.
[KURAMA]
Hm...
[KURAMA grunts]
That's not happening.
He's crushing my Vipers.
The bastard's on a rampage.
[LEONARD] Keep him
occupied as best you can.
I'll be there shortly.
[SABINA] Is it really necessary
that you go yourself?
Every now and again, I do
need to get some exercise.
Well, be careful. I'd hate
to see you get injured.
[LEONARD] Thank you, Sabina.
I doubt I'll be gone long.
[SOUSUKE]
That should be... all three.
Huh?
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[computer beeps]
[gasps]
[AL] Transport plane detected.
Affiliation unknown.
[SOUSUKE] It looked like...
something dropped.
[AL]
Enemy unit at Six 'o clock.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[CROWD shouts]
[AL] Its strength and mobility
surpass that of the Codarl type.
We are outclassed. I recommend
immediate withdrawal.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[LEONARD]
Greetings, Sagara.
[SOUSUKE gasps]
So it's him.
[LEONARD]
This is your last chance.
Can I persuade you to let
me take Miss Chidori?
I think you know my answer.
Yes, I suppose I do.
[LEONARD]
Tell me...
In refusing to acknowledge the
hopelessness of your position,
do you think you look cool?
Huh? What are you getting at?
[LEONARD]
Nothing really.
It's just something I...
hate about you!
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Huh?
[KANAME pants]
Kyoko. No.
[WRAITH] Hm? You're supposed
to be hiding!
[KANAME pants] Kyoko,
you're hurt. Kyoko? Kyoko!
You have to stay back.
I'm treating her wound.
Will she make it?
I can't say for sure.
[KANAME gasps]
No... She can't...
I'm so sorry Kyoko.
It's my fault.
[gasps]
You have seen how
this plays out.
[KANAME gasps]
Don't do this!
[LEONARD]
You get it, don't you?
[KANAME]
No, don't kill him!
[LEONARD]
I'm in a foul mood.
[KANAME]
I'm begging you, please!
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[LEONARD] No one can stop this.
Except for you.
[KANAME]
I'll even love you.
That determination
and selflessness.
That heroic strength.
[KANAME]
I'll try hard. I will.
[LEONARD] Why? Why does
she waste it on him?
[AL] Condensors are
critically damaged.
Generator is disabled.
I advise you to abandon--
mech--and escape.
Thanks for everything.
Al. Your discharge...
...is approved!
[KANAME]
Stop it right now!
[SOUSUKE]
Chidori!
Let him live, and I'll go!
[LEONARD]
Go with whom?
[KANAME] With you.
I'll go wherever you want!
Huh?! Chidori,
don't do this! Chidori!
[LEONARD] The lady made
her choice. You lose, Sagara!
[SOUSUKE]
Chidori. Come back. Chidori!
[KANAME]
I have no choice!
Goodbye.
I swear to you. I give you
my word. I'll bring you back!
I promise you I'll find a way!
You belong here, and no
matter what I have to do,
I'll bring you back! Chidori!
[SOUSUKE groans]
Go on! Defend the
captain with your life!
Wait! No. Don't-
[YANG]
Don't stop! Hurry!
[TESSA gasps]
[MALE SOLDIER A groans]
[YANG shouts]
[TESSA grunts]
You're hit. No! Yang!
[YANG grunts] You have
to run. Just leave me!
I won't!
[MALE SOLDIER B]
This is Alpha Six.
We've secured the
enemy commander.
[MALE SOLDIER C]
Stand up. Get out of the way!
Stop it!
--[gunshots]
--[MALE SOLDIERS grunt]
What a pain. These creeps are
showing up all over the place.
Melissa!
[MAO]
What's our situation?
[TESSA]
This base will fall soon.
I ordered a withdrawal
to the Danaan.
But I don't know
how many made it.
Lieutenant Commander
Kalinin stayed behind.
[MAO]
I see.
[TESSA] We haven't heard
from Captain Clouseau,
or Sergeant Weber.
I fear that they... well...
Damn it all. I'll make those
Amalgam bastards pay for this.
[TESSA]
I intend to, as well.
[MAO gasps]
[MAO chuckles]
Now that's the spirit.
That's why I love ya, Tessa.
[TESSA chuckles]
Same to you, Mao!
[MARDUKAS] We've been waiting
for you, Madame Captain.
The Tuatha de Danaan,
ruler of the seven seas,
and mightiest ship
in human history,
is ready to depart at any time.
We wait for your command.
Commander Mardukas. Mao?
I am astounded,
that even now,
you still act with
such discipline.
[MARDUKAS]
Of course, ma'am.
It's in battle that
discipline is needed most.
All hands, board the ship.
[DANA]
Performing final assessment.
Group A: complete.
Group B: complete.
Group C: Conditionally complete.
Awaiting acknowledgement
from XO.
[MARDUKAS] She'll make
it for now, Captain.
[TESSA] Very well. Set out.
One third ahead!
[MARDUKAS] Aye, Madame Captain.
Set out. One third ahead!
[MALE PROPULSION OFFICER A]
Setting out. One third ahead.
[TESSA] Good. Now open
all torpedo tubes.
[MARDUKAS] Aye, Madame Captain.
Open all torpedo tubes.
[FEMALE CONTROL OFFICER A]
Opening all torpedo tubes.
[MALE RADAR OFFICER A]
Contact!
Whatever this is, it's huge.
And it's dead ahead.
[TESSA]
That's fine.
Launch all of our torpedos.
And take us to full speed.
[MARDUKAS gasps, grunts]
Aye aye, Madame Captain.
Launch every torpedo as we
accelerate to full speed!
All hands, brace
yourselves for impact!
Do not falter. Push ahead,
no matter what!
[CREW grunts]
Who fired those shots?
[KURZ chuckles] Mind if
we hitch a ride, captain?
That was a close one,
even for us.
Sergeant Weber!
Captain Clouseau!
[MARDUKAS]
Those soldiers of ours.
They truly are tenacious.
And that's our
greatest advantage.
Open hatch 13 immediately.
Once we've safely recovered
Urzu One and Six, we'll break
through the enemy's net.
[MARDUKAS] Aye aye, ma'am.
Prepare to dive!
[ERI] Class, I know this
is a terrible situation,
but we all need to be strong.
I'm told that it's going to be
a while before the
school's fully repaired.
I now things won't seem very
normal during that time.
But I'm going to do my best,
and I encourage you--
Mister Sagara.
[SOUSUKE] I don't know what
you've already been told,
but it was me inside
of that white AS.
I am employed, by a
certain mercenary force,
as an active duty AS pilot.
I apologize...
for keeping that secret.
[ONO-D]
I don't want your apology!
Why don't you give it to the
girl you sent to the hospital?
Kyoko's still in there,
did you know that?
[SHINJI]
Ono-D, cut it out!
It's screwed up.
She didn't do anything!
Damn you. She would be fine
if it weren't for you!
[SOUSUKE gasps]
It should've been you!
It was your fight!
Don't just stand there!
Say something!
[ALL gasp]
[ONO-D]
We were friends, weren't we?
So say something.
Say something.
[ONO-D] Tell us. Why?
Why'd you come here?
[SOUSUKE]
I came here to say--
What?
[SOUSUKE]
That I'm going to find Chidori.
And bring her back here
where she belongs.
I give you my word.
I will bring her home.
So when she comes back,
please be ready to welcome her.
Thank you. That's all
I have to say.
[SOUSUKE] Next time:.
"Welcome to the Jungle."