[MARDUKAS] This isn't
just affecting us.
Commercial satellites
are failing too.
How is this happening?
[SHINOHARA] The entire
Navstar GPS network is down.
Comstar's gone offline too.
From what we're able to see.
It looks like every
communication system on
the planet was affected.
There's no telling when
they'll be restored.
It's a solar storm.
The largest that's hit
earth in this century.
A "solar storm," you say.
Can we confirm this?
[SHINOHARA]
It's likely, sir.
Solar wind does carry
a magnetic field
capable of disrupting ours.
And there've been reports of
increased sunspot activity,
which can indicate an
upcoming solar flare.
[MARDUKAS]
Even so.
Could that really cause
damage on this scale?
[SHINOHARA]
Well.
There's no modern precedent
for such an event,
so it's hard to say.
[MARDUKAS]
I see.
I might not know sunspots,
but I do know storms.
And typically, natural disasters
of this scale leave both sides
in a war unprepared to fight.
For the enemy to have taken
advantage of this event,
they may have known
it was coming.
I agree. Solar storms are
known to be unpredictable.
And yet...
[MARDUKAS] Lieutenant Commander.
Have any thoughts?
[gasps]
Yes sir. We're blind for now,
so we can only wait and react.
I was already aware of
that much. But in your opin--
--[alarm beeps]
--[MARDUKAS gasps]
[FEMALE AIR GUARD OFFICER A]
We have supersonic
cruise missiles incoming!
Eight of them.
From sector D-Four!
At Mach six point three,
from seventy miles.
They'll hit in 65 seconds!
Go to red one!
Launch interceptors!
Evacuate troops from our
surface observation posts.
[alarms blaring]
Air traffic control.
Gebo Six is to abandon their
craft and take shelter.
As should all other
base personnel.
[MALE AIR TRAFFIC OFFICER A]
Yes ma'am.
What about Gebo five,
he's taxiing.
He's clear for takeoff. Have him
fly west of Merida island
and wait for further orders.
[MALE AIR TRAFFIC OFFICER A]
Yes, ma'am.
Our interceptor missiles have
been prepped. Launching now!
[MALE STAFF D]
Alert. Red One. Alert. Red One.
All surface personnel are
to abandon their work
and take shelter underground.
Interceptors should collide
in three, two... Contact!
[MALE AIR GUARD OFFICER A]
We've intercepted three
of their missiles. The other
five are still approaching!
[FEMALE AIR GUARD OFFICER A]
Second wave of
missiles incoming!
From Sector E Four!
There are nine.
No, make that twelve!
Eighty-five miles
away and closing!
BOL! Get our
interceptors in the air!
Understood. Initiating
Bearing Only Launch
for missile batteries
six through nine!
The first wave of missiles
will hit us in ten seconds!
No reason to panic!
It'll be fast if they're nukes.
♪
Lie down as low as possible.
No matter what happens,
don't sit up.
Why? What's going on?
The enemy found us,
so we're running.
[KANAME gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
Stay down!
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[gasps]
[KANAME shouts]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[KANAME]
Sousuke, up top!
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[KANAME grunts]
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Chidori, did it hurt you at all?
No, I'm all right.
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[KANAME shouts]
Just stay down!
Hey. Want me to shoot
while you drive?
Negative.
But I could--
Don't touch that gun!
Just don't. Okay?
Sousuke, I... I...
Sorry... but you can't.
[HENCHMAN A] They're fleeing
westward on Route 14,
towards Nogawa Park.
[KURAMA]
Don't let them escape.
[HENCHMAN A]
Can we shoot 'em?
Yeah, sure.
Shoot your heart out.
[HENCHMAN A]
Yes, sir.
[car honks]
[HENCHMAN B groans]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Sousuke, look out!
[gasps]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Huh? Chidori.
[SOUSUKE groans]
Chidori!
[KANAME grunts]
[MALE DRIVER A]
Uh, hey kid. You okay?
Get down!
[HENCHMAN C grunts]
[ONLOOKERS gasp, scream]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Can you stand?
[KANAME]
Yeah, I think so.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Do you think you can run?
I can manage.
[HENCHMAN D grunts]
[KANAME gasps]
I'm never getting in a
car you're driving again.
Not for the rest of my life.
Sorry, but you'll do
it any number of times
if it's for
your protection.
[KANAME gasps] Innocent people
are getting caught up in this!
[SOUSUKE] There's nothing
we can do about that.
[KANAME pants]
[SOUSUKE] Uruz seven to
Gebo Nine, do you read me?
[SANTOS] Gebo Nine to
Urzu Seven. I read you.
Report your situation.
[SOUSUKE] We've managed to get
some distance from the enemy.
We're now heading
northwest on foot.
[SANTOS] Gebo Nine, roger that.
Any change in the LZ?
No changes.
We're 500 meters away.
Just look for a
yellow smoke signal.
[gasps]
--[KANAME shouts]
--[SOUSUKE grunts]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[KANAME yelps]
Come on. Hurry!
[MALE ONLOOKER B groans]
[KANAME gasps]
The shrapnel hit him!
[groaning continues]
Are you okay?
[KANAME gasps]
He's hurt because of us!
[SOUSUKE] Don't think
about it. Just move.
[KANAME]
Sousuke!
[groaning continues]
Sorry.
[gunshots]
I can't keep running like this!
We're almost there. Keep going!
[SOUSUKE] Stay low while
we wait for the chopper.
But what about the--
Get down!
[KANAME shouts]
--[helicopter hums]
--[KANAME gasps]
[KANAME]
Is... Is that...?
Yes, just in time.
[KANAME gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
Nice shooting.
[SANTOS]
Come around to the north side.
I'll bring you in from the rear.
Come on. We gotta move.
[KANAME gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[KANAME pants]
[KANAME shouts]
[KANAME gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
Damn it!
[HENCHMAN D grunts]
No more!
Please, I can't take it!
[SOUSUKE]
Don't give up!
No! Stop! I--
[SOUSUKE]
Down!
Running out...
[AL] Executing Emergency
Evacuation Protocol,
as instructed in
file X-ray One.
Use of external
audio is mandatory.
That sounds like...
[AL] This is the
ARX Seven Arm Slave.
Serial Number C-002.
Code name: Arbalest.
[SOUSUKE chuckles]
[AL] If any officers
of affiliated forces
are nearby,
please respond verbally.
Are you still in
one piece, Al?
[AL] Checking Identity.
Sergeant Sousuke Sagara.
Affirmative, Uruz Seven.
I am in one piece.
However, due to rising heat
levels at my current position,
I request permission to move.
Permission granted. Come to
my location immediately!
[AL]
Roger.
[HENCHMEN groaning]
[KANAME gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
Chidori! Climb on!
[KANAME whimpers]
[KANAME]
No... Stop.
[MYTHRIL STAFF chatters]
How many casualties?
Eleven serious injuries.
Twenty-eight minor wounds.
And five deceased.
Observation Post Two
didn't evacuate in time.
[TESSA gasps]
[TESSA]
I see.
That airstrike won't
be the end of it.
It was only to soften us
up for the real attack.
You think they'll
send in troops?
I do.
We should prepare for
an airborne assault.
[GEBO 5]
This is Gebo Five.
To the Merida Island
Command Center.
I'm detecting a group
of large aircraft.
More than ten of them.
They're approaching
from sector F Eight.
[MYTHRIL STAFF chatters]
Scramble our Super
Harriers to intercept them.
Yes, ma'am!
Kalinin. Do you think that
we'll be able to stop them?
If we were at full strength,
I'd say we could.
But as the situation stands,
our forces are both
wounded and blind.
[TESSA] And our front
door's been demolished.
In preparation for the
worst-case scenario,
we should consider the
crew's escape route.
[MARDUKAS]
Yes, ma'am.
How badly was the
runway damaged?
[KALININ] We'll be able to
send out the super harriers,
but not transports. Repairs will
take three days at least.
What about the Danaan?
The Tuatha de Danaan could
transport every last person
on this base.
It wasn't hit.
But as you know, it's been
undergoing maintenance
since last week.
It'll be at least half a day
before it can put out to sea.
[TESSA]
They must hurry.
Please go and oversee the
work yourself, Commander.
Yes, Madame Captain.
Lieutenant Commander.
Prep every AS unit we
have with D Equipment.
All of them, even the
M6's we use for training.
Have them deploy on
the northern coast.
[KALININ]
Yes, Madame Captain.
[SHINOHARA]
Wait a moment!
Gebo Five is calling in
with new information.
[TESSA]
Put him through.
[GEBO 5] This is Gebo
Five to Merida Island.
I'm picking up some, uh,
heat signatures from the sea.
Sector G Two.
There are three of them.
I suspect they're
underwater vessels.
[TESSA]
Clarify your report, Gebo Five.
What exactly are they?
[GEBO 5]
A-Apologies, ma'am.
I've never seen
readings like this.
Wait, I just picked them
up on my optical sensors.
I'll send you the image now.
What in the world is that?
It's a Behemoth.
[MYTHRIL STAFF gasp, shout]
[SPECK, KURTZ gasp]
[KURZ]
Behemoths, huh?
Yeah, same as the one you
guys tangled with in Tokyo.
Only there's three
of 'em this time.
You've gotta be kidding.
This as bad as I think?
It's probably worse.
Those things can
shrug off missiles,
and our 57 millimeter cannons
won't even tickle 'em.
Those monsters sound invincible.
How does the captain expect
us to take them on?
[KURZ ] Well ya can't
complain 'em to death.
I don't like this one bit.
We're gettin' played here.
You can skip everything
before process C.
[MALE STAFF G]
Yes, sir!
Put those 40 millimeter
rounds over there!
And get those GECs to
site Two, on the double!
Is this everyone? As you've
all doubtlessly noticed,
Amalgam has launched
a major offensive.
The behemoths they've deployed
pose an especially great threat.
They're set to reach
us in 40 minutes.
The solar storm allowed them
to get this close unnoticed.
Now it's on us to
intercept them.
And how's that
supposed to work?
I heard that those giants
were equipped with those
Lamba Drive whatevers.
That's true.
Our standard weaponry won't
do a goddamn thing to them.
Yeah, I read the damn report.
The mission's screwed.
[CLOUSEAU] We're doing
it regardless, soldier.
This base is very
well-fortified, but it can fall.
The Danaan is in maintenance.
If those behemoths
reach the shore,
they'll eventually destroy it.
So what's your point?
[CLOUSEAU]
It's our only means of escape.
We're on a solitary island.
If we allow the
Danaan to go down,
then every one of us will
end up dead in this cave.
Our only option is to
defeat those behemoths.
So that's what we'll do.
Actually, there is
another option.
How about instead of getting
killed in a losing battle,
we grab some rifles and trot on
down to the command center.
You'd better not be saying
what I think you are.
I bet the enemy would go for it
if we promised to hand over
Tessa and her submarine
without putting up a fight.
I mean at the end of the day,
they are businesspeople.
Why wouldn't they take
a sweet deal like that?
[CLOUSEAU] Go ahead and keep
running your mouth, Speck.
You'll be court-marshalled
for treason.
[SPECK groans]
Oh, come on.
I didn't sign up for this out
of humanism. I was hired.
So you want me to die here?
For what, my comrades?
You son of a...
Call me what you will,
but I wanna live to
spend what I got paid.
Heh. And I know I'm
not the only one.
I warned you, Corporal.
You give me no choice.
I'm putting you
under arrest for--
[TESSA]
You'd like to sell me out?
I've heard worse ideas.
[SPECK grunts]
[CLOUSEAU]
Madame Captain.
I suspected one of you
might broach this topic,
so I thought I'd come
check up on you.
So you were listening.
Well, hey. Ya know it
wasn't personal, right?
[TESSA]
Hand me your side-arm, please.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Tessa!
[TESSA]
Morality aside,
Mr. Speck's logic
would be sound.
Except, it fails to account for
my willingness to shoot every
traitor among you dead.
[SPECK chuckles]
Whoa there, be reasonable.
I think you're a
great girl and all, but--
[gasps]
[CREW gasps]
[sighs] Reconsider
your attitude, Corporal.
[gasps]
[TESSA] Perhaps you thought I
came here to plead with you.
That I'd beg you, teary eyed,
to spare me. To save us.
[SPECK grunts]
That I'd appeal to your
compassionate nature
and seek to turn
pity into loyalty.
The fact that
you're here now,
means that you too walk
the path of the warrior.
Were you forced down the path
that led you to this fight?
Or did you choose it?
[SPECK grunts]
[TESSA] Did you think that
I was given this command
through some accident?
No ma'am.
Address me fully.
Tell me who I am.
[SPECK gasps]
You're Captain
Teletha Testarossa.
Commanding officer of the
Tuatha de Danaan's forces.
That's good.
Now retract your previous
statements and apologize to me.
At once.
I'm sorry, captain. And I
take everything back, ma'am.
Very well.
Mr. Speck. Your team is in dire
need of your skills as a pilot.
I'll overlook your
treasonous instigation.
Feel free to stay on
once we've survived this.
Once we've survived?
And how exactly do ya figure
that miracle's gonna happen?
You've misunderstood
this arrangement, soldier.
The troops I command can't
die until I tell them to,
and I have given no such order.
You will survive. You don't
have permission to die.
Come back alive.
That is an order.
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am. Right.
Good luck out there.
[SPECK groans]
So. Sorry about that. Shit.
But cut me some slack.
It crossed your
minds too, right?
C'mon guys, don't look
at me like that.
At least ya know enough
to be ashamed of yourself.
[CLOUSEAU]
Oh, gimme a break.
We'll just have to rack our
brains for a clever plan.
And in the event that
this mission succeeds,
we'll get paid with our lives.
Sounds fair enough to me.
Hey. We've fought against
odds this bad before.
[SPECK laughs] Ya know what?
I think I wanna marry that girl.
[CLOUSEAU]
Tough break, Corporal.
Huh?
Tessa's suitors are processed
in order of rank.
[ALL laugh]
All right. Let's talk
about strategy.
Someone among us has actually
engaged a Behemoth in combat
and done damage to it.
[KURZ grunts, gasps]
[KURZ gulps]
You mean me?
--[cars honking]
--[sirens blaring]
[helicpoters humming]
[PEDESTRIANS chattering]
[metallic grinding]
[SOUSUKE]
Stay on alert mode four.
[AL]
Roger.
[SOUSUKE]
You all right now?
Yeah, more or less. Did the
people in that helicopter--?
Yes.
If they hadn't
tried to rescue me,
they would still be
alive right now.
[SOUSUKE]
They died in the line of duty.
But still.
You can't blame yourself.
So many people were
hurt because I--
Chidori.
[KANAME]
Sorry... I'm scared.
You have a right to be.
That was intense.
It's not fair.
[phone rings]
[KANAME]
No. No, not her.
What's the matter?
They took Kyoko.
They took them all!
[BOTH gasp]
♪
[SOUSUKE] Next time:
"Big One Percent."