♪
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Where are we going now?
Down to the helipad.
So you're running.
We're swarmed with visitors.
We can't possibly
entertain them all.
Sousuke's here, isn't he?
[LEONARD] What would you
do if he were here?
Would you look for a chance to
cut me down and run to his side?
Like I'd get one.
The entire reason you're here
is because you don't want
more people to get hurt.
Or has that changed?
No, but that doesn't mean...
We have little time. Come on.
Let go!
[KANAME grunts]
Release the girl at once.
Do nothing else to her.
[ALASTOR]
Roger.
[KANAME coughs]
[LEONARD]
Here's your chance.
[gasps]
Shoot me right now
and you can escape.
That one's no longer a threat.
If you have the resolve,
then prove it.
[LEONARD] Ten... Nine...
Eight... Seven... Six... Five...
...Four... Three...
Two... One....
...Zero.
Time's up. And still
you do nothing.
[KANAME gasps]
[LEONARD] Perhaps you're
not so resolute after all.
No, that's not true.
Were our roles reversed,
I'd've fired in a heartbeat.
But, you're unwilling
to dirty your hands.
[KANAME gasps]
[LEONARD]
We're done here. Let's go.
Just wait a second.
[LEONARD]
You've lost. Give that here.
No, get away from me!
[gunshot]
[KANAME]
Leonard? Are you--?
[SOLDIER A]
What happened here?
[SOLDIER B] Put the weapon
down on the ground!
[KANAME gasps] Wait.
You're Mister Kalinin, right?
I-I didn't mean to--
I just panicked, and--
[KALININ]
Take her to the helipad.
[SOLDIER A]
How is he?
The bullet only grazed him.
He was lucky this time.
[explosion]
[SOLDIER A]
Reinforcements?
[KALININ]
No. More enemies.
[KURZ grunts]
How about this?
No friggin' way.
Just who is this guy?
You're good, Kurz, but you've
got a ways to go.
[gasps]
[CLOUSEAU growls]
Give up. You can't
keep running forever.
Our com links are jammed.
They're not just strong,
They're better at
electronic warfare too.
We're completely outmatched.
[computer beeps]
[SABINA gasps]
[KALININ] We have more visitors.
Return at once.
Roger that.
They're running away?
Can't be...
Something must've
happened at their base.
Yeah. And it saved
our friggin' butts.
[MAO]
I hope Sousuke's able to manage.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[SOUSUKE]
Reinforcements?
No. They're after Leonard too.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[gasps]
It's Chidori!
[KALININ]
Take off.
Is that? No way.
[SOLDIERS grunt]
Chidori!
No! Sousuke!
I came to save you,
like I promised!
Sousuke!
Chidori.
[SOLDIER F]
Drop your weapon!
[SOLDIER F] The girl we were
after might've gotten away,
but at least we can get
some information out of you.
Cuff him.
[SOLDIER G]
Sir!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[LEMON]
Sousuke! Get down!
Hell yeah! Just like
Khe Sanh, ain't it, Seals?
[SOLDIERS groan]
[SOUSUKE]
That's enough, Lemon. Withdraw!
The mission's a failure.
[WRAITH]
Heads up, Sagara!
We're about to drop
you the Laevatein.
Laevatein? What are you saying?
It's your new AS.
As for the name, it came up
with that all on its own.
[ALL grunt]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[SOUSUKE]
Impressive.
[AL]
Been some time, Sergeant.
That really you, Al?
[AL]
Affirmative.
However, this mech is
known as the ARX-8.
AKA Laevatein.
Sergeant Sagara.
I'd like to request permission
to rejoin you in battle.
Permission granted.
Glad you're back.
[AL] I am honored.
You may board when ready.
Let's go.
[AL] Warning. Multiple hostile
AS's on approach.
Three Behemoths,
and three Codarls.
Shall we start things off
with a bang, Sergeant?
[SOUSUKE breathes deeply]
Why not? Let's do this!
[AL]
Roger.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Hey Al. That was a bit much.
[AL]
Pardon me, Sergeant.
This mech has yet to undergo
an actual field test.
[SOUSUKE] That's a problem.
Does the driver work, or not?
[AL]
You mean the Lambda Driver?
[SOUSUKE]
Of course.
[AL] I do not know.
It has never been tested.
[SOUSUKE] Well get ready.
We're about to.
[AL]
Ready!
[AL] Success.
Our foes are outclassed.
You had me in a
cold sweat, though.
[computer beeps]
[AL]
Threats approaching.
Our weapons?
[AL]
Leave it to me.
[grunts]
[AL]
Hold still.
[SOUSUKE]
We have four arms?
[AL] I will control
them autonomously.
You don't even need me.
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[AL] Current overweight
estimate: fifteen hundred tons.
Escape immediately.
No!
[yells]
[SOUSUKE gasps]
What other weapons
do we have, Al?
[AL]
Try this.
[SOUSUKE]
The Demolition Gun?
That thing's bigger
than most Howitzers.
[AL] Its recoil and damage
potential are equally high.
It cannot be fired
without a Lambda driver,
so be cautious.
Manual fire.
[AL]
Ready.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[AL] Success. It penetrated
the enemy's field.
[SOUSUKE]
One more!
Amazing.
Any others?
[AL]
One Behemoth-type remains.
It has abandoned the
field and is withdrawing.
Shall we pursue?
[SOUSUKE] It's outside of
this weapon's range, right?
[AL]
Technically, no.
What?
[AL] Demolition Gun
switching to Howitzer mode.
Maximum range is
30 kilometers.
All right, let's give it a try.
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[AL]
Direct hit. Target destroyed.
Airspace is clear of hostiles.
Good. Maintain altitude.
And take us north-northwest.
[SOLDIER B grunts]
Shit. What the hell have
these guys gotten us into?
[KANAME grunts]
[SOLDIER B gasps]
Don't move an inch.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Whoa. Don't do
anything crazy, kid.
Then don't test me.
Just turn this thing around!
You're a lot livelier
than expected.
[KANAME]
Take us back.
If you don't. I'll kill him.
What do I care?
The man can't even keep
track of his own weapon.
I'm not bluffing.
I really will shoot him!
Oh will you? You mean the same
way you shot Leonard Testarossa?
You shouldn't pick up a gun if
you're not prepared to shoot.
[KANAME grunts]
In order to enforce your will,
you must first be
ready to hurt others.
And I don't believe
that you are.
You've no idea what I can do.
I know what I can do. And I
know that you're not like me.
[KANAME gasps]
Just tell me this. Will I
ever get to see him again?
No, you will not.
Give me the gun.
[KANAME]
Then I'll do this.
Hold on!
I've had enough.
Just calm down. I'll do
what I can for you.
So turn us around.
[KALININ] I'm sorry,
but that, I can't do.
Leonard is still in need
of medical treatment.
Then there's the risk of the
enemy shooting us down.
Please calm yourself
and lower the gun
so we can talk about this.
Fine. Then let me say goodbye.
Goodbye?
Give me a radio.
[MAO chuckles]
[KURZ] Damn. You're tellin' me
that Sousuke did all of this?
That's crazy.
[MAO] It's called
the Laevatein, right?
That's one promising mech.
[KURZ] If only we had it
back at Merida Island.
[SOUSUKE]
What are you talking about?
[CLOUSEAU] We'll tell you later.
More importantly, Sagara,
I want the prisoners to see as
little of that mech as possible.
Yes sir.
Well, Al, activate ECS.
Make us invisible.
[AL] Not possible.
This mech is not equipped
with an Electronic
Concealment System.
Seriously?
[AL] Between its powerful combat
features and the Lambda driver,
there was no space for any
extraneous electronic equipment.
[SOUSUKE]
There're barely any electronics.
This is modern warfare.
That's crazy.
[AL] We'll rely on allied
support on that front.
Let us fight on, and not
lose heart, Sergeant.
[SOUSUKE] I can think of
some extraneous equipment.
[AL]
What might that be?
Well, you. If I threw
you in the trash,
I could fit an ECS
in here easily.
[AL]
That suggestion is nonsense.
Without me, this unit
is an utterly useless-
I've picked up a
new radio transmission.
It would appear
that it's for you.
For me?
[AL]
Shall I patch them through?
Do it.
[KANAME]
Sousuke?
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[KANAME]
Can you hear me? Come in.
Chidori! Are you okay?
Where are you?
Don't worry about me, I'm fine.
[SOUSUKE]
Well things aren't fine.
A lot's happened since they took
you. It wasn't an easy journey.
But I came.
I came to save you,
and take you back to school,
just like I promised!
Where are you now? Tell me!
Please, Sousuke. Stop this.
Stop what? Coming for you?
[KANAME]
I get it now.
If I keep trying to be free,
then no matter what,
innocent people are
bound to get hurt.
I mean, just look at
what happened to Kyoko.
That was my fault!
Chidori.
[KANAME] I can't take
it anymore. So please...
...just forget about me.
[SOUSUKE]
You mean that?
We have to end it.
This is goodbye.
I won't ever...
hear your voice again.
I've changed my mind.
[ALL gasp]
Look, forget what I just said!
I don't care if I hurt someone!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[KANAME] Don't move.
I'm not done talking.
Sousuke, I have
an order for you.
[SOUSUKE]
What is it?
Find me and take me home.
Rescue me, no matter what
it takes! Even if someone dies.
Just do it. Save me. Even if
hundreds of people die.
Or thousands, or millions!
You come and get me.
Put all of those stupid,
annoying, nonsense, soldier
skills of yours to use, okay?
No matter who you're up against,
or how strong they are.
You beat them up and
come hold me tight.
You can do that,
can't you? Well?!
Yes. Not a problem.
[KANAME whimpers]
Don't you worry. I'll find you.
Sousuke. I love you.
I love you, Chidori.
[KANAME]
I'm glad.
So. The next time I see you,
We had better kiss.
No holding back,
no matter who's around.
Kay? You promise?
I promise.
[KANAME] Oh. You know
that part about millions dying
was just a figure
of speech, right?
[SOUSUKE gasps]
Right... I know that.
[KANAME]
I'll be waiting.
Chidori?
I feel as though
you tricked me.
[KANAME]
What do you mean?
You had me thinking you
truly intended to die.
I wasn't acting. I did mean it.
That said...
Now, I have resolve.
Wow, buddy. "Sousuke,
I love you so much!"
And then, "Yeah, well I
love you even more, baby."
I could barely take it.
It's so sweet I almost
threw up in my cockpit.
Half a year apart and
that's what you open with?
I gotta say, it really
seems like you've grown.
You're doin' your big sis proud.
[SOUSUKE]
Mao...
Well. Anyway, it's good to
see you're still kickin'.
I'm sure that we'll have
a lot to talk about.
Sir.
Hey, Lemon.
So, you are a ladies' man.
Well uh... You see--
No sweat. You mind introducing
me to your commanding officer?
I feel like we're already
allies unofficially,
but I'd like to make it formal.
The captain? Uh...
[TESSA gasps]
Sergeant Sagara!
[TESSA giggles]
Hey, Tessa.
[LEMON chuckles]
It's been quite
a while, hasn't it?
[SOUSUKE]
I'm glad you're all right.
[TESSA giggles]
So, uh--
[SEALS, COURTNEY]
Lil' Tessa!
[SEALS]
Girl, I've missed you so much!
[COURTNEY]
I've missed you more!
[TESSA gasps]
We've been lonely without ya'.
[SEALS]
Mm-hm!
[TESSA] What on earth
are those two doing here?
[SOUSUKE]
Well, a lot's happened.
[SEALS] Hey nurse!
I need some TLC!
Just ignore this idiot.
I'm the one that needs care.
Take them to the brig.
[MITHRIL SOLDIER A]
Sir.
[SEALS, COURTNEY giggle]
[COURTNEY] Get your hands
off me! I'm an American soldier!
Any attack on me will be
taken as an act of war!
[SEALS]
Tell 'em you love me too!
[SOUSUKE]
Ahem. Moving past that,
I'd like to introduce Lemon.
He's an agent
with France's DGSE.
And he saved my life twice.
[LEMON gasps]
Lemon. This is Captain Te--
Lemon?
[LEMON grunts]
What's that?
I was just introducing
you to my commander.
Wait? Really?
You mean... this girl?
So you can introduce me to her?
[SOUSUKE]
Hey.
That guy is head over heels.
[MAO]
Talk about easy to read.
Guess the fan club's gonna
have to make more jackets.
[MARDUKAS]
Ahem... Captain.
We still haven't verified
Sagara's intentions.
Oh yes, I almost forgot.
Mr. Sagara, will you
rejoin our forces?
Yes. With your permission,
I'll return to my unit.
Permission granted.
On behalf of the Danaan's crew,
I'd like to welcome you home.
[AL]
Excuse me, Captain Testarossa,
but does that welcome
extend to me as well?
Yes, of course it does, Al.
I'm relieved to see that
you made it back safe.
[AL] Thank you, Captain.
I am honored.
♪