[MAINA]
Just one?
Do you really only
have one ticket today?
[ERIPIYO grunts]
[ERIPIYO]
Yeah.
I guess if I can't buy merch,
I'm kinda worthless.
[MAINA]
That's not true!
Not true at all.
I'm happy just knowing that
you come to see me, Eripiyo.
The fact that you
come to see me...
[ERIPIYO]
Wait, what?
[gasps]
[ERIPIYO] Hold the phone.
Is she trying to lure me in?
Ah, right, that makes sense.
It's because of the
popularity contest.
Well, it's working!
I really wish she would
make this a regular thing!
I...
[ERIPIYO] Uh! She doesn't even
know how to do it, does she?
How adorable!
I--
Don't force it.
Huh?
You don't have to say anything
if you don't want to.
No, that's not--
And your time's up.
Thank you very much.
Your support means
the world to me.
I'll do my very best!
Just promise me you won't
push yourself too hard.
You have to take care of
your health, too, you know.
Thanks so much,
but I hope you don't have
any creepy ulterior motives.
I'm so happy to shake your hand
I might break your fingers!
You came to see me here, too?
I hope you come by
the studio again!
Your dancing was incredible
as always, Yumeri!
You really deserve to be at
the center, you know that?
There's no way. Do you really
think I deserve that?
Of course, you deserve
the whole world!
So I'll give you as many
of my votes as I can!
You mean it? Thanks so much!
[ERIPIYO, KUMASA]
Phew.
I'm startin' to think this whole
popularity contest thing
is gonna burn us out, too.
I'm just stressed because
I can't support her
like I want to.
Hey, know of any part-time jobs
I could do with a bum leg?
[KUMASA] Why don't you
just swallow your pride
and beg your parents for money?
Like I told you, my leg
prevents me from groveling!
Uh.
But my kidneys...
Good God.
I've got an idea!
How 'bout you and I go to a maid
café and blow off some steam?
What?
Maina's the only girl
I want attention from.
Well, sure, and Reo's
the only one for me.
But we're talking about
two different things here.
I just think we need
a break from the norm.
There's this new place I
heard a lot about lately.
And don't worry,
this one's on me.
Okay, if you insist.
But don't expect me
to act all excited.
[ERIPIYO]
They're so dang cute!
This is so great!
[MAID]
Welcome home, masters.
I'm so honored to
be your maid today!
My name is-- Uh...
[BOTH]
Uh.
It's Aya.
[AYA] It's Reo's stan
and Maina's stan.
It isn't what you think!
There wasn't a performance
today, so we thought we'd--
Kumasa, would you shut up?
You really think Aya would
remember our faces?
[AYA]
Of course I do.
And I'm telling Reo and Maina.
[ERIPIYO, KUMASA]
No! Please don't!
I'm not her stan!
[AYA]
Whaddaya think I am, a moron?
[ERIPIYO] Please don't
tell Maina I was here--
I'm begging you!
I'll do whatever you say!
Come to think of it,
you've been stingy
about buying Maina's
merch lately.
But you'll spend money
in a maid café?
[ERIPIYO] There's a perfectly
good explanation!
I've been buying Reo's
merch. I'm safe, right?
That's not it! Dude!
Reo's gonna be so sad!
[KUMASA gasps]
Kumasa, I thought that I was
supposed to be your number one.
Why did I ever think
I could believe in you?
--[KUMASA] Reo!
--[ERIPIYO] Maina!
No! Don't believe her...
[sighs]
I mean, I guess I can
keep it a secret.
You angel!
So, let me see here.
I'll get the "have our maids
make you a parfait" thing.
You bounced back fast!
Hey, Aya. Try to lure me in.
Really? So you're
testing an idol now?
Yeah, what of it?
We all want someone to
be nice to us, right?
[BOTH]
Uhh...
[KUMASA]
I'm surprised you've been able
to keep being a Maina
stan for this long.
Huh?
If Reo treated me the
way Maina treats you,
I think I'd pass out.
Jeez, and Motoi? He'd probably
drop dead on the spot.
Meh, it's cool.
I don't ask for any
special fan service,
her being alive
is enough for me.
I'm happy just knowing
she's out there.
I am eternally grateful that
her parents got together
and I got to meet
her in this life.
[AYA]
Thanks for your patience!
Here you go!
Your maid-made parfait!
[ERIPIYO]
Wait, are those salmon filets?
[KUMASA] You managed to work
Maina's color into the mix!
What excellent service!
Maina was really happy that
she placed third in the ranking.
So you had better keep
supporting her, or else!
[ERIPIYO, KUMASA]
Aya!
[AYA] Also, since I'm keeping
your dirty little secret,
you each have to put
in one vote for me!
Did an idol just blackmail us?
I didn't realize she
was such a tsundere.
[AYA]
I'm not!
[ERIPIYO]
So Maina was happy.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'd love for Maina
to be the center,
just so I could see her smile.
For that to happen,
I'm gonna have to ramp up
my support even more!
[ERIPIYO] My organs are the only
things I have worth selling!
Kidneys for sale!
[AYA groans]
[MAKI]
What's the matter, Yume?
[gasps]
[YUMERI]
Oh, uh, it's nothing!
Okay.. Well, let's
head out, then.
[YUMERI]
Yeah, sure.
Ever since I joined the agency,
all I've ever done is watch
Maki from behind her.
I never thought people
would notice me next to her,
let alone vote for me.
Yet... here we are.
[MAKI]
Hey, Yume.
Do you remember the
dance for the front row?
Huh?
Yeah. I've watched you do it
a million times, so I know it.
That's good. You're ready to
move up front any time, then.
[YUMERI]
What?
Let's do our best again today!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[AYA]
Maina, your neck tie's crooked.
Thanks for your help, Aya.
Oh, yeah, yesterday,
when I saw Eripiyo, I--
Wait, what?
[AYA]
Ah!
You saw Eripiyo yesterday?
But there was no show.
Where were you?
[AYA] Ha. Never mind!
Let's do our best!
[AYA] Oh, crap! I promised
them I wouldn't tell!
[MAINA] I wonder what
Aya's freaking out about.
♪ ♪
[singing in Japanese]
[GIRLS]
Thanks for coming, everybody!
[AYA]
Hey, Eripiyo. Sorry!
Huh...?
[ERIPIYO]
What the heck was that about?
[ASAMI] Hang on, did Aya just
personally respond to Eripiyo?
[MURAKAMI]
But why Eripiyo?
Hey, now that I think about it,
I saw her coming out of the
maid café where Aya works.
Whoa, seriously?
[OTAKU A]
No way!
[ASAMI]
This can't be.
[GUYS]
Is Eripiyo changing her fave?
[FUJITA] Well, she lined up
for Maina, as always.
[FUJIKAWA]
But she only bought one again?
[MURAKAMI] Is she only in
her line to say goodbye?
So, Maina, if you had
to make a choice,
which organ would you say
that humans need the least?
I was thinking one of the lungs,
since we have two.
Hey, Eripiyo. Uh, did you
see Aya somewhere yesterday?
Huh?
[ERIPIYO]
Wait, was Aya's weird wave to me
an attempt to say sorry
'cause Maina found out?
[AYA]
My bad!
[ERIPIYO]
But because I'm so broke,
I couldn't even vote
for Aya once.
So I'm just gonna have
to forgive her for it.
Why, though?
You never come to see me
except at an event,
and I want you to.
Huh?
[ERIPIYO] No way! Could she
be trying to lure me in?
Or, I mean...
Wait, you don't?
That's not-- I mean...
Time's up. Thanks so much.
Come back and see us some time!
Wow, creepy.
That Maina. I'm all
twisted in knots!
[KUMASA]
Twisted how? Like, your leg?
Sure! I'd break my other leg
for Maina in a heartbeat!
I wish I had more than
two to break for her!
I hope I can buy two
CDs next week!
You planning to sell
an organ by next week?
My organs ain't that cheap!
[KUMASA]
Eripiyo, listen.
I hate to rain on
your parade, but...
There isn't even a month left
to vote in the contest.
[ERIPIYO screams]
[MAINA]
Oh, Eripiyo.
I wonder why she only
bought one again today.
Then there's Aya.
Oh, yeah, yesterday,
when I saw Eripiyo, I--
Ha. Never mind!
Let's do our best!
[MATSUO] The popularity
ranking is almost over!
I mean, Reo's probably not
gonna lose first place.
Yeah, well, you never
know what could happen.
The real battle starts
now, at the end!
[MAINA] Those are fans of ours.
I run into fans a lot.
Maybe I should start
taking a later train.
Not that anyone other than
Eripiyo's ever noticed me.
I think voting would be easier
if we all just agreed to stan
the same girl Eripiyo does.
Dude, as if Maina
even stands a chance.
[FUJIKAWA]
Get this:
I heard Eripiyo switched
her fave to Aya.
Huh?
[KOSUGA] Perfect timing, too.
Aya's in last place now.
[FUJIKAWA]
You see it all the time--
fans who only ever root
for the underdogs.
[MATSUO] Yeah. They just
like to be unique.
[FUJIKAWA] That must be what's
going on with Eripiyo.
[ERIPIYO] I guess if I can't
buy merch, I'm kinda worthless.
[MAINA]
That's not it, Eripiyo.
I don't just want you
to come buy things.
It's more than that.
I want you to come see me
because I really love
being near you.
[MAINA]
Such a simple thing to say,
but I can't ever seem
to get it out.
I guess... all I can do
is just wait and see.
[MAINA]
But at this rate, will Eripiyo?
Wow, so Maina's in seventh now?
I guess your rank increase
was short lived.
Yeah. Sure seems that way.
[YUKA]
And Yumeri moved up to third!
Yume's a great dancer, so she
could probably handle front row.
Wait, does that mean Maki's
gonna be in the back now?
No way. Maki's too flashy--
she's gotta be in front.
[YUMERI]
Please shut up.
Guys, I'll be fine
wherever, for real.
[YUMERI]
You will?
We have some time
before we go onstage,
do you wanna play a card game?
Let's say that the loser has to
buy five CDs from the winner,
and they have to
vote for them, too!
Veto! Those five votes mean
a lot to us bottom feeders!
[YUMERI]
They're so carefree!
[YUKA] Okay, then the loser
has to lick the floor
in the greenroom!
[MAINA]
That sounds fair enough to me.
[YUMERI]
"Fair enough"? Hang on.
Am I the only one here who's
worried about the ranking?
Well, Aya seems
fired up, at least.
Hey, Maki? You cool being fifth?
Well, yeah, of course I am.
You shouldn't be! It's not
cool. It's super uncool!
I hope you do get to
be on the front row.
It feels so amazing.
[YUMERI] But I'm fine. I like
the way things are now.
The girl I like is in trouble.
Please, Mom.
I can pay you back! Just...
[ERIPIYO] ...please let me
borrow some money!
Oh, wow.
Look at how strong
your arms have gotten
since you broke your leg.
[ERIPIYO] Well, I have been
training for this moment.
[KUMASA] You trained your
upper body just to beg?
Oh, yikes. You really
are trash, huh?
So... did she lend you
the money or what?
Your mom, I mean.
Classic Mom move.
Thinking that some silly millet
dumplings can solve everything.
Apparently, durians
are like persimmons,
and they take eight whole
years to bear fruit!
Oh, yeah. Also, durians are
the official fruit of--
[SORANE] Uh, Yumeri,
don't you like durians?
What? Oh, no way.
I'm more of a mango
fan, honestly.
Wow, that's so interesting!
[FANS laughing]
[FAN A] Yume! Congrats
on getting third place!
They must've seen the
most recent ranking!
Well, Yumeri. Wanna give
a little speech, then?
Um, thank you all.
I never expected this.
I guess I just kind of assumed I
would always be in the back row.
[FAN B]
You deserve it!
[FAN C]
Yeah!
[FAN D]
What he said!
You're amazing Yumeri!
[FAN E]
Believe in yourself!
--[FAN F] Yume!
--[FAN G] You've got this!
Well, thank you!
Hey, I've got an idea:
Let's change the formation
to the current ranking
for this song.
Ooh, yeah!
Wait. So what does
that mean for me?
[MAKI] It means you're in
your usual spot, Yuka.
[YUKA] Maki, do you even know
the back row choreography?
Don't underestimate
the top three, hon.
Yume, you know the front
row choreography, right?
[FANS cheering]
[YUMERI]
Beautiful.
My Yumeri's coming into her own.
[YUMERI] They're so happy
to see me up here.
I can't believe I'm
in the front row!
Now, here's "Hot
Summer Holiday!"
[FANS cheering]
[singing in Japanese]
Wow, Yumeri can really dance.
I can't believe I never
noticed before.
Yeah, she's the best
dancer out of all of them.
I read online that she's
been taking lessons
to polish her technique.
[ERIPIYO]
Mmm...
Maina's good, too.
I hope she makes it
to the front row soon.
[OTAKU A]
Great job!
I've supported you for so long.
I was so happy to see
you in the front row!
You were just so incredible.
I can't get over it!
I owe it all to you,
Mr. Nagai, so thank you.
[YUMERI]
I'm grateful.
But it's just my regular
crowd, no one new.
[SORANE]
That's weird.
For coming in third,
Yumeri doesn't have
many people in her line.
[MAINA]
Oh, no. Only one again today?
Maybe Eripiyo really does
want to start supporting Aya.
Why aren't you supporting
me as much anymore?
Sorry, I haven't been able to.
[MAINA gasps]
[MAINA]
There I go again.
No, that's not what I--
I couldn't sell
my organs in time.
I'm not even sure where
one would sell organs,
to be honest.
Does the black market have
an app or something?
[YOSHIKAWA]
Thank you very much! Time's up.
[MAINA]
It always seems to end with her
talking about
selling her organs.
I don't get it. I don't
understand you, Eripiyo.
If you wanna change
your fave, just tell me!
[BOTH laughing]
[MAINA] But that's the
last thing I want!
[RENA]
Hi, Maina.
I was able to buy three
of your CDs today.
Eripiyo usually buys them
all up, so I'm glad.
Thanks, Rena!
[ERIPIYO]
Ugh.
Ouch. This hurts. But still...
Ah! They're so cute!
Like two little birds
of a feather!
It seems like that new girl
might be a Maina stan.
She's so cute!
Hm? You don't mean
Eripiyo, right?
Of course I don't mean her.
What about "new
girl" says Eripiyo?
No, I mean Sorane look-alike.
[ERIPIYO]
Yeah, I know, right?
Rena is super cute!
Maina must be happy to have a
fan who's so adorable for once.
[ERIPIYO]
Yeah, you're onto something.
Maina never looks
that happy with me.
[MAINA giggles]
[ERIPIYO]
Gloom.
I can't buy any CDs, but...
Oh, wow. Did everybody go home?
Unlike us, the front row has
busy lives to get back to.
Hey, speak for yourself.
I was on the front row
before this last vote!
Maina, someone brought
a present for you.
Huh? For me?
Well, this is a first.
Who could it be from?
Um, let's see.
It's from Eripiyo, so
you'd better be careful.
[MAINA]
Eripiyo brought me a gift?
Yeah, and I examined
the packaging.
There didn't seem to be
a wiretap or anything.
[MAINA] This is the very first
present Eripiyo's ever given me!
[MAINA] Hey, Aya, did you
get millet dumplings?
No, why would I get
anything from Eripiyo?
She's terrifying.
Oh. Well, okay, then.
[MAINA] I'll be your pet
as long as you'll have me!
Woof, woof!
So Eripiyo will bring
you dumplings,
but won't buy your CDs?
What's up with that?
Huh?
Maybe she just doesn't feel
as compelled to buy your stuff
since you got to
third place once.
[FUJIKAWA]
You see it all the time--
fans who only ever root
for the underdogs.
[MATSUO] Yeah, they
just like to be unique.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Oh, my bad.
Oh, Maina, we're really sorry.
[MAINA]
It's fine.
Really.
[MAINA]
Oh, Eripiyo.
[MAKI] Doesn't being on
the front row feel amazing?
[YUMERI]
Yeah.
You looked like you were
having a lot of fun up there.
Was it obvious?
I've never experienced
anything like it.
That being said, I don't
wanna get used to it.
I would much rather just
stay in the back row.
Seriously? That's what you want?
Well, yeah, sure.
If I stay in the back row,
I can always watch you.
[clatter]
[MAKI]
Jeez. Look what I did.
I didn't expect you to say that.
You've been carrying a lot
of stuff lately. What's up?
[MAKI] Uh, don't worry
about it. I, um...
[YUMERI gasps]
What? You didn't
steal those, did you?
[MAKI]
Hey, calm down.
There's no reason to be weird.
I bought these all myself.
[YUMERI]
Huh? But why?
That means you're going to
fall in the ranking, Maki!
[MAKI]
I wanted them all to see you
and the work you've put
into your dancing.
So they'd know that
even in the back row
you're still amazing.
That's why. But I
won't buy any more.
And from this point on,
you're going to have to
work hard for your fans.
Maki.
[FANS cheering]
[YUMERI]
That gorgeous view.
Maki showed me that.
And my fans did, too.
They made it so beautiful
for me up there.
[YUMERI] But still, wouldn't
this count as cheating?
[MAKI]
Aya votes for herself.
She buys her own CDs.
[YUMERI]
Oh, wow. Does she really?
[MAKI]
I voted for you, and I'm glad.
But now I have all these
handshake tickets.
So, then. Can I have
a handshake, Yume?
Sure!
Thank you for always
supporting me.
It means so much.
You deserve it.
You were so cute up there.
How many tickets is this worth?
[YUMERI]
Just one, I think.
[NAGAI] Your dancing was
incredible as always, Yumeri!
Also, congrats on placing
third in the latest ranking!
If it were up to me,
you'd be first!
I'm so grateful to have
supported you all this time!
You'll always be front
and center to me!
[YOSHIKAWA] Thank you!
Come back and see us.