[NARRATOR A] The day was
December 31st. New Year's Eve.
The Okayama City Shopping
District bustled.
Shoppers were on the hunt,
determined to find
New Year's supplies
and good luck charms.
Everyone was getting ready
to ring in the new year.
[MAINA gasps]
Oh, no! I totally forgot!
Maina, calm down.
I'm sure it's no big deal.
Try not to worry.
There's still some time
before the concert.
Yeah, you're right.
It's just, you see...
[REO]
Mh-hm. Mh-hm.
I didn't buy black beans!
You know, for health
in the new year!
[REO]
Mh-hm! Hm.
I totally forgot.
I can't ring in the new year
properly without them.
[REO chuckles awkwardly]
I'm sure you'll have time to buy
some after the concert. 'Kay?
You're right.
Actually, the stores might have
marked them down at that point.
I can't believe the year's over.
This one sure flew by
quickly, didn't it?
Probably because
so much happened.
Like the Girls' Festa
and the sports festival.
And the popularity ranking.
At least Reo didn't break
her legs again this year.
Come on--am I ever gonna
live that one down?
I'm not happy with the way this
stupid year turned out at all.
I'm so gonna be in the
Girls' Festa next year.
And I'm winning the
sports festival, too.
Then the top ranking's
mine--just you wait.
Now that's confidence.
Okay, Aya, we'll believe
it when we see it.
That was the most
Aya thing ever.
All right, let's all channel
that confident Aya energy
and have a great concert!
Ring in the new year right!
And next year,
the Budokan is ours.
You think so?
[YUKA]
Hmm.
[AYA]
Hm?
You guys are always obsessing
about playing the Budokan. Lame.
[OTHERS]
Uhh...
Huh? Here, there's plenty!
[MOTOI] This is the very
first time I'm getting
to ring in the New Year
with my fave.
I'm beside myself! There's like
this... mysterious energy!
[MOTOI yells]
Kumasa! Eripiyo just up
and died in this mofo!
Be a shame if the concert
got cancelled because of her.
I hope she has an extra
life or something.
[ERIPIYO groans]
Closing for repairs?
Oh, yeah.
Apparently, the lightning
that struck on Christmas
caused some major damage.
Wait, so, if they're not
performing here,
where are the Cham
Jam shows gonna be?
[ERIPIYO] The situation is
even more dire than that.
Since they don't have a venue,
where is Maina's birthday
celebration in January gonna be?
Why does she have the
worst luck of all of them?
But even her bad luck is cute!
Is that really a legitimate
reason to get so excited?
To be fair, Eripiyo is a
very odd breed of super fan,
who's like, "Oh wow
the sun? How cool!"
when she's looking through
Maina's pictures.
Maina's the cutest!
Maybe the universe took note
of her extreme cuteness
and gave her such
bad luck as a way
to even out the playing
field, you know?
[NAGAI] Y'know, it sucks that
Yumeri's birthday celebration's
gonna be a day late,
but it's lucky that
they'll be finished
with the repairs by then.
Yeah, the universe really
seems to be blessing her
with good luck for
the end of the year.
[ERIPIYO]
This planet sucks!
Maina's lot is so unfair!
This place should be destroyed!
I have no response to that.
Well, regardless,
I'm not so sure
Eripiyo could've organized
a birthday celebration.
Shut up!
[ERIPIYO] Maina's birthday
should be a national holiday!
Therefore, I say we make it so!
Are you really gonna
bypass Okayama City
and take this straight to
the federal government?
[YUKA] So none of you nerds
have anything better to do
on New Year's Eve?
[FANS]
No!
[REO] Yuka, seriously,
what's wrong with you?
[MAKI] Everyone here
leads a full, busy life.
They just make time to come
see us 'cause they love us.
So let's all have fun
and ring in the New Year
like nobody's business!
[FANS]
Yeah!
[giggles]
Thanks for all your support!
Have a happy New Year!
Don't choke on your
black beans and die.
It was awesome spending
New Year's with you!
Thank you for everything!
You're all the best!
If you support me, I'll
never forget your face.
Even more so if you don't!
Uh. Thank you so
much for coming!
[GIRLS] We hope you'll keep
supporting us next year!
[FANS cheering]
And thank you from us, too!
We love you all!
That was great.
A perfect end to the year.
[ERIPIYO]
It's over...
And the level of despair
I'm feeling right now
is enough to engulf
the entire world
in a thick blanket of
never-ending darkness.
[ERIPIYO cackles]
Could you not spoil
everyone's good time?
No one came here to be part of
your villainous origin story.
It's our last concert
of the year,
so we have a special merch
booth as a treat for our fans!
We're so grateful to you all!
[FAN A]
Special merch booth?
[REO] This is the first
time we're trying it,
so we're a little nervous.
[FAN D] Nice. I wonder what
I should have her say.
Oh, wow. I'm so overwhelmed!
I can record her saying
anything I want
as long as it's not
inappropriate or creepy?
[KUMASA]
This must be divinely ordained.
Only godly intervention
could bring us such fortune!
And now Eripiyo can come back
from the edge of the abyss
of villainy and darkness!
Eripiyo, I love you more
than anything in the world.
Our civilization was
built upon hypocrisy,
but Eripiyo's mere existence
is the balm my soul needs
to persist in the
face of it all.
Her love shows me
the way and lights the path
I must walk in order to become
the number one idol of all time.
I get lonely sometimes,
like anyone else,
but when that happens,
I just imagine Eripiyo's smile.
Yes! That should be
doable in five seconds!
I don't know what five seconds
looks like in your dimension,
but the one we're in,
it's way shorter than that.
Just wait!
Time's relative when it
comes to words, you'll see.
You are totally insane,
you know that?
Not to mention the fact
that nothing in that speech
sounds like something
Maina would ever say.
Attention, please: The special
merch booth begins now!
Okay, Kumasa, so what
would you like me to say?
Hold on.
How 'bout, "Morning, Kumasa.
Wakey, wakey, eggs and bakey"?
Okay!
Morning, Kuma. Wakey,
wakey, eggs and bakey!
I hope you set
that as your alarm
so you can hear me every day!
[KUMASA]
I will, thanks! You rock.
So, what would you
like for your message?
Oh. Uh. I'm not really sure.
[MOTOI]
"Motoi, kiss me now!"
"Motoi. We're having
instant curry tonight!"
"Darling, I love you!"
Gah! How could I ever
choose just one?
You wouldn't change
your favorite?
Wait! Did you record that?
I would never ever cheat on you!
Oh, I know.
[gasps]
[inaudible]
Huh?
So, um, Eripiyo.
[ERIPIYO]
Wait!
Could you say "Eri"?
Please, can you address
me as a person,
not just as a random wota!
[MAINA]
What?
Not just as a wota,
but as the woman that I love?
[NARRATOR A]
No one asked her to go that far.
And please say,
"Eri, support me!"
I'll play it to remind
myself why I have to work.
[MAINA]
Eri, support me!
So good.
The way Maina's voice vibrates
against my eardrum
gives me chills.
It almost feels like
Maina's inside my body.
[ERIPIYO laughing]
Um.
[MAINA] Eripiyo's talking about
internal organs again.
[ERIPIYO]
Uh! Was I too creepy just now?
So, um, I, uh...
[MAINA] I need to think
of something to say
whenever she brings
up her organs.
Ah! Sorry if I creeped you out!
[MAINA]
Huh?
Happy New Year!
Cool, well, I hope you two
have an awesome New Year!
Reo's gonna be on one of
those count down shows,
so I'm going to the
studio to watch it.
Catch ya on the flipside!
Lucky duck. I wish I could ring
in the new year with Maina.
If I don't hurry home,
I'm gonna end up counting down
to sunrise with you, Motoi.
And no thanks!
Why you gotta be like that?
Okay, see you in a month or so.
Sure thing. Guess I'll
see you in about a month!
[ERIPIYO] A month usually
goes by super-fast,
but without her, it'll crawl.
[yells]
I won't see her for a month,
and I made our last
conversation so awkward!
[ERIPIYO wailing]
[ERIPIYO]
Hey, I'm home.
[SAKIKO]
Welcome back.
Now can you lend me a hand
with the New Year's food?
Sure.
Oh, for the love of--
I'm a pro at flipping buns,
and I'm also a pro
at supporting people.
Well then, just stand
there and support me.
There's just one thing
I've gotta say.
Sakiko's the cutest,
in a major way! Uh.
Eri. How come you're
always so loud?
Eri, what are you
doing these days?
Do you have a job?
Uh, I'm currently the best
bun flipper at the factory.
I meant a career,
not a part-time job.
Dang, Eri, still don't know what
you wanna be when you grow up?
Uh. Come on, I think I still
have some time before I decide.
With that kind of mentality,
you'll wake up one day and
find you're an old maid.
There's someone I would love
to introduce you to, Eri.
He's a wonderful man.
So wonderful, in fact,
that he's already had five wives
and he's not even 40 yet!
[ERIPIYO]
I don't know.
If you don't have a career
now, when will you?
Nothing is more important than
finding your purpose in life.
Listen, kid.
Make sure your employers
know how grateful you are
that they throw
you a bone, 'kay?
It'd be a shame to
waste your youth
waiting around for
the perfect man, Eri.
Eri, come play games with me.
Support me! I can't hear you!
[ERIPIYO screams]
This is exactly why I
hate spending holidays
with my family.
[HOST B] Well, folks, only 30
minutes left till the new year!
Thank you for being with us!
Tonight, we're looking
back on the year
with some local celebrities!
Let's meet our New
Year's guests! Tom?
[HOST B]
Okayama's favorite comedians.
Chieko Bloomers
with special guest, V!
Hello!
[HOST A]
Mr. Otomo from Ibara,
shigin poet and winner of
the Demi Katsudon award!
Glad to be here!
[HOST B] Last but not least,
pop idol from Okayama,
Reo Igarashi!
Hi, everybody!
This is my first time appearing
on a show like this on my own,
so I admit I'm a bit nervous.
Well, it looks like
a lot of your fans
came out to support you,
so that should calm your nerves.
Thanks, everyone!
So you usually perform as part
of a group, is that right?
Yes, sir, we're called
Cham Jam and...
...the rest of them
are under 20,
so I'm a little sad
that they couldn't
come on the show
with me tonight.
We're super close.
So cool!
But I'm pretty sure all of them
are watching this from home!
[FANS]
We sure are!
[ERIPIYO coughing]
It's not fair!
Must be nice to ring in the
new year with your fave.
Man! How can I sit here and
eat soba at a time like this?
"Hey, Motoi. Let's visit a
shrine for luck right now!"
Send!
Uh. Hey!
Hi, there, Eripiyo.
Happy New Year to you.
Happy New Year!
I'm so glad you're the
first person I'm seeing
other than family
this year, Rena!
Am I chopped liver?
Rude, considering you
called me out here
in the middle of the night.
[MOTOI]
I'm a mess.
I'm all in my head.
Sorane spending New Year's
with a boyfriend kills me.
I couldn't sleep at all.
Yeah, but you already know
those rumors aren't true.
[MOTOI]
I mean, I hear you, but...
At the same time, we only
know the version of them
we see at concerts.
That's not at all
who they really are.
[ERIPIYO]
Yeah, you're right.
And we spent so much of the year
thinking about that
version of them,
it feels strange sometimes.
I wonder who Maina thinks about.
Like, does she obsess about
someone in the same way?
[YUKA]
Hey, Maina!
[gasps]
[MAINA]
Hi, Yuka. Happy New Year!
Same!
Wait! Are you
wearing a disguise?
You're such an idol!
No! I'm trying to stay well!
Anyway, there's only one person
who would recognize me,
as pathetic as that sounds.
Aww.
Well, let's go!
[MAINA]
Sure.
I'm kinda bummed we won't have
another concert for a month.
Me, too. But we can
do temp work.
[MAINA]
Temp work, huh?
[ERIPIYO]
They won't stop bugging me
about a career and marriage.
You're lucky to be young.
I bet no one bugs you since
you're still in high school.
Yeah, but I do have
entrance exams.
So I can't go to
concerts for a while.
Aww.
And I'm sure Maina's
gonna miss seeing you
at the meet n' greets, too.
But they're not having any
concerts until February, so...
[ERIPIYO]
Yeah, that's true. But...
[groans]
[RENA]
Something wrong, Eripiyo?
My time with Maina
yesterday was so awkward!
Ugh! I don't wanna have to live
with this awful feeling
for a whole month!
I can't wait for
the next concert!
But I feel so awkward.
What in the world did you
do to warrant all this?
I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
I bet Maina's not
upset about it at all.
Rena! You're the nicest
little sister around!
Let me buy you an Ema plaque!
She's my little
sister, you know!
No, I mean, we're just fans,
they don't think about us.
--[MOTOI] Huh?
--[ERIPIYO] What?
They're idols.
In the grand scheme of things,
I don't think we have much
of an impact on them.
Address me as a person,
not just as a random wota.
[ERIPIYO yells]
I really messed up, didn't I?!
[ERIPIYO wails]
[YUKA sighs]
[YUKA]
We're finally here!
Welp, guess I'll pray now.
One whole gacha pull! Here!
[MAINA] I pray that Cham Jam
will go to the Budokan.
Also...
[MAINA] ...I pray that Eripiyo
doesn't get hurt anymore.
[ERIPIYO] Please let Maina
have another healthy year.
Please let Maina always have
delicious, nutritious
food to eat.
Please let Maina
be happy all year.
go to the Budokan.
[RENA]
Hey, Motoi.
Did you ask that I get
into a good college?
I bet you only prayed for things
that you want for
yourself this year.
I just ended up praying for
my own good health. Sorry.
It's cool.
Well, I guess I only said
prayers for things I want, too.
[ERIPIYO gasps]
I totally forgot to make any
wishes or prayers for myself!
Really? Then who were you
saying prayers for? Uh.
[BOTH]
I see.
What's that mean?
Hey, why do you too
suddenly seem so distant?
Come on!
I don't care what
Motoi thinks of me,
but, Rena, don't shut me out!
Why the heck have you been
so hostile towards me lately?
[ERIPIYO]
Rena!
[YUKA]
This amazake's so good!
It sure is.
So what did you pray for?
Did you wish that we
would go to the Budokan?
[MAINA]
Mh-hm.
Wait, Yuka, did you wish
for the same thing?
Yup!
But I thought that you
had said you didn't care
if Cham Jam went to the Budokan.
[YUKA]
I did.
Ya know, I think being
an idol is so much fun.
That's the reason I do this.
I get such a big kick
out of total strangers
telling me that they love me!
So as far as I'm concerned,
it doesn't really matter
what stage I'm on.
I don't care where I perform.
[MAINA]
Oh.
But then, at
yesterday's concert...
Thanks for coming!
You want a recording?
What should I say?
Um... "We're going
to the Budokan"?
If you don't mind.
Huh? Is that really
all you want?
That's all I want, thanks.
[FUMI]
Say, "Hey Fumi.
I can't wait to see you in
the crowd at the Budokan."
Wait, you want me
to say that, too?
Why is that?
You don't seem to be that
interested in performing there,
but for fans, it would
mean the world to us
to see our favorite
idols making it there.
[YUKA] If everyone who
loves me is saying
that they want to see us up
there, I guess I wouldn't mind
performing at the
Budokan for them.
You know, I feel
bad saying this,
but I thought you'd pray
for something different.
Something like,
"Please let me eat lots of
non-conveyor belt sushi."
I guess.
That's so mean! You think
I'm that self-centered?
But while we're on the subject,
I'd love to be the
center at the Budokan!
You know, you have to have
an odd numbered group
to have a center.
I know.
So seven's the perfect number.
[MAINA]
Mh-hm.
[YUKA chuckles]
Huh?
[MAINA]
[YUKA]
Hey! Maki! Yume!
Oh. Hey, Yuka.
Jeez, keep it down!
[YUKA]
Don't worry.
We're not so famous that
we'd cause a big ruckus.
[MAKI] That's not why you
should be quiet here.
[MAINA]
Happy New Year.
[YUMERI]
Yeah. Happy New Year.
Spending New Year's together--
you girls are so close.
Uh. Well, we... We were
scared we'd get separated.
I wasn't talking about
that, but okay. See?
Oh, sure. Right, yeah.
[BOTH chuckle]
Made it!
And we stayed together,
thanks to this!
Yeah, it's a good thing you
thought to bring it with you.
I wonder how long until sunrise.
Fear not, friend!
Morning comes no matter what.
And Cham Jam's gonna shine
brighter than the sun!
There you go with
random proclamations.
Speaking of the new year,
did you watch Reo on
the countdown show?
Yep, I did, actually.
Although...
[ALL]
Five, four, three, two, one...
Happy New Year!
[MOTOI] I was so distracted
by Kumasa's weirdness
that I ended up
missing the countdown.
[ERIPIYO]
He was super creepy, right?
If I look anything like him,
I've gotta change my ways.
But still.
He also looked happy, didn't he?
[MOTOI] Yeah. I thought
it was pretty awesome.
[MAKI] Oh, hey, did you
guys watch Reo on TV?
[MAINA]
Yeah.
[YUKA]
Me, too!
[YUKA] Reo was looking
right at all her fans
when the new year began.
It looked amazing.
She spent New Year's with
people who love her.
[MAINA]
Yeah.
I'd like to do that
someday, too.
Oh, I see how it is.
I guess I don't fall into
that category, then?
That's not what I meant!
[YUMERI, MAKI chuckle]
[gasps]
[ERIPIYO] In Maina's eyes,
I may just be another fan.
But she's the one who showed me
just how happy I could be
giving everything I have
to just one person.
If Maina made it to the Budokan,
then I could die happy!
I could die period!
In fact, if Maina made it to
the Budokan, I would just die!
Jeez, we get it!
Maina! I swear I'll love
you even more this year!
[gasps]
Why are you so fidgety Maina?
[MAINA] I thought I heard
Eripiyo's voice just now, but...
No, it couldn't be.
[MAKI]
Well, we saw the first sunrise.
Let's go home.
What? Leave already?
[MAINA] I'm getting
pretty tired, too, Yuka.
You're no fun!
Aya's got her part-time
job in the morning,
Reo is at home, sleeping,
and Sorane's at some
relative's house.
The Cham Jam crew's
not gonna be able
to get together again
until February!
I'm sure we'll be doing
some outdoor event this month.
I mean, you know how management
is, everything's last-minute.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[MAINA] That means I'll be able
to see Eripiyo soon, too!
[YUKA]
And our outdoor performance
will be at the Budokan!
[MAKI, YUMERI]
Yeah, I seriously doubt that.
[ALL laughing]
[KUMASA] You were amazing on
the countdown show, Reo!
I totally clocked how
you looked at me first
as soon as the new year started.
But I didn't get invited
to the first shrine visit.
I wonder why.
Uh, Reo, are you going
to cheer me up?
Thanks so much! Wow,
I'm feeling better already!
[YOSHIKAWA] Thank you
very much! Your time's up!
[KUMASA]
Kuma, kuma, kuma!