[inaudible]
[KUMASA]
Reo.
[KUMASA] Next time, I-I'm
gonna do everything I can
to get you to number one, so...
[inaudible]
[gasps]
Cham's schedule of events
has officially been updated!
Hey, there's a sports festival!
Heck yeah! I go crazy
for that type of stuff.
[KUMASA chuckles]
Scroll down for
the important part.
There's more?
Oh, it's Reo's
birthday. Awesome.
Can't you feign interest
just this once?
That's important to me,
but look below it.
Ugh, fine.
[gasps]
No way!
I've been waiting for this day
for what seems like an eternity,
and now it's finally here.
Oh, cool. What happens
when Maina loses?
Why're you giving up
before it's even started?
[ERIPIYO groans]
So what's the breakdown with
the handshake lines these days?
Reo has a clear lead, as usual.
Of course.
Well, Sorane's in second,
and Maki's in third,
right behind her.
Yuka's neck and neck in fourth.
And as for fifth...
Probs Yumeri, and then
Aya, then Maina, last.
So the voting goes till
the end of November, huh?
Even people who don't
usually buy duplicates
will go all out for this one.
Then this means war.
The 30,000 other Maina fans
will need to step up their game.
Whoa. You think she
has that many fans?
Did you hit your head when
I wasn't lookin' or something?
Maybe they're hermits
and never go outside!
No. I've got your number.
I know all about it.
You frequent Maina's blog,
but you post under different
aliases, so people will think--
Don't you ever speak
of this again.
If you do, you'll pay.
I hate this!
C'mon, you have nothing
to worry about.
I mean, it's not like
they're gonna kick us out
if we don't get first place.
But still.
If you work really hard,
you might even get
to be in the center!
I'm gonna work so
hard I might die!
I'm actually content
right where I am.
Being in the top three
is way too much work.
Yeah, well, you have
room to say that
because you're one of
the more popular members!
[YUMERI]
I don't want this.
If Yuka works hard and advances,
there's a chance Maki could get
knocked out of the top three!
Or even worse than that...
What if my own fans
were to band together
and pull off some sort
of miracle for me?
That would mean--!
[gasps]
Let's both be in it next year.
[YUMERI]
I made a promise to Maki.
What would I do?
[MAKI]
You're gonna be fine, Yume.
I'm sure of it. Your fans can
all see how hard you work.
Thanks, Maki.
[YUMERI]
That's not what I'm scared of.
[sighs]
[REO] I hate it when they make
us compete with each other.
I don't think our rank
should even matter.
Uh, yeah.
Don't worry.
[gasps]
You have lots of fans.
[inaudbile]
'Kay?
[door opens]
What's with you guys?
You look like someone
broke the sheath
on the Momotaro statue again.
We've got bigger fish to fry
than some dumb ranking.
[ALL]
Ugh, that's right.
Huh.
I guess we're renting out
a grade school gym
for the festival this year?
Yeah, we owe that to
a certain someone.
She misjudged the space last
year and broke both legs.
[REO chuckles nervously]
[MAINA sighs]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[SORANE]
Something wrong, Maina?
I wish I was like Sorane.
I'm so bad at sports. For real.
Sorane was in the tennis club
in high school, right?
Tennis? Wow.
[GIRLS] We don't stand a
chance against you, ace.
Yeah, I was in tennis
club--stop being weird.
[MAINA chuckles]
[REO] It's Cham Jam's...
Big Autumn Sports Festival!
[OTAKU cheering]
[REO] Sorane, Aya, and Yumeri
are on the red team.
Maki, Yuka, and Maina
make up the white team.
And as for me, Reo,
I'm your ref!
I hope to hear you cheering
all the girls on!
You're the best, ref!
Don't let the ref
break her legs!
[REO chuckles]
Ah, my legs will be fine!
She's not competing?
Can you blame her?
Poor girl broke both
of her legs last year!
That was traumatic.
Wait. They made a print
of her on crutches?
They did. And it was
a secret draw, too.
I'm sure Motoi's
at home, fuming.
What a crappy time to
come down with a cold!
A fan must take care of himself
or face the consequences.
[sneezes]
[OTAKU chattering]
[REO] Our first event
is the team relay!
And they're off!
Wait. Has Aya always
been this fast?
Wow, Aya, I can't believe you're
so fleet of foot! Amazing!
You're so cute and
sporty! I love you!
I have to vote for you now!
I'm changing my fave!
[AYA]
First! First! First!
[AYA screams]
[ALL]
Aya!
[YUKA gasps]
Come on, you can do
this, Aya! Get up!
[AYA groans]
[AYA]
Is she campaigning?
She helped Aya up, even though
she's on the other team!
Yuka's the sweetest!
Welp, gotta vote for her!
Changing faves again!
Uh! I know exactly what you're
up to, and I won't fall for it!
What?
[AYA groans]
[NAGAI] But Yumeri's such a
good dancer. I don't get it.
[ASAMI]
Dancing isn't running, buddy.
What do they think this
is, a Sunday stroll?
Go, Maina! You've got this!
Eripiyo's here!
Can't let her down!
Yumeri!
[YUMERI] I have to keep going.
I've got to impress my fans!
[YUMERI]
Sorane's really fast.
She's our anchor!
If I can just get
the baton to her,
Maki has no chance of winning!
Uh?
Here, Maki!
You killed it out there, Maina.
[REO]
Wow, just look at Sorane go!
Maki never stood a chance!
Finish! The red team
wins the relay!
[MURAKAMI, ASAMI]
Sorane!
You ran like the wind
out there Maina!
I'm so proud of you!
Yume. We both have
to do our best.
Huh? You mean at the festival?
Yeah, that, too.
But I meant the ranking.
I... hate competing.
Okay. I have an idea.
What if the loser has to do
what the winner says?
How 'bout it? We got a deal?
So then, motivated?
[REO] Come on, Aya,
you have to get up!
[AYA]
Can't. I'm giving up instead.
This is only the first event.
Last minute substitution!
I'm going to tag into
the red team, 'kay?
[OTAKU gasping]
Don't break your legs again!
[REO]
I won't!
But if they do get
broken... sorry!
Reo!
[MASUDA]
Break a leg!
[KOSUGA] Break three--
yours and one of Sorane's!
Ugh. Things took a real
weird turn all of a sudden.
--[REO] There!
--[SORANE] Take that!
Revenge!
Ah! My head!
[BOTH yelling]
[ALL laughing]
[gunshot]
[moans]
Wait, this says...
A, um, kokeshi ?
Maina, look! I've got one!
[gunshot]
[GIRLS]
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Hey, wouldn't the team with
the highest overall weight
have a clear advantage?
[YUKA screams]
[gunshot]
That's right, boys!
I'm back! Yeah!
[AYA yells]
[REO]
And now, the results!
The white team got 45 points!
Red team comin' in at 68!
Red team is the winner!
[REO] And even better,
no broken legs!
Yeah! Reo!
[KUMASA] I'm so glad I got
an event photo op with you!
Thank you!
But I'm even happier that you
didn't get hurt this year.
[REO chuckles]
Listen, Kumasa?
Remember when you told me
you would do anything
to make me number
one the next time?
And then the group
ended up disbanding...
...and there never
was a next time?
Well...
[KUMASA] Next time, I-I'm
gonna do everything I can
to get you to number one, so...
You can believe in me.
Can I... that is, can I
keep believing in you now?
Of course!
And this time, I know
I'll keep my promise.
[ERIPIYO]
You were fantastic today, Maina!
And you look so cute
in your gym outfit!
We sorta match--
what a coincidence!
I-I'm kind of embarrassed.
Maina, for the ranking...
Huh?
Nothing would make me happier
than you taking
home first place.
So I'll vote as much as I can!
[gasps]
You have lots of fans.
Believe in them.
[ERIPIYO]
Careful...
[MAINA]
Eripiyo?
[ERIPIYO]
Uh.
Thank you... for
everything you do.
Sure!
[MAINA]
I can believe in Eripiyo.
She always works so
hard on my behalf.
And I need to do everything I
possibly can to get first place.
[ERIPIYO] They're all so good
at updating their blogs.
And Maina's posting her usual.
[gasps]
[MAINA] Popularity
rankings can be rough,
but I'm going to do my best!
I'll work hard!
Maina. I'm so proud of
you for being vulnerable.
I'm gonna leave 80 comments
on this post right now.
From different accounts.
[ERIPIYO]
Her birthday? Not fair!
How's it not fair?
The place'll be swarming
with Reo stans!
Ah! Can we just move Maina's
birthday to next week instead?
More importantly, there's
no accounting for taste--
your crappy taste, that is.
I've never met a fangirl
so sorely lacking
in artistic talent.
Yeah. I've never been
crafty in a good way.
This is the first year
that Cham's allowed us
to celebrate their
birthdays with them.
I try to help you out
and you just complain.
What are you going to do
for the birthday event?
[KUMASA] I'm in charge of
the cake and flower stand.
Oh. I'm gettin'
the glowsticks, too.
Something just occurred to me.
Isn't this going to get
harder every year?
Indeed.
No one can know what
the future holds,
or when the last birthday is.
Put that death flag down, dude!
You wanted message cards?
Well, I got 'em.
Sorry to put you to work
as soon as you got better.
It's cool.
But why did you ask me instead
of the other Reo stans?
Well, uh...
They put me in charge of the
birthday committee this year,
but to be frank, that's
about the only thing
those guys want
from me these days.
Ever since the Halloween concert
last year, they've been weird.
Oh, that's right.
Hey, you two just reminded me.
It's coming up, what're
you gonna cosplay?
No cosplay!
I swore never again!
I refuse to be a pariah!
Look, Motoi. You're not going
to abandon us, are you?
[MOTOI]
Huh? No, man.
Now the he's mentioned it,
the more I hang with these two,
the more I start to stick out.
I just may have to
abandon them soon.
Anyway, what're you paying me?
I'm not paying you!
It never hurts to ask.
[ERIPIYO] But the truth is,
I really am broke.
It's an otaku's lot
to be strapped.
That's right.
We're all flat broke.
[COWORKER B]
She's so fast! Like lightning!
But the belt isn't
moving any faster!
[COWORKER A] Can you even
see what you're doing, Eri?
Good work, everyone!
That's basically the gist
of things. Can you handle it?
You know it, boss!
Also, you should see how fast
I can flip some buns!
Uh, good for you,
but no flipping buns here.
Good work, everyone!
That's weird. That girl kinda
looks like she's flipping buns.
[ERIPIYO]
Good work, everyone...
[chuckling]
[screaming]
[KUMASA]
Good God, Eripiyo!
Huh? Oh, sorry.
Are you okay? You're
not looking too good.
It's just that...
I'm poor and destitute.
I can't be eating here.
I'd rather save my money
so I can buy Maina's CDs.
Uh, hey. Don't worry about
the bill, it's on me today.
Maybe you need
some time off work.
[ERIPIYO]
It's all good!
I'll be fine, as long as Maina
doesn't come in last place.
Here. This week's pay.
Thank you very much, sir!
[ERIPIYO]
That'll buy 30 CDs!
Okay, thanks for the help!
[ERIPIYO]
That'll buy 26 CDs!
Here. Great job, kid.
[ERIPIYO]
That'll buy 24 CDs!
Okay. Tomorrow's Reo's
birthday celebration.
One last chance to give
my all voting for Maina.
Huh?
[thud]
[FUJITA]
Man, thanks, Kumasa.
Best birthday
committee lead ever.
[MURAKAMI] Reo's gonna
have a great birthday.
'Preciate it, guys.
[door opens]
Oh, hey... Eripiyo.
'Sup?
Are you injured again?
What happened this time?
Well, you see...
Huh?
[WARTHOG]
Oink!
A freak wildlife attack.
Apparently, they've become an
issue here in Okayama city.
You can't be here!
You need to get your butt
back home and rest!
[ERIPIYO sighs]
Being a part-timer's
not cutting it.
I'd probably make a
whole lot more money
working in an office.
That wouldn't work.
They rarely ever get days off.
That's the main reason
I quit my office job.
You really are trash, Kumasa.
You've inspired me
to quit my job search!
[MOTOI]
You're both weeb trash.
[KUMASA]
Upsy-daisy.
All right. I'm gonna go hand
out the glow-sticks now.
Yeah! Let's do this!
[ERIPIYO]
Kumasa.
[KUMASA]
Hm?
I got you right up front.
My line number was pretty low,
so I saved you a spot. C'mon.
You did? But I--
Kumasa! Get over
here, ya big dork!
[OTAKU E]
Yeah, dude!
[OTAKU A]
You comin' or what?
[OTAKU B]
Hurry up, man!
Thank you, guys. For real.
[GIRLS]
One, two, three, go!
Yeah!
[GIRLS]
Wuh-oh!
All right!
♪ Sometimes, I feel so lonely
and I need you here. ♪
♪ Although I am the oldest
out of all of us! ♪
[KUMASA]
Pretty in pink, leader Reo!
[gasps]
"Reo Igarashi.
Well, Happy Birthday.
Thank you for your leadership--
for supporting us in
all that you do.
Looking back, you and I"--
To all the other girls, and
of course, to our lovely fans,
thank you so much
for this special day!
[ERIPIYO]
Yep, a total success!
And Maina was cuter
than ever today!
I mean, it'll take me
weeks to recover.
But still, that's not
important right now!
Take my money!
Eighty of Maina's CDs!
[AYA]
You're kidding! Last place?
But how could this even happen?
Hey, it's okay. I ended up
in sixth place, so--
Yeah, but you still
came out ahead of me!
Dang, Maina, you're
third in the ranking!
I'm proud of you, Maina!
[giggles]
Wait, should I be worried?
[REO giggles]
Hey, Maina, aren't you glad
that you believed in your fans?
[MAINA]
Thank you, Eripiyo.
[KUMASA]
Holy crap, Maina killed it!
Yeah, I guess all
30,000 of her fans
across Japan came through!
But I'm gonna be out
of work for a while.
Can't be helped.
Doctor's orders and all.
I'm worried about what's gonna
happen without my votes.
[ERIPIYO]
I'm so nervous I might puke.
Not on me, please.
By the way...
Um, is it just me,
or do we stand out again?
[WOTA A] Two top fans
are both in costumes!
[WOTA B] Were we supposed
to be wearing them, too?
[MOTOI]
Crap.
Now I can't even pretend not
to be with these weirdos.
[FUJIKAWA]
Breaking news, Aya!
[KOSUGA]
I figured this day would come,
but I can't believe
it's finally here!
[FUJIKAWA, KOSUGA]
Cham Jam's popularity ranking!
[KOSUGA] Apparently, Eripiyo
changed her fave! Right, Aya?
--[FUJIKAWA] But...
--[KOSUGA] Still...
[KOSUGA, FUJIKAWA]
You're the only one for us, Aya!
[YOSHIKAWA]
Thank you! Wrap it up!