[MOTOI] Listen, guys. Sorane's
reputation's in jeopardy!
[KUMASA]
Jeez, again?
[ERIPIYO]
What's up?
Did a suspicious,
lurking shadow show up
in one of the pics on her blog?
[MOTOI]
No, not that.
Wait, what are you talking
about? I'm scared!
Ever since the whole
thing with Sorane,
I've just been totally paranoid.
Then on Maina's blog,
there's this!
"At the grocery store today,
fermented bean curd
was super cheap!"
Notice anything suspicious
in the background?
Are those a dude's clothes?
You see that?
Then there's the fact that
she's using a blue plate. Ah!
She's cooking at some
guy's house--I know it!
I've sunk to looking in
the mirrors to try and see
who took the pictures of her!
Even in her selfies,
I look for people's shadows!
And I'm terribly ashamed
to admit this, but...
...I zoom in on her eyes to see
if there's anyone
in the reflections!
[ERIPIYO]
I'm so neurotic. Ugh! It hurts!
I almost wish she'd stop
posting pictures altogether!
Not gonna lie,
I feel a lot better
about my own situation now.
[KUMASA] Anyway, what's
going on with Sorane?
Oh. I never said, did I?
So do you remember the
clothes I bought her?
Well, apparently, there's
a matching guy version.
People are assuming she and her
boyfriend bought them together.
[KUMASA]
Ohh.
I see.
[MOTOI] Man, you couldn't care
less about other people's faves!
Look, why don't you just buy
the matching outfit then?
Since you're the one who got it.
Oh! Yeah, great idea!
There's still time
before the show starts.
Right. Thanks for the tip!
[MOTOI] Looks like everyone
had the same idea.
[SORANE]
That's it--I'm done.
From now on, I'm posting
nothing but nudes.
[MAKI] Somehow, I don't think
that would solve anything.
But for real, why did you
search for yourself again?
[SORANE]
I didn't.
I was looking up how to
take care of pet moles.
[gasps]
Hey, Reo, check it out!
There's a new, free,
ten-pull-a-day gacha game
coming out today!
Morning, guys.
Good morning.
[REO]
Hi, Aya.
Good morning.
Uh.
Aya.
[AYA]
Ugh.
What?
If you don't like me, fine,
that's your prerogative.
But people are
always watching us.
So no matter how you feel,
you have to at least
act like we get along.
People are watching us?
A lot of fans on social
media seem to think
you said something bad about me.
[gasps]
Why is Sorane ranking
higher than me
when there's that rumor
about her and some guy?
It's so not fair.
[grunts]
[SORANE] I think I have
a pretty good idea
of why you don't like me.
And there's nothing I can do
to make you change your mind.
But let's try to do our best
at the show today, m'kay?
Huh?
[FANS cheering]
So winter's here!
When the weather
starts to get cold,
I want stew--something
to warm my bones!
[MATSUO]
Really?
Sorane! As usual, your emcee
style is pretty weird.
Hah. Well.
Aya and I made plans
to grab dinner together
and get some sundubu!
Huh?
[SORANE]
Right?
[gasps]
Yeah, and I'm super excited!
We're going tomorrow
after our voice lessons!
Aya, you promised me we would
have dinner together tomorrow!
Why don't you three
have dinner together?
That would be fun.
Good idea. Crab for me!
[MAKI]
Hey, I wanna come, too!
[YUMERI]
Yeah! So do I!
[REO] We should all go
together! You, too, Maina!
[MAINA]
Oh! Sure!
Oh, and I just remembered!
Aya gave me the cutest pair
of fuzzy socks the other day!
I'll upload them to my
blog sometime soon.
[AYA]
Sorane's such a good idol.
[MOTOI] It really is beginning
to look a lot like Christmas.
Speaking of which,
do you two have any special
Christmas plans lined up?
[ERIPIYO, KUMASA]
Huh?
What do you mean special
Christmas plans?
Why would you ask
an otaku that?
Oh, go easy on the guy.
I'm sure Motoi meant no harm.
I took off work for both
Christmas Eve and Christmas day,
just like I do every year.
That way I'm free to
make last-minute plans.
[MOTOI]
You're taking time off
even though you don't
have set plans yet?
As for me, I'm already
planning to spend Christmas
with the person I love most,
so I'm going to be busy,
without a doubt.
Hope you losers find
something to do!
Later, nerds!
[ERIPIYO laughing]
Eripiyo! Judas! Betrayer!
We always spend
Christmas together!
Oh. I understand
what's happening now.
You're going to the
Christmas concert.
Yep, that is correct!
[KUMASA] It isn't nice of you to
scare us like that, you know.
Why would I ever make
plans to do anything
but go to the Christmas concert?
That's what I'll be
doing next year
and the one after
that, for sure!
You don't think you'll
have anything going on
in the next few years?
[ERIPIYO] I can't imagine my
future without Maina in it!
[MOTOI gasps]
I wonder if all
the Cham Jam girls
are gonna wear Santa outfits!
Of course they are! And
there'll be photo ops, too!
[MOTOI]
They're gonna be insanely cute!
[KUMASA] Yeah. Reo was
adorable last year!
Must be nice to be you guys.
Maina didn't wear a
santa outfit last year.
[MOTOI]
Wait, just Maina?
She was only wearing
a santa hat.
And the photo op
was sorta awkward.
I'm sure she just felt
embarrassed to.
She has a hard time
with that stuff.
Actually, do you
want my opinion?
[BOTH]
We do!
It's nothing!
It's nothing at all!
See you guys next week!
Eripiyo, wait!
You were in the middle
of saying something!
[ERIPIYO] I know why she didn't
wear a Santa outfit last year.
She didn't have enough money!
So if I do my best and support
her even more this year,
she'll have all the
money that she needs!
And she'll be able to afford
a super cute Christmas costume!
I mean, I don't know what
will actually happen,
but if the other stans
get word of this,
then they'll work hard, too,
and all the girls will end
up in incredible outfits!
Even though I would
be supporting her,
Maina wouldn't
stand out as much!
And so, it's a secret!
[FANS cheering]
So our Christmas concert
has finally been announced!
[MAKI]
Yeah!
[REO] You're all coming
to see us, right?
[FANS]
It's gonna be a sold-out house!
[REO]
Hello, there!
[FANS chattering]
[YUKA]
So you're a new fan right?
[FAN C]
Yeah.
[YUKA]
So here's the thing...
I'm stupid!
[FAN C]
Huh?
[YUKA] I'm terrible with
remembering people's faces.
But you know what?
If you keep coming to see me,
I'll remember you!
[FAN C]
Okay. I will!
[AYA]
Boy, oh, boy.
Maina, could you pull that off?
Uh! No way!
[AYA]
Didn't think so.
Maina. Yumeri. Time
to start. You ready?
--Okay.
--Yeah.
[FAN D]
It's Yumeri! Oh, god!
Maina, too!
[sighs]
[SORANE]
Aya, what are you doing?
[AYA]
Hm?
[SORANE]
[AYA] I always wanted
to become an idol.
I've worked hard and
believed in myself.
And yet...
Sorane, you just decided
to join on a whim,
and somehow, managed to
become more popular than me.
And you're a natural
at dealing with fans.
And I... I don't know
how you do it.
The guys who come to see you
end up falling for you.
I guess I'm just
a little jealous.
Uh. I didn't try to
make them fall for me.
[grumbles]
That makes me feel worse!
I don't have any fans
who are in love with me!
Even with the rumors about you,
none of your fans would stray
from you and start liking me!
[gasps]
[SORANE]
Aya, this doesn't always
have to be some competition.
Here's what I do.
I hope you never stop liking me.
[gasps]
That's all there is to it.
[chuckles]
[AYA]
But I... I can't do that!
I'm not like you!
No wonder they go crazy.
[SORANE chuckles]
But we're at least
friends again, right?
I mean, I guess it isn't like
we're fighting or anything!
[YUKA] Benjamin! Oscar!
You both made it!
[REO]
You're the sweetest!
[gasps]
This many tickets
on a regular day?
[REO]
Thank you so much!
[MAINA]
Why?
[ERIPIYO]
I'm sure she's like, "Why?"
I wanted to see you in
an adorable Santa outfit,
so I went all out!
But that might sound creepy.
I'm doing this because I want
you in my future, Maina!
[ERIPIYO] Next year,
and the one after that.
I wanna spend every
Christmas with you.
And I want you to have
nice things to wear.
Oh. Uh, you do?
[ERIPIYO]
I said that out loud!
[ERIPIYO] Even the top
of her head is cute!
[YOSHIKAWA] Thank you
so much. Your time's up!
See ya!
Oh, Eripiyo.
[MAINA]
Reo!
I'm so late! Sorry.
No.
[REO giggles]
[MAINA]
Wow, so many options.
[REO]
Right? Isn't it exciting?
Uh.
[MAINA]
Umm.
[REO] You're wearing one
this year, right?
Huh?
[REO]
A Santa costume.
Even though you were too
embarrassed to last year?
[MAINA]
Yeah.
I'm still embarrassed,
to be honest.
But I do want the fans
to see me wearing it.
[REO]
Isn't it nice?
There're so many other
things those people
could be doing Christmas day,
but they all choose
to come spend it
with us instead, you know?
I love that. Like, a lot.
[ERIPIYO]
Hmm...
That'd look so good on her.
So would that. And that one!
[grunting]
Right! Mental training complete!
Now I won't get a nosebleed
seeing Santa Maina,
even in real life!
[sighs]
[ERIPIYO]
Hm?
[GIRL A]
Let's buy matching rings!
[MAN A]
Yeah, I like that!
[GIRL B] Or we could
get the same rings,
but with each of
our birthstones.
Jealous.
What are you even
talking about?
We're gonna be spending
our Christmases
with the ones we love, too,
just like those idiots!
[ERIPIYO]
Yeah!
The fact that we're spending
Christmas day with them
kinda feels like
we're dating them!
Uh. Yeah, you're right!
Today is our big
Christmas date, guys!
[ERIPIYO, MOTOI]
You said it!
[thunder rumbles]
[ERIPIYO]
Hm?
It's really dark.
[KUMASA] What, you mean the
darkness of your heart?
No!
Over that way. Look.
Giant storm clouds.
[KUMASA] I'm sure
everything'll be all right.
I mean, the concert space
is underground.
So I don't think we
really have anything
to worry about, do we?
[MOTOI]
Nah, we're good.
Better hurry to get to
our Christmas dates!
Yeah, we wouldn't wanna
keep the ones we love
waiting on Christmas!
[ERIPIYO]
That's the truth! Woohoo!
[thunder rumbles]
It's our Christmas concert!
So, welcome!
Yeah! Your Christmas would be
boring without us, wouldn't it?
Jeez! Have some tact!
Yeah, don't say
things like that!
[YUKA chuckles]
Ma...
[ERIPIYO]
Ma... i...
...na...
[ERIPIYO yells]
Maina's the most adorable
little Santa Claus ever!
[KUMASA, MOTOI]
Congratulations.
Oh, Santa Maina!
Your being born is the
best Christmas present
a girl like me
could ever ask for!
I love you today
and every other day!
[lightning crashes]
[REO gasps]
[YUKA]
Huh?
[FANS yell]
A blackout?
It's so dark now!
Did lightning strike
the building? Uh!
Oh, jeez.
No, no, no! I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared!
[ERIPIYO]
Maina! Don't move!
Huh?
It's dangerous to move around!
Everyone! Staff included!
Whoa, Eripiyo. Do you have
night vision, like a cat?
What? No. I can sense
where bodies are.
What the--?
Well, that's creepy.
I happen to have
a light source.
[gasps]
I knew I'd get a
Santa Maina photo,
so I dressed for the occasion.
Because I totally had faith
that you would be wearing
a Santa outfit this year!
[ERIPIYO]
Okay! Remain calm!
Right. Now, fans,
light up those King Blades!
[KUMASA]
Oh!
Yeah, good idea!
[MATSUO]
You heard her, guys!
[FAN A]
Here goes.
[FAN B]
Be careful.
[KUMASA]
Hey, Reo. Are you doing okay?
[REO]
I am. Thank you!
[SORANE]
Thanks for the light.
Be sure to watch
your step, guys!
[FANS]
You, too!
Yume. Watch out for
that cord there.
Yeah. My eyes are getting
used to the dark now.
Man. Not me. I'm still scared!
[FAN B]
You've got this, Aya!
[FUMI]
Are you scared, Yuka?
Oh, nah. I'm just making
this weird face for funsies.
[FUMI]
Oh. Cool.
[ERIPIYO] We're almost to the
exit. Just a bit farther!
[GIRLS]
Okay!
[gasps]
[ERIPIYO]
This is amazing.
I feel like a hero.
Like I'm actually
helping Maina to safety!
I'm doing this because I want
you in my future, Maina!
[MAINA]
I know this much:
Even if the whole world somehow
went pitch black in the future,
as long as I have Eripiyo's
light to guide me,
I can keep moving forward.
[MAINA]
And as long as I live,
I will never forget
this image of her.
[MISAKI] All right, folks,
we'll begin the photo ops now!
They're so pretty they
might not need our light.
You can feel the
holiday spirit.
You totally saved
Christmas today, Eripiyo.
I have a feeling I might've been
a reindeer in a previous life.
[MISAKI]
Maina's line is starting now!
[ERIPIYO]
Great job today, Maina!
I'm sorry if today was hard.
Oh, not at all.
I think today was
probably harder
for you than anyone, Eripiyo.
What? No, not a chance!
I didn't think it was rough--
not even for a single second.
In fact, this is the most
satisfied I've felt in years!
[YOSHIKAWA] All right.
Time for the photo op.
Oh. Yes, sir.
[ERIPIYO gasps]
[ERIPIYO] Whoa! Maina's way
closer to me than usual!
[ERIPIYO] Wait, could this
be a Christmas miracle?
[YOSHIKAWA]
Here we go!
Ready. Say "cheese"!
[REO] Thanks, everyone.
We're so grateful for you!
[applause]
This has certainly been one of
the more eventful Christmases
I've had in a while.
But I'm so happy...
'cause we spent it together!
[MAINA gasps]
And Maina.
She actually wore a cute
Santa outfit this year!
She's cute, huh?
Uh. This year--
[MAINA gasps]
No. Next year, and the next,
and even the one after that...
I hope we can celebrate
Christmas again.
And I hope that when we
celebrate it in the future,
that we all do so together.
[MAINA]
And most of all, in my future,
I hope Eripiyo will
always be there.
[ERIPIYO humming]
I don't think I've ever seen
you this happy, Eripiyo.
Santa and her reindeer--
name a more iconic duo.
I'm gonna treasure this forever!
[KUMASA, MOTOI grunt]
[BOTH] This is more
unfortunate than usual.
I know you're jealous.
Don't hide it.
[ERIPIYO laughs]
Uh.
[inaudible]
Wow.
[MAINA]
If there ever comes a day
where Eripiyo's world goes dark,
I hope that I can
be there for her.
More than anything,
I wanna be the one
who lights her way.
I can't believe it.
I saw this picture and
didn't feel the need
to look for clues of some guy.
You're so cute, Maina!
The cutest ever!
[ERIPIYO]
Now that Christmas is over,
it's time for the
New Year's concert!
I can't believe my luck
that I get to spend
the end of the year
with Maina, too!
Ah! Do your best, Maina!
I believe in you!
I'll be cheering
you on, as always!
Jeez, my cup runneth over!
I have so much to say!
[YOSHIKAWA] Thank you very
much! Your time's up!