♪♪♪
[MAINA]
Reo.
[REO]
Maina.
Oh, man, thanks.
[MAINA]
Reo, are you okay?
You've been getting to practice
early every day lately.
Aren't you worn out?
No, not really. What about you?
You've been right here with me.
[MAINA]
Yeah, you're right.
But I'm here because I'm not
nearly good enough yet.
[REO]
That's not true at all!
But I understand how you feel.
No matter how many
lessons you take,
it's hard to feel
confident sometimes.
[MAINA]
You've felt that, too?
[REO]
Of course I have.
In this group,
and even my last one,
I was so fixated on
being in the center,
I became obsessed
with practicing.
I wanted to work harder than
everybody else on the team.
But then...
[FANS cheering]
[REO] There are some people
that you just can't beat,
no matter what.
At the end of the day, hard
work only counts for so much.
I get that, logically,
but it's all I have.
I work hard. That's it.
No way! That's not all!
[YUKA]
Morning!
'Sup, overachievers?
[SORANE, MAKI, YUMERI]
Morning.
[AYA]
Okay! The festival's coming up!
Let's kick its butt!
Heck yeah! Shall we?
Let's do this!
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
[ERIPIYO]
Ohh!
I'm so nervous!
Will we even get a spot
where we can see them?
[KUMASA]
Hm.
They're on earlier than
I would've expected.
You're right.
Oh. So Maple is the final act?
Looks that way.
Well, they are the
most popular group,
so it kinda makes sense.
[RENA]
Wait, does that mean
the least popular groups
perform earlier?
[KUMASA, MOTOI gasp]
No, no, no, no!
Not what I meant!
[RENA] They're on right
around the middle.
That's a weird spot.
[ERIPIYO, KUMASA, MOTOI]
Gloom...
[YUKA]
Whoa.
Here we are: The staff entrance!
Let's go in! Yay!
[YUKA]
Yay, the staff bathrooms!
[AYA] We're idols, so we
won't use 'em, but yay!
Ha! Now we're in
the staff hallway!
There's catering!
You can see the steam!
Yay.
[YUKA squeals]
You're right.
Yeah, they call it
kraft services.
[BOTH]
Smells good!
Guys, cut it out,
or everyone's gonna know
that we're total noobs.
Seriously. Let's go.
[AYA, YUKA]
Okay.
[YUKA]
Wow! Awesome!
Gorgeous idols everywhere!
[SORANE] Just remember
that we're idols, too.
[YUKA] ♪ I can't wait to find
out where our green room is! ♪
[MAKI]
Oh. I believe we're in this one.
[YUKA]
Okay, girls. Open the door!
Tiny.
Hold up. For real?
[YUMERI]
Don't worry, guys. Look!
We actually have a pot
to cook with today!
[AYA]
But we're not making udon.
[MAINA]
Um.
Would you guys mind if I go
brush my teeth real quick?
[MAKI]
Wait. I wanna come, too.
When you go out, take a right,
and there'll be a sink there.
You can't miss it.
How do you know where it is?
Oh, yeah. This isn't your first
time up here, is it, Reo?
Yeah, that's true.
And you were in the
final act before.
Uh.
I'm sorry! I wasn't
trying to be mean.
[MEI]
Hey, Reo, you feeling nervous?
[REO]
Um, yeah.
[MEI sighs]
At a festival this small?
[REO]
Huh?
Keep that up and you'll
never play the Budokan.
[STAFF A]
Thank you very much!
Man, you went all out.
Dang, Eripiyo.
I wanna enjoy this.
It's Maina's first
festival appearance!
It's time to let go of the past.
We've had some rough times,
but I never wanna
miss another first!
That makes sense.
Right. BRB. Buying more!
[RENA]
What about you?
I'm good. I've got what I need.
One is enough.
Today's a very special day.
I want to savor it
as much as I can.
[ERIPIYO grunting]
[ERIPIYO]
Oh, God, they fell!
I guess one's
enough for me, too.
[FANS cheering]
[ERIPIYO]
It's almost time!
[AYA]
We're only two acts away.
[SORANE]
I know. I'm getting so nervous.
[REO]
We'll be great!
[OTHERS]
Huh?
[SORANE, YUKA, AYA chuckle]
[REO]
Let's go... Cham Jam!
Hey, Reo!
[gasps]
It's been forever!
Wait, you're already on?
That's pretty early.
Yeah.
Are you nervous?
A little.
[MEI] I guess it has been
a while, hasn't it?
Since you played
such a big venue?
[REO]
I guess so.
But we're just here to have fun.
We don't care how
big the venue is.
Yeah!
[YUKA]
Mh-hm!
How cute! Well, I hope
you have fun then!
[FANS cheering]
By the way, my group's gonna
be playing at the Budokan.
[ALL gasp]
See ya! And break a leg!
Reo!
[REO]
I, uh...
I guess I need to get a grip.
After all, I'm the
center, you know?
Sorry. I suck.
[AYA]
You do not, and don't apologize!
You know, when we first met,
I thought you were too good
for a group like Cham.
We weren't bad, but you
were just amazing, Reo
And you still are.
For real. You blow me away!
[YUKA] Same here.
I love you so much, Reo.
You probably don't
even know this,
but energy just radiates
from you when you perform.
I even see it from behind you!
What do you mean? Energy?
Love!
I think about it all the time!
Cham Jam is special.
That's because love is what
fuels our group, ya know?
[YUMERI]
Reo.
[MAINA]
Hard work.
You said there's
no real guarantee
that hard work will
pay off, and I agree.
Nothing is promised.
But still, I don't believe hard
work ever goes to waste either.
[REO]
Maina.
If we give it 100%,
and only 1% of that pays off
in the end, I don't even care.
I'll still be proud that
we left it all out there.
I believe in us, and I owe
so much of that to you, Reo!
[REO]
You guys, thank you so much.
I'm happy because I'm with you.
We made it here together!
[REO]
I'm okay now.
I won't get down again.
No matter what!
[FANS cheering]
Woo! Yeah!
[REO]
Because we'll make it.
[REO] And someday, we'll go
to the Budokan together!
[FANS cheering]
Are you ready?
[gasps]
Go, Maina, go!
Yeah, Maina!
Eripiyo's here!
Good luck.
♪♪♪
[singing in Japanese]
[REO]
We're all in this together!
But that's not all!
[MAINA]
I can't believe I'm here!
[REO]
I'm so happy. Truly happy!
[MAINA]
I'm grateful.
I'm so glad to be an idol!
[REO]
Thank you all!
We're Cham Jam! See ya!
[FANS cheering]
[MOTOI]
Sorane!
[KUMASA]
Reo!
[ERIPIYO]
Maina!
[ERIPIYO] Ugh! I know I
keep saying this, but--
[KUMASA]
We're with ya; keep saying it!
That was so awesome!
It sure was!
Cham killed it! Their
performance was so amazing!
I still can't quite believe it--
that I saw Sorane
on that huge stage!
[ERIPIYO]
I guess Sorane was great, too.
I mean, I wasn't
watching her much.
[KUMASA] All right,
we've still got some time
before Cham's merch line starts.
How should we kill
time until then?
How about another bowl of udon?
Y'know, to celebrate!
[KUMASA] You're confusing
udon with champagne.
[FANS cheering]
[KUMASA, MOTOI]
Huh?
[MOTOI] What do you think
that's all about?
Wow.
Sounds like Maple
Doll's performance
is about to kick off.
Hey, guys! Long wait?
[ALL]
Well, we're Maple Doll!
[YUKA] Whoa! The crowd's
getting so hyped up!
[MAKI] They are the
final act, after all.
Let's keep the fun going
till the very end!
[FANS cheering]
[YUMERI]
Wow.
Well, we performed on that exact
stage a little while ago.
Yeah, and we kicked
its butt, too!
Did you notice?
You could see where the Cham
fans stopped--in the crowd.
Yeah.
You could tell by the motion
of their king blades.
We've still got room to grow.
But we took a step forward,
and it was a big one!
[MISAKI]
Hey, girls.
Remember to touch
up your makeup?
We're gonna go hand
out some fliers. Uh.
No time to waste before
the special fan event!
We will be promoting
you heavily.
We won't rest until every
person here knows who you are!
Whoa! Mr. Yoshikawa's on fire!
He does work!
I resent that remark!
[MISAKI]
You ready?
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
[SORANE]
We're Cham Jam.
You should swing by
our merch booth later!
Hello, you should come see us!
Thanks. Hope to see you later!
[gasps]
[MAINA] Is Eripiyo watching
Maple Doll's performance?
Wh-Which girl? Who does
she have her eyes on?
[SORANE]
Maina, what's wrong?
Nothing! I'm cool.
Could I get one of those?
[MAINA]
Uh, sure.
[SORANE]
Here ya go.
If you can, you should
come by our merch booth.
Uh, for sure.
That girl was a total babe,
don't you think?
[FAN B]
Changing your fave?
Better hope they don't find out.
[FAN A] They won't if you
keep your trap shut!
Hey, Sorane?
Do you think there's an idol
here who has more fans
than the rest of
us put together?
Probably in Maple Doll, huh?
[SORANE] When someone tells
me I'm their favorite,
I can't help but feel honored,
but then I look at
that person's blog
and there's nothing there.
They say I'm their favorite,
but they never write a
single thing about me.
It's kind of strange.
At the end of the day, we have
to take their word for it.
I just hope one person
continues to like me the most.
All you can do is keep being
your best, authentic self.
The rest is up to the fans,
but I'm sure they'll fall
in love with you more
every time the see you.
If you keep it up,
you could be number one.
Huh.
I guess there are lots of
different kinds of idols.
[KUMASA]
Yeah, that's true.
If you can imagine it,
there's an idol for it.
But in spite of how
many there are,
I feel so lucky to
have seen Reo first.
Truly, it's the greatest
gift fate has given me.
[ERIPIYO] Even watching these
"bigger" idol groups,
all I can think of is
how much I love Maina.
True, there are tons of them.
But in my world,
there's no one but Maina.
She's not just my number one.
She's the only one.
[AYA]
I'll fight you in the Budokan!
[SORANE]
Motoi!
What'd you think of our
performance today?
[MOTOI] Man, it just reinforced
how much I adore, you, Sorane.
And also, it made me so grateful
that you became an idol.
Huh?
[MOTOI]
If you had never become one,
how could I tell you how
much I really like you?
[SORANE gasps]
[MOTOI] So, uh, thank you
for allowing me to.
For real.
Wait, what?
Am I... your number one?
Uh. Of course you're
my number one, duh!
I'll take your word
for it. 'Kay, Motoi?
So, um, great job today.
I only watched you.
When Cham was done,
I just went and ate udon.
I figured. Thank you.
And with you there,
I was way more confident.
But did I dance all right?
I want you to be honest, now.
Yeah.
[YOSHIKAWA] Right, folks!
Maina's line's open! Hey, you!
I'll go ahead.
Is that cool with you?
Oh, sure!
[ERIPIYO]
What should I say?
Hey, Maina! You were
super cute today.
Aw, thank you!
[ERIPIYO]
Such pressure.
I wanna say something
extra special!
'Cause it's a special day!
So, uh, listen, ever since
I became your fan,
I've had so many neat firsts.
With Eripiyo, and my brother,
and even with Kumasa.
[ERIPIYO] But telling her
to keep doing her best
sounds weird.
Like, who do I think I am?
I'm having so much fun,
and I'm so grateful that
I was able to meet you.
[gasps]
[ERIPIYO] Something I can
only tell her today.
What can I tell her just
for this special day?
[YOSHIKAWA]
Anyone else for Maina?
I'm gonna cut off the line
if there's no one else!
[ERIPIYO]
Maina, right here!
Uh... Lovely weather we're
having, don't you think?
[MAINA]
Eripiyo.
I was really happy to see
you right there up front.
[gasps]
So, did you enjoy it?
Are you kidding? I loved it!
I had so much fun,
and I was so happy!
You worked so hard up there!
Your performance was the best!
That means so much.
And I really hope that someday
you'll come to the
Budokan with me!
[gasps]
[MAINA]
No. I don't just hope that!
It's gonna happen!
I'll do everything in my
power to make it there!
[ERIPIYO] What in the
world is this creature?
How can she be so cute?
Nothing in the world could
ever top her cuteness!
D-Did she level up?
Did this festival
multiply her cuteness?
Does this mean that when she
makes it to the Budokan,
or to something even bigger,
her cuteness will
become unstoppable?
[MAINA]
Eripiyo.
[gasps]
[MAINA] It's all because
of you, Eripiyo.
That I was able to do my best!
I owe it all to you!
I love you.
Huh?
[ERIPIYO]
The Budokan.
[MAINA]
Yes?
[ERIPIYO] If you were to make
to the Budokan, I could...
...die happy.
Huh?
If you made it to the Budokan,
I'd die... happy!
Huh?
[ERIPIYO gasps]
[KUMASA]
Well, we finally made it.
This is it.
[ALL]
The Budokan!
It's huge! Stretches as
far as the eye can see!
That part must be
the golden onion.
We were so excited
from the festival
that we went all
the way to Tokyo!
Yeah, I'm really glad we did.
So, Cham'll be on
that stage someday.
I feel it!
This is it? This is the Budokan?
It's, uh, not at all what
I pictured in my mind.
You sure this is it?
Yes! That's the Budokan!
But I thought that there was
an onion on top or something.
I mean, that looks
like onions to me!
Maybe they're diced onions!
Excellent point.
Someday, we'll be on that stage.
Yeah. I'll do my best.
[YUMERI]
Sorry, you guys.
Looks like this is the
wrong place, after all.
[OTHERS]
What?!