[ERIPIYO]
Kumasa!
[KUMASA]
Hm?
[laughs]
Guess who's back?
Every bone in its right place!
Oh, congratulations.
I gotta say, I'm surprised
it took you this long
to get back in the action.
I know. A whole month
since the tragedy.
[WARTHOG]
Oink!
[ERIPIYO screams]
Good thing, you made
it just in time.
The popularity ranking.
Deadline's this weekend.
Don't tell me you forgot.
[ERIPIYO gasps]
Oh, God, that's right.
My leg has kept me
from buying merch,
and because of that,
Maina's fallen into last place.
Well, this sucks!
I'll never see her smiling
in the center at this rate!
[ERIPIYO] I will not be
accused of being a casual fan!
[AYA]
Listen to this!
I told Yuka that the
show was starting,
but she wouldn't
put down her phone!
It's like she doesn't even
care or something!
She said there was some
kind of event in her game!
Be quiet! Are you trying
to sabotage my votes?
[AYA]
You deserve it!
Ugh. Can you two
just give it a rest?
[YUMERI chuckles]
Well, voting does finish
up this week, after all.
So I'm pretty much
guaranteed a spot
on the front row, regardless.
[ERIPIYO growls]
[KUMASA chuckles]
Yuka, you shouldn't
say things like that!
Huh? What's the problem?
[FUMI]
Oh, goodness.
Yuka is terrible at
reading a room.
[REO]
Oh, well!
We hope you'll support
us till the end!
[FANS]
Yeah!
Fifteen Makis!
Gimme 20 Yukas!
[ERIPIYO] Here. Maina's
handshake ticket.
I have to go to work,
unfortunately.
I'm trusting you to interact
with Maina in my place.
[KUMASA]
Wait, only one?
You're back for real now,
so I thought you'd
be going all out.
Don't tell me you're
a casual fan now!
How dare you! I'm going
all out on the last day.
Everyone loves a comeback kid,
you know what I mean?
Oh. That's a good idea.
Still, don't push
yourself too hard.
I'm willing to bet that
wearing yourself out
is what got you into
trouble last time.
[ERIPIYO]
Don't worry!
I'm full of energy 'cause
I can work for Maina again!
Okay, then.
[MAINA]
Uhh...
Sorry that it's me.
I'm here to see you in
Eripiyo's place today.
Oh. Okay. But... is she--?
Did her house burn
down or something?
Oh, uh, not that I know of.
No need to worry.
Eripiyo's out there
working as hard
as she possibly can for you.
[MAINA]
She's out working hard for me?
Please tell her not to
push herself too hard!
[KUMASA]
I did.
But I think she might
actually listen
now that it's coming
from you, Maina.
--[phone dings]
--[ERIPIYO] Huh?
[ERIPIYO]
Oh my God, that angel!
I'm pumped! Now I can
work even harder!
[MOTOI] Not as many of Sorane's
blue King Blades out there.
Stupid rumors.
Well, that just means
I have fewer rivals!
I don't care what place she's in
as long as she's
standing on that stage!
If she's in the back row,
it will be harder for her
to gain popularity.
Oh, well.
If I had my way, she'd
belong to no one but me.
[AYA] There are more blues
than greens out there!
Why, though?
[growls]
[SORANE]
Hm?
What's the matter, Aya?
You mad I'm beating you?
[AYA]
Shove it, Yuka!
Hey. Aya!
[FANS]
Hey! Hey...!
[AYA] This doesn't make
any sense at all!
How could this be happening?
Why in the world would
Sorane be ahead of me
in the popularity
ranking at this point?
With all those rumors?
There's been no talk about me
catting around with some guy!
Well, you're more of the
little sister type, you know?
Wait, are you saying that my age
will keep me out of
the number one spot?
Uh, no.
But to be fair,
it would be pretty unusual to
have a loli in the center,
you know what I mean?
Still, we'll be there
cheering for you!
You're the only loli in
the group, after all.
That's right,
you gotta represent!
[AYA]
Lolis can't be in the center?
Yikes! Is tomorrow really
the last day for voting?
Yeah, it's been a whirlwind!
The whole thing went by so fast!
[AYA]
Good morning.
[REO]
Wait. Who are you?
Is that Aya? What the--?
What happened?
Cham Jam needs a cougar.
Not what that means.
Reo and I have always
been a little too alike,
so I'm trying to
be more like Maki,
'cause she's in second.
Time for some deep
self-reflection.
[GIRLS] ♪ I may be young and
silly, but I'm not a child! ♪
♪ I can do it
if I actually try! ♪
♪ Oba leaves are completely-- ♪
My favorite.
Who is that?
She's small, so Aya?
Whoa, getting sixth in the
midterms did a number on her.
How could Aya be so
obtuse about her role?
So sad. You're a loli, Aya.
Hey, Aya! I can see your
flop sweat from over here!
Sowwy I'm so wate, fwiends!
[NARRATOR A] She failed so
badly, she quit immediately.
Your absence was felt.
Just look at this pathetic
pile of unflipped buns.
I'll take care of it!
Look at her flipping those buns!
She's like a
thousand-armed diety!
[ERIPIYO]
My hard work will pay dividends
in the form of Maina's CDs.
And Maina will have sustenance.
She'll be able to buy all
the buns her heart desires!
This rocks!
I guess, in a way, I'm working
to keep Maina alive!
[groaning]
[ERIPIYO]
So much work. I'm pooped.
But today is the last day.
Now, Maina will
surely get first.
Eripiyo, thank you so much
for all your hard work.
I love you.
Maina, my angel.
[splash]
[REO]
Okay, let's do this!
Cham Jam...
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
[FANS cheering]
[GIRLS]
♪ One, two, three, go! ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
[MAINA]
Eripiyo's not here? But why?
It's the last day.
Popularity voting ends today!
[FAN A]
Ten Makis!
[FAN B]
Twenty Yukas!
[FAN C]
Two Ayas!
A hundred Reos!
Look, Reo. Please don't worry.
I made a promise.
So no matter what, I'll make
sure you take number one.
You're the best.
I believe in you, Kumasa.
[MAKI]
Thanks so much for coming!
Aw, Motoi. Thanks for
coming to see me again.
There aren't as many
people in my line now.
It means a lot.
Sure!
[MOTOI] None of these
morons has any idea
that the rumors are a lie!
I'll have her all
to myself soon.
Advantage: Motoi!
Right, send it over
to the agency now.
[MAINA]
I can't believe it.
Eripiyo really didn't come.
--[RENA] Maina.
--[gasps]
[MAINA]
Oh, hi, Rena!
How are you? By yourself today?
No, with my brother.
Oh, of course.
Awesome show. You were so cute
up there again, as usual.
Really? Well, thank you.
[AYA] I still think I'll
be on the front row.
[MAINA] If Eripiyo doesn't
come to see me here,
then where will I ever see her?
[gasps]
[ERIPIYO coughing]
[OLD MAN]
Oh, she's awake!
[OLD WOMAN]
You okay there, girl?
[ERIPIYO]
Where am I?
Well, we found you drifting
down the channel earlier.
You were just a-bobbin' up
and down like an apple.
Yup, that's right,
and mutterin',
"Today's the last day,"
or something.
Whatever that means.
Last day?
[gasps]
Nothing broken?
Not sure. Ambulance
is on its way.
[ERIPIYO]
If nothing's broken, I'm fine.
Sorry if I caused any trouble!
[ERIPIYO]
Um...
Can I still buy CDs?
[MISAKI] A demon!
Oh, Eripiyo, it's just you.
[ERIPIYO] Let me buy merch.
Let me buy merch...
But the deadline
has passed already.
Even if you did buy merch,
it's not gonna count!
It's okay.
I just wanna buy her stuff.
For Maina's sake.
It's not about the contest.
[KUMASA]
Man, Reo was amazing.
Like, did you see her smile?
Yeah!
Ya know, I think I
connected with Sorane
even more than usual today!
I love Reo.
Eripiyo?
What happened?
You're super late!
I figured you
might be late today,
and I totally considered buying
some of Maina's CDs for you,
but I figured you would tell me
there was no point in doing that
if you didn't buy them
with your own money,
so I didn't do it, and I--
[ERIPIYO]
Shut up, liar!
All other fans are sworn enemies
during popularity ranking!
[ERIPIYO] I worked so hard
for this, and all for nothing.
I at least wanted the chance
to tell her it was worth it.
That I wasn't working too hard
because it was for her,
so I enjoyed it.
Yeah, awesome! I got two SSRs!
[MISAKI]
Maina? You here?
Listen, Eripiyo stopped by.
Wait, what do you mean?
So she was just here?
Yup, downstairs.
[MISAKI] I told her the
deadline had already passed
so they wouldn't count as votes,
but she bought all
your CDs anyway.
[gasps]
[MAINA]
I'm so confused.
Eripiyo wasn't at
our show today.
[MISAKI]
She was drenched with sweat,
so I'm guessing something
must've gone wrong.
You've got one devoted
fan in that girl.
[MAINA] I wonder if she
already got on the train.
Probably so.
I'm an idol, anyway.
So I can't see Eripiyo unless
she comes to an event.
I hate that!
[gasps]
Eri--!
[MAINA]
My CDs!
She makes me... so happy!
The next time she comes to shake
my hand, before anything else,
I'll tell her how
she makes me feel!
[MOTOI]
The day has finally come.
[MOTOI chuckles]
Yeah, I guess.
[MOTOI] Hey, Eripiyo. Which one
of these do you like best?
[ERIPIYO]
Eh. Either one is fine.
Could you try to take
this seriously?
[ERIPIYO] I think it's fine
for you to get her a gift
to say congrats for the ranking,
but why's it gotta be clothes?
I stole the idea from Fumi.
You know, the Yuka stan.
Apparently, if you
get them clothes,
there's a pretty good
chance they'll wear 'em.
Wow, that's totally
hot. I'm melting.
[MOTOI]
Do I detect a sarcastic nuance?
Your face doesn't match
your words at all!
I need some assistance here,
but I'm scared to ask
the employees for help.
I know! They don't seem too
eager to talk to me, either!
Well, you don't look like
you're here to buy clothes.
Why would they
wanna talk to you?
Here's an idea.
Why don't you buy Maina
something nice to wear?
[ERIPIYO]
I can hear her now.
There's no way I'm wearing that!
Uh-huh. Just like with
the millet dumplings.
You poor thing.
[EMPLOYEE A] Looking for
something in particular?
[MOTOI]
Uh. Something for a girl?
So I'm assuming it's a gift.
Yeah.
[EMPLOYEE A] I'm guessing
for your girlfriend?
Huh?
Okay, mind telling
me how old she is?
And her size if you know it.
Oh, she's 18,
158 centimeters tall.
She's slim with short hair
and plays tennis.
She looks great with black hair,
and her eyes are kinda cat--
Okay, small or medium.
What kind of clothes
does she usually wear?
Let's see. Stylish, but
casual at the same time.
Ah, gotcha. Well...
[ERIPIYO]
That seems like fun.
Pardon me.
[EMPLOYEE B]
Huh?
I need help finding a gift for
someone, if you don't mind.
Oh, sure.
[EMPLOYEE B]
A tracksuit?
Okay, Who's the gift for?
Who's it for?
[ERIPIYO]
How do I answer that?
What is Maina to me?
Well, that's actually a pretty
difficult question to answer.
A hundred fifty-two centimeters.
Blood type A positive,
a slim build and long limbs,
hair about like this,
and the cutest face!
She's basically like
an angel on earth!
[EMPLOYEE B]
An angel?
Maybe this is some
unhealthy sister
dynamic or something.
[ERIPIYO] But her wings
haven't grown in yet,
so no need to worry
about clothes
with wing holes in the back.
[EMPLOYEE B] Okay...
What do you think about this?
[KUMASA]
Yo!
My shift went longer
than I expected.
Hey, glad you could join us.
Oh, have you two been doing
some shopping together?
Whaddya get? Any presents
for Reo's birthday?
Her birthday was more
than a month ago, dude.
No, no. I celebrate her birth
every day of the year!
I agree. We celebrate them
all the time! Always!
Whatever, can we
just go in already?
Yeah!
Maybe the 30,000 or so
home-bound Maina fans
came through and voted
to get her to first place
where she belongs!
[ERIPIYO groans]
I'm not sure if I can do this.
'Cause if I give
her this present,
I'm going to want
something in return.
It's true!
But I'm not doing this
because I want something
from Maina, you know?
And yet, if she ignores you
after you give her your gift,
that's gonna feel pretty crappy.
Listen! I admit that I
expect something in return!
Hey! Please deliver this
present to Sorane for me?!
[FUMI]
Aw, we got ignored again.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Are gift certificates
to cafés not allowed?
Welp, that puts a
damper on my plans.
Wait, you were gonna
get her one of those?
I mean, it's not like I have any
idea what Sorane actually wants.
I wish she would just write
about it in her MC on her blog.
[ERIPIYO groans]
I wouldn't be caught dead
wearing something like that!
[ERIPIYO] Maybe I'll wear
it myself instead.
[FANS cheering]
[KUMASA]
Ooh! Oh, yeah!
Look, you guys! There's Reo!
She's in the center!
Yeah, so what's new?
This is different!
This center is the most
special center of all!
It's symbolic! It represents
the hard work of her fans!
Hello, everyone. I'm Reo.
I won first place, but I have
mixed feelings about it.
But I'm standing here right
now because of all my fans.
So thanks for voting for me.
We believed in each
other, and I'm glad.
Thank you again, from
the bottom of my heart!
[FANS cheering]
[MAKI]
Hey, everyone, I'm Maki.
I came in second place in
the ranking. What an honor!
I promise that I'll
keep doing my best.
Thank you all!
Yeah, go Maki!
Third place? You guys rock! Hah!
I'm so pumped I'm
in the front row!
I mean, I was pretty sure I
would be up here all along,
but still.
You're the best!
[FUMI]
Mh-hm! Mh-hm!
Hello, there, I'm Yumeri.
Thanks to all who voted!
You got me the
fourth-place spot!
I had trouble finding
my confidence at first,
but I will do my best to
live up to your belief in me.
So I'm going to work hard.
Hi, I'm Sorane.
I'm fifth in the ranking.
Thanks for voting for me!
I have to say,
I'm a little nervous
about you dancing behind me.
Don't you worry. I won't
be too hard on you.
Man!
[chuckles]
[MOTOI]
This is a first.
I've never seen
her make that face.
It's my fault.
I didn't try hard enough.
[AYA groans]
[MATSUO]
Who the heck's that?
[FUJIKAWA]
Aya, looking like a zombie!
This is awful!
[KOSUGA, FUJIKAWA]
Ready, go. Aya!
[AYA gasps]
Hey! It's me, Aya!
Everyone's little sister!
I placed sixth, but I hope
you'll keep supporting me!
[MAINA]
I'm Maina. I placed seventh.
I, um, I'm glad to be here,
and I hope you'll
keep supporting me.
Ah! Kill me!
House-bound fans, you failed us!
Am I the only true Maina fan
left on the battlefield?
Did you actually believe
that they existed?
Eh, in any case, Maina
seems to be taking it well.
Her face is blank.
Whaddaya mean?
She always looks like that.
[KUMASA]
Hey. Is somethin' wrong?
I dunno. I always tell
Maina things about myself.
Things that make
me happy or sad,
I share them when I see her.
But I wonder,
does Maina have somebody
that she can talk to when
she's feeling down like this?
Well, in the end
a fan is just a fan.
Although Reo's happiness means
more to me than anything.
Well, I feel the same way.
[MAINA]
How should I tell her?
I want Eripiyo to know
how I felt that day.
[MAINA]
Uh, so... I feel really happy.
[ERIPIYO] It seems like Maina's
trying to say something.
Makes sense, I guess.
I told her I would put her
in the center and I didn't.
I wish I could have done more
to get you first place.
I guess I failed.
Huh? No, that isn't true!
You did a lot!
[gasps]
[MAINA] Only the staff
is supposed to know
that Eripiyo bought my CDs
after the performance.
I'd better not
mention that part.
Why the heck couldn't
I have woken up faster?
[MAINA]
But I know how hard
Eripiyo worked for me
this whole time.
I feel like I let you
down and I'm sorry.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I know it would've made
you happy if I'd won.
It means nothing!
You've always been
number one in my heart!
[ALL]
Huh?
[ERIPIYO]
You know that, don't you, Maina?
I do.
Aw, man. You're a literal angel.
You're the best!
[ERIPIYO laughs]
[MAINA]
Angel?
You're so cute!
I can't even handle it!
[MAINA]
I'm embarrassed, but so happy.
I love you.
[KOSUGA] Aya definitely doesn't
understand her character.
[FUJIKAWA] I wish Aya would
embrace her loliness.
By the way, we're
gonna get to see Aya
in a Santa outfit at the
Christmas event, right?
[KOSUGA] Something magical
is gonna happen
on that holy night, Aya!
[KOSUGA, FUJIKAWA] Right, Aya?
Say we're right, Aya!
[YOSHIKAWA]
And thank you! That's enough!