[REO] Thank you so much for
coming shopping with me today!
I found some really
cute stickers!
[SORANE]
For your fan letter replies?
[REO]
Yep!
[giggles]
[SORANE]
What's up?
It's Yumeri. I loved seeing
her so happy the other day.
Yeah.
[SORANE]
She was really glowing.
[REO]
Right?
I think it's awesome that
everyone in the group
works so hard to
be in the center.
Except me.
Huh? You don't wanna
be in the center?
I'd love to see you there.
You're amazing, Sorane.
[SORANE] I just respect
you too much, Reo.
You're "it" in my mind.
The picture-perfect idol.
That's why...
...I always want you to be
the center, no matter what.
[cheering]
[singing in Japanese]
Reo!
They perform here every week.
I think they're those
"idols" you hear about.
Idols, huh?
You mean you can be
called an idol
even with a crowd this small?
Guess so.
You know, you're way
cuter than them, Sorane.
Oh, don't flatter me.
Love you!
[chuckles]
It's not true. They're
all way cuter than me.
[SORANE'S AUNT]
You could be an idol!
I could never do that.
No point trying.
[SORANE]
No way.
You have to work so hard to
become an idol. I'd just fail.
[STUDENT A]
Hey, for our next match,
I decided to pair with someone
else for doubles, okay?
Huh? But why?
I mean, no real
reason, I guess.
I just figured I would mix
it up a little this time.
It's nothing personal, ya know?
Okay.
[SORANE]
So it isn't about me, then?
[STUDENT D]
So did you tell her?
[SORANE]
They all knew?
It's no use.
I need to stop believing
these people are special.
They're all the same.
[MISAKI]
Hey, girls. Do you have a sec?
I have some news.
This is Miss Matsuyama.
She's joining you.
Hello. My name's Yumeri.
And I'm Maki. Nice to meet you.
It's a pleasure
to meet you both.
Um, I hope I won't be--
Nice to have you!
I'm Reo Igarashi!
I'm Matsuyama.
Um, sounds weird, but
I've seen you perform.
Just me, though?
[SORANE] With some other
girls in the mall.
Oh! You must have seen
me with my old group!
They disbanded a little while
ago and Cham scooped me up!
Honestly, I've never really
danced before. Or sang, either.
My aunt sent in my application
without telling me.
Yeah, but you got this far
on your own merit, didn't you?
You'll be fine! If I can
do this, anyone can!
[SORANE]
But you're... pretty.
Not prettier than you!
I'm here 'cause I had
fans cheering me on.
The truth is, being an idol
is about more than looks!
You have to work
really hard, too!
[giggles]
[SORANE] Does she not
understand she's stunning?
Don't worry. It'll be fun.
You'll be the center
soon, Sorane!
[SORANE]
Huh?
I never said my first name.
[REO chuckles]
I knew right away I
wanted to be friends,
so I did some stalking online!
[SORANE] I'm sort of
struggling with this part.
Yeah, right before
the last hook.
[YUMERI]
It's such a tongue-twister,
and the lyrics change
slightly there,
which makes it hard to memorize.
Oh, I know!
If you change where you
breathe, it's a bit easier.
Like, for you, Sorane.
If you breathe here, and then
breathe again right there,
I think going into the hook
won't be as difficult.
Ohh.
Well, it's clear who's been
doing this the longest.
Singing's like anything else--
the more you do it,
the easier it gets!
[SORANE] I guess so,
but you're a natural.
[REO]
Oh, come on now!
I try to make it seem that way,
but I have to work at it, too!
[REO giggles]
Aya Yokota!
And get ready, 'cause I'm
destined to be the center!
[REO]
I hope so!
Hey, no fair, Aya!
[AYA]
Huh?
Yuka's number one!
[AYA] Who are you? I've never
seen you in my life.
I told you, my name's Yuka!
[MAINA]
Um, I'm Maina Ichii.
I know I might seem shy,
but I've always had deep
admiration for idols.
[REO]
Maina!
Gorgeous!
[MAINA]
Huh?
No. I'm really not.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I'm
way cuter than this girl!
[AYA]
Jeez, you're insufferable!
[YUKA]
Okay, just a little cuter.
Seven. Perfect.
[REO]
This is it! Our first concert!
Here we go!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Nice to meet you all!
We're Cham Jam!
[GUYS cheer]
I mean, I figured we'd have
a small crowd, but come on.
[REO]
Don't worry.
Pretty soon, we're going to
fill up that whole plaza!
There's no doubt in my mind.
The seven of us can do it.
Um, we can?
That's right! And not
just the plaza!
Where else are you thinking?
Ooh, the symphony hall!
Yeah, maybe even city hall.
You do realize city hall
is pretty big, don't you?
Well, yeah. Seems far-fetched.
But who knows?
The Budokan.
How 'bout it?
Let's fill the Budokan.
[SORANE]
Reo must be pretty worried.
Because the last group
she was in broke up.
I've been by her side for
so long, so I understand.
[YUKA]
Holy crap!
I can't make sense
of this! Bored.
Now, wait just a minute!
You're here because you wanted
help with your homework.
If you don't care,
then just go home.
[YUKA]
Stare...
Ugh. What?
You're a devil with a bob.
You should try acting a
little more like an idol.
So what's an idol
supposed to be like?
Huh? I dunno.
[SORANE]
What should I say?
What is an idol
supposed to be like?
Huh?
Did you seriously just
fall asleep on me?
[MATSUO]
Eripiyo's holding an eggplant!
Yumeri's her fave now!
[KOSUGA]
Eripiyo's eating the guardrail?
She must be switching to Yuka!
[MURAKAMI] Eripiyo's growing
cherry blossoms now?
She's gotta be a Reo stan!
Stop the madness!
You're the ones
who need to stop!
I'm not switching, okay?
What's with you?
Are you the stan police?
[MOTOI] They sure are
a pain, am I right?
[ERIPIYO] All blue?
Try stanning with dignity!
[KUMASA]
What's that saying about
the pot and the kettle again?
I just keep buying blue stuff.
I can't even help myself!
Oh, here.
I picked these up when
I went back home to Wake.
I want you to have some.
[KUMASA]
You bet.
Thank you. What is it?
Aonori sashimi konjac.
It's blue, so I kept
buying more and more.
[ERIPIYO] I mean, this is
technically green, so...
[REO]
Hello again!
[AYA]
You just can't stay away!
[SORANE]
You're wearing blue. I like it.
Did you think of me
when you bought it?
[MOTOI]
Whoa! How did you guess?
[chuckles] Oh, come on.
You picked out that ensemble
just for me, didn't you?
[gasps]
Cool, right?
Come on!
You wait right there.
I'm gonna show you
just how adorably cold
Maina can be to me!
[ERIPIYO]
Uh, Maina?
You know, I can't help
thinking about you
every time I eat salmon.
[MAINA]
Huh? Why though?
Um, thank you for the nice gift.
Millet dumplings--
you're so nice.
[ERIPIYO]
They got to you!
I'm glad. I was worried!
Did you eat them?
Oh, no, of course I didn't!
[ERIPIYO]
Huh? Why though?
[MAINA]
I wanted to keep them.
[MAINA] Why does Eripiyo
have something green
tucked in her shirt?
Green is... Aya's color!
She's switching on me!
[chuckles]
[ERIPIYO]
She seemed to zone out
when I told her the thing
about eating salmon.
Well, duh.
Has it ever occurred to you
that you're just as boring
as the rest of us even
though you're a girl?
More importantly, isn't there
new merch coming out soon?
The stuff with the new design.
Oh, that's right!
I think I saw some
post on social media.
[grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[MOTOI yells]
[KUMASA]
What happened?
I'm pretty sure Motoi just died!
[MOTOI]
There was a sighting.
Apparently Sorane was spotted
walking with some stupid guy.
[BOTH]
Wha--?
What the heck?!
The Idol Stan Paradox
is our strong desire
to become idols ourselves,
in order to get closer
to our faves.
But if this were ever achieved,
we would lose the ability to
see our faves as idols anymore.
Exactly!
I've been trying to reconcile
that for almost a year now.
Oh, don't worry.
'Cause you two have zero chance
of ever becoming idols.
More importantly, can you
guys not blatantly ignore
the information that almost
killed me a moment ago?
Have a little compassion--
my fave has a boyfriend!
Other people's faves are boring.
Yeah, literally no interest.
[MOTOI groans]
Come on! I'm dying here!
[ERIPIYO] But I mean,
Sorane was in the tennis club.
[MOTOI]
Curse you, tennis club!
[MOTOI] Honestly, I don't
think I can bring myself
to show my face
around here again.
[MAKI]
Are you searching yourself?
Ew, gross, no.
I'm learning about what it
takes to raise a hamster.
[MAKI]
Uh.
Caught in the act.
Just what is so wrong with
the tennis club, anyway?
[sighs]
This isn't looking good.
Someone's claiming they spotted
me, and to make matters worse,
they're saying I was
out with a guy.
No.
They're liars!
I was helping Yuka with her
homework that whole afternoon!
The last thing I want is for
people to get the wrong idea.
So I was hoping
Yuka'd do me a solid
and tell everyone at the show
tomorrow that I was with her.
But she claims she
doesn't remember!
Are you kidding? Sorry, fam.
I could never tell a lie!
Ugh!
[MAKI] You're way too
worried about your fans.
I've never even bothered to look
up my name in the first place.
[SORANE] You're too lax
about this stuff, Maki.
No, I just don't care.
I'm not doing anything
I'd be ashamed of, anyway.
Still, though. Cham is the
only good thing in my life.
[REO]
Check it out!
The samples for our new
merch line came in!
Totes adorbs, right?
Hey, Reo. Did ya
hear the rumors?
Maki!
[REO]
You're a true-blue idol, Sorane.
You would never do anything that
could tarnish your reputation.
So tomorrow? Just hold your
head high and do your job.
If anyone brings it up,
I will defend you.
[SORANE]
That's Reo. Always so kind.
[ERIPIYO] You know...
otaku are funny sometimes.
[KUMASA]
Are you thinking about Motoi?
You're right, but honestly,
it's pretty common for dudes to
fall in love with their faves.
I guess I never thought about it
'cause I was alone at
these shows for so long.
So are we gonna do that
thing or what? Come on.
I'm on crutches, hold on!
[ERIPIYO]
Gah! This is rad!
A new pastime and
it's totally free?
It's the Cham Jam
Blog Selfie Tour!
[KUMASA] Yeah, we're taking
the exact same pictures
in the exact same places!
[ERIPIYO]
Yeah, but...
We're doing the same poses,
so why do our pictures
look so much dumber?
[MOTOI] You two look
carefree. Must be nice.
Hey, Motoi! So you
decided to show up!
Yeah. I guess I just wanted
to make one final pilgrimage.
Sorane was everything
good in my world.
She was my one
true happiness in life.
But apparently, our love
meant nothing to her.
So I see no point in my
coming here anymore.
Would you like to
express it with a poem?
Sorane. Pain.
You broke my heart,
it's killing me-ay.
Deep, man.
[CROWD cheering]
[singing in Japanese]
[gasps]
Motoi! See?
Sorane just gave
you heart hands!
Guys, do you really think
I'm gullible enough
to believe she would?
[MOTOI chuckles]
[ERIPIYO]
You are.
[MAINA]
Sorane's incredible.
So resilient. She inspires me.
I'm gonna do my best!
[ERIPIYO]
Um, Maina?
You have my support from now on!
You're so cute!
I'm your fan for life!
Please accept this
decorative candy I made!
[MAINA] I'd started to take
Eripiyo's love for granted.
I didn't show her how
much it means to me.
I'm sure she felt like
her efforts were wasted.
It makes perfect sense
that she would stray!
[MAINA] These heart hands
are for you, Eripiyo!
Take that!
[MAINA]
She's not looking?
I gave Eripiyo her own
special heart hands
and she wasn't even watching?
[MOTOI]
Ten of Sorane's please.
Wow. He's back at it.
Welp, here goes.
Twenty of Reo's please.
Gotta make up for that
whole maid café fiasco.
[ERIPIYO grunting]
I want to support Maina.
I'll die if I don't.
I want to spend all
of my money on her.
Just let me spend my money!
No! Eripiyo's become a
"take-my-money zombie"!
Let me support her.
Take all my money.
Snap out of it, Eripiyo!
Look, being a stan
isn't all about
buying your fave's merchendise!
Your desire to support
her's worth more
than all the money in the world!
If my support could
make her popular,
all would be right
with the world.
[KUMASA] Why does she have
to make such good points?
[ERIPIYO]
But you're right.
Our feelings about them
are super important.
So thank you. You're the best!
[YUKA]
You want to pay me to slap you?
[ERIPIYO]
One, please!
[MAINA] She only bought
one again today.
If she strays, I don't know
how I could live with myself.
What if she really does
pick another fave?
[gasps]
How about we play a game where
I tell you everything I feel?
[MAINA]
Huh?
[ERIPIYO]
Maina, you have the most
beautiful face in the world.
I love the way you dance
and your gentle demeanor.
I love how you
always do your best.
If I could spend every minute
of my life supporting you,
then I could die happy.
The fact that you're alive
brings me so much joy.
I'm honored to be
on the planet as you.
I love you so much, it hurts!
Maina, I just... love you!
Uh, thank you.
Your time's up now?
Sorry. I just wasn't sure
if you knew any of that,
so I thought I should tell you.
Yeah. I think I got it all.
[MISAKI] Okay! Up next:
Reo, Sorane, and Yumeri!
Wow, you came!
So glad to see you!
--[FAN A] Yeah!
--[REO giggles]
You're so sweet!
--[FAN A] Well, thank you.
--[REO] Sure! See you soon!
[REO] Hello! Ha! Aw, you
don't have to say that!
[MISAKI]
Ten for Sorane.
[gasps]
[SORANE]
Motoi!
[MOTOI gasps]
Thank you!
[MOTOI]
You remembered my name!
You wrote me a letter
the other day.
I knew who sent it immediately!
But to think you
actually remembered me.
[SORANE]
I promise.
I love my loyal fans, and those
who go out of their way for me
are even more special.
So don't stop. I won't forget.
[MOTOI]
Of course!
[SORANE]
In the end,
I guess it's hard not
to fall for everyone
who tells you they love you.
It's not exactly
romantic love, but...
[SORANE]
Hm?
Sorane. I love you.
Uh, thanks, but you
love everybody, Reo.
[REO]
Heh. That's true.
But still, it's one of the
many things I love about you.
Aw, thanks!
[ERIPIYO]
Hmm...
[KUMASA]
Looks like Sorane's in trouble.
She fell from the top three.
[RENA]
Wait, really? Why is that?
There was a sighting.
She was seen walking
with some guy in Wake.
[RENA]
Wake?
That means Sorane was spotted
with a guy near our place then.
[ERIPIYO]
Huh...
Now that I think about it,
maybe the people
they saw that day
weren't Sorane
and her boyfriend.
Motoi, it might have
been the two of you.
I mean, Rena looks
just like Sorane.
[KUMASA] Oh! That does
make perfect sense!
Well, holy crap! That's it!
[RENA groans]
[KUMASA]
Ha! It was just a false alarm!
[MOTOI]
Hooray!
[ERIPIYO, KUMASA]
Congrats! Mystery solved!
[MOTOI]
Thank you!
[MOTOI laughing]
[ERIPIYO] I hope it gets
sorted out! Poor Sorane!
[MOTOI]
Hey, hold on!
So... I'm the only Sorane stan
who knows the truth right now.
That means I could be
her shoulder to cry on
while everyone else
abandons her.
This is great!
[MOTOI groans]
No, not great. Creepy.
[MOTOI, KUMASA]
Peace! Peace. Peace!
All wrong, guys! Look younger!
Younger! Please!
[MAINA] I wonder what they're
doing. Seems like fun.
[KUMASA]
This is harder than it looks.
[ERIPIYO] Watch and learn.
It should look like this!
It's like an angel angle!
No, more like a
goddess, actually! Uh.
[MOTOI, KUMASA]
Maina.
[ERIPIYO]
Huh?
Uh, sorry! I, uh...
[gasps]
[MAINA]
I'll get this right!
Hearts!
[ERIPIYO] Whoa, what in
the world is that pose?
Uh! She's trying!
In that case...
My heart!
[ERIPIYO yelling]
It worked?
[giggles]
[yelling]
[MOTOI]
What is the matter with you?
Maina's fan service!
So should we call an
ambulance, or what?
[RENA] Maina, you look
super cute again today.
The last day of popularity
voting is almost here.
I'm so busy studying for
college entrance exams
that I can't vote as
much as everyone else.
By the way, do I really look
as much like Sorane
as everyone says?
[YOSHIKAWA]
Thank you so much! Time is up.