[REO]
Hi, friends!
We have some really big,
super exciting news to share!
For real. You're not
gonna believe this!
ChamJam has been invited to
perform in an idol festival!
Hello?
[FANS]
Silence.
[MATSUO]
Crap! We already knew that!
[KOSUGA] Their management's
always so behind the ball
on stuff like this!
[FUJIKAWA] We can't let
them find out we found out
when the other artists
posted about it!
Uh, what's up?
Do you guys not think that's
awesome news, or what?
[FANS gasp]
[ALL]
We had no idea!
That's awesome! We'll be there!
[ERIPIYO]
I'll be there a million times!
That information had definitely
been leaked on social media.
There's no other way.
[YUKA]
Ah, don't sweat the small stuff!
Yeah, it's a festival!
Just being invited is
a huge break for us!
I'm happy, sure, but it's
a huge venue, isn't it?
I'm already so nervous.
I mean, there are bigger groups
from other prefectures
going, too, aren't there?
And we're definitely not
the most famous one.
Who knows if they're even
gonna like us or not.
[REO]
It's scary, true.
But still, if we can just
clear this hurdle,
next stop's the Budokan.
[YUKA] What do you mean,
"the next stop"?
The Budokan's so far away!
[MAKI] That's not the main
obstacle here. Oh, Yuka.
[AYA, YUKA, REO laugh]
The Budokan, huh.
Hello to all of Okayama and
Kagawa! Nice to meet you!
I'm ChamJam's Maki Hakata!
Heck yes!
First Reo was on TV, and now,
Maki's following suit!
The front row sure does
get preferential treatment.
So, does that mean
Maina's gonna get
her big TV debut soon, too?
I mean, she did make
it to the front row.
Not that I got to witness that.
[KUMASA] Eripiyo's never
gonna let that one go.
[MOTOI]
Check this out, guys!
I'm here today to share
some exciting news with you.
My group, ChamJam,
is appearing in a festival.
I would love for all of you
to come out and support us!
Wow, she's doing
a fantastic job!
I think the reality of this
news is finally hitting me.
[MOTOI]
Uh. Look.
They really seem to be pushing
this Maple Doll group.
Well, I mean,
it does make sense.
They're the top-billed group
at this festival, after all.
They're from Hiroshima,
but they've already had a
debut with a major label.
And I heard they even hold a
concert in Tokyo once a month.
[ERIPIYO]
Huh.
I've only ever paid attention
to Maina, so I had no idea.
[KUMASA]
The center is Mei.
And, in fact, it just so happens
she was the center in the last
idol group Reo was a part of.
What? That's crazy.
[KUMASA]
Yeah... at the time,
Yoshimune invited me to come
with him to one of their shows.
See, he was a Mei fan,
and since I was at the show with
him, I got into her line, too.
But it was just that one time--
I never had before
and haven't since.
[KUMASA]
Uh.
[gasps]
[KUMASA]
No matter how much time goes by,
Reo can't seem to forget
about that day or let it go.
Even though I've
been a loyal fan
ever since I made that
one stupid choice.
Aw, man.
I'm jealous that you've known
about Reo that long, honestly.
[KUMASA] What? Did they
just ignore my despair?
That hurts, man.
'Cause not only did I miss
Maina's front row debut,
but I also never got to
witness the first moment
she ever stood onstage.
It makes me sad to think that
there are facets of Maina
that I'll never know.
I didn't get to celebrate
her first birthday.
Or any of her early birthdays.
I don't even know how she felt
at her elementary
school graduation.
Like, sometimes I wish
I had given birth to Maina
myself, you know?
Because if I were her mom,
I could've been her fan from
the very beginning of her life.
[MOTOI]
Uh...
By the way, Kumasa, question.
What are these idol
festivals even like?
I'm curious. Never
been to one before.
Idol festivals?
They're kinda like a fun
ChamJam event with more groups.
[ERIPIYO] Hello? Are you guys
ignoring my despair?
And, to be frank, you might
be forced to confront
some cold, hard truths
about your fave.
[MOTOI]
Huh?
For instance, a rude
awakening could be in store
about just how difficult it is
to get to where Maple is now.
Or that the Budokan may well be
but a dream within a dream.
That could hit hard.
♪♪
Huh? Aya, what are you watching?
[REO gasps]
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
I brought a gift from Kagawa.
Yay!
[MAKI]
Wait. Only Yuka cares?
You all asked me for something
even though Kagawa's
basically next door.
I'm a big fan of souvenirs.
And it's always
nice to get them.
I wonder what the
present could be!
What the--?
Udon?
[MIANA, YUKA, SORANE, YUMERI]
Of course that's what it is.
But, like, when are we
supposed to boil it?
We have our special
fan event after this.
Well, we appear in order
for the fan event.
Maybe one of the later people
can come back here and do it.
But we don't know how
long that will take,
and by the time
we get back here,
the noodles might be all soggy.
More importantly, don't
we need to figure out
how we would boil them?
[MAKI] Should I see if I can get
a big pot from the office?
[MAINA]
I'm pretty sure they don't have
anything like that here.
[YUKA]
To the hundred-yen shop!
[MAKI] Who's gonna take it home
with them when we're done?
[YUMERI] I would need
a container from home.
I'd be happy to take it.
That is, if you
guys wouldn't mind.
[AYA]
Ugh!
Who freakin' cares
about udon? Like...
How can you all be so cavalier?
Just take a look at this.
We were on the same level
as Maple when we started,
but now when they perform,
their crowds fill
entire shopping malls.
Their songs and dances are
super similar to ours,
so who's to say our fans
aren't gonna see them
and ditch us for them?
I mean, you saw how they reacted
when we announced the festival.
Didn't that make you guys
a little bit nervous?
Aya, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you
feel bad about that.
It's not your fault, Reo.
There's no point in
apologizing to me.
We have no choice.
We just have to step
up our practice.
I'm going to buy the pot.
[phone rings]
[gasps]
Sorry. Been waiting long?
Not at all.
I guess more people have
been recognizing you
since you were on TV.
That girl'll be at the festival.
That's great.
[MAKI]
What's wrong?
Huh? Oh, nothing's wrong.
I'm glad.
I love seeing that more people
seem to be admiring
you these days.
It makes me feel so proud.
It started with the
popularity ranking, huh?
[YUMERI gasps]
What if the loser has to do
what the winner says?
How 'bout it?
That's right!
I'm supposed to be doing
whatever you say, aren't I?
[MAKI]
You finally remembered.
I've had something in
mind for a while now.
I was wondering when you were
gonna bring it up again.
[YUMERI]
What then?
Is it even something I can do?
[MAKI] Yeah. I have
no doubt about that.
And I think the
timing's perfect.
From now on, I want you to
try and surpass me, Yume.
Huh?
But I... can't do that.
Then try to stand
right beside me.
It might be hard at this
festival, but still.
You'll do it.
When we make it to the Budokan.
You think so?
Okay!
[AYA]
Pathetic!
You are totally off the beat!
And you've got to
energize your moves!
Again! From the top, please!
Come on! You look like amateurs!
I'm exhausted!
I have to take a break!
[AYA] You're one of our
best dancers, Yuka.
You've got to set an example!
How about I do all the
moves, but smaller
so I don't wear myself out?
I'm tired!
I don't see why I have to go
full-out every time we dance!
You're such a tyrant!
[AYA]
Am not!
[BOTH yelling]
Stop yelling!
[SORANE] Hold for a beat,
then step to the right.
Try putting your hips
into it a little bit more.
Oh, yeah, good call.
[GIRLS] ♪ And even if the people
laugh at us and make us cry ♪
[KUMASA]
Reo!
[GIRLS] ♪ We'll keep singing in
the shining spotlight always!  ♪
Go Maki!
[FUJIKAWA, KOSUGA]
All right! Aya!
[GIRLS]
Yeah!
Wow!
Okay!
All right!
Yeah, Maina!
Don't you think Cham's dancing
was exceptional today?
So then, you noticed
it, too, huh?
Yeah, they were a lot
more together than usual.
They must be working extra
hard for the festival.
[ERIPIYO]
Right. No messing around today.
Not that I ever mess around,
but since Maina's been working
so hard for the festival,
I'm gonna wow her with my words!
I'll say the best words ever!
All right, Maina, listen up.
O... kay?
So, like, I know
we're not close,
and I'm just one of
your many ferns--
[ERIPIYO]
Oh, God.
...your many fans. And, um...
In my heart,
no one can compare.
You will always be the homely--
[ERIPIYO]
Oh, God! No!
I mean, the only one for me!
Thanks, I guess?
[ERIPIYO]
The fartstival can't change--
Kill me.
Sorry. I mean--
[YOSHIKAWA grunts]
Thank you. Your time is up!
[ERIPIYO]
I'm a failure.
[YOSHIKAWA] I said,
thank you. Your time is up.
[ERIPIYO]
Gloom...
[MAINA]
Hold on. Eripiyo, wait!
[ERIPIYO]
No way!
Maina stopped me from
leaving--it's a miracle!
Will you come to the festival?
[ERIPIYO]
Of course. She must be nervous!
I'll say the perfect thing
to put her mind at ease.
Of source I kill.
Wha...?
And... that's all she wrote.
Thank you. Hope to see
you again soon.
[ERIPIYO]
She's gonna think I'm an idiot!
[YOSHIKAWA]
Move along. Exit's that way.
Oh, hey, Shakespeare.
Did you wow her
with your words?
Sure did. With how
much they sucked.
[yells]
I wasted all my tickets! Ah!
Hey, I'm sure it
wasn't that bad.
I need a freakin' time machine!
Someone invent one now!
[KUMASA] It couldn't have
been bad enough to warrant
ripping a hole in the
space-time continuum.
[wails]
[ERIPIYO]
Maina!
Of source I kill.
[ERIPIYO screams]
[ERIPIYO]
You will always be the homely--
[screams]
[ERIPIYO]
Huh?
T-TV?!
Eh...?
[ERIPIYO] Sorane has no idea
where you even live, Motoi!
Eri, what are you
yelling about now?
Can you keep it down?
[ERIPIYO]
Miyu!
I'm freaking out because someone
I like's gonna be on TV tonight.
Wanna come watch it with me?
What? Since when do you
have feelings, Eri?
[ERIPIYO] Uh, since
spring three years ago.
So, um, will you come watch them
on TV with me tonight, then?
You bet! I love other
people's business!
[COMMERCIAL A]
Another drink won't kill you...
[MIYU]
I know I agreed to come over,
but now that I think about it,
why do I need to be here?
I have my own TV at home--I
could just watch it from there.
I just wanna watch
it with you, okay?
Because, like, I might puke
the moment she comes on TV!
[MIYU]
I should've stayed home.
[ERIPIYO]
Uh! Oh, man. Crap.
It's about to start.
And what are you so
nervous about anyway?
Don't you see this person
in real life all the time?
I guess so.
But seeing them on TV for the
first time is super special!
Idols from all around Setouchi
will appear at the
Setouchi Idol Festival.
And, no, this cute deer
is not one of them.
Here's the group
to watch this year.
The headliners!
Aren't they the cutest?
Hiroshima's own Maple Doll!
[GIRLS]
Hello, there!
[ANNOUNCER A] How about a
few words from their leader?
Welcome, Mei!
[MEI]
Thanks!
Of course, I do hope everyone
comes to the festival to see us,
but it's also a great
opportunity to find out
about other idol groups
from the area.
Are there any in particular
to look out for?
Let's see. I mean, they're
all cute and talented.
But I'd have to say Moko
from Time Machine Pudding.
[ERIPIYO grunts]
I can barely even
breathe anymore.
I wish they would just hurry up
and get this whole
thing over with.
So hold on, the person you
like hasn't come on yet
and you're this worked up?
Yes, because I know that they're
gonna come on eventually!
And I don't think my
heart is prepared
for that to happen yet!
[MIYU]
Hm?
[ANNOUNCER A] And that was
Maple Doll from Hiroshima!
Here are some of the other
fabulous idol groups
set to appear at this
year's festival.
What a lineup, am I right?
[gasps]
There she is.
Maina was...
Maina was just on TV!
Oh, jeez. My little Maina!
She's coming into her own.
She's worked so hard.
And come so far.
I'm just grateful to have loved
you for three whole years!
Maina! I love your past,
your present, your future!
And you obviously shine so much
brighter than the other girls.
This just means
you were destined
to get more and more
fans around the world!
[MIYU]
Okay, so, I gather that you like
some idol girl or something.
I mean, I don't judge.
You should hear about
some of my hobbies.
But, um...
You're being kinda
creepy about it.
[MIYU] She screamed herself
into a wild-eyed frenzy
and passed the eff out.
Why did I come over?
♪♪
Huh?
I'll use my magic
to idolize you!
[ERIPIYO]
Miyu!
So, what did you
think of the show?
[MIYU]
What do you mean?
I didn't even know what I was
supposed to be watching.
[ERIPIYO]
Seriously?
But I have no idea when they're
gonna be on TV again!
I will say, that last night
while watching TV at your house,
something strange happened.
I think I fell in love, too.
You did?
This is my Fuyutaro!
And I'm head over heels
for him right now!
[FUYUTARO]
I'll idolize you!
What? That guy?
[MIYU]
Bless my magical boy!
I know he and I were
never meant to be,
but that's just a minor detail.
I love him with all my heart,
though the gulf of the
LCD display between us
is as vast as the
Milky Way itself.
[ERIPIYO]
Mh-hm! I feel the same!
'Scuse me? Watch out! I'll
idolize the crap out of you!
Wait! What's that mean?
[MIYU]
Just be grateful you live
in the same dimension
as your idol
and stay the hell
away from mine!
'Kay. My bad.
[ALL]
Ready, and...
[ERIPIYO grunts]
None of our numbers
are that great.
You think we'll be able to
get spots in the front row?
[KUMASA] Well, it's a festival,
so that should help a little.
The fans won't all be there
to see every group,
so they'll shuffle around,
based on who they stan.
That's true.
But then, if people who've
never seen Cham have good spots,
then the fan base could grow
exponentially from this!
And I want everyone there to see
how freakin' cute
Maina is up close!
She's cute from far away, too.
I just mean some
idols are Monets.
Oh, yeah! Did you guys
draw for the new prints?
Maina's is even cuter than
the last, believe it or not.
[MOTOI]
Wait, how'd you get so many?!
[ERIPIYO]
I'll never tell.
I'm just so thankful.
[MOTOI]
Thankful for what?
My friend told me to
be eternally grateful
that the fates allowed
me to be born
in the same dimension
as the one I love.
Huh?
For instance,
I'm thankful knowing that Maina
was alive and breathing
in the same realm as me at the
moment this photo was taken.
It's just so amazing!
I'm having trouble
following your logic.
I'm not! It's science!
Say what?
[BOTH] Science gave them good
genes and we are grateful!
[MOTOI]
Uh...
[sighs]
I just wanna share this feeling
with as many people as possible.
Truly, this is nothing short
of an absolute miracle to me.
You really like to toss
that word around, huh?
Listen, if you really wanna
share your feelings,
then maybe you should
tweet about it.
Oh! Is that what you're supposed
to use Twittan for then?
[MOTOI] You've never really
tweeted, have you?
[ERIPIYO] I only created an
account because someone said
Maina needed more followers.
Right. Here I go.
What the heck am
I supposed to say?
You had plenty to
say a minute ago.
Just put it in a tweet
and hit send already.
[ERIPIYO] But what if something
bad were to happen to Maina
because I tweeted about her?
Or what if someone responded
and said that Maina's fans
were creepy and gross?
I don't wanna make her look bad.
You? Worry about
what people think?
[REO]
Great! I think we look good.
Yeah! You've earned
some break time!
Who died and appointed
you queen?
[REO chuckles]
[YUKA]
You guys!
Our dancing is really
coming together, huh?
At this rate, we're totes gonna
kick butt at the festival!
Heck yeah we are, buddy.
Practice really does
pay off, am I right?
Our popularity might
explode after this!
You bet. I won't rest
until it does!
[MAINA] I'm the only one still
having trouble keeping up.
I don't even deserve to
be on a smaller stage,
let alone one in a
big festival venue.
[ANNOUNCER A] Are there any
in particular to look out for?
Let's see. I mean, they're
all cute and talented.
But I'd have to say Moko
from Time Machine Pudding.
She's an amazing
singer and dancer,
and I hear she likes Mandarins.
Maybe 'cause she's from Ehime!
[REO] For a second there,
I got my hopes up.
I thought maybe Mei
was gonna say my name
and say those nice
things about me.
Not like she has to.
Just wishful thinking, I guess.
[phone dings]
[MAINA]
No way! Eripiyo!
She's never tweeted before,
and her first one's about me?
[gasps]
Huh?
[ERIPIYO] Part Four:
Her hand is always so warm
and soft when I shake it.
Part Five: She never fails
to find something
cute and fun to blog about.
Part Six: Even though
she didn't do well
in the popularity ranking,
she didn't let it faze her
and kept smiling.
Part Seven: When she says hello,
it's the sweetest sound
to ever bless my ears!
Part Eight: When she bows,
we get to see how adorable
the top of her head is.
This is so sweet.
But I'm nothing without all
the other members of ChamJam.
[YOSHIKAWA grunting]
[MISAKI] Mr. Yoshikawa,
what in the world are--?
[YOSHIKAWA] Readying my
stopwatch for the festival.
[MUROTA] Next episode's
the last one, you know.
[YOSHIKAWA] Man!
I was gearing up for more!
[MUROTA]
What, so you could say,
"Thank you! Your time's up!"
a dozen more times?