[singing in Japanese]
[CROWD]
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Maina!
[sighs]
[REO] All right, then!
Time for the Q&A!
You ready?
[CROWD]
Yeah!
Great! Here's our
first question.
Mocchi Heart, from Kita,
wants to know this:
Back in high school did
you belong to any clubs?
If so, which ones?
Who first? Sorane?
Huh? Oh, me?
I was in...  Well, there
was the tennis club!
Seriously?
Gah!
Tennis is so lame!
[KUMASA laughs]
[KUMASA]
Well, what can ya do?
We're superfans, not gods.
We can't control what our
idols are interested in.
Man, if I had the chance,
I'd die and be reincarnated
and be Maina's classmate!
So you would die right
now just for that, huh?
Why do you always have
to be so dramatic?
She was in the "go
straight home" club.
Uh, that's a euphemism
for a lazy bum.
It means Maina
wasn't in any clubs.
I don't care.
Maybe she was a rebel.
No one who dances like that
could've been in
some preppy club.
Sorry? You lost me.
Dances like what?
How dare you both
pretend not to notice
how she dances like a goddess.
Man, if Eripiyo's reincarnation
idea really happened,
I'd come back as a
powerful record exec,
and then I'd give Reo
a mainstream debut!
Great idea!
Huh? Do you guys understand
the implications of all that?
Anyway, I just wanna make
Sorane happy in this life.
Huh?
What're you sayin'?
[MOTOI] I'll work hard and make
enough to support us both!
She'll stay home and
make amazing meals
for us to enjoy together!
Perfect!
Welcome home, my husband.
[MOTOI]
That's my dearest wish!
Oh, no. Poor Motoi thinks
he's gonna marry his idol.
[MOTOI]
Uh.
Wait--what'd I say?
Is that weird?
[ERIPIYO, KUMASA]
Yeah. It's weird.
[MOTOI]
Huh...?
Whoa... Hey, check that out!
[KUMASA]
Huh?
You would never even know
that some of those girls
performed in the Girls' Festa.
Judging by that line.
Our place in line are
assigned at random today.
So I figured we wouldn't need
to get here super early,
but still, this turnout
seems pathetic, you know?
All right, folks!
Ticket distribution starts now!
[KUMASA]
Yep. This seems about right.
[MOTOI]
Hm? Ah!
Gah! Vomit!
[sighs]
Well, there aren't that
many people here,
so my number's more like 30.
And I was planning to watch from
the back today anyway, so...
[MOTOI]
Hey, um, Eripiyo?
[KUMASA] I "mustache" you
everyone's burning question.
What's goin' on with
that creepy get-up?
Are you joining the circus?
Ugh. Read much?
Maina gave a great interview
in this month's Mellow Magazine.
[MAINA]
Someone who's tall
and looks good in
dapper scarves, and...
Oh! I'd be over-the-moon if
they had a neat mustache!
See? Maina said so herself!
That's her ideal type, you know?
I hear that, but I think she
was referring to her ideal guy.
Gender is only a construct
when it comes to
matters of the heart.
My love for Maina
transcends such minutiae.
[KUMASA]
Oh. Cool.
[MOTOI] You know,
I gotta hand it to Maina.
She totally described someone
you'd never find in
a Cham Jam crowd.
She's so smart!
My Maina is the most brilliant,
capable idol in the world!
[KUMASA]
Wait just a minute!
My Reo would never be so foolish
as to give such an
oddly specific answer.
She's far too wise for all that.
[REO] My ideal partner would be
whomever I happen to fall for!
Uh, but if I had to be specific,
someone who's kind.
Heh. Still too generic?
See?
[ERIPIYO]
Shut up!
To each their own!
Maina's perfect!
She can answer
however she wants
and it will always be right!
[KUMASA]
A Maina stan at all costs,
even at the expense
of her dignity.
[GIRL A laughing]
[BOY A]
They're kinda funny lookin'.
[REO laughs]
[REO]
Hello, there!
--[YUMERI] How are you doing?
--[SORANE] Thanks for coming!
[AYA] I mean, nothing beats
oba leaves as a filling!
They've got powerful
medicinal properties!
[ERIPIYO]
Good morning, Maina.
Still the cutest in
the universe, I see.
[MAINA gasps]
You look...
Oh, this? I'm trying
out a new look.
I wanna be your type.
[gasps]
[MAINA] I never said
stilts were my type!
That Mellow piece. You described
this as your ideal type.
[gasps]
[MAINA]
Oh, that?
Those things are so silly.
[ERIPIYO]
Mh-mh.
You could have written anything
and I would've tried to be it.
The truth is,
I was just so happy
to be able to read
your words at all.
I could barely contain myself!
Uh. Hey, Eripiyo?
So I am going to do
whatever it takes
to become your ideal man, Maina!
You don't have to do anything!
Uh.
[ERIPIYO] Are you saying
there's no point in trying?
I'm nothing more
than a fan to you?
[MAINA]
I don't want you to change.
I want you to stay
exactly as you are.
[ERIPIYO] Uh, in one of the
wish strips I sent you,
I wished you would
go mainstream.
[ERIPIYO] Wait, did I just sound
impatient for a reply?
[MAINA]
Oh, you did?
You want me to break
into the mainstream?
[ERIPIYO]
Uh, yeah.
[MAINA] Then why didn't she
send me any of these wishes?
[ERIPIYO] I want you
to be front and center
and perform in
all kinds of stuff,
'cause that's what you deserve!
Also, I want you to
go to the Budokan.
I'm flattered.
[MAINA] But all I really wanted
was a letter from you, Eripiyo.
I'll spend my entire
paycheck on you!
Every last yen is yours!
[MAINA]
That's not what I want.
[MUROTA]
Thank you, come see us again.
Oh. Eripiyo.
Hey, there you are.
How'd it go with Maina?
I'm not sure what to
make of that hand signal.
[ERIPIYO]
She wasn't actually cold to me,
but I'm sure it seemed that way
from the outside looking in.
Maina, is there nothing
I can do to make you smile,
just for me?
Come on! Hurry!
Slow down!
[KUMASA]
Eripiyo?
[sighs]
It just hit me that
they're people, too.
[KUMASA, MOTOI]
What?
[ERIPIYO] Behind their smiles,
it's totally up to them
whether they love
you or hate you.
Don't you guys find that
absolutely terrifying?
It didn't occur to me to
be scared until now--thanks!
Well, great--how am I
supposed to think about
anything else now?
Look, it just occurred
to me, too!
I couldn't be alone with
this kind of despair--
I had to share it!
Look, I felt really
bad for triggering
your existential crisis,
so I found a way to
see Cham this week
during their promotional
activities.
Oh-ho!
And unlike the event at
the zoo the other day,
we can line up
in order this time.
Here's the catch:
It's at a mall in the boonies.
Even if we took the first train,
the earliest we could get there
is an hour before they start
handing out the tickets.
And that makes me nervous.
So I was thinking we could
stay at an internet café
in the area the night before.
How does that plan
sound to you?
[KUMASA]
You know me, kid, I'm in.
Even if it is in the
boonies, I'm down.
I'll be right up front,
cheering my head off!
Okay. It's on.
[BOTH]
Let's live our best lives!
[KUMASA snoring]
[MOTOI] What time are you
getting there today?
Let's line up together.
[chuckles]
[ERIPIYO]
Too bad! Way ahead of you!
We're out in the boonies,
camping out for a prime spot!
[MOTOI]
The boonies?
But they're supposed to be
playing in the city today.
Wha...?
Wait.
[ERIPIYO]
Oh, no. I got the wrong week!
You can't be serious!
Huh?
[KUMASA]
You sounded so confident
that it didn't even occur
to me to double check!
Why wouldn't I believe you?
[ERIPIYO]
You should've checked anyway!
I'm not infallible,
and she's your favorite!
Well, what about you?!
How can you call yourself
Maina's top stan?!
It isn't like I did
this on purpose!
Man! Every frikkin' stop?
I wish they would let me
drive this stupid train!
[ERIPIYO]
Streetcar?
No. We'll get there
faster if we run!
Come on, really stretch
your legs, Kumasa!
[KUMASA] I can't!
Don't you see how fat I am?
[KUMASA]
Please. Let's give up already.
If we walk normally,
we'll make it in time for
the special fan event.
What?
Am I some rich girl
who does this
'cause she has too much
time on her hands?
Am I?
But if you're tuckered out,
I'll run on ahead without you.
Come on, tracksuit!
Let's relive our glory days!
I saw this coming...
but it still stings.
[FANS cheering, applauding]
Hi, lovely people!
We're Cham Jam!
[FANS]
Yeah! We know!
[MAINA gasps]
[MAINA] Eripiyo's not there
in the front row.
I wonder where she is.
Here's our first song!
Sing along if you know it!
[FANS cheering]
[FANS]
One, two, three, four!
[MAINA]
There's Eripiyo.
Why is she so far back?
And she's soaking wet.
Did she fall into a river?
Maybe that's why she's late.
[ERIPIYO]
Uh.
Another girl?
I've never seen one here before.
[RENA]
She's really sweaty.
[ERIPIYO]
Wait, Maina.
Your pulse.
Normal. Good.
[MAINA]
Yeah.
[MAINA] Seems like Eripiyo
might be testing the waters.
I'm not sure how to respond.
[YOSHIKAWA]
That's it for today, everyone!
See you at the studio!
Till tomorrow, then!
[MAINA]
Eripiyo.
[YUKA]
I'm wide open here!
Come hit me up!
[FUMI]
Hey.
I'm here, aren't I?
[YUKA] Obviously, but you're in
my line literally all the time.
You're basically invisible
to me at this point.
Man. She's so confident.
Makes sense. She is most popular
of the back-row squad.
Do you have to
call it that? Jeez.
Oh, right, sorry.
I wish I could be
like Yuka, too.
[AYA]
No, it wouldn't suit you.
Your sweetness is your
main selling point.
Ha. You think so?
I'm wide open!
Hit me up, people!
Uh.
Really, though. Wide open.
[MAINA]
Yeah. I'd just look pathetic.
[YOSHIKAWA]
Maina, here's one for you!
Hm?
[MAINA]
Wow, it's a girl!
Hello! Nice to meet you!
Uh. Nice to meet you, too.
This was actually my very first
time seeing idols perform live.
Oh, really? So how did
you find out about us?
[MOTOI]
Oh, I see.
You just mixed this week's
schedule up with next week's.
I feel dumb. I should
always check just in case.
'Sup, Motoi?
[MOTOI]
Hey.
Oh. My little sister, Rena.
Hello.
You brought your sister?
Nice to meet ya.
I saw you in the back earlier.
I couldn't stand up
front. Too nervous.
I, uh-- I'm not really sure
if I should say this, but...
[RENA]
Huh?
[ERIPIYO]
She looks just like Sorane.
[MOTOI yelping]
Wait, isn't Sorane
the one that you like?
Well, that's creepy.
[MOTOI]
No! Shut up! You're wrong!
Well, you're right
that I like Sorane,
but the likeness is
just a coincidence!
Yeah, I get it.
So, who's your favorite
Cham Jam girl?
My fave?
Lemme see... The one I saw when
I went to the Girls' Festa.
I thought Maina looked prettier
than any of the
other girls there.
[gasps]
Maina? For real?
You hear that?
Someone else picked up on her
ethereal beauty and grace!
Aw yeah! I win! I win! I win!
Yay, good for you.
[ERIPIYO] Rena! At tomorrow's
show, let's line up together!
[chuckles]
[MISAKI]
Thank you so much for coming!
[gasps] I forgot!
I bought them all on autopilot
without thinking of Rena!
I hope she won't be mad at me.
Um, Eripiyo?
Hi, Rena.
Uh, they told me, um, they're
sold out of Maina's merch.
Do you think maybe you'd
be willing to share yours?
It's my fault! So of course!
How many do you want?
Huh? Just one is fine.
[ERIPIYO]
Just one, really?
Yeah.
Maina's line, single file,
along the wall!
So what did you and Maina
talk about yesterday?
Huh? Girls' Festa, and I said
I'd always support her.
That's it.
[ERIPIYO]
Nice! And how'd she respond?
[MAINA] I'm so happy to
finally have a girl fan!
I hope you come back!
I'll be waiting!
[RENA]
So...
Huh...?
[YUMERI]
Hello!
[MAINA] Uh! It's the young
girl from yesterday!
Uh! She and Eripiyo
seem really close.
What's going on? And why?
All right! Maina's
handshakes start now!
Hello! Can't wait to meet you!
[YOSHIKAWA] Everyone in line,
please step forward.
I'm so nervous.
You've got this! Yeah!
Maina's a little shy, but if
you initiate conversation,
she'll totally answer,
so don't be afraid to speak up!
And if you run out of
things to talk about,
just compliment her on her
dancing--she loves that!
[RENA]
Hello.
[MAINA]
Hello! You came to see me again!
Did you have fun
at the show today?
[RENA]
Uh. Yeah.
[ERIPIYO] Maina's chatting
her up like an old pro!
I'm so proud!
[RENA] I'm glad they brought
me. It's been awesome.
[MAINA]
Eripiyo brought her?
Wow. You and Eripiyo
must be really close
if she's willing
to bring you here.
That's great.
Really close?
No. She and my brother
know each other.
I only just met her.
Oh, that makes sense!
[ERIPIYO yelps]
[ERIPIYO] Maina's having
more fun talking to Rena
than I've ever witnessed before!
Everyone should fall
in love with Maina.
I want her to belong to us all!
[ERIPIYO]
I never considered this
because for so long,
I was the only Maina stan.
Thanks so much!
[ERIPIYO]
But, like...
Please come see me again!
[ERIPIRO]
Right now?
I don't ever want Maina to smile
at anyone else besides me!
[MAINA]
Did I act too excited?
Eripiyo was watching.
I hope she's not mad.
[ERIPIYO]
Just one.
Just one?
[YOSHIKAWA]
[ERIPIYO]
I mean,
if Rena got all that
attention with one ticket...
...so should I.
Why just one?
[ERIPIYO] Actually,
I have 28 more tickets.
[ERIPIYO] In order for her
to get to the Budokan,
she has to get more popular.
I can't do anything
to help her get there
if I keep her to myself.
When did this happen?
When did I become
such a selfish jerk?
[MAINA] There's something
bothering Eripiyo.
I can tell.
Eripiyo? Do you, um,
well, like me?
Huh? Of course I do!
I love you, in fact!
I tell you all the time, right?
[MAINA] I mean it in a different
way than you do.
[YOSHIKAWA] Thank you so much,
folks, that's a wrap!
[ERIPIYO] Maina, was
something wrong today?
[MOTOI]
Eripiyo!
We're waiting for you!
[ERIPIYO]
Rena.
Yes?
From an OG Maina stan
to a newbie,
I hope we can continue to share
our mutual love for her.
Yeah, me, too.
I'm looking forward to it.
Though I won't be able
to come by that often.
Oh, well, isn't that a shame!
Such a shame!
[ERIPIYO] Stop it!
Don't let on that you're happy!
Yeah. College entrance exams.
Oh. I see.
[bell ringing]
[gasps]
[ERIPIYO]
Maina in the wild?
I've never seen her like this!
A white dress. Normal clothes.
I've never imagined her
not in salmon pink.
[ERIPIYO]
An angel.
Right here in this train car,
a real-life miracle!
Sorry. I can change cars.
Next stop's mine, anyway.
Um. Okay.
Thank you.
For, um, always
coming to see me.
And coming to shake
my hand after.
[ERIPIYO] Does she mean:
"Giving me your undying support"
and "Cheering me on
no matter what"?
[ERIPIYO] I don't love her
just 'cause she's an idol.
I love her because she's Maina.
That's why I get so scared.
I won't stop. I'll keep coming
to shake your hand.
I love you.
[ERIPIYO]
Everything about you.
I love you!
[FUMI] Yuka, please,
don't get too excited
at the Autumn Sports Festival
and hurt yourself.
What kind of stuff have you
been into lately, Yuka?
Do you like the present
I gave you the other day?
If you want something else,
just write about it in
your blog and I'll get it!
I can't wait to see you again
on Halloween this year!
[YOSHIKAWA]
Thank you! Wrap it up!