[GIRLS giggling]
[AYA]
Excuse me, miss!
We're having a concert on
that stage over there at 2 P.M.
If you're not busy,
you should come!
[MAINA]
That's right.
Um, please come watch!
[ERIPIYO]
I always thought idols
were supposed to be
like dazzling stars.
[ERIPIYO] But things are
rarely what we think.
[REO]
Thank you all so much for coming
to Cham Jam at the
Cherry Blossom Festival!
Truly. We're so
grateful to you all!
[GUYS]
Yeah!
[REO]
It's such a relief!
I had no idea what
we were going to do
if nobody had shown up today!
Honestly, I never
worried for a second.
[REO]
What? For real?
Reo, you are kind
of a worry wart.
Yeah, you should really
learn how to relax.
[REO]
I don't know how!
[gasps]
[giggles]
[heart beating]
[ERIPIYO]
But you?
You were far more dazzling
than I ever could've imagined.
And that afternoon, your
brilliance nearly killed me.
[MOTOI]
That's amazing, Kumasa!
You've already got
a full Reo set?
See, that's what makes
you a famous otaku .
No, no.
I could never have gotten there
without all your help, Motoi.
Here you go.
The Sorane I promised you.
[MOTOI]
Thanks, man!
I really wish they'd stop
giving us all these randos.
It's gettin' old.
[KUMASA] I dunno, at least
they're part of a photo set
and not some lame
CD extra or something.
I'm pretty sure you're
the first to collect
all the pics of your fave,
ss far as I know.
I mean, each girl has 20 shots.
Nope, someone I know collected
all 20 of their
favorites at once,
if you can believe it.
They didn't even have
to trade or anything.
Isn't that crazy?
Wha--?
Wait, you've gotta be
talking about that, uh,
that Maina fan.
Oh, man.
[SORANE] We're doing a
concert right over there
at that theater!
You should totally come
see us, if you can!
Oh. Hey, guys!
You are coming to see us
again today, I hope.
Sorane.
Yup!
So, uh, is Reo gonna be
performing with you today?
Why? Are we not enough
for you or something?
[MOTOI] Of course you are!
More than enough!
[KUMASA] Yeah. You two are
adorable in your own right.
[giggles]
[gasps]
Maina?
[SORANE gasps]
[MOTOI gasps]
[KUMASA]
Oh, hey, Eripiyo!
Hang on. I could've sworn I saw
Maina with you just now.
[KUMASA]
You did.
She was just here,
handing out fliers.
What?!
Then it's true--
she really is avoiding me?
[MOTOI]
She's so extra.
She spends her entire paycheck
on her favorite idol,
and the only outfit she wears
is her track uniform
from high school.
Word on the street is,
newbies to the fandom
tremble at the sight
of her bright red likeness.
They fear the name Eripiyo!
She's an OG fan and the
only true Maina stan.
Hold it, buster!
The only reason it
may seem like Maina
doesn't have any other fans
is that her color is
salmon pink, okay?
[FANS cheering]
[ERIPIYO]
It's a rare color,
and you'd have to
put salmon pink film
into your KING BLADE
to achieve the right hue!
Gotcha.
Also, it only looks like
there are more Reo fans
because her color
is regular pink!
That's blasphemy!
There are more,
'cause Reo's the cutest!
Are you implying
Maina's not the best?
You wanna get your butt kicked?
[whimpers]
[SORANE]
Don't worry about those two.
They're at it all the time.
Anyway, you're one of
my fans, aren't you?
[MOTOI gasps]
You came to see us
two weeks ago.
I'm so happy to see you again!
No way! You actually
remember me?
[SORANE]
Of course I did!
It's only natural that I love
anybody who's faithful to me.
Hey, you wanna come
see a concert?
Sorane.
Hey, Motoi, let's head
over to the theater.
Huh? Won't we be early?
Oh, I see. You're scared...
[KUMASA] Calm down,
Eripiyo. Come with us.
[KUMASA] It's not the best
idea to try and talk to them
while they're handing
out fliers.
Oh. Yeah, that makes
sense. Sorry.
No worries. It's not a hard-
and-fast rule or anything.
Besides, I prefer
to pay for the honor.
I just like the way it feels!
A thousand yen for
five second of bliss!
Gets your blood pumping, right?
Uh. I guess.
I get it--I buy up
all that time with Maina
and then end up spending
a ton more on her merch
while I'm at it.
I'd like to purchase
all of Maina's handshake
tickets, please.
Aren't you afraid monopolizing
all of Maina's time
will kill any chance of her
building up a fanbase, though?
I just wonder why she's
always so cold to me.
I sincerely appreciate
all your support.
Ah! How can I make you like me?
Maina! Maina!
If I may, could it be
that the sheer intensity
of your passion freaks her out?
[MISAKI] We'll be opening
the doors in a moment.
Please be waiting with
your ticket in hand!
And, naturally, you two
are the first in line.
Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
Yeah, we know the drill.
They go in order of when
you purchased your ticket.
You'll get the hang of it soon.
[ERIPIYO] In other words,
they line you up in order
of who wants to see their
favorite the most.
[KUMASA] And how badly
you want world peace.
[ERIPIYO]
And how fast your wifi is!
I'm inspired by you both.
We're officially
opening the doors!
So, who's holding
ticket number one?
Me!
[REO]
Hey, everyone!
Who's ready to have
a great time?
[FANS cheering]
Is there anyone here for
the first time tonight?
[FANS]
Yeah!
A special welcome to you guys!
Reo!
[ERIPIYO]
Maina.
You managed to make it
onstage again tonight.
It's actually kind of strange
that our eyes don't meet,
even though we're so close.
You must be looking
for fans farther back!
Good luck, Maina!
[REO]
Okay!
Let's get things started
with our opening song!
I wanna hear those chants!
[CROWD cheering]
[ALL]
One, two, three, go!
[GIRLS, FANS]
Yeah!
Come on!
[ERIPIYO]
Okay, I'm gonna stan Maina
with everything
I've got again today!
[singing in Japanese]
Sorane.
Huh? Why can't I see Maina?
[ERIPIYO] For two years now,
the distance has felt so vast.
[ERIPIYO]
Get out there.
Step further to
the front, Maina!
Yeah!
Salmon pink, Maina!
Maina! I love you!
[BOTH gasp]
[KUMASA]
Huh?
Eripiyo? Are you... dead?
[ERIPIYO]
Nope. Just a nosebleed.
Wha--? But why right now?
Maina. I love you!
I'm gonna be just fine.
Eripiyo. You just became even
more of a legend than before.
[FANS]
Hey! Hey! Hey! Woo!
[ERIPIYO whines]
[ERIPIYO] The fact that I can
still hear them singing
makes it even more painful!
You're the girl who
comes to every show
to support Maina, right?
The first in line?
Yeah, that's me. Is she
ever happy to see me?
It's okay if she's not.
I don't mind that as long
as she doesn't hate me,
but it's just...
She's cold.
I wish I could help you, but
I can't really speak for her.
[ERIPIYO]
I'm going back in.
But the bleeding
hasn't stopped yet.
[ERIPIYO] She might not care
if I'm there or not,
but I need all the
Maina I can get.
Every minute--no,
every second counts!
I want to soak up
all the Maina I can!
So devoted!
--[ERIPIYO yelps]
--[crack]
[giggles]
[REO]
Thank you. We love you all!
[KUMASA]
Man, that was blast, wasn't it?
Yeah, you could say that again.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[KUMASA] Whoa, I had so
much fun at the concert
that I almost forgot all
about you, Eripiyo!
What's up, guys?
How're ya doing?
You feeling better?
[ERIPIYO]
Don't worry.
I'm still coming to
the special fan event.
Do you really think
that's a good idea?
You should go to the hospital.
Oh. I don't know what
happened to all my CDs.
I'll take ten CD singles.
The ones with Maina's
handshake tickets.
[KUMASA]
Why is she buying more?
[MUROTA] The special
fan event begins now.
I'm gonna be the first
in line for Reo!
Yeah! Guess I should go
line up to talk to Sorane.
[YOSHIKAWA] Maina's line
is right this way!
[YOSHIKAWA]
Right. That's ten yen for Maina.
Um. Hello, again.
[ERIPIYO]
Whoa!
I don't really need a
handshake, I guess.
[MAINA]
Huh?
To be honest, I'm
satisfied just seeing
your beautiful face
up close like this.
The truth is, you are the
most effective pain killer
anybody could ever
ask for, Maina.
[ERIPIYO]
That was a killer line!
[MAINA gasps]
I, um.
Thank you, your time is up!
I appreciate your support.
[ERIPIYO gasps]
[ERIPIYO]
This again? But why?
[OTAKU B] Maina, what's your
favorite internal organ?
Uh, well.
[ERIPIYO]
Maina, why do you torture me?
[KUMASA]
Climbing up these stairs
is like stepping
back into reality.
So, how was it talking
to Reo today?
She's a total goddess!
Called me Kuma Bear!
Uh. Oh, I take it Maina
was as cold as ever, then?
It's fine. She's just
shy, that's all.
My sweet, salmon pink girl.
I love you so much, Maina!
Forever!
[ERIPIYO]
Oh. That one's flipped.
I just don't understand.
Do you see this new flier!
Every other girl has a flower
or fruit to go with their color,
but Maina gets a salmon steak?
What do you want me to say?
Her color is salmon pink.
There's nothing
cute about that!
So, what, Maina's symbol
is lean protein?
What am I supposed to do,
wrap a salmon around
my KING BLADE?
It's a total pain to
change the film color.
So, should I stuff some
salmon in there?
Are Maina fans expected to wear
clothes with salmon on them now?
No one expects you to wear
anything but that track suit,
so no worries there.
[ERIPIYO]
That is beside the point!
If I were a producer,
I would never give her
such a ridiculous color.
She'd get to dazzle everyone,
like the Aurora Borealis!
If you were their producer,
you'd have to at least
try to hide your bias.
Mama.
We're super excited to unveil
our new song tomorrow!
[FANS]
We can't wait!
We're going to hold a special
fan event in our new outfits!
If you buy five CDs, you get
an instant camera photo op!
We've been waiting for so long!
[REO]
Oh, one more thing.
We have some top-secret
work to do tomorrow
after the fan event,
so unfortunately,
we'll have to shorten
the meet n' greet a little bit.
[FANS]
What?
And that means the merchandise
will be more limited, as well.
Show up early
before tickets run out!
[AYA] Yeah, we'd hate to miss
the opportunity to meet you!
[MAKI] We're looking
forward to the photo-op,
and we hope you are, too!
This is a total emergency.
What is?
Sorry, I was distracted by the
fact that Maina wasn't talking.
What's up?
Five CDs per person,
and fewer CDs than usual.
So, according to
my calculations...
...we have to rush to
get our hands on them
before supplies run out!
[KUMASA]
Yeah. Sounds like a plan.
Great minds think alike,
but fools seldom differ.
Indeed.
We can't risk the CDs selling
out before we get 'em.
I mean, a photo op
in their new get-ups?
Cham like never
gets new outfits!
I know, right?
[KUMASA]
Well, summer is almost here,
I'm sure their new costumes
will reflect the season.
[ERIPIYO]
Yes, exactly!
[KUMASA]
It sure is sunny out today.
It's gonna get hot.
Well, we're in the shade,
at least, so that's good.
I'm glad this event's
below street level.
Yeah, we're lucky they're
an underground group!
[KUMASA] I mean, I do hope they
become more mainstream someday.
[ERIPIYO] Hopefully their CDs
get wider distribution.
[ALL groaning]
[ERIPIYO] How long till
the merch booth opens?
[KUMASA]
Seven more hours.
[ERIPIYO]
Welp, guess I'll die.
Yeah, the air really doesn't
circulate down here, does it?
[NARRATOR] On this June
day in Okayama City,
where Eripiyo and
the others live,
the temperatures soared,
reaching record-breaking highs.
I can't take it anymore!
You've got this!
Remember the photo op!
[MATSUO] Is all this
suffering really worth
one little photo op?
I mean, we're gonna
see their new outfits
at the show anyway!
[BOTH gasp]
[OTAKU E] That's the one line
we're never supposed to cross!
[OTAKU F] No. He said
the quiet part out loud!
We're here to memorialize
this moment
when our favorites reserved
special time just for us!
[KUMASA]
If you decide to leave now,
all the time you've spent
waiting will have been in vain.
But go on.
I'm sure that your favorite
won't doubt your
dedication to her.
[MATSUO gasps]
[OTAKU E]
This guy knows what...
[MOTOI] The OG fans are
seriously on another level!
[ERIPIYO] It's so hot that
I'm not even really sure
what's going on anymore.
But I know this:
Kumasa's the coolest!
[OTAKU F]
I'm not gonna make it.
[REO]
Good morning, everyone!
Thank you all for
showing up here so early!
[ALL gasp]
[MAKI]
Good morning!
[YUMERI, AYA]
Okay! We'll see you
all in there!
[OTAKU G]
Oh, man, they're so cute!
Are you okay? Maina just
walked right by you.
It's embarrassing.
I don't want Maina to realize
that I'm the first in line
to buy her merch again.
Wha--? What's gotten
into you all of a sudden?
I'm sure Maina would be thrilled
that you braved this
heat to be the first
to get a photo op with her!
I'm a freak.
No, really, what's
gotten into you?
[ERIPIYO]
I just told you.
[KUMASA] You've been
a freak for two years.
Why worry now?
[NARRATOR] At 1500 hours, their
exhaustion reached its peak.
[KUMASA]
My butt is melting off.
[FANS yelling]
Ah! This ice cream is awesome!
I've had 60 now.
[NARRATOR] The pain has passed
and transformed into delirium.
The merch booth is now open!
[MISAKI] First in line, you can
approach the table now.
Here you go. Five for Maina,
is that right?
But I haven't even
said anything yet!
[MISAKI]
Here's your photo op ticket.
Your reward for buying five
copies of the new single!
[chuckles]
[ERIPIYO] It looks like we only
get one photo op today.
Yeah, that's fine with me.
As long as the new
outfits are cute.
I'll just treasure it even more.
[ERIPIYO]
Huh?
Hang on, this means that
I'm all drenched in sweat
for my one picture with her!
Maina's gonna see my
puffy, red, tomato face.
I was so worried about
getting here on time
that I forgot to wear makeup!
Oh, crap. I bet I have
major B.O., too.
[ERIPIYO]
I bet I smell like onions.
[REO]
Hey, guys!
Thanks so much for
coming out today!
Now, here it is!
Our first new song
in four whole months!
[ERIPIYO] Their outfits
aren't cute at all.
[MASUDA] How long will
they be wearing these?
[MATSUO] Any one of us could've
come up with outfits
500 times better than these.
All right. We hope you like it!
Here's "Hot Summer Holiday"!
She's so cute she'd look
good in a burlap sack!
The special fan
event starts now!
We'll take the Reo and Sorane
photo op ticket holders first.
Yay! Hey, Kumasa!
[YOSHIKAWA]
Everyone in line for Maina,
please wait over here.
[ERIPIYO] My first photo
op in four months.
Crap! I'm sweating even more!
I'm gonna smell terrible!
I'll will my sweat to dry!
[MAINA]
Hello, there.
[ERIPIYO gasps]
You wanna do heart hands?
[gasps]
[ERIPIYO] The outfit's a
whole lot cuter up close.
She's really makin' the
salmon thing work for her.
Or maybe I'm just
getting used to it.
Um, I'm sorry, I look
freaking terrible today,
and I got really sweaty,
so I'm sure I stink.
I don't wanna gross you out.
Please don't get any closer!
But you--
[ERIPIYO]
It's fine!
Sir, can you please hurry up
and take the picture?
I'm begging you!
[KUMASA, MOTOI]
What's the point?
What even is this photo?
[ERIPIYO] Actually,
this one was the retake.
[MOTOI, KUMASA]
What?
[ERIPIYO] In the first one,
you could only see my hand,
so we took it again.
But you waited in that
awful heat for hours
and this is all you got?
This is what the picture's
supposed to look like.
Isn't it cute?
Guys, it's fine!
Maina looks great. Back off!
[KUMASA]
I mean, to be honest,
she's barely in
the picture, either.
[ERIPIYO] But the angle of
her fingers is adorable!
Look! Look at her ring finger...
No, wait! It isn't just her
finger--it's everything!
I love her!
She's amazingly adorable!
[ERIPIYO squeals, laughs]
I want everyone in the
world to know who she is
and fall in love with her!
That's what Maina deserves!
You mean you don't wanna have
your favorite all to yourself?
The thing I love
most about Maina
is how hard she
works as an idol.
So I don't want to
keep her to myself.
I want her to belong
to everyone.
But even if she did,
there's no doubt in my
mind that I love her
more than anyone ever could.
Yeah. I know exactly
what ya mean.
[ERIPIYO] If Maina were
to make it to the Budokan,
I'd die happy.
If Maina were to make it to
the Budokan... I'd die happy!
[ERIPIYO] It's so important,
I had to say it twice.
[KUMASA]
Yeah, that's never gonna happen.
[MOTOI]
It never even occurred to me.
[ERIPIYO]
Maina.
[MISAKI]
You girls ready to head out?
Almost time to go.
[AYA, YUMERI, REO]
Okay!
Huh? Someone left their photo.
Oh, that's mine.
[YUKA]
Ah.
[MAINA]
Eripiyo.
It means so much that you
came to see me again today.
Hopefully tomorrow
I'll have the courage
to tell you how I really feel.
[KUMASA] So, Reo, I heard
you're gonna perform
in the Okayama Girls Festa.
Congratulations!
Now everyone in town
will see how cute you are!
I bet you'll be
scouted as a model,
then get a part
on a big TV series,
and get big and famous
and totally unattainable.
Not that you're attainable no--
[YOSHIKAWA] Thank you
very much. Time's up!