[KING'S AIDES chattering]
[KING'S AIDE A]
Is this a joke?
The Strategos of Zaibach is
truly asking us for asylum?!
[KING'S AIDE 7B]
You left the empire
because you disagreed
with Dornkirk's methods?
[KING'S AIDE 7A] And you allege
that he and his followers are
leading Gaea toward the greatest
disaster in her history?
[KING'S AIDE 22A] This is why
you're requesting sanctuary?
[KING'S AIDE 7B]
You can't honestly expect us
to trust your word!
I happen to agree. This is
all suspiciously sudden.
[FOLKEN] If it helps,
I've come bearing gifts.
[HITOMI]
Folken's arrival in Asturia
and request for safe haven
changed everything.
It proved everyone's
suspicions about Zaibach,
and Asturia quickly
formed a military alliance
with her neighboring countries.
[HITOMI] They finally agreed
to grant Folken asylum
as he requested, in exchange
for information on Zaibach.
[HITOMI]
But Van still didn't trust him.
[MEN chattering]
[CHILDREN laughing]
Wouldn't you rather help out at
the castle's shelter instead?
Not really. I'm partly to
blame for what happened here.
I want to help as many
people as I can.
[MERLE] Yeah? Then why didn't
you come all by yourself?
Hey, nobody forced you
to tag along, did they?
You wanna step outside?
Eh?
[ALL]
Uh?
[PRIEST A] We're honored
that you traveled so far
out of the way to grace us
with your presence, Princess.
Not at all. So many
have met hardship here.
I want to do whatever I can
to ease their burdens.
[GADDES] Don't push!
There's plenty for everybody!
[MERLE laughs]
I'm gonna go help out!
So am I!
Thanks a lot!
[GIRL B]
Me next, me next!
We still have to
keep our guard up.
While we're doing this, Zaibach
could be launching an attack.
My goodness, you really
do always have battle
on the brain, don't you?
If you're not ready to fight,
then you are just
waiting to be killed.
[DRYDEN] Hmph.
You soldiers are all alike.
Not everything's about death
and destruction, you know.
Zaibach is going
to destroy Gaea.
The same way they
did my country.
[sighs] All right. Just be
patient, O' King of Fanelia.
We'll see what happens.
Do you have any toys? We
want some toys to play with!
Toys and candy?
I'll go take a look.
Mm...
You're gonna have to
let me by, though.
[screams]
Hey, kid! Don't you
pull my tail! [screams]
Come back here!
Look at Merle play with them.
[gasps]
She seems to fit right in.
[VAN] She knows what
they're going through.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
All of those children have lost
their homes and their families.
And so did Merle.
That's something war always
seems to leave in its wake--
Orphaned kids.
Hey, Van,
back when you and
Folken were growing up,
what did you do for fun?
None of your business.
I'm sorry.
[ALLEN] Hitomi! What
are you doing here?
I've been searching all
over the grounds for you!
I'm helping. I noticed
everybody else is...
Couldn't just sit on the
side and do nothing.
You shouldn't have
left the castle!
Don't you realize that your
being here jeopardizes
your safety and therefore
the safety of Gaea?
You're always leaving
without asking.
Like when you flew off
to Fanelia with Van.
But that was...
Actually, I don't
think that trip's
any of your business, Allen.
I just don't like it when
you hide things from me.
Well, I'm not.
And I'm offended you
would even think it!
[ALLEN]
Hitomi!
[HITOMI] I'll go back to the
castle later... by myself.
[ALLEN]
Hitomi...
[HITOMI] What's the
matter with me today?
I don't think I've ever
snapped at Allen like that.
I just felt so mad
all of a sudden.
[panting]
[FOLKEN] You must be
missing your homeland.
Oh, Folken!
[FOLKEN]
So that's why you were there.
[HITOMI]
I thought I could help somehow.
I know Van would feel better
if things were straightened
out between you.
Van is a very stubborn boy.
Yeah, no matter what I say,
I can't get through to him.
[FOLKEN] What about you?
Do you not fear me?
[gasps]
I'm the one who brought the
Intensified Luck Soldiers here.
And I did it for the
purpose of kidnapping you.
[HITOMI] Well, I can't say
I'm okay with that, but...
But what?
[HITOMI]
If I were scared of you,
then we'd both be on our guard.
And that's not what I want.
If you want someone
to trust you,
you have to be willing
to trust them.
Should you be so eager
to trust me, though?
For all you know, my coming here
could be part of a Zaibach plot.
That's possible.
But I still don't think
you'd try to hurt me.
I believe you're
an honorable man.
Even if that's not always
obvious to people.
[FOLKEN] So that's your power.
You see the good in people.
The Egzardia army's
Triville has arrived!
[ROYAL GUARD B]
And the forces from Palas?
We expect them at the hour
of ripla tomorrow morning.
[ROYAL GUARD B]
The armies of Daedalus, Cesario,
and even Basram are involved.
Looks like this will
be the first Great War
in Gaea's history.
[HITOMI]
What's going on?
[ALLEN] Dispatch orders
have been issued.
[HITOMI]
Uh...
[ALLEN]
Van and I will leave together.
We go at the break of dawn.
But first, there's something
important that I must tell you.
[HITOMI]
Uh...
[ALLEN] I'm sure you
remember Prince Chid.
The truth is that he is my son;
Princess Marlene is his mother.
We never told anyone,
but we were in love.
It was secret tryst, and
then she married the duke.
Why tell me now?
Because I realized something--
That I never wanna hide
anything from you.
I love you too much to do that.
[ALLEN]
Now that I've told you this...
Now that you know everything...
Can you possibly love me?
Under the same stars,
the same moonlight.
I want us to be
together forever.
[DILANDAU]
What is this? Where am I?
You are currently aboard the
floating fortress, Delate.
[DILANDAU] What do you mean,
Delate? Where's Shesta?
Shesta is dead.
Get Gatty, then. Where's he?
He died, as well.
[DILANDAU]
And Dallet?
[JAJUKA]
Dead.
[DILANDAU]
Viole?
[JAJUKA]
Also dead.
They're all dead?
[whimpers] No!
I didn't catch your name yet.
My name is Jajuka, sir.
Doesn't sound familiar.
[JAJUKA] I am a soldier
under your command.
I, alone.
No one else...
[screams]
[whimpers]
[pants]
Jajuka...
Can you tell me whether or not
my new Guymelef
is finally ready?
Yes, sir!
[DILANDAU chuckles]
It's been a long time since
I've had a good battle.
I'm so looking forward to it.
[ALLEN]
Van, I've been looking for you.
[VAN]
Allen?
A word about Hitomi.
All right. And what about her?
So you know, I proposed
marriage to her last night.
She'll give her answer
when I return.
I can't explain it, but I'm only
at ease when I'm with her.
You had better keep her
safe. I mean it, Allen.
I will never allow anything
to happen to her.
Even if it costs me my life.
[HITOMI] Prince Chid is
actually Allen's son.
[CHID]
Hitomi!
[HITOMI]
Am I stuck here?
Will I ever be able to
go back home to Earth?
[MILLERNA]
Hitomi?
What do you think
of my outfit?
[ATTENDANT A] Princess! You
really shouldn't be doing that!
Don't worry. I doubt that
Dryden would have a problem
with me doing a little
laundry. Right, Hitomi?
Uh. Eh, yeah, sure.
[HITOMI]
Um, hey, Millerna?
[MILLERNA]
Yes?
[HITOMI] I could use a
little advice on something.
Maybe you can
help me out?
Me? Now what could I possibly
give you advice about?
Well, uh. I have this friend
and I'm sort of worried
about her, you see.
Yes?
[HITOMI] There's this
guy she's kind of with,
and she really likes him.
But she's found out
he's sort of a playboy.
Uh-huh.
And he even has an
illegitimate child, too;
so she isn't sure what to...
[MILLERNA] But she found out
that he's really a playboy
and... even fathered a child
that no one knows about.
[BOTH gasp]
So that was who you meant?
[MILLERNA]
How did you find out?
You knew this whole time.
[MILLERNA] Yes, I knew,
and now so do you.
The truth is, you never know
what life has in store for you,
and sooner or later,
we all make mistakes.
But we can't go back in
time and change them.
[HITOMI] Millerna is
still in love with Allen.
[GADDES] Right, there it is.
That's Rampant.
Kio! Be sure to set her
down real easy like.
We're representing Asturia;
they need to know
we're the good guys.
[ALLEN gasps]
[ROYAL GUARD C]
What is that?!
Zaibach's attacking!
Send Garrison units!
And the Melefs aswell!
[ROYAL GUARDS]
Sir!
Did you miss me?!
[laughing]
[REEDEN]
It's on fire!
The harbor's going up in smoke!
They launched a
surprise attack!
[ALLEN] Gaddes! Just lower us in
there! And I'll take Scherazade.
[GADDES] Commander! You heard
the man, drop Scherazade now!
Take us down! Kio!
Go, full power!
Yes, sir!
[VAN] Allen! I'll go in first
and split their forces.
Van!
[VAN growls]
[HITOMI] Now that I know,
what should I believe?
Who do I trust?
It's a sea of flames
down there. Damn it!
[ROYAL GUARD A] Right flank!
Cover our right flank!
[GUARDS scream]
[VAN]
Stop!
[yells]
It's here! The Ispano Guymelef!
[VAN yells]
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A screams]
[gasps] Oh, no. What was that?
[ROYAL GUARD 23A]
Squad three!
We need you up front!
Get in there!
[VAN yells]
[VAN]
I'll protect Hitomi.
[HITOMI gasps]
[VAN grunts]
[DILANDAU laughs]
Well, fancy meeting you here.
It's the red
Guymelef again!
I've missed our old
war games; let's play!
Now. Burn away!
[VAN yelling]
So sorry, Van;
did I singe you?
Dear Allen Schezar.
Oh, how I hate you!
Van! I need you
to watch my back!
No. Wait, Allen!
That's the Ispano Guymelef
everyone's been talking about.
If we defeat it, we'll
be heroes for sure!
Come on!
No, Van! Stop!
[VAN]
I'll protect her.
[yells]
[gasps]
[VAN]
I'll protect her.
[VAN growls]
You haven't lost your touch,
Allen. I'm very impressed.
[ALLEN yells]
Lord Dilandau!
Stay out of this, Jajuka!
You must listen to me!
He's too good.
[yelling]
[whimpering, screams]
Why am I seeing this?
[VAN]
I'll protect her!
[yelling]
Please, stop it!
[VAN growls]
That's enough.
I can't take it.
Van!
[VAN]
I'll protect her!
[grunts]
[DILANDAU laughs]
[VAN growls]
Van. Stop. I'm begging you.
Oh, thank you, Van!
This is so much fun!
What's with him? Why's
he always out for blood?
The anticipation's killing me!
Damn you!
Van!
Now die!
[DILANDAU]
What?!
I'll never die by your hand!
I'll protect her!
Just shut up!
Lord Dilandau!
What?
Jajuka! Help me!
[VAN yells]
I'm trying, my lord!
[whimpering]
[screams]
He vanished.
I'm coming, my lord!
[ALLEN]
It's over.
They completely
outmaneuvered us again.
We must return to Palas.
[HITOMI]
Why?
Why is everyone
always fighting?
I hate this.
I don't want to see it anymore.
[DRYDEN] So, then. Rampant
was completely destroyed.
[ALLEN]
Yes.
We need to hold a meeting
here with all of our allies.
[DRYDEN]
You're right.
Zaibach will hit even
harder next time.
We have to start preparing
for it immediately.
Yes.
We could launch a
preemptive strike.
It's going to come
down to us, or them.
[HITOMI] Why is fighting the
only thing you ever think about?
How can you even ask?
You know why.
We're fighting to protect you
and everybody else here.
I saw your face!
You were enjoying the
battle and the bloodshed!
[ALL gasp]
If that's what war
turns you into,
I don't want you to protect me!
I'm sick of all this fighting.
I'm sick of this
whole stupid place!
Hitomi, wait!
[HITOMI] Just send
me back, already!
Please, all I want to do
is go home to Earth!
[BOTH]
Hitomi!
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[DILANDAU]
"Celena"?
[MERLE] And I know why.
It's 'cause you love her.
He's calling.