Naria! What now?
[FOLKEN] I want you both
to hold your positions.
[NARIA]
But, Lord Folken!
That can't honestly be the
entrance to the Mystic Valley.
It's... It's just a fairy tale.
[KIO]
The helm's not responding!
Our lift indicator's
off the scale!
[VAN]
Impossible.
Did we truly make it through?
Yes. Looks like
we finally found it.
The lost capital of Atlantis.
So this is... the Mystic Valley?
[HITOMI gasps]
Hitomi!
[VAN]
Allen!
[MERLE]
King Van!
[GADDES]
What's going on?
[MERLE] How could they
all just disappear?
[KIO]
This is insane.
I see her!
Hitmoi's down there!
What's happening here?
None of my research
prepared me for this.
[HITOMI]
Hold on. I know this place.
Yeah. I've been here
in a vision before.
The vision I had
when Van almost died.
What is this place?
I'm in Fanelia.
[VARIE]
Van.
Is that you, Mother?
Celena!
No, don't go!
What is that?
[MERLE]
Hitomi!
There you are!
Where's King Van?
What's happening?
Look at that.
This monument is decked out
with Atlantean writing.
No doubt about it.
These are Atlantis's ruins.
The Mystic Valley.
[MILLERNA] Do you have
any idea what it says?
[HITOMI] "New Galactic
Era. Thirteenth moon."
Wait, you can
actually read this?
"We, the Draconians,
are descendants of Atlantis.
Our people are born
of the capital,
which lies on the Mystic Moon
and will forever
be our true home."
Stop. You can't be serious.
So the Atlanteans really
came from the Mystic Moon?
"We are a broken people.
Though Atlantis's power
had become great,
and her children fit to surpass
the gods, it was not enough.
In their avarice, they
constructed a horrible machine
capable of transforming human
thought into energy.
It made them omniscient
and omnipotent.
It seemed their power
knew no limits.
Wings sprouted from their back.
They soared through the
clouds like angels. Until..."
That's my pendant!
[HITOMI] "Their desperate wish
brought forth a new world
to hang among the stars
in the heavens.
Its name was Gaea.
This was the final wish
of the Atlanteans:
It is with the
deepest of regrets
that we write these words.
Our only hope is that
none shall be so foolish
as to repeat our mistakes.
Gaea.
A beautiful world
embraced by the heavens
with blue, rolling oceans
and green, verdant land.
A second chance."
You're telling me they willed
our world into existence?
And the machine that can
turn thought into energy.
That must be the
mystery of Atlantis.
Or at least one of them.
[LEON]
I entrusted that to her.
Who're you?
[ALLEN]
Father.
[VAN]
What is this?
It almost feels like
a distant memory.
[BALGUS]
It is.
A memory from the
bloodstained Draconians.
The very same blood that runs
through your veins, King Van.
Balgus.
Now, listen.
You are Atlantis's progeny.
And thus, bear its destiny.
Although it is grave, you
cannot shy away from it.
You must fight in order
to prevent Gaea
from meeting that same fate.
This responsibility rests
entirely with you, King Van,
and no other.
You will have to take up your
steel in Escaflowne once again.
[VAN]
No. You're wrong.
I don't wanna fight anymore.
I hate it. Let me go!
[HITOMI gasps]
What is it?
I think I know
where they are.
Van and Allen are inside.
Are you sure? How can
that be possible?
I'm sorry, Mother.
What is that?
What's happening?
[LEON]
Allen.
Is that really you?
[LEON]
My son, I'm glad you've come.
And it appears you
followed my wishes.
Now then. Where would
you like to begin?
You honestly think I have
anything to say to you?
[LEON] You managed to
be named a Knight Caeli.
Your mother must
be proud of you.
How is she? How is Encia?
[ALLEN]
My mother's gone. She died.
It happened while you
were off travelling.
I'm so sorry. I didn't
know that she had--
Are you actually crying?
[LEON]
It's natural to shed tears
when someone you love dies.
And I loved your mother dearly.
You liar!
How can you say that to me?
You're the one who left us!
I'm sorry, Allen.
[BALGUS]
Yes. You've always hated it.
Don't come closer!
Stay away from me!
[screaming]
Just go away!
Oh, no!
[MILLERNA] What is it?
What's wrong?
Are you all right?
[DRYDEN]
Huh?
Well, I don't know
what that means,
but I kinda doubt
it's anything good.
You don't think
we're gonna get stuck
if we stay here
much longer, do you?
[DRYDEN] This place both
is and isn't part of Gaea,
so it's hard to say either way.
Hitomi, you have to do
something about this, please!
[HITOMI]
I'm begging you.
Bring back Van. And Allen, too.
We have to get out of here.
[VARIE]
Don't do that.
You must refrain from using the
power of your wishes so freely.
While you mean well,
your desires are spawned
from your anxieties.
Your wishes make those
anxieties real,
bringing unintended
pain to those around you.
I'm the reason
they're suffering?
It's because of me?
Yes.
The difficulties your
friends have faced
were not chance happenings.
They were caused by you.
But how? I was only...
[VARIE]
Fortune telling?
Although your intention may be
merely to predict the future,
that isn't what
actually happens.
[HITOMI]
I did that?
[VARIE]
You didn't mean to, of course,
but your wishes were made
with a troubled mind.
And so they turned
your fears into reality.
The power of that pendant is not
something to be used lightly.
Yes.
Even now,
the uncertainty in your heart
is bringing forth grief.
I don't want it to be true.
It's my fault?
I'm the reason all these bad
things keep happening?
[HITOMI]
It's because of my wishes?
Because of me? I'm so sorry.
[HITOMI'S GRANDMOTHER]
Don't cry.
Have faith in them.
Believe in the people you love.
That's what they need.
Really, Grandma?
Where am I now?
Those are Zaibach soldiers.
They were on top of me
almost as soon as I
left the Mystic Valley.
I could neither run
nor hide from them.
They would do anything
for the mystery of Atlantis.
[ALLEN]
Atlantis?
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A]
Lord Dornkirk.
We have secured the item,
as you requested.
So much trouble
for a simple thing.
No.
Damn you!
Stubborn man.
You still deny me the secret
of the Mystic Valley?
Even at the cost of your family.
At the cost of your life itself?
[LEON]
The power of Atlantis.
The power of my wishes.
I want to see that girl.
Please, just one more time.
It's really you. You came back.
And you haven't aged a day.
But it's been so long,
how can that be?
Then it's true.
It's really true.
The mystery of Atlantis
is the power of the heart.
My hunch has been
right all along.
That's how this is possible.
Take this, and remember,
our wishes really do come true.
No matter the distance,
they transcend time
and space altogether.
To make dreams real.
[LEON]
I'm sorry... Encia.
[ENCIA]
Leon.
[ALLEN]
Mother.
After all that time, she loved
my father to the bitter end.
And though I didn't believe
it, he felt the same way.
[LEON]
Yes, I did.
Then why did you leave us?
I married and became a father
out of duty to my family,
which meant sacrificing
my own desires
for the good of those around me.
When people are forced
to live like that,
they yearn to break free
from the thread of fate.
When I saw that girl
for the second time,
I finally understood.
All along, I had loved Encia.
And you. My beautiful son.
You mean that?
[LEON]
We humans are nothing but fools.
What good is having
Atlantis's power to grant wishes
when we don't even know
what it is we want?
I'm so sorry.
Allen. Always be
true to yourself.
And to your heart.
[ALLEN]
No, wait!
Father! Come back!
Allen, here!
Where am I?
[GADDES]
Commander!
It's you.
[MILLERNA] Thank goodness.
We were so worried about you.
[DRYDEN]
Welcome back.
[ALLEN]
Thanks.
Hitomi?
That thing looks
dangerous to me.
Yes, I agree. Let's do
something about it.
[ARMORED SOLDIER A] Naria and
Eriya's Teirings are climbing!
They're entering the gate!
Stop, both of you. What do
you think you're doing?
[NARIA]
Don't worry so much.
Because our luck will
get us through this.
We'll bring your little brother
back kicking and screaming.
Almost! We're almost there!
Now all will see the power
of our good fortune!
W-What's that rumbling?
[BALGUS]
Hear that? The sounds of war.
[VAN]
No. I don't wanna fight anymore.
Please don't make me do it!
Those are Guymelefs!
Well, what do you know?
Our luck's even stronger
than I thought.
[PYLE]
What's going on?
Now Escaflowne's here?
He'd better be careful.
[VAN] So you're the ones
who called me back.
You should've let me be.
[ERIYA] You're not gonna
get away this time.
[NARIA] And no kitten
is going to save you.
[BALGUS]
You must fight for your life!
The only way to escape
from the sorrow of war
is by your own
bloodstained hands!
Now, my liege!
Van!
[HITOMI'S GRANDMOTHER]
Believe in him.
[HITOMI]
But Grandma.
[HITOMI'S GRANDMOTHER]
If your fear and anxiety
are what's causing all of
these bad things to happen,
then the opposite should
be true as well, right?
It's simple.
Just have faith in your friend.
Okay, I'll try.
He seems... different.
He's not shaking
like he was before.
[VAN]
Escaflowne's pain is my pain.
The pain of war.
If this truly is my fate...
...if the nightmare of war
is truly inescapable...
...I will shoulder its burden.
I will endure.
[VAN] And I will carry with
me the sorrow of the dead!
Van!
What is going on in there?
[FOLKEN]
No.
[ARMORED SOLDIER A]
Brace for incoming shockwave!
Van!
It disappeared.
The Mystic Valley is gone again.
Is King Van all right?
[VARIE]
The power of Atlantis.
It must never be reawakened.
Van's mother is here.
Wha--? What? Where?
You must always remember, Van.
What will ultimately determine
Gaea's future... is your will.
But, mother, how?
[VARIE]
Remember that... Van.
An Energist.
What's happening now?
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[MALE SORCERER A]
Alteration has begun!
[MALE SORCERER B]
[MALE SORCERER C]
Alteration has begun!
[MALE SORCERER D]
[DORNKIRK]
Begin alteration!