[HITOMI]
Was it all just a dream?
Or was it a vision?
[HITOMI]
I learned that the guy I liked
was moving out of the country.
[HITOMI] My farewell
to him was interrupted
when the boy from my dreams
appeared, followed by a dragon.
[HITOMI] A mysterious
beam of light came down,
and I found myself
in a strange world,
where the Earth and
moon hung in the sky.
They have us surrounded.
[AMANO]
What a crazy night.
At least Kanzaki's mom
believed us about what happened.
And she even seemed hopeful.
She thinks Kanzaki
will come back.
Until she does,
I'm not going anywhere.
[YUKARI]
I'm glad.
Hitomi.
[RUHM] Seriously?
You went to the Mystic Moon?
So this girl
you've got with you?
A native. She followed
me home. Can I keep her?
Well, that's a
surprise all right.
You haven't been to
the village in how long,
and then you show up one day
sayin' you've gone to
another world and back?
You know, according
to village legend,
our people actually
used to travel
to and from the Mystic Moon.
I never imagined
the stories were true,
but maybe I was wrong.
Sorry. What is the
Mystic Moon, exactly?
Look up. See the pretty
blue moon there?
Supposedly that's
where you're from.
[HITOMI]
The Mystic... Moon.
[VAN]
What's wrong?
Uh, it's nothing. I'm fine.
[RUHM]
Now that I think about it.
The Mystic Moon has
been different lately.
A lot brighter than usual.
Maybe that's why strange
things have been happening.
[YURIZEN]
It's already been three days.
[ASONA] If he doesn't return,
what will become of us?
What will become of Fanelia?
[YURIZEN]
He's not like his older brother.
Surely he won't flee the
ceremony like Folken did.
[LUVA] Balgus, what's
your take on this?
I have been in charge of Prince
Van's education for ten years.
I know him well.
He's devoted himself
to preparing for the
rite of succession.
I can tell you this
without a doubt:
He wants nothing more
than to erase the shame
brought on the Fanel
family by his brother.
Prince Van would never
abandon his duty,
even if that dragon ripped
all the limbs from his body!
Well, that's Fanelia down
there. What do you think?
C'mon everybody, hurry!
Prince Van is back!
[WOMAN A] What? Is it true?
Is he really back?
[MAN B]
Opening the gates!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[MERLE]
Prince Van!
Prince Van! You're back!
[VAN]
Merle!
[MERLE, VAN chuckle]
[MERLE] I'm just so happy
that you aren't dragon food!
I was worried to death.
I don't think I breathed
the entire time you were gone!
Okay that's enough. Easy,
Merle. Everyone's watching.
[MERLE] I can't help it.
I'm so relieved!
[VAN chuckles]
[VAN]
Aw, c'mon, cut it out.
First wolf men, now a little
cat girl. Where am I?
[BALGUS]
Prince Van?
It is you.
I see you've returned.
Hear me, all of you!
I, Prince Van Fanel,
have completed the
Rite of Dragonslaying
and have returned
with a Drag-energist!
He's not lying.
That's the real thing.
An authentic Drag-energist.
As the brigadier generals
of the samurai of Fanelia,
we verify your
completion of the rite.
It's good to be
home. Thank you.
[HITOMI]
He's a prince?
Ahh. Now there's
a smell I've missed.
Can't beat a
freshly-oiled Melef.
That's the trouble
with peacetime,
you don't get to use these
beauties often enough.
A tournament on
coronation day.
This is what I've
been waiting for!
[WORKER] Careful, sir.
You're not a kid anymore.
Don't push yourself.
[ASONA]
Hey!
[sighs]
[HITOMI] What am I doing
in this weird place?
[YUKARI] Hitomi! Hey!
Keiko's looking for you.
She wants you to do a
tarot reading. Come on!
Amano. I miss you.
[HITOMI yelps]
[HITOMI]
Jeez!
There's a door for
a reason, you know!
[MERLE]
Hmph.
Uh, can I help you?
You better keep
your paws off of him.
I've got my eye on you.
Just stay away from
Prince Van, okay?
You're a funny-looking
foreigner.
You don't need to be getting too
familiar with him, understand?
Uh. Who says I'm getting
familiar with him?
Hey! What're you doing?
Ah!
[MERLE laughing]
Quit digging through my stuff!
This is a really pretty stone.
I think I'll keep it.
[HITOMI]
Hey, stop! Damn it.
Come back here!
Talk about a cat burglar.
[MERLE chuckling]
[HITOMI]
Oh!
Don't think you're
getting away from me!
I'm an athlete!
[HITOMI]
Wait, what was that?
[VAN yelling]
You have to be more
aggressive! Really charge.
Come at me like you want nothing
more than to see me dead.
I don't like mortal sword
combat, Balgus. I just don't.
Listen to me, Prince.
In a short time, you will
become King of Fanelia.
You cannot afford to have
such weak sentiments.
[VAN] It's not like being king
is something I chose.
Don't say that!
We'll continue this later.
We have a guest.
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
I'm sorry!
The door was open.
I didn't mean to snoop.
Well then, what did you want?
Well...
[MERLE humming]
That's the problem
with you foreigners.
No manners at all.
Hey, you! Gimme back my pendant!
Stupid cat!
[MERLE]
Prince Van!
[BALGUS] I heard what
happened with the dragon.
It would seem that Prince
Van owes you his life.
We'll do right
by you, don't worry.
After the coronation
ceremony is over,
we'll do everything in our power
to return you
to the Mystic Moon.
Really? You will?
Don't doubt it. A samurai
of Fanelia never lies.
[RUHM]
Whoa!
Something smells off.
I don't see anything
out of the ordinary, though.
I guess it's nothing.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
[MERLE]
Aww.
No fair! I wanted to see
Prince Van all dressed up.
Why do I have to wait out here?
[HITOMI] A front-row seat
is more of an honor
than I was looking for.
[CORONATION OFFICIATOR] Rise,
Van Fanel, King of Fanelia,
and accept the sword
that I bestow upon thee
as proof of thy accession.
[SOLDIER A] Can't wait
for the celebration tonight.
[SOLDIER B] You gonna
bring that girl of yours?
[SOLDIER A]
You bet I am.
What was that, a mirage?
See something?
Nah.
[SOLDIER B]
Hm?
[SOLDIER C]
What's happening?!
What the hell?!
What is that thing?!
[SOLDIER C screams]
It's huge! A ghost?
A demon, maybe?
[VILLAGERS whispering]
Hey, do you see that?
Yeah, it looks like smoke.
[FANELIA MAN E]
Is it a fire?
[SOLDIER H]
We're under attack!
You hear me? It's an attack!
Get the women and
children to the mountains.
You men prepare
yourselves for battle.
Now! Clear the road!
An invisible enemy?
[ASONA]
Balgus.
Quickly, to your Melefs.
Hold them off!
And Luva, Asona, Yurizen,
I am counting on you.
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
And me? What should I do?
Leave the fighting to us.
For now, take Lady Hitomi
and go to the shrine.
Shouldn't I help?
No.
Majesty, should it
prove necessary,
take Escaflowne and flee.
Escaflowne? You're sure?
[SOLDIER I]
First cavalry, to the gates!
[SOLDIER J] Third squad,
to the western road!
[VILLAGERS yelling]
[MERLE]
King Van!
King Van, I wanna stay
here and help you fight!
Please let me stay with you!
Are you crazy, Merle?
We have to get out of here!
[MERLE]
King Van!
[GUYMELEF SOLDIER A screaming]
You damn cowards!
Show yourselves already!
Come on. Where are you?
You!
[groans]
Striking from behind.
Cowardly dog.
[SOLDIER K]
General!
I'm sorry, Balgus.
I fear I've failed you.
[GUYMELEF SOLDIER C groaning]
You're not going any
further while I'm alive.
[yelling]
I... failed.
[VAN]
I, Van Fanel, King of Fanelia,
bind myself by blood pact
to thee, Escaflowne.
Your time has come.
Sleeping dragon, awake!
That's the giant.
The one from my dream.
Done.
[HITOMI[
Wait a sec!
[HITOMI]
What're you going to do?
[VAN]
What do you think? Fight!
Good. So the old texts
were right. I can work it.
So that's it.
That's Escaflowne.
Do you wanna get killed?
Hurry and hide somewhere!
Here they come.
Where is it?
Where is the enemy?
Quick, Van! To your left!
What?
Oh, no! Look out!
[groaning]
You're not getting away from me!
Another Guymelef?
Again, a giant from
my dream. But how?
[VAN yelling]
[HITOMI]
Van! Behind you!
[BALGUS yelling]
[HITOMI]
Balgus!
What's he doing?
[BALGUS]
King Van!
Take Lady Hitomi and get out
of here while you still can!
You really expect me
to turn tail and run?
[BALGUS]
Please, King Van!
[VAN yelling]
Incredible!
[BALGUS]
Go!
Get out of here, Majesty!
[VAN]
Damn it!
We're leaving! Come on.
Come on, Balgus. I'm not
leaving you behind!
No! Look out, Balgus!
[BALGUS]
Hm?
Balgus!
Is he okay?
Your Majesty. You must
take Escaflowne.
Take it now and flee!
And then someday,
you can return and make
our land great once again.
You can rebuild Fanelia.
No. No, you can't die!
[HITOMI]
No. No! No!
You can't be dead... King Van!
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[MAN]
That was foolhardy.
[yelling]
[HITOMI]
Can it be? Is he the one?