[HITOMI] Was it all just a
dream? Or was it a vision?
We are in an outlying area
of the Kingdom of Asturia.
In a forest there, I met
a brave and dashing knight.
His name was Allen Schezar.
[HITOMI] After he defeated
Escaflowne with his Guymelef.
I was overcome by
a terrifying vision.
[VAN]
She's doing it again.
[ALLEN]
Hitomi! What's wrong?
You have to get away from here!
I mean it! Take everybody
and leave, right now!
The invisible enemy is
coming to attack you!
Perhaps you should
lie down for a bit.
Watching our duel seems
to have disturbed you.
No, that's not it!
You have to believe me!
If you don't, everything and
everyone is going to burn!
[HITOMI]
I'm not lying!
Please! I know what I saw!
The same invisible giants
that attacked Fanelia.
They're going to
burn this place down!
I-I saw it! Honest!
What's all this stuff
she's babbling about?
Jeez, That little lady's
givin' me the creeps.
Well, o'course she is.
She came to Gaea from the
Mystic Moon is what I hear.
And everyone and their
mother knows full well
that place is cursed.
Yeah, I've heard that, too!
Does that mean
something's gonna happen
to the castle?
[ALLEN]
Enough!
Soldiers of Asturia are not
afraid of old wives' tales!
I'm sorry. Please
forgive their rudeness.
You look tired
You need to get
some rest, Hitomi.
[TEO]
Boss!
--[TEO grunts]
--[HORSE whinnies]
[ALLEN]
What is it, Teo?
We just caught a
suspicious character
out in the forest.
Suspicious how?
[ORT] Wait, was the little
lady's prediction really true?
[KIO] Here we are, Boss!
We've got the prisoner!
[gasps]
That's Merle!
Merle.
[VAN]
Merle!
King Van!
[whimpers]
Help me!
Hold on.
You know this girl?
Yes. She's from Fanelia.
So, here you are!
I finally found you!
Tell me. How's Fanelia?
There's nothing left.
It's gone. Fanelia
is gone, King Van.
[sobs]
[MERLE sobs] All the Samurai at
the castle--they were killed.
And the survivors were
scattered like ashes.
[MERLE]
Everybody was gone.
There was nothing
left but ruins.
But I, I still hoped
you were alive somewhere.
And I've been looking
for you ever since.
Merle. I'm so glad
I didn't lose you.
[gasps] A fire?
What's happening?
It feels so hot. What's goi--
Hitomi? She has a fever.
Van. Bring that girl
and follow me.
[DORNKIRK]
Folken.
Take heed--the dragon
has almost disappeared.
The dragon?
[DORNKIRK] Yes, and the
distortion has begun
to appear in the image
of our ideal future.
If the dragon slips
through our fingers,
then there is no telling
how profound the impact
upon our future will be.
You must rectify the
situation, and quickly.
Capture the dragon!
[FOLKEN]
Yes, Majesty.
Where are you going?
To make preparations
for an attack, obviously.
We can move at once.
We know where the dragon is.
Yes, but Asturia is an ally.
[DILANDAU]
Oh, come now.
If we go through proper channels
and wait for the politicians
to act, our prey will escape.
[FOLKEN] Have you considered
the repercussions?
[DILANDAU sighs]
There's no need to worry.
We'll use those
stealth cloaks of yours.
Then there won't be
any evidence to prove
Zaibach was behind the
attack, now will there?
[FOLKEN]
Hmph.
[DILANDAU] I think you'll
like the souvenir
I'll bring back, Folken.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to trouble you.
It's no trouble at all.
Besides, I think you'll
find my bedside manner
is more pleasant than
that of my soldiers.
[HITOMI]
The Earth.
My poor Mom. She
must be so worried.
Your mother, huh?
What about your mom?
What's she like?
I bet she's really
pretty, isn't she?
She was.
She passed away when I was
still very young, though.
[gasps] I shouldn't
have said anything.
No, it's okay. That
happened a long time ago.
You are right, though.
My mother-- She was
very beautiful.
[ALLEN]
She was a gentle woman.
One who loved flowers.
And I had a sister
who was just as beautiful.
[ALLEN]
But, sadly,
one day, my sister was spirited
away. She just, vanished.
[ALLEN] After that, my mother
fell ill, consumed by her grief.
And then...
If my sister was
still alive somewhere,
she'd be about your age now.
Oh, really?
I don't know why I'm
telling you all this,
but I feel like I
can be open with you.
Allen...
[HITOMI] I just told Amano
how I felt, and now this?
Geez, am I really
that flaky about guys?
[whimpering]
[gasps]
Is this what I think?
[gasps] Oh, hey.
Van?
Van!
[ALLEN]
I'm sure he'll be back soon.
I should go, too.
I have patrol duty.
Wait, Allen. Please!
Be careful. I know
my vision was real.
Whatever those things
are, they're coming.
If that is the case,
I'll protect you
and everybody else here.
[MOLE MAN snoring]
[yelps]
Oh, Your Majesty, to what
do I owe the pleasure?
Surely you didn't
come all the way down
to the dungeon just
to disturb my nap?
[VAN] You're one of the
forest people, so you must
have some glar leaves, right?
Huh? Why, yes, of course I do.
You know about these leaves, eh?
[VAN]
My brother told me about them.
According to him, they can
neutralize most poisons.
Come hold this bowl
for me, Mole Man!
Eh?
[VAN]
Hurry up!
Ugh. All right, no need
to get grouchy about it.
[GADDES] So you believe in
those old wives' tales, too.
Why do you say that?
[GADDES] These emergency combat
preparations, for one.
What that girl from
the Mystic Moon said
has you worried, doesn't it?
No, what has me worried
is that man, Dilandau,
and the look in his eyes.
[ALLEN]
There's darkness in him.
You can tell he's
thirsty for blood.
[GADDES]
You think they're gonna attack?
[REEDEN]
Would Zaibach really do that?
[ALLEN]
They came here for a reason.
They know Escaflowne is here.
If they come again,
it'll be to wipe us out.
[GADDES, REEDEN gasp]
[REEDEN]
They'd go that far?
[ALLEN]
I wouldn't put it past them.
No survivors means
no witnesses. Gaddes.
Sir?
I want the Crusade
prepped for flight.
Right! Come on, Reeden!
[REEDEN]
Yes, sir!
[ALLEN] When you attack,
Dilandau, we'll be ready.
[DILANDAU]
All units, hold position.
[DILANDAU chuckles]
It's time to end this
game of hide and seek.
No, King Van!
[gasps]
[MERLE] It's that girl
from the Mystic Moon.
[HITOMI] Why is she
looking at me like that?
[MERLE] She's got weird
hair and weird clothes.
What's her deal?
[HITOMI]
Those ears and that tail...
She's a cat, but a
girl, too. So strange!
She wouldn't be so bad
if she was nicer.
[MERLE gasps]
[MERLE] Why did I get a
bench while she got a bed?!
[MERLE growling]
[HITOMI]
She looks really ticked off!
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Something's coming!
Uh?
[screams]
Whoa!
Oh, it's King Van!
Why'd you run off like that?
There are sick people
to care for, you know!
Uh. What's that?
Did you make it for me?
Thanks. That feels nice.
It's medicine?
That's what you were up to?
[giggles]
Huh?
[HITOMI shrieks] Hey! What the
heck do you think you're doing?
Ow!
[VAN]
Just hold still.
Some poison from a plant
got into your wound.
This ought to bring
down your fever.
Thanks.
[gasps]
They're here. They came,
just like I saw!
[CRUSADER 4E]
What the--?
[CRUSADER 4F gasps, screams]
[CRUSADERS shouting]
[CRUSADER 4G gasps]
[CRUSADER 4H]
Fire!
[gasps] So that's
the invisible enemy.
The curse of the Mystic
Moon! We're gonna die!
It's just Zaibach, you idiot!
I'm going out there
in Scherazade!
[GADDES]
Sir!
[CRUSADERS scream]
[yelling]
[DILANDAU chuckles] Come on!
I'm not even breaking a sweat!
[GATTY] Lord Dilandau!
We found a tunnel!
[DILANDAU]
All right! Follow it!
Smash everything to bits!
Set it on fire! And most
of all, smoke out Escaflowne!
Damn you, Zaibach.
You'll pay for this!
[KIO groaning]
[ALLEN]
Are you hurt, Kio?
[KIO]
Boss, I'm so sorry!
[ALLEN]
About what?
I wasn't able to stop the enemy
from getting into the tunnels!
We have no chance of
holding them off now.
[VAN]
Allen!
Where's Escaflowne?
It should be safe.
It's been loaded
into the Crusade.
What's the Crusade?
[ALLEN] The castle's
fallen. We're withdrawing.
What? You're running?
After what those animals
did to your men?
If I stay, it'll only mean
more lives will be lost!
[VAN]
And you call yourself a samurai.
Well, I won't run!
I'll never turn my back
on an enemy and run again!
I'll make them pay for
what they did to my people.
I'll fight them until I die!
Choosing to die isn't
brave, Van, it's selfish!
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
Look, you're Fanelia's king.
As long as she has you and a
people, Fanelia has a future.
Sometimes, retreating takes
more courage than fighting.
A samurai gives his life
so that others may live.
Never forget that.
[ALLEN] Kio, I'm transferring
headquarters to the Crusade.
Tell the men!
[KIO]
Understood, sir!
I'll never hand you or
Escaflowne over to Zaibach.
You have the word of
Allen Schezar on that.
[KATZ]
Get moving, guys!
[TEO]
Aye! Just one valve left!
[KATZ]
Hurry!
--[rumbling]
--[HITOMI, MERLE yelp]
Aw, don't worry.
This old cave can
hold up to anything.
[PYLE]
Okay, check! Ready over here!
[KIO]
Pressure?
[KATZ]
Climbing, sir!
[TEO]
Good!
Allen's not here!
Neither is King Van.
Where are those two?
They'll meet up with us soon.
Let's weigh anchor, men!
[TEO]
Aye-aye, weighing anchor!
Set sail!
[DILANDAU cackling]
Burn! Burn!
[FOLKEN]
You're a fool, Dilandau.
This plan's nothing
more than senseless
slaughter and destruction.
[DILANDAU] It's also the surest
way to destroy any evidence.
All we have to do now
is capture Escaflowne
once it's out in the open.
This Allen Schezar's
a brilliant commander.
Do you actually
believe he wouldn't
have an escape plan in place?
[DILANDAU]
What are you getting at?
[FOLKEN] The waterfall at
the cliff behind the castle.
They say that birds build
nests behind waterfalls.
To prevent them
from being attacked.
[gasps] Follow me
to the waterfall!
What are you doing?
Okay, Van, hold on tight.
What? No, wait!
[yelps]
[HITOMI, MERLE,
MOLE MAN yelping]
It's Allen!
Yay! King Van!
[GADDES]
Okay, unfurl the sails!
[KATZ]
Unfurling sails!
[DILANDAU] Not bad,
you provincial low lifes.
You still aren't going
to escape, though.
I'll just have
to shoot you down!
But we can't use
our stealth cloaks
while we're in flight mode.
They'll see our Guymelefs.
If anyone sees us, we'll
just kill them, you idiot!
[VAN]
Where are we headed?
To the capital of Asturia.
There's no way their floating
fortress can keep up with us.
Allen, behind us!
Impossible! Their
Guymelefs can fly?
They're fast!
They got above us?
Now die!
[screams]
[ALLEN] I'll make you pay for
all the men you've killed.
I am going to
crush you, Dilandau!
Go on and try,
Allen! Please do!
Allen! Above you!
[yelps]
We're hit and the
rudder's not responding!
We're surrounded!
What's happening?
King Van, help me!
[VAN] Everyone's in danger
because of Escaflowne.
[ALLEN] A samurai gives his
life so that others may live.
[grunts]
Van!
Van! What do you
think you're doing?
[GADDES]
Hey! Hold up!
Well...
[gasps]
[yells]
Escaflowne is capable
of transforming?
I see now.
That must be the dragon
Emperor Dornkirk's
been going on about
all this time!
This one's yours, Gatty!
[GATTY]
I'm on it!
That's it, chase me!
What? King Van's leaving?
[HITOMI]
He's trying to help us escape.
[BOTH yelp]
Damn it!
[ALLEN]
Van, don't get yourself killed.
[HITOMI]
Gaddes! Turn the ship around!
We have to try and save Van!
[GADDES]
We can't right now!
Our sail's hit and the
rudder's not responding.
[HITOMI]
Oh, no...
So we're just leaving?
[MERLE]
King Van!
All right! All I have to do
is catch a dragonwind.
Yeah! Caught it!
[cackling] I haven't done
any dragon hunting
in such a long time.
This ought to be
very entertaining!
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
I should've killed
you the first time,
but better late than never!
[HITOMI]
Faster! I've gotta warn him!
You're... my brother.