[FREID] I've heard what
happened, Fanelia.
Regarding the tragedy
that befell your country.
As a fellow leader of men,
you have my utmost sympathy.
I thank you, Duke Freid.
That's very kind of you.
[FREID]
I have also been informed
of Zaibach's activities.
Hence our current meeting.
I thought it best
I returned here,
to our capital of Godashim.
Unfortunately... Allen!
No matter the reason,
a knight brings nothing
but shame to himself
by abandoning his country.
To disobey the word of one's
lord is absolute treason.
We have no use for
such an immoral ruffian
in the Duchy of Freid.
[CHID]
Please, wait!
Consider everything Allen
and his companions have
done for our country!
Father. They risked
their lives for us.
They defended Freid and
found the Doppelganger!
[FREID]
That's enough!
You're too inexperienced to
speak with such authority!
Have you considered what
those actions cost?
Your decisions may have
assured our demise!
[CHID sighs]
[MILLERNA]
Excuse me!
[CHID]
Uh!
[FREID]
Hm?
Come in, Princess Millerna.
Well. Here we go...
Princess.
It is good to see you, but
we'll have to talk later.
I hope you will forgive me
because this cannot
wait, Brother.
Sorry. After everything
that's happened,
I suppose don't have the right
to call you that anymore.
I, too, have abandoned Asturia.
[gasps]
[MILLERNA]
Your Grace.
Zaibach's actions
are sheer madness.
Their intention is to
plunge all of Gaea
into the bloody chaos of war.
Fanelia is only the beginning
of their destructive conquest.
And what's more.
They're on their way here now to
make Freid their next target!
And unfortunately, my father.
No, "King Aston" won't do
anything to stop them.
He honestly believes it is
in Asturia's best interest.
But once the rest of Gaea has
fallen under Zaibach's control,
there's no way Austuria
will be left in peace.
[MILLERNA] To prevent
this from happening,
Allen Schezar came here on
his own to warn and aid you!
So. Please, your Grace.
Find it in your heart
to forgive Allen!
[FREID]
Princess Millerna.
[gasps]
You are both wise
and benevolent.
Those are signs of
a good upbringing.
Asturia has produced
a fine princess.
[FREID]
Hear me!
Allen will you join my soldiers
and fight against Zaibach?
It would be my honor
to offer my life in service
to you, Your Grace.
We shall be glad to
have your sword.
I expect your very best!
[ALLEN]
Sir!
[HITOMI] I can't believe
this man is Chid's father.
[DORNKIRK]
Did you say...
"a girl from the Mystic Moon"?
[FOLKEN]
Yes. It's an oddity.
She's proven she can see
through our stealth cloaks,
revealing our
Guymelefs' locations.
Also. According to the
reports I've received.
She's been guiding the dragon
based on predictions
of the future.
[DORNKIRK]
Yes. That is excellent news.
M'Lord?
[DORNKIRK]
This must be the anomaly
that has so confounded my
Destiny Prognostication Engine.
I wish to see it!
[FOLKEN]
Yes, Lord.
It's been so very long.
Since the last time I set
eyes on the planet Earth.
But still...
I remember.
[MOLE MAN]
Mm-hm.
[MILLERNA]
That's a relief.
Your wound seems to
be healing up nicely.
[MILLERNA]
Allen. I want you to know.
I don't care about
Asturia or Freid.
So long as you're safe,
I'll be happy.
[MOLE MAN]
Mm?
[MERLE meows]
[yelps]
So what'cha doin'?
Nothing! I wasn't
eavesdropping!
--[MERLE] Hey, Allen!
--[MOLE MAN shouting]
Have you seen Hitomi
around here?
[ALLEN]
No. Not recently, at least.
[MERLE] Oh. Well,
sorry I bothered you.
[gasps]
[ZONGI screaming]
I can't take it anymore.
These awful visions.
Why won't they stop coming?
[MERLE meows]
You know, I'll say
one thing about you.
You're entertaining.
[HITOMI]
I appreciate you mocking me
when you have no idea
what I'm going through.
"Ohhhhh! I can't
take it anymore!
Why? Why won't they
stop? Why, oh, why?"
[exhales]
Fine!
If you're gonna be no fun,
King Van wants to see you!
[REEDEN] Man, would you look
at the nicks on this thing?
You're way too rough on
this sword, Your Majesty!
[VAN]
I am?
Yeah, you are.
Meanwhile, Commander
Allen's sword
ain't got a single
scratch on it!
Well, excuse me!
I'm not as good as Allen,
just go on and say it.
[REEDEN]
C'mon. No need for a hissy fit.
[VAN grunts]
Besides, he's just
yankin' your chain.
Don't let the little
twerp get to you.
It's got scratches.
Just not as many.
[REEDEN chuckles]
[MERLE]
King Van!
[MERLE laughs]
There you are!
[MERLE grunts]
Do you need something?
I could really use your
help, if you don't mind.
[HITOMI]
Uh.
Oh. Don't worry, I don't want
you to fight or anything.
It has to do with your
ability to see the future
and gauge where
invisible targets are.
I was hoping you could
use that power to tell us
which direction Zaibach is
planning to attack from.
Whoa, that's actually
a really good idea!
Yeah, and if it works,
we can stop 'em all
dead in their tracks!
That kinda knowledge,
that little lady will be our
very own Goddess of Victory!
[MEN laugh]
[MERLE growls]
[HITOMI]
No.
[VAN]
Uh...
[HITOMI]
I won't.
What's wrong?
[HITOMI]
Everything.
I hate having those visions.
[VAN]
Uh.
And now you want to use me
like I'm just some tool.
[VAN gasps]
[HITOMI] Back on Earth,
I was nothing special.
Just a normal girl.
I mean, yeah, I did readings,
and they were more accurate
than other people's.
But, it's different now.
Since I came to Gaea,
my readings are so
accurate it's terrifying.
And the things I see
are awful! So I won't!
Hitomi.
Stop relying on me!
[gasps]
I can't stand to have
another vision like that,
so don't ask me to do more
readings. Just, don't!
[VAN]
Hitomi!
What was that about?
[STUDENT A]
Hitomi!
Can you do a reading about
my boyfriend and me?
[STUDENT B] Aw, I wanted
her to do my reading first!
[STUDENT A] I need to
know if it's too soon
to say 'I love you.'
[STUDENT C] Your predictions
almost always come true!
[STUDENT B]
I'm counting on you, Hitomi!
I was a fortune-teller.
It was just a game.
Just for fun. But not now.
Now I want it to go away.
Make it stop.
Duke Freid! Good evening.
[FREID]
Hello, Princess.
[MILLERNA]
What is this place?
[FREID]
This is a villa
that Marlene used when
she lived in Asturia.
When she became my wife,
I had it recreated here
so she would feel more
at home in Freid.
Oh, wow!
I guess that explains why
it looks so familiar.
[FREID]
Yes. An exact copy.
You are welcome to use these
rooms while you're here.
I'm certain it's what Marlene
would have wanted.
Uh?
Yes, of course!
I remember this.
[MILLERNA]
You're leaving me, aren't you?
I want you to stay!
It will be all right.
Come, Princess Marlene.
It's time to go.
I'm going to miss you, sis!
I hope you'll be happy!
[music plays]
I still miss you.
[gasps] What is this?
[VAN growls]
[CHID] Hitomi? What's
wrong, can't you sleep?
No, I guess not.
I feel like if I went
to sleep now,
I'd never wake up, and
that'd be the end of me.
I understand.
[HITOMI]
Uh?
No matter how hard I try, I
can't stop thinking about war.
And my body won't stop shaking.
[CHID]
My father's right.
He tells me all the time I don't
have what it takes to be a duke.
Stop relying on me!
[CHID]
No matter what I do,
I'll never be strong
like my father.
My mother always wanted
me to be a good ruler.
That's why she told me so
many stories about Allen.
But it's hopeless,
really. I know it is.
I'll never be able to live up to
my parents' expectations of me.
That can't be true.
[HITOMI]
You know something?
People have an amazing ability.
[CHID]
Uh?
It's something my grandmother
told me about a long time ago.
You should always
say to yourself,
"I wish I were,"
or, "I want to be."
Do that, and before you know it,
those wishes will
have come true.
Do you really think so?
Of course I do.
When you set your mind
on something like that,
you give it your all
and never quit
until you finally
achieve your goal.
But at the same time,
if you only tell yourself,
"It's hopeless, I can't do it.
My dreams will
never come true,"
well, then they never will.
It works both ways, you see.
[HITOMI]
If you want it bad enough,
your wish will eventually
reach the stars,
and they'll give you the last of
their power to make it happen.
The power of the stars.
Heh.
Hey!
How would you like it if
I did a reading for you?
It's like talking to the stars.
My tarot cards can
use the stars' power
to reveal all sorts of
things about the future.
If you want me to, I can
tell you your fortune!
[MILLERNA] "Yellow,
thirty-fourth moon.
I attended a tournament today.
Uncle Nueva insisted
on taking me..."
[MARLENE] He's been concerned I
spend too much time in my room,
so I know he meant well enough.
But I wasn't the least bit
interested in the fighting.
Until...
[MARLENE]
I saw a young swordsman
against whom no one could stand.
A knight of Asturia:
Allen Schezar.
Incredible! This must have
been Marlene's diary.
"Green, middle of twelfth moon."
[MARLENE] The blonde youth
I saw at the tournament
has been named to
the Knights Caeli.
Given his age, and considering
only a dozen knights
may hold that title at a time in
Asturia, it is quite the honor.
They dubbed him the
"Knight of the Heavens".
If you ask me, it's a
perfect description.
He's been assigned guard
duty at the royal palace,
and has since left
for the capital.
Looks like my hints
to father paid off!
Oh, Sister.
[HITOMI]
The Emperor.
Justice.
Okay. What this means is,
you're going to grow stronger,
and everyone is going to
help you along the way.
Really?
The Wheel of Fortune.
There is a great
trial in your future,
but you will overcome it.
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Whoa. What was that?
[CHID]
Are you all right?
[HITOMI]
Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
[MARLENE]
Red, third moon.
I've been betrothed
to the Duke of Freid.
Why must I have been born
into the royal family?
I like him well enough.
But I'm in love with another.
Sadly...
This is the fate of knights
and women born of the blood.
Allen, know that I
will always love you.
[MILLERNA]
Marlene and Allen were in love?
What the...
No. That can't be.
[MILLERNA]
To think that one night
could have resulted in a child.
What am I supposed
to tell the duke?
And what will he say?
He only has to count
the days to know the truth.
I can't hide this.
Are you sure you're all right?
Uh. Sorry, I just can't seem
to keep my concentration.
Let's see...
[HITOMI] That card.
The Inverted Empress.
That suggests....
a forbidden love?
Then...
Prince Chid is really the child
of Marlene and Allen,
not the Duke!
[ADELPHOS laughs]
At last.
Zaibach's Four Demon Armies
have gathered once again.
[GENERAL A] Yes, General.
As for your orders, sir.
When would you like for us
to initiate the operation?
Now.
[SOLDIER A]
All ships are in formation!
[ADELPHOS]
Very good.
The time has come!
[ADELPHOS] The grace
of the gods is with us!
Ready? Move out!
Army of Bronze, mobilize now!
Beginning operation!
Army of Iron!
Army of Silver,
deploying forces!
Just how many Guymelefs
are they fielding?
[VORIS] Majesty. The enemy
has flanked us on all sides.
There's roughly 55,000 troops.
And they have 10,000
Guymelefs as well.
This is more than a mere siege.
Voris. Do you accept
the responsibility
that comes with being born a
citizen of the Duchy of Freid?
I will admit, it's a fine
day for what's written
in the Book of Lions.
Book of Lions?
What does that mean?
[SOLDIER A]
To the gates! Hurry!
King Van, what are you doing?!
What I can! Take care
of Hitomi for me!
Please be safe.
Please, King Van.
Come back to us alive.
[ALLEN] Gaddes, take up position
above the castle in the Crusade.
I'll head out in Scherazade.
[GADDES]
Yes, sir!
[MILLERNA]
Allen!
[ALLEN]
Yes, Princess?
[MILLERNA]
I'm sorry.
But there's something
I need to ask.
Is it something to do
with Princess Marlene?
[gasps]
[ALLEN] It's true. Marlene
and I were in love long ago.
It was before she was
betrothed to Duke Freid.
And...
Due to our time together,
it's likely that Prince Chid--
No! I don't want to hear it!
[FREID] Chid is my son,
do you understand?!
[MILLERNA]
Duke Freid.
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A]
Dragonslayers are in position!
[FOLKEN] Hold steady
for the time being.
I expect you to follow the
plan to the letter, Dilandau.
[DILANDAU] Of course,
Strategos. Don't I always?
[FOLKEN]
Van.
[NARRATOR] Escaflowne.
[CHID] They gave their lives
so that we could escape.