You're kidding!
This is who we've
been looking for?
Guess so. No point in
sticking around here.
Agreed. Then let's go!
[HITOMI gasps]
[VAN]
Uh.
[ALLEN]
Uh!
[DRYDEN, MILLERNA gasp]
[VAN]
Hitomi!
Let her go right now!
You'll get yourself killed!
He sure is stubborn,
I'll give him that.
[NARIA gasps]
[VAN growls]
[HITOMI]
Uh! Van!
[gasps]
[FOLKEN]
What happened?
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A] The Luck
Intensifier's malfunctioning!
How?
[VAN grunts]
Oh, no!
Hey, Eriya! You mind
giving me a hand?
Yeah, I'll get him.
We're gonna make Lord
Folken very happy!
[NARIA gasping]
[NARIA, ERIYA groan]
[HITOMI]
Huh?
[groaning continues]
[HITOMI screams]
--[ALLEN grunts]
--[HITOMI yelps]
Thank you, Allen!
Something's wrong, Sister.
I'm having trouble breathing!
[NARIA whimpers]
Why is this happening?
[NARIA, ERIYA gasping]
[FOLKEN] Naria. Eriya.
That's enough. Withdraw.
[NARIA pants]
Sorry, Lord Folken.
We really screwed this one up.
What?!
Naria, no!
[NARIA]
Don't worry about me!
You have to get
back to Lord Folken!
Naria!
[SOLDIERS chatting]
Get your backs into it, or
we'll never put out this fire!
[NARIA panting]
[NARIA]
Guess I really am lucky.
All of this was my fault.
[DRYDEN]
Don't be ridiculous.
[DRYDEN] It really wouldn't
have mattered if we had
followed your prediction and
called off the wedding.
They were always gonna
attack us, no matter what.
Besides, I don't believe
in fortune-telling,
so I wouldn't have
listened to you.
But I still lied to you.
[MILLERNA]
It's okay.
I pushed you to read my fortune
when you didn't want to.
I'm sorry about that.
I know it was wrong of me.
And because of it you've
suffered so much.
I hope you can
forgive me someday.
[ERIYA whimpering]
[DORNKIRK] Why did you order
them to withdraw, Folken?
Why did you disobey
my instructions?
I beg your pardon, Majesty.
But had they remained,
their lives would have been
placed in grave danger.
[DORNKIRK]
What must be must be.
Sacrifices will have to be made
to achieve our ideal future.
Hello, Lord Folken.
Eriya. I'm sorry.
For all of this.
[ERIYA] Don't be. I would do
it all again in a heartbeat.
I'm concerned about Naria.
You must be, too.
[ERIYA]
No. I'm not worried.
She's safe. And I know
she'll make it through this.
[ROYAL GUARD A groans]
[NARIA groaning]
[ALLEN] It was always
just a matter of time
before they learned of
Hitomi's abilities.
Eventually they'll
come for her again.
[ALLEN]
But the problem is:
they're protected by
that infernal luck.
I couldn't even get close to
them during the last attack.
Then new plan.
[ALLEN]
Hm?
[VAN] Rather than
fight the soldiers,
we kill the man pulling
their strings.
The man who betrayed Fanelia.
The one who now serves Dornkirk.
[ALLEN]
Who's that?
[VAN] Zaibach's Strategos.
Folken Lacour de Fanel.
Hold on a second.
You heard right.
That man is my brother.
[gasps]
[screams]
Oh, that's just great.
[HITOMI] Well that
can't be a good sign.
[MERLE humming]
Oh, wow, what a mess!
Why would Hitomi leave her
shoe here? That's weird.
[alarm whistles]
[ROYAL GUARD A] Hurry!
They've left the castle!
You stay here and
keep an eye out.
I'll go search for
Hitomi in Escaflowne.
[MERLE]
You're gonna leave me?!
[NARIA]
Don't try to fight me.
[alarm continues]
Hitomi.
[ALLEN]
Mother! Please wake up!
You can't leave me all
alone! Please, mother!
[ALLEN whimpers]
Why?
Why is it I lose everyone
who's important to me?
If you make a sound,
you're dead.
[HUNTER A]
Hmph. That's what they get.
[HUNTER B] Yeah, shouldn't've
got in the way of our hunt.
[HUNTER A] Tellin' us
not to hurt the forest.
Mangy beast-men. They
oughta know their place!
They killed Father.
[NARIA]
And Mother.
[HITOMI gasping]
[ERIYA]
Please don't cry, Belubelu.
We still have each other.
[HUNTER A chuckles]
Finally found 'em.
[HUNTER B] A set of
gold and silver twins.
[HUNTER A]
Talk about rare catch.
They'll be worth a fortune!
[NARIA grunts]
[ERIYA gasping]
[HITOMI]
I see now.
[NARIA]
Uh.
[HITOMI]
So that's what happened.
[HITOMI] Can you tell me
why you're doing this?
Is it for Van's brother?
Is it for Folken?
[NARIA growls]
So this is all just to repay
him for saving you?
Shut up!
But what you're
doing is wrong!
Can't you see that? Can't you?
[HITOMI yelps]
[NARIA groaning]
[HITOMI gasps]
[NARIA] Don't even think
about trying to escape.
Do you hear me, girl?
I'm taking you with
me. To Lord Folken.
[NARIA groaning]
Talk to me.
Tell me your name.
Please. You're in no
shape to continue on.
Would you mind if I
took you back with me
to get help from my friends?
Uh! I mean it. I'll talk
to Allen and the others!
Trust me.
Despite everything
that's happened,
I know they'll understand.
You're not a bad person.
Just let me prove it to them.
[NARIA laughs] Sounds like an
easy way to get me to surrender.
Do you honestly expect me to
believe what you're saying?
[HITOMI]
It's true.
The only person I trust...
is Lord Folken.
[HITOMI]
Uh!
[HITOMI] Oh, I see.
She's in love with Folken?
[FOLKEN]
The harbor?
[DORNKIRK] The girl will
be arriving there shortly.
We must be ready to greet her.
Dispatch the Intensified
Luck Soldier
to that location at once!
We can't do that!
She hasn't fully recovered
from her recent injuries yet.
[DORNKIRK] That will not
inhibit her success.
There is nothing to fear. The
device is functioning normally.
[FOLKEN]
But, sir.
[ERIYA]
Lord Folken.
You don't have to
worry about me.
I can handle this. I beg of
you. Let me prove my worth.
[FOLKEN]
Eriya.
Where is she? Come on.
[gasps]
One of those luck soldiers!
[GADDES]
Hafta say, I'm surprised.
I was sure they'd use this
harbor to make their escape.
[ALLEN]
As was I.
Prep Scheherazade
for deployment.
[GADDES]
Yes, sir.
[ROYAL GUARD B]
Look!
No! I don't have time to fight
with you right now, dragon!
Get back here!
[VAN]
Uh. What the...?
Is this more of
that damn luck of theirs?!
[yells]
It's no use.
I can't get anywhere close like
this. It's time for Plan B.
[VAN]
Where are you, Folken?
I've found you!
[HITOMI] Whatever you do,
don't go back to Folken!
If you're gonna take this ship,
use it to get someplace
far away!
Don't you understand all
he's doing is hurting you?
Using a machine to
change your body.
Even if it's done for the
sake of someone you love.
It isn't right!
Be quiet.
I won't! It's wrong
and you know it!
[HITOMI] But. Doesn't she
care about herself at all?
[VARIE] You didn't
mean to, of course,
but your wishes were made
with a troubled mind.
Even now, the uncertainty
in your heart
is bringing forth grief.
[HITOMI]
My uncertainty?
[GRANDMOTHER]
Trust your feelings.
Believe in those around you.
Your wishes will come
true. Just have faith.
[HITOMI] Trust my feelings.
I have to have faith.
I'm surprised.
I thought you'd be more afraid.
[HITOMI gasps]
Do you not realize what's
going to happen to you?
Well. I am afraid, but...
You're afraid? Then
why not try to run?
You could've escaped by
now if you wanted to.
But you're here. It
doesn't make sense.
[HITOMI] It's because...
I believe in you.
[NARIA]
Uh?
I can feel it in my heart that
you're not a bad person.
And I'm trusting that
feeling with my life.
[NARIA]
Heh.
[gasps]
There you are!
[NARIA]
Eriya!
--Listen.
--[HITOMI grunts]
Serving Lord Folken is
all that matters to me.
If I do that, then
I have no regrets.
[HITOMI]
I can't get through to her!
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A]
Dragon approaching!
How could he have spotted us?!
Folken!
[ZAIBACH SOLDIERS scream]
[VAN] Where are you, coward?
Show yourself!
[NARIA, HITOMI gasp]
Lord Folken!
What now?
Come on, we have to go!
[HITOMI] What can I do
to make you understand?
[NARIA groaning]
Huh?
[ERIYA gagging]
[NARIA gasps]
[HITOMI]
What's happening?
[NARIA]
Get back, stay away from me.
"Hitomi". That's a pretty
enough name, I guess.
Uh.
[NARIA]
Naria.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
[NARIA] You asked
me what my name was.
Lord Folken gave it to me.
Naria. Please.
Ah!
[ERIYA]
What are you doing?!
All she'd do is get in our
way if we took her with us.
Let's go, Eriya! We have to
get back to Lord Folken!
Naria.
[ALLEN]
Hitomi!
Hitomi! Up here!
[VAN]
Folken! Come out and face me!
That's Enough.
There you are!
Why don't you
understand, Van?
We have no choice but
to make a new world.
And we've almost succeeded.
All that's left
is the final battle.
Just accept it... please!
[VAN growling]
[VAN yells]
[NARIA] It's all right, my lord.
We'll take care of him.
[FOLKEN]
Naria!
You should get out of my way!
[ERIYA]
What is your problem?!
[VAN]
Uh?
You have no idea what Lord
Folken has done to protect you!
If it weren't for him,
you'd be dead by now!
And this is how you
choose to repay him?!
What are you trying to say?
Oh, Eriya.
[ERIYA] I won't let anyone
make Lord Folken sad!
Not even his own brother!
[NARIA]
Lord Folken!
What could have done this?
Naria. I'm sorry.
Please, Lord Folken. You
have to get away from here.
Don't worry about us, we'd
only slow you down like this.
We're so grateful that you saved
us all those years ago, my lord.
And we're happy our last moments
in life can be spent with you.
Goodbye, Lord Folken.
[DORNKIRK]
There was a reaction?
I never would have
expected such irony.
That enhancing their good luck
could bring about this
misfortune in the end.
And yet, this experiment
was still a success beyond
all of my wildest expectations.
At last!
After all this time, I
finally have the answer.
With this information, our fate
equations shall now be flawless!
You know nothing
of which you speak!
[DORNKIRK]
What?
He survived?
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[FOLKEN] Van, put
your weapon down, now!
You're no brother of mine!
[VAN groans]