[SOLDIER A]
What's that strange light?
[SOLDIER B] It's coming from
the capital of the empire.
[SOLDIER A]
Could it be?
[SOLDIER B]
It's finally all over.
The Zaibach empire has fallen.
Zone of Absolute Fortune?
[DORNKIRK] Yes. The activation
of the Fate Alteration Engine
has achieved what we intended:
A complete change of destiny.
It will grant
everyone their wishes,
creating perfect
happiness and harmony.
This is the ultimate purpose
of the Atlantis Machine
and the ultimate
test of its power.
That's insane.
Atlantis was totally
destroyed because of it!
[COMMANDER A] The Zaibach
forces are withdrawing.
[GENERAL A] Hmm. With the
majority of its army wiped out,
Zaibach is as good as gone.
It is the actions that we take
now that will truly determine
Basram's place in
the world, however.
Change course,
and Make for Norte!
[OFFICER A]
Huh?
We might as well strike down
those alliance pigs too
while we still have the chance!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[OFFICER B]
It's the Daedalus army!
They're launching
a surprise attack!
So the moment our success
is ensured, they turn on us?
Then we will cut them
off at the knees!
Men of the Kingdom of Cesario,
go forth and seize your
moment of triumph!
Kill them all!
[GENERAL B]
Those worthless wretches.
Without our assistance, they all
would have fallen to Zaibach!
Give no quarter!
Annihilate them!
[SOLDIER C]
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
The Basram army!
[ROYAL SOLDIERS scream]
[SOLDIER D grunts]
[scoffs] So the alliance is
now shattered in pieces?
[GADDES]
What the hell?
They're all fighting each other!
Oh boy, Sarge!
Up ahead- A Basram leviship!
[GADDES]
Huh?
There are the sniveling
Asturian cowards!
Strike them down at once!
Take us down lower!
They nailed us!
[TEO]
We just lost a levistone!
Prepare for landing!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
What the--?
Why are they
fighting each other?
Zaibach's the enemy!
Stop it. Now!
[HITOMI]
What's going on?
Why are the allies all turning
against each other now?
[DORNKIRK] It's the destiny
they've chosen for themselves.
[HITOMI gasps]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Hunting down these
stragglers couldn't be easier.
Huh?
[DILANDAU]
Sadly for you,
I'm still nowhere near
finished fighting my battle.
Van!
[DORNKIRK]
The Zone of Absolute Fortune
has granted everyone
their wishes,
but in so doing made
the fighting worse.
Given the chance,
people still embrace the
most violent of destinies.
It's almost as if that's what
they've wished for all along.
That's not true!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
Where is he? I've lost
sight of Lord Dilandau.
[MALE SORCERER A]
Jajuka, I have another child
for you to look after.
Remember, you are not to speak
of our experiments with anyone.
[CELENA whimpers]
[CELENA]
Don't leave me alone in here.
I just want to go home.
Eat something, child.
If you should die,
they will punish me.
[CELENA whimpers]
Huh?
You poor thing.
They've even cut your mane.
I have to find him quickly.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[HITOMI]
Please! Stop that machine!
All this fighting needs to end!
[DORNKIRK]
Impossible.
Once it has been set in motion,
fate cannot be stopped.
[DORNKIRK] If it is
destruction that people desire,
then we must
accept that reality.
Damn it!
[gasps]
[GUYMELEF SOLDIER  screams]
There it is; the red Guymelef.
[DILANDAU laughs]
[DILANDAU]
Ah, there you are1
I knew you couldn't hide
from me forever, Van!
[grunts]
Dilandau!
Let's end this!
Nice!
[grunts]
[yells]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
Jajuka!
Please, Lord Dilandau!
You've got to get out of here!
It's all right, now!
Don't be afraid to change back!
It's safe to become
Celena again!
Jujuka.
I won't hurt you, child.
You can call me Jajuka.
What the--?
Behave yourself,
uppity beast-man!
Jajuka!
Let me go!
Please don't take her away!
Celena!
[DILANDAU]
Jajuka.
Don't leave me. Don't go.
Time to end this!
No, Van!
[VAN]
What?
[SOLDIERS shouting]
Allen?
Van, that's enough!
Weapons down!
No way! That lunatic is
obsessed with fighting!
I'll be erasing a source
of evil from the world!
[ALLEN]
Wrong!
Killing Dilandau like this
won't solve anything!
It just continues
the cycle of violence!
What?!
My country was destroyed!
You can't possibly
understand my pain!
Then you'll have
to go through me.
[grunts]
'Cause Dilandau is
my younger sister!
[VAN grunts]
Allen, have you lost your mind?
I accept responsibility
for her crimes.
Even if she was being controlled
by the twisted magic of Zaibach.
Don't hold back!
Take your shot!
[growls]
[ALLEN]
Well, Van Fanel!
Fight me!
[VAN yells]
I am Allen Schezar,
Knight Caeli,
we shall fight until
the bloody, bitter end!
[GADDES]
Scherazade and Escaflowne!
Uh! The boss and the king
are going head to head!
Yeah, and it's
definitely for real.
It ain't gonna be over until
one of them ends up stone dead.
Why, Sarge?
[HITOMI]
Why are Van and Allen fighting?
Because this is what
they both wished for.
No, please.
Stop it Van!
I'm amazed at how much
better you've gotten.
Keep it up, Van!
[grunts]
[ALLEN yells]
Alan controls his Guymelef
better than I remember.
[VAN grunts]
Come on. Is that all you've got?
Van, you've become an
excellent swordsman.
You almost remind me of Balgus!
I want to beat him--
No, I have to beat him!
[DORNKIRK]
Gleefully fighting like a pair
of bloodthirsty dogs.
Look at how happy they are.
And why wouldn't they be?
The Zone of Absolute Fortune
has granted their
deepest wishes.
Celena!
[CELENA]
Brother?
Brother, wait!
[gasps]
Please help me, Brother!
Celena?!
Come on!
Stop it!
That's enough!
[VAN gasps]
[HITOMI]
This fight has to end!
[VAN]
What? Hitomi?
This is all because
of Dornkirk's machine!
What do you mean?
It set this insanity in motion!
If we don't do something,
Gaea will end up
just like Atlantis!
Fine. So I'll finish
things with Allen,
and then I'll go kill
Emperor Dornkirk!
No! The point is, you have
to stop fighting, Van!
But I'm trying to put
an end to this war.
I will avenge my brother.
And I will keep you safe!
Please just stop!
Those emotions are what make
you want to keep fighting!
[VAN] Don't you get it?
I'm fighting to protect you!
[HITOMI] I never
asked you to do that!
You don't have to!
Besides, you aren't protecting
me by fighting Allen.
Oh, so that's it.
You're just worried
about your boyfriend.
I'm not!
You're not listening to
what I'm trying to say at all!
I worry about you all the time,
and do you know why?
Because I care about
you more than anything.
Why can't you
understand that, Van?
[FOLKEN]
It will be all right.
As long as you believe in him.
[HITOMI]
How did you?
[FOLKEN] Some emotions
are powerful enough
to move the very heavens.
But when one heart holds
two conflicting emotions,
it can cause great strife,
and terrible unhappiness.
If that conflict
can be resolved,
much harm can be avoided.
So, you're saying that,
my heart is conflicted.
I know I feel bound to Van,
but in what way, exactly?
I've cared about him
deeply ever since we met.
And I believe in him.
Because I...
I love Van.
The truth is right
in front of me.
I really do love him!
[HITOMI]
His familiar smell.
The smell of a field.
[HITOMI]
I love Van... with all my heart.
[VAN]
Hitomi?
[HITOMI]
I'm sorry. Now I know.
I was the one who
didn't understand.
[ALLEN]
Celena!
[VAN gasps]
Celena.
It's really you.
Do you truly recognize me?
[CELENA]
Brother. I missed you.
[ALLEN]
Celena!
I'm so glad you've returned.
[ALLEN] I'll never
leave you alone again.
That's Celena. Allen's
little sister.
Van, I heard Hitomi's
voice before.
Well, go, she's waiting.
Right.
Good.
Look.
It's a white dragon.
[ASTURIAN SOLDIERS cheer]
[DORNKIRK] Ultimately, I was
unable to control fate.
Just as I could not produce
gold through alchemy.
Perhaps it was always
my destiny to fail.
[HITOMI]
That's where you're wrong.
[DORNKIRK]
Hm?
I don't think fate
is ever certain.
We create a new destiny
with every breath we take.
[SOLDIERS chatter]
Dragons are drawn
to an angry heart.
And all conflict arises
from hate and fear.
[grunting]
Escaflowne, no!
[VAN]
Hi--!
Hitomi.
[growls]
No!
Look at that.
It's a white dragon.
[CESARIO SOLDIER]
What are we doing?
Is that it?
Hitomi!
Van!
I can feel it!
Van's coming for me!
[DORNKIRK]
Impossible.
Once activated, the Atlantis
Machine can't be stopped!
Van!
[DORNKIRK] This pure love
they have for each other...
This emotion they share...
Is it stronger than the violence
that dwells at the
heart of humanity?
Can anything overpower that?
But, can a moment
like this last forever?
It is only fleeting.
A moment created by two
easily swayed human hearts.
Hitomi.
[SACHIKO]
I really think he's into me.
I just have a feeling about it.
[NAO] Aren't you being
a little overconfident?
[SACHIKO giggles]
[GIRL STUDENT]
Nao, don't be so mean about it.
Hey, you could have
your fortune read!
See if Takuya's really
interested in you, Sachiko!
Hey! Hitomi, help us!
You know all about
that stuff, right?
Read Sachiko's fortune for her!
Actually, I gave
up fortune telling.
Sorry, Nao.
[CARPENTERS chatter]
--[VILLAGERS chatter]
--[CHILDREN giggle]
[MERLE]
I brought you your dinner!
Thanks! I'll be right there!
[VAN] Brother,
you've finally returned.
You're back home.
Back in Fanelia.
Now, you can watch over our
country's future from here.
[HITOMI] It feels almost
like a lifetime ago.
Meeting you for the first
time and coming to Fanelia.
[HITOMI]
So what happens now?
[VAN] Everyone's dreams
will go on creating Gaea.
[VAN] Thank you
for everything, Escaflowne.
[HITOMI]
Van?
[VAN] Escaflowne should
be kept asleep from now on.
My brother's greatest wish
was for a Fanelia, and a Gaea,
that could stand
strong without it.
I think now, his wish
may actually come true.
I'd love to see
that transformation.
It sounds amazing.
I don't know.
I do like it in Gaea.
Maybe I could be happy here.
You're welcome to stay, if that
really is what you want to do.
[gasps]
But, you know, we can be
together anytime we want to.
So long as our thoughts
reach each other.
Van...
[HITOMI]
Here.
I want you to keep it.
Please.
[HITOMI]
I'll never forget you,
even when I'm old.
You're the greatest thing
that ever happened to me.
[VAN gasps]
Goodbye, Van!
I won't forget you!
Hitomi...
Bye-bye, Hitomi!
[giggles]
Have a safe journey, Hitomi.
Goodbye, little lady!
Be good, now!
[SACHIKO]
I'm so jealous of Yukari!
[NAO]
I know, right?
She and Amano make
the perfect couple!
[SACHIKO] It's almost like they
were meant to be together!
[gasps]
Van...
Don't worry. I'm doing fine.