[FOLKEN] I'm glad you're
back. Did it go well?
[NARIA] Yes. We
completed our training.
[ERIYA] Even more
successfully than we'd hoped.
[FOLKEN] Excellent.
I'm very proud of you.
Some Sorcerers came with us.
What do they want with the
flying fortress, my lord?
They've come for Dilandau.
They'll be taking
him back with them.
It seems they were in
quite a hurry to get away.
I don't know why,
but they hate me.
If they act like they hate you,
it must be to
disguise their envy.
I have nothing but contempt
for all Sorcerers.
Don't say such things.
You may not like them, but you
should always respect them.
After all, my girls,
I was once a Sorcerer.
[NARIA]
Forgive us! We didn't know.
[ERIYA]
Lord Folken.
We missed you terribly
while we were away.
[NARIA] We counted the days
until we would see you again.
I missed you both, too.
I'm very sorry.
And now I must ask
for your help.
Please, lend me your strength.
[NARIA]
Anything for you. Our bodies.
[ERIYA] And our souls,
belong to you, Lord Folken.
[DRYDEN] That was trickier
than I thought it would be.
It took me a while
to figure out
that it's written in the
language of the Mystic Moon.
The Mystic Moon.
Are you certain?
Please, young master!
Leave well enough alone.
Zaibach is keeping a close
eye on your every move!
Nothing good can come of this.
I think it's time you went home.
[CLERK]
Uh?
I've decided that
I'd like to see
the Mystic Valley for myself.
So, turn this ship around,
and take it back to Palas.
[CLERK gasps]
[CLERK] No, please!
I beg you not to go!
How will I explain
to your father?
I can't return without
you or any cargo!
I'll write a note
for you to give him.
He won't have a problem if I say
I'm with Princess Millerna.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Don't argue with me. Besides,
Allen's coming, too.
And why should I be
a party to this?
Be honest with yourself.
What choice you got?
Your father ruthlessly abandoned
his home, his fortune,
and his family in search of
the fabled Mystic Valley.
Everyone in Asturia knows
your sad little story, even me.
[HITOMI] So that's where
Allen's father went.
[VAN]
Then I want to go, too.
The Mystic Valley is the
homeland of the Draconians.
I wanna see the place
my people came from,
the source of the blood
that flows through my veins.
To understand the bond between
that land and Escaflowne.
Well, I'll be damned.
So many of you people
seem to be connected
through the Mystic Valley.
I wonder if it's by design,
or if it's by destiny?
[DRYDEN] "Year of the Crystal
Northeast. Green, 12th moon.
I'm currently journeying towards
the dark continent of Asgard,
upon which no human
has set foot.
Yes, I am certain that's
where the Mystic Valley lies.
There, I will undoubtedly find
that which I've searched for
all these years. A power
that works miracles.
The incomparable power
of Atlantis itself."
[CREWMAN A]
Boss, the helm's not responding!
We're never gonna make it
through this crazy storm!
[CREWMAN B] Bad news, Captain!
The Energist isn't cooling down.
Damn it all! It's the blasted
curse of the Draconians!
We were fools to think we
could sail these waters.
Okay, boys! Turn us around now!
[CREWMEN]
Sir!
[LEON] I don't think so.
That wasn't our agreement.
This ship had better
not turn around.
I paid your fee, and I intend
to get my money's worth.
But the ship'll break apart!
If we go any further,
then we're all gonna die.
Come on, man, even
you can't be that crazy.
I paid enough to buy
your lives twice over.
So keep flying, Captain.
[LEON] Countless days
passed after that.
In my hazy stupor, all I
could think about was her.
Her voice. Her face.
Nothing else mattered
to me. And then...
Asgard loomed ahead
before my weary eyes.
The gods have guided me here.
This is my one true destiny.
I've traveled so far.
It must be.
His destiny?
[LEON]
A cruel twist of fate
led to that first
meeting in my youth.
Crueler still, our
sudden separation.
But what is she to me, truly?
I have journeyed
here to find that out.
She is etched so
deeply into my mind.
I will never be free
until I see her again.
Everything is there
in the Mystic Valley.
Everything I've been
searching for.
[ALLEN]
What a joke!
So he left his home,
he left his family,
just to find some girl he'd only
seen once before? Pathetic.
Well, honestly, he sounds
like my kinda guy.
[ALLEN]
What?
He's a lot more interesting
than my old man, anyway.
All he does is sit
and count his money.
Your father was a risk taker.
Wasn't afraid to
chase his dreams.
Ignore him, Allen.
[AMANO] Really? Nobody
has found Hitomi yet?
[HITOMI'S MOTHER]
No. I'm afraid not.
But please, you really
mustn't blame yourself.
This isn't anyone's fault.
I dream about her.
I'm standing alone
at the station.
I'm on my way to school, waiting
for Hitomi to meet up with me,
like she does every day.
Then she comes running over,
and says, "Good morning."
But right after-- That's
when I always wake up.
[AMANO]
It's okay.
I know how you feel. I dream
about Hitomi, as well.
My daughter will be all right.
I feel that in my soul.
She'll hit some
difficult patches,
but I know she'll pull through.
[REEDEN] Awww. Nothin'
but horizon out there.
All that ocean's
messin' up my view.
What now, Sarge?
Keep going straight ahead.
Dryden insisted this is
the best way to get there.
Yeah, but can we really
trust that shady guy?
Commander gave us
an order, so do it!
I'm not gonna tell you again.
Hey, Pyle! How's it
goin' down there?
All right, we're
makin' some headway.
It's still gonna take
a little more time
to install the control
chamber parts
we took out of Dryden's
Guymelefs, though.
[TEO]
Oh, that's just great.
I have the wrong
size screw here.
[ORT]
Careful. You'll break it.
[TEO]
Don't tell me what to do.
[DRYDEN]
"Blue, 16th moon.
Driven snow and jagged
rocks block my path,
as if to warn those who
dare challenge the mystery.
Has anybody else
ever made it this far?
Yesterday. I came upon a cave."
[LEON] Inside was a man, another
who sought the Mystic Valley.
Despite his age, he searched
as I did, eager for answers.
Desperate to find that which
had eluded him for so long.
A fellow traveler.
When I asked him his name,
the old man said Isaac.
[HITOMI'S MOTHER]
I've never shared this
with anyone before now.
But I think it's important
that you two know.
You see, when I was
only a little girl,
my mother told me
an amazing story.
She was just about the
same age Hitomi is now.
[HITOMI'S MOTHER] She was on her
way back home from a festival,
when a bright light
shone down on her,
and she suddenly realized
she was standing by herself
in a frightening
and unfamiliar land.
[LEON] Isaac and I sat down to
talk, and he told me his story.
He, too, was looking
for the Mystic Valley,
and the ancient
mystery of Atlantis.
Then he told me
something incredible.
Something I almost
couldn't believe.
He'd come from the Mystic
Moon, just like her!
He was from the
Mystic Moon, too?
Yes. Pretty amazing, isn't it?
Wait, is that--?
[YUKARI]
Hitomi?
No, it's my mother, actually.
[HITOMI]
Then this means...
That man must be Allen's father.
That light again.
That girl looks like...
Am I seeing things?
[LEON] You're from the Mystic
Moon? That's incredible.
I left on this journey
because I wanted to be free,
to roam the world
without any ties.
But now, when I gaze
into your eyes,
I begin to think that's
not what I want at all.
How can I feel both lost
and found at the same time?
[HITOMI'S GRANDMOTHER]
Hitomi.
[gasps]
Hitomi?
It was my Grandma.
[SORCERER A] Thank you for this
audience, General Adelphos,
we have come to ask
your permission
to take Dilandau back with us.
[ADELPHOS]
Hmph.
I never heard of a Sorcerer
asking permission for anything.
Do what you want.
Besides you were the
ones who sent him to me
in the first place.
I am curious, though. May I
ask why you want him back?
[SORCERER A] We've received
word from Strategos Folken.
Dilandau has fallen ill
and needs immediate care.
Ugh. Quite frankly, I find
that difficult to believe.
I didn't know monsters could
get sick like we humans.
If you'll excuse me, we can't
afford to waste any time,
given the serious nature
of his condition.
Once he has recovered,
we will return him to you.
[DILANDAU screaming]
He's becoming more
unstable by the moment.
But what's causing it?
[SORCERER A]
The fate alteration experiment
wasn't completely successful.
[SORCERER B] Folken doesn't
need to know the details.
[SORCERER A]
Very well.
No! Shesta! Dallet!
Where are you?!
[MALE SORCERER B] He will get
much worse if this keeps up.
[MALE SORCERER C]
Put him to sleep.
That will do for now.
Once we return to the Homeland,
we will try performing
another alteration.
[DORNKIRK]
Asgard, you say?
That can only mean one thing.
Unless I am very much mistaken,
they're heading for
the Mystic Valley.
Forgive me, Emperor,
are you sure?
The Mystic Valley is a legend.
[DORNKIRK]
Indeed it is.
The homeland of the Draconians,
the ancient people of Atlantis.
And it would appear
they've found it.
[LEON]
White, 3rd moon.
Isaac and I had come upon a
moor shrouded in fog so thick
we could hardly see.
I felt certain we were closing
in on the Mystic Valley.
But at some point, I don't
know exactly when, or how,
Isaac disappeared.
Did he become lost in the fog?
Perhaps he was injured
somehow and fell behind?
It doesn't matter.
I cannot allow myself to be
distracted by anything now.
I must focus on reaching
the Mystic Valley.
Then I can solve the
mystery of Atlantis
and harness that ancient power.
Then perhaps, after
all these long years,
I can look upon that girl again.
If I could only see her
face, just once more.
I've heard enough!
Allen, wait!
Aw, running away?
I can't believe
this is all it takes
to get a rise out of one of
the fearless Knights Caeli.
That's just so sad.
Think it's safe to say that you
and I will never be friends.
Ha! Well, I am relieved
to hear that!
Being your friend is
the last thing I want.
[HITOMI]
Dryden.
Why are you being so mean?
Hitomi!
Ahh. I'm not very popular
with the ladies today.
Are you okay, Allen?
[ALLEN]
Hitomi.
[HITOMI]
Yes.
[ALLEN] I'm sorry you had
to witness that ugliness.
[HITOMI]
That's okay. Dryden's a jerk.
I still can't forgive my father,
and I don't think
I'll ever be able to.
He abandoned us.
He's dead to me.
I don't think you
really mean that.
You kept your father's
journal all this time.
I bet it's more important to
you than you even realize.
You could've thrown
it away, but you didn't.
I think, somewhere
deep down in your heart,
you wanted to know more
about who your father was.
To try to understand him better.
You're one of the
kindest people I know.
You don't have it in you to
hate somebody else that much.
Everyone here thinks
the world of you.
If you were really
that cold inside,
then nobody, including me,
would feel that way.
We wouldn't even like you.
You should forgive him.
Hatred doesn't solve anything,
and it only hurts
you in the end.
Maybe I was afraid of
finding out the truth.
That he didn't love us enough
and he really did abandon us.
I didn't wanna believe it,
and reading it
would've made it real.
I understand.
I know I don't deserve it,
but please say you'll
forgive my weakness.
We're almost there.
Just a little more chop.
I'm going up to check.
You stay here, Merle.
King Van, come back.
What in the hell?
There's a levistone
storm out there!
Hey, Reeden! Keep
your eyes wide open!
If we hit one, we're dead!
[REEDEN]
Yes, sir!
I'm so sorry.
There you are, I've
been looking all over.
We should get up
to the pilothouse.
C'mon. We're in the homestretch.
[REEDEN]
Levistone ahead! Hard to port!
[KIO]
Can do!
Steady, man! We're
getting real close, now.
[KIO]
Aye, sir!
A clear patch.
The Mystic Valley is just ahead.
[HITOMI] Is this really
the Mystic Valley?
[VAN]
There's nothing down there.
What do you mean?
That's impossible.
Uh.
Hey, what's the matter?
[DRYDEN] A page has been
torn out of the log.
[PYLE] Sarge! Zaibach
floating fortress in sight!
[GADDES]
What?
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A]
Asturian skiff spotted!
[FOLKEN]
Excellent.
Naria. Eriya.
Girls, do you read me?
Absolutely, Lord Folken.
We're ready at any time.
We'll bring your little brother
back to you alive and unharmed.
I'm counting on you.
Let's do it, Eriya.
Loud and clear, sister.
No doubt about it.
That's them for sure.
What? How did they find us?
They're trying to force us down.
Pyle! How's Scherazade coming?
[PYLE] Not even close! We're
still less than half done!
[HITOMI'S GRANDMOTHER]
Hitomi.
[HITOMI gasps]
[HITOMI'S GRANDMOTHER]
I promise,
if your wishes are pure
and clear enough,
every last one will come true.
Hitomi, I want you to have this.
[HITOMI] Grandma.
Show us the Mystic Valley.
Please tell us where it is.
We need your help.
[DRYDEN] I won't be denied.
I've come too far.
I will see the Mystic Valley!
[VAN] Mother, what would
you want me to do?
[ALLEN]
I refuse to die now. Not here.
Mark my words, Father.
I'll settle things with
you once and for all
in the Mystic Valley.
[chuckling]
So, brother,
what truth do you hope the
Mystic Valley will reveal?
[FOLKEN] It can't be. The Gate
of Atlantis is opening.
But how?
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[VAN]
Stay away from me!
[BALGUS]
Listen to me King Van.
[VAN yelling]