[DILANDAU] Shesta! Have you
located the dragon yet?
[SHESTA] No, sir. There
hasn't been any sign of it.
Most of the enemy's Melef
units have been wiped out.
We now control
the castle grounds.
Something strange
is going on here.
They're not putting up
nearly enough resistance.
And there's no sign
of the dragon, either.
Something's not right.
[SHESTA] We're preparing to
enter the castle itself.
[DILANDAU]
Don't, Shesta.
We're going to hold
position right here.
[SHESTA]
But, sir!
Don't make me repeat myself.
We stay in place and wait for
the dragon to make its move.
Lord Folken, sir.
The Dragonslayers appear to
be holding their position.
So, he's using caution.
A nice change.
I sense something off here, too.
It can't be this easy
to steal a secret treasure
that's been passed down
since time immemorial.
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER 13A]
There's still one left.
Freid has safeguarded its
treasure for generations.
We will not relinquish it now.
Farewell, Prince Chid.
May you grow to be a wise ruler.
[ZAIBACH SOLDIERS screaming]
What? What's happening?
This was your plan from
the beginning, wasn't it?
Lure us in and bring the
roof down on our heads.
I have to admit: I'm impressed.
[chuckles] You sacrificed
that many troops to keep
your precious treasure safe?
Admirably pragmatic of you.
Well played, Freid.
This round goes to you.
[DILANDAU cackles]
[SHESTA]
Lord Dilandau!
The castle's burning.
There's almost nothing left.
[CHID]
Voris... All those men...
They sacrificed themselves.
They're all dead.
They gave their lives
so that we could escape.
[VORIS]
Wait, Fanelia! I need a word.
Voris? What do you want?
This is not easy for me
to do, but there is
a special favor I would ask of
you, on behalf of all of Freid.
You don't need to ask.
I'm on my way to defend
the castle gate now.
[VORIS]
We'll see to that ourselves.
Please, Your Majesty.
I beg you hear me out
and do as I ask.
[FREID]
Stop crying!
Rather than wasting
your time on tears,
look down at the castle.
Look at the place where
Voris and his men
gave their lives to protect you.
Those soldiers died
bravely, doing their duty.
And we who rule Freid
have a duty as well.
Those men don't want your tears
and we have no time for them.
[MILLERNA]
Allen...
I see how you look at Chid,
with such sad eyes.
He's your son.
Yours and Marlene's.
Chid is my son,
do you understand?
[MILLERNA] Chid and I are
the only ones who didn't know.
[HITOMI]
We're moving fast.
Soon it'll be out of sight.
[DORNKIRK]
Listen carefully, Folken.
Aberrations have appeared in my
Destiny Prognostication Engine.
What we seek lies to
the west of Godashim.
You must find it.
Do you understand, Strategos?
To the west of Godashim.
Fortona Temple!
[DORNKIRK] I have grown
so very weary of waiting.
I want to see our
ideal future realized.
Until that happens,
our work is not finished.
We make for Fortona.
The oldest temple
in all of Freid.
[FREID] We are about to
fight our final battle.
The ancient treasure of Freid
must be protected at all costs.
Fortona Temple is
our last bastion.
I have come to ask you,
the Zegu Clan, for your aid.
We will need it in this
dark and desperate hour.
[KAJA]
We understand well.
Our clan has lived in
anticipation of this day.
Those who have died already
did not do so in vein.
It's our duty to guard the
treasure entrusted to Freid.
We do that duty willingly.
My Duke.
We return to you the
treasure sword of Freid,
which was given into our care
so very many years ago.
Come, Chid.
Young though you may be,
it is time for you to learn
the duty of those born
into Freid's royal house.
Huh?
[FREID]
Fanelia. Allen.
I would have you
hear this as well.
You who fight along side us.
[MERLE]
Meow. It's creepy in here.
[HITOMI] What is it about
this place? It's like...
...like I feel a
strange power here.
[gasps]
Whoa!
That looks like...
[FREID] This writing is
that of ancient Atlantis.
This is the secret
treasure of Freid,
which we have guarded
for countless years.
We protect the
power of Atlantis.
It's all set down here in this
ancient Atlantian writing.
The power of Atlantis!
What's wrong with you?
I can see it. I can see it all.
The people of
Atlantis were powerful.
They had absolute
dominion over the land,
the seas, and skies.
As time passed, they grew
prideful and arrogant.
They styled themselves as gods,
with dominion over all things.
[HITOMI] With their ability to
turn human will into energy,
they ruled absolutely.
However...
Hey!
Hitomi?
Atlantis was destroyed
by the same power
that had ruled it, collapsing
amid fire and smoke.
The survivors sealed that
power here beneath Fortona.
So fearful were they,
of it ever being used again.
Now, here we are today.
Whatever happens, we
must defend this sword,
the key to the
ancient Atlantian seal,
the duty of Freid's
royal house. And, Chid,
we must never allow the power of
Atlantis to be awakened again.
As my son, you share
this burden with me.
Are you ready to do your duty?
Yes. I am, Father.
[MERLE]
Hitomi?
What's he...?
--[clock ticking]
--[heart beating]
[HITOMI]
Van?
Uh--
Hitomi? What's wrong?
Nothing, but Allen's
looking for you.
I had a pretty good feeling
I'd find you here.
You were right.
[HITOMI] You don't look
like you feel so good.
What were you doing just now?
I was trying that mind
trick you told me about.
Hey, you know, earlier...
I was outta line.
I shouldn't have pressured
you like that, I'm sorry.
I didn't stop to think
about how you might feel.
I can't stand to have
another vision like that!
No, I'm sorry, too. I guess
I was a little hysterical.
Let's just forget about it.
Anyway, like I said,
I was trying that
thing you showed me.
The trick you do
with the pendant.
You called it
"dowsing," didn't you?
[HITOMI]
Yeah, that's right.
I thought it sounded useful.
I like the idea of being
able to see the unseen
just by concentrating.
Maybe with dowsing,
I can control Escaflowne
in a different way:
by linking it to my thoughts.
Can you imagine how good
a pilot that would make me?
If I can get the hang
of this, I won't just
use Escaflowne, I'll
become it when I fight.
I don't know...
[VAN]
Hitomi. I meant to tell you...
[gasps]
Tell me what?
[HITOMI]
Oh, no!
[gasps]
Duke Freid, are you okay?
It's raining. Raining blood.
[gasps]
What's the matter?
It's starting now.
The battle's begun.
[gasps]
[REEDEN]
Sarge! Sarge! They're coming.
Those Zaibach bastards
are heading our way.
Okay.
If they manage to
breach the third line,
I want you to prep the Crusade.
We will defend this temple
to the death. Got it?
[FREID SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[MERLE]
Please, God.
You are a god, aren't you?
Well, whoever you are.
I beg you, please
protect King Van.
Let him live through the battle
and come back to us safely.
Please just keep him alive.
Will you do that? Will you, God?
Will you protect
King Van for me?
[GUYMELEF SOLDIER 13A]
Here they come!
[grunts]
[SOLDIERS grunt]
[ALLEN grunting]
They've broken through!
Filthy Zaibach scum! Die!
Out of my way!
You're mine, Duke!
[grunts]
[DILANDAU yells]
[GUYMELEF SOLDIER 13B groans]
That was almost as difficult
as swatting a fly.
[FREID yells]
[groans]
Three more limbs to go!
[GUYMELEF SOLDIER 13C]
Duke Freid!
[FREID]
Damn you, Zaibach!
[yells]
Now, say goodbye!
So, you came out to
play again, Allen.
[ALLEN] Duke. I'll take it
from here. You get to safety.
[grunts]
[KAJA]
Please, Duke!
We need to fall back to
the temple and regroup.
It's clear to me now.
What?
The gods do not want
the power of Atlantis
to remain buried. They
want it to be revived.
I can see now that
it is their desire
for the people of Gaea
to undergo that trial.
They shall have their wish.
I will give the treasure
into Zaibach's hands.
Even so.
The power of Atlantis is
the power of human will.
The ancients may have
seen their world
destroyed by it.
But Gaea is not Atlantis.
We won't necessarily
meet the same fate.
Destiny is not
fixed, but something
that we can forge ourselves.
A bright future may yet await
us, and it is the children
who will lead the way.
So, Kaja. I leave the
future in younger hands.
It is for me to shoulder
the burden of the past.
I will die with it.
Look after Chid for me.
He must finish
what I have begun.
His path will be difficult,
but I know he will persevere.
He is, after all, my son.
[laughing]
[growls]
Go. I'll handle this.
See to the duke!
Be careful!
[yells]
[DILANDAU grunts]
[grunts]
[yelps]
What are you doing?!
[FREID] I am Mahad dar Freid,
and this is my land!
If it's glory that you're after,
then come and try your
sword against mine.
I am ready for you.
Stand and face me!
Your Grace!
[groans]
Please, Your Grace.
I don't have much time left.
Before I go, say
you'll forgive me.
I never wanted to
leave you so soon.
However things began with us,
in time, I fell very
much in love with you.
[FREID]
Marlene...
Your Grace!
[KAJA]
Wait, Allen! Leave him!
The duke needs our help. Let go!
Our fight for the
ancient treasure is over.
That was his decision,
and we must honor it.
Please, try to understand.
[VAN yelling]
Is he a samurai, or a demon?
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER 9A]
Dilandau.
The Dragonslayers
are to fall back.
Duke Freid is dead.
This battle is over.
Your other task can
wait for another time.
[DILANDAU]
Damn it. Fine.
I guess I'll just have
my fun later, then.
The Dragonslayers
are returning, sir.
Good. Let's send a message
to General Adelphos.
Tell him: "In the name
of Emperor Dornkirk,
we will now be entering
peace negotiations.
As Empire Strategos, full
authority for these talks
has been given to me."
[CHID] Thank you for
your service, Kaja.
I will obey Father's
last request.
[GADDES]
Highness! We can still fight!
The commander hasn't given up.
I thank you, too, Gaddes.
Freid will never forget all you
and your men have done for her,
but my father believed
in this decision
so much that he died for it.
I will do as he wished.
And then I'll turn my
attention to rebuilding Freid.
That won't be easy.
I know I can do it
if I try hard enough.
You taught me to believe
in my dreams, Hitomi.
Your Highness...
[CHID]
I'm not going to cry anymore.
Father was right.
I need to be strong.
I'm the one who has
to rule Freid now.
I commend you for your wisdom
and your valor, Prince Chid.
We are all relieved to see an
end to this senseless fighting.
We had an agreement.
You plan to keep your word,
don't you, Lord Folken?
According to our
negotiations, Your Majesty
will offer the Zaibach Empire
a sign of his friendship.
In return, we agree not to
harm the airship Crusade.
So long as it stays
within Freid's borders,
we will not touch it.
Now then, as to your
part of the agreement.
[CHID] As ruler of this land I,
Chid zar Freid, hereby pass
on the secret treasure
we have protected
since time immemorial.
I entrust the seal sword
to the Zaibach Empire
as a sign of friendship.
[REEDEN]
We need help, Boss.
Well? What's the matter?
Something's not right
with the king.
He ain't comin' out of
Escaflowne for some reason.
--What?
--[HITOMI gasps]
[REEDEN] It hasn't moved
since he brought it
into the hangar. Not a twitch!
Boss, something's really wrong!
King Van, it's Merle.
Can you please say something?
King Van! Please!
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
No!
[MERLE]
Hitomi, I don't want him to die!
I can still fight!