[HITOMI]
Van! Snap out of it!
[MILLERNA]
What is it? What's wrong?
It's Van! He's in trouble.
Say something! Open your eyes!
Van!
[gasps]
Please! You have to wake up!
Wait, be careful!
You might not be
able to come back!
Remember the Doppelganger!
Hitomi!
[HITOMI] I have to do
something, or Van may die!
Wait! No!
Hitomi...
[HITOMI]
Van, where are you?
Van!
Wait! I'm coming!
No!
[MILLERNA gasps]
Her pulse stopped!
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
What is this place?
I don't think it's Heaven.
[gasps]
[panting]
Van. Let's go back.
[HITOMI]
Everybody's waiting.
[VAN whimpering]
[gasps] What's wrong?
[rumbling]
[SOULS screaming]
A fire.
Come on! You have
to snap out of it!
[HITOMI gasps]
[DRYDEN]
It's been three miets.
[MILLERNA] We have to bring her
around or they'll both die.
Wait, no!
Hey! Listen to me!
You can't give up!
Get your act together and
bring King Van back here!
Hey! Can you hear me?
Please, King Van!
That sounded like Merle.
[MERLE]
King Van!
[HITOMI]
Merle!
Van! We need your wings!
Please!
[MERLE yelps]
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasp]
[HITOMI grunts]
[MERLE, HITOMI gasp]
[VAN grunts]
[ALL laughing, cheering]
King Van's alive!
Ah... My face hurts.
You did it. You brought us back.
[MERLE]
Meo--
Thank you, Merle!
[CRUSADERS laugh]
[DILANDAU]
What a bunch of incompetents.
Guimel, Dallet,
Shesta, Gatty, Viole...
What did you do?
There's no glory in getting
yourself slaughtered like that.
[CHILD] Please! Please
don't leave me alone!
Don't leave me in here!
[pants]
All alone...
[DILANDAU gags]
[DORNKIRK]
With the conquest of Freid,
the Power Spot is ours.
However, we have
another concern.
[FOLKEN]
I believe you mean the dragon?
[DORNKIRK]
Yes.
The fate of the dragon
remains shrouded in mist,
growing ever dimmer
as time passes.
Yes, Imperial Majesty.
Fortunately, I already
have a plan in motion.
[DORNKIRK]
Capture the dragon.
You must capture it!
[screams]
[VAN pants]
This shaking...
It happens every time
I hold my sword.
Poor Van.
Ah. Allen?
[ALLEN] Don't worry
about Van. He'll recover.
How do you know?
He's been like that
since the battle.
I've seen it many times.
This is a trial all
swordsmen must endure.
[gasps]
Something I've endured
myself, in fact.
Grief can make people
do foolish things.
Especially arrogant young men.
[BALGUS]
I've heard of you.
You're the boy who's been
picking fights with swordsmen.
Seems like a reckless
thing to do.
[ALLEN] Heh. It sounds like
you're scared to fight me,
old man. Why not drop
the purse and walk away?
If you do that, I'll see
fit to spare your life.
[BALGUS] You hold your sword
skillfully enough, anyway.
What's your name?
I am Allen Schezar. Fight!
[yells]
[BALGUS]
You have excellent technique,
but that isn't enough.
True swordsmanship is much more.
You're not there yet.
[ALLEN]
Kill me!
[BALGUS]
Hm?
Just kill me and have done!
Why are you so eager to die?
[ALLEN] I have no family
or home, only my sword.
Life isn't worth living
if I've been defeated!
[BALGUS] Swordsmanship
isn't about strength.
It's not about technique.
It's what about lies within you.
That is what matters.
Your skills are sharp.
Hone yourself.
[ALLEN]
And that was how I met Balgus.
He became my master.
I was so frightened,
so lost, but with his help,
I was able to find my way.
Mastering the sword means
mastering yourself.
Someday I hope to match Balgus's
skill as a swordsman.
I haven't yet.
I don't know if I believe that.
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
You're an amazing fighter
and a great commander.
And you're kind, too. And smart.
I don't know much,
not about swords
and that kinda thing, anyway.
I can't think of anything
I could say that would make
Van feel better, but I'm
sure he would listen to you.
You know all about fighting
and leading people.
Everyone really looks up to you.
I don't know if I've ever met
a guy I like as much as you--
[gasps]
[HITOMI] Uh... So, if you could
help Van, that would be great!
Well. Thank you.
You may not realize, but you're
a pretty special person
yourself, Hitomi.
[DRYDEN] Hitomi, the girl
from the Mystic Moon,
and the mysterious
power she possesses.
Van, in whose veins runs
the blood of the Draconians.
Escaflowne...
...and the Zaibach
Empire's pursuit
of the Power Spot.
An incredible confluence of
strange events and people.
[groans] What does it all mean?
I keep feeling like
I almost have it!
Excuse me, but I, um...
I want to thank you.
Yeah? For what?
Spare me the court
manners, please.
Bows and timidity
don't suit you at all.
What's the matter with you?
There's no need to be rude.
I came to thank you
and to apologize
for how I acted before.
[laughs] There we go!
Confident and direct.
That's much more your style.
Well, I had ulterior
motives, of course.
I'll do anything to get
a lady's attention.
I'm sorry. It's only...
[DRYDEN]
Allen, right? I don't mind.
I'll just wait. I always
get what I want in the end.
[gasps]
[DRYDEN]
Well, anyway.
There's actually something
I could use your help with.
I'm not one to take advantage,
but if you'd like to thank me...
[ALLEN] I believe this is
what you were looking for.
My father's final logbook,
from his study.
Ah! Yes! This is it!
An old book? Is that
thing really so important?
[DRYDEN]
It absolutely is!
This "old book" may be the
key to solving the mystery
that's at the heart
of all of this.
Mystery?
Why, the mystery of Atlantis.
[MILLERNA]
Atlantis?
When I was younger,
my father told me
about Leon Schezar
and his great quest.
He was searching for the
secret treasure of Atlantis.
I'm just going to
borrow this for a bit.
Look I get it.
The man's a celebrity.
But he is also
continuing to humiliate me.
Even out here in
the middle of nowhere.
We should just give it
to him and be grateful.
It's a bargain compared
to what he paid
to have Escaflowne
repaired for us.
You're right, of course.
Let him have it.
[HITOMI groans]
I'm a moron!
Why did I have to
go and say that?
Now he probably thinks I'm
some sort of obsessed fangirl.
[MILLERNA]
Hitomi?
Hey, Millerna.
[MILLERNA]
I, uh...
I was wondering if I
could ask your opinion
about a, uh, friend of mine.
Sure.
[MERLE]
Meow?
[MILLERNA]
Well, she's been seeing a man
who she likes a lot, but she
found out that he's really
a playboy and even fathered a
child that no one knows about.
[HITOMI gasps]
What a jerk!
[MILLERNA]
Just listen until I'm through.
[HITOMI]
Sorry.
[MILLERNA] Anyway, my
friend met another man.
He's kind of weird,
but he's wealthy,
and he seems very sweet.
He really appears
to care for her.
[MERLE groans]
Could you be any more obvious?
A friend? Really?
[HITOMI]
And?
Well, that's it.
What do you think
my friend should do?
That's really rough.
But, to be honest,
if I found out the guy
I was seeing secretly had a kid,
I probably wouldn't
ever speak to him again.
Really? Why not?
[HITOMI] Well, not only
does he have a kid,
but he didn't tell anyone?
That just seems really
messed up to me.
That's true.
He is very handsome, though.
What about the other guy?
Is he attractive, too?
Well, yes. I suppose
he is good looking.
Plus, he's good in
the money department
and he likes her.
Sure sounds like she
should go with him.
That's pragmatic.
I guess she could also
go out with both of them
at the same time.
But that's immoral!
Or she could give up
on both of them
and die all alone.
A poor, tragic heroine.
Stop that! You're teasing m--
You're teasing my friend.
And what about the fact
that she has feelings
for one of them?
Doesn't that matter?
Yeah, that's what makes
this so complicated, I guess.
It's hard to go against
what your heart is telling you,
even when your
head knows better.
It just feels wrong somehow.
What your heart is telling you?
I could do a Tarot reading.
You know, to see
which of the guys
would be better for your friend.
I'm pretty accurate
for other people.
[MERLE]
Please! Don't be stupid!
Who cares about your readings?
You wanna figure things
out for someone else?
Why don't you figure out your
own feelings first, huh?
What do you mean?
My feelings about what?
Once and for all,
Do you like Allen
or do you like Van?
[gasps]
Uh...
Gah!
Who's it gonna be?
It's not any of
your business, but...
I like Allen. I'm just...
I'm just worried
about Van, that's all.
[HITOMI] "Worried"? Is that
really all, though?
Then maybe you should
just stay away from Van!
Allen, too. He's out
of your league.
Thanks a lot, you guys.
[ERIYA]
That's it. It is, right?
I can't believe we
ran into them here.
Must be our luck.
What do you think
we should do, sister?
Let's go introduce ourselves
and get a present
for Lord Folken.
[NARIA]
That sounds good.
Things were goin' real good,
but then my old lady found us.
Aw, man. That's rough.
[CREWMEN yell]
[ERIYA] There's a Guymelef here
by the name of Escaflowne.
[NARIA]
You will send it out now.
[ERIYA] If you don't
do as you're told...
[CREWMEN yell]
...you're all going to die.
[CREWMEN gasp]
Boss, quick! It's the empire!
Zaibach Guymelefs are here!
What?
--[MERLE] Wait, King Van!
--[HITOMI] Van, stop!
It's too soon! You're not ready!
She's right for once!
Fly!
[grunts]
He took Escaflowne out?
[ERIYA]
There it is.
[NARIA]
Come on. Let's get it.
[VAN grunts]
[HITOMI, MERLE yelp]
[grunts]
[VAN grunting]
That's a woman!
[ERIYA]
His stomach's wide open!
[VAN groans]
Get off!
[whimpering]
Oh, poor baby's shaking.
[NARIA]
I think he's scared.
[whimpering]
[NARIA] This guy took
out the Dragonslayers?
[ERIYA] He's been a real
hassle to Lord Folken.
I say we finish him off.
[BOTH gasp]
[MAN A]
Freaks!
--[MAN B] Mangy little...
--[MAN C] We don't need you...
[MAN D]
Get outta here!
[MAN E]
You're disgusting!
No, I won't let you!
If you want him,
then kill me first!
Get back, Merle.
[ERIYA] That isn't fair.
We almost had him.
[NARIA]
I know, but she is a cat.
[ERIYA]
I guess you're right. Let's go.
[sighs]
Merle!
You okay?
Ah!
I was so scared.
[whimpers]
But you're alive!
Oh, thank god!
I thought they were gonna
kill you! But you're all right!
[VAN]
Thanks to you.
[HITOMI]
So brave...
[DRYDEN laughing]
[DRYDEN]
I found it! I finally found it!
This is the confirmation
I was looking for.
The heart of the mystery
lies in the Mystic Valley.
What is the Mystic Valley?
The legendary place
where the Draconians
are said to have lived.
[gasps]
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
I have heard enough!
Shesta!
He was from the
Mystic Moon, too?