[HITOMI]
Was it all just a dream?
Or was it a vision?
Thanks to Allen,
we were able to rescue Van from
Zaibach's floating fortress.
Though I still had questions
about the man Van called
his older brother.
Now we're headed for
the city of Palas,
capital of Asturia.
[TEO]
Altitude, 4,000!
[KIO] Right! We've crossed
the Chatal Mountains.
[HITOMI]
Allen wasn't very happy
about the reading I
did for him earlier.
[HITOMI]
He seems so distant.
I wonder if he hates me now.
Our altitude is
2,000 and falling.
We're nearing our destination.
Hey Katz, stay sharp!
Looks like we've got
some turbulence ahead.
[KATZ]
I know that!
Uh, Commander?
[ALLEN]
Uh. What is it?
We should be arriving
at Palas pretty soon.
There something wrong?
It's nothing.
I'm just distracted.
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
I have good news.
We'll be on the ground
again before long.
We're nearing Palas.
To be honest,
I'm a little nervous.
There's nothing to
be worried about.
I'm sure we're in
for a warm welcome.
Asturia is my country,
and Palas is her capital.
Although...
Huh?
That special power of
yours is quite impressive,
but I think it best
you keep it a secret.
A girl who is both
beautiful and powerful?
I fear you'd make much
too of a tempting target.
Heh.
I'll leave landing
preparations to you.
Find me if you need me.
Roger that.
I think I might faint.
[HITOMI yelps]
[ORT] What're you doin'
in this area, kitty?
We're gonna be landin'
soon, you know?
Yeah, but I need
to find King Van.
The King, huh? Easy.
He's back there,
with his Guymelef.
[MERLE laughs]
[ORT]
Hey!
There'll be some turbulence
when we descend. Be careful.
I'm always careful!
[MERLE]
Hm... Uh!
[laughs]
How, Brother?
How could you turn
your back on us?
King Van looks so sad.
[ALL chatting]
I'm headin' into town
tonight. Who's with me?!
Look at that water!
It goes on forever!
That's the ocean? I've never
seen the ocean before.
Yeah. Me neither, actually.
Huh, I guess the sea
smells the same
no matter what
planet you're on.
[MILLERNA]
Allen!
Whoa!
[MILLERNA] Why didn't you let
anyone know you were coming?
You cad!
Princess Millerna.
It's delightful to see
you as always, Highness.
But why are you
wearing trousers?
Have you ever tried riding
a horse in a dress?
Honestly, why didn't you
send a message ahead?
We could've arranged a
proper welcome for you.
[ALLEN] My apologies. We, uh,
came in a bit of a hurry.
[MILLERNA]
We?
Who's that young man?
May I introduce His Majesty,
King Van of Fanelia.
Oh! I see.
That explains it. I could
have sworn that I recognized
his face from
somewhere before.
I have actually been to Fanelia.
So, as it happens,
this isn't the first time
that I've met His Majesty.
I found Fanelia to be such
a beautiful, lush country.
I still remember that
visit quite clearly.
The castle had a blue roof.
And there was a garden in the
back. That's where you were.
You and your brother.
[MILLERNA]
Folken, right?
I always thought he seemed
like such a nice person.
If I may, I'm afraid I have
to ask a favor of you.
Please, ask anything!
You know I'm always
happy to help, Allen.
You okay, King Van?
Well, you see,
I really ought to
get to the castle
as swiftly as I possibly can.
Oh, yes. Absolutely!
As a matter of fact,
Father mentioned that
there was something
he wanted to
discuss with you.
You're welcome to take
my horse if you'd like.
[ALLEN]
Thank you, I will.
I'll see you at
the castle. H'ya!
[HITOMI]
The knight and the princess.
Basically the perfect couple.
Well, I suppose we should
be going. You there, girl.
You can take care of Allen's
things, can't you now?
Uh! Uh... Who? Me?
[MERLE laughs]
Of course. Is that a problem?
Actually, she's
not a handmaiden.
She's here with me.
[MILLERNA]
Oh.
[MERLE growls] I would
say she's here with Allen!
[MILLERNA]
You're joking.
Uh. You thought I was a
servant? Well, I'm not.
Oh, dear. I'm sorry.
I saw your strange clothing,
and I just assumed.
My mistake.
Handmaidens dress
better than that!
I'll pull your tail!
[MERLE laughs]
I've met all kinds of people.
We get folk from everywhere
here in Asturia.
But I don't think I've ever seen
anyone quite like you before.
No, I would bet money
that you haven't.
I doubt you get very many
visitors from the Mystic--
Oops.
Way to go.
[ALLEN]
The Zaibach Empire
attacked our fortress in a clear
violation of our treaty.
This is not the
action of an ally.
We must ask ourselves:
How long before they
attack Asturia in force?
Shall we ready our
defenses, King Aston?
[KING ASTON] Considering your
recent actions I can only assume
it is your intention to bring
disaster upon our country.
[gasps]
You would invite
the wrath of the
Zaibach Empire for the sake
of one insignificant outpost?
Are you out of your mind?
Uh! Chivalry demands we
protect the King of Fanelia,
whose country was destroyed
by those Zaibach traitors.
[FOLKEN]
That's quite an accusation.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
[FOLKEN]
I'm sorry,
but you seem to be the victim
of a misunderstanding.
As I'm sure you
will come to see.
Who is this man?
[KING ASTON] Allen Schezar, I
would like to introduce Folken.
Zaibach's own Strategos.
Did we come too late?
[ALLEN] Zaibach may already have
secured the king's cooperation.
[FOLKEN]
King Aston.
The truth of the matter
is that it was Fanelia
who launched a surprise
attack against us.
Really? This is the first I've
heard of any surprise attack.
Even so, it is true.
Now, here is my proposal.
Hand over the king of Fanelia
and his Guymelef to us.
If you do that,
then perhaps we can overlook
this unfortunate incident.
I would hate for anything
to endanger our alliance.
We are happy to count Asturia
among our loyal friends.
I hope that will not change as a
result of this misunderstanding.
[KING ASTON]
Mm-mm.
I'm glad we could come
to an agreement so quickly.
[FOLKEN chuckles]
[KING ASTON]
If you love your country,
you will turn over the king
and his Guymelef at once,
and I expect no more
reckless behavior.
It takes more than chivalry
to protect a country, Allen.
Best try to remember that.
[ALLEN gasping]
You'll want to
burn some incense
with a strong
fragrance, as well.
We don't want any lingering
aroma of sweat and animals.
[WOMAN A] I'm going to
rinse out your hair now.
Um! Okay.
[HITOMI] I'm happy to
finally get a bath, and all.
But I can't relax like this.
[footsteps]
There you are.
[MILLERNA]
You clean up well.
That dress looks
wonderful on you!
You look good enough
to be a handmaiden now.
Do you want to fight?
Is that it?
Aw, is someone a little
self-conscious?
Are you sure you don't mind
me borrowing this, though?
It's such a beautiful dress.
It wouldn't do to have you seen
out and about in your clothes.
It might reflect
poorly on Allen,
and we wouldn't want that.
[HITOMI growls]
[HITOMI] It's like she's going
out of her way to insult me.
Uh! E-Excuse me?
Aren't those my clothes?
Yes, of course.
She's disposing of
them for you, dear.
You can't do that!
Give them back!
What's the matter?
You may have as many new
dresses as you would like.
You only have to ask.
No, it isn't that.
These clothes have
sentimental value to me.
I appreciate you lending
me this dress.
I'm happy to wear it. But,
I'd like to keep my things.
Uh... Huh.
I get the impression that
there's a longer story
behind this than I've heard.
I'll have to sit
Allen down later
and have him tell
me everything.
[MILLERNA chuckles]
[FEMALE A]
Princess Millerna?
A message for you
from Lord Allen.
Oh. Thank you.
He's been detained.
He says we should go down
to the bazaar without him.
It isn't very gentlemanly of him
to break his word like that.
[sighs] Well, there's no
sense in waiting for him.
Let's do as he said and go.
Sure. Sounds good.
[VAN]
Hitomi.
Huh? Uh! Jeez! What's this for?
Keep that with you.
We can't afford to get
too comfortable here.
Uh. Okay.
[TEO] Left! No, your
other left. That's it!
[GADDES] That oughta
make it less noticeable.
Come on down!
Let's get some grub.
[KATZ, TEO]
Yes, sir!
[REEDEN]
Hey, Sarge!
We started without ya,
hope you don't mind.
[GADDES]
Nah.
You were planning to leave
a little for the rest of us,
though, weren't you?
Uh. What's all this about?
[GADDES] The Royal Guard.
What can we do for you?
[TEO]
Get your hands offa me!
Hey! Stay away from that!
[GADDES]
Uh!
[GUARD A]
So this is Escaflowne,
the Guymelef everyone's
so interested in.
By order of His august
Majesty King Aston,
you will turn it over at once,
and I suggest you do so quietly.
Hey. Thought we
were friends here.
What's goin' on,
Sarge? Do we fight?
Rotten bastards.
[MILLERNA]
Well? What do you think?
Exciting, huh?
[HITOMI]
Sure is busy.
Uh.
Hello, miss, and
good day to you.
You all right?
For someone from
the Mystic Moon,
you sure do surprise easily.
I do not!
[MERLE laughs]
Hurry up, you two.
We'll leave you behind.
[VAN]
Zaibach Soldiers.
Folken's here!
What? Is something wrong?
[MILLERNA]
Van!
See anything
you like, miss?
I'm sure we can
work out a price.
[HITOMI]
No way!
How did one of these get here?
[MERCHANT A] That's a nice
piece. It'll look great on you.
I've got the perfect
chain for it.
[HITOMI]
A CD?
That could mean I'm
not the first person
from Earth to come here.
[music plays]
[HITOMI]
Yukari.
Amano...
[gasps] Van! No!
[MILLERNA]
Hitomi?
What's the matter?
You seemed sort of far away.
Where's Van?
Where did he go?
He ran off toward the harbor.
It seemed like he was
upset about something.
[HITOMI gasping]
[MERLE]
Come back! Not you, too!
We certainly do get
some odd visitors.
[VAN panting]
One of Zaibach's
floating fortresses!
[DRIVER A] I've come to
take you back, Lord Folken.
[VAN panting]
[VAN]
Brother!
[panting]
[FOLKEN]
Van, I'll be leaving soon.
Are you prepared
to come with me?
My cheek won't stop
throbbing. It stings.
It stings. It stings.
It stings.
Should you touch
it so much?
It looks like your wound
is starting to bleed
again, my lord.
[DILANDAU]
What's that?
[GATTY grunts]
Maybe I should give you a
cut to match mine, Gatty?!
[GATTY]
F-Forgive me, my lord!
My face! He cut
my beautiful face!
[SHESTA]
Lord Dilandau!
What is it now?!
It's Lord Folken, sir.
[VAN]
I don't get it!
Why are you working
for Zaibach?!
[FOLKEN] Because Folken
of Fanelia is dead.
[gasps]
[FOLKEN]
Van, Do you see this?
I fought the dragon, and it
ripped an arm from my body.
I died that day.
That Folken died.
Yet I was fortunate enough
to be given new life,
at the hands of Emperor.
[HITOMI panting]
[MERLE]
Why you running? What's wrong?
I had a vision, a bad one.
Cut it out!
I don't like when you say
stuff like that. It's scary.
Excuse me, sir.
Which way to the harbor?
The same direction
you're facing.
Thank you!
[MERLE gasping]
[SHESTA panting] Hold on,
Lord Dilandau! Please wait.
What about Lord Folken's order
not to leave the anchorage?!
Not an issue. I wasn't
planning to leave the Vione.
[DILANDAU chuckles]
[DILANDAU]
Van!
[FOLKEN] Van, you are
my family, my brother.
The same blood runs
through our veins.
I can read your heart as
easily as I can read my own.
This is a hard world for
a gentle soul like yours.
This world, where man
fights against man.
Where it seems every
living creature struggles
to take the life of another.
We kill beasts. We kill
dragons. We kill other men.
Fighting begets fighting and
the slaughter begins anew.
Such is the way of the world.
From what I can see,
the Zaibach Empire's doing
most of the fighting.
[FOLKEN]
Hmph. The difference is
that we are fighting to bring
an end to such conflict.
To establish a new order,
one with peace at its heart.
This is a just war
we fight. A holy war.
That's it?
You're fighting to put
an end to fighting?
That's ridiculous.
It doesn't work that way!
[FOLKEN]
Van. I want you to join us.
Come with me now. Together
we'll create a new world.
[VAN]
Brother...
[HITOMI, MERLE panting]
[HITOMI]
Something's wrong.
I can feel it!
I have to hurry!
[SHESTA]
Lord Dilandau!
He's got his Energist
on the maximum setting.
How far is he attempting
to shoot the Crima Claw?
[DILANDAU]
I'm coming for you, Van!
[MERLE]
Huh?!
[HITOMI]
Hold this for me!
[MERLE gasping]
Further! Reach him, my claw!
Van is going to die today!
[HITOMI panting]
[HITOMI]
Van!
[screams]
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Look out!
[DILANDAU gasps]
Lord Dilandau!
Uh!
[SHESTA] Lord Dilandau! That
looked bad! Are you all right?
[DILANDAU]
Damn that girl.
[HITOMI panting]
Van.
Hitomi?
Thank you.
It looks like you saved me.
[panting]
Just barely.
I'm glad I made it.
[FOLKEN] Dilandau, you fool.
How dare you interfere!
[VAN]
Hey, Folken!
What was that about putting
an end to all fighting?
[FOLKEN] I never intended for
you to be attacked here today.
[VAN]
Is that all you have to say?
[HITOMI]
That's Van's older brother.
The guy from the fortress.
[MERLE panting]
King Van!
Don't go running
off like that.
Do you know how
worried I've been?
She keeps saying
the weirdest things!
Van Fanel, King of Fanelia, if
you will please come with us.
King Aston wishes to see you.
So he sent the guard?
Well, that's kinda rude!
The king is waiting.
Shall we be on our way?
[KING ASTON]
Welcome, Van of Fanelia.
I extend you warmest greetings
on behalf of all Asturia.
I hope you will rest
easy in my land,
knowing that you
are among friends.
As proof of our friendship,
I ask a favor.
I am interested to see both
your skill as a fighter
and the power of your Guymelef.
Perhaps you'd be so kind as
to give us a demonstration?
I'm sure everything
will be all right, Allen.
Don't worry.
Father knows what he's doing.
There's no need to
look so serious.
[HITOMI gasps]
I know that Guymelef.
It's Sajima's.
He's a bounty hunter,
not a knight.
Just greedy lout who
fights for money.
[HITOMI] My heart, it's racing!
There's something wrong here.
I can't believe I'm actually
seeing an Ispano Guymelef.
I've heard rumors
of its magnificence,
and it seems they
weren't exaggerated
so this will be an
interesting fight, indeed.
[KING ASTON]
Perhaps just looking at it
will be enough to
satisfy you, Meiden.
[MEIDEN chuckles]
I will admit, the sight
of it is enough to set
even the coolest
merchant's blood aboil.
But as everyone knows, you can't
tell a Guymelef's true worth
until you've seen it in combat.
I do wish we had more
satisfactory opponents
for him, though.
Like Allen. Why not
put him in the ring?
Ha! Allen isn't the
only fighter in Asturia.
Watch. I'm sure you will
not be disappointed.
[HITOMI] Was I wrong? Was what
happened earlier just a fluke?
Is this what that
horrible vision
was really warning me about?
"Proof of our friendship," huh?
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[MILLERNA] I would be willing
to give up everything for you.
The city is burning
because of you!