[KIO]
Let us outta here!
[TEO]
Yeah, what's the big idea?
[ALL shouting]
--[ALL shouting]
--Hey, jerk, let us out!
Okay. Quiet down,
you dogs! Shut up!
[ALL shouting]
[REEDEN] Just see if we help
out when Zaibach attacks!
Your allies might
talk and act tough,
but as you're about to find
out, no one can stand up
to Plaktu's ability
to divine the truth.
[PRISON GUARD A]
Wait in here.
[HITOMI grunts]
Geez. Talk about spooky.
[gasps] Prince Chid?
Please, Your Highness,
you don't actually
believe it, do you?
That we're rebels seeking
to overthrow Asturia?
Look in my eyes, do I look
like I'm lying to you?
[CHID] Unfortunately,
I'm not entirely sure.
But Plaktu's magic
can differentiate
between lies and the truth.
Have some faith
in us, please.
[CHID] I wish I could, but
as prince of this kingdom,
I have to be certain.
Therefore I must follow
my family's tradition,
and that's to use Plaktu's
powers in matters such as this.
Please understand.
I have to do what's best
for my country and people.
I've heard something similar.
From King Van. You're
a lot alike, you know.
[ZONGI]
Let us begin.
[HITOMI gasps]
I have others to
interrogate after you.
[VAN] Why are you
starting with Hitomi?!
She's got nothing
to do with this!
What does it matter
who goes first?
If you and your allies have
truly done nothing wrong,
then your interrogations
will prove so.
You're wasting time on this
while Zaibach's
prepares to attack?
He's right, Voris. Please,
you have to believe us.
Everything we've said to you
is the truth, I swear it.
One of your fellow
countrymen told me
to treat anything you might
say to us as suspect.
[MILLERNA whimpers]
[ALLEN]
Hm?
Wait, what do you mean?
A messenger from Asturia
recently arrived here
with some urgent news.
According to him, the lot
of you are fugitives.
There's a price on your heads,
and one on Escaflowne as well.
Aston, you fool.
I can vouch for both Allen's
story and his honesty!
What he's saying is the truth!
I hope so.
Because we're
going to find out.
The truth is always revealed
when Plaktu conducts one
of his interrogations.
[ZONGI]
"Earth"?
That's the name of the
place from which you hail?
[HITOMI]
Yes.
[ZONGI]
And where is it located?
[HITOMI] It's very far away.
You call it the Mystic Moon.
Wait, did I hear
you correctly?
Do you mean to say
you hail from a land
that's on the actual
Mystic Moon?
Yes.
The girl's really from
that accursed place?
Truly, Aunt Millerna?
Yes, she is.
I have been informed that you
and your compatriots launched
a sneak attack against a
Zaibach floating fortress.
I was also told you managed
to destroy an Energist mine.
Are both of these
accusations true?
Well? Answer me!
Are they both true?
Yes.
[gasps]
This corroborates the claims
that the Asturian messenger
made against them,
Your Highness.
[MILLERNA] Hold on! At least
ask her why they did it!
I'm sure it was part of their
plot to overthrow Asturia!
It's exactly like the
Zaibach prisoner told us!
[ZONGI]
Tracking a flying fortress
is near impossible,
and the location of the
mine was well hidden,
so how did you find them?
By dowsing for them. With this.
[ZONGI]
"Dowsing"?
Using your mind.
To see what can't be seen.
[ZONGI] So that's
her mysterious power!
Does this also explain
how you were able to see
the invisible Guymelefs?
Yes.
Give me your pendant.
Hand it over to me right now.
[ZONGI groaning]
[gasping]
[ZONGI]
Where am I?!
What have you
done? Answer me!
I've seen through
your disguise.
You're in your true form now.
[gasps]
My spell's been broken?
But... how did you do this?
Uh! Prince Chid,
what's happening?
Voris, do you know?
I, uh, do not,
Your Highness.
[ZONGI] Let me out!
Do it now or else!
[ZONGI]
What, but how?
[ZONGI gasps] Impossible.
How are you able to see that?
You're a murderer, Zongi.
[gasps]
Not just that, but a
Doppelganger, too.
You will wear many different
faces in your life,
but none of them will
ever be your own.
Our kind is destined to
live and die in battle
until the end of time.
E-Elder.
[ELDER A] Such is the fate
that our clan is cursed
to bear forever, my boy.
[gasps] Uh. Oh, no.
Brother!
[FOLKEN] You curse this
world, don't you?
And the life you've
been granted.
You loathe that you were
born to be a killer,
but only feel truly alive when
you're in the heat of battle.
If you want this to change,
come with me, Zongi.
I can break you from
the chains of fate
that have bound your
people for so long.
[ZONGI gasps]
[ZONGI]
Please tell me how!
[ZONGI] So, you can
see right through me.
Very well.
Since you know my secret,
I'm afraid that you must die.
[ZONGI]
Wh-What's going on?!
This is how the
deceptive life you lead
will soon be extinguished.
What do you mean?!
[ZONGI screams]
In fact, it will happen
sooner than you can imagine.
[ZONGI groaning]
You let me go!
[HITOMI gasps]
No! No. This is some
kind of trickery!
[HITOMI screams]
What's happening now?
No, please stop!
No! No!
[HITOMI gasping]
[HITOMI screams]
[ALLEN, VAN, MERLE gasp]
Hitomi!
[gasping] She's a monster.
She's a strange and
terrible monster!
[MILLERNA]
Hitomi!
[CHID]
Are you all right?
[VORIS] You seem shaken.
What's the matter?
[ZONGI] It's nothing.
I'm just a little tired.
[MILLERNA]
Her pupils are dilated!
[ZONGI, VORIS gasp]
What is it?
What's wrong with her?
Oh, no, it's her heart!
It's not beating!
[CHID, VORIS gasp]
What happened
down there?! Hey!
[growls] What was that scream?
The prisoner died!
[ALL gasp]
I don't know how it happened,
but your friend is dead!
[VAN]
Uh!
What? No.
[CHID]
Allen! Allen!
Hitomi! She just died!
Please, Your Highness, you've
got to let us go see her!
Uh. But, I...
[VAN]
We don't have time to waste!
He's right!
[CHID gasps]
Uh! What are you doing?
[VORIS]
Your Highness!
And you call yourself a knight?
Open the door and
he won't get hurt.
[MILLERNA whimpers]
Everything is going to
be all right, Hitomi!
Just hold on, okay?
I'm going to make
you pay for this
if it's the last thing
I ever do, Schezar!
Perhaps, but for now I just
need you to clear the way.
[MILLERNA gasping]
[VAN panting]
[VAN]
Hitomi!
Don't die! Please, you've
gotta pull through!
I can't... get her
heart to beat!
So just like this, right?
[MILLERNA gasps]
Yes. Hands right there.
Then push in time with
your own heartbeat!
[VAN]
With my own...
[heart beating]
[VAN grunting]
Good! But much harder!
Quick!
[VAN] Come on, Hitomi!
Just take a breath!
Please!
[VAN grunting]
[VAN]
Beat! Damn it!
Keep going, King Van!
Please, Hitomi.
You have to make it!
She feels cold!
I refuse to let
you die, Hitomi!
[gasps]
[HITOMI coughs]
[VAN gasps]
You saved her, Van!
[HITOMI coughing]
[VORIS]
Thank goodness she's alive.
PRISON GUARD A]
It's a miracle!
Welcome back!
I'm glad you made it! Seriously!
Hey, Merle.
Meow. Oh, so that's
where my nail file went.
[CHID gasps]
[PRISON GUARD A] All right,
on your feet, scum!
Oh.
[VAN]
Hitomi? What happened?
[ALLEN]
Uh?
[HITOMI whim
Pl-Plaktu.
He's an imposter,
and what's worse...
Yes, tell us.
He's going to die.
Not just soon, but, terribly.
No!
[ZONGI] She can see my past
and my future as well?
[ZONGI gasps]
[gasping]
Apparently, she's not
the only one seeing things.
Regardless, I must report
this to Lord Folken.
[CHID] He was a Zaibach spy?
This Plaktu impostor?
Yes. I saw it,
Highness!
The Doppelganger killed the
real Plaktu and took his shape.
He also killed Miguel,
the Zaibach prisoner.
And...
I saw how he'll die,
too. It's horrible!
[CHID] Where is
Plaktu now, Voris?
He's nowhere to be
found, my prince.
[VAN]
He's on the run!
We have to track him down
and stop him right away,
Your Highness! If we don't,
he'll tell Zaibach about Hitomi
and they'll attack
Freid to get her!
[VORIS]
Silence! Your Highness.
Until we get this sorted out,
I think we should ignore
anything they say!
That's enough!
[VORIS]
Uh!
[BOTH gasp]
Chid.
Very well.
[ALLEN] That is a kind
of bravery, you know.
Sometimes it can take
even more courage
to believe in someone
than to fight them.
You spared me?
Yes.
Because I want you to track
down the Zaibach spy
and bring him here to me.
Your Highness!
Have you taken leave
of your senses?
"One proves one's innocence
through one's deeds."
I'll take full responsibility,
but I am giving him a
chance to prove himself.
I have made my decision,
and it's final.
[gasps] Highness.
[ALLEN]
Well, then.
[ALL gasp]
His wounds haven't healed
yet, Prince Chid.
With your permission,
I'll go in his place.
And I would like to
come along, too.
[HITOMI]
I don't care
what kind of person
this Zongi is.
I can't let that
vision come true!
Do you see anything yet?
A tower, that way!
Right! [grunts]
[VORIS]
There is a chance
that they might very well
run away, Highness.
I'm not worried about that.
If Allen places his trust
in Van, then so do I.
Hold on, this girl came
from the Mystic Moon?
Yes.
Through the use of a pendant,
she has the ability
to see the unseen.
She also knows the
past and the future.
So she can see the invisible
and foretell the future, eh?
That explains it.
[DILANDAU]
How she knew then.
And that time...
[DILANDAU]
And also when...
So this is all her fault.
That girl's the one
responsible for this.
Uh!
[DILANDAU]
Job well done, Zongi.
I... humbly accept
your praise, lord.
How about you accept
this instead?
[ZONGI gasps]
I don't understand!
[DILANDAU]
You killed one of my best men.
Bu...! I was only
doing my duty!
He deserved a death
more honorable
than the one that you gave him.
Such tactics are the reason
I despise your kind.
[ZONGI]
No! Have mercy! Ah!
Is that it?
Yes! We need to hurry!
[ZONGI gasping]
Don't kill me!
[ZONGI screams]
[DILANDAU chuckles]
We won't make it!
[gasps, whimpers]
[HITOMI]
Help me Van! No!
Lord Folken, save me!
[HITOMI]
Don't! No!
[ZONGI gagging]
[screams]
Hitomi!
Escaflowne is here, too?
This night just got even
better! Shesta! Gatty!
[VAN] Come on, Hitmoni,
snap out of it!
[VAN growls]
[DILANDAU laughing]
[VAN] Those invisible
bastards are back!
Can you help me find them?
You...
You just concentrate, and
picture them in your mind.
Uh! While we're
being fired upon?
Trust me on this. If anybody
can do it, you can.
Yes! Fire!
Take down Escaflowne!
Like I told you, Van, you
just have to concentrate.
And picture them in your mind.
Found 'em!
What?!
Damn you!
[VAN yells]
Uh! So she's here, too!
The girl responsible
for my disfigurement!
I've got them, my lord!
[VAN]
Got 'em!
Die, you bitch!
[VAN growling]
Just hold on!
[HITOMI gasps]
[DILANDAU]
That's it, girl!
You've gotten in my way
for the very last time!
[HITOMI whimpers]
[VAN growls]
[DILANDAU]
Get back here!
You cowards!
[CHID]
Just like Hitomi predicted?
[VAN] Exactly, and since
there was nothing left,
we lost the only proof that
Plaktu was an imposter.
No, that's where
you're mistaken.
During your absence,
more evidence supporting
your claims was uncovered.
[MILLERNA]
The real Plaktu was found.
Or his corpse to
be more accurate.
Seems a group of monks
stumbled upon him in the forest.
He was but a dried-out husk,
which is proof that a
Doppelganger killed him.
But I would still believe you
even if no proof was found.
Because you proved your
innocence through your deeds!
[HITOMI, VAN]
Uh.
Heh.
They sure did!
We have done you many
wrongs. Forgive us.
If it wasn't for you, Chid
wouldn't have been convinced.
You know, it's strange.
I just realized how
alike you two look.
Your eyes and hair
are the same color.
You could almost
pass as brothers.
[CHID]
Uh...
[gasps] My friends!
I was just given word that
the Duke has returned!
Father is back?!
[HITOMI]
Chid's father, huh?
I wonder what kind of man he is.
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
Hey, I'll tell you what.
How would you like if I
did a reading for you?
[gasps]
A forbidden love...?