[CESARIO SOLDIER A]
It was a rout.
We... we didn't stand a chance
against Zaibach's forces.
[CESARIO SOLDIER B]
Regardless, we must hold that
position until we
hear otherwise.
[CESARIO SOLDIER A]
Or at least until the alliance's
main force arrives.
[CESARIO SOLDIER B]
We soldiers of Cesario
will gladly lay down our lives.
But I fear even that won't
be enough in the end.
There are simply too few of us.
But if we had the aid
of the King of Fanelia,
pilot of the legendary
Ispano Guymelef,
surely it would help
boost our morale.
[BOTH] Your Majesty!
Please give us your aid!
Very well, then you have it.
I will gladly lead the frontline
in the battle that's to come.
[BOTH gasp]
[CESARIO SOLDIER A]
We thank you, King Van.
But I have a favor
to ask of you.
I want you to take my
friend to Asturia first.
[CESARIO SOLDIER A]
Very well, sir.
A ship will be
made ready at once.
Wait a second! I'll stay.
I might be able to help
you if you let me, Van.
I know that. But if you stayed,
I'd rely on you too much.
[gasps]
I won't use your power for war.
I've caused too much
damage already.
But, Van...
[ADELPHOS]
This is madness!
With such a large
and powerful army,
Why haven't we
received permission
to advance on the enemy?
Our army is 40,000
troops strong.
Anyone can see defeating
that alliance rabble
would be child's play!
What reason could
the emperor have
for not acting on our advantage?
[DORNKIRK]
Yes. I can see it clearly.
Fate is about to
deliver the girl
right into my waiting hands.
The Zone of Absolute
Fortune is approaching.
All is in motion.
We await only her arrival.
There is no turning back.
[ALLEN]
Rain...
[HITOMI huffs]
[ALLEN] There's something
melancholy about it.
Everything it touches
gets washed away.
Allen, um. We should talk.
All you ever wanted was
to escape from Gaea.
The only thing that could
bring you back to this world
was Van's love. A love
that you obviously return.
Uh...
[ALLEN]
I'm stunned, honestly.
This may be the first time
a woman's ever refused me.
I am sorry.
I hope you'll try not
to worry too much.
I'm sure Van will come back
from battle in one piece.
And with very good reason.
The most important person
in the world to him is here.
[DRYDEN]
This is pointless.
War has no justifiable purpose.
Nothing positive
ever comes of it.
All it does is ruin
lands and lives.
[MILLERNA]
Dryden?
We merchants see the world
as a bunch of goods
marked with price tags.
War destroys all those goods,
and the price is much too high.
What is the point of it?
What is the matter?
You don't seem
like yourself today.
No. I'm definitely not.
[gasps]
You're absolutely exquisite.
Even a goddess could
not help but envy you.
Are you all right?
[gasps]
[DRYDEN]
I've realized that I'm not yet
the sort of man you deserve.
[MILLERNA]
What are you saying?
[DRYDEN]
This war will be over soon.
It doesn't matter who 'wins' it.
The people who remain will still
have to rebuild their lives.
[MILLERNA gasps]
[DRYDEN] And I want to be by
their side to help with that.
Maybe there will be some
use for a man like me
in the post-war world.
I'll live and work
as a merchant,
among the survivors.
That seems to be
the most honest way
to earn your respect
and affection.
When you do come back,
I can't promise that
I'll be waiting.
Eventually, you will love me.
And that is because I am
deeply in love with you.
[FOLKEN] You're here because
you want to help Van?
[HITOMI] That's right,
but I need your help first.
Tell me how to create a pillar
of light so I can go to Zaibach.
I'll go find Emperor Dornkirk,
and I'll talk to him.
And ask that he stop
all this fighting!
I'm afraid that request
will fall upon deaf ears.
Besides, if you willingly
put yourself in harm's way,
that will make things
worse for Van.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
I believe the better solution
is for me to speak
with the emperor.
[gasps]
[FOLKEN] I'll put a wave in tune
with the Fate Alteration Engine.
That should be able to
direct the pillar of light.
It's why I recovered this
device from the Vione.
This is for me to settle,
and no one else.
Folken, are you sure?
[HITOMI]
What?
[HITOMI gasps]
Oh, no.
If he goes to see Dornkirk,
he'll definitely die!
[MILLERNA] Yes, He cared for
me the best way he knew how.
I had convinced myself he would
make me happy, eventually.
[MILLERNA] But...
That's who I've always been.
I just wanted someone
to make me happy.
But now, I know
that's not right.
My happiness isn't someone
else's responsibility.
Allen. You knew it the
entire time, didn't you?
[ALLEN]
Princess Millerna.
Please, I--
[MILLERNA]
No, don't say anything!
If I keep hearing kind
words from you.
I'll start to rely on you again.
I refuse to be a
burden to anyone.
Please don't worry.
I'll be fine.
[ALLEN]
Knight Caeli, Allen Schezar,
will now depart for battle.
I bid you goodbye,
Princess Millerna.
[MILLERNA]
May the sea dragon god, Jichia,
always watch over you,
and may good fortune
bestow blessings upon you
in the battle to come.
[JAJUKA]
Lord Dilandau.
[DILANDAU]
Huh?
We've just been
ordered to accompany
the 32nd Division to Galfo.
So, I recommend that we
prepare to leave immediately.
Is that so?
It's been quite a while...
...since we've had
a great battle.
Sounds like fun,
don't you think?
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[gasps]
[SOLDIER A screams]
[yells]
[panting]
[COMMANDER]
Use our ultimate weapon?
We have to!
At this rate, we won't make it
to the enemy's headquarters.
We'll just have to
blast our way through.
[COMMANDER] But sir, our allies
are on the battlefield as well!
I don't care!
We'll teach those
Zaibach bastards
a lesson they'll never forget!
[COMMANDER]
But, General!
[GENERAL A] They'll feel the
power of Basram's new weapon!
All its power!
Oh, Van...
[door clatters]
[HITOMI]
Merle?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
[MERLE]
Can I stay with you?
[HITOMI gasps]
I'm so scared, Hitomi!
I have this terrible feeling
King Van isn't ever
gonna come back!
[MERLE whimpers] I've never
been so afraid before.
[HITOMI]
You have to believe in him.
Van's definitely coming back.
I promise, Merle.
[OFFICER B] We're over
the target's airspace.
Let's do it!
[OFFICER A] Right. Climb and
bank while it's dropping.
[OFFICER B]
Now dropping.
I can't believe
they actually did it!
[gasps]
[ZODIA SOLDIER]
Something's flashing above us!
[ZODIA gasps]
Ah!
What is that? What the
hell is happening?
[HELIO SOLDIERS scream]
Hey, Sarge! They activated it!
Kio, get us behind
the mountains, now!
Aye, sir!
This ain't no war.
This is a damn massacre.
[gasps]
Damn it! What is this
weapon of theirs?
[BRIGADIER GENERAL] Helio Fleet,
Zodia Fleet, and Gedin Fleet
have all been destroyed!
We're losing power!
[CREW screams]
How dare you,
cowardly alliance filth!
This is an act of the devil!
We will have our
vengeance on you!
What happened here?
It's all gone.
This is a wasteland!
You'll pay for this, demons!
You think you can wipe
Zaibach entirely off the map?!
[gasps]
You'll never get away with this!
We'll make you pay!
No, I... Please, wait.
[gasps]
That was Van.
He's in pain. I can feel it!
What's that?
I have to put a stop
to this fighting!
It's hurting him too much!
Hitomi!
[FOLKEN whistles]
[HITOMI]
Folken!
[panting]
[HITOMI]
Van's suffering badly.
I have to do something!
I have to help him!
I've told you helping Van
is my task, not yours.
Don't go. Something bad
will happen if you do.
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Please believe me.
Don't go to Zaibach, Folken.
If you do, I believe
you're going to die there!
[HITOMI]
I'm telling you.
I saw something,
and it was horrible.
[FOLKEN]
You needn't worry about that.
I don't believe I have too
much time left to live anyway.
[gasps]
[FOLKEN] The reaction of fortune
is rapidly shortening my life.
Look at my wings.
They are the proof of that.
That's why your wings are black?
Conspiring with Dornkirk was an
unforgivable transgression.
For that, I can only
pay with my life.
This is the fate that awaits me.
You can't do that!
If you die, Van's gonna
be all alone in the world.
He'll suffer even more!
I don't want that. I can't
stand seeing him in pain!
My brother will both
survive and succeed.
And he'll understand
the sacrifice I've made.
He, too, wants a better
future for the world.
But it just isn't right!
I still have to try
and do something.
It doesn't have to end this way!
Where's the red Guymelef?
I don't see it anywhere.
They have arrived.
Where are we?
[DORNKIRK]
Right where I want you.
[BOTH gasp]
[DORNKIRK] The time has
come to use the full power
of the Fate Alteration Engine.
My entire life's work has been
leading up to this one moment.
And thanks to you, it's here.
It's all coalescing,
just as my will has dictated.
Your will?
[DORNKIRK] Correct.
I guided fate, making certain
you would bring the girl from
the Mystic Moon directly to me.
And so here you are, Folken.
[gasps]
How much longer
do you plan to keep
bending the laws of destiny?!
[DORNKIRK] I'm surprised you'd
ask such a foolish question.
By this time, you of all people
should well know
my true intentions.
Then by the same token,
you should know what
I've come here to do.
[DORNKIRK] You've come to
kill me, have you not?
[gasps]
[DORNKIRK]
Then do it. Take my life.
I am alone and unprotected,
you'll have no better chance!
[HITOMI]
Wait, Folken!
[DORNKIRK laughs]
[DORNKIRK]
Come, Folken!
Step forward and finish what
you've started, for a change!
[FOLKEN]
You're a monster!
Folken, please stop!
No, wait!
[yells]
[DORNKIRK]
Yes...
[DORNKIRK groans]
[gasps]
[FOLKEN] I understand.
This is the heart of
the fate alteration.
Where action and reaction
are at their most powerful.
Pushing against each
other with equal strength.
But now the war will end.
At least I have done that much.
Sweet Gaea.
May you find true peace.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Van...
[HITOMI]
Folken, no!
My brother.
[VAN]
Brother!
Van.
[VAN, FOLKEN laugh]
Folken's dead.
[VAN]
Brother!
I can feel his heart breaking.
Van!
It's too much.
It's just too much!
I can't take it anymore!
I don't understand!
Why do terrible things
like this keep happening?
[whimpers] If this is our fate,
Then I don't want it!
[DORNKIRK]
It has begun.
[HITOMI gasps]
Who are you?
Pay close attention, young lady.
Watch the Zone of
Absolute Fortune.
You are about to witness
the true meaning of fate.
That's impossible!
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[VAN]
Don't you get it?
I'm fighting to protect you!
Goodbye, Van!
I won't forget you!