[HITOMI] I'm sorry.
I'm just not sure.
[ALLEN]
But I am sure.
[HITOMI gasps]
Van, wait.
[footsteps]
[MERLE] Take those wet clothes
off before you catch a cold!
[MERLE grunts]
C'mon!
I did try to tell you to stay
away from her, you know.
Why couldn't you
have listened to me?
[HITOMI] Well then. I guess
I'll see you in the morning.
[ALLEN]
Hitomi.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
[ALLEN] Please make sure you
change into something dry
right away, so you
don't get sick.
You wouldn't want to miss
Millerna's wedding
ceremony tomorrow.
I hope you rest well.
[door closes, footsteps]
[ERIYA chuckles, gasps]
You almost won that one.
But I'm afraid that
almost doesn't count.
You arrogant little minx.
Heh. I'll concede this
one to you, though,
after the prize my luck
landed me recently.
[ERIYA] I'd say we're
more than even.
[NARIA]
Careful,
or I'll slap that smug
look right off your face.
Oh, do I detect a
note of jealousy?
Maybe.
[ERIYA grunts]
I want to know more about
Lord Folken's lips.
Were they warm?
How did they taste?
Let me feel them, too. Please.
Just for a moment.
[exhales]
[ERIYA grunts]
Quit it!
[NARIA sighs]
[ERIYA grunts]
[ERIYA]
Naria.
[NARIA] Don't you see? I want
to have Lord Folken's love, too.
[ERIYA]
There wasn't any.
[NARIA]
Huh?
[ERIYA] It wasn't how I dreamed
it would be, full of love.
I wish we had never kissed.
Lord Folken has been
very kind to us,
and we should always
be grateful for that,
but I don't think
he'll return our love.
[NARIA]
Still... we've been lucky.
[ERIYA]
Yeah.
[NARIA]
We almost died.
We would have if it
hadn't been for him.
[ERIYA, NARIA growling]
[FOLKEN whimpering]
You poor things.
Fate has not been
kind to you, has it?
[ERIYA, NARIA growing]
[FOLKEN groaning]
[FOLKEN] I will give you new
names and a fresh start.
Today... you will be reborn.
I promise this life
will be luckier
than the one you've known.
For a while that was true,
but our luck has been
pretty rotten lately.
You're right about that.
If we could just
beat the dragon.
[FOLKEN] You're not really
to blame for that failure.
At its current level, your luck
cannot overcome his power.
[NARIA, ERIYA]
Lord Folken!
Naria. Eriya.
I have news that
may cheer you up.
If you truly wish for it, I can
grant you even greater luck.
This luck would
be unparalleled;
with it you would never
again lose to anybody.
[MILLERNA sighs]
This isn't it either.
[MILLERNA]
How odd.
I could've sworn I had one
that would match perfectly.
[MILLERNA]
Mm?
[MOLE MAN]
Uh!
What are you doing here?
[MOLE MAN]
Mm...
[MOLE MAN grunts] Princess,
hello! No offense, but...
you used to have
this glow about you.
It seems to have
vanished recently,
and I wondered if
you were all right.
I thought I'd look in on you.
[MILLERNA]
Uh?
[MOLE MAN chuckles]
[MILLERNA]
Uh. Hey! Stop that!
You found it!
[MOLE MAN] Hm...
How should I say this?
You have an abundance
of treasures
waiting right at your
fingertips, Princess,
but in the end only one of
them will suit you perfectly.
Choose wisely.
[FOLKEN]
I will completely replace
the blood in your
body with this liquid.
It's known as Fortune Blood.
[ERIYA]
Fortune Blood?
[FOLKEN]
Emperor Dornkirk's research
located people
throughout Zaibach
who were especially
lucky. From there,
he narrowed the field down
to those who were adept at
surviving against great odds.
From the nuclei
of their cells,
he was able to extract
what we call Fortune DNA.
He fused that DNA together using
the Fate Alteration Engine,
creating this artificial blood.
It's a risky procedure.
One mistake could kill you.
Please don't worry about
us. We'll be all right.
Not to mention the fact that
we're already pretty lucky.
[FOLKEN]
Hm.
Intensify luck!
[HITOMI]
I can't help but wonder,
is this what's right
for Millerna?
[gasps, sighs]
[MILLERNA]
There you are.
[HITOMI gasps]
Millerna! Hi!
Hitomi. I need you.
[HITOMI]
A reading? But why now?
[MILLERNA] It's just...
I have all these doubts.
I-I'm worried Dryden might
not be the right one for me.
[HITOMI]
Come on,
this isn't some shotgun
wedding or anything.
[MILLERNA] I'm not
sure what that means.
[HITOMI]
I'm saying you've got
some pre-marriage
jitters is all.
[MILLERNA]
No. It's more than that.
[HITOMI] I'm sorry, I can't
tell fortunes anymore.
I know how dangerous it is now.
[MILLERNA]
Please, Hitomi!
If you do a reading for me,
I know it will put me at ease.
[HITOMI] But, what if I call up
some strange future again?
Listen, I need to know.
I'll believe whatever the
cards predict, so please?
[HITOMI]
Three of Serpents.
The Hanged Man and the Moon.
[HITOMI]
Tension... Self-sacrifice.
Uncertainty.
It's like she said,
she's worried about this
political arrangement.
She doesn't like being
pressured into it.
[gasps] Let's see,
the cards say...
you're feeling nervous because
the marriage seems so sudden and
you're overwhelmed
by all the changes.
Still, you shouldn't
be impulsive.
[HITOMI] Ace of Birds.
Five of Fishes.
The Devil. Five of Beasts.
[HITOMI]
If she gets married now,
then Millerna will
know a deep sadness
and be caught in
some kind of feud,
because of someone close to her.
[MILLERNA]
What's it say?
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Um, give me a second.
Well, it looks like
there might be
a few small
difficulties at first.
[HITOMI]
The Lovers?
Whoa! What was that?
[MILLERNA]
Is something wrong?
[HITOMI]
Huh?
The Falling Tower?
This can only mean one thing.
The marriage is a mistake!
If I tell her these results, I'm
sure she'll cancel the wedding!
And then... She and Allen...
[HITOMI]
The Emperor.
The sign of good fortune.
I wonder, if I were to try
and switch out the cards,
what would it do?
Maybe I could draw a better
future into place.
[HITOMI]
That's it!
I can use the power of my will,
and call up a different
future for Millerna!
[HITOMI]
I'm sorry.
but if I wish for
it hard enough,
I can change your destiny
for the better.
[HITOMI]
Lucky you!
This card indicates
good fortune to come.
Basically, it says
if you go through with
this marriage to Dryden,
then you'll be happy!
You'll have a good
life together.
That's the outcome
of the reading?
I'll be happy with Dryden.
[HITOMI] Millerna, I really
do want you to be happy.
Hey, whatcha got there?
Um.
Well, It's kind of like a charm.
What does it do?
My hope is that it will bring
both of them good luck.
so that they'll have
a blissful marriage.
[PRIEST A]
O ye wise children of Asturia,
a land which is blessed with
rich earth and pure water
and embraced by
the sun's fair light.
We have come together
on this day
to bear witness to a
most blessed event.
Today shall see the joining
of these two people,
Princess Millerna
of Asturia, and...
[DORNKIRK] Now that the girl and
the dragon have been separated.
The probability graph
is stabilizing.
This is the perfect opportunity
to capture Hitomi Kanzaki.
That girl is the key to our
successful alteration of fate.
[FOLKEN] I understand and if the
dragon should try to interfere?
[DORNKIRK] If he dares
to challenge us yet again,
then he must be eliminated.
We won't fail you, Lord
Folken, not this time.
The luck you've given us
will make us invincible.
We will capture the girl
for you, I promise.
Please trust us in this.
[VAN, MERLE gasp]
[HITOMI gasps]
This can't be...
No way!
[HITOMI] This vision is
like my first reading!
[CROWD cheering]
Married life's really gonna
calm that tomboy princess down.
[HITOMI gasps]
It's all wrong!
[GADDES, ORT, KIO]
Hm?
[HITOMI]
This marriage is a mistake!
Hey, wait!
[VAN, MERLE grunt]
That looks like...
my brother's ship!
Peekaboo!
See? The dragon guided us
to their exact location!
I guess our luck really is
operating on a whole new level!
[HITOMI]
No, wait!
[CROWD chattering]
Hitomi?
[HITOMI]
No!
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Wait, stop! Don't do this!
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Uh...
What's that?
There was no eclipse
predicted for today!
This is an ill omen!
What's happening?!
[ROYAL GUARD A] We're under
attack! Prepare yourselves!
Zaibach again!
[DRYDEN]
Millerna!
[MILLERNA gasps]
But it can't be Zaibach!
We're allies!
The Guymelefs are ready!
[SOLDIERS clamoring]
[ALLEN]
A malfunction? No, not now!
[DRYDEN]
Look out!
Dryden!
[NARIA chuckles]
So much smoke.
Not you two again!
[ERIYA]
I won't let you near the girl.
No matter what I have to do!
[ERIYA growls]
[ERIYA]
Heh.
[VAN]
The hell?! [grunts]
[ERIYA laughs] Behold the power
of our luck intensification!
[HITOMI]
Oh no, Dryden!
Hitomi, help! Here!
[HITOMI]
Uh... 'Kay!
[DRYDEN] Well, this is a
pretty pathetic showing.
[HITOMI]
Hush. Save your strength!
[MILLERNA] All right.
I think that ought to do.
[crash]
[HITOMI]
Escaflowne!
[VAN grunting]
[ALLEN]
Van!
[VAN]
What's going on?!
[gasps]
No! Van!
[FOLKEN]
Attention, people of Asturia.
These are the Zaibach
Intensified Luck Soldiers.
You're encouraged to cooperate.
[VAN]
Folken.
[FOLKEN] I repeat: if you value
your lives, we suggest...
"Intensified Luck Soliders"?
Wait a minute, luck?
[FOLKEN]
Resistance is futile.
Anyone who dares to refuse...
[HITOMI] This card,
could it be possible?
When I did Millerna's reading
earlier... I did this!
It happened because I tried
to manipulate destiny!
[FOLKEN]
We have but one demand.
Give us the girl from the
Mystic Moon. Hitomi Kanzaki.
What?
[FOLKEN] If you wish to
avoid further devastation,
you will relinquish
her to us immediately!
[MILLERNA]
You can't go!
[DRYDEN] She's right! Don't
do what they say, Hitomi.
[MILLERNA]
Stay still!
It's all my fault.
This happened because I told
you a fortune that wasn't true.
[MILLERNA gasps]
What are you talking about?
When I did your reading
the cards revealed
that this marriage would
result in disaster.
But I thought maybe I
could change it, so I...
I tried to use my will to alter
the course of the future.
[MILLERNA]
But why? Why do that?
Because, Millerna, I saw
the man you're meant for.
Just like you thought.
It was Allen, all along!
[HITOMI] The problem
is, I love him, too!
Do you see now?
I didn't want to lose him to
you, so I changed the reading!
I manipulated the order.
I tried to switch out one
destiny for another!
Hitomi, how could you?
[HITOMI cries]
[HITOMI] This is my mess,
and I have to clean it up.
[MILLERNA]
What are you...?
Don't go!
Dryden? Dryden!
Stay with me!
[HITOMI]
I'm the one you want!
[VAN whimpers]
Don't do this!
I'm Hitomi Kanzaki, and I'll
go with you right now.
Just leave everyone else alone!
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[FOLKEN]
Just accept it, please!