[HITOMI] Was it all just a
dream? Or was it a vision?
No. Crazy as it seems,
it really happened.
It all began with
a tarot reading
on a seemingly normal day.
I asked the cards
if I would find love.
[COACH]
Ready!
[STUDENT A] Hey, Hitomi,
do a reading for me!
[HITOMI]
Maybe later!
You're killing me! Come on,
Hitomi! Where are you?
[YUKARI]
Hey, practice is starting!
[HITOMI]
I know! I know!
[COACH]
'Kay, next up!
[YUKARI]
Finally! There you are!
You're late.
Late, late, really late!
You know who gets yelled at
when someone shows up
late for practice?
The manager. That's me.
Try to keep that in mind
next time, would you?
I will. I'm sorry.
I got hung up
working on my paper.
[chuckles]
Uh. How late am I? Did I
miss the guys' time trials?
[YUKARI sighs]
You're hopeless, you know that?
Your knight in shining
gym shorts is up now.
Good luck, Amano.
[COACH]
Ready!
[gunshot]
Whoa! Ten point six-four!
Ah! He really is awesome!
Amano beat 11 seconds, can you
believe it? He's amazing!
[YUKARI giggles]
[COACH]
Okay. Girls' times are up next.
[FEMALE STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
Ready? Hm?
[HITOMI yelps]
I can do it myself, thanks.
Get your butt out there.
Fine, I'm going.
All right.
Ready!
[gunshot]
You can do it, Hitomi!
[HITOMI gasping]
[screams]
[HITOMI]
What's this?
It's hot. Why is it so hot?
[BALGUS]
Prince Van, are you ready?
Yes. Don't worry about me.
[BALGUS] It's the dragon
that should be worried.
I've no doubt that
you can slay it.
Try to forget your
brother's disgrace.
Enough, Balgus! Stop there!
I won't be defeated. I will
never show my back to an enemy.
[yelping]
[screams]
Amano? Wh-What's going on?
Where--?
[AMANO] Easy. You should
stay in bed for now.
[HITOMI]
I'm sorry.
[AMANO]
I'm just glad you weren't hurt.
That was some fall.
[HITOMI]
Yeah.
[AMANO] You know, your form
is pretty much perfect.
I can really tell how hard
you've been practicing.
I'm not that good.
I mean, I still haven't
managed to break 13 seconds.
I'm not nearly
as fast as you are.
I don't know how you do it.
For me, it's all in the way
you come off the blocks.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
You have to focus
everything you've got
and then launch
yourself forward.
Really? Is that what you do?
S'bout it.
Huh? Hey, that's a cool pendant.
Oh. Thanks, you like it?
It's a good luck charm.
I got it from my grandmother.
It's really neat.
When you swing it like this,
it acts like a pendulum clock,
completing one cycle a
second, never slowing down.
[AMANO]
Huh?
Think I could give it a try?
That's one.
Two. Three. Four. Five.
Six.
[BOTH]
Seven. Eight. Nine. Ten.
And Eleven. And Twelve.
And Thirteen.
[HITOMI]
Fourteen. Fifteen. Sixteen.
--Seve--
--[AMANO] Kanzaki.
[AMANO]
I wanted to tell you.
You see, I...
[YUKARI]
Hitomi!
[gasps]
I brought y--
[HITOMI]
Yukari!
Come on, say something already!
You can't ignore me
forever, you know.
[YUKARI] I can let it
slide for a rice cake.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
[YUKARI] And some cheesecake,
and a bean-jam pancake,
and some peppermint ice cream.
You know what,
let's just say a different
dessert every day for a month.
I think that'll do it.
[HITOMI]
Cut me some slack.
I didn't collapse
on purpose, okay?
[YUKARI]
Oh, really?
You weren't hoping somebody
would rush to your side
compelled by your fragile
state to declare his love?
[HITOMI]
You're a jerk.
[YUKARI, HITOMI laughing]
[YUKARI]
Hitomi?
[HITOMI]
Yeah?
[YUKARI] Have you ever done
a reading for you and Amano?
[HITOMI]
Never.
[YUKARI]
Why not?
[HITOMI] Well. What if it told
me things wouldn't work out?
[YUKARI]
Oh.
Right.
What's wrong? You seem
upset about something.
[YUKARI]
The thing is.
I overheard some other students
talking about Amano before.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, but I think
he's moving out of the country.
I don't know if he's even
going to the track meet
that's coming up.
So...
If you feel that
strongly about him...
...I think you should tell him.
See what he says.
I know you, you'll
regret it if you don't.
[HITOMI'S MOM]
Hitomi!
Where are you?
The bath's ready! Hitomi?
[HITOMI]
There it is. The Tower.
It can indicate distant
separation. It's true.
[HITOMI] Amano's moving
out of the country.
I'll never see him again.
[HITOMI]
The Dragon of Light? Courage?
[AMANO] I'm sorry I'm gonna
miss out on the meet,
but you guys are gonna kill it.
Make sure to tell me how
everybody does, okay?
I'll be waiting to hear.
I expect good news.
[STUDENT A]
We want updates, too.
Let us know when you get there.
[AMANO]
Sure.
[STUDENT B]
Don't forget us.
Even if you like
your new school.
[AMANO]
No way!
[STUDENT C]
Goodbye, Amano!
[STUDENT D]
--[STUDENT E] Bye, buddy!
--[STUDENT F] Take care, Amano!
[STUDENT G]
Goodbye!
[HITOMI]
Amano, wait!
Amano.
I... I have a proposal to make.
[HITOMI]
I want you to time me.
My goal is to run
a hundred meters
before the pendant can
complete 13 cycles.
If I beat the
13 second barrier...
[AMANO]
Huh?
[HITOMI] I'd like you
to give me my first kiss.
Well, let's see what
you got, then.
[HITOMI]
I'll do my best!
Kanzaki! Are you
ready for this?!
Yes! I'm ready anytime you are.
Yukari.
[AMANO] Focus everything you've
got and launch yourself forward.
Ready!
Just focus everything
you've got.
Go!
Almost there. Come on.
Uh?
Just who the hell are you?
[HITOMI]
Huh?
What the--? Where--?
[AMANO]
Kanzaki!
[YUKARI]
Hitomi! Are you okay?
Say something.
That guy.
[YUKARI]
Huh?
I've seen him.
That guy was in my dream before.
Yeah? Who are you?
Creatures from the demon world!
No, we're not from the demon
world, whatever that means.
What's going on?
Why don't you tell
us who you are?
I'm Van of Fanelia.
Where... Where am I?
What now?
Hold on. How can understand
what this guy is saying?
[HITOMI]
Huh?
If I came here, then so can he.
[VAN]
You should get out of here!
A land dragon's coming!
A dragon?
Get moving now! Or do you want
to be a dragon's dinner?
[BOTH gasp]
[AMANO]
Hey, easy, man.
That same lightning.
Not again. What's
gonna show up now?
Hitomi?
[HITOMI] I don't feel good.
I think I might puke.
Here it comes.
[growls]
What the hell is that thing?
It's a monster.
[VAN]
Over here!
You were fighting me, remember?!
What's the matter?!
Aren't ya hungry?!
Well, come and get me!
[LAND DRAGON roaring]
Did that finish it?
[YUKARI screams]
Huh, so that's how it hunts.
It wounds its prey then
finishes it off later.
Get out of here!
[HITOMI] Right!
Come on you two. Let's go!
[AMANO]
Yeah!
[yelling]
[AMANO]
Hurry!
[yelps]
[HITOMI]
Yukari!
[YUKARI]
It's my ankle.
It looks like you twisted it.
Here. Get on.
[YUKARI]
Thank you.
Let's go!
[HITOMI]
Coming!
Come back!
You're not gonna get away!
We should be safe up here.
[VAN]
Hey! Over here!
[AMANO]
Come on!
[HITOMI]
Yeah!
[yelling]
It's no use.
Its scales are too tough
to cut with this sword.
Looks like that thing's
about to make a meal of him.
[gasps]
He's gonna die. I have
to do something quick.
What are you...? Kanzaki!
[HITOMI]
Above you! Look!
[VAN]
Now!
[yelling]
[yells]
[HITOMI]
Um...
That was intense. Are you okay?
I'm not so bad off that I need
a girl to worry about me.
Why're you still here, anyway?
Let me guess: you want a reward.
Fine, then. Come to my castle.
But you better not think this
makes you some kind of hero
or anything.
It's just an apology for
involving you in dragonslaying.
Wow, you're a major jerk!
I didn't help because
I wanted a reward.
I thought that dragon was
gonna kill you. That scared me.
I didn't want you to die, okay?
So I risked my life to save you.
I don't think a simple "thank
you" is really too much to ask.
I should have let that
stupid dragon eat you.
Saving your life was
obviously a waste of effort!
[crying]
What's the Energist doing?
What's happening?
[AMANO]
Kanzaki!
Help me, Amano!
Where's it taking me?!
Kanzaki!
They vanished.
[YUKARI]
Hitomi?
Hitomi!
I made it back.
Where are we?
That looks like...
that's the Earth.
If I'm looking at the Earth,
then where am I?
We're in a field not far
from the village of Arzas.
How... How did we get here?
[HITOMI] The card of separation
and the serpent of light.
I was beginning to understand
what they truly meant.
The Earth and the moon
hung bright in the sky
of the strange world
I'd found myself in.
Its name, I would come
to learn, was Gaea.
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
Good. So the old texts
were right. I can work it.
[VAN yelling]
So that's it.
That's Escaflowne.