[FOLKEN] This land of Fanelia
is guarded by dragons,
and yet hands borne
of those dragons
are the ones
that destroyed it.
Naria. Eriya.
We're very grateful to
you for saving our lives
all those years ago, my lord.
And we're happy our
last moments in life
can be spent with you.
I have worked so
hard for so long.
Yet still, my wishes are denied.
[KING's AIDE B]
We are not at war with them!
[KING'S AIDE C]
Indeed!
The empire hasn't announced the
abandonment of the alliance!
[DRYDEN]
Then we should probably
postpone any demands
for reparations.
[KING'S AIDE A]
Of course!
Zaibach is clearly
after only one thing,
and that's the girl, Hitomi!
If we turn her over,
that should appease them.
Give them what they want and
surely they'll leave us alone!
But their floating fortress
has been destroyed!
They still have an
axe to grind with us!
We shouldn't give them a
chance to strike again.
Deal with the problem
at its source.
If you hand Hitomi over to them,
that may lead to
Gaea's destruction!
[KING'S AIDE C]
The power of Atlantis
is nothing but a silly myth!
[KING'S AIDE B]
Our country will only be safe
if we maintain the
alliance with Zaibach.
[DRYDEN] I'm afraid
this is a fools' paradise.
Even if we were to give
Hitomi to Zaibach,
do you think that would
satisfy our people?
Countless Asturians
lost homes,
family, and lives during their
unprovoked attack
on our country.
Therefore, in King
Aston's stead,
I, Dryden, hereby decree that,
in accordance with the alliance
with our neighboring countries,
economic sanctions be
imposed against Zaibach.
[MAN A]
Folken's a shameful coward!
[MAN B] He fled the
Rite of Dragonslaying!
[MAN C] A sorry weakling
who abandoned his country!
You're wrong! My brother's
great! He's no coward!
--[door creaks]
--[MERLE] Meow?!
[MERLE]
King Van!
[HITOMI]
How did it go?
I'd like to believe that we're
making some progress.
[VAN] Words mean nothing.
We need action.
[HITOMI, ALLEN]
Uh?
Folken has disappeared again.
He's the one
responsible for this.
And I've had enough.
So, I'm gonna kill him.
You can't really mean that!
[VAN] I am Fanelia's king. It's
my duty to avenge its people.
But you can't do that,
he's your brother!
There has to be
another solution!
[HITOMI] He sounds so
brutal and heartless.
This isn't like him at all.
[HITOMI gasps]
[ALLEN] It's fine to believe
in people, Hitomi.
But the truth is, no matter how
much faith you have in someone,
they may still disappoint you.
[HITOMI] Please, Allen.
Don't say things like that.
[NARIA]
Listen, serving Lord Folken
is all that matters to me.
If I do that, then
I have no regrets.
[HITOMI] Naria never stopped
believing in Lord Folken,
not even for a second.
[NARIA] All she'd do is get in
our way if we took her with us.
Let's go, Eriya! We have to
get back to Lord Folken!
[HITOMI]
He is Van's big brother.
[howling]
[HITOMI gasps]
[HITOMI]
Are those wolves?
Somebody is calling!
[howling]
[ADOM MAN A]
Hello, Van Fanel.
[VAN] Are you the
one who sent for me?
[ADOM MAN A] I have a message
from pack leader Ruhm.
Folken is expecting
you in Fanelia.
What?
[MAN C] I think Prince
Folken's gone for good.
[MAN B] Rumor has it
that he fled the country.
[MAN A]
I had a feeling he would fail.
He was too young to face
the Rite of Dragonslaying.
[BALGUS] That's enough!
Mind your own business.
No more rumormongering!
Don't you worry, Prince Van.
Prince Folken will surely
return to us. I have no doubt.
[VAN grunts]
Who's there?!
Oh. You startled me.
What do you want?
[ALLEN]
Escaflowne's vanished?
[DRYDEN exhales]
What's he thinking,
disappearing at
a time like this?
[MERLE meows]
King Van! Where are you?!
[GADDES]
Whoa!
Allen, have you seen Hitomi?!
I can't find her
anywhere in the castle.
Her room's been cleaned,
and her bag is packed!
Could she and Van have
gone off together?
That does seem likely.
[gasps] Do you think
she seduced him?!
I bet she did. She's
real sneaky like that!
[MOLE MAN]
I saw them last night.
Hitomi and Van,
I mean. [grunting]
Get outta there, ya derelict!
And it looked
pretty cozy to me.
What were you doing lurkin'
under the carriage
like that, huh?!
[MERLE]
Hey, mole man!
Did you really see them?
And don't you lie to me!
[MOLE MAN]
Yeah.
[MERLE]
Oh, no! They eloped! Oh!
How could you do it, King Van?
How could you leave me?
[ALLEN] When she
believes in someone,
nothing seems to
shake her faith.
[VAN] You shouldn't
be here, Hitomi.
[HITOMI] Oh, don't worry,
it's not a trap or anything.
[VAN]
What do you mean?
[HITOMI] That guy said the
message came from Ruhm, right?
Do you think Folken's
so cowardly that he'd
even turn your own
friends against you?
Once you see him,
everything'll make sense.
Quit yelling into my ear!
I heard you.
I'm sorry.
[VAN]
I'll keep my word.
[HITOMI gasps]
[VAN]
You'll be protected.
Whether I have to bring
you back to Allen,
or return you to
the Mystic Moon.
Either way, I'll make
sure you're safe.
[SORCERER A]
The shadows of the dragon
and the girl from the Mystic
Moon have overlapped.
I detect no irregularities
in fate density, though.
[DORNKIRK]
Folken's plan is still working.
All is proceeding as it should.
There is no need to fear.
Our new future is close
enough to touch,
and it looks glorious indeed.
[GETIN]
The Vione has been destroyed,
and Folken is missing.
[ADELPHOS] And those upstarts in
Asturia are now turning on us,
along with their allies.
They've threatened
us with sanctions!
Yet the emperor still
doesn't seem inclined
to make the slightest move!
What is he waiting for?!
That alliance is powerless.
It's nothing but a mindless mob.
I believe he's done nothing
because he has far more faith
in us, his four generals,
than any band of common rebels.
I wish I could believe that.
[GETIN]
What's wrong?
[ADELPHOS]
Hm?
You look pale.
Are you troubled?
[ADELPHOS grunts]
[ADELPHOS]
I cannot understand it.
What's happening to Zaibach?
[RUHM]
Do you think he'll come?
Yes, of course.
He is my brother.
This seems like an
awful lot of trouble
to go to for a family reunion.
Uh! There he is!
Hello, Brother.
[FOLKEN] She's quite the unknown
element. I find her intriguing.
[HITOMI]
Uh.
Hi, little lady!
I had a feeling you might
be tagging along with Van.
[HITOMI]
Uh.
[RUHM] I don't blame you
for being concerned,
but I wouldn't put yourself
in the middle of this mess.
I'm staying out of it, too. Van,
Folken, I'll see you boys later.
[FOLKEN]
Thank you, Ruhm.
[VAN]
Did you come alone?
[FOLKEN] Do you think I'd try
to entrap my own brother?
[VAN]
Tsk.
--[VAN grunts]
--[HITOMI gasps]
[VAN]
You're no brother of mine!
[HITOMI]
Van!
[VAN]
Look!
Look at what happened to
the homeland you abandoned!
This once lush, protected
land now lies in ruins!
Do you hate me, then?
A man who shares name
and blood with you?
[VAN]
Your crimes were brutal.
Your punishment
will be the same!
Please...
Be careful! [gasps]
[LAND DRAGON A roars]
[VAN]
A land dragon.
[gasps]
What the--
[roars]
I get it.
He was planning this all along.
Just one more betrayal!
Are you sure?
[roars]
It's only been a few months,
and they're already
wandering freely?
This way!
[LAND DRAGONS roaring]
[LAND DRAGON B growls]
[FOLKEN]
Stop fighting, Van.
[VAN gasps]
[FOLKEN] Let go of
the rage in your heart,
and the dragons will retreat.
That's enough! I'm not falling
for any more of your lies!
[LAND DRAGON B roars]
[HITOMI yelps]
Damn.
Folken! Show yourself right now!
[FOLKEN] Fighting will
not solve anything.
[FOLKEN]
Yes.
To become Fanelia's king,
one must slay a dragon,
a task at which I failed.
[panting]
[gasps]
[roars]
[FOLKEN yells]
[FOLKEN] I was ready
to die at that moment.
But then...
Am... Am I going to survive?
No, my wounds are too severe.
[DORNKIRK]
Awaken,
young nobleman of the
land protected by dragons.
[FOLKEN]
Who's there?
[DORNKIRK]
My name is Dornkirk.
I am the man who intends to
master the power of Atlantis
and use it to control destiny.
What do you mean,
"the power of Atlantis"?
[DORNKIRK] The power that
flows through your veins.
You escaped death because the
strength of ancient Atlantis
is in your blood.
Join me and together
we'll create a world free
from the sorrow of war.
[FOLKEN]
Where am I?
[FOLKEN whimpers]
[FOLKEN screams]
[FOLKEN]
Under Dornkirk's tutelage,
I learned the ways of science,
and used my heightened skills
to become a Sorcerer
of the Zaibach Empire.
I did it to ensure
Gaea's future.
So that's the reason you
betrayed your homeland
and sold your
soul to Zaibach?!
--[crash]
--[BOTH gasp]
[LAND DRAGON A roars]
[HITOMI yelps]
[HITOMI]
Van!
[VAN]
Run, Hitomi! Go, now!
Over here!
[HITOMI panting]
[LAND DRAGON B roars]
[HITOMI gasps]
[LAND DRAGON B snorting]
[LAND DRAGON B growls]
[HITOMI gasping]
Not a sound.
[LAND DRAGON B exhales]
[HITOMI sighs]
[FOLKEN]
Please trust me.
I want a peaceful
future for our world,
but I'll need help
from both of you.
You had something in
common, you and Naria.
[FOLKEN gasps]
[HITOMI]
Think about it.
Both your bodies were
rebuilt by somebody else.
Naria?
[FOLKEN]
How did you...?
[VAN groaning]
[HITOMI]
And now Naria is dead.
Along with all those people
in Fanelia, and in Asturia.
[FOLKEN]
You are correct.
Which is precisely why we must
change the fate of man now.
After all the sacrifices
that have been made,
we must bring peace to Gaea!
How will you do that?
[FOLKEN] Dornkirk's
theories were correct.
I'll learn the laws of destiny,
and bend them to make
the world a better place.
It's been done before,
by the people of Atlantis.
[gasps]
[HITOMI] But don't you see
that isn't how changing fate
actually works? It's cheating!
[NARIA]
Your feelings change people.
[HITOMI]
Naria?
[LAND DRAGON A roars]
[HITOMI gasps]
[LAND DRAGONS roar]
[VAN whimpering]
Van!
[HITOMI]
Uh!
Folken has wings?
Wha... What are you doing?
Van, put your weapon down, now!
[LAND DRAGON A growls]
[FOLKEN]
I said, put it down.
--Do it!
--[VAN gasps]
He was right.
The dragons are leaving!
[FOLKEN] Van, anger
and fear have great power.
That's what drew
the dragons to you.
Just as a drop of water causes
ripples to appear in a pond,
if you have anger
and fear in your heart,
conflict will follow.
I will change the future of
mankind, to create a new world,
free of that poisonous
rage and terror.
A world truly without war?
[FOLKEN] "And thus, our hero
slew the ferocious dragon,
and became king of
the land of Fanelia."
[VAN] Why did he have to
kill the dragon, Brother?
That just seems so mean!
You're right, Van.
Killing dragons is mean.
I don't care for it, either.
[FOLKEN] The king of
Fanelia is destined to fight,
and I wanted to spare
you that awful fate.
No one should have to bear that
burden, least of all my brother.
So I have fought for years
to change the world.
To make it a peaceful place
worthy of your peaceful soul.
However...
Dornkirk's methods,
no, our methods,
disrespected human life.
That, I cannot abide.
Van. This man must be stopped.
Please, fight with me.
Your wings, Brother.
What happened to them?
[HITOMI] So, in the ruins
of their homeland,
the brothers were
finally reunited.
But, where Van's wings
were white as snow,
the feathers that flew from
Folken's were black as night.
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[ALLEN] There's something
important that I must tell you.
[VAN yells]
[ALLEN]
Now that you know everything,
can you possibly love me?
[DILANDAU]
Burn away!