Amano. I am right here.
It's true.
You have wings like an angel.
[MERLE] Stop it!
You leave him alone!
Quit staring at him!
Why? What's wrong?
[HITOMI]
This feather.
Please don't cry.
Okay, Mother?
It was present when something
incredibly tragic happened.
[TEO] Hey, watch it!
That was pretty close!
Sorry about that!
Commander.
This route is about to get
a whole lot tighter soon.
Maybe we should just
look for another way.
Negative. We stay
on this course.
But, sir.
[ALLEN]
Look, I know it's dangerous.
But it's also the only
way to make it into Freid
without being
spotted by Zaibach.
I'm not worried.
I know I've got a crew who can
pull off a stunt like this.
Thanks, Boss.
Hey, ya dirtbags!
Stay sharp now!
We're gonna kick
some Zaibach ass!
So let's make it through
this valley, okay?
[CREW]
Aye!
[ALLEN] Van, I hope
you're coming, too.
We'll see you in Freid.
I'm sorry, Eries.
[ERIES]
Millerna!
[MILLERNA]
I've made up my mind.
I have to help him.
[ERIES]
Please. Don't do this.
You can't help yourself,
let alone Allen.
Would you stop treating
me like a child?
If you haven't noticed,
I'm an adult.
For once in my life,
I wish you and Father
would treat me as such,
instead of continuing to
make my decisions for me
without asking how I feel.
The choices we make
are for your own good.
Like forcing me to give
up my medical studies?
You were wasting your time.
Honestly, what use
does a princess have
for such knowledge?
[MILLERNA]
To help people, why else?
To comfort them and
make them feel better!
You can still do
that right here,
by carrying out your duties.
If what you want is
to help your people,
then don't run away.
Don't put Allen above all.
But I love him! Can't
you understand that?
[MILLERNA] Like I said,
I've made up my mind.
Goodbye, Eries.
Take care of yourself.
I will miss you.
[LEON] The Draconians.
The winged people.
The descendants of Atlantis.
The accursed clan.
[HITOMI]
What? "Draconians"?
[LEON] Avoid their
kind at all costs.
They will end your world.
Just as they
destroyed Atlantis.
It's you.
[HITOMI]
This is Fanelia.
[MERLE]
No, Prince Van!
Please don't do this!
I'm begging you!
[VILLAGERS yelling]
[VAN]
Geez, you're flaky!
Just a few minutes ago,
you were the one telling
me to go for it.
[MERLE] That was before I
realized how high up we'd be!
Don't worry, 'cause
I'm gonna be fine!
No, don't do it!
[YURIZEN] Wine tastes better
after a victory, does it not?
Steel yourselves for
the final battle at dawn,
and then we'll drink our fill
after we've taken
the enemy's castle!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[HITOMI]
Soldiers from Fanelia.
Escaflowne?
[GOAU]
Balgus?
[BALGUS]
Sire?
[GOAU] When this war ends,
will you leave us?
[BALGUS]
Yes.
With all due respect, I'd like
to hone my spirit once more.
[GOAU]
I see. You will be missed.
[BALGUS] I'll never forget
your kindness, Sire.
It's all right, Balgus.
Besides, I too
want you to master
the ways of the warrior.
Once you've done so,
I hope you'll return home
and take what you've learned
and use it for the
benefit of Fanelia.
Yes, Sire.
[GOAU]
That woman.
She's a Draconian!
A descendant of Atlantis,
those demons of legend!
Run! Flee, Sire!
You're in danger!
[GOAU]
No need for that.
She may be a demon,
but a beautiful one.
Perhaps I've been
totally possessed,
because I'd gladly
let her devour my soul.
[BALGUS]
But, Sire.
[VARIE] We meet at last,
King Goau of Fanelia.
[GOAU] Tell me, how
do you know my name?
[VARIE] When I was born,
a prophecy was made
foretelling the coming of the
man for whom I was destined.
He would approach me
on a night like tonight.
When the Mystic
Moon hangs bright
above the western mountains.
"Destined," is it?
Yes, Sire. Our meeting
was fated long ago.
Well, if that's the case...
...may I know your name?
It's Varie.
[GOAU]
Varie.
Would you be so kind
as to come with me?
[VARIE]
Yes... beloved.
Wow, so those two are Van's
mother and father, huh?
[ADVISOR A]
You can't, Sire!
Marrying a Draconian woman
would be sheer folly!
[ADVISOR B] Need we remind you
it was her accursed people
that brought about the
destruction of Atlantis?
[ADVISOR C]
Surely she'll bring disaster
upon our country as well!
Remember what the legends
tell us, Your Majesty! Beware!
[GOAU]
I don't care what they say.
They have nothing
to do with my Varie!
I've fallen in love with her
and she and I will be married!
Nothing you say
will change my mind.
Varie is going to become
my bride and queen!
[GOAU chuckles]
[GOAU] It's a boy!
A healthy baby boy!
Come, Folken.
Say hello to your
new little brother.
[FOLKEN]
What's his name, Father?
[GOAU]
Van. Van Fanel.
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[yelps]
[FOLKEN]
Van!
Mother?
Your wings. You can't
let anyone see them.
You must keep
them a secret, Van.
It's important you
understand this.
Never show your wings
until you know that
the time is right.
Please promise me.
I'll be worried
sick if you don't.
I promise, Mother.
I'm so sorry I upset you.
[VARIE crying]
It's Balgus. So you got word?
[BALGUS]
How is he?
[BALGUS] I'm too late.
I'm sorry, my king.
[VAN]
Don't worry, Mother.
Even though Folken ran away,
I'll step up and take
his place on the throne.
I'll be a mighty king
like father was!
Just wait, you'll see!
So don't cry.
Everything's going to be
all right. Okay, Mother?
[VAN]
Soon afterwards,
mother went into the forest
where the dragons nest
to look for my
brother, Folken.
[VAN] When she didn't come back,
Balgus went to look for her,
but he found no trace.
My mother never
returned to the castle.
And I never saw her again.
[HITOMI]
Thank you.
[VAN]
Uh?
[HITOMI]
For telling me about that.
And your wings, too.
If you don't mind me saying,
they're very beautiful. Your
wings. I like them a lot.
[chuckles]
[VAN]
You know what?
That's the same thing
Merle told me once.
[HITOMI]
Hey.
Did you just compare me
to that mangy little minx?
Thanks a lot, jerk.
[HITOMI chuckles]
[DORNKIRK]
Hmm...
Why can't I see it?
Why can I no longer
see the future?
My visions, which
were once so clear,
are now in disarray
and sinking into chaos.
Why won't you show me?
I must see what will transpire!
Until I can, the dragon's
shadow will obscure my visions
of what is to come.
[HITOMI]
Um, Van, where're we going?
[VAN]
To the Duchy of Freid.
Gotta to be
somewhere near here.
[HITOMI]
Oh.
Van, wait!
What is it?
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
I don't know why. It's just...
[MERLE]
Just what?
Is something out there?
Is that them?
What's doing that?
It's gotta be them again, Van.
Those invisible
bastards from Zaibach?
I think so.
They're around here somewhere.
[HITOMI]
They're close.
But where are they hiding?
They're straight ahead of us!
Dammit!
[VAN]
Hitomi, Merle, hang on tight!
To your right, Van!
Now behind you!
[HITOMI, MERLE scream]
How are you missing them?
Are you clods aiming?
They were dead center
in our sights.
[MIGUEL] It's like they
can see us somehow.
No, that's utter nonsense!
Shut up and hit him, would you?
But please try not to kill him.
Where're they now, Hitomi?
There! Dead ahead, Van!
[DILANDAU]
What the--?
[VAN]
Hold on!
[HITOMI yelps]
Get after them!
A river, eh?
Yeah, that's perfect!
Hop down, you two! Hurry!
[HITOMI]
What, but why?
[VAN]
Just do it!
[MERLE]
'Kay!
[HITOMI]
Hey, wait!
[MERLE]
Please be careful!
Why is he going into the river?
[HITOMI gasps]
[HITOMI]
This way, quick!
They fell for it.
Turning invisible
won't do them any good
if they're in the water.
And now that I can see them.
Clever move.
[yelling]
Do it now! We've got him!
Perfect.
[DILANDAU]
Hah!
So much for that
little strategy of yours!
King Van's in trouble!
Maybe I should disobey orders
and just crush you right here.
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A] The
Dragonslayers have captured
the target.
Ah, good.
In that case, let's go down
and retrieve the dragon.
Yes, sir.
Oh, no. We have to do
something to help him!
[HITOMI]
Save him!
Somebody, please, save him!
Save Van!
[FOLKEN]
Van, this was inevitable.
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A]
Leviship closing in
from the Norte quadrant!
What's that?
It's Allen!
[yelling]
Not you!
Allen!
And it's a pleasure to
see you again as well, Van.
You're going to pay
for interrupting me.
With your fool life!
Hitomi.
Dammit!
Oh, no!
[screaming]
[yelling]
You weakling!
Get out of there!
Hitomi!
[HITOMI screaming]
[HITOMI]
Allen?!
[ALLEN]
Careless fool.
[VAN yelling]
[HITOMI]
Oh, no! Are you okay?
Say something! Allen, please!
This doesn't look good at all.
Please be all right, Commander.
[REEDEN]
Ships!
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A]
Freid convoy approaching, sir.
Damn their hides.
Fall back. Now.
That's an order.
We've got Freid
ships incoming.
We can't let them see us.
If we're spotted, they might
catch wind of our plan.
[DILANDAU] It was just
getting interesting!
You cowards.
[HITOMI]
Allen!
Please, answer me!
[GADDES] Hurry, we've
gotta stop the bleeding!
[TRADESHIP CAPTAIN] What
exactly happened to this man?
[GADDES]
We'll explain later!
Right now, we
need your doctor.
Get him up here!
[TRADESHIP CAPTAIN]
Look, I'm very sorry.
But we're just a simple
tradeship that makes daily runs
between Rampant in Asturia
and Godasheem in Freid.
We don't have a doctor,
or anyone who could handle
a serious wound like that.
[HITOMI]
This is my fault.
He got wounded saving me.
Oh, Allen.
[MILLERNA]
Gaddes!
I thought that was
your voice I heard.
[GADDES]
Princess Millerna.
I see the rest of you
are here as well, eh?
Where's Allen?
Shouldn't he be with you?
Allen? What
happened? Oh, no!
That wound.
He's losing blood.
Too much and too quick!
Gaddes, if the bleeding
isn't stopped,
he's not going to make it!
Get the ship's doctor
in here and help him now!
They don't have one,
Your Highness.
[MILLERNA]
You don't?
But... he needs a doctor.
[MOLE MAN]
He has one, Princess.
You.
Unless I'm mistaken, you did
study medicine, correct?
Well, yes, but...
Studying in books doesn't
make you a doctor.
I'm not one.
Maybe you aren't,
but you're the closest thing
we have to one, Princess,
that's for sure.
You are the only person with
even a chance of saving him.
Yes, you're right.
We must be quick.
I need you to go fetch
my blue bag, Mr. Mole.
This one, right?
[KIO] Come on out,
nice and slow!
[REEDEN] If the commander
doesn't pull through,
you're a dead man, you hear?
[MILLERNA] The anesthetic
should've taken effect by now,
but I'll need you to hold
him down if he thrashes.
[GADDES]
Yes, ma'am. Of course.
[HITOMI]
Please, God.
I'm begging you. Save Allen.
Let him make it.
He's a good man,
and the only reason
he's hurt is because of me.
Oh, Van.
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[ALLEN] Have you ever
believed in someone
with your whole heart?
[DILANDAU]
You summoned a Doppelganger?
[VORIS] A rebel, eh?
And who might that be?