You must always remember, Van.
What will ultimately determine
Gaea's future... is your will.
But, Mother, how?
[VARIE]
Remember that... Van.
An Energist.
The Energist is lighting up.
What's going on here?
It's coming from Escaflowne.
[MERLE]
King Van!
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
Hitomi!
[MILLERNA]
No, wait!
Don't leave me.
What? They just disappeared...
This is bad.
How could this happen?
Where could King Van have gone?
[SORCERER A] The Power Spot
energy influx is at 72.
[SORCERER B] Causality Detector
sensitivity set to nominal.
[SORCERER C]
Power is stable.
All functions are
operating properly.
[SORCERER D] Fate Oscillator
has reached the critical level.
[MALE SORCERER E] Power Spot
energy charge, one hundred.
Fluctuation rhythm,
point zero three.
Everything's primed.
[DORNKIRK]
Finally.
After all this time, the
preparations are now complete.
I've been imagining this
moment for a very long while.
Begin Alteration!
[SORCERER A]
Alteration has begun!
[SORCERER C]
[SORCERER D]
Alteration has begun!
[DORNKIRK laughing]
[DORNKIRK] That's right!
Show me what I wish to see most!
I must see my dream!
My ideals come to life!
[DORNKIRK] Huh? What's wrong?
It doesn't seem to be working.
Hmm. What's this?
What happened?
[HITOMI]
Whoa, Allen.
Van. Where are we?
[HITOMI]
Escaflowne.
It must've been
transported here as well.
Why's it glowing?
[HITOMI]
Van!
What's going on here?
[HITOMI]
I'm not sure.
It almost looks like we're
in some kind of planetarium.
[ALLEN] Whatever this place is,
it's definitely strange.
Whoa, the floor is moving.
[DORNKIRK]
Welcome to my humble abode.
You who are bound together
by the fate of the dragon.
[VAN]
Who's there? Show yourself!
[HITOMI]
Oh, wow.
Are you the person
who brought us here?
[DORNKIRK] Indeed. You have
answered the call of fate.
[VAN]
Fate?
[DORNKIRK]
Yes.
You see, I am the leader
of the Zaibach Empire.
The one who will guide Gaea
to her glorious future.
I am Emperor Dornkirk.
But that's impossible.
That means we're in
the heart of Zaibach.
What, there's no way.
If what he's telling
us is the truth,
that's the man behind it all.
He's the monster that
my brother serves.
[HITOMI]
Wait!
I'll end you now and save
Gaea from any more suffering!
[DORNKIRK]
It won't help.
[VAN]
What?
[DORNKIRK] Conflict can erupt
at any time, from any source.
War is the destiny
from which humanity
has never been able to escape.
What could someone like you
possibly know about destiny?
[DORNKIRK]
As it happens,
I possess the power
to predict fate.
Just as the ancient people of
Atlantis were once able to do.
Wait, Atlantis?
Could it be possible?
Are you Isaac?
Hmm. Haven't been called
that in a long time.
Isaac was the name I used in my
previous life back on Earth.
The emperor is from
the Mystic Moon?
No way, that's ridiculous!
You're the Isaac my father met.
The one he wrote about.
[DORNKIRK] I see now.
You must be Leon's son.
Fate has delivered
you here as well.
You know, he was
truly a wretched man.
He refused to reveal
the secrets of Atlantis to me.
How dare you!
[DORNKIRK] But in the end,
I didn't need your father.
I solved the mystery
of Atlantis on my own,
and now my Atlantis Machine
is finally complete.
I don't understand.
Why did you even come to
Gaea in the first place?
If you stayed on Earth,
this world would've
been so much better off!
[DORNKIRK]
I'm afraid I have to disagree.
Gaea may be soaked
in the blood of war,
but it has been that way
for a very long time.
Certainly long before I arrived.
It was the same on Earth.
Yes.
That's where all this
began, of course.
There's an idea took hold of me,
and I've never been
free of it since.
All bodies share
a common principle.
Based on their masses,
bodies create a force.
That force attracts them
to the center of the earth
as well as to other bodies.
This is gravity.
"But why does gravity
exist?" I asked myself.
Why should bodies be
drawn to one another?
Could there be a greater force
of which gravity was a part?
Something that controls the
universe with an unseen hand?
I came to believe that there is.
A force that gives
order to all life.
One that gives meaning
to each birth,
and purpose to every death.
Yes. The answer is destiny.
The fundamental force
that governs the universe.
Destiny?
[DORNKIRK] But how does
destiny function, I wondered.
Does it obey certain laws in
the same way gravity does?
I dedicated my life
to solving that mystery,
immersing myself in research
and experimentation.
Unfortunately,
despite all my efforts,
I never found the answers
that I had so hungered for.
I was at death's door.
And still, that hunger
had not abated.
If anything, it was
stronger than ever.
[ISAAC]
Please, I must know.
I must know the
principles of destiny.
[DORNKIRK] When I awoke, I
found myself in a strange land.
It was a desolate place with not
one, but two moons in the sky.
The second moon was blue.
[DORNKIRK] The land was barren.
And the climate harsh.
Its people survived
by harvesting what little
the earth yielded.
They struggled on,
living in constant fear
of an invasion from their
neighboring countries.
Theirs was a hard
and brutal fate.
[DORNKIRK]
And then I had a realization.
My purpose in this new world
was to guide these poor people
to a better life.
I gave them everything I had
and explained all that I knew.
I taught them what we
on Earth called "science."
Using that science,
they learned how to tame nature
and bend it to their needs.
Harvests began to improve.
I also taught them to
drive away their enemies
and to forge their
own destinies,
rather than allowing a cruel
destiny to rule them.
Through all those trials
and tribulations,
a great and powerful
new empire emerged.
We called it Zaibach.
I sought to learn more
of my adoptive world.
In time, rumors came to my ear
regarding the creation of Gaea.
And so, I heard the
legend of Atlantis.
And learned of the ancients'
ability to manipulate destiny.
Since then, I have
devoted all my time
and dedicated all my resources
to continue my research.
And here, at long last,
is the result.
A device with the power
to control destiny.
[DORNKIRK]
The people of ancient Atlantis
could convert human
thought into energy,
an ability that gave
them immense power.
In fact, Gaea itself is
one of Atlantis' creations.
Nobody could do that.
It's impossible!
[DORNKIRK]
I sought to build a machine
that would duplicate the
Atlanteans' capabilities.
In order to do so, however,
I needed to access the Power
Spot that was left here on Gaea
by its ancient creators.
That is why I had
to conquer Freid.
Obtaining that brought me
one step closer to my goal.
And now, at last,
the remaining key,
the dragon Escaflowne,
is in my hands.
But why Escaflowne?
So long the legendary Atlantis
Machine has filled my dreams.
This is the culmination
of my life's work.
The Fate Alteration Engine
is finally complete.
Controlling fate
is not possible.
[HITOMI]
How could you?
Using some sort of machine
to alter the world's destiny?
How many people have you killed
for your own selfish goals?
You had no right to their lives!
[DORNKIRK]
Individual sacrifices
are sometimes necessary
for the good of all.
A small misfortune
becomes the cornerstone
of something greater.
If I succeed in
creating a perfect fate,
the happiness that will result
will be worth the lives
it may have cost.
But that's crazy.
No, more than that.
It's just wrong!
Happiness that's created by a
machine isn't happiness at all!
It's a cheap lie!
[ALLEN]
Hitomi?
[VAN]
Are you okay?
I invite you all
to watch with me.
Watch the new fate of mankind.
[DRYDEN] Staring out there isn't
going to save them, y'know.
[DRYDEN] I was just
speaking with Gaddes.
We're going to
return to Asturia.
So your plan is to abandon
them? You disgust me!
[DRYDEN]
I'm sorry, Princess,
but we don't really have
a way to tell where they are.
Flying around in circles
would only be a waste
of time and fuel.
A waste of time and fuel?
Spoken like a merchant!
Yes. That's what I am, Princess.
I know those Zaibach guys are
serious about destroying Gaea.
I'll do everything I can
to try and stop them,
but it will have to
be done my way.
Don't worry. I have faith
they'll be back soon.
How can you?
It may sound strange,
but I think everyone's wishes
are connected somehow.
Who knows.
Maybe that's just me
hoping that someday
my wishes might get
through to somebody.
[SORCERER C]
So, this is the final key
to a Fate
Alteration Engine.
[SORCERER C] It's hard to
believe that an Ispano Guymelef
would have that
kind of capability.
We must do whatever it takes
to solve this mystery
without any assistance.
No matter what,
we cannot allow Folken to gain
any more ground over us.
[ALLEN]
Thank goodness, you're awake.
How're you feeling?
[HITOMI]
Where...?
A dungeon of sorts, but
at least we're still alive.
[HITOMI] Back there...
I had another vision.
In it, the ground fell away
and then the world exploded.
That sounds frightening.
You think it was an image
of Atlantis' destruction?
I'm not sure. But I think
it was something bigger.
[VAN]
Something bigger?
Maybe what you saw was
actually the fate of Gaea.
[HITOMI]
Don't say that.
[VAN] It's just like
my mother told me.
She warned me about
the power of Atlantis.
She said it must
not be awakened.
If Dornkirk activates the
Fate Alteration Engine,
then Gaea might meet the
same fate as Atlantis did
and be obliterated.
No way.
[VAN groaning]
[HITOMI]
Van?
Van! What is it? What's wrong?
This isn't good.
They must be trying to
disassemble Escaflowne.
If they do...
Please! Just hang in there, Van!
What is it?
Of course...
Van! Listen, if you can
feel Escaflowne's pain,
then it should work
the other way around too!
If your thoughts can reach it,
you should be able to operate it
no matter how far away you are!
[ALLEN]
Huh?
Hitomi.
I'll help you, okay?
If we work together, I know
we can make it happen!
No, it's too dangerous!
You'll be feeling
the same pain he his!
Allen's right, there's no need
for you to suffer like this.
Would you quit
being so stubborn?
If we don't hurry up
and do something,
then you're going to die!
Now please, give me your hand.
[ALLEN]
Please don't do this.
[HITOMI]
It'll be okay. We can do this.
[DORNKIRK] What in the world
are those two doing?
What's happening?
[HITOMI groans]
Hitomi.
I'm okay. Van,
focus on Escaflowne.
Keep concentrating.
You can do this. Come on...
[VAN]
Move... Come on, move!
[HITOMI] Escaflowne....
please... help us!
What?
[SORCERER B]
No! This is impossible!
[SORCERERS yelling]
[DORNKIRK] I don't understand.
Why can't I see?
[DORNKIRK] The girl from the
Mystic Moon. Is this her power?
Escaflowne's here!
Yes! Can you believe it, Van?
We actually brought it to us!
Quick, we need to find an
escape route, right away!
I'm on it!
It's a Guymelef!
Allen, take Hitomi!
Right.
Van!
I'll hold them off! You just
protect her, got it?
[HITOMI]
No!
[VAN]
Go on ahead!
Listen, we'll meet up
on the roof. Get going!
Okay, then.
But be careful. Come on,
let's get to the roof.
[ALLEN]
Let's go.
[DORNKIRK] Hm? I can see
them again. Why is that?
Which way?
[HITOMI]
Um.
Over there!
Right, let's go!
[HITOMI]
Yeah!
I hope Van's doing all right.
He'll meet us on the
roof soon. I'm sure of it!
[ALLEN] You have a lot of
faith in him, don't you?
[HITOMI]
Huh?
[ALLEN]
Nothing. Never mind.
This city seems so
lonely and desolate.
I wonder if the people
here in Zaibach
are really happy
like Dornkirk said.
[ALLEN]
We've got company.
I'll never let you have Hitomi,
even if it costs me my life!
Allen! Hitomi! Get on!
Van!
Here, hurry!
Coming!
[ALLEN]
Let's go!
Right, hold on to something!
Hurry! They're gaining on us!
Please, Escaflowne,
we must go faster!
They're gaining!
Come on, faster!
[HITOMI yelps]
[DORNKIRK] When the dragon
and the girl are close together,
the image of the future wavers.
One way or another,
that girl from Earth will
be the key to everything.
I must find a way
to separate them.
[ARMORED SOLDIER A] There's
an object closin' in on us.
It's remarkably fast.
Be on alert.
Allen, please, that hurts.
Uh. Sorry about that.
[HITOMI] I can't believe
Dornkirk, emperor of Zaibach,
is actually a man
from the Mystic Moon.
Fate really does work
in mysterious ways.
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[MILLERNA]
Please do a reading for me.
[HITOMI]
He reminds me so much of Amano.