[HITOMI] Was it all just a
dream? Or was it a vision?
The giants that attacked
Fanelia appeared again,
setting fire to Allen's castle.
Just as I thought, another one
of my visions had come true.
They started chasing us,
but Van changed Escaflowne
into a dragon to divert
their attention.
His trick worked.
The enemy followed Van.
And the rest of us escaped.
[DILANDAU]
Come on, move it!
Fly faster, or we're never
going to catch up!
[VAN grunts]
How I love a moving target!
[VAN grunting]
[VAN]
The wind's too strong!
You bastards. You can't
hide from me forever!
What?!
[VAN]
Damn it!
[DILANDAU chuckles]
Too late, you're mine now.
[VAN growling]
You set yourself up as a decoy
so the others could escape, huh?
Well, this'll be the last
time you'll ever dare
make a fool out of me!
[VAN groans]
[VAN grunting]
I've had it with you!
Really? He's down already?
[FOLKEN] Don't you dare
kill him, Dilandau.
I told you I wanted him alive.
[DILANDAU] Aw, I was just
having a little fun, Folken.
[REEDEN]
Fire, sir!
[ALLEN]
Is there any Melef wreckage?
[REEDEN]
I don't think so, sir.
[ALLEN]
I see.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
[MERLE] They wouldn't
kill him, would they?!
No. They won't do that,
they need him far too much.
As the King of Fanelia,
he's the only one
who knows how to
operate Escaflowne.
[GADDES]
Don't fret, kitten,
we'll get him back here
without a scratch.
We owe those lowlifes
payback for the castle.
We gotta hit 'em hard,
right where it hurts!
They won't see it comin'.
Let's do this!
Ready for orders, Commander.
How many men do we have left?
Including me,
we've got seven fighters.
That won't be
nearly enough men
for a frontal assault against
that floating fortress.
Besides, we still have
to locate them first.
Listen. Hey, Allen?
[ALLEN]
Hm?
I think, maybe.
I have an idea how to find Van.
I'm pretty sure it'll work.
Well, you did predict
the attack on the castle,
but that's not
enough. I'm sorry.
But I swear, that
was no coincidence!
I can see it in my mind!
I mean, ever since I was little,
I've had these hunches,
and they're usually right.
Lately, I can't explain it,
but that power has been
getting stronger, and I want
to put it to good use!
Be that as it may, my dear,
I'd prefer that you leave
this to us knights.
You understand, don't you?
[foot steps]
Hey, wait! If it will
help you can test me!
I'll prove it to you!
[DILANDAU] I've sent out
search and destroy teams.
They can't return
to their homeland.
There's no reason we should
have to keep hiding out here
like cowards anymore.
[FOLKEN] There's no
need to be careless.
We'll wait for your
men to report back.
[DILANDAU] Hm. I don't know
why you're always so cautious.
Uh!
Come on, what are
you worried about?
Now we've got this,
our future is secure.
Let's drag the samurai out
of there and destroy it,
so we can finally
move forward!
[FOLKEN] I'm afraid
I can't allow that.
[DILANDAU]
Why not?
There is much more
to learn about it.
We do not yet understand
its full power.
Or what makes it a credible
threat to our future.
[gasps]
[whimpering]
What?! That jerk!
[FOLKEN] Yes, Fanelia's
brand new monarch.
[TEO] Close one!
Glad they didn't look down.
[PYLE]
Hey. So what's your take?
Think she'll get it
all out of him?
Y'know, his past and stuff?
[REEDEN]
Shh! They're gonna hear you!
[HITOMI]
This is the Fool card.
A life of independence.
Rash actions,
defying common sense.
The essence of your
father's personality
is revealed in this card.
Its shadow haunts and poisons
your heritage, and always has.
A family... divided.
[PYLE]
So, think she right?
[KIO]
How should I know?
It's not like the boss ever
talks anything personal with us.
[HITOMI]
It's a good reading.
His sister's mysterious
disappearance.
His mother's early death.
He blames his father for it all.
Please, what else do you see?
[HITOMI]
What should I do?
He looks pretty upset!
Maybe I should stop.
[HITOMI]
No.
It's important for
him to believe me,
or this won't work.
What is it?
What's wrong?
Uh! Nothing!
[HITOMI]
Come on... spit it out!
[HITOMI] This is Justice.
The judgment card.
According to this,
it's possible you and your
father will be reunited
in the near future.
But, you can't let
go of the past.
You still have a lot
of anger towards him.
And, um, this one.
Th-This card here.
That's enough,
Hitomi. Thank you.
[gasps] Uh, there's
still more, though.
[ALLEN]
I'm convinced.
So now, here's your chance.
It's time to find Van.
Uh!
Okay!
[whistling]
Who are you?!
Why are you whistling
a Fanelian song?
[gasps]
[VAN grunts]
All right, show me the way
back to my Guymelef, now!
[FOLKEN] Hmph. You can
swing that sword around
as much as you want.
It isn't going to
get you anywhere.
There will be no escape
from this floating fortress,
not for you, or Escaflowne.
[gasps]
[growling]
I would rather perish by my own
hand than become your pawn.
[gasps]
[FOLKEN] I wouldn't be so quick
to throw your life away.
You're... my brother.
Will that stupid little toy
really help us find him?
[MERLE]
Shh!
[exhales] Hey, if she says
it'll work, it'll work.
[FOLKEN] It's been a
long time indeed, Van.
Ten years now, is it?
The story always did seem odd.
I never really believed
you ran away from the
Rite of Succession,
I thought the dragon killed you.
I thought you'd
faced it head on,
that you'd battled it
to the bitter end.
It was all a lie!
Why are you with Zaibach?!
How could you destroy Fanelia?!
Are you going to answer?
Wipe that smile off your face.
Look at me!
[gasps]
Van, my brother, the Zaibach
Emperor needs someone like you.
Come with me and we will
both serve Dornkirk.
You and I will help the empire
set the future back on course.
[gasps]
[snoring]
[ALLEN]
Do you want to rest a bit?
No, I'm fine.
I need to keep at it.
Although, I wish we had
something of Van's here.
[MERLE]
We do! Look.
[HITOMI]
Uh.
Okay, now what?
Picture him in your mind,
as clearly as you can.
[HITOMI gasps]
[ALLEN]
Look at that.
It picked out a place where
the wandering earth collects.
What does that mean?
Well, it means Levistones like
the ones we power the ship with.
Bullseye! That's the
perfect hiding place
for a floating fortress!
[ALLEN]
Hitomi!
[MERLE]
Hey, wake up!
[DILANDAU]
Hm. So this is the threat
to the future of the
Zaibach Empire, huh?
Heh. It's just a pile
of old scrap metal.
I can't make any
sense of this.
There must be some trick to it,
Folken got it to open for him.
[REEDEN]
Well, well. We gotcha now!
Floating fortress is spotted!
Right, heat the levistones!
Cut our levitation power and
let's charge the fortress!
[TEO]
Levitation down to 20!
Good! Furl sails, and dive!
[HITOMI, MERLE scream]
[screams]
[ZAIBACH SOLDIERS gasp]
[MOLE MAN grunting]
[HITOMI yelps]
[gasps]
[FOLKEN]
What happened?
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER A] Explosion
in the hangar! Cause unknown!
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER B] We're
under attack! They're on us!
[FOLKEN]
What?
--[ZAIBACH SOLDIERS grunt]
--[ZAIBACH SOLDIER B screams]
Anchor!
We're up again, sir!
Okay, cut the tether!
Raise the propellers!
Aft mooring anchors:
ready... fire!
[ALLEN]
We're boarding, men!
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
[GADDES]
Charge!
[ALL yelling]
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER N]
Boarders!
[ALLEN grunts]
[ZAIBACH SOLDIERS yell]
Here they come...
We're ready for ya!
Yeah!
Some kinda fight
going on out there.
[ORT grunts]
[ARMORED ZAIBACH SOLDIERS groan]
[ORT]
Heh.
Heh, heh. No one'll
miss a sword or two!
Where's Lord Dilandau?
I don't know!
Well we certainly
can't do anything
until we know what
his orders are.
Let's go find him!
[DALLET, SHESTA]
Right!
[ZAIBACH SOLDIERS yell, groan]
[ALLEN]
Escaflowne!
[SHESTA]
Stop there!
[SHESTA grunting]
Easy. You don't want to
lose your head, now.
I hope they're okay.
[DILANDAU yells]
[HITOMI]
Ah!
[MERLE]
Hey, what's wrong?
I saw it!
Saw what?
I have to go!
Go where?
Van is in really big trouble!
[MERLE]
Huh? Hold on!
[rattling]
[groaning]
You're still in one piece.
Allen! You came to rescue me?
[ALLEN] There's no time
to explain. Let's go.
[HITOMI] Looks like five,
maybe six meters across.
[MERLE]
Hitomi! Hitomi!
Don't be stupid!
What do you think you're doing?!
[yelps]
Hang on to that.
I'm gonna jump over
to the other side.
[MERLE shrieks]
I've jumped about
this far once,
five-point-four meters. Yes!
You're out of your mind,
no way you'll clear that!
Please, I'm telling you,
just don't do it!
Can't you see how
far away that is?
If you fall, you're
gonna die for sure!
Even I don't want that!
Are you listening to me?!
Huh?! Ah!
[HITOMI panting]
[MERLE]
Huh? [squeals]
[grunts]
Told ya! [laughs]
Whoa, she's some kind of freak.
[HITOMI] Faster!
I've gotta warn him!
[ZAIBACH SOLDIERS,
CRUSADERS grunting]
[HITOMI panting]
[ALLEN]
Escaflowne's that direction.
I'll stay here and
hold them off.
[VAN]
Got it!
[HITOMI]
There he is!
[FOLKEN]
Van!
[VAN]
Huh?
What, Brother?
His brother? They're related?
[VAN grunts]
Come back here!
Van.
[DILANDAU chuckles]
Van! Behind you!
[VAN gasps]
[VAN grunting]
I should've killed
you the first time,
but better late than never!
I hate your guts!
I loathe you!
You scum! Die, already!
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[DILANDAU screams]
My face, it's bleeding!
So much blood...
[VAN]
Hitomi! This way!
[HITOMI]
Coming!
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER L, ALLEN grunt]
Allen! We have to go!
[ALLEN]
Gaddes! Fall back now!
[GADDES]
Yes, sir!
Okay, men! Operation complete!
[KATZ, TEO]
Yes, sir!
You savage.
Why have you done this
to my beautiful face?
[ZAIBACH SOLDIER B]
Skiff ascending!
They're getting away!
[FOLKEN] Brother, someday you'll
stand by my side, I swear it.
[MERLE]
Oh, King Van!
[BOTH laugh]
[MERLE]
I'm so happy you're safe.
[VAN]
Hey, don't cry.
I was trying to save you
guys, but once again,
you wound up saving me.
We have Hitomi here
to thank for that.
Oh, yeah?
Uh.
[VAN]
Thanks, I guess.
[HITOMI gasps, growls]
[REEDEN]
Hard a-starboard!
[ALLEN] Set course for
Palas, we're going home!
Palas, huh?
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[MILLERNA]
Allen!
[ALLEN]
Princess Millerna!
[MILLERNA chuckles]
Do you want to fight?
Is that it?