[HITOMI]
Was it all just a dream?
Or was it a vision?
That night I watched them
hold each other close
on the roof of Palas' Castle.
I saw there was another side
to Allen that I didn't know.
Then Van and I flew away,
leaving them behind.
I know this is goodbye, Allen.
Yet, I can't help but...
[OPERATOR A] Once you have
completed dialing the number,
please press the pound key
to begin your message.
[phone rings]
Amano? You're here?
[ringing continues]
[ALLEN] I threw away
everything I had to come here.
What do you mean?
[ALLEN]
My country... The war...
My duties as a knight...
I realized none of it
mattered without you.
Allen...
Sweetheart! Were
you waiting long?
Aah! Millerna!
[HITOMI]
But... You said...
[gasps]
[HITOMI screams]
[HITOMI]
Allen, please!
Help me!
[HITOMI groans]
[HITOMI gasps]
Sorry, I fell asleep.
[VAN]
Don't worry about it.
If you're tired, sleep.
[HITOMI]
No, I'm okay.
--[MERLE laughs]
--[HITOMI gasps]
"Allen, please! Save me!"
Really?
--You're still stuck on him?
--[HITOMI gasps]
Wait! I didn't say that, did I?
You would think you'd
take this seriously!
We barely made it
out of there alive,
and your head's in the clouds!
I mean, have you
already forgotten
that you were almost sold
off to that Meiden guy?
No! I remember!
It's understandable; we wouldn't
be here if it weren't for Allen.
--[MERLE] Here.
--[HITOMI screams]
Don't worry, they're cooked.
Though, really, I like them raw.
Nah. They're way
better this way.
[HITOMI groans]
[MERLE]
Have you tried these things?
They're good!
Hey! Those were the
snacks from my bag!
What about the rest
of this stuff?
[sniffs]
Geez, you took my lipstick?
And my watch, too?
Give me back my things!
This looks tasty!
That's a pager, moron!
--As in "not edible"!
--[MERLE growling]
[HITOMI yelps]
[MERLE grunting]
You get back down
here! Cat burglar!
[MERLE laughs]
[HITOMI]
Ugh! You're such a stupid brat!
Hey, Van?
[HITOMI] Is it just me,
or do these look similar?
[VAN]
Yeah, I guess they kinda do.
Where'd you get that?
[HITOMI]
From my grandmother.
[VAN]
It was a gift?
[HITOMI]
Yeah.
She gave it to me
when I was little.
It's kind of like an heirloom.
But you have more
family, don't you?
Yup.
I have my mom and dad.
And also a little brother.
Oh, yeah? That sounds nice.
[HITOMI]
It's nice,
but my brother and I
fight all the time.
He's always mouthing off,
which drives me completely nuts.
And then, of course, I'm the
only one who gets yelled at.
"Hitomi! You're his big sister!
Hitomi! You're in high
school now, so grow up.
Hitomi! You should
act like a girl!"
That kind of thing.
I get so sick of it.
Worst of all, my dad just
sits there the whole time
laughing at me.
[HITOMI]
I wonder how they're doing.
I miss them... a lot.
I... I know how you feel.
My folks passed away.
It happened when I was little.
Now Fanelia's burned down,
and Balgus is gone.
I don't have much
family left anymore.
It's basically just her.
I'm sorry.
But what about... There was
that guy you called "brother."
--[VAN] He is not my brother!
--[HITOMI gasps]
[VAN]
His name... is Folken.
And he's a traitor!
[HITOMI gasps]
[VAN] Ten years ago, he was
sent off to fight a dragon.
That's part of the rite
to become king in Fanelia.
But he ran away and
joined Zaibach instead!
That bastard has even
tried to kill me!
Sorry, that just slipped out.
No, I'm sorry.
So what do you think
you're gonna do now?
If I've learned one
thing through all this,
it's how much I
still have to grow.
And I'll start with the sword.
I'm gonna train and get better.
What about you?
What will you do?
H-Honestly, I don't know.
There's no way I can go
back to Allen's country
after what's happened.
[VAN]
Well, Zaibach is hot on my tail,
but if you've got nothing better
to do, you could come with us.
[HITOMI]
A-Are you sure?
[VAN]
Yeah.
You never know, there's a chance
I might need your help someday.
Besides, I want
to help you, too.
I'm gonna find a way
to send you back home.
Promise.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
They're preparing
for an invasion.
[MILLERNA] Father, what
is the meaning of this?!
Why have you thrown
Allen in the dungeon?!
Because there's no
telling what trouble
he would get into otherwise.
Think of it as a necessary
precaution, my dear.
And just what do you
think he's capable of?
[KING ASTON] Quite a bit,
considering he aided
in Escaflowne's escape.
And he's made it perfectly clear
he wishes to defy Zaibach.
It's madness!
You're the only one
who's gone mad, Father!
How could you let their fleet
within our country's borders?!
Zaibach doesn't
consider us allies.
We're more like lackeys!
This wouldn't have happened
if Marlene were alive.
If she were here...
I swear, I never would
have allowed them passage.
[MILLERNA]
If Marlene were alive?
Don't tell me.
Zaibach is massing their forces
to attack the Duchy of Freid?
[KING ASTON]
I have heard enough.
You should be concerned
with the future of
your own country,
not others'.
What have you done?
[MESSENGER A]
Message from General Adelphos.
"Energists are in short supply.
Accelerate the excavation
and transport timetable."
End message.
Uh... [groans]
Does he even know what
he's asking of me?
Generals, ugh.
They have no idea what it's like
to be out in the field
doing actual work.
Ugh... It's just a dragon.
The Dragons' Graveyard!
That reading you did was
supposed to lead to safety!
But this place is
crawling with bad guys!
I'm sure the cards said
this was a good direction.
Were they wrong?
[VAN]
Nah, not at all.
This is right where
we want to be!
[HITOMI]
Huh?
I'm taking us closer!
[GUARD A]
Who's there?
--Princess Millerna?
--[ALLEN] Huh?
[GUARD A] M'lady, this
is no place for you.
It's all right my father has
given me permission
to come down here.
[GUARD A] That's the first
I've heard about it.
[MILLERNA]
Oh!
[yelps]
--[GUARD A] A-Are you all right?
--[MILLERNA] Oh, it hurts!
Is there anything I can do?
[MILLERNA]
I don't know; it feels broken.
Do you think you could
take a look at it?
--[GUARD A] Uh...
--[MILLERNA] Please?
Hey, Commander.
[ALLEN]
Gaddes!
[MILLERNA]
Hurry!
--Let's go!
--Right!
[HITOMI]
What's the Dragons' Graveyard?
[MERLE]
Hm?
What it sounds like:
where dragons go to die.
[HITOMI] Huh? So what
are they digging for?
[MERLE] They're digging up the
fossils to take their Energists.
I'm counting six Guymelefs.
[HITOMI] Okay, and what do
they do with the Energists
once they've got them?
[MERLE]
Hm? Oh.
Well, they, uh...
[VAN] Use them as power
sources for their Guymelefs.
[MERLE laughs]
That's right!
What he said.
Hold on, if that's the case...
[VAN]
That's right.
Escaflowne is powered
by an Energist, too.
Although, technically these
are called Drag-Energists
because of where they come from.
And what do they do exactly?
[VAN] The Drag-Energists
they take from here
will power their
Guymelefs and Leviships.
Mining these Dragon Graveyards
is a very serious business.
In a war, the side with the
most Energists will win.
Simple as that.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
Okay, the two of you stay here.
What? Why?
I refuse to let
Zaibach take them.
[ALLEN] The empire's going to
attack the Duchy of Freid?
Are you sure?
[MILLERNA] I am, and my father
will do nothing as Prince Chid,
his own grandson, dies!
Unbelievable.
Yes, and you're the only one who
stands a chance at stopping it.
But I'm not going to
let you do it alone.
[TEO]
When's the boss gonna get here?
They're gonna find us
if we stay much longer.
[REEDEN gasps]
Here he comes!
[GADDES]
Whoa!
All right! This is our stop!
[ALLEN grunts]
[MILLERNA gasps]
Eries!
Listen, I promise I won't tell
father about this, Millerna.
But you have to come back
to the castle with me.
Tell him whatever you
like I'm not going back.
I'm leaving today!
My mind is made up!
I'm going with Allen
and you can't stop me!
[yelps, gasps]
Allen!
Stop! What are you doing?
Put me down!
I'm not going back;
I want to stay with you!
Tell me.
What is the meaning--
Take care, Princess.
And goodbye.
--[whip cracks]
--[horse neighs]
[MILLERNA gasps]
Allen!
[GADDES]
Uh?
Oh, damnit!
Set sail! It's time to go!
Commander!
I'll be off then.
Thank you.
Allen...
I'll find you.
I'm not going to give up.
[COMMANDER A] I don't care! Just
do something about it already!
--And you, get back to work!
--[MINER A groans]
Ugh... Another dragon.
[gasps]
Wait!
A Guymelef?!
It's an enemy attack!
Garrisons, move out!
[VAN growls]
[VAN] That looks like
their storehouse.
If I can take that out...
[VAN grunts]
[MINERS scream]
That must be the "Escaflowne"
Dilandau's been ranting about.
Lucky me!
[HITOMI]
You think he'll be okay?
[MERLE]
I sure hope so...
[BOTH]
Huh?
[MERLE chuckles]
[SOLDIER A]
Uh...
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH scream]
[HITOMI]
No!
[SOLDIER A]
Hold it!
--[HITOMI] Someone help!
--[SOLDIER A groans]
[HITOMI]
Merle!
[growls]
You coward!
[MINERS screaming]
[VAN yells]
[COMMANDER A]
That's quite enough.
What?!
Sorry...
[COMMANDER A] Now, come on
out of there, nice and slow.
[chuckles]
--[whip cracks]
--Knock it off!
--Just leave him alone!
[whipping continues]
What... should I do...?
No... Van...
I take it yours is the "dragon"
Emperor Dornkirk is looking for.
Well? Come on, talk to me.
[VAN groans]
What is it you're after?
And how exactly did
you find this place?
Huh?
[sighs, chuckles]
[VAN groans]
All right, if you don't
want to talk to me,
I'll find someone else who does.
Ha, ha, hello, young lady,
I would like to introduce
you to my friend.
This is Nina.
She's so poisonous
that one bite will kill, ha, ha!
But don't worry about that.
She only does what
I tell her to do.
Go on, Nina.
Say "hello" to your new friend.
[HITOMI gasps]
[HITOMI whimpers]
Hey! Stop that!
What are you doing?!
Leave Hitomi alone!
[VAN]
Get it off! Please stop!
Don't hurt her!
That's it, Nina. Why not
give her a little kiss?
[HITOMI whimpering]
And put some love into it.
[ringing]
--[ringing continues]
--[COMMANDER A, HITOMI gasps]
--What the... hell?
--[ringing continues]
--Hey, what's that?
[MERLE]
Ah! Whoops!
Uh... Ah!
Quiet you!
Ah, it stopped.
What the hell was that?
Maybe a spy whistle?
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[VAN grunts]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[SOLDIERS groan]
[MESSENGER A yells]
Run, Van!
[HITOMI]
Van, that's enough!
--You've won!
--[COMMANDER A] You bastard!
[COMMANDER A yelps, screams]
[groans]
You've gotta hide!
There are more soldiers!
Now it's time to take
out that storehouse.
[SOLDIER G]
He's heading for our stock!
[SOLDIER H]
Hurry!
Be careful, King Van.
[HITOMI gasps]
My Energist is
reacting to something.
[gasps]
It's not just mine.
They're resonating!
[MINERS screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH grunting]
[HITOMI screams]
[VAN]
No!
[HITOMI yelps]
[screams]
Hitomi!
[HITOMI screaming]
[HITOMI gasps]
[HITOMI]
The angel... It's you...
[ringing]
--[ringing]
--[HITOMI groans]
[ringing continues]
[STUDENT A]
C'mon, Amano!
The banquet's about to start!
Okay!
[HITOMI sobs]
Amano...
I am right here...
It's true...
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
If you don't mind me saying,
they're very beautiful,
your wings.
Maybe I should disobey orders.
Our meeting was fated long ago.