[REEDEN] Man, it seems like
they've been in there forever.
[KIO]
Yeah, I know.
He'll be okay, though.
The boss is tough.
He ain't dyin' anytime soon.
You're right. He ain't.
Come on, Allen.
Allen's operation
went successfully.
So you're saying
that he's all right?
[MILLERNA]
Yes,
but he's still unconscious
from the anesthetic.
[HITOMI]
Millerna!
[VAN]
We're very lucky
Princess Millerna
was here to help.
[GADDES]
Yeah,
and her pressence guarantees
us a ticket into Freid.
[VAN]
How do you mean?
[GADDES] Because she has
family connections there.
Her older sister, Marlene,
was once married to its ruler.
[VAN]
Princess Marlene?
[GADDES] Yeah, she was the
eldest princess of Asturia.
She got sick and
died three years ago.
But... she left a
young son behind.
[VAN] The Prince of
the Duchy of Freid.
[VORIS] Announcing the arrival
of the third princess
of the Kingdom of Asturia,
Princess Millerna Sara Aston.
[CHID] You must be tired
from your long journey.
My father, the duke,
is on an inspection tour
of the realm right now,
so I welcome you in his place.
Prince Chid? I simply
can't believe my eyes.
Yes. It's me, Aunt Millerna.
I'm so glad you're here.
You've grown so much
since I saw you last.
I almost didn't recognize you.
You were still little
more than a baby then.
So small I could
hold you in my arms.
[CHID]
Aunt Millerna?
I heard a rumor that a knight
accompanied you on your
journey: Allen Schezar?
Is that him just behind you?
Before she died,
mother told me many
exciting stories about him.
She said that Allen Schezar,
the greatest swordsman on Gaea,
called Asturia his home.
"The invincible knight."
"The gallant Guymelef pilot."
I always hoped to meet him.
[VORIS]
Your Highness.
If I may clarify for you,
this is his royal majesty,
Van Fanel, of the
Kingdom of Fanelia.
I was mistaken. I'm sorry.
Then let me please welcome you
to Freid, Van of Fanelia.
I want you to think of
my country as your own.
It's important that you feel
at home here, so please enjoy.
Thank you. I'm grateful
to have Freid's friendship.
It means a great deal.
So where is Allen Schezar
now, Aunt Millerna?
[DOCTOR A] I believe he's out
of danger. His pulse is steady.
He should regain
consciousness momentarily.
[MILLERNA]
Thank you.
[CHID] I can't believe Allen
Schezar could ever be defeated.
I should've known better.
Invincible knights only exist
in stories. They're not real.
I think Mother just wanted
to make me feel better
by telling me fairy tales,
because she didn't
wanna disappoint me.
You're awake!
[CREW chattering]
[ALLEN]
Hitomi. And Princess Millerna?
Oh, Allen.
I'd like you to meet Chid, the
Prince of the Duchy of Freid.
It's you.
[ALLEN] That ring. If you
have it, then that means...
Allen, It's such an
honor to meet you.
Are you feeling better now?
[ALLEN groaning]
Your Highness,
Zaibach is planning
an immediate attack
on your country.
Please, grant me one favor.
I must speak with the duke.
There is little
time to prepare.
You're all in grave danger!
[ALLEN coughing]
[HITOMI]
Take it easy.
[VAN]
Prince Chid,
Allen travelled
here to warn you,
and he put both his honor and
life at great risk to do it.
What your mother told
you was no fairy tale.
He really is the gallant
knight she said he was.
Thank you.
[VORIS] But we've had
no conflict with Zaibach.
Why would they
want to attack us?
[VAN] You're detaining
one of their soldiers.
If you interrogate him,
he'll probably confess.
Good, because we're already
making arrangements for that.
Oh, are you?
As you know, the duke is away,
so we must question
the prisoner.
And we must be
careful about it.
He's a slippery little eel.
[FOLKEN]
The dragon has fled to Freid.
[DILANDAU]
Hmph. What of it?
[FOLKEN]
Along with their prisoner.
[DILANDAU]
Don't worry about it.
Are you forgetting?
Miguel is one of my men.
He'd sooner die than
give anything away.
[FOLKEN]
That may be.
But Freid has the advantage
of Plaktu, you see.
[DILANDAU]
Who's that?
He is a high priest.
A true master of
hypnotic suggestion.
He can use his techniques
to extract information
from the furthest
recesses of the mind.
It's been confirmed
that he's already on
his way to Godashim.
And you tell me this now?!
We have to kill him before
he reaches the castle.
He'll discover our plans!
[FOLKEN]
Zongi.
[ZONGI]
Yes, Lord.
[DILANDAU]
Huh? What--?
Who said that?
[DILANDAU]
What's that horrible smell?
You summoned a Doppelganger?
[FOLKEN] Zongi, I have
a special task for you.
I am ready.
Tell me your wish, master, for
I wait on you, and you alone.
[MILLERNA]
Hitomi?
[HITOMI]
Oh, hi, Millerna.
Here's this. I thought you'd
like to have it with you.
That's my duffel bag.
[HITOMI] Thanks,
that's very nice of you.
But I'm surprised you
brought it, though.
How'd you know
you'd run into me?
[MILLERNA]
What can I say?
I had a feeling I'd be seeing
you again someday, I suppose.
It seems we'll be spending
quite a bit of time together.
We might as well
try to be friends.
Maybe it was
women's intuition.
[DILANDAU]
Their ship is in range.
One single shot, and I could
bring it down in flames.
[ZONGI] Lord Dilandau,
please use discretion.
[DILANDAU]
Mind your own business.
Using a Doppelganger.
That is so cheap.
Folken, this idea of
yours had better work.
[ALLEN]
Princess.
It was very reckless of you
to follow me like that.
[MILLERNA]
I had to.
I know you better
than you think I do.
You had another reason
for leaving Asturia
besides wanting to
save Freid, am I right?
You were worried that Zaibach
would eventually attack
Asturia as well,
and you wouldn't stand for that.
I know my father will come to
accept that choice someday.
He'll recognize that you love
Asturia more than anyone else.
[HITOMI]
Van, it's the crack of dawn.
What'd you wake me up
for at this crazy hour?
And Merle?
Great. Why are you here, too?
[MERLE] I don't like the idea of
you being alone with King Van.
[HITOMI]
Gimme a break.
[VAN] You're the only one
so far who's been able to spot
those invisible Guymelefs.
I'll never be able to see
them without that power--
Your power, I mean.
I'm gonna need it if
I'm going to fight them.
So how do you do it?
How can you possibly
see an invisible enemy?
Well, I...
[PLAKTU]
An assassin.
You're awfully clever
entering this room
without my noticing you.
Now, get out!
[PLAKTU choking]
[ZONGI]
Yes. Excellent.
This body will work perfectly.
[HITOMI]
Picture what you're looking for
in your mind very clearly.
That's all there is to it.
When you sense what
you want to find,
the pendant will
follow your thought,
and it'll swing
in that direction.
With practice,
you can do it by just picturing
the pendant in your mind.
Okay, what should I look for?
Well, let's see.
Me, me, me.
Look for me, King Van!
I know you can find me!
All right, Merle it is.
What do you suppose
they're doing?
I don't know.
King Van is gonna find me
here for sure, any second!
[HITOMI]
Keep your eyes closed
and think hard about
what she looks like.
Clear a space in your mind,
and concentrate on her.
That's great,
now focus on her image.
Take all the time you need to.
Picture her long, crazy tail.
Also,
those big pointy ears,
that wild, curly hair.
Imagine those giant eyes,
that obnoxious personality.
That big, loud mouth of hers.
I'm gonna turn her skinny legs
into two scratching posts!
I give up. It isn't working.
[HITOMI]
I'm not letting you quit yet.
Anyone starting out
has some trouble,
but with a little practice,
it gets much easier.
Here, watch me.
There!
[MERLE yelps]
Yeah, right. Like I'm
gonna admit she found me.
[VAN]
Merle.
[squeals]
[MERLE] Hey, King Van!
You found me! Yay!
[VAN]
Uhh...
[HITOMI]
Prince Chid.
Well done! That was
just amazing, Hitomi!
I'm impressed!
How'd you do that?
[HITOMI]
Oh, uh, no big deal.
[MERLE]
No, Your Highness!
Don't you listen
to a word she says.
She's nothing but
a cheap fortune-teller.
In fact, I think it's creepy
how she goes snooping
into everyone's past and
future and stuff! Ooo!
Okay, knock it off, Merle!
[CHID]
Is that true?
Do you honestly know
how to tell the future?
I'm not sure how to explain it.
When I do readings, I see things
in my mind at the same time.
That's incredible.
Not even Plaktu can do that,
and he can do almost anything.
[HITOMI]
Oh?
Hey, Hitomi, do you think maybe
you'd be able to predict
my future for me?
Well, uh... I don't know.
Please, it would mean so much.
Then, I would be happy to.
[MESSENGER A]
Voris!
We've just received notice that
Plaktu has arrived at the port.
[VORIS]
Ah, excellent.
Your Highness,
Shall we proceed then?
[CHID]
Of course.
[CHID] Thank you for coming.
We're counting on your skills.
Leave everything to me.
[ZONGI]
Voris,
I must insist on having a few
moments alone with the prisoner.
[VORIS]
Uh. But why?
[ZONGI]
You must be Miguel.
Hold on. How do
you know my name?
[gasps]
Folken must've sent you.
[MILLERNA]
I brought you some dinner.
You have to eat if you want
to get your strength back.
[ALLEN]
Princess Millerna.
Yes, Allen?
Would you please ask Hitomi
if she'll come up here?
What do you mean,
"a strange woman"?
You heard me.
My Guymelef was invisible,
but she pointed straight at me
as though she could see it.
[ZONGI]
Hmm...
Interesting.
Not to worry, I'll ensure
she's taken care of.
Are you gonna help me
get outta here now?
[ZONGI]
No.
I have a special job
for you to do.
[ZONGI]
Voris.
Uh. I... What just happened?
The prisoner is
ready for you now.
[VORIS]
Uh. Ah.
[CHID]
Plaktu.
[VORIS]
Huh? Your Highness.
I would like to observe
the interrogation.
[ZONGI]
He's already under hypnosis.
You may make your inquiries.
Very well.
Now then, young Zaibach.
I would like to know your name.
My name's Miguel.
Miguel Lavariel, to be exact.
And why were you sneaking
around on our border?
I was tracking
down a lone rebel.
Asturia requested me to do it.
A rebel, eh?
And who might that be?
A clever knight. Who plotted
to overthrow Asturia.
With the help of Fanelia's king.
His name... is Allen Schezar.
You can't mean that.
No. I don't believe it.
You're lying! I'll skin
you like a snake!
I'm telling you the truth.
[VORIS]
Then tell me this,
why did Allen
turn you over to us?
He said if I abetted his plan,
then he'd spare my life.
[VORIS]
What?
[MIGUEL]
He claimed the deception
would cause a rift
between Asturia and Freid.
Then, he would take
advantage of that rift
in order to become
the king of Asturia.
He what? No. No, you're wrong!
[CHID]
It's a lie.
There's no way this
is true. It can't be.
It's a lie!
Are you serious?
Yes, I want a reading
for the Zaibach soldier
we've taken prisoner.
[MILLERNA]
Truly? You believe all that?
Please.
Okay, I'll do it.
Emergency stations! Dispatch
the entire Royal Guard!
And watch the prisoner.
[GUARDS]
Yes, sir!
[HITOMI]
Danger. Conflict.
This suggests tension.
And this is the
Warrior of Dragons.
It's hard to imagine
that's anyone but Van.
Oh, please.
Keep going.
[HITOMI]
World. Death.
A great power is guiding
everything towards an end,
so that it can all be reborn.
The end of everything. So
that's what Zaibach is after.
Let's read the prisoner.
The spare card?
I always take that one out
before I start, though.
I'm confused. It's blank.
[gasps] Not that!
[ARMORY GUARD]
Hm? Huh?
[MIGUEL]
Hello, girl. Ready to play?
Where are you going?
What's this about?
Well, just what is
the meaning of this?
Your Highness.
How could you?
I thought you were true
knight, but you betrayed us!
What're you saying?
That makes no sense.
Prince Chid.
Voris, the prisoner
has managed to escaped!
[VORIS]
What's that?
That's impossible!
The cards predicted this.
[GUARDS whispering]
Great, she's working. Looks
like her stealth cloak is, too.
[ZONGI]
What is that fool doing?
There's no sense to this.
He should make his escape.
What?
There! The Zaibach Guymelef!
No good, I'm too
low on pressure!
Keep coming.
It's gone!
You're not getting
away from me again!
What? How could
it just disappear?
[GUARD A]
Send out the Melef unit!
Where are you?
You won't get far.
Got'cha now, Van.
Without that girl's help,
he's unable to see anything
through this stealth cloak.
[VAN]
Where is he?
Where is that coward?
I may as well try.
What is he doing in there?
It doesn't matter.
If I kill him, then I can stay
in Lord Dilandau good graces
and he won't punish me
for getting captured.
[VAN]
Focus.
Concentrate on what
you're looking for.
[HITOMI]
If you focus hard enough,
you'll be able to see it.
[MIGUEL] If I pour all of my
liquid metal into one claw,
it ought to be enough.
I can take him out for good.
[VAN]
Please. I have to find it.
Where's the Zaibach Guymelef?
There!
Now die!
Oh, no. He saw me!
[yelling]
I've got you.
Hey! What're you doing?
They're... They're after me?
[GUARDS shouting]
[MIGUEL] I can't run.
I'm hurt too bad.
What now?
[ZONGI]
My apologies,
but my true identity needs
to remain entirely secret.
The power to see the unseen.
I must investigate.
Your Highness, this must
be some sort of mistake!
I promise, we're on your side!
Please, Prince Chid.
I've always respected you
because of everything
my mother said.
Sadly, the reality is different.
I don't know what to think.
Was she telling me the
truth about you, Allen,
or did she make it all up?
[ALLEN]
Prince Chid.
Can you tell me something?
Have you ever believed in
someone with your whole heart?
Just doing that is a kind
of bravery, you know.
Sometimes it can take even more
courage to believe in somebody
than to fight them.
Highness,
do you think that is a kind of
courage you're capable of?
[HITOMI] In that moment,
I realized something.
There was a bond between
Allen and Prince Chid.
A bond that seemed to run
very strong and very deep.
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
You've gotten in my way
for the very last time!
[PRISON GUARD]
I don't know how it happened,
but your friend is dead!