Allen, I...
Good, you're awake.
[gasps]
Is that you, Amano? How?
[AMANO] Whoa, easy,
you need your rest.
[HITOMI]
Am I, dreaming?
[HITOMI] Or is this real?
Am I back home?
[STUDENT C sighs]
[STUDENT B]
Man, I'm thirsty.
[STUDENT D] Me too.
Wanna go out for a bit?
[STUDENT A] You gonna
get tea with us, Yukari?
Sorry, can't. I've still got
some work to finish up here.
I'll go home with Hitomi.
[STUDENT A] Don't you think
you should leave them alone?
[STUDENT D]
Yeah, give 'em some space!
[STUDENTS giggle]
Or, they can deal with it!
[STUDENT A]
Wow. That is coldblooded.
--[STUDENT B laughs]
--[STUDENT C] Ready?
[STUDENT D]
Later!
--See you tomorrow, Yukari.
--[STUDENT B] Bye!
Have fun, you guys!
[door clatters]
[AMANO] So it was a
planet called "Gaea",
and you could see the Earth
and the moon in the sky?
And this Escaflowne thing.
Hmph. I had no idea that
you were such a romantic.
[gasps]
To have such a fantastic dream.
Think so?
[AMANO]
Hm.
[gasps]
Hey, that's a cool pendant.
Oh. Thanks. You like it?
It's a good luck charm.
I got it from my grandmother.
It's really neat.
When you swing it like this,
it acts like a pendulum clock,
completing one cycle a second,
never slowing down.
[gasps]
Think I could give it a try?
[HITOMI]
Wait a minute. I think...
...I know what's
about to happen.
[HITOMI] He's going to
test the pendant's swing
against the clock.
That's one...
Two. Three. Four.
Five. Six. Sev--
Seven.
[BOTH]
Eight. Nine. Ten.
And eleven. And twelve.
And thirteen. Fourteen.
[HITOMI]
Here it comes.
[AMANO]
Kanzaki.
I wanted to tell you.
[HITOMI]
Then next he says.
You see, I...
[HITOMI gasps]
[door clatters]
I brought you--
[gasps]
[YUKARI sighs]
[HITOMI] Yukari! Come on,
say something already!
You can't ignore
me forever, you know.
[YUKARI] I can let this
slide for a rice cake.
[gasps]
[YUKARI] And some cheesecake,
and bean-jam pancake,
and some peppermint
ice cream. You know what,
let's just say a different
dessert every day for a month.
I think that'll do it.
[giggles]
[HITOMI]
It's all the same.
This is exactly what happened
the day before I went to Gaea.
[YUKARI]
So, anyway.
Did you hear about that
new place "Shonan Dock"?
Akane was telling me their rice
with hashed meat was
absolutely awesome!
Let's go sometime.
Hey, are you okay?
[HITOMI]
Huh?
You're not looking so good.
Uh... Yeah! I feel fine!
[YUKARI]
Don't tell me... you know.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
Eh. Oh, sorry.
Forget I said anything.
Come on. Let's go.
[HITOMI] Wait a second.
It can't be that Yukari...
[YUKARI]
Hitomi?
[HITOMI]
Yeah?
[YUKARI] Have you ever done
a reading for you and Amano?
[HITOMI]
Never.
[YUKARI]
Why not?
[HITOMI] Well. What if it told
me things wouldn't work out?
[YUKARI]
Oh.
Hey, you seem upset
about something.
[YUKARI]
It's just that.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
If you really like him...
...Then you should tell him how
you feel before it's too late.
Maybe.
Not "maybe". You have to.
The thing is, I overheard
some other students
talking about Amano before.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
But I think he's moving
out of the country.
His father's job is taking
them to England or something.
You're my best friend in
the whole world, Hitomi.
And that's why...
...If you feel that
strongly about him,
I think you should tell him.
See what he says.
I know you.
You'll regret it if you don't.
[HITOMI]
Yukari. You love Amano so much.
What do I do?
[HITOMI gasps]
[MILLERNA]
Hitomi's disappeared?
[DRYDEN]
But how's that even possible?
Really, what the hell's
going on around here?
[MILLERNA] This must be
the work of Zaibach.
[FOLKEN] They aren't
the ones responsible.
[ALL gasp]
[FOLKEN] The power of
Dornkirk's science may be vast,
But it is incapable of producing
such a pillar of light.
It wasn't him.
Then where could Hitomi be?
She went back home.
[All gasp]
After everything
that's happened,
she wanted to return
to the Mystic Moon.
That's where...
But, I guess her being gone
is a good thing for us, right?
We don't have to
worry about Zaibach
using their Fate
Alteration Machine now.
[door slams]
[GADDES] Commander!
The Zaibach army's here!
They've set up a perimeter
around our borders!
[SORCERER B]
We're sorry, sir.
We can't detect
the girl's signal.
[DORNKIRK]
The unknown element.
Why must I always be denied
the realization of my dreams?
[HITOMI'S MOM]
Hitomi? Where are you?
The bath's ready! Hitomi?
I didn't know...
...you've loved Amano
this entire time.
And I never realized it.
All this time.
[HITOMI] And I wasn't
really serious about him.
[gasps]
[ALLEN]
Father. I wanted to protect her.
I was ready to give
my life over to Hitomi.
But now, I'm not
so certain anymore.
It's strange.
It's not that I don't miss her,
but my heart is calm.
And although she's
left a void here,
I'm happy she was finally
able to return to her home.
If I accept her
absence so easily,
I wonder what that
means about my feelings,
and how genuine all the
things I told her really were.
Honestly, I am starting
to believe that I just saw
a lot of our long
lost Celena in Hitomi.
You understand.
[ALLEN]
Huh?
I don't believe it.
[ALLEN]
Celena!
Of all the cards, why this one?
[gasps]
Escaflowne, but...?
Why?
I don't want to go back
to Gaea ever again.
I refuse to.
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Van...
[MERLE]
King Van?
[VAN]
Uh.
What's up, Merle?
Are you okay? You haven't
been acting like yourself.
Is there anything
I can get you?
Thanks, but I'm fine.
You're thinking about her.
Even though she's gone.
[gasps]
That isn't true.
Yes, it is!
[MERLE]
You can't lie to me.
I've been by your side
ever since we were little.
I know you better
than anyone else.
No point denying it.
You can't stop
thinking about Hitomi.
[MERLE]
And I know why.
It's 'cause you love her.
[gasps]
[MERLE] I guess stuff like
that is always more obvious
to those not involved, so it
makes sense you didn't realize.
But I could tell from
the very beginning
how you felt about her.
And I think you need to
remember what she always said.
About the power of our feelings.
I'm sure that yours
can reach her.
If you want them to.
[MERLE]
You just have to try.
[ERIES] And you're
sure that she's Celena?
[ALLEN]
Yes. It's been ten years.
But I know.
I'd recognize her anywhere.
But she doesn't
remember anything.
Not a single detail
from that entire time.
[ERIES]
Amnesia?
Princess Eries?
I must ask you to
watch over my sister.
While I'm away fighting.
Will you do this?
There's no one else I can trust.
Ahh...
[CELENA gasps]
[ERIES]
It shall be done.
How could I refuse
a Knight Caeli?
I'll take her to the palace,
and keep her safe by my side.
[CELENA screams]
What's wrong?
[CELENA, DILANDAU groan]
Are you alright, Celena?
Celena?
[gasps]
[DILANDAU]
Who's that? And what...
...and what the hell
am I even doing here?
[screams]
Tell me, are you a Doppelganger?
[DILANDAU]
Jajuka! Help me!
Where are you?!
What?
Stay back, Princess!
[JAJUKA]
Lord Dilandau!
[sighs]
Jajuka!
[grunts]
Dilandau?
No, wait! Stop!
[FOLKEN]
Dilandau...
I don't know that much.
The details of his past are
a complete mystery to me.
However, If I had to speculate,
I would guess the Sorcerers
had a hand in his origin.
What Sorcerers?
That's the term they use to
refer to the Zaibach scientists.
They're incredibly powerful
and answer only to Dornkirk.
According to rumor,
they performed experiments
on live subjects to learn
how to manipulate fate.
And they acquired those test
subjects by kidnapping children.
Human experiments?!
[BOTH gasp]
[ALLEN]
They did that... To Celena?
[TEACHER] I'm sure
you've all heard the story
of how Isaac Newton discovered
universal gravitations
by witnessing an apple
fall from a tree?
What you probably don't know,
is that Newton
also had interests
in alchemy and other
magical subjects as well.
Quite a surprise.
[gasps]
He's calling.
Lord Dornkirk, sir,
preparations have
been completed.
By channeling the
gravity between
the girl and the dragon,
We believe it will be
possible to generate
elemental fate particles.
[DORNKIRK]
Yes. Gravity is indeed crucial.
It is that ever-constant
force that shall summon
the girl to Gaea once again.
[YUKARI]
Hitomi, you've gotta hurry!
Amano's gonna leave soon.
You'll miss him!
Let's go!
I'm sorry, Yukari.
Uh-uh...
I didn't even
realize it until now.
You're my best friend!
How could I not have noticed it?
Sorry. I don't have much time.
I have to see him again.
And that means I have to leave.
So, for now. Goodbye.
What was that?
Good luck, King Van.
[SORCERER D] Elemental fate
particles at critical.
Now activating.
[VAN]
Hitomi. I want to see you.
Kanzaki! Are you ready for this?
Yes! I'm ready anytime you are.
[gasps]
Yukari.
Ready!
Just focus everything
you've got.
Go!
[SORCERERS shout]
Ahh!
Almost there. Come on.
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Huh?!
[HITOMI gasps]
Here!
[HITOMI]
Van!
Hitomi? Don't leave me again.
[HITOMI]
I won't.
[AMANO]
Kanzaki! Don't go!
[sighs]
We're back.
We made it to Gaea.
This can't be.
[HITOMI] And just
like that, I've returned.
This is Gaea. A world at war.
[NARRATOR]
Escaflowne.
[yells]
Come, Folken!
Step forward and finish what
you've started, for a change!
[VAN]
Brother!