Welcome! It's been a while, hasn't it?
What do you say...
A toast...
to my latest venture, Café Zero Two!
Salue!
Who would've thought Tamaki had such a flair for business?
It's not that impressive given the name he settled on.
That's the truth.
Now, now. What's all the fuss about, sweetheart?
Everything okay?
There's a changing station upstairs, if you need.
Thanks. We're fine.
Someone's just a little cranky, is all. Yeah.
Ah. I see.
Ohgi!
Yes?
Tell me, why you aren't you still Prime Minister?
That natural apathy catch up with you?
I wouldn't call him apathetic.
He just wasn't cut out for it, y'know?
Bein' one of the brass takes brass!
Not his area of expertise.
It's so strange seeing them like this.
Ah, the spoils of peace.
Refreshing having all of us together like this, no?
Never thought I'd live to see the day.
Year two of the Kowa Era.
Approximately one year since the death
of Emperor Lelouch at the hands of Zero.
Owing to the newly reorganized Federation of Nations,
the world celebrates an unprecedented time of peace.
A time history will remember as the Miraculous Tomorrow
when the threat of war and terrorist
insurgency all but disappeared.
And yet, simmering beneath the surface,
conflict continues to lurk in the hearts of mankind.
The Miraculous Tomorrow will inevitably pass.
Very well, then.
I'll consult with the legislator to ascertain
if the refugees can be taken in
by the Principality of Britannia.
That said, I ask you to bear in mind,
at present my authority is limited.
Hm?
...I'll try to accommodate them as...
It's me.
Knightmare Frames approaching from the west.
Who are they attached to?
Terrorists!
Get the honorary consultant inside! Now!
Heh.
Wait! It's not armed!
This unit's strictly ceremonial!
The float system's disconnected!
It's the only one available. I'll make do!
What's going on?
This is a demilitarized zone!
Take cover!
Just like that, a full year of peace broken.
Lelouch, your legacy is tarnished.
Hm?
Low visibility, but I can still take 'em!
He's gifted. Just as my sister's prophecies foretold.
Zero! There's another unit coming in hot!
No info on their weaponry.
Yeah? Let's see what I can do about that.
Ugh. I could really use a sand board.
Uh?
Exactly as she described!
Where'd this come from all of a sudden? The hell!
I don't have enough thrust to break free!
Urgent breaking news.
An honorary WHA Consultant has been
abducted during a refugee camp inspection.
Nunnally vi Brittania was taken by parties unknown,
along with the chief advisor of the Black Knights.
Wow. It's been over a year, hasn't it?
Since Jeremiah took us in, I mean.
I... I really owe you one, Shirley.
Don't... Don't think I'm not aware of the risks you took.
It's just...
Y... Yeah, well...
Anya knows what she's talking about.
Right.
There's a gateway left Charles didn't touch.
Think I'll go and see for myself.
This is Milly Ashford reporting from Zilkhstan,
a kingdom universally renowned as a nation of warriors.
Impregnable as a fortress, Zilkhstan has
fended off countless invasions for centuries.
Its soldiers are held in high regard by military experts,
hired as mercenaries the world over.
Comprised of 90% desert with
precious few resources to go around,
Zilkhstan's chief export is entirely represented
by their fighting force and military technology.
It appears the Royal Guard has just
returned from a reconnaissance mission.
I'll see if I can have a word.
Is this a good idea?
The situation calls for a public statement.
I'm sure you're doing your best to unravel
the so-called "Puzzlement" at the Hashvess refugee camp.
Care to comment on the missing WHA workers,
in particular Honorary Consultant Nunnally?
I regret to say no new information has come to light.
The area is rife with border disputes, I'm afraid.
There are five countries are involved, including us.
Progress may be slow, but our efforts will continue.
We feel Miss Nunnally's loss acutely.
Her contributions to the humanitarian
effort cannot be overstated.
As we look to the future, we must think on the
lasting peace she worked so hard to bring about.
Also, I should add that our country's Divine
...is greatly troubled by this turn of events.
Okay. It's just about ready.
Lelouch, spread out the sofreh, would you?
Like last time, remember?
Oh!
Never mind.
Hope you're hungry.
Help yourself to as much as you like.
Hm?
Calm down! It's all right!
There's nothing to be afra...
That's it. Breathe.
Everything's going to be just fine.
Nothing here can hurt you, I promise, okay?
Hey, why don't I make you some warm milk?
I'll put lots of honey in it.
Well, if it's not here either, I suppose...
They haven't homed in on Lelouch,
but better safe than sorry.
Subject knows we're here and is preparing to retaliate.
Come on, come on, please don't drag us into this mess.
Wait a second! You can't be who I think you are!
Hey, Kallen.
Rough as ever I see and in more ways than one!
Pizza girl. What're you doing in place like this?
I could ask you the same question.
I wasn't exactly expecting us to run into each other.
It's been far too long, Miss C.C.
Fancy meeting you here.
If you're wondering what we're up to in this wasteland,
Prince Schneizel asked us to find Nunnally and Zero.
Zilkhstan seemed the obvious place to start.
He couldn't come out and say it publicly.
There'd be a diplomatic outcry
over lack of evidence, so...
Here we are.
Right. If you hadn't noticed,
they're trying to eliminate us,
which strengthens our case.
Have you seen the news? Very interesting, I'd have to say.
Um, actually, I'm just...
If you're a tourist...
...I sincerely apologize.
Let's move!
All of you stand down.
Are you the one in charge?
This attraction's a bit much for a
couple tourists, wouldn't you agree?
Maybe so, but it's perfect for a bunch
of mangy dogs here on Federation business.
Tch. Yeah? Well, how 'bout we settle this one on one?
I don't think so.
You're not exactly dealing with a samurai.
What the...? What just happened?
I've got your back. What's the score?
How'd you do that?
No, you don't!
Stop! What on earth has gotten into you?
Now we just sit back, relax, and
watch the fools destroy each other.
Wait!
How many freakin' brothers do you have?
Get off of me, you bastard!
Looks like a Geass!
Wow. You've heard of Geass?
Seems I'll have to delve into your background.
You...
But you were...
I believe the word is dead.
Wait, what?
Is that your Geass?
You can warp a person's perception at will?
Not the most impressive power.
Believe me. It's got its uses.
Hey, come over here and give me a hand.
Looks like we're dealing with someone special.
As you wish.
What? My Geass didn't work?
Impossible!
Afraid you picked the wrong fight.
So it would seem.
How rude of me to treat a former master so disgracefully.
I'll show more respect next time.
They're from a splinter faction.
Hm?
Think he was one of yours?
I haven't been part of the Order in a while now.
V.V.'s gone, so it's not clear who has the authority.
We can talk about it later.
I apologize.
It wasn't my intention to bring you into this.
For the time being...
Look, I'm ready to go.
Thing is...
What's the problem?
I'm not traveling alone.
I hate to say this, but they'll have to come with us, too.
Well, if you insist, so be it.
I wouldn't want the police finding him.
You, on your feet. We're moving out.
Not to be that guy, but we need to disappear.
Master Lelouch?
It's all right. Calm down. Please, it's okay.
Is... Is that really?
It's rather complicated.
It is, and it isn't.
Things aren't what they seem.
Hm?
This is the service center.
The issue's source was more or less as we expected.
We need to salvage a couple of
parts and could use your help.
Also, we've managed to find
ourselves a new customer, so to speak.
We'll need the sheet music for
the requiem, if you don't mind.
If my instincts are right,
Lelouch may have inherited a Code from Charles.
You mean the one that gives him immortality?
Correct.
He used his Geass in addition to this,
which resulted in...
Well, the code issue was not
resolved, thus the Zero Requiem.
And I'm assuming that's when Shirely got involved.
Yes.
She's a private citizen, so nobody keeps tabs on her.
So Shirley recovered him.
When things died down she brought
his body to a place Jeremiah set up.
And, well, the idea was to reconstruct
Lelouch in C's world, but as you can tell he...
What do you mean reconstruct?
The reason I can't die is because any defective body parts
get replaced with ones designed and built in C's world.
So it's like a mirror backup!
Well, not exactly.
But I supposed that's one way of looking at it.
The problem now, is that Lelouch
affectively destroyed the God of that world.
As a result, it's impossible for me to re-enter on my own.
Hang on,
but you came back to life during the shootout.
Luck. There must still be some parts left over.
However, Lelouch's mind has gone missing.
Then who is this guy?!
The empty vessel of his essence.
The pitiful remains of what he once was.
Come on!
You think this is what Lelouch wanted?
I'm nothing if not good on my word. I made a promise.
And you'd still keep it even if...
Even if...?
I know.
I don't plan on leaving him like this forever.
Why else do you think I came here?
That assassin last night used Geass. You saw it.
There's an organization here in Zilkhstan,
distinct from the Geass Order, called Farlaf.
They control an access point into
C's world known as the Aramu Gate.
If I can use it, there's a chance.
Forgive me.
The Federation dogs proved more than we bargained for.
I realize a third party intervened,
but this is hardly like you, Qujappat.
How was I supposed to know what she had up her sleeve?
You say she was a former master?
Yes. Master V.V.'s predecessor.
C.C., is it?
One wonders whether her appearance is a
revelation or along the lines of an offering.
Federation Spies or users of Geass,
the intruders can have only one of two objectives.
We must bear that in mind while weighing our strategy.
They either mean to gain the Temple of the Princess...
...or the Wailing Prison of Gimsura Plains.
Indeed, where the hostages are being held.
Should the United Federation of
Nations obtain evidence in that regard,
our region is subject to air strike.
I see, but within the Wailing
Prison is the ancient the Aramu Gate.
I assume my brother Shalio is there?
He is, as usual.
No doubt still conferring with him.
Have him return to me at once.
Relieve him and be ready to engage
at a moment's notice, Shesthaal.
Namjala latak.
As a proud son of the great and mighty Forgnar,
I'll gladly acquaint the Federation
of Nations with my superior genes.
Can you see the screen, Zero?
Or shall I call you Suzaku Kururugi?
I've made a close study of your fighting prowess.
What was your attitude control?
These moves aren't in the programming.
Come on.
How is it your technique changed halfway
through the battle while using the Albion?
Tell me, was it the unit's design?
What about you?
How were you able to anticipate my moves?
You knew I'd fall backward. Your trap was counting on it.
This again?
I'd prefer you answer my questions first.
We have Nunnally, lest you forget.
You're... You're a monster.
Am I? Okay.
If that's what it takes to become
the world's greatest warrior, fine.
I accept that.
Protecting those dear to me requires strength.
Quite a lot of it, actually. Unadulterated guile.
Complete and total ruthlessness. All qualities you have.
Yes. Our data on you paints quite a picture.
But it's hardly complete enough to satisfy me.
Now then, what is your method?!
Educate me for Nunnally's sake!
Mark my words, your strength will be mine!
Your Majesty.
My sister?
Yes.
Very well.
Once the data is collected and backed up,
return to the castle.
Namjala latak.
Your Majesty?
I've noticed more of those lately.
Yes. The energy packs have been falling short.
General Forgnar has reached out to
India for whatever they can spare,
but everyone's preoccupied with rebuilding.
It all boils down to strength.
Our nation will prevail. It must.
We have no choice but to succeed.
They gone?
Yes, and If they get suspicious and come back,
we'll have made it to the prison by then.
Thanks for carrying all this stuff, by the way.
It's a big help.
Whatever.
Next you're gonna tell me you didn't even have a plan.
Well, I mean, it didn't involve these fancy uniforms,
but I had something in mind.
Please tell me this Aramu Gate isn't just some fairy tale.
It was as temple once upon a time.
Now an infamous prison...
the final home of political enemies.
Dr. Lloyd, if you please, we're about to go inside.
So if we access this C's world from in here,
Lelouch will be his old self?
It's a possibility, not a guarantee.
Great.
Should it not work, well...
There's a faint glimmer of hope.
Let's focus on that.
Dissenters and terrorists, huh?
Why the lower block?
I'll thank you to keep this between us,
but these malcontents gave our forces more trouble
than they're worth and are slated for execution.
What's his story?
That one? Brain's been fried by drugs.
Oh, ho! Fresh meat!
What're you pretties in for?
Hey, ladies!
Wanna have some fun?
Ditch the boyfriend!
Better yet, bring him over here!
Right, Dr. Lloyd.
We're inside.
I'd like to make our move before the strip search.
How are the cameras?
How unfortunate, it's just fine.
I've already replaced it with a fake image.
This is good. You can stop.
What d'ya mean this is good?
Son of a...
We appreciate the escort.
Whoa. What the hell?
The new kids have really done it now.
Heh. Jackasses!
Believe me. You're never getting outta here.
Guards! You seein' this?
What is this?
You're just throwing me the damn keycard?
Yes, and what you do with it is your business.
You breakin' us outta this joint?
Aw, right!
This is gonna be good!
What are we waiting for? Let's do it!
Death to the guards!
Not sure if that was a good idea, but it buys us time.
Very well, and the Aramu Gate
is located on this level, yes?
Lower. We have to go farther down.
According to my information,
it was once part of an underground aquifer.
It's no longer used,
but I see no reason for them to have destroyed it.
Huh?
Hmm. Well, that's unfortunate.
What is this? A dead end?
Uh, please tell me that's not the thing we're looking for.
It's submerged under groundwater.
Which actually improves our odds.
It's been too inaccessible for anyone to disengage.
We're in luck.
The system's engineer built it to last.
That is impressive.
Is it stupid of me to ask where all the water's going?
Okay. Hey, no worries. There's
nothing to be afraid... of...
Okay, then. You don't have to stare at me
like a wounded animal. I was just trying to...
What is it?
The prison's water volume has increased.
Ministry of the Interior wants us to check the floodgates.
Hmph. Isn't that Warden Bitool's responsibility?
Well, sir, there's been an incident.
Emergency protocols are in effect...
I'm well aware!
Huh. It would appear that our unwanted guests
appreciate plumbing more than Knightmare Frames.
C.C., you sure you got this?
Yes. Stay there and keep watch.
On it.
Miss Kallen?
Yeah? What do you need?
Ma'am, I think it would be prudent for me to
monitor the riot and secure our route of escape.
Sounds like a plan.
I'll return shortly.
Wherever you are, Lelouch, come back.
Try to relax. It's for the best.
With luck you'll be whole again.
I believe it's safe to say we made it in.
What's going on?
Why are these poor souls frozen in place?
Lo, she rises. My Lady?
There has been no change.
Is this attachment or absent longing?
Absent longing?
Forgive me, Princess Shamna!
Yes, of course. That's it.
The remnants of what you left behind.
Desires, aspirations they've created a natural barrier.
Well, then.
Nunnally will have to be utilized after all.
All right, ya animals!
At least try to act civilized.
How many intruders are we lookin' at?
Hard to say, Warden.
Far as we can tell, it's just the few we saw
when we were playing prisoner in the cell block.
Say what? They don't even make a half a dozen!
What the hell are they trying to accomplish?
All we know is they're headed for the aquifer.
Great. Somethin' down there for them to give a damn about?
Just the temple from before the relocation.
So they're probably casing all the lower floors.
Right! Plan: We let 'em make
their way to the bottom level,
then stamp 'em out like insects.
Tell the elites to stand by and we'll
try not to tear the place up too much.
And by elite, sir, I'm guessing you mean the
great, honorable captain of the royal guard?
Don't be cute. His ass gets kissed enough.
Stand by?
Sir, Warden Bitool maintains that
due to the building's unique design,
he and his men are better equipped to handle this.
Man's a glorified thief...
one who would do well to remember his place.
Sayoko!
What are you doing bringing a Knightmare down here?
Yes, yes. I know. Too bulky.
Let's just say we stumbled on something
that'll shake things up a little.
What happens if the prisoners get their hands on this?
Did you think about...
Oh, crap.
Exactly.
Turns out they're not prisoners at all.
This whole thing has been a charade.
Damn it. I'll buy us some time!
Keep an eye on C.C. and Lelouch!
All right. I don't know what you expect me to do, though.
Huh. I suppose this is a rather
good subject for scientific research.
I live for this stuff.
Right there with ya.
Glad the security system didn't get 'em.
Neither of you fellas were around
for the big manhunt last week, were you?
Hell, I'll take this over that any day.
I love me a redhead!
Ooh! Firing without warning?
Gotta say, I like your style!
A Ghedo Vakka! Oh, crap!
Bursting through the floor like a ground hog! Nice one!
I hate to do this, but I really don't have a choice.
Come in, Control!
There's been a collapse. We need backup, stat!
Hold your fire! I can't hear!
The hell is going on with this thing?
Son of a... They're jammin' us!
Give me break. I can barely see anything!
My compliments, friend!
Not bad for an unfamiliar machine!
Charles,
why have you become a wedge between worlds?
Is this Lelouch's doing?
Because he...
Lelouch!
No! Take my hand!
We can't keep using our Knightmares!
No kidding!
At this rate we'll be buried alive!
Over there!
Miss Kallen!
You picked the wrong day...
Yeah, I'd surrender if I were you.
Next one I toss your way's a
bomb that'll blow us both to Hell.
Come in, Warden Bitool.
We've lost contact with the outside.
The visitor cut us off.
Take a look below you.
I, uh, don't see anything.
I know! That's exactly what's bothering me!
Understood!
Now then, where were we, my little spitfire?
Oh, right! We were about to have some fun!
So, uh, you with the Federation or the Black Knights?
Where are you? Where are you?
Call out to me!
Are these lost souls or Refrain?
Listen to me, Charles!
Stop holding on and let Lelouch go free! Please!
Nothing.
Send a message to Shesthaal.
Tell him to receive the master should he find her.
I suspect that she may be of some
assistance with the new gateway.
Namjala latak.
Oh, no! What's left of his consciousness will be consumed!
Lelouch! We have to get out of here!
Welcome back, young lady.
May I ask what you're doing?
Who are you?
Next time you break into a man's castle,
you really oughtta do your research.
Huh. Guess that clears up the main point.
You're definitely the one we're looking for.
Is it true immortality, or what?
How do you know who I am?
Ho, ho! A complete Southern Cross!
Should we try acid next, or blow her up?
Hey. Don't worry, we're not gonna leave you guys out.
Break their arms.
Ah... All finished healing yourself, are ya?
Why don't you and me cut a deal.
You tell me what you're doing here
and I won't bring the roof down
on everybody's head. Sound fair?
This... was a dead end after all.
No. On the contrary...
You put your body on the line for me again,
just like you did before at Narita.
Even though you can't die that doesn't
mean that your pain is any less of a sacrifice.
Where'd this idiot come from?
Hold on! You can't...
I thought you were supposed to be dead! Weird.
Heh.
I see! They had you hidden away in here this whole time!
You're in exile! Except that doesn't make sense.
Ah, either way, I admire you for being
able to pull off such a massive lie!
Should I be grateful?
I certainly don't admire men like you.
Aw, please. Come on, are you that dumb?
You can't run your mouth like that when you're unarmed!
Emperor Lelouch was supposed to be smart!
Unarmed? I'm afraid you're mistaken,
as my direct subordinates would no doubt tell you.
Lelouch vi Britannia commands you...
...to kill yourself, right here, right now!
The only people dying here today, pal, are
you and your so-called direct subordinates...
Namjala latak.
Hey! What the hell is goin' on down there? Hey!
We have quite a bit to talk about, you and I.
It's been awhile, but I'm back.
I can see that. Good to have you with us, Lelouch.
Bitool stopped responding? Why?
As you said sir, he's just a glorified thief.
I don't know what I expected.
The man has no backbone.
At the first sign of real danger, he flees.
Tch. We don't know what the intruders are up to.
Could be anything. What do they want from me?
Not like I can use my Batalalan Du in here.
Live to fight another day. That's my philosophy.
We have a special plan for the lady?
Oh, normally I'd let you have
fun with her until I was through,
but... no. Her? She'll be a gift. Ha!
Go. Take her to the infirmary, now.
Master Lelouch?
Yes, go ahead.
Miss Kallen is being transported to the infirmary.
Probably on the fourth level.
Also...
Please continue.
Command of the operation is being
turned over to the royal guard.
Is that so?
Yes.
They're holding their position on the outside.
Very well. We'll switch the mission to Zebra.
As you wish, sir.
I take it there's an internal conflict?
This move suggests a territorial dispute.
It's a nation ruled by siblings.
The sister acts as religious leader,
the brother heads the military.
One generally hatches an escape plan before breaking in.
Your Excellency, I have control of the system. We're up!
Well done. Thank you, Lloyd.
What do you think is being kept in this area?
You've made note of the anomaly, too, I see.
One last person is being held there.
Will they try to move him out or
will they just leave him down there?
Evidently he's too vital a piece for them to risk losing.
My apologies.
It wasn't my intention to disturb you, Zero.
You still need plenty of rest to recuperate.
The doctor tells me you'll be fine
provided you don't push yourself.
Incidentally you being here keeps the enemy in check.
We have the advantage,
though I will of course need your help to secure an exit.
Lelouch?
Yes?
Is this a dream? Is it really you?
You should rest.
You...
You... You're actually alive.
So it would appear.
Appear?
Don't do that! Don't sound so detached!
Forgive me. Old habit.
Bastard!
Why? How many times are you going to lie to me?!
I won't make excuses. Do what you must.
Damn you!
Do you have any guilt what you put us through?!
The doubt?! The pain?! You're a coward!
Why couldn't you have told us?
Why? Tell me why!
Suzaku, no! Stop this right now!
Lelouch never wanted to come back from the dead!
He's here because I gave him no choice!
C.C.
I'm impressed.
That's quite an outburst for someone in your condition.
Attention, intruders.
This is Captain Schesthall
Forgnar of the royal guard speaking.
I serve the Divine.
Your situation is hopeless.
The facility is entirely surrounded.
Surrender at once.
There is no way out. Surrender at once.
Nearly all prison personnel have been evacuated.
Comply before we are done or else.
If you choose to ignore this warning
then I cannot guarantee your survival.
In addition, should the former member of
the Order come to us of her own volition,
I've been given authority to
treat her as a guest of the state.
Attractive offer.
I wonder why they feel the need to make it.
I couldn't say.
This kingdom parted from the Order over 300 years ago.
Who knows what happened to their founders?
The program is done, Your Excellency.
Designed around the Knightmare
Frame simulator, as requested.
Communications?
Have a look for yourself.
They wish to speak with us?
Yes, sir. Please advise.
Very well, then. Put them through.
Attention, Shesthaal Forgnar.
We are tourists, nothing more.
Kindly remove your cordon and leave the area immediately.
How dare you presume to speak to me this way.
Your lack of deference is an insult to my family!
Really?
Who knew the son a merchant
clan would have such thin skin?
The Forgnars must've forgotten their
roots over the last century or so.
Please accept my sincerest apologies.
I didn't know you were proud.
Gah.
If you happen to also be smart,
you'll do as I suggest.
Fair warning.
All personnel prepare for battle!
We'll neutralize them from the ground level down!
Can't say I didn't try.
Suzaku?
I know, I know.
You really have come back.
Whoa! Hold on! What are you doing?
You can't pilot that scrap heap in your condition!
Calm down. I'm Zero. It's my job.
Sacrificing myself is what I signed on for.
A noble sentiment,
but it also happens to make
you a profound pain in the rear.
I'm sorry.
If you know another way to get
us out of this, I'm all ears.
Till then, this is the only thing I know how to do.
Huh?
All apologies, but it seem I require your assistance.
Lelouch vi Britannia commands you.
Thank you, Sayoko.
Glad I made it in time.
We have to get back and guard Doctor Lloyd.
If she is a master, withstanding
this ought not be a problem.
We shall see.
Move in, now. Secure all levels.
Engage the enemy in the name of Forgnar!
Namjala latek.
Hmph.
Be honest. There's no way this is gonna work.
Do as I say and it will.
Your confidence isn't exactly reassuring.
Then trust in my strategy!
They've closed off the only entrance. How quaint.
P9, keep backing away.
P2 and B4, rendezvous with R and draw them in!
All personnel, continue taking control of each floor.
Madin, maintain position.
Guard the bridge-laying tank en route from Ablaq Base.
K1, move into action!
A Ghedo Vakka? Ignore it. Merely a decoy!
Perfect. Just what I want them to think.
What a joke. Is this all they've got?
Heh. Keep running the enemy down!
Q Team, you have two minutes to wrap it up.
He talks big, but he's an incompetent fool.
K1, lure them in.
Captain, the captured Knightmare has fled.
It's moving to the lower level.
Excellent! Press the attack!
It will lead us to our quarry!
These bandits are nothing against a superior bloodline!
K1, proceed as planned.
Show yourself, impudent fool! Face me!
Now, Zero,
if you're entertaining any thought of escape,
permit me to remind you what will become of our hostage.
Captain Shesthaal of the royal guard,
it seems your pride was unearned.
Too bad, it was fun.
Check and mate.
You son of a bitch!
Father...
What the...? My precious Sakuradite!
Hello, Kallen. I'm pleased to see you...
Master Lelouch.
Yes, what?
Sir, don't you think it would be wise
to deal with the other staff members?
Indeed. Let us turn them all loose.
I've released them from the Geass. They're free to go.
Something about you is different.
Hm. Quite possibly.
Anyway, we'll cross the border
at a village called Lodus...
No. That won't work.
Why not?
Well, Lelouch can't run the risk
of being publicly rescued, can he?
Right. Of course.
Besides, I'm not finished here yet.
They're holding Nunnally hostage. The damn fools.
Your Highness. It is I, Forgnar.
I've been given to understand King Shalio is in residence?
Let him enter.
Most Gracious Majesty,
word has reached me that my
son, Shesthaal, has been slain.
Is this true?
Yes, Warden Bitool confirmed it.
My condolences.
Bitool, when may I ask did Shesthaal perish?
Midday, Your Highness. Around eleven o'clock, I would say.
We had no idea their ring leader
would be such a formidable foe.
I see.
That would put the time of death at six hours ago.
What of it?
My king.
I beseech you for orders. The Federation dogs must pay.
Please, let me hunt down the Black Knights
responsible and tear them limb from limb!
Generalissimo.
Highness.
Your military might is undeniable,
but the enemy may be in league
with one who possesses Geass.
Your Highness, with respect,
we don't this is related to the master I met.
Nonetheless, we must prepare for the worst.
Forgive me. Yes, Your Highness.
Sister, if they do in fact have a Geass...
Worry not.
I have the gift of prophecy with which to thwart them.
But even when we captured Zero...
Put that out of your mind. Focus on our advantage.
Hapless girl. Caught in the middle.
Your wavelength so closely aligned to Charles.
Your brother decimated the principals of C's world.
Having done so, he will soon become the means
by which I transcend the limitations he himself could not.
Implicating Zilkhstan in Nunnally's
abduction is nothing to be impulsive about.
I trust the report given to
us by Lloyd and Agent Shinozaki.
I'm a little insulted you'd go to
the Earl of Pudding before coming to me.
As a matter of fact,
I'd be honored to have you
onboard as my technical advisor.
Tch. None of this makes sense.
Why would such a small, backwater country
insist on turning the whole world against them?
I'm not so sure their motives are entirely political.
One report in particular gives me pause.
Huh. And you can't share the details?
The problem is, we've reason to
believe someone involved has a Geass.
That would explain why you
called in Shanti and the others.
Precisely.
I thought it best if the one who brought
these child prodigies together in the
first place could be the one to figure it out.
Hey, sis?
I sent that Frame Coat to Pudding like you asked me to.
You don't mean the Lancelot?
Are we not concerned that unit
will be seen as a symbol of tyranny?
Was that the wrong choice?
Sorry, I thought it necessary, provided Zero is safe.
It was absolutely the wrong choice.
Send a different set.
If you say so. Shanti?
I know. I had a feeling you'd say
that, so I already sent another one.
I hope they don't find out.
We may be over the border, but still.
The region lives in fear of Princess Cornelia.
Not only that.
They owe their chief source of
income to thievery and espionage.
And of course it doesn't hurt they're able to use Geass.
A shrewd hiding place. His Excellency is cautious.
We really must come up with
something else for you to call him.
I agree. Wouldn't want word to get out he's alive.
The only ones who should kill
are those who are prepared to be killed.
Consequently, the world is not mine to change.
At the end of the day,
Lelouch vi Britannia forfeited that right
the moment he turned his back on existence.
The only reason I've chosen to don the persona...
is to save Suzaku and Nunnally.
For that, and that alone,
I will once more become Zero.
Wonder what that's all about.
Something must be keeping C.C. busy.
Shirley!
Prez! How was Zilkhstan?
Complete waste of time.
They couldn't even be bothered
to give me decent press access.
I don't know what happened,
but things got kinda dicey so
we decided to come back home.
Oh, well, you definitely made the right call.
Yeah, how's that?
You haven't heard? It's all over the Internet.
They're locking up foreigners left and right.
You're lucky you're not behind bars right now.
Huh?
Oh, man! Apparently they're gonna
start shutting down the airports!
Hurry up and get inside!
As a rule I pay rumors no mind.
But it seems the ones about you
still kicking around were true.
Hello, Lelouch.
Suzaku.
You're on the run from Zilkhstan.
Congratulations on making it to this little border town.
Take it in. This is as far you go.
Turn around and leave or die.
Sister, I must correct you.
I'm not running from Zilkhstan.
I've come here to join forces with you.
Enough of your absurd talk!
You will meet your end here again!
Just a moment!
Are you really him? Zero?
Yes, he is.
As surely as the sun will rise.
Take it from us. We've seen him in action.
Master Lelouch,
a message from Undersecretary Kannon, regarding backup:
Additional Knightmares will be arriving by air soon.
Good. Distasteful as it may be,
I'd like you to work under my orders.
We must rescue Nunnally.
We believe she's being held either at the
Mu Base in the capital, the temple at Mefeng,
or some comparable place in the area.
We want Nunnally's safe return as badly as you,
but... there are 12,000 enlisted
soldiers protecting the capital.
Our forces are only 20 strong, if you count the civilians.
I can spare a reconnaissance team to
help you survey the field, but that's it.
Take it or leave it.
So basically the enemy outnumbers us by, what?
Uh, 600 to one.
We wouldn't stand a chance! That's crazy!
We barely have enough supplies to go around!
It's a rescue mission.
We don't need to kill all 12,000 of them.
Is that right?
You make it sound so easy.
The Zilkhstan military once crushed
a Britannian army twice its size.
They have the home advantage. This is their land.
The fact we're even here is a tremendous risk.
It would be far better to try the diplomatic route.
Would it?
And how would that go without my help?
I'll ask you one last time.
After taking so many lives, Euphie, Dalton and the rest,
you expect us to risk our necks for the likes of you?
What entitles you to our help?
I beg you. I can't do this without you.
I can't save Nunnally on my own.
I need all the help I can get.
You're a selfish bastard.
If we go along with you...
Victory is certain.
Is it, though? Can we trust you?
I will never lie to you again, Cornelia.
There's no longer any need.
I'm not so sure about Lelouch,
but I'll put my faith in Zero.
Ohgi...
I doubted him once and it didn't go well for me.
If I could do it all over again, I'd trust him.
Same goes for me! I'm with Zero!
Man's a miracle worker and that's all there is to it!
We may not share a mother,
but Nunnally is without question my sister— my blood.
As far as I'm concerned the only choice is to act!
Indeed. Well said, Your Highness.
Thank you.
Woo-hoo! I think this alliance calls for a celebration!
Yeah!
What are we waiting for?
A contribution to the cause in our capacity as civilians.
Jeremiah Gottwald, sir.
It's both a pleasure and an honor.
Oh, the lady is Anya Alstreim.
Charmed, I'm sure. Nice to meet you.
I'm guessing the extra Knightmares
Kannon sent came care of you?
We can't thank you enough.
Of course. It's the least we could
do to show our support for Lelouch.
Appreciated. We'll give him our best, right?
Yeah!
Yo, Guilford! How's it goin'? Heh.
You stooping so low to make small talk
with the rabble, or you passin' out bribes?
No, no, I'm simply showing my appreciation.
Heh! Those rats'd sell out their
homeland for a few greasy coins.
They have a right to survive.
We can't fault them for that.
They do what they must.
Don't you see?
If I can bring the results I'm seeking back to the center,
I'll be made in the shade, believe you me!
I thought you were doing this for Suzaku.
Heh, heh. That's another reason, sure.
You don't have to explain.
That's just the kind of person you are.
Oh, really? You say that so offhand.
You seem like you know him inside out.
I do?
Are you okay, Dr. Lloyd?
Uh-oh. Did I make it too strong for you?
I added in a Dragon's Breath
chili and a splash of orange liquor,
and a dash of corn starch to give it body.
It certainly has a unique smell.
That's the fresh durian zest.
You sure? Shouldn't you discuss it with Lelouch?
I would, but...
I don't have the faintest idea how to talk to him anymore.
I wouldn't take it for granted that
you'll have the opportunity tomorrow.
Mm?
If there's something you need to tell him,
don't put it off.
Why don't you take your own advice then?
Oh?
I guess being immortal makes procrastination okay?
Lady Kaguya, she held onto this for you,
just in case you were still alive.
Thank you.
You surprise me, Ohgi.
I felt sure you'd be the last person to join.
A topographical map of Zilkhstan. Useful.
Excuse me. Thank you, Zero!
I, uh...
Japan wouldn't be what it is today without you.
Please, consider this my apology...
Stop.
It's in the past. Water under the bridge.
I'm glad you're all right, Kururugi.
Huh? Oh. Thank you very much.
So now there are two Zeroes.
For the time being.
Well, you don't have to put it like that.
I'm not trying to be dramatic. It's how things are.
It's a small world. Even one Zero is a little much.
Ah. I thought I'd find you here.
What are you doing?
Studying. Got something on your mind?
Two things, actually.
First off, Lelouch, since you're back,
it's clear Zero should be you and you alone.
No. It belongs to you.
C'mon, I'm a placeholder. That's all I'll ever be.
Why's everyone doing that? I'm not back for good.
You're here in the flesh.
What are we supposed to think?
That I'm... just passing through.
Uh...
I don't know the rules governing C's world.
I'm a ghost. I could vanish tomorrow.
Don't say that.
What was the other thing you wanted to say?
Make it quick. I have a mission to be concerned with.
And you, my friend, need to conserve your energy.
What is it?
Huh. The data Kaguya gave me.
Ah. That's Ohgi's wedding reception.
It was the first time we'd all been together since...
Don't throw your life away.
He means congratulations.
I mean my condolences!
Mwah!
That's it. I'm cutting you both off.
Sorry! Ignore that, please!
Who'd have ever thought Ohgi
and Villetta would end up together?
It's a good thing for a man to settle down.
Matrimony builds character.
Hm.
Who knows, perhaps one day I'll have the
honor of attending the reception of your wedding.
Oh, don't be silly.
You look so nice. I can't believe it.
You're a real live Cinderella story!
What is wrong with you? Just
let her enjoy her special day!
Real talk, though.
You guys could afford a way bigger party than this, right?
Well, we didn't want...
Yes, allow me to offer my congratulations.
This is Kannon Maldini from the table in the back.
I don't believe we've had the pleasure of being...
You've outdone yourself.
The black forest cake is absolutely scrumptious.
Oh! Thank you!
Please excuse them, madam.
They're being too familiar.
Oh, it's fine. There's no need for titles.
This is the world you saved.
Kaguya, thanks.
Lelouch,
the other thing I wanted to say was...
...I'm really glad you came back to us.
Oh, yeah? Our reunion was a little rough.
A world without you is just less
interesting and a lot lonelier than I expected.
Thank you for that.
Also, about Nunnally...
I'm aware. Believe me.
That's another reason we have to succeed.
With both of us together?
There's no way we won't win.
True enough...
True enough.
Permits please,
and we'll need to have a look at your cargo.
The cargo is property of the Black Knights.
We'll be using it to blockade the capital.
For the remainder of this operation,
you will be answering to me.
What are you? Some kind of spy?
Namjala latak.
Listen very carefully.
Your role in this is as follows,
we are on a rescue mission.
At midnight uprisings will break out at
four bases in the vicinity of the capital.
Enemy communications will be jammed.
The squad flanking Cornelia will deploy
Knightmares and the like to keep the enemy off balance.
Based on their movements, Sayoko's team will be able
to pinpoint the location where Nunnally is being held.
Understood, sir.
Suzaku and Kallen are already in position.
What's the verdict? Yours work?
It's been a while, but I can manage.
I'm actually more concerned about the additional armor.
Well, we'll just have to use it and hope for the best.
What's so funny?
Just the way we're talking.
Never thought the day would come.
It's go time.
Good.
Whoever's behind this, make your move.
I'm waiting.
Communications with Ajbeg Base have been cut off!
No response from 113th Ginujaya Squad!
An uprising, or are the Black Knights to blame?
Probably. I'll defend the temple's rear gate, sister.
Please be careful.
We don't yet know whom it is we're fighting.
It's all right.
Once I'm piloting the Knightmare,
I can move just as freely as I like.
Forgnar, defend the seaward side.
Your Majesty.
Highness, forgive me, but might
we not be walking into a trap?
The King's general must do as he instructs.
Namjala latak.
I will defend the temple with every ounce of my strength.
Jeremiah,
in five minutes, you and your men will move
into the gulf district and divide their ranks.
Understood.
Mr. Qujappat?
Princess Shamna wishes me to join the city guard. I obey.
Attention.
A national state of emergency has been declared.
Corresponding protocols are now in effect.
All soldiers are hereby ordered to
devote their efforts toward securing...
I for the people.
The people for me.
King Shalio.
The advance force on the
Gimsura Plains has been wiped out.
That fools.
That was your warning.
You've seen what happens if you don't back down.
Nice. Looks like you've got the hang of it, Suzaku.
The Suzaku you knew is dead.
From this point on...
Zero's not a symbol— he's flesh and blood.
At least to me, so don't go there.
Otherwise we got a problem.
In 60 seconds, power to Category
Three and Category Four facilities
will be cut to stabilize the grid.
Ha! The Ministry couldn't have
been easier to bring to its knees!
Wow! The power of Geass is truly something to behold!
Your report, please.
Of course! Nina, if you would!
Finalizing! One moment!
Nothing in the air or along the
ground particularly stands out.
Anya has the seaways covered.
I've got something here!
Backup power has been rerouted to the temple!
Has it?
They must think they're clever.
Right.
We proceed to the sanctum sanctorum and
take the king's beloved sister hostage.
C.C., you handle any Geass users.
Roger that.
My Lady, it's far too dangerous to remain here! Come...
Silence!
We will stand firm and complete the system. Is that clear?
If the name Zero carries any weight with you,
surrender at once.
Fascinating. Shalio believed you were dead.
Are you the real Suzaku Kururugi, or
merely someone content to wear his name?
I'm inclined to think there are dozens of you.
I am not here to engage in conversation.
My business is with Nunnally.
Surrender now and you'll live.
Hold fast and your country will burn to ash.
Oh, will it now?
I will not be your pawn.
You don't wish to spare your people?
I say again, surrender!
Careful, Lelouch.
She almost certainly possesses a Geass.
I can feel it.
I see.
And to think six hours ago...
I was enjoying a luxurious bath.
Damn you!
Cunning as you may be,
this nation's warriors would never lose in a fair fight.
You've not seen the last of me.
Yet again, my life is reset,
pushed back by six hours.
What? Something troubles you.
Not at all.
Connect me to Forgnar.
Ah, another prophecy?
Yes.
What is your bidding, Highness?
Listen to me.
In six hours time...
rather, just before that, there will be an attack.
An attack?
The Black Knights will be involved
so it behooves us to expect subterfuge.
Further details are forthcoming.
For now, raise the alert level.
Namjala latak. Your gift is our guide, Highness.
Zero, I vow that even with the master on your side,
you shall not defeat me.
For when I die, I am destined to relive the past.
Whatever move you make, I will foresee.
Zilkhstan will rise like a phoenix.
My sister.
I am here, Shalio.
How I long to be of use to this nation.
And yet, I am cursed to stand
aside while you fight to protect it.
But you're indispensible. Don't worry about me.
No. I have to worry.
The world is broken, but with the power of prophecy,
things will be as they should.
The enemy's forces in Majbeq
Station Two have been eliminated.
Dissidents at Radar Site Three are confirmed neutralized.
As always, my sister is exactly right,
and yet, I wonder if Zero will dare to emerge.
Your Highness, should we declare a state of emergency?
Hm?
The insurgents will no doubt be bolder
if they believe themselves to be winning.
Ah, so draw them out in the open.
Exactly.
Attention.
An emergency alert has been issued.
Citizens are advised to remain indoors.
Repeat. An emergency alert has been issued...
What?
This can't be! Our lord's plan was...
They saw us coming!
No kidding!
They're waiting in ambush all over the place!
Zero, what the hell are we supposed to do?
This was a suicide mission from the word go!
This match is lost, but how?
Bad news!
The area around the temple is under heightened security!
Um, Your Excellency...
What?
Well...
This facility's been put on lockdown.
Damn it!
They've seen through the entire plan!
Their tacticians are formidable, but this?
No!
My diversionary team is vulnerable!
Oh, man. I should've brought
something to help pass the time.
Well, whaddya know! They're here!
If you idiots are tired of sittin' around,
dust yourselves off and have a go at my Batalalan Du!
Kallen! Get some distance! I'll use my PNC...
It's him again!
When dealing with a long-range Knight Gigafortress,
it's simply a matter of getting close. However...
in this case...
You little bastard!
Heh, heh. I've got you.
Megistos Omega!
Damn it! The weight of this thing is working against me!
No! Come in, Suzaku! Kallen!
Oh, could this be ECM?
What do we do?
We at least have to retrieve the data!
Let's just go.
Wait, if Zero's plan has been anticipated
like this, then it stands to reason
fleeing by air would be an incredible risk.
Princess, I'm returning to Zero.
Good. Tell him our unit's en
route to storm the castle walls.
That ought to buy him some time.
Too late!
There's no way they could've known this was our next move!
Hello, is that the Witch of the Britannia I see before me?
Bovona Forgnar.
Great, the Brown Bulwark himself.
Too slow.
Wait, Sayoko.
You've gotta slow down!
I can't keep up... My knee!
Wasn't sure you'd make it.
I can't seem to reach Master Zero.
The rest of you, follow the shoreline to the border.
I'm afraid we can't have that.
Ya know, in this country,
terrorists are publicly crucified.
I feel for you...
not being able to tell your enemies from your allies.
Heh.
Wh... What? No! Miss Cecile!
I'm all right.
Just let me start the Knightmare.
This is spiraling out of control!
Reports say the terrorist command
unit has been successfully brought down.
Very good.
Am I too late? Oh, dear.
No. Perfect timing, Anya.
That's a relief.
Jerry would be quite upset if anything happened.
Hurry! Can you get the hatch open?
Climb out and switch to my unit!
I told you to stay at the border!
Why is the Gekkoei not...
You may have noticed circumstances have changed.
Granted it's not quite finished, and it's
meant to be covert, so there are limits to what...
This is madness!
Who could've seen through my plan like this?
Should we gather intel or pull back?
If we retreat now it will leave
Suzaku, Kallen, and the others out to dry.
Don't you think I know that?!
If you want Nunnally back,
you have to come up with an alternate plan.
It has begun.
The system that should have ground to a halt is in motion.
Nunnally, because of you, I
can once again enter C's World.
Now, where is it?
The source, the provenance, the origin of consciousness?
Please, make me the first human! Let us start afresh!
Let me forge Zilkhstan into an empire! Shalio into a god!
Let me raise our people from the
dirt and reform the world in our image!
Princess Shamna?
You appear to have gone quite deep.
Are you all right?
Here, allow me.
I'm so close.
Report on the terrorist incursion?
They have all been subdued, Highness.
The threat has now passed.
His Majesty and Forgnar repelled the intruders.
Good. Most welcome news.
Now a readjustment. I care not if Nunnally dies.
Namjala latak.
She's being kept in the temple.
But...
Lelouch, your orders, quickly.
I can't! Everything's in shambles!
What?
Even if I knew how to proceed, communication is down.
And knowing about my Geass doesn't explain how they
predicted every aspect of our attack before we made it!
We can't fight an opponent like this!
Tch. It's impossible to keep up!
The needle marking...
Ugh! Both of them are out!
The people, yes.
I for them, and they for their leader.
Their king shall now triumph over Zero!
Here, you can take one of my arms!
But it'll cost you!
You fool! That move couldn't have been more transparent!
Zero, what do I do?
Zero, please!
I can't hold the line! Give us your orders!
It appears that our military
secrets have been leaked to your side.
This is the first I'm hearing of it.
I've also been given reports that
your country has had an uprising.
Just a military exercise.
Where, may I ask, is Shesthaal?
We're told he's under the weather.
And what of the search for Nunnally and Zero?
It's beginning to feel as though our country
is being unfairly singled out in the that regard.
This would be one thing if we had a
treaty with the Federation of Nations,
but involving the Black Knights seems somewhat egregious.
I've been pinned down. At this rate I'll...
Somebody, please tell us what to do!
C'mon! What are we waitin' for? Contact Zero!
Look, I don't know what you want me to tell you.
Our radios are jammed!
Ah, yes! There you are, my lord!
I was worried!
I have news. A state of emergency was
declared in the vicinity of the capital,
but it appears to have been a
ploy to draw us into an ambush.
What's our next move?
Next?
We... We...
Surrender?
Under the circumstances...
Are things really that desperate?
Yes.
I've been here before, ready to quit.
Desperate.
Hoping against hope for the tiniest speck of light.
Even so, I never let myself give in.
I clung to the idea that somehow
I'd find a way to bring you back.
And now, here you are...
just not the "you" I wanted!
Where's your ego? Your arrogance?
Where's the Lelouch who doesn't
know the meaning of give up?
I'm sorry.
I... I didn't... I shouldn't have said that.
If you want to quit, quit.
You selfish creature.
Let us consider the enemy's mind.
They, too, have a Geass, correct?
Wait, are you... are you sure?
Reasonably.
Given that hypothesis, let us narrow down what it does.
If we're wrong, we're no worse off than where we started.
Oh, and also...
Uh?
...Nunnally's rescue is non-negotiable.
We will get her out of there.
I've got you now!
Nice!
But, uh, how do we use this to contact Zero?
Heh! Easy, just stand back and let me work.
Choose one and look it over,
whichever you like.
That will be our plan.
I get it now.
The point is for me to be the
only one who knows the details.
Right. Geass doesn't work on you, after all.
So, now, the question is how we
organize the others accordingly.
Zero! Zero!
What is that? It's across all frequencies.
Zero! It's Tamaki!
We took over an enemy Knightmare!
You idiot!
You're blabbing it on every channel!
You got a better idea?
I just didn't realize a living person could be so stupid!
Gentlemen, well done.
Yes. Excellent. Excellent!
C.C., hack into everything you can!
My pleasure.
Shamna, I've done it at last!
I've become strong enough to protect you!
Your attention, please!
My name is Zero.
We are now entering the last phase of our mission.
Wait, another Zero?
This can only mean...
How intirguing!
Why is he broadcasting on their channels?
What's he talking about, final phase?
I repeat: my name is Zero.
Those of you who still stand with me,
we are now entering the final phase of our mission.
We're doomed,
so I guess it doesn't matter if
the transmission's intercepted.
Yes, but what does he mean?
I don't recall our discussing a strategy
for this particular turn of events.
My lord?
Do you wish us to strike back?
So, this final phase, what did you have in mind?
Empty words,
though I doubt the enemy will interpret them as such.
There's the Zero I know.
Attack pattern?
Already chosen.
But, um, won't our allies be just as baffled as the enemy?
What will they do?
Not a problem.
All that's left is to narrow down the variables.
Damn you, Zero.
What the devil are you playing at, announcing yourself?
Inform all forces that the perimeter has taken priority.
Nonsense. Why is now the first I'm hearing of this?
Shouldn't we all have been apprised?
It's a ruse.
He's forcing the enemy to reconnoiter. It's brilliant.
Gives us a chance to regroup.
This is my brother.
Surely you realize he's never known when to quit.
Their commander is slow to give in.
Princess Shamna, Forgnar sends an urgent message.
He requests that you evacuate to Udunmu Base.
He really expects me to run now?
We don't yet know how many terrorists there are, Highness,
and the announcement moments ago was concerning.
Could it be the Fifth Fleet?
My Lady, if Chief of Staff Schneizel is entering the fray,
we can be sure the entire Federation is committed.
Hm. I don't like this.
Why is Shesthaal so quiet?
All right, C.C., from here on out, command is yours.
Understood.
Although, I should point out,
you're the one who came up with this plan.
CIC to Rook One. Execute as planned.
Focus on populated areas.
Rook One, copy.
Why would they be using our comms channels?
This is ridiculous! We can hear everything!
What's going on?!
Princess Shamna, it's too dangerous here.
You must leave.
My work here is too important.
I will not let it claim your life, madam.
We must escort you to the castle where...
I can prevent this.
Perhaps we intercept their aerial units first.
And what of the search for Nunnally and Zero?
It's beginning to feel as though our country
is being unfairly singled out in the that regard.
This would be one thing if we had a
treaty with the Federation of Nations,
but involving the Black Knights seems somewhat egregious.
Rook One to CIC.
Enemy forces are deployed around the target area.
Please advise.
They know the infiltration routes?
In that case...
CIC to Rook One.
Abort mission. Proceed to rendezvous point.
CIC to Bishop One. Carry out mission as instructed.
Copy that.
Behold my loyal heart!
Princess Shamna, don't worry, we'll protect you!
They've cut the substation's power.
We don't have time to wait for them to recharge.
What?
Bishop One to CIC. They were lying in wait.
I'm falling back.
So much for that.
Despite me not knowing the details.
Right, the only one who knew is me,
and I'm immune to Geass.
Precisely.
Which tells us that their Geass
doesn't allow them to read minds.
And also, that they're in a position of power.
They can mobilize the military at will.
This narrows it down.
Do you think it's King Shalio?
No. He's too fixated on Suzaku.
The likelier culprit is Forgnar or Princess Shamna.
I suggest we engage Aegis mode
and proceed to the next plan.
Right.
Something's off.
They have Nunnally in their grasp,
but haven't made use of her intelligence. Why?
Is she herself the objective? Strange.
It's as if they don't care
whether the kingdom is jeopardized.
No. That doesn't make sense.
Wait.
Well, there goes another one.
They saw the gas attack coming, too.
Covered the vents to prevent it.
So what now?
Looks like a rush job.
ETA on the Black Knights'
arrival is approximately four hours.
Okay, do we order Suzaku and the others to
fall back until the main forces get here...
No.
Hold firm. If we fall back now,
they'll shore up their defenses.
Can you find out how long ago
the vent covers were put in place?
Of course.
Okay. I narrowed their Geass down to 22 possibilities.
I have to be careful.
Can't exhaust our moves trying to figure it out.
Seventeen perhaps, sixteen.
Twelve... No, that's not it.
Eight. Good, that eliminates Forgnar.
Can we still hold out?
Three, not the advisors. That leaves Shamna.
Yet...
Two. No good.
I'm out of moves with nothing
conclusive enough to protect Nunnally.
It comes down to a coin toss.
This is unacceptable!
At last, my wish has...
How unfortunate. You've died again I see.
Nonetheless, if I connect once more...
You won't.
You're trying to gain access to C's World, aren't you?
That face...
You're the detested Emperor Lelouch!
Huh.
I shouldn't really be surprised. Heh.
Such an amusing thing, fate.
To think I would be standing here across from
the very catalyst for what I'm attempting to do.
Is it true what I hear about the Black Knights
making landfall within the next four hours?
Yes.
Huh...
Shamna, would you like to know why
I nearly conquered the world?
No.
You must have an inkling,
considering we possess the exact same Geass.
Imagine my surprise.
I'd always assumed the power was unique to me.
Incidentally, this may take a while.
Would you mind preparing some tea?
Not interested?
Fair enough.
But you couldn't possibly...
The same?
He's bluffing.
There are any number of ways he could've figured it out.
And yet, the fact remains that for
all intents and purposes, I'm cornered.
Is this the first time we've spoken, or just one of many?
I can't...
Don't be coy, use your Geass against me while time allows.
Check. It's your move.
Insolent fool.
If you're so confident, show me your power first!
Don't kill him! I order this man be kept alive!
Excellent! All the other variables are eliminated!
What trickery is this? You coward!
We don't possess the same Geass at all!
I knew it! A spineless move!
I had to be sure what yours was before I could use mine.
So that's your Geass.
Your death sends you back in time.
And you're using Nunnally to
expand the bounderies of its power.
Tell me, Lelouch,
is there nothing in your own past you would change?
Imagine what you could alter with
an infinite number of new beginnings!
You could restore your legacy.
You could shed the venomous
name foisted upon you and join me!
You would deny me my pain?
Why would I shed the greater part of who I am?
My past is the crucible in which I was forged.
My scars are a testament.
Undoubtedly, but don't you wish for a better future?
Of course I do, but it doesn't belong to me.
It belongs to everyone.
You and I would both do well to remember that.
Silence... Uh!
You are a fool.
I assure you, this path leads nowhere.
A ruler worthy of the title would turn from it.
What would you have me do?
My people were hopeless. Does such love deserve death?
I won't kill you, merely render you unconscious.
You will sleep now.
No! Please!
Sure we should leave her like this?
The vents were covered nine hours ago,
meaning she can go back only as far as that.
Ergo, we'll destroy this place ten hours from now.
When her Geass triggers and she travels back,
she'll find herself unconscious.
Why has nothing been said?
What did you see sister? What will they do?
Your Majesty!
Communications with the temple have been severed!
You're breaking up. I can't understand you!
Hello? Can you read me?
Zero speaking.
The mission was a success.
Nunnally has been retrieved!
That's patently false.
Mission accomplished.
Allies withdraw.
Repeat: Allies withdraw. Abandon your Knightmares.
Rendezvous and regroup accordingly.
Well done, everyone.
This is my final transmission.
Thank you. It's been an honor.
Um, okay. Attitude control holding.
How is she doing? The bleeding stopped?
Luckily, yes. She'll need a few transfusions, though.
Blaze luminous, I believe it was called?
The moment you run out of energy,
you'll be completely helpless!
Damn you, Zero. Face me, you coward.
Move out!
Apprehend the terrorists as they attempt to flee–
dead or alive.
This battle's not over yet!
Guilford, I'm taking the castle...
even if I have to do it alone.
Wait, no!
It's personal now.
If I can't beat them, I'll at least put them off balance.
You are not going in there alone.
Suit yourself.
Let's go.
Your Majesty...
What's going on?
That does it. I'm going back.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
There! What more do you want from me, damn it?
Huh? What the...
No offense, Shanti.
Your Frame Coat's not meant for a brawl.
Being lighter may have its advantages, sure,
but your armor is also easily shattered!
You're joking.
It's been hiding an anti-Knightmare mode?
I can do this.
Hey, Nunnally.
Do you suppose her mind is stuck in C's world?
But the gateway beneath the prison has been destroyed.
We have no choice then.
We have to use the one Shamna built.
Where're you kids running off to? The fun's just starting!
I'm honestly impressed you made it
this far in that useless Knightmare,
and under the sway of my Geass no less.
Ha! Too bad it's all been for nothing!
Sorry...
You let the water conduct.
Well played...
Witch of Britannia,
I will surround you and crush you flat.
Leave Forgnar to me. He's mine.
Have at him.
How did she break through?
Forgnar! Show us what you're made of!
Give me your worst!
It's over, old man!
If you value your life, you'll stand down!
Attention all forces! Kill her! Blast both of us together!
I'm perfectly capable of doing this alone.
I couldn't let you do that.
She's over that way then.
Good luck.
What about you?
There's something I need to check.
I'll go back first.
Someone needs to make sure our bodies are in a safe place.
How long has it been since you left the Order?
I can't help but wonder what your story is.
I hope you'll forgive my impertinence.
Master C.C. An honor to meet you.
Didn't you see this coming?
No, not entirely.
My original Geass allowed me to look ahead,
but it changed into the power I have now.
Because your reasoning became corrupted.
I chose instead to embrace a lofty dream.
To reshape the world of men.
For the people of my nation,
economic power lies solely in fighting.
Lelouch's peace put our backs against the wall.
Ironic, isn't it?
Because of him, you're condemned to wander between
life and death for all eternity.
I can send you on if you so wish.
I will stay.
In this realm I may again walk with those lost to me.
Shalio will be among them one day.
Shalio, dear brother.
How many times have you fought for me?
Died for me?
If that is your desire, I can do nothing.
May you have no regrets.
There we go! Clear shot!
Rashid! Zamzar! Jose!
Ugh.
Fine! Just means there's more money for
me when I bring this little birdie down!
My machine is second to none!
You don't know the meaning of
the word resilience, sweetheart!
Ha! I can take whatever you dish out and then some!
Wait. Suzaku's got a problem.
Shamna! I need your power. I need your prophecy!
I'm... alone. Then...
if she is gone, I will fight.
For the people!
Nagid Shu Mane, do not fail me.
Be my spirit. Be my body!
You sure you wanna play rough with me?
You'll end up wearing yourself out before long.
'Sides, you'll never break through my
armor if all you do is duck me like a coward!
Pretty good advice. How 'bout I fire at you headlong?
Idiot!
Maybe. You're tough. I'll definitely give you that.
The hell is this? What happened?
The prophecy was unbeatable!
But my machine! My money!
What is that?
I don't know, but I don't think it's good.
Listen to me. I will save you Nunnally!
No! Wait!
I won't let you sacrifice yourself for me!
There's something I have to tell you!
What gives? He's still asleep?
We'll give him as long as he needs. He's exhausted.
Please! We carried him here.
If anyone's exhausted, it's us.
Why are you taking so long? Come back!
The minds that comprise this realm, hear me!
I, Lelouch Lamperouge, command you!
Nunnally.
Yes? What is it?
My Geass is my sin to bear.
Mine alone.
Would you look at that.
Once again I owe my life to you.
Why? Why is this happening to me?
Why?!
You shattered the peace. You abducted Nunnally.
Answer for your crimes!
What was I to do?
Don't you understand?
There's no place for my country in a world of peace!
Surrender. This fight is over.
No, it's not! In the name of my great sister's burden,
I defy you!
I am a warrior!
Wha...
There's no honor in dying!
How many have suffered for me?
How many have died to maintain my body?
If I lose now, it will have all been meaningless.
Shamna...
Sister...
Tell me... what should I have done?
That light... What is...
Ugh! Where is His Majesty?
Where is Princess Shamna?
Damn it, men! What are you waiting for?
I told you to fire! Forget about me! That's an order!
Stop.
They're not going to let you die.
You're Generalissimo Forgnar,
the only one standing between them and chaos.
It's over.
The prophecy was wrong.
Good news concerning Honorary Consultant Nunnally.
It seems the event many have called
the Puzzlement in Hashvess has ended well.
Early this morning, a rescue squadron
led by Lieutenant General Cornelia
found the consultant alive and unharmed.
A nation known for its soldiers and its prophecies,
and yet even they couldn't defeat him.
Well, the cavalry's arrived.
Better late than never, I suppose.
Now we can get you some proper medical attention.
That's a relief. Thank you, Doctor.
Sorry if I made you miss out on anything.
Not to worry.
There are plenty other war-torn
regions for us to visit I'm sure.
Feels like congratulations are in order if you ask me.
Oh, thank goodness! You're back.
What is it? He finally awake?
Perfect timing.
You should come see this.
Huh?
This is breathtaking.
I see you made it back. Good for you.
Huh?
Farewell, Suzaku. That's yours now.
What're you talking about?
We talked about this, remember?
I can't stay.
Lelouch.
Hm? Yeah?
I... I tried to tell you this before, but...
I had assumed the worst of you and it was wrong of me.
You deserved better and I'm sorry.
Water under the bridge.
Please, you don't have to carry it alone.
I'm just as guilty as you!
It's not right for you to have to bear
the burden by yourself and it never was!
Let me share it with you!
That's very kind. Thank you.
You forgot this.
Oh. Thanks.
So what, you're just gonna sneak away?
I have my own road to follow, but I'll be around...
...from time to time.
Hmm.
Lot of folks leaving the country, I see.
Hey, we did the right thing, didn't we?
I dunno. That's for history to decide.
Sometimes, you have to go with
your gut and stumble through it.
C.C.! Where are you going?
Wait!
Well, I guess some things never change, huh?
It's not that. You just... You left without telling me.
Yes? What of it? Did I forget something?
I'm coming with... you.
What? But Nunnally...
Will be just fine. She's a very capable young woman.
If I stay around, I'll just get in her way.
Y... You have other options.
You could drop in on Shirley, or Kaguya for that matter.
Eventually, sure,
but this doesn't feel like the right time.
I don't want to cause a scene.
If you're looking for someone to
be your servant, look somewhere else.
I'm tracking down the Geass fragments Shamna left behind.
I have no interest in being your sidekick.
Oh, I see how it is.
You bring me back to life and leave like it's nothing.
You're such a selfish creature!
Yes, I am!
We've established that already, remember?
Idiot.
You haven't even decided what to call yourself.
You can't stick with Lelouch.
I know that.
Still, I don't have to abandon my name altogether.
What if I went with L.L.?
Has a ring to it.
Really?
By having Geass, you're able to live.
And yet, the same power that allows
you to live in the world of men,
compels you to abide by a different set of rules.
Act by a new logic, move to its
rhythms, lead a different life.
Be warned, the king's power may isolate you.
Geass will be taken from those lacking resolve.
However...
...for those that do have the resolve...