The train to New Ikebukuro is
now arriving on Platform One.
Please watch your
step when boarding
and stand clear of
closing doors.
The Tokyo Metro
New Marunouchi line
would like to thank you
for riding with us today.
This train is currently
bound for New Ikebukuro.
We'd like to take a moment
to inform all passengers
that Tokyo Metro is cooperating
fully with the nine pm curfew
required by the
Tokyo Government's
Youth Protection Act.
This curfew applies to all
citizens under twenty years old.
Minors may circulate
after the curfew provided
they have an approved permit
or constant adult supervision.
If you are without
the proper permit,
please proceed to the nearest
staff member for assistance.
Again, minors may
only circulate after nine
with an approved permit
or adult supervision.
If you need assistance,
please proceed to the
nearest staff member.
Shall I eat you now
or play with you first?
The train to New Ikebukuro
is arriving on Platform One.
Please wait behind
the white line
until the train comes
to a complete stop.
Go figure.
They're not so subtle this time.
Ready to head out?
Not yet. Gimmie a sec.
He's not there.
He ran off.
What?
Another group.
They saw him somewhere else.
Let's go, then.
Hello?
Who are you?
Destruction of target confirmed.
Two witnesses.
Recovery team, you're up.
It's dead!
It's totally been killed!
Hey.
Who the hell are you?
Fujimura?
Mana?
Whoa.
Are you okay?
So that's it.
That's an Elder Bairn?
Elder Bairn.
What are you doing out here?
Matsuo. Hi.
Fuji, we gotta roll!
Right!
I got ya.
Not good!
Hurry!
Move it.
Who is she?
I don't know.
We should go.
Damn it!
Witnesses are fleeing by car.
In pursuit, now.
Ground squads, make your move.
Hurry!
They're right there!
Then tell me where
the hell I need to go!
Come in, Sirrut!
It's Fujimura!
Come in!
There's a Tower
copter chasing us!
Please!
Help us!
Yanagi!!
Fujimura.
You need to calm down...
Yeah. Okay.
Stand by.
I'll have your route
for you in just a minute.
Try to go ahead and
transfer any information
you've already gathered
in the meantime, all right?
'Kay.
I'll do what I can.
Tsuki.
You think you can get into the
transportation system networks?
Yep.
Wonderful, and what about the
Department of Motor Vehicles?
I can do that.
Mister Mogari.
Do you approve?
Yes.
Right there!
Turn right!
I can't!
It's a one way street!
Oh, sorry.
Okay, awesome.
It looks like they've
finally got a route for us.
We're good to go!
Turn right up here.
Yeah, right there!
Right at the light
Where are you going?
Shut, up!
So, I think we
might be off route.
Yeah, I didn't have
much of a choice!
Gimmie a sec.
Look, you guys!
What the hell?
They're behind us again!
I need something!
Yanagi, help!
Keep going straight ahead.
Whatever you do,
don't slow down!
Hurry!
Okay, don't
blame me if we crash!
You got 'em?
Yep.
They should be good to go now.
I'm guessing we
should keep running.
For the blood.
I'm fine, thank you.
Is that man dead?
The important thing
is we're all safe now.
My poor car has had
the crap beat out of it.
I'm so sorry, baby girl.
'Twas a noble sacrifice.
I'm Mana Hiiragi.
So, um.
What's your name?
What?
I thought this girl
was a friend of yours.
No.
But she... she saved me.
From that thing.
Seriously?
She saved you?
From the Tower's Elder Bairn?
Tell me.
What do you know
about the Elder Bairns?
I know nothing.
What's your problem lady?
Let him go!
No.
So this Tower.
Where is it?
What do you know?
I don't know anything.
I wish I could tell you.
That's what we've
been trying to find out!
He's telling the truth.
Our goal is to find out
what the Tower is up to.
Guess you've got
something against them?
You mind telling
us what that is?
And, while you're at it.
What happened
back there, anyway?
How the hell did that thing die?
It died because I killed it.
Oh-kay.
What was your name again?
It's HQ.
Maybe it's Yanagi.
Hello, Saya Kisaragi.
Fumito Nanahara.
You want him dead, right?
Fumito?
I'd be happy to meet with you.
Perhaps you and
I can discuss the matter.
There's a reward for the victor.
And a punishment for the loser.
Excuse me, sir.
The Governor's office is
requesting a meeting with you.
They'd like to discuss the
measures they're prepared
to take against last month's
Youth Protection Act Violators.
Things will be so much easier
when you become governor.
Then, I won't have
to waste my time
on these ridiculous meetings.
Don't you agree, Yuka?
Yes, sir, one hundred percent.
How old are you again?
I'll be twenty-eight this year.
Isn't it amusing how you
were a high school girl
up until only six months ago?
Although, I'm sure
you'd rather forget
about that particular
unpleasantness.
Indeed, I would.
Thank you for understanding.
Also, about your meeting with
the US Ambassador later today.
They're requesting
to see you earlier.
It seems like that
happens a lot these days.
Everyone wants to change things.
If you ask me, given the
influence of our corporation,
Seventh Heaven, as well as
the secret you and your clan
have been keeping in
order to maintain peace.
You deserve far more than
you've been getting, sir.
You're so ambitious.
Mister Nanahara?
Yes, what is it, Kuto?
I have an update on our lab
escapee.
It's been terminated, sir.
The subway cleanup
is complete, as well.
But unfortunately, there were
two witnesses to the death.
Don't tell me they escaped.
I've already dealt with the men
who allowed them to get away.
Next time, I'll be
sure to go myself.
I don't know.
You may not be up to it.
Saya is here now.
If you're finished, shall we go?
What's wrong?
Follow me, please.
Come in.
Mana, I understand; thank you.
No, thank you.
Welcome, Saya Kisaragi.
I'm Kuroto Mogari.
Are you?
How do you know my name?
Ukishima.
An experiment
was performed there.
During which, everyone
was reportedly killed.
Have you heard of it?
Judging from the pictures,
it was a violent
and brutal massacre.
However.
One person was fortunate
enough to survive the ordeal.
That person was
you, Saya Kisaragi.
Clearly.
And how exactly did
you find this out?
Itsuki sent it to me.
You knew him by the name,
Itsuki Tomafusa, correct?
He hacked the Tower's cameras
and managed to get a
few images out to us.
Without him, we wouldn't
have known the truth.
Was he a part of Sirrut?
He never worked with the core
of this team, directly; no.
But technically,
he was a member.
What happened to him?
He died.
I knew it.
He was a participant in
the Ukishima experiment.
His goal was to try
and expose The Tower.
Tower?
The name of the
actual organization
led by Fumito Nanahara.
On the surface,
he's something else.
CEO of a company
known as Seventh Heaven.
It's an impressive,
massive corporation
and has significant
global presence.
Not surprisingly,
he has many connections
politically, as well.
It's widely accepted that
he was directly involved
with the new
Youth Protection Act.
In reality, his public persona
is just smoke and mirrors,
a redirection of attention.
Away from the Tower?
That's correct.
Fumito has been
using Seventh Heaven
and the Tower to achieve
a very specific objective.
And that would be?
I wish I knew,
but unfortunately,
we aren't entirely certain.
But, what we do know
is that numerous people
are being killed to fulfill it.
Hundreds, maybe more.
We've learned creatures
called Elder Bairns
are somehow a part
of this thing, too.
And, how do you know
all this information?
Simple.
I did research.
Using all my resources:
time, money and power.
But why?
Because Fumito
Nanahara is pure evil.
He took my freedom from me,
and for that he must pay.
That's not all.
Itsuki was only able to send us
images very sporadically,
so I saw but a fraction of
what occurred at Ukishima.
That was enough, though.
And then, there was you.
Funny.
You seem quite different,
from all the pictures, I mean.
Almost like Fumito was trying to
manipulate you for some reason.
Now you're here.
I'm assuming to find him
and punish him for his crimes.
It's taken you six months,
but you've finally
made your way to us.
Although you've attracted
a fair amount of attention
wherever you've gone.
Not that any of your
actions were reported.
Then how did you know?
It's not that
difficult, actually.
Internet restrictions might
be severe, especially in Tokyo.
But we have a couple
of talented hackers
that help us find
useful information.
This is one.
Hiro Tsukiyama.
We call her Tsuki.
And me.
The other hacker is me!
True.
Though your
talent is in question.
Meet Fuji, Shun Fujimura.
And the big one, our resident
driver, is Iori Matsuo.
Hey.
I imagine Mana already
introduced herself?
My name is Haruno Yanagi.
I'm Mogari's assistant.
And together, we make up
the entirety of Sirrut
working from this mansion.
Welcome, Saya.
Although, there
are other members.
They're located
all over the world
and help us out online;
we've got a lot of support.
That's right!
Our goal is to overturn
the Youth Protection Act.
Not to mention the
stupid web restrictions
and all those lame new laws.
We're taking down the man!
Fumito. Tell me.
Where is he?
Yes, where is Fumito?
That's a very good question.
These days he rarely makes
any public appearances.
And his location is kept secret.
Meaning you don't
know where he is.
Oh, I have a way to find him.
Just take a look around you.
These people along
with other Sirrut members
out there will provide help.
They are willing
and able to give you all
of the information
you need on him.
In return, we request your
assistance, Saya Kisaragi.
Fumito Nanahara
is my only concern.
Do not forget that.
Guys!
Think this chick
should be joining us?
Hey?!
Thanks, Fuji.
Here you go, Tsuki.
Thank you.
Why are you asking, Matsuo?
Don't tell me you're not
wondering the same thing!
Unless, I mean,
you have a good reason
to trust her that you
haven't shared with us yet.
I don't like her.
She's quiet and
really freakin' pretentious.
Come on; she sure
is pretty, isn't she?!
That girl almost ripped your
face off with her bare hands.
But being pretty is
all that matters to you?
Uncle!
It's Mister Mogari's decision.
Yeah, I'm not stupid;
I know that.
But just for the record,
I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
Tsuki agrees with me!
Isn't that right?
No, I know what
Tsuki doesn't like.
Mana finally made her
way back to our group.
But now, thanks
to our friend Saya.
she's way too busy with
someone else to play with her.
For that.
I'm not gonna show you the
new kitten video I downloaded.
No, show it to me!
Don't listen to him!
Take away his kittens!
Shut up!
That's not fair!
Please let me see them!
Amazing place, isn't it?
You know, Mister Mogari is
also the president of Cisnet.
That's a company
most kids right
out of school dream
of working for.
So, Saya.
That's a really pretty name.
Oh, um, I think Kisaragi sounds
like a cool last name, too.
That is not my last name.
It's not?
Oh, wait, stop!
Your room is right here.
The bathroom's um, over there.
Do you need clothes?
This is fine.
But you need to
wash off all the--
I can just have Haruno find you
a change of clothes; it's okay.
I said this is fine.
All right.
Just so you know,
everyone else kind
of goes back and forth
between here and their homes.
But Mister Mogari
has been kind enough
to let me live here permanently.
My room is right
next door, so uh.
If... If you need anything,
just let me know.
That's all. Ohh...
Good night!
Well, if you have
like a problem
or there's anything
else you need.
You can, um, just.
Well, I guess just let me know.
There's nothing I need, but
there is a place I'd like to go.
Why are you following me?
Sorry?
It's dangerous out here.
Well, I guess maybe
it's not dangerous for you.
But you... you don't
have a cell phone, and I do,
so if Sirrut needed you,
I could help you out.
You see?
Yes?
Yes.
Really?
You mean you want to
go through that again?
No, I just wanted
to be with you.
Why's that?
I don't know.
That's so crazy.
All this time, I never knew a
mansion like this was out here.
So you can see it?
What do you mean?
So I can see what?
This isn't a mansion.
It's a shop.
It's been a long time, Saya.
It's only been six months;
that's not that long.
I meant that it's
been a long time
since I've seen the real Saya.
Here you go.
Oh. Yes, thank you very much.
Saya?
None for me.
Wow. It's delicious.
I'm glad you like it.
So.
So um what does
this shop sell exactly?
We don't sell; we grant wishes.
Wishes?
I deal in odd-jobs,
you could say.
Um.
Saya.
Do you come here
often to make wishes?
No, only once in a while.
Right now, I just know they
happen to have what I want.
It's true.
Saya, I was quite surprised to
see you with a friend, I mean.
Actually, I just followed her.
Only because she
allowed you to, Mana.
I was with you in Ukishima.
We can both give thanks
to this little one for that.
I have to apologize
for not being more help.
Yet as it turned out.
You recovered your
true self on your own.
Even still.
The words you spoke were
the key and are appreciated.
And now, you're here?
I am.
I need a sword.
A new one.
Strong.
Can you help me?
Wow.
Lots of weird stuff in here.
I had a feeling
you'd choose that one.
What does it cost?
We'll discuss price later.
Very well.
Hey, wait for me!
Do you think you could
stay by her side for me?
Please?
I don't know.
I um...
I kinda have a feeling
I'm annoying her.
I doubt that.
You were able to enter my shop.
That should be more than enough.
So, um.
So how do you
two know each other?
Shop owner and customer.
That's it.
However, when both
have lived as long as
we have, you get attached.
It's interesting.
Isn't it?
The threads of fate
already connect them.
Saya, wait up!
A message from
the Tokyo Government.
It is now past eight pm.
Under the Youth Protection Act,
minors can circulate
after nine pm only with
a guardian or a permit.
Minors without permission
are to return home immediately.
A message from
the Tokyo Government.
It is now past eight pm.
Under the Youth Protection Act,
minors can circulate
after nine pm only with
a guardian or a permit...
One more sec.
Sorry.
I'm just letting everyone
know where we are and stuff.
What's "and stuff"?
They are.
They're called "watchers."
You heard that
announcement, right?
As minors we can't be out
without permission after nine,
and they're the ones
who enforce the law.
They're not nice
about it, either.
I hate that curfew.
Time to go home, kids.
We know.
They're horrible.
That's why so many rumors
were spread about you online.
You're the mysterious girl
who walks alone at night
and ignores the Act
like she doesn't care.
Rumors should never be ignored.
Some of them hide
real information,
like with Seventh Heaven or
sometimes even about the Tower.
Makes me wonder.
Is the Act supposed
to keep us from truth?
The internet's a
lot faster than TV,
and, you know, pretty much
makes newspapers irrelevant.
It's harder to hide
what's going on;
people can get information
as soon as it's happening.
And, well, people
who are online the most...
They're the younger ones.
Exactly.
They might be trying to
keep the next generation
from questioning the
Tower, or the government,
or who knows what, really.
At least that's what
Mister Mogari says.
It makes you curious about what
could be worth so much effort.
And then there's Fumito.
He's-- Ugh!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I've been doing all
the talking, haven't I?
Hold up, you two!
What's wrong?
It's only just after eight.
This isn't about the time.
It's about her.
Do you have your ID.
I'm gonna need you
to hand that over, okay?
Gotta check something.
Hey!
Wait!
Come back here.
Now!
What do you think you're doing?
What?!
You're gonna pay for that!
Number thirty-one, twenty-five.
Please check in.
Thirty-one, Twenty-five,
please check in.
She is like completely awesome.
What are you doing?
We need to get out of here.
Like I said.
That was way too dangerous!
I said I'm sorry.
How bad was it?
Do you think they could
have found out about us?
No, I seriously doubt it.
They barely looked at me;
they were focused on Saya.
Why were they talking to her?
Who knows?
But she took those watchers
down like it was nothing.
For what it's worth, she
kept me from getting hurt.
That makes me glad.
Me too, Tsuki.
Me too.
If it happens again, you just
run and leave her ass there.
Let Miss Gloom and Doom
deal with it on her own.
She's still super pretty.
Whatever; she's
not my type at all.
No, of course she's not;
your type is Yanagi, isn't it?
No!
It's not, you idiot!
I think you should
have just left her, too.
Try to understand.
I know going was dangerous,
but I couldn't help it.
Y'know?
You can't ignore her?
Yeah.
That's kind of it.
Mana.
I'm sorry, I-I couldn't find
more info on your dad.
I did try.
It's been four
months already, huh?
Wow.
You might need to start
facing that chance that-
No, it's okay!
I'll work harder.
I'll cover for you.
So please, don't worry, Mana.
I'll find him.
I swear it.
Oh, sweetie.
She's right.
Heck, yeah.
Damn right, she's
right; we're a team!
We are Sirrut,
and we take down evil!
Bring it on!
--Nothing's gonna stop us!
--Thanks, you guys.
--Nothing, am I right?
--Thank you.
I see you have a sword, now.
I'm guessing for a purpose.
You're planning to
kill Fumito with it?
Correct.
Mister Mogari, I'm sorry,
but I have to say, carrying
a weapon inside this building
may not be the best idea.
No, it's fine.
Don't worry; I'll be sure to
prepare a special covering
so no one gets suspicious.
Do you mind if I call you Saya?
Do as you like.
The Tower is searching
for you specifically, Saya.
According to the
information Tsukiyama found,
the Tower has contacted the city
government via Seventh Heaven.
They've increased
the number of watchers
in this town for
one reason: to find you.
Next time,
I would appreciate it
if you refrained
from such actions.
I have no intention
of obeying your orders.
Yes, I know.
But still, if you want revenge,
you must await your moment.
Trust me, it will come.
In fact, I will ensure it,
no matter what.
What happened
between the two of you?
What did he do?
It's complicated.
Fumito and I are cousins.
Come with me, if you'd like.
You've heard of the
Shrovetide, I'm sure?
Yes.
It's the ultimate pact.
One between humans
and Elder Bairns.
They are allowed to eat humans,
but only a prearranged,
agreed upon number.
The Shrovetide Covenant.
Fumito and I are
members of certain clans.
These clans have not
only hidden the Shrovetide,
but they've perpetuated
it for generations.
We are descended from those
who originally forged the
Covenant with the Elder Bairns.
My family, The Mogaris,
took a more open role.
We worked with political leaders
to conceal the
Covenant's existence.
The Nanaharas, Fumito's clan,
secretly protected the
Mogaris with their magic crafts.
Together, they were
known as the Tower.
But then, Fumito
broke the rules.
You are the first person I have
ever brought to this place.
Six years ago
Fumito showed up here.
He had a squad of
armed men with him.
His goal was to take
control of the Covenant.
He killed my father,
the Mogari clan leader.
He murdered my mother, as well.
He took them away
right in front of me.
He took everything.
Saya.
I'm asking you.
Please, kill him for me.
I'm going to kill Fumito
for my own reasons.
They've nothing to do with you.
Yes.
Although, I'm sure
you have to admit.
You understand my pain.
Welcome back.
Or not.
It's whatever.
I wanted.
I, uhh... I wanted
to tell you thank you.
Thank me? Why?
For saving me
from those watchers.
They were after me, not you.
Well, you didn't have
to take me away, though.
So thank y...
Um.
What is it?
Just wanted to say goodnight.
Mana, tomorrow
you're going to try
to talk to her longer, okay?
You can do one more minute!
Saya.
Stop it!
You were so lovely at Ukishima;
all your memories wiped out,
but there was something
else I was drawn to more.
Mister Nanahara.
Everything is ready, sir.
Wonderful.
We will see each other.
One more time, Saya.
Look at those cute little
paws; I can't stand it!
Have you ever thought about
asking Tsuki or Fuji
to give you lessons?
It wouldn't work; I'm illiterate
when it comes to the
internet or computers.
Text messaging is
about the most I can do.
You know, my actual job is
as Mister Mogari's assistant.
But I'm managing to
help out elsewhere anyway.
Well, I'm so sorry.
Not everyone is
super-awesome like you.
You're such a brat.
Is that supposed to
make me feel guilty?
Hey.
Look.
My job is doing the
driving and dealing
with other non-computer
related issues.
What?
Honestly.
Is something wrong?
You seem upset.
I didn't make it to my
one-minute goal with her.
I suck.
I'm jealous.
You and Matsuo seem
to get along so well.
What?
What makes you
think we get along?
Why're you so defensive?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I did it!
I found part of
Fumito's schedule.
Not the whole thing,
but I still found it!
Awesome!
A high school?
Yes.
Seventh Heaven donates a
whole bunch of money to it.
So, he'll be there.
Yeah, well there are a
lot of places like that.
They don't just
donate to schools.
They give out money all over.
Orphanages,
hospitals, you name it.
You sure?
We are.
Tsuki and I split up
their charitable donations
and checked them all out.
And then- Bingo!
Tsuki found it.
Yeah.
Tsuji's a private Academy.
Fumito will be there tomorrow
to give a guest lecture
during an open assembly.
Impressive.
I don't know how
you do it, Tsuki.
Hey, that's not all.
We found a bunch of
gaps in the security, too.
Tsuki found those.
And you're certain of this?
Hacking skills are
very important,
but that won't matter if you
can't verify the information.
Least that's what I was taught.
Well then.
Saya?
I'll go.
Oh, come on!
You can't be serious, lady.
They're gonna have security
literally swarming that place.
You can't just waltz right in.
I doubt if you'll even be able
to make it past the front gates.
Don't worry, guys!
I took care of everything!
I found out the locations
of all the guards.
Well, look at you go, Fujimura.
And what about the
uniforms, genius?
I thought the idea
was we were gonna sneak
in there as students.
Where do you figure
we'll get those costumes?
Unless you know how to sew.
Do you?
Actually.
I might be able to do
something about that.
Well, at least the weather
today is awesome, right?
Wait for me, Saya!
The sound's working fine.
And the GPS is on target, too.
Dude, how did we not know Mana
was a student at Tsuji Academy?
That's not that big of a deal.
The thing I don't get is why she
asked Mogari to let her go, too.
Mister Mogari.
Will please you let me
go along with Saya?
Please let me go!
Saya?
Do as you like.
Well, whatever the reason.
There's no way we're
letting Mana down.
Right.
Agreed.
Guys, if something goes
wrong and it gets nasty.
Be sure to go in
after them, immediately.
Got it!
Just so you know,
I'm pretty worried, too.
But we'll do whatever we can to
help them out from here, okay?
Yeah. Okay.
It's funny.
You don't seem like
this is the first time
that you've ever been here.
Being too cautious
only makes you stand out.
Oh yeah, I guess
that makes sense.
Did you know about this?
About what?
About this school.
Did you know that it was
connected to Seventh Heaven?
Yeah.
There's a plaque
the school made
to thank them for
their donations.
And also, the teachers
are always talking
about it like nonstop.
I really wanted to
drop out, but I didn't.
Mana!
You made it!
Oh.
Yeah.
I figured you'd
skip this assembly.
It's like the middle
of winter break, y'know?
So how's it been going
living all by yourself?
You doing okay?
Yeah.
I heard about what
happened to your dad.
I'm so sorry.
We're glad you're
doing well, though.
Oh.
Thank you.
Good to see you all.
Let's go.
Hey, lucky us!
Looks like they're not going to
divide us up by classes today.
Um.
That's what they
would normally do.
What did those girls mean?
About your father.
Just asking.
Never mind.
Everyone, please be quiet...
We will now begin today's
very special lecture.
Please welcome
Mister Fumito Nanahara.
From Seventh Heaven?
Seriously?
So, that's why they wouldn't
let us bring in our phones.
I wonder why he's talking to us.
What?
Please remain calm.
Obey the staff's instructions,
and evacuate the hall
in an orderly fashion.
Saya, we have to get out!
Come on!
Mana!
What's going on down there?
I-I don't know!
I heard screams
just after the bell.
I can't tell. I have no idea!
But their position
hasn't moved at all.
It's been too long, Saya.
Saya!
Fumito!!!
Saya.
You came all this way for me.
I'm flattered.
And yet, I must apologize.
I'm sure you understand.
You're so strong;
I had to take precautions.
But I wonder, will you at
least play with me awhile?
So close.
Why?
Saya!
Get down!
Saya.
Saya!
Matsuo?
What?
Let's get them out of there!
All right.
Hang on to what you got!
You're bleeding.
Saya.
Mana.
Let's go!
'Kay.
I will go.
The rest of you
recover it immediately.
Saya, please move!
I think I can open it.
So, you're Saya.
What's wrong?
Are you in pain?
You're a freak,
just like that monster.
Shut up!
Saya!
Don't worry about me; go!
You're done.
It's a shame you
can't kill humans.
I got it!
If you could,
you might have a better chance
at protecting your friends.
Get in!
Come on, let's go!
She needs a doctor!
Unfortunately, she fled.
What a shame.
We recovered the blood
per your previous orders.
I'll take it to the lab as
soon as we're done here.
Nicely done, Kuto.
Basically, the entire
thing was a set up.
I'm sorry.
Tsuki.
This wasn't your fault at all.
I confirmed the
information provided
as well as approved the plan.
It's my responsibility.
It's cool.
Well.
I'm just glad everyone
made it out in one piece.
Yeah.
Except for my car, that is.
She's wrecked again!
Another noble sacrifice.
Well, considering somebody
actually did get hurt.
I guess it's not
that big of a deal.
Right?
Yeah, I mean,
I thought you didn't
even like Saya,
but it's whatever, man.
Look, I can't ignore that
she was protecting Mana.
She could have just left her
there to die if she wanted.
I don't mind changing
my opinion, bro.
Not if that's what
she's really like.
Where is Saya?
She said no doctors,
so Mana got mad
and ran down the hall after
her; I imagine to her room.
That was a high
tech electronic lock.
Mana's the one who
opened it, right?
Seems that way.
You mean.
Mana hacked something?
That she did.
And in like no time at all, too.
That's good news.
Our other genius hacker
is proving rather
impressive herself.
Of course she is!
Mana is incredible!
I learned from her;
she's the best.
I'm not nearly as good.
If anything, this could
help her regain confidence.
I hope.
Stop!
I said stop!
There's no way you're fine
after getting hurt like that!
It's not as bad
as it looks, Mana.
Saya!
I'm really sorry.
Don't be; there's
nothing to be sorry for.
I don't want this.
I don't want it to happen again.
Not because of me.
I really am alright.
The wounds are healing.
They really are.
But how?
Whatever the reason.
What's important is I'm fine.
Do you understand?
Why did you say "again"?
Has something like
this happened before?
Sorta.
My mom died when I was little,
so it's just been me and
my dad for the most part.
He was really awful
at cooking and stuff.
But he always did
his absolute best
to make something
I'd at least eat.
He was always so
busy with his job.
He still found a way to cook
for me everyday, though.
His job?
Newspaper reporter.
He liked the old
fashioned newspapers,
printed and all of that.
When he'd been drinking,
he liked to say:
"What a reporter needs is
curiosity and inquisitiveness."
He taught me to take an interest
in anything and everything.
And most importantly,
he told me not to let
other people decide for me.
"You should always take
care of your own research
and make your own decisions."
He had a bunch of
quotes like that about life.
His favorite was, "When you
decide to do something,
you should follow it
through until the end."
A year ago.
He had an idea; he'd
focus his next article
on an exclusive
about Seventh Heaven.
Eventually, pressure
came from higher up,
and the project was cancelled.
But my dad refused to quit.
He said he would
write the article anyway.
He wanted to find out the truth.
I wanted to help him,
so I conducted some
research of my own.
It helped that I was pretty
good with computers, too.
I hacked into
Seventh Heaven's systems
and discovered they were hiring
a lot of people out of the blue.
People who, not much later,
were reported missing.
I also found out something
called The Tower was involved.
Although, I wasn't sure how.
Dad took the proof I'd gathered
and said he was gonna
meet with Fumito Nanahara.
He thanked me for
helping him and left.
And then.
He never came back.
If I hadn't helped him,
then my dad wouldn't--
He hasn't come back,
and it's all my fault.
I came here cause.
I wanted to find my dad.
But, I was afraid
of what I might find,
so I stopped hacking altogether.
What if he...
What if he's dead?
I-I don't think I can
make it without him.
What about you?
Your father?
I don't have one.
But I knew a man who
was like a father to me.
I never thought
I would miss him.
How do you manage
to be so strong?
Your father and I share
the same philosophy.
Whatever I start, I see
through to the bitter end.
No matter what, I finish it.
I don't give myself a choice.
I do it because
I have to, so I can be me.
Now it makes sense.
Why I couldn't leave you.
Why I wanted to be near you.
We're a lot alike.
You and me.
We're lonely.
Nothing about what happened
at the high school
is showing up.
Big surprise, huh?
Yeah, right.
Assholes.
Mana and Saya
are still back there.
They haven't come out yet.
She was hurt pretty bad.
I bet Mana is
taking care of her.
Saya will be back
to gloomy in no time.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning!
Hey!
It's about time!
Sorry.
We were up late last night.
Good morning, Tsuki.
Mana!
I'm sorry the stuff
I found out was wrong.
I'm sorry, Saya.
You didn't mislead us
on purpose, did you?
No, I would never do that.
No.
That's good to hear.
Then you have nothing
to apologize for.
Are you... Are you hurt?
No.
You mean it?
Yes.
That's nice.
I'm glad that you're all right.
So.
I, um, just... Uh.
I think I might have gotten
the wrong impression of you,
so what a relief I was wrong.
If that was supposed to
be an apology, it was crap.
I didn't ask you!
Anyway!
Thank you for saving Mana.
You're awesome!
Hey.
She just ignored me!
Can you blame her?
You guys.
I wanna talk to you
about something, okay?
Hacking?
Yes.
Are you sure?
You're ready?
I'm sure. Yes.
I'm never gonna
accomplish anything
if I just keep running away.
I'm ready, no matter
what the result is.
Very well.
Let's do it.
After the events
at the Tsuji Academy,
they now know all about
our organization's objective.
The Tower, Fumito, specifically,
will be coming for us.
We need to find the Tower's base
before they neutralize ours.
Everyone, bear that in mind.
Right.
You make a prisoner out
of everyone you meet.
At least that's
what the rumors say.
Well, they're wrong.
I don't do anything.
Ask, and it shall
be given to you.
Seek and find.
Knock and the door shall open.
That's what we're promised.
Just ask the right question.
And yet, we humans
are still forced
to find the answers ourselves...
Tell me.
Do you know what
your answer is, Saya?
I can't believe
you got this for me.
I just poured some of
what was already there.
Well, thank you.
Didn't you want any?
It wasn't for me.
That's not true.
Mister Mogari made it.
He said it was his way
of thanking all of us
for the work we've been doing.
He wanted to do something
for everyone, including you.
You aren't going to rest?
I have a feeling I'm
really close to finding them.
So I can't sleep, not yet.
See, this is kind of like my
version of the power you have.
Hacking is my weapon.
I understand.
What's going on?
I found it, Saya.
The Tower's headquarters.
You're sure it's the
Tokyo Bay Breakwater,
'cause that seems weird.
She's sure.
You should have seen
her; it was amazing.
The way she dodges walls
and pursues stuff
is almost godlike.
Well, then why
didn't you wake me up?
I enjoy godlike things.
I don't understand how;
there's nothing out there.
Well, not from an
address search, no.
But when you look at the
area from an aerial view,
it's a completely
different story.
Where?
I don't see anything.
They put false data
on the satellite image,
but all you have
to do is remove that.
Watch.
That's crazy!
Good job.
She truly is a gifted hacker.
Saya.
Are you ready to face Fumito?
I can't believe they
hid something this big.
Those Tower guys are good.
And we still managed to find it.
Guess that makes us better. Huh?
I would say that it does.
Um, about me not going with you.
You sure?
I'm sure.
I need you to help me from here.
If you go, then you'll die.
But Saya, what about you?
I'll be fine.
You've seen the truth.
Remember that.
Most injuries won't stop me.
Don't you have a
weapon to use, anyway?
Yeah, you're right.
And I still have to find my dad.
All we can do is support,
but we'll be here.
You can count on us, and you
ladies are ready, too, right?
Definitely; we're both
ready and standing by.
If something happens,
let us know.
We'll hold out as
long as we're able to.
If it gets bad, do
yourself a favor and run.
Thank you.
Okay, we're changing positions.
Where's the target?
Hey, it's goin' down.
Fuji.
Make sure we don't
lose sound with her, okay?
On it.
Hey, Tsuki.
Can you see what's
going on inside there?
Gimmie a sec.
Got the frequency!
Can you tell how
many there are?
Sure thing!
Saya, we have their
numbers and positions.
The farther you ascend,
the more they carry radios.
Fumito must be on the top floor.
You're wrong.
Fumito knows about things
that aren't entirely human.
Dangerous things
that don't use radios.
Where are the Elder Bairns?
What area has the fewest people?
The basement.
Then get me there.
Just a sec.
Nice trick, you bastard.
Saya?
Keep going.
Right.
I will never let you
reach Mister Nanahara.
You are pathetic, Saya Kisaragi.
Do not call me that name!
I have the route
to the basement!
From the elevators.
Take the door on the
right, far in the back.
Saya?
Kuto.
That should be enough.
Of course.
Thank you, Mister Nanahara.
It's time.
You will now witness the power
of the one who
will rule the world!
Behold.
Fumito!
I can't tell what's going on.
Get her out of there, Mana.
Listen, Saya, run
straight in front of you!
Then take the exit just ahead!
Good job.
Take your next left.
You'll be able to reach
the lowest lever from there.
Saya?
I'm fine.
I made it.
Good evening, Saya.
How are you?
What have you done?
What is this?
I don't. Stop.
Fumito.
Saya!
Saya, what's wrong?!
No!
Saya!
Fuji!
It's no use!
I've lost the connection!
I'd prefer no interruptions,
now that we're finally together.
I had to shut down your radios.
I'm sure you understand.
I'm delighted
you came to see me.
Although, I do wish you hadn't
broken so many of my things.
Yes.
It's finally taken
effect, Kuroto.
I brought the
amount you requested.
It took long enough.
All that running,
and she's only down now.
What a freak.
The coffee.
No.
Will you tell me
now why I personally
had to put that
stuff in her coffee?
Your young assistants
are just so good.
They'd never imagine slipping
something bad into her drink.
Luckily, I had you.
"Good" is not your forte.
This doesn't work on humans.
It's for you and
you alone, my Saya.
You must be worried about
your little Sirrut friends.
They are gifted, aren't they?
In fact, you can thank them for
getting you to where you are.
You were too suspicious
to eat anything.
But you let your guard down.
With that coffee.
Who'd have imagined?
Those kids were useful.
Don't get the wrong idea:
I never lied to them per se.
All I did was just
use them a little.
Sirrut originated as
a small internet group.
They were full of all those
"more freedom in Tokyo" types.
I know what you're thinking;
I should've just ignored them.
But you can never predict
what someone on the internet
might do to people like us,
so I decided to keep
an eye on them myself.
I offered financial support and
became their mentor and patron.
They believed any and
every bit of information
I 'leaked' to them, which
made things very easy.
I was impressed with myself.
Eventually, they found
fascinating leads about you,
resulting in your
arrival in my mansion.
I admit, I never expected
Mana would find this place.
She is a talented girl.
But, I did immediately
let Fumito know
they had found him.
So then.
What's next, dear cousin?
You do have a plan, yes?
I still don't get why you spend
so much effort on that thing.
I spend effort
because Saya is special.
Yes, I suppose she must be.
You did dedicate all
of our resources to her.
Our arrangement was to
kill each other's families,
take control over The Tower,
and use the power we had stolen,
to seize control of
the world, correct?
Oh, yes.
That's right.
It's not over.
There's still more
glory, money, influence.
I do not crave such things.
My desire has
always been the world.
Of course, what was I thinking?
It's small, this world.
It really is quite small.
Isn't that right, Saya?
So this thing is
the world to you?
You let your guard down.
How sad.
You and your freak
will die here together.
I'll make it look as
though she killed you.
Then, everything will be mine.
That was terribly
rude, dear cousin.
How dare you judge!
You've always looked
down your nose at me.
And I've hated it!
No.
No!
And now, I'll take
back what I loaned to you.
Because you're ungrateful.
Fumito.
Can you feel her blood?
Watch him, Saya.
He is the Covenant in action.
All of that power you've
desired, dear cousin.
You will now have
the chance to feel.
Saya.
For generations, the
heads of the Mogari clan
have buried something.
Do you know where
they put the key
to controlling the
Elder Bairns?
It's hidden within them.
Your blood has power.
It is the sole thing that
can destroy the connection
we have with the Elder Bairns.
Fumito!
See, Saya?
It's as I thought.
Humans don't become it.
They are born to it.
You cannot kill humans.
You are not human.
The only things that
can satiate your hunger
are the Elder Bairns,
your own kind.
Did you know the number of
humans is always increasing,
but the number of Elder Bairns
has dropped dramatically.
There's hardly even a need
for the Shrovetide anymore.
Saya.
How old are you?
How many years?
How long will you live?
Does the Elder Bairns
decline concern you?
Do you worry at all
how you will survive
when they finally
become extinct?
It worries me.
I tried to create
Elder Bairns for you.
I used your blood,
and The Tower's magic.
But it didn't work.
No matter what I did.
They all ended up dying soon
after their transformation.
I did my best.
I experimented on
all types of people.
Practically anyone
I could get my hands on.
Mana, was it?
I saw the footage
from the Mogari mansion.
Her father was a reporter, yes?
He lasted longer than most...
But he ran away and died.
Not too long ago, in fact.
You knew him.
He was on the
same train you were.
Surely, you remember.
After all, you did kill him.
What the hell?
There's the true Saya.
In all her loveliness.
A reward for the victor.
This is the strongest
power that I can summon.
It's all for you, my, love.
Back then, all I could
do was run away from you.
Not now, Saya.
Is that an Elder Bairn?
Those eyes.
They're exactly as they were
when I shot you in the head.
So beautiful.
I want you, Saya.
Fumito!
Fumito.
Why did you do this?
Right here, Saya.
Fumito?
I told you.
It isn't easy.
I tried it on me
before anyone else.
I wanted to see, if I could
be like my beloved Saya.
I've been waiting for this.
To finally hold you.
Forgive me, Saya.
If I were still human.
Your curse would be lifted;
you would be free.
A reward for you, the victor.
And me?
I'll receive the
punishment as the loser.
You were supposed
to dodge that, Saya.
Now it feels like a reward.
And in the end, I am alone.
Always alone.
We can't see anything.
Cops are all over the place.
Right now they're only allowing
the emergency
vehicles to get through.
Yeah, we're stuck here, too.
We still can't get
ahold of Mister Mogari.
Um, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Most importantly,
I think we can all agree
what the youth really
need for growth is freedom.
Unnecessarily tying them down
will only invite rebellion.
Also, we must avoid
any circumstance
that would create
generational distrust...
So lady, how was your class?
Did you have fun?
Yeah.
I mean, I stayed the whole time.
Why don't you join a club?
Cause I'm not a nerd.
I have more fun here anyway.
Mana!
Hey, what's up?
I have to say,
I like how much
more relaxed things are
with this new governor.
At least the
internet restrictions
are lifted, you know?
The Youth Protection
Act is gone;
that's the most important thing.
Compared to back then,
this is heaven.
Almost heaven.
I wish Mister Mogari
was still here.
Cisnet was absorbed
by another company.
So, Seventh Heaven's executives
have all been replaced.
Even Fumito Nanahara
vanished from public life.
There's no telling
where Mister Mogari went,
but surely he's fine.
Oh, I'm sorry about that.
This got dark.
Sorry.
It's okay.
You know, thinking about it,
it's been like a
year and a half.
It's crazy.
I wonder.
Wonder what?
You do realize this is
all your fault, Matsuo!
How do you figure that?
You are such a brat!
Am not!
There they go again.
You think they'll get any better
when they get
married next month?
Nah, they'll never change.
I think that's why they work.
Hey, knock it off!
Can you two quit
fighting for once?
Okay.
Lucky for you, you're pretty.
Lucky for what?
You are such an idiot.
To be with you?
Never.
I wonder, why do I have the
feeling we'll see her again.