( theme music playing )
♪ CAN'T YOU SEE
THAT I AM A PIONEER? ♪
♪ UNLOCKING
THE GREATEST MYSTERIES ♪
♪ MY KEY IS A FEARLESS HEART
SO PURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ YOU CAN'T BE A HERO ♪
♪ HIDING UNDERNEATH YOUR BED ♪
♪ GOT TO LIVE THE LIFE ♪
♪ YOU CREATE INSIDE YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ SO I OPEN THE WINDOW ♪
♪ CAUGHT THE WIND ONE NIGHT ♪
♪ NOW I SAIL WITH THE BIRDS ♪
♪ IN THEIR FLIGHT ♪
♪ SOME WILL SAY ♪
♪ YOU'RE SAFER HERE ♪
♪ NEVER MIND THAT,
BE A PIONEER ♪
♪ CAN'T YOU SEE
THAT YOU ARE A PIONEER? ♪
♪ NOT ONE
OF THE ENDLESS TALKERS ♪
♪ WHO TELL YOU
THE SAME OLD RULES ♪
♪ YOU'VE HEARD BEFORE ♪
♪ WE WILL BE PIONEERS ♪
♪ FOREVERMORE. ♪
- ( rumbling )
- ( beeping )
- Female voice:
CAPTURE FIELD NORMAL.
250 PARSECS TO TARGET POINT.
- Male voice:
CARRYING THE WHOLE GALAXY.
MARVELOUS IS THE POWER
OF HER MAJESTY.
WHAT A FANTASTIC POWER.
WE'RE GOING OUT.
- Female: YES, SIR.
ADJUSTMENT OF THE FIELD
SPACE PARTICLES COMPLETED.
- THERE SEEMS
TO HAVE BEEN COMBAT AGAIN.
- ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS, DOCTOR?
OUR MISSION
HAS NOT BEEN COMPLETED YET.
- NO NEED TO BOTHER.
I DON'T NEED
TO DO IT PERSONALLY.
LEAVE IT TO THE MACHINES.
THAT'LL BE FUN.
I HAVE JUST RETURNED.
- Male voice:
I UNDERSTAND YOUR MISSION
HAS NOT BEEN COMPLETED YET,
DR. CLAY.
- WELL, NO.
BUT I HAVE COME
TO MAKE AN EXTREMELY
IMPORTANT REPORT TODAY, D3, SIR.
- OH.  MORE IMPORTANT
THAN THE REPORT
ON THE MISSION ASSIGNED TO YOU,
I SUPPOSE.
- I HEAR THAT LADY TOKIMI
IS LOOKING FOR A CERTAIN PERSON.
- HMM?
- AND THAT THE ORDER WAS
GIVEN TO SOMEONE ELSE
TO SEARCH
FOR THAT CERTAIN PERSON.
- I WILL NOT INQUIRE
AS TO HOW
YOU CAME TO KNOW THAT.
- I DEMAND AN INTERVIEW
WITH LADY TOKIMI.
- LADY TOKIMI IS RIGHT HERE.
- HUH?
- HOWEVER,
THERE IS NO GUARANTEE
THAT THE CERTAIN PERSON
YOU KNOW
IS THE ONE OUR LADY
IS LOOKING FOR, IS THERE?
- THAT'S EXACTLY WHY I NEED
TO SEE LADY TOKIMI, TO CONFIRM!
- CONFIRMATION CAN BE GIVEN
BY ME.
YES, MY LADY.
AS YOU WILL.
YOU MAY MAKE YOUR REPORT
TO LADY TOKIMI.
- YOU ARE TOO KIND.
BUT WILL YOU TELL ME
WHERE LADY TOKIMI IS?
- YOU DON'T SEEM
TO REALIZE YET.
VERY WELL.
YOU MAY SEE HER
WITH YOUR OWN EYES.
LADY TOKIMI WILL DESCEND
AND REVEAL HERSELF.
- WH-- WHAT?
- HIGH-LEVEL DIMENSION REACTION.
- OH!
- D3: NOW YOU MAY SPEAK.
WHATEVER YOU HAVE TO SAY,
SAY IT.
- OH!
YOU-- YOUR MAJESTY.
LADY TOKIMI, YOU DO
ME TOO MUCH HONOR
BY SEEING ME IN
PERSON LIKE THIS.
I BRING YOU NEWS.
- ABOUT WASHU?
- HUH?
- VERY WELL.
I'LL LEAVE IT ALL TO YOU.
SUCCEED,
AND I MAY GRANT YOUR WISH.
BUT WE SHALL
HAVE THE RULING RIGHTS
OVER ONE ENTIRE GALAXY.
- OH-- WHAT?
- IT IS LADY TOKIMI'S WISH
TO MEET
WITH LADY WASHU IN PERSON.
BUT BE SURE
NOT TO HURT HER.
- YES, SIR.
THANK YOU, SIR.
( laughs )
SOON AN ENTIRE GALAXY
WILL BE MINE.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
- I AM SCARED.
- YOU CAN'T BE.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
HAVE SUCH EMOTIONS, SO DON'T.
MAYBE YOUR MEMORY
HAS NOT BEEN COMPLETELY ERASED
FROM THE LAST ASSIGNMENT.
- IT IS ERASED COMPLETELY, SIR.
HOWEVER, I CAN'T HELP MYSELF
FROM SHAKING ALL OVER
JUST LOOKING AT LADY TOKIMI.
- WELL, IT CERTAINLY
WASN'T YOUR FIRST TIME
WITNESSING A HIGH-LEVEL
DIMENSION OF LIFE FORM.
- WITH ANYONE ELSE,
I CAN MAKE LOGICAL
COMPUTATION OF EXISTENCE,
BUT LADY TOKIMI--
LADY TOKIMI IS--
IS--
- WHAT ABOUT LADY TOKIMI?
- HER VERY EXISTENCE
IS IMPOSSIBLE,
EVEN THOUGH SHE WAS PRESENT
RIGHT THERE IN FRONT OF US.
AND YET, NO SUCH INFORMATION
IS FOUND ANYWHERE
IN THE DATA BANK.
- NONSENSE!
THE ABSOLUTELY RING
OF THEORETICAL SYSTEM
IS ESTABLISHED HERE
IN THE DATA BANK.
ABSOLUTELY EVERYTHING
IS KNOWN HERE,
EVEN THOUGH WE ARE NOT ABLE
TO COMPREHEND IT ALL.
FOR THE MOMENT,
YOU'D BETTER NOT INVESTIGATE
THE MATTER ANY FURTHER.
- I UNDERSTAND.
- YOU MUST CONCENTRATE
ON THE TASK AT HAND.
I HAVE A LOT FOR YOU TO DO
FROM NOW ON.
- ( birds singing )
- Sasami: ONIONS--
- Mihoshi: ONIONS HERE.
- BELL PEPPERS.
- BELL PEPPERS HERE.
- CARROTS.
- CARROTS HERE.
- SALT.
- SALT HERE.
- ( meows )
- PEPPER.
- PEPPER HERE.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- NO, YOU CAN'T EAT YET!
- ( meows )
- OH!
- OH MY.
- ( gulping )
THIS IS THE LIFE!
- ( birds scurrying )
- WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WANT?
- RYOKO.
- THAT'S MY NAME.
( grunting )
AHHH!
- HA HA HA HA.
- HEY!
YOU LET ME GO NOW!
HA HA HA!
SERVES YOU RIGHT.
( laughs )
- OH, YOU-- YOU HURT ME.
IT'S CRUEL OF YOU TO MAKE A SCAR
ON A WOMAN'S FACE.
- LOOKS LIKE ME.
IS THAT MY CLONE?
- ( voice changing ) I'M GOING
TO BORROW YOUR BODY AND MEMORY.
- OH, THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK!
( grunting )
- Dr. Clay: I ASSUME YOU HAVE
COMPLETED DUPLICATION PROCESS?
- YES, DOCTOR.
- LOOK AT THIS. ( laughs )
EVEN WASHU WON'T BE ABLE
TO TELL THE DIFFERENCE.
- ( computer beeping )
- HMM?
THIS REACTION IS--
- AH!
- WHAT?
WHAT IS THE MEANING OF THIS?
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING
THAT CAN'T BE DUPLICATED
BY THE POWER ENDOWED IN ME BY
LADY TOKIMI. IT'S INCONCEIVABLE.
- AND THERE'S NO ANSWER
FOUND IN RYOKO'S
MEMORY EITHER, DOCTOR.
- WASHU WILL DETECT ME
IF I STAY LONGER.
IF WE CAN'T DUPLICATE THE JEWEL,
WE HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE
BUT TO TAKE HERS.
WE'LL DEAL WITH THE OTHERS
AFTER WE CAPTURE WASHU.
- UNDERSTOOD, DOCTOR.
- ( groans )
- IT SEEMS TO HAVE WORKED
THIS TIME.
HOWEVER... HMM.
- ( grunting )
- I WAS GOING TO DISPOSE OF HER
ON THE SPOT.
BUT SHE MAY BE WORTH
TAKING TIME TO STUDY.
- AH!
( grunting )
OH, TENCHI!
- WHAT THE--
- Washu:
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU, TENCHI?
- I-- I THOUGHT
I HEARD SOMEONE CALL ME.
- YOU'RE HEARING THINGS.
- AH!
- ( scanning )
- HMM.
BY THE WAY,
DID YOU HAVE ANY LUCK?
- NO, AND BELIEVE ME,
I'VE TRIED SEVERAL TIMES
SINCE THE COMBAT
WITH KAGATO, BUT--
- YOU COULDN'T
GENERATE LIGHT HAWK WINGS AGAIN?
HMM.
- IT WAS PROBABLY
JUST AN ACCIDENT,
I GUESS.
OR CREATED
BY TSUNAMI'S POWER.
- I DON'T THINK SO, TENCHI.
THOSE WINGS WERE
DEFINITELY GENERATED BY YOU.
NOW LISTEN UP.
YOU WERE COMPLETELY BLOCKED
FROM ANY OUTSIDE POWER
INCLUDING TSUNAMI'S
AT THAT TIME, AND YOUR BODY--
- Sasami: TENCHI!
- HMM?
- ( gasps )
TENCHI, WASHU?
IT'S MEALTIME.
- GREAT!
I'M STARVING!
- HMM.
WELL, PROBABLY IT'S ALL MENTAL.
NORMALLY YOU DON'T NEED THINGS
LIKE LIGHT HAWK WINGS
IN YOUR DAILY LIFE.
- MMM, UH, TRIVIAL QUESTION,
BUT DID I REALLY
NEED TO TAKE MY CLOTHES OFF?
- ( laughs ) NO!
- OH, I KNEW IT.
- OH, I AM STARVING.
- TENCHI, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU DON'T SEEM TO BE HURT,
BUT--
- OH, I'M FINE.
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- OH NO, NOTHING.
( laughs )
- GO ON, TENCHI, EAT.
AND EAT A LOT.
- HEY, WHERE'S RYOKO?
- RYOKO WENT OUT A WHILE AGO
TO BUY SOME SAKE.
SHE SHOULD BE BACK
ANY MINUTE NOW.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- SHE PROBABLY DRANK
IT ALL ON THE WAY
AND FELL ASLEEP,
AS USUAL.
- OH MY,
NOW THE RICE IS GETTING COLD.
- ( meows )
- DON'T BOTHER WAITING FOR HER.
LET'S JUST EAT.
JUST GIVE HER THE LEFTOVERS
AND SHE
WON'T KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
- WELL, I THINK
I'LL GO LOOK FOR HER.
- OH, YOU WILL?
- ( Zero laughing )
WASHU--
SHE IS NOT AWARE OF ANYTHING.
WELL THEN, I'LL TAKE YOU
TO THE DOCTOR NOW.
- OH, RYOKO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU'RE KEEPING EVERYONE WAITING,
YOU KNOW.
- OH, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHY IS MY HEART BEATING
SO FAST ALL OF A SUDDEN?
AND MY FACIAL CAPILLARY VESSELS
ARE OPEN ALL THE WAY.
TENCHI MASAKI.
I'VE KNOWN HIM
SINCE I DUPLICATED THE DATA,
BUT I HAD NO IDEA
ABOUT THIS KIND OF REACTION.
- RYOKO, UH--
- YES?
- WHAT--
- OH!
TENCHI, I WENT TO BUY IT
SO THAT WE COULD DRINK IT
TOGETHER.
- DRINK IT TOGETHER?
- IT'S LIKE INDIRECTLY KISSING.
- HEY!  WHAT ARE YOU--
- OH!
- DOH!  MISS AYEKA!
- ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
- HUH?
- HAVE IT YOUR WAY.  HA!
- AH.
- RYOKO, GO EAT.
GO EAT.
- MMM.
WHAT IS IT
ABOUT THAT BOY?
WHAT'S THIS SURGE OF EMOTION
THAT'S FLARED UP IN ME?
IS IT THAT BOY
WHO'S CAUSED IT?
OH!
- HMM?
- OOOH.
- All: HMM.  MY!
- ( ducks calling )
- ( meows )
- ( pulsating )
- WOW, WHAT'S THIS?
- YOU DON'T TOUCH THAT!
- OH.
- ( beeping )
- HMM.
NOW STRETCH THE FACE.
AND CLOSE YOUR EYE.
AND CLOSE YOUR OTHER EYE.
AND OPEN YOUR MOUTH--
WIDER!
OH, THAT'S GOOD!
AND SMILE.
- WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
- I'M JUST
CHECKING YOUR LIFE-FORM DATA
FROM THE TIME YOU CAME
TO LIVE IN THIS HOUSE.
YOU KNOW,
SCIENTIFIC STUFF.
BE A GOOD GIRL
AND SIT STILL FOR ME.
- OH.
- RESPONSIVE, AREN'T WE?
WORTHY OF A PRINCESS
OF PLANET JURAI.
- MISS WASHU!
- HEY! EASY. JUST KIDDING,
JUST KIDDING.
- SO THAT'S WASHU,
THE GENIUS SCIENTIST
EVEN MY DOCTOR
CAN'T COMPETE WITH.
- Washu: HEY, NEXT!
RYOKO, DEAR!
- HA!  WHY SHOULD I BOTHER
WITH SUCH A THING, HUH?
- SIT DOWN.
- ALL RIGHT.
- ( pulsating )
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S THIS?
JUST AS I SUSPECTED.
- HMM?
WHAT IS IT YOU SUSPECTED?
- I SUSPECTED
YOUR BREASTS ARE SAGGING.
- SAGGING?!
- ( laughs )
- HUH?
- HMM?
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- OKAY.
- STOP IT, BUBBLEHEAD! I TOLD
YOU NOT TO PLAY WITH THAT!
- ( both squealing )
- Dr. Clay:
ZERO, CAPTURE WASHU.
- I'M LEAVING!
- OH, TENCHI, PLEASE,
IT'LL JUST BE A MINUTE,
ONLY TO EXAMINE YOU
A LITTLE BIT.
- BUT I HAVE TO GO
TO THE FIELD NOW.
- YOU PROMISED YOU WOULD BE
MY GUINEA PIG, DIDN'T YOU?
- NOW THERE'S A CONVERSATION
I DON'T RECALL.
- MMM!
TENCHI, DARLING, PLEASE?
- MAYBE LATER, WHEN I COME BACK.
I GOTTA GO, OKAY?
- OOH, YOU MEAN THING!
- ( laughs )
- Tenchi: LITTLE WASHU?!
DO YOU KNOW
WHERE MY GLOVES ARE?
- OH!
HOW'D THEY GET HERE?
- I KNEW IT WAS YOU, WASHU.
- ( both laugh )
- OH, AND BY THE WAY,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
HELLO?
- Both: OH, WELL.
- DAMN WASHU!
SHE WON'T FALL
INTO OUR HANDS VERY EASILY.
FUNNY, SHE CALLED THAT BOY
HER GUINEA PIG.
HMM.
- WELL.
- RYOKO?
ISN'T TODAY THE DAY
THAT YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO DO THE LAUNDRY?
- OH, IS IT?
- DID YOU FORGET?
- WELL, THEN WHY DON'T YOU
JOIN ME, TENCHI?
- ( grunts )
- ( alarm sounding )
- ( groans )
MY COTTON! WHAT AM I GOING
TO DO? IT'S AN EMERGENCY.
( sighs )
TENCHI?  OH.
I GOT AN EMERGENCY CALL,
SO I GUESS I'M GOING
TO BE OUT FOR A WHILE.
- WELL, TAKE CARE, MIHOSHI.
- OH, IT'S SO SWEET OF YOU
TO SAY THAT.
SHOULDN'T TAKE TOO LONG.
I'LL BE BACK BY DINNERTIME.
AHHHHH!
I'M WET!
- MIHOSHI, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN
ALL THIS TIME?
I'VE BEEN SENDING
SIGNALS REGULARLY
TO YOU SINCE YESTERDAY.
- OH, WET! YUCK!
- MIHOSHI!
- HMM?  YES?
- AN EXTREMELY IMPORTANT MESSAGE
WAS RECEIVED FROM HEADQUARTERS.
- I WONDER WHAT IT IS.
YUKINOJYO,
PLEASE PLAY THE MESSAGE FOR ME.
- ROGER.
- AH, IT'S ME.
THIS IS PROBABLY NEWS
THAT YOU'VE HEARD ALREADY.
THE NEW GALAXY POLICE
BATTLESHIP SHONGA
WAS ROBBED,
AND BY SOMEONE UNKNOWN.
NOW WE HAVE A REPORT
THAT THE BATTLESHIP WAS DETECTED
IN THE AREA YOU ARE IN NOW.
- ARGHHH!
- ANYTHING HAPPENS, MIHOSHI,
YOU CONTACT HEADQUARTERS
IMMEDIATELY.
YOU GOT THAT?  MAKE SURE
YOU CONTACT HEADQUARTERS.
REPEAT-- SIMPLY CONTACT
HEADQUARTERS, NOTHING MORE.
OVER.
- ROGER!
FIRST CLASS DETECTIVE MIHOSHI
IS ON THE WAY TO INVESTIGATE.
YUKINOJYO?
- YES, MA'AM, MIHOSHI?
- EEEK!
SHHH!
- ( laughs )
- ARGH!
- LITTLE WASHU? DINNER'S READY.
- OH, IT'S SO LATE ALREADY?
AND WHAT DO YOU WANT,
LITTLE RYOKO?
- UH, I, UH...
I JUST THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
NEED MY HELP WITH SOMETHING.
- ALL RIGHT.
THEN YOU CAN PUT THIS
AND THIS AND THIS DATA
IN FOR ME.
THANKS, RYOKO.
- ( sighs )
- RYOKO, DINNERTIME.
- OH!
OH, YES,
I'LL BE RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- ( laughs )
EH, DON'T WORRY.
SHE'S OKAY.
- ( sighs )
( moans )
- I DON'T THINK MIHOSHI
IS GOING TO MAKE IT,
NOT FOR DINNER, ANYWAY.
RYOKO?
RYOKO!
DON'T YOU LIKE THE FOOD?
- HUH?
OH, NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S DELICIOUS.
UH, WHY IS EVERYBODY
STARING AT ME?
- ABOUT TIME FOR A TEA BREAK.
OH!
RYO-OHKI!
OH!  OH, WAIT,
YOU HAVE TO WASH IT FIRST!
COME BACK HERE!
- MMM.  WHAT--
WHAT NOW?
- WON'T YOU TAKE A BATH WITH ME?
COME ON, LET'S GO!
- WHOA!
I DON'T WANT TO.
HEY, LET ME GO!
- WILL YOU LISTEN
TO YOUR MOM FOR ONCE?
- HMM, PERFECT.
IMAGINE-- SHE'S GIVING ME
THE OPPORTUNITY
TO BE ALONE WITH HER.
SCRUB YOURSELF WELL
WHILE YOU CAN.
- COME HERE NOW,
MY LITTLE RYOKO.
WE'RE ALL ALONE NOW.
- OH.
- YOU SHOULD KEEP YOUR BODY
NICE AND CLEAN
OR YOU'LL DISAPPOINT TENCHI.
- UH...
- THAT'S A GOOD GIRL,
LITTLE RYOKO.
HMM?
HMM.
BY THE WAY, TENCHI WAS
TALKING ABOUT YOU, RYOKO.
- WHAT?
ABOUT ME?
- MM-HMM.
HE WAS COMPLAINING
THAT YOU HAVEN'T
CLEANED THE TOILET YET TODAY.
- I SEE.
- ( laughs )
- ( flushing )
- WOW, WHAT A SURPRISE!
YOU MEAN YOU VOLUNTEERED
TO CLEAN THE TOILET?
- WHAT?
BUT I THOUGHT IT WAS MY TURN.
- NO.
YOU'RE IN CHARGE
OF CLEANING THE YARD.
I BELIEVE IT'S WASHU'S TURN
TO CLEAN THE TOILET TODAY.
- HUH?
- BUT I'M IMPRESSED, RYOKO.
- UH...
( laughs )
THAT DARN WASHU.  SHE'S A CHEAT,
THAT'S WHAT SHE IS.
BUT IT WORKED OUT FINE
FOR ME.
- Dr. Clay: ZERO?
- I GOT COMPLIMENTS FROM TENCHI.
- ZERO!
- ( laughs )
- ( gasps ) DOCTOR.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
YOU HAVE A MISSION. YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO BE CAPTURING WASHU!
- I'M SORRY, DR. CLAY.
- MMM!
I HAVE BEEN WATCHING YOU
AND I SEE THAT BOY CALLED TENCHI
IS DISTRACTING YOU
FROM DOING YOUR JOB.
- OH, NO, NOT REALLY, DOCTOR.
- ZERO?
- OH!
- YOU GOT IT?
- YES, SIR.
- RYOKO?  RYOKO?
RYOKO.
RYOKO?
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- HMM?  OH, IT'S ONLY YOU,
RYO-OHKI.
- ( meows )
- I AM A LOYAL SERVANT
OF THE DOCTOR.
AND THE ORDER
GIVEN TO ME WAS--
- ( whimpers )
- IF THAT BOY IS IN YOUR WAY,
YOU MUST OBEY ME.
ELIMINATE HIM.
- ( grunts )
AHHH!
- ( Dr. Clay laughing )
( laughter continues )
- ( theme music playing )
♪ I AM LONELY
LIKE THE MOON ♪
♪ YOU ARE FAR AWAY
AS THE EARTH ♪
♪ THOUGH YOU SAY
I LIGHT YOUR THOUGHTS ♪
♪ NIGHT AFTER NIGHT ♪
♪ SOON YOU FORGET ♪
♪ WE ARE DRIFTING
IN THIS DANCE ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL YOU
CIRCLE MY HEART ♪
♪ KEEPING SUCH
A GRACEFUL DISTANCE ♪
♪ SO CLOSE
BUT SOMEHOW APART ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I CRY FOR YOU ♪
♪ KNOWING
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WHISPER
TO THE STARS ♪
♪ UP IN THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT I WANT TO FIND
A WAY TO YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ KISSING THE SUN
WHEN MORNING COMES ♪
♪ YOU DON'T SEEM
TO COUNT THE HOURS ♪
♪ WHEN WE ARE NOT TOGETHER ♪
♪ I'VE SEEN THE TENDER FIRE
IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ YET WHEN I'M GONE,
YOU CARRY ON ♪
♪ I FLOAT IN THIS EMPTINESS ♪
♪ TILL AT LAST
LOVE RETURNS ♪
♪ WITH THE NIGHT ♪
♪ AND THE LONELY MOON. ♪
- Sasami: OH, NO,
TENCHI IS DEAD AGAIN.
WHERE'S RYOKO--
THE REAL RYOKO?
YOU'LL FIND THE ANSWERS
IN OUR NEXT EPISODE,
"ZERO RYOKO."
THE TWELFTH EPISODE OF
THE TENCHI SERIES.