( theme music playing )
- ( birds, insects chirping )
- ( zapping )
- Kamidake:
ALL SYSTEMS ACTIVATED.
UNLOCK THE TIME FREEZE NOW.
ALL SYSTEMS SYNCHRONIZED
TO BREECH STANDARD TIME.
- WHAT PLANET IS THIS?
- Azaka: COLONIZED PLANET
NUMBER 0-3-1-5, EARTH.
- THEN THIS IS WHERE
MY BROTHER YOSHO IS.
- Kamidake: NO, WHAT WE DETECTED
FROM THIS PLANET IS RYOKO.
- HUH?
NOT THAT WOMAN!
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
- Azaka: WE HAVE YET
TO DETECT YOSHO'S SHIP.
BUT HE WAS IN PURSUIT
OF RYOKO.
LOGICALLY,
IT WOULD FOLLOW THEN--
- I SEE.  THAT WOMAN
AND RYO-OHKI MUST BE CAUGHT
AND TRIED FORMALLY
BY OUR PLANET JURAI
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- Azaka:
PRINCESS AYEKA,
UNFORTUNATELY, ALL OF RYOKO'S
CRIMES WILL BE CANCELED
BY STATUTE OF LIMITATIONS
AT GALAXY STANDARD TIME
0-0-4-3-2,
OR IN FIVE SECONDS.
- HMM?
WHAT?
- ( beeping )
( tone sounding )
- Azaka: AS OF THIS MOMENT,
THE STATUTE OF LIMITATIONS
HAS TAKEN EFFECT,
AND RYOKO'S GALAXY WANTED FILE
HAS BEEN DESTROYED.
- DESTROYED?!
ANSWER ME, WHY IS IT?
- THE STATUTE OF LIMITATIONS
IS BASED ON DECISIONS
MADE BY THE HOLY COUNCIL
OF PLANET JURAI.
- THAT IS NOT
WHAT I HAVE ASKED.
I WANT TO KNOW WHY THAT WOMAN
IS NOT SOUGHT FOR ALL ETERNITY.
- THE STATUTE OF LIMITATIONS
IS BASED ON DECISIONS
MADE BY THE HOLY COUNCIL
OF THE PLANET JURAI--
- NEVER MIND.
THE ONLY CLUE LEFT TO US
IS THAT WOMAN.
WE MUST CAPTURE HER
AT ANY COST.
- BUT THE STATUTE
OF LIMITATIONS--
- THIS IS AN ORDER.
WE WILL THINK OF A REASON.
- Kamidake: YES, MA'AM!
- GOOD.
NOW PREPARE FOR DESCENT.
- Azaka: ANTI-AIR GUARD,
STORMING LEVEL FOUR.
- BEWARE, MY DEAREST YOSHO.
PLEASE BEWARE.
- ( groaning )
HOW COULD--
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
- NOW I WANT YOUR BALLS,
PLEASE.
- WHAT?!  NO WAY.
THEY'RE MINE AND I'M GOING
TO HANG ON TO THEM.
- OH, YOU NUMBSKULL!
I MEAN THE THREE JEWELS
ON YOUR SWORD.
OTHERWISE,
I CAN'T CONTROL RYO-OHKI.
- RYO-OHKI?
- OH, DON'T TELL ME
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
IT'S THE OTHER DEMON
IN THE LEGEND, YOU DIMWIT.
- SO THAT MEANS IF I GIVE
THE JEWELS BACK TO YOU,
THE DEMON WILL COME
BACK TO LIFE?  FORGET IT.
- NO "IF" ABOUT IT.
GIVE 'EM TO ME.
- NO WAY!  YOU MADE THIS MESS
ALL BY YOURSELF.
YOU THINK I WANT TO DEAL WITH
ANOTHER MONSTER FLYING AROUND
WHEN YOU'RE
ALREADY BLOWING THINGS UP?
JEEZ, THAT'S THE LAST THING
I WANT TO SEE!
OH!
- ARE YOU SURE?
BECAUSE THE ONE APPROACHING US
RIGHT NOW IS EVEN WORSE.
- HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- JUST GIVE ME THE SWORD.
I WANT IT AND I WANT IT NOW.
- ( grunting )
- HA!
- OH!
- ( laughing )
- AH!
( straining )
- OW!  OW!  OWW!
DAMN IT!
OH!
- AHH, SO YOU
CAN'T TOUCH THIS THING, CAN YOU?
- UH...
- HEY, BE QUIET. WHAT'S GOING
ON UP THERE, TENCHI?
THESE KIDS TODAY,
I TELL YOU.
I DON'T KNOW...
OH MY GOD!
OOH, AND I WORRIED ABOUT HIM
BEING TOO SHY WITH WOMEN.
( laughs ) NOW HE'S GONE AND
SNEAKED ONE INTO HIS ROOM.
IF I WERE HIS MOTHER, I'D FIND
SOME EXCUSE TO BARGE IN,
BUT AS HIS FATHER, IT'S MY
DUTY TO RESPECT HIS PRIVACY.
- PLEASE GIVE THEM BACK.
I BEG YOU.
- WELL,
NOW I REALLY CAN'T DO THAT.
- PLEASE, I'M BEGGING YOU.
- OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
BUT ONLY IF YOU'LL TELL ME
WHAT'S APPROACHING US.
- OH, SHE'S THE DEVIL.
- HUH?
- SHE'S LIKE A DEVIL.
- SHE'S SO DANGEROUS AND MEAN.
SHE'LL FIRE AT YOU
WITHOUT EVEN GIVING YOU A TEENY
WEENY LITTLE CHANCE TO EXPLAIN.
- ( sneezes )
HUH?
BEGIN THE CAPTURE PROCESS
AS SOON AS WE ARRIVE.
AND YOU MUST REFRAIN
FROM FIRING.
- Kamidake: YES, MA'AM.
- Azaka: WE WILL SOON
ARRIVE AT OUR DESTINATION.
- WELL, IT'S VERY SIMPLE.
WE'LL TALK TO THIS PERSON,
AND WE'LL JUST TRY
TO SETTLE MATTERS PEACEFULLY.
- HMM.
- MM-MM.
- NOT A GOOD IDEA, HUH?
IS SHE REALLY THAT BAD?
- YES.
LISTEN TO ME,
WE NEED TO WAKE UP RYO-OHKI NOW.
- DON'T TELL ME
WE'RE GOING TO FIGHT.
- NO, WE'LL RUN AWAY.
- HUH?
- YES, IT'S MY DUTY
TO RESPECT HIS PRIVACY,
BUT ALSO MY DUTY TO RECORD
MY SON'S DEVELOPMENT IN SEX--
I MEAN, LIFE.
OH, MY WIFE IN HEAVEN!
YOU SHOULD SEE
HOW YOUR SON HAS GROWN.
WHAT?  OH-OH!
AAH!  HONEY?
IS THAT YOU?
- Ayeka: RYOKO, COME OUT!
- WHAA!
- DAMN, I KNEW IT.
SHE'S HERE ALREADY.
- HUH?
- RYOKO!
RYOKO, YOU MUST COME OUT.
I KNOW THAT YOU ARE IN THERE.
YOU CANNOT GET AWAY FROM ME NOW.
ARE YOU SURE THIS IS ON?
- Kamidake: YES, MA'AM.
- WELL THEN,
WHAT IS SHE DOING?
OH, NEVER MIND.
I WANT YOU
TO FIRE A SHOT NEARBY.
- Azaka: I THOUGHT WE WERE
TO REFRAIN FROM FIRE.
- THAT'S AN ORDER.
- ( grunting )
- I TOLD YOU.
- WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO NOW?
- HMM.
WELL, FOR STARTERS,
WHY DON'T YOU STAND UP?
NOW POINT THE SWORD HILT
TOWARD ME
AND PRAY TO HAVE THE JEWELS
RETURNED TO ME.
- THAT'S IT?
THAT'S ALL I DO?
- THAT'S ALL.
- HMM.
- ( buzzing )
- ( trilling )
- HUH?
- ( sighs )
ARGH!
WHAT-- WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU ONLY GAVE ME ONE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- HUH?
( laughs )
WELL, THAT'S OKAY.
COME, RYO-OHKI.
AWAKEN.
- ( screeching )
( meowing )
- COME!
- ( meowing )
- Azaka:
RYO-OHKI IS HERE.
- Ayeka: THERE YOU ARE,
YOU HEINOUS CRIMINAL BATTLESHIP.
ATTACK THAT SHIP.
FIRE NOW!
- WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SHE'S TRYING
TO BLOW UP MY HOUSE!
- LET'S GO, TENCHI.
- OH, WHY ME?
OH!
- OKAY, RYO-OHKI,
LET'S MAKE OUR GETAWAY!
- ( squealing )
- YES, THIS IS THE FEELING.
OH, IT'S GOOD TO BE MOVING
SO FREELY AGAIN.
- OH MY GOD.
MY HOUSE!
- SORRY, I DIDN'T HAVE TIME
TO WORRY ABOUT IT,
SO I SHRANK IT AND BROUGHT IT
ALONG WITH US, IF THAT'S OKAY.
- DAD!
- DAMN THAT WOMAN.
FIRE AT HER WHEN READY!
- AAH!
SEAL HER UP.
- HA!  AH! OH!
( screaming )
AAH!
- SHE CANNOT ESCAPE US.
AZAKA, KAMIDAKE, GO!
CAPTURE HER!
- Kamidake: YES, MA'AM.
- Azaka: YES.
- ( grunting )
DON'T GET NEAR.  STAY BACK.
- AAH!
- ( grunting )
GUARDIANS OF JURAI.
AAH!
- AAH!
HUH?
- AH!
- GET AWAY FROM ME!
RYOKO, SOMEBODY, HELP ME!
- IT'S BEEN A WHILE,
HASN'T IT, RYOKO?
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU
FOR SOME TIME.
I HAVE A QUESTION.
TELL ME, WHY DID THAT EARTHLING
HAVE THIS SWORD WITH HIM?
ANSWER ME!
- HMM?
- ( groaning )
- ( screaming, laughing )
STOP, STOP!
YOU'RE TICKLING ME!
- ENOUGH.
THIS SEEMS TO HAVE
AN OPPOSITE EFFECT ON YOU.
YOU'RE BEHAVING LIKE, UM,
WHAT'S THAT CALLED?
- Azaka: A MASOCHIST?
- OH, YES.
THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL IT.
- ACTUALLY, LITTLE PRINCESS,
I'M MORE OF A SADIST.
- OH MY!
DOES THAT MEAN YOU LIKE TO--
NEVER MIND,
THAT'S COMPLETELY UNIMPORTANT.
- ( chuckles )
- I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN.
WHY DID THAT YOUNG MAN
HAVE THIS SWORD?
- YOU BONEHEAD!
- WHAT?
- DON'T YOU FEEL IT
IN HIS BLOOD?
- YOU'RE NOT ANSWERING
MY QUESTION.
- BECAUSE THE SWORD IS HIS.
- DON'T BE SO RIDICULOUS.
YOU KNOW THIS SWORD
BELONGS TO MY BROTHER.
NOW WHERE IS HE?
WHERE IS MY BROTHER YOSHO?
- HALF-BROTHER, YOU MEAN.
AND YOU CAME ALL THIS WAY
JUST TO LOOK FOR HIM?  HMM!
THINGS MUST BE DULL
ON PLANET JURAI.
YOU ROYAL TYPES
MUST BE REALLY BORED.
- SILENCE, CRIMINAL!
HOW DARE YOU?
- WELL WELL!
- MY BROTHER'S DISAPPEARANCE
ALL STARTED BECAUSE OF YOU.
- OH, IS THAT WHAT HAPPENED?
- AH!
- OH!
( screaming )
STOP!  STOP, PLEASE!
YOU CAN STOP NOW!
- NOW ANSWER ME.
- TENCHI PROBABLY KNOWS MORE
ABOUT YOSHO THAN I DO.
GO TALK TO HIM.
- BUT WHY WOULD THIS SWORD
KNOW THE WHEREABOUTS
OF MY BROTHER?
- OH, YEAH, I FORGOT,
THE SWORD IS CALLED TENCHI TOO.
NO, I MEAN THE EARTHLING BOY.
HE'S CALLED TENCHI ALSO.
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
- PRINCESS AYEKA,
IT IS TIME FOR BED.
- LATER, I AM BUSY.
NOW GO AWAY.
- I CANNOT ALLOW THAT.
THE QUEEN
HAS GIVEN ME STRICT ORDERS.
- OH, VERY WELL.
AND TAKE HER OFF TO JAIL.
- BEDTIME, LITTLE GIRL.
SWEET DREAMS.
- ARGH!
- COME, PRINCESS, THIS WAY.
- ( belches )
- ( beeping )
- ( groans ) HMM?
WHERE AM I?
WHAT'S THIS PLACE?
HEY!  RYOKO!
WHERE DID SHE GO?
( grunting )
- ( buzzer sounding )
- AAH!
( grunts )
ARGH!
OH, YOU--
STOP IT!
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
JUST LET ME OUT!
- ( squeals )
- OH!
THAT DOES IT.
THIS CALLS
FOR SOME REAL ACTION.
ARGH!
TAKE THAT.
- Sasami:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WELL, I'M TRYING TO ESCAPE
FROM THIS STUPID LITTLE--
HUH?
- ( squealing )
- ( giggles )
- WHO-- WHO ARE YOU?
- MY NAME IS SASAMI.
SASAMI?
HAVE YOU BEEN KIDNAPPED ALSO?
- NO, YOU SILLY! ARE YOU
JOKING? THIS IS OUR SHIP.
- THIS IS YOUR SHIP?
YOU'RE AN ALIEN
FROM PLANET SASAMI?
- NO, YOU ARE SILLY!
I COME FROM THE PLANET JURAI.
- WHAT ABOUT THOSE WEIRD LOGS?
- ( laughs )
THEY'RE NOT REALLY LOGS.
THEY'RE GUARDIANS,
OUR SERVANTS.
- AW, MAN, WHAT A RELIEF.
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- OH, RIGHT, MY NAME'S TENCHI.
HOW DO YOU DO?
- HOW DO YOU DO?
WILL YOU PLAY A GAME WITH ME?
- HMM.
YOU LOOK JUST LIKE WE DO.
AH, THAT'S A CUTE PET.
- MM-HMM.
- AAH.
HEY, THAT LOOKS LIKE--
UH, HUH?  OH, IT'S GONE!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- OH, I HAD A SWORD
LIKE THAT ONE, BUT IT'S GONE.
- IT MUST HAVE--
- HMM.
- ( squeals )
- HEY, SASAMI,
COULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
COULD YOU RETURN
ME HOME RIGHT NOW?
I WAS BROUGHT HERE BY MISTAKE.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH ANYTHING.
- WELL, I'LL DO A FAVOR
FOR YOU,
IF YOU DO ME A FAVOR.
- ( sighs )
- MY DARLING AYEKA.
I MUST LEAVE HERE
TOMORROW MORNING
TO DO BATTLE
WITH A RAMPAGING CRIMINAL.
BUT DON'T WORRY,
I WILL DEFEAT THIS CRIMINAL
AND RETURN.
AND WHEN I COME BACK--
- WHEN YOU CAME BACK,
I WAS TO BECOME YOUR BRIDE.
BUT YOU NEVER RETURNED.
YOSHO.
( crying )
- MY SISTER'S ROOM
IS RIGHT OVER THERE.  SEE?
( laughs ) SHE'S ASLEEP NOW,
SO YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- YEAH, I THINK SO.
GO IN THERE AND GET HER
HEAD ORNAMENT, IS THAT RIGHT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- BUT WHY SHOULD I?
I MEAN, IT DOES BELONG TO HER,
DOESN'T IT?
- JUST GET IT.
- OKAY OKAY, I'LL GET IT.
JUST MAKE SURE
YOU REMEMBER YOUR PROMISE.
- UH-HUH.
- DON'T WORRY.
( panting )
- ( giggles )
- SORRY TO BARGE IN LIKE THIS.
EXCUSE ME.
EH?  OH.
OH, MAN, GIVE ME A BREAK!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO GET THAT OFF OF HER, HUH?
I-- HUH?
THE SWORD?
SHE'S GOT IT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
( grunting )
AH!
- ( moans )
YOSHO.  YOSHO.
- ( grunting )
COME ON.  AH...
COME ON.
- HUH?
WHAT?
- AH.
- ( screams )
- NO NO NO, LET ME EXPLAIN.
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
- ( screams )
- AZAKA!  KAMIDAKE!
- Both: YES, MA'AM!
- I WANT YOU TO PUT
THAT SCOUNDREL TO DEATH!
OH MY,
HOW QUICKLY HE RUNS.
- Both: HERE WE COME.
HERE WE COME.
HERE WE COME...
- ( laughing )
- VERY FUNNY!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- Both: WAIT!
- YOUR LOGS
ARE TRYING TO KILL ME!
- THEY'RE MY SISTER'S!
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
THAT WAY, HURRY!
- WHOA!
- HURRY, GO IN THERE.
- ( yawns )
HUH?
- AAH!
- ( grunts )
- WELL, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
- OW!
OH, MAN, NOW WHERE ARE WE?
- YOO-HOO!  YOO-HOO!
TENCHI!
- IT'S HER.
- YOU SHOWED UP JUST IN TIME.
- YOU GOT ME INTO THIS MESS.
YOU GET ME OUT.
I WANT TO GO HOME RIGHT NOW!
- YOU KNOW, I'D LOVE TO HELP,
BUT WITHOUT THE OTHER
TWO JEWELS, I JUST CAN'T.
SO STOP YELLING
AND GET ME OUT OF HERE.
- LISTEN TO ME.  FIRST OF ALL,
I CAN'T OPEN THIS THING.
YOU KNOW THAT.
AND ANOTHER THING--
- ( sword trilling )
- HUH?
WHOA!
- I GUESS YOU WERE MISTAKEN.
- Sasami: UM, EXCUSE ME.
- HMM?
- ( giggles )
- WHO'S THIS?
- HELLO, NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M SASAMI.
- UH, HO-- WHAT?
- HEY, TENCHI,
WHO IS THIS OLDER LADY?
- ( gong strikes )
- IS SHE A FRIEND OF YOURS ALSO?
- ( grunting ) OLDER?!
( laughs )
YES, I'M HIS FRIEND.
BUT NOT AN OLDER LADY.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN, LITTLE GIRL?
- WOW, YOU'RE A STRONG LADY.
THAT HURTS.
- I WONDER WHY THIS OPENED.
- Sasami: HEY!
THAT SWORD BELONGS TO YOSHO.
- WHAT?  YOSHO?
- UH-HUH.
BUT WHY WERE YOU ABLE
TO USE IT?
- OH, YES!
SHOW ME THAT SWORD OF YOURS.
- UH-OH.  NOW JUST A MINUTE--
- NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
- WAIT!
YOU CAN'T TOUCH THIS!
- JUST TRUST ME.  RELAX.
- COME ON, STOP IT.
GET AWAY FROM ME.
- SHH.  BE QUIET.
- ( grunting )
- Ayeka: STOP!
- HUH?
- AND HERE COMES THE PRINCESS.
- SASAMI!  I SEE IT WAS YOU
WHO RELEASED HIM.
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS.
YOU REALLY
SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT.
- SORRY, I WAS JUST BORED.
- THAT'S NO EXCUSE.
YOU, TENCHI--
I BELIEVE YOUR NAME IS TENCHI--
I HAVE A QUESTION
I'D LIKE TO ASK OF YOU.
- SURE.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
- WHERE IS THE OWNER
OF THAT SWORD YOU HOLD?
- HUH?  WELL, I THINK HE DIED
A LONG LONG TIME AGO.
- YOU ARE LYING!
- I'M SORRY,
BUT THAT'S WHAT IT SAYS
IN THE ANCIENT LEGEND.
- AND WHAT WAS HIS NAME?
- WELL, I'M PRETTY SURE
HIS NAME WAS YOSHO.
- OH NO.
- UH, DOES THAT HELP AT ALL?
- OH, YEAH,
HE DIED, DIDN'T HE?
THAT'S TOO BAD.
- IT ISN'T TRUE!
YOU'RE ONLY TRYING TO TRICK ME.
AZAKA, KAMIDAKE!
- Both: YES, MA'AM.
- AYEKA!  HUH?
- ORDER YOUR BLOCKHEADS
TO PULL BACK.
- YOU PLAY DIRTY TO THE END.
- AAH!
- BYE BYE, LADY.
- Ayeka: SASAMI, COME HERE!
- AAH!
GET BACK, AZAKA!  NO!
GET BACK!
- GET BACK!  STOP!
- ( both grunting )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, TENCHI?
- WHAT'S HAPPENING? I GAVE YOU
AN ORDER TO CAPTURE THEM.
THE SWORD.  THE MASTER KEY
IS IN SYNCH WITH HIM.
BUT IT SHOULDN'T REACT TO ANYONE
BUT THOSE OF ROYAL BLOOD.
SO WHY IS IT--
IT CAN'T BE.
NO, IT CAN'T BE TRUE.
- TENCHI?
- WHOA.
- CALL RYO-OHKI.
YOU WANT TO GO HOME, DON'T YOU?
- YEAH,
IF YOU RETURN MY HOUSE TOO.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I WON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT IS IMPOSSIBLE.
- SUIT YOURSELF, BUT YOU MIGHT
WANT TO GET OUT OF THE WAY.
- AAH!
( squealing, meowing )
- DON'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU.
LET'S GO, TENCHI.
THANK YOU, LITTLE GIRL.
- BYE BYE, TENCHI.
- DO SOMETHING QUICKLY.
- Kamidake: YES, MA'AM.
- I WILL NEVER
FORGIVE THAT WOMAN.
- I'LL MAKE HER FOLLOW US
DOWN TO EARTH.
AS LONG AS SHE'S ALLOWED
TO FLY AROUND UP HERE,
SHE'S ONLY GOING
TO GIVE US TROUBLE.  HA!
- DON'T DO THAT.
YOU'LL HURT HER.
- HEY, WHOSE SIDE
ARE YOU ON ANYWAY?
IF YOU LIKE HER SO MUCH,
GO JOIN HER.
- SHE'S JUST A GIRL!
- SO WHAT?
- Azaka: RYO-OHKI'S MASS
IS GROWING ABNORMALLY.
- BUT WHY AREN'T THEY
UNDER OUR CONTROL?
- Kamidake: THEY SEEM TO HAVE
USED THE MASTER KEY.
- OH!
ATTACK ATTACK! WHAT ARE
YOU DOING? WE MUST ATTACK!
- Azaka:
DESCENT VELOCITY INCREASING.
IF WE WERE TO FALL TO EARTH,
EVEN OUR SPACESHIP, RYO-OHKI,
WOULD NOT ESCAPE
WITHOUT SERIOUS DAMAGE.
- OH, HOW UNREASONABLE
THAT WOMAN IS.
- ( Ryoko laughing )
- RYOKO, STOP THIS IMMEDIATELY!
EVEN YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO ESCAPE
UNHARMED FROM THIS, RYOKO!
SAY SOMETHING!
- ( laughing )
- STOP THIS IMMEDIATELY!
I KNOW YOU HEAR ME.
- Kamidake: 20 SECONDS
TO EARTH'S SURFACE.
- AAH!
- ( Ryoko laughing )
- RYOKO, STOP, PLEASE!
EXPLODE EXTERIOR WALL UNIT!
- HUH?
- Tenchi and Ayeka: AAH!
- ( Ryoko laughing )
- OOH!
- News Anchor:
OUR TOP STORY THIS MORNING--
AROUND 4:00 A.M., AN OBJECT
THOUGHT TO BE A METEOR
FELL ON THE GREAT SATO BRIDGE,
COMPLETELY DESTROYING
THE BRIDGE ON IMPACT.
AS A RESULT, JAPAN RAIL HAS
BEEN UNABLE TO OPERATE
THIS MORNING, WITH NO WORD YET
AS TO WHEN SERVICE
WILL BE RESTORED.
- ( murmuring )
- OTHER DAMAGE IS CURRENTLY
UNDER INVESTIGATION...
- WOW, TAKE A LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S A MAJOR STORY.
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG? YOU DON'T
LOOK WELL AT ALL, TENCHI.
- ( mumbles )
- CHEER UP!
WE GOT BACK SAFELY, DIDN'T WE?
YOU SHOULD BE THANKFUL FOR THAT.
- RIGHT.
- OF COURSE, NOW OUR
HOUSE IS RIGHT BY
YOUR GRANDFATHER'S SHRINE.
BUT I SURE THINK THAT'S KIND
OF CONVENIENT IN A WAY.
DON'T YOU THINK SO, TENCHI?
- EAT THIS TOO.
IT'S GOOD.
IT'LL MAKE YOU BIG AND STRONG.
- HMM?
- YOU'RE LUCKY--
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A SCRATCH
AFTER ALL
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH TOGETHER.
YOU REALLY OUGHT
TO BE THANKING ME.
AFTER ALL, I TOOK CARE OF YOU
AND PROTECTED YOU
AT MY OWN PERSONAL RISK.
- BUT MOST OF THE ENERGY OF THE
CRASH WAS ABSORBED BY OUR SHIP!
YOU SEE,
THAT'S WHY YOU WERE OKAY.
- SO THAT'S WHY
OUR LANDING POINT WAS OFF?
UGH!  I ALMOST LANDED
BACK IN THAT DAMN CAVE.
- I THOUGHT THERE WAS
ANOTHER YOUNG LADY WITH YOU.
WHERE DID SHE GO?
- SHE'S OVER THERE.
- ( grunting )
OH, NOW WHAT?
SASAMI!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
COME AND HELP ME
SAVE RYU-OH, MY SHIP!
- BUT IT'S TOO BIG
FOR US TO HANDLE.
WE'LL NEVER
GET IT OUT OF THERE.
- OH!
I CAN'T GET STRANDED
ON A REMOTE PLANET LIKE THIS.
I SIMPLY CAN'T.
I HAVE TO SAVE MY SHIP.
MY RYU-OH--
OH!
( crying )
- ( birds squawking )
- ( end theme playing )
- ♪ LIFE IS SO FULL
OF HURRY AND HUSTLE ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I THINK
IT'S PASSING US BY ♪
♪ THE DAYS ARE LIKE HOURS,
HOURS LIKE MINUTES ♪
♪ I'M CAUGHT IN IT
TILL I LOOK IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND TO MY SURPRISE ♪
♪ I FIND THERE IS A HEAVEN ♪
♪ TIME IS UNREAL,
MAKING ME FEEL ♪
♪ FREE AND ALIVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME,
YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
IN SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME,
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE
LIGHT-YEARS AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TALENT FOR LOVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME, YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
TO SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME ♪
♪ WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE LIGHT-YEARS
AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TALENT FOR LOVE. ♪
- ( inaudible )