- ( theme music playing )
- ( ground crunching )
- ( grunts )
- ( chewing )
( whimpers )
- DON'T BE SO GREEDY!
- ( meows )
- THANKS TO YOU, WE'VE HAD
TO TURN ALL OUR FIELDS
INTO CARROT FIELDS, YOU KNOW.
- ( meows )
- WHOA!
- ( screeches )
- WELL, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
HUH?
OH, IT'S ONLY SNOW.
THAT'S ALL.
SO THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
YOU'VE EVER SEEN SNOW?
- ( screeches )
- HUH?
- AHH!
MMM.
( sighs )
NOW THIS IS WHAT I CALL
HEAVEN ON EARTH.
MMM!
- HUH?  OH.
- HEY, HOW ABOUT A DRINK?
- NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
- JOIN ME, HUH?
- UGH!
( gulping )
- WOW!
YOU SURE KNOW
HOW TO PUT THIS STUFF AWAY.
- NOW LET ME REMIND YOU,
I HAVEN'T QUITE FORGIVEN YOU
FOR THAT INCIDENT THE OTHER DAY.
- COME ON,
WHAT ARE YOU TELLING ME?
YOU'RE STILL UPSET
ABOUT THAT?
I AM CERTAINLY SORRY
THAT YOU COULDN'T SEDUCE TENCHI.
( laughs )
- YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
UGH!
YOU SEE, TENCHI AND I
ARE RELATED BY NOBLE BLOOD.
( gulping )
I'M NOT LIKE YOU.
- YEAH, BUT IT'S ONLY BEEN
TWO MONTHS SINCE YOU TWO MET.
I, ON THE OTHER HAND,
HAVE KNOWN HIM
SINCE HE WAS THIS TINY.
HE SURE WAS A CUTIE PIE.
HE SURE WAS.
AHHHH.
- Grandma: YES?
WHAT'S THE MATTER, TENCHI?
DO YOU SEE A MONSTER?
HEY, TENCHI?
- HUH?
OH, GRANDMA.
- DID I SURPRISE YOU?
- YEAH, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GRANDPA.
( Tenchi crying )
OH, GRANDMA.
HEY!  HEY!
AH!  OW!
OH, COME BACK, HOT POTATO!
- Grandpa: TENCHI!
- I'M COMING.
- Ryoko: I ALWAYS HOPED
THAT ONE DAY
TENCHI AND I
WOULD PLAY TOGETHER.  HMM.
BUT NOW HE TREATS ME
LIKE I'M SOME SORT OF
MONSTER OR SOMETHING.
SO OF COURSE
I TEASE HIM SOMETIMES.
YOU UNDERSTAND, DON'T YOU?
- ( Ayeka laughing )
- MMM?
- YES, BUT DARLING,
YOU WERE A MUMMY.
MAYBE TENCHI JUST DOESN'T
WANT TO PLAY WITH A MONSTER.
- THANKS FOR THE SYMPATHY.
- WELL, LET'S BE HONEST,
SHALL WE?
YOU'RE WONDERING
WHY HE TREATS YOU LIKE HE DOES.
I THINK I KNOW THE PROBLEM.
I'M PRETTY SURE THE PROBLEM
IS YOUR AGE!
YOU'RE OVER 1,000 YEARS OLD
AND IT'S ANNOYING TO BE SEDUCED
BY AN OLD LADY.
- ( gasps )
- JUST LOOK
AT MY BEAUTIFUL SKIN.
IT'S SO YOUTHFUL,
AND YOURS IS SO, WELL,
MAYBE YOU'VE BEEN
SOAKING TOO LONG.
( cackling )
- I HATE YOU.
YOU'RE SO CRUEL.
( bawling )
- SHOULD I JUST
CALL YOU OLD BAT?
- HELLO.
AM I DISTURBING YOU?
- ( crying continues )
- HELLO!
- YOU!
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN THERE?
- ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT TENCHI?
I HOPE IT'S OKAY
IF I MAKE MYSELF COMFORTABLE.
AT THAT MOMENT...
( gulps )
...WHEN I HEARD
THAT IT WAS TENCHI WHO SAVED ME
WHEN I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO BE SUCKED INTO A BLACK HOLE--
WELL, WHEN I HEARD THAT,
I THOUGHT HE JUST MIGHT
BE MY DESTINY.
- ( groaning )
- YES, THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
HE MIGHT BE MY DESTINY.
( laughs )
WE JUST MET AND I'M TALKING
TO YOU LIKE THIS.
- ( bird squawking )
- ( both groaning )
- ALL RIGHT, HOW LONG ARE YOU
GOING TO STAY IN THE BATH?
WHOA!  IT'S STINKY.
IT SMELLS LIKE SAKE.
- ( meows )
- OH, YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO
UNDERSTANDS MY FEELINGS.
- ( screeches )
- HMM? AH.
- ( Kagato laughing )
- ( all gasping )
- ( laughter continues )
WELL, I FINALLY FOUND YOU,
RYOKO.
- KAGATO!
- AHHH!  YOU PERVERT!
( both shouting )
- AHH!  AHHH!
OOH!
- RYOKO, NO!
- ( laughs )
- ( grunting, screaming )
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- ( alarm sounding )
- HEY, WHOA!
- ( alarm stops )
- THIS ONE'S THE REAL ONE,
THE INFAMOUS BRUTAL CRIMINAL.
KAGATO!
ETERNAL AND MOST WANTED CRIMINAL
KAGATO,
COME OUT NOW.
I KNOW YOU'RE HERE.
I SAID COME OUT!
- ( meows )
- PLEASE EXCUSE
MY BEHAVIOR EARLIER.
I DEEPLY APPRECIATE
YOU COMING OUT TO WELCOME ME.
- RYOKO!
- HOWEVER THIS ONE
BELONGS TO ME.
SHE IS, HOW CAN I SAY IT
DELICATELY?
WASTE PRODUCT.
STILL SHE IS AGILE.
I'LL BET SHE'S GIVEN YOU
SOME TROUBLE.
PRINCESS SASAMI,
PRINCESS AYEKA,
DON'T YOU THINK IT'S BEST
WE TALK SOMEPLACE PRIVATE,
SOMEPLACE WHERE
THERE'S NO ONE TO BOTHER US?
- ( grunts )
KAGATO, I WILL ARREST YOU.
THIS IS A SPECIALLY
PROTECTED AREA.
ANY KIND OF COMBATIVE ACTION
IS FORBIDDEN.
IF YOU INVOLVE ANY CIVILIAN,
I'LL BLAST YOU TO BITS.
- OH MY, OH MY.
YOU REALLY FRIGHTEN ME.
YOU SEE, I'VE HEARD MUCH OF YOUR
HEROIC EPISODES IN THE PAST.
NOW I HEAR YOU'RE OVERWORKED
AND YOUR PERFORMANCE STINKS.
- ( grunts )
- ( laughs )
- ( clicking )
- HUH?
OH!
- PLEASE, I DON'T WISH
FOR YOU TO MISUNDERSTAND ME.
I'VE ONLY COME HERE TO INVITE
YOU ALL TO MY SHIP, THE SOJA.
VERY PLEASANT PLACE.
A PLACE WHERE WE CAN
GET TO KNOW ONE ANOTHER.
- ( sword zapping )
- OH, I SEE--
YOU HAVE THE SWORD.
BUT THAT'S THE KING'S PROPERTY.
WAVE IT AROUND LIKE THAT
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO HURT YOURSELF, YOUNG MAN.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT KING?
- YOU WOULD FIGHT ME WITHOUT
FULL KNOWLEDGE OF THE SWORD?
ALL RIGHT THEN.
- ( grunting )
AHHHH!
- DON'T WASTE YOUR LIFE.
NOW JUST HAND ME THAT SWORD.
- Ryoko: TENCHI!
- HMMM?
DON'T LET HIM HAVE IT!
- FASCINATING.
AND WHAT ABOUT THAT BOY
INTERESTS YOU SO MUCH, RYOKO?
- ( grunting )
- RYOKO!
- AHHH!
- WHOA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- IT IS SAID THAT SWORD
HOLDS THE GREATEST ENERGY
IN THE UNIVERSE. BUT THE SWORD
WILL ONLY RELEASE THAT ENERGY
WHEN HELD BY A SUITABLE OWNER.
MY QUESTION IS,
ARE YOU THAT SUITABLE OWNER?
- MAYBE I AM, MAYBE NOT.
I DON'T KNOW!
- I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN.
ARE YOU A SUITABLE OWNER
OF THAT SWORD?
- RELEASE HER.
LET RYOKO GO!
( groaning )
- TENCHI, NO!
- ( squeals )
- EH.
- ( grunts )
AHHHH!
AH!
COME, I'LL TEST YOU.
- ( grunting )
AHHH!
- ( all gasping )
- WHOA!
- HA!
- OW!
- THIS IS NO FUN.
DO YOU ENJOY MAKING ME
WASTE MY TIME?
- ARE YOU PLAYING WITH SOMETHING
THAT DOESN'T BELONG TO YOU?
- GRANDFATHER.
- COME, RYOKO,
I'LL GIVE YOU ONE MORE CHANCE.
- THERE YOU ARE,
THE FIRST CROWN PRINCE
OF JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY.
I WONDER, COULD YOU SHOW ME
THE SECRET OF THE UNIVERSE?
WILL YOU SHARE THAT TREASURE?
- PLEASURE?
WELL, I DO KNOW OF A REALLY
COMFORTABLE HOT SPRING NEARBY.
- AHHHH!
- WELL, AREN'T WE COCKY?
- THE GREATEST ENERGY
IN THE UNIVERSE?
THERE'S NO SUCH THING.
AND IF THERE WERE, IT COULDN'T
BE CONTROLLED BY HUMANS.
- I HAVE JOURNEYED THROUGH
SEA AFTER SEA OF THE STARS
IN ORDER TO FIND THE SECRET.
WHAT WILL IT TAKE
TO GET THAT POWER?
YOUR BLOOD?
JURAI ROYAL FAMILY'S BLOOD?
- AH!
( grunting )
( grunts )
- HA!
- Tenchi: RYOKO!
- USING A WOMAN
AS YOUR SHIELD, COWARD!
RYOKO, WAKE UP!
WAKE UP!
AYYYY!
- DON'T KILL HER, GRANDPA!
HELP HER!
- ( moaning )
- HMM?
- ( laughs )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HAVE YOU GIVEN UP?
( yelling )
AHHHHH!
- IT'S NOT YOURS, EH?
- ( moaning )
I SEE.
THEN THIS BOY
IS YOUR SUCCESSOR.
- TENCHI. ( gasps )
- RYOKO!
- I WILL TAKE
YOUR PRECIOUS RYOKO WITH ME.
IMPROVE YOUR SKILLS.
THEN COME TO US.
I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
- ( grunting )
OH!
- YOU'RE MY BROTHER!
YOU'RE MY BROTHER YOSHO,
AREN'T YOU?!
- SORRY, I--
I GUESS NOW YOU KNOW.
- BUT WHY?
TELL ME!
- EASY NOW, DON'T SCOLD ME.
- ( Ayeka crying )
THAT HANDSOME BROTHER.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
YOU'VE CHANGED SO MUCH.
AND YOU--
YOU'RE OLDER.
- DON'T CRY. AYEKA, I WAS
NOT GOING TO TELL YOU THIS.
BUT IF I HAD STAYED
ON PLANET JURAI,
THERE WOULD HAVE BEEN A CONFLICT
BETWEEN YOU AND ME
OVER SUCCESSION TO THE THRONE.
AYEKA, YOU SEE,
MY MOTHER WAS AN EARTHLING.
AND I AM TOO.
OR AT LEAST HALF OF ME.
- BUT WHY SHOULD THAT MATTER?
OUR FATHER MADE THE LAW
THAT AFTER HIM,
WE SHOULD MIX WITH BLOOD
OF OTHER PLANETS.
- IT WAS A LAW
THAT MANY JURAIANS DIDN'T LIKE.
IN THOSE DAYS,
THERE WAS TREMENDOUS PREJUDICE.
I-- I COULD NOT BEAR IT.
SO WHEN WE WERE ATTACKED
BY RYOKO,
I LEFT TO FIGHT,
NEVER TO RETURN.
NOW THIS PLANET IS MY HOME.
AND THIS IS WHERE I WISH
TO BE BURIED.
I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF RETURNING TO JURAI.
- BUT WITHOUT JURAI,
WITHOUT ITS LIFE TREE
AND WATER...
- I WILL DIE.
I KNOW THAT, AYEKA.
AND SUCH A THING DOESN'T MATTER.
SOMEDAY YOU WILL UNDERSTAND.
- THEN IT'S TRUE, GRANDPA.
YOU'RE YOSHO.
AND THE STORIES,
THE LEGEND, ALL OF IT IS TRUE.
- YES, AND YOU ARE CROWN PRINCE
OF PLANET JURAI.
YOU LOOK SURPRISED.
- BUT YOU NEVER SAID A THING.
- AND IF I HAD, WHAT THEN?
WOULD YOU HAVE KNOWN
WHAT TO DO?
SILLY BOY!  NOW IS YOUR TIME
TO GRASP THE FUTURE.
I AM SORRY.
I HAD NO IDEA
YOUR HEART WAS SET ON ME.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
WE COULD GET MARRIED NOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- BROTHER, PLEASE!
DON'T MAKE FUN.
- OH!
YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M TOO OLD.
BUT TENCHI, HOWEVER,
IS ABOUT THE RIGHT AGE.
HE'S A VERY GOOD GRANDSON.
- ( grunting )
- AND YOU TWO
ARE PERFECT TOGETHER.
- UH...
- ( crying )
- Ayeka: HUH?
- I'M SO MOVED!
I'M SO MOVED!
SORRY, BUT IT'S SO TOUCHING,
I CAN'T HELP MYSELF.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- GRANDPA,
I HAVE TO SAVE RYOKO.
BUT--
- BUT SHE'S THE CAUSE
OF ALL OF OUR TROUBLE.
YOU CERTAINLY
DON'T HAVE TO SAVE HER.
- TENCHI, I WILL GIVE YOU
THAT SWORD.
KAGATO IS VERY DANGEROUS.
YOU MUST GO AND DEFEAT HIM.
IN ORDER TO GET HOLD
OF THE SECRET TREASURE,
HE WOULD THINK NOTHING
OF DESTROYING THIS PLANET.
- BUT CAN I DEFEAT HIM?
I DON'T KNOW, GRANDPA.
I HAVE A HARD ENOUGH TIME
HANDLING THAT SWORD--
- WITH THAT KIND OF ATTITUDE,
HOW DO YOU EXPECT TO
PROTECT THESE WOMEN?
YOU HAVE A POWER
THAT HASN'T BEEN AWAKENED YET.
TRUST YOURSELF.
- GRANDPA?
I UNDERSTAND.
- NO, TENCHI, YOU SHOULDN'T!
- AYEKA, LISTEN NOW.
FOR EVERY MAN, THERE'S A TIME
WHEN HE MUST FIGHT.
- YES, BUT--
- PLEASE, TENCHI, WATCH OUT!
- ( grunting )
- THE SWORD HAS ACKNOWLEDGED
TENCHI AS ITS TRUE OWNER.
- YES.
- JEEZ!
- Yosho: ARE YOU GOING, TENCHI,
WITH THE SWORD
YOU CAN'T QUITE HANDLE YET?
EVEN SO,
ARE YOU STILL GOING?
- HMM!
RYOKO, I MUST SAVE HER.
- TENCHI, I'LL GO WITH YOU.
- I'LL GO WITH YOU TOO.
- THANK YOU.
- AS A MEMBER
OF THE GALAXY POLICE,
IT IS MY DUTY.
- Sasami:
SIS, YOU'LL COME, WON'T YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- AYEKA, PLEASE TAKE CARE
OF GRANDPA.
- OKAY, HOW ARE WE GOING
TO GET THERE?
- UH?
- ( squeals )
( meows )
- HE MUST SEE SOMETHING.
LET'S GO, TENCHI.
- OKAY.
- AYEKA?
AYEKA!
- MM-HMM.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- ( ship beeping )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH HIM?
- ( growling )
( squeals )
AHHHH!
- NO, MY LITTLE RYO-OHKI!
- ( squeals )
- OH MY! THAT POOR LITTLE
CREATURE. WHAT DID WE DO?
OH NO!
- RYO-OHKI!
- WELL, I GUESS WE CAN USE THAT
TO TRAVEL IN, HUH?
- ( machines beeping )
- Kagato: HERE THEY COME,
THE FOOLS.
IT'S STRANGE.
THEY'RE COMING HERE
TO THROW AWAY THEIR LIVES
TO SAVE SOMEONE
AS DEFECTIVE AS YOU.
- I AM NOT YOUR MACHINE ANYMORE.
I AM A HUMAN BEING!
- HUMAN BEING?
COMPARED TO THE INFINITE WILL
OF THE UNIVERSE,
HUMAN FEELINGS AMOUNT TO LITTLE,
NOTHING MORE THAN DUST.
YOU KNOW, YOUR CURRENT FORM
WAS CHOSEN
ONLY BECAUSE IT WAS CONVENIENT.
YOUR ORIGINAL FORM COULD HAVE
BEEN ANYTHING THAT I WANTED.
LIKE A STONE.
SHALL I TURN YOU INTO A STONE?
WOULD THAT MAKE YOU HAPPY?
( Kagato laughs )
I'D LOVE TO STAY AND CHAT,
BUT I'D BETTER PREPARE
TO WELCOME OUR GUESTS.
- OH!  IF YOU LAY
YOUR DIRTY HANDS ON TENCHI,
YOU'LL BE SORRY.
I SWEAR IT!
YOU'LL BE SORRY!
- ( machine beeping )
- ( beeping )
- Ayeka: KAGATO'S SHIP
IS ABOUT TO ATTACK.
PLEASE AVOID IT.
- WELL, BELIEVE ME,
I'D LIKE TO,
BUT I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING!
- ( all shouting )
- RYO-OHKI, ATTACK!
I COMMAND YOU.
OH, I CANNOT OPERATE THIS SHIP.
- ( all shouting )
- OH.  OH, THIS MIGHT HELP.
- HMM?
EXCUSE ME OVER THERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU ARE DOING?
- WELL, THIS ONE IS DIFFERENT
FROM ALL THE OTHERS.
DO YOU HAPPEN TO
KNOW HOW IT WORKS?
- NO, I DON'T!
BUT I COMMAND YOU
TO FIGURE IT OUT RIGHT NOW!
AHHH!
- I AM THE ONE WHO BUILT
THE SHIP THAT YOU ARE IN.
EVERY MOVE YOU MAKE,
YOU KNOW I WILL SEE THROUGH IT.
- AHH!  IT'S HOPELESS!
WHAT CAN WE DO?
- ( all scanning )
- HUH?
- Both: WHOA.
OOOH!  AHHH!
- WHAT-- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- MAYBE THE BALANCER WAS HIT.
- ( laughs )
MORE?  AHH!
- NOW I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS HAPPENS TO BE
A COMPUTER UNIT.
- YEAH, WELL, I JUST
DON'T HAVE VERY MUCH TO DO.
( laughs )
- NOW THAT'S
A VERY CAPABLE EVASION.
I WONDER IF IT'S DUE
TO THE POWER OF THE BOY'S SWORD.
- AYEKA, WE NEED
TO DO SOMETHING.
CAN WE ATTACK FROM YOUR SHIP?
- IT IS POSSIBLE.
BUT I'M NOT SURE THE SHIP
IS FULLY FORMED YET.
- I DON'T NEED THIS.
- IT'S DANGEROUS.
- WELL, WE CAN'T JUST SIT HERE
AND DO NOTHING.
- I WILL GO.
- NO, YOU CAN'T.
IT'S MY RESPONSIBILITY.
- UH, TENCHI!
- ONCE I GET THERE,
YOU'LL HAVE TO DIRECT ME.
AYEKA, I'M READY.
- FIRST YOU MUST OPEN
THE LIGHT HAWK WINGS.
- LIGHT HAWK WINGS?
- IT'S THE SHIELD
FOR THAT CRAFT.
ITS ORIGINAL FUNCTION
IS A DEFENSE SYSTEM.
HOWEVER, YOU CAN USE IT
TO ATTACK ALSO,
BUT IT ISN'T MEANT
FOR THAT PURPOSE.
WE WILL BE VULNERABLE.
- IT'S OUR ONLY HOPE.
HOW DO I OPEN THE WINGS,
AYEKA?
WHOA!
TELL ME WHAT TO DO!
- AH, THEY'RE USING
THE LIGHT HAWK WINGS.
I'M VERY IMPRESSED.
JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY
IS POWERFUL INDEED.
BUT I HAVE A SUITABLE STRATEGY.
- TENCHI, PLEASE HURRY!
- ( grunting )
- ( gasps )
- AHHHH!
AHH!
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs )
- Ayeka: TENCHI?  TENCHI!
TENCHI!
TENCHI?  TENCHI!
TENCHI?  TENCHI?
TENCHI, TENCHI!
TENCHI, TENCHI?  TENCHI!
AHHHH!
- AHHHH!
TENCHI?
WHERE ARE YOU?
( gasps )
OH!
( sobbing )
KAGATO, KAGATO,
YOU HAVE STOLEN THE ONE
THAT WAS MOST PRECIOUS TO ME.
AND I WILL MAKE YOU PAY.
YOU WILL PAY!
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ LIFE IS SO FULL
OF HURRY AND HUSTLE ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I THINK
IT'S PASSING US BY ♪
♪ THE DAYS ARE LIKE HOURS,
HOURS LIKE MINUTES ♪
♪ I'M CAUGHT IN IT
TILL I LOOK IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND TO MY SURPRISE ♪
♪ I FIND THERE IS A HEAVEN ♪
♪ TIME IS UNREAL,
MAKING ME FEEL ♪
♪ FREE AND ALIVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME,
YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
IN SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME,
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE
LIGHT-YEARS AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TELEPHONE LOVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME, YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
TO SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME ♪
♪ WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE LIGHT-YEARS
AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TELEPHONE LOVE. ♪
- ( silent )