( theme music playing )
♪ CAN'T YOU SEE
THAT I AM A PIONEER? ♪
♪ UNLOCKING
THE GREATEST MYSTERIES ♪
♪ MY KEY IS A FEARLESS HEART
SO PURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ YOU CAN'T BE A HERO ♪
♪ HIDING UNDERNEATH YOUR BED ♪
♪ GOT TO LIVE THE LIFE ♪
♪ YOU CREATE INSIDE YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ SO I OPEN THE WINDOW ♪
♪ CAUGHT THE WIND ONE NIGHT ♪
♪ NOW I SAIL WITH THE BIRDS ♪
♪ IN THEIR FLIGHT ♪
♪ SOME WILL SAY ♪
♪ YOU'RE SAFER HERE ♪
♪ NEVER MIND THAT,
BE A PIONEER ♪
♪ CAN'T YOU SEE
THAT YOU ARE A PIONEER? ♪
♪ NOT ONE
OF THE ENDLESS TALKERS ♪
♪ WHO TELL YOU
THE SAME OLD RULES ♪
♪ YOU'VE HEARD BEFORE ♪
♪ WE WILL BE PIONEERS ♪
♪ FOREVERMORE. ♪
- ( birds singing )
- HMM.
WELL WELL.
HMM, THIS IS QUITE A MESS.
- GEE, WHAT A DUMP. ARE WE
REALLY GOING TO STAY HERE?
- HEY, YOU MADE THIS MESS!
- OH MY!
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU CARED.
HOW SWEET.
- ( sighs )
- WELCOME.
IT'S A LONG TRIP.
THANKS FOR COMING ALL THE WAY.
- WELL, THANK YOU
FOR INVITING US BACK AGAIN.
( laughs )
- HERE YOU GO.
- HMM?
MMM!
- BOYS, YOU GET TO WORK
REPAIRING THE DAMAGE.
GIRLS, YOU START ON CLEANING,
LAUNDRY AND COOKING.
- ( all grumbling )
- BUT WE'RE TIRED.
CAN'T WE REST
A LITTLE BIT FIRST?
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- HMM?  ME?
OH, NOTHING.
- WE SHOULD PROBABLY
DO WHAT SHE SAYS.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
COME ON, LET'S GO NOW.
- EXCUSE ME, MA'AM.
PARDON ME.
WHAT'S MY ASSIGNMENT TO BE?
- YOU'RE NEW, AREN'T YOU?
- YES I AM.
HOW DO YOU DO?
MY NAME IS WASHU
AND I AM AT YOUR SERVICE,
O GREAT RESPECTED ONE.
- WELL WELL,
FOR BEING SO YOUNG AND ALL,
YOU ARE A GOOD POLITE GIRL
AND I LIKE THAT.
NOW I'M NOT PLANNING ON MAKING
ANY CHILDREN DO ANY WORK,
SO WHY DON'T YOU RUN ALONG
WITH SASAMI AND PLAY?
- AHA!
YES, MA'AM.
- HMM?
- HUH?
- HMM!
- WASHU, YOU SLACKER!
OUCH!
JUST WHAT THE--
- QUIT WASTING MY TIME.
- ( grumbles )
- ( laughs )
- AH, NOBUYUKI.
I THOUGHT
YOU WERE A PARTY OF EIGHT,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE GOT ONE MORE GUEST.
- HUH?  HMM?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THERE ARE ONLY EIGHT OF US.
- THAT'S STRANGE.
I COULD SWEAR I SAW A YOUNG LADY
RESEMBLING ME AS A YOUNG WOMAN.
- WELL, THERE'S NO ONE LIKE THAT
WITH US.
NOT AT ALL.
- SHE'S STARTING TO SEE THINGS.
WATCH OUT!
- OH!
- I SAID GET TO WORK
AND I MEAN IT!
- All: YES, MA'AM.
- SHALL WE GO?
- OKAY.
HMMM.
HEY, AYEKA.
- HMM?
- UH, NOTHING.
NEVER MIND.
- ALL RIGHT.
- COME ON NOW, SASAMI.
- OKAY.
- THIS IS A MILFOIL.
DID YOU KNOW THESE FLOWERS
ARE SUPPOSEDLY GROWN
FOR THEIR BEAUTY
AND MEDICINAL VALUES?
BUT I WONDER WHAT THEY CURE.
SASAMI?
- HUH?
- COME OVER HERE, SASAMI.
COME ON, IT'S A WONDERFUL VIEW.
IT REALLY IS.
- WOW.
( gasps )
- ( yawning )
AH!  SASAMI?
WHAT?
- ( animals scurrying )
- WHERE'D SHE GO?
OH WELL.
RYO-OHKI IS WITH HER
SO SHE'LL BE FINE, I'M SURE.
- ( banging )
- Nobuyuki: THIS MUST BE
WHAT SHE HAD IN MIND
WHEN SHE CALLED
AND INVITED US OVER.
HMM, I WAS SO STUPID.
- Yosho: LET'S JUST SAY NAIVE.
- WELL, YOU WERE EXCITED
ABOUT COMING HERE TOO.
- DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- UH, NO.
NOTHING NOTHING.
( laughs )
OH!
- MMM.
I TOLD YOU TO BE CAREFUL.
OH!
- ( both grunting )
- BONEHEADS.
- HEY, TENCHI, LOOK.
- HMM?
- OH!
- NOW WHO'S A BONEHEAD?
- AHH!
- HMM.  YOU'RE A BIG HELP.
WITH THE WAY
YOU'RE PEELING THEM,
WE WON'T HAVE ANYTHING
LEFT TO EAT.
- IS THAT RIGHT?
WELL, WITH HOW SLOWLY
YOU'RE PEELING THEM,
WE'RE NEVER GONNA FINISH,
MADAM SLOWPOKE.
- MM-HMM!
WELL, AT LEAST I HAVE A TALENT
FOR NOT WASTING FOOD.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- THE TRUTH!
- ( both grumble )
- SETTLE DOWN, BOTH OF YOU.
I MEAN, LET'S NOT ARGUE
OVER NOTHING, OKAY?
I MEAN, AT LEAST WAIT TILL
IT'S SOMETHING TO ARGUE ABOUT.
- Both: MMM.
EH.  OOH!
- WHAT?
HMM!
- HEY, I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
- ( sighs )
- IT WASN'T ME, I TELL YOU.
I REALLY DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
AND YOU'D BETTER BELIEVE ME.
SASAMI, WAS IT YOU?
- ( meows )
- OH, AYEKA.
- HMM?
DID YOU SEE SOMEONE ELSE HERE
JUST NOW?
- NO, AYEKA, I DIDN'T.
- ( meows )
- I THOUGHT I SAW SOMEONE.
- AYEKA, I NEED TO TELL YOU--
- Ryoko: HEY, AYEKA!
WHAT WAS IT?
- OH, NOTHING!
UH, SASAMI, YOU WERE SAYING?
- UH, NOTHING REALLY.
- HMM?  MMM.
- ( hammering )
- PLEASE HOLD IT TIGHT,
GRANDPA.
- I KNOW.  HURRY UP.
- HMM?
AHHH.
DID-- DID YOU--
DID YOU SEE THAT?
- HMM.
- ( men groaning )
- SHH!  I'M TELLING YOU
WHAT WE SAW.
WE SAW A VAGUE GHOSTLIKE FIGURE.
- OKAY, YOU-- YOU GUYS ARE JUST
TRYING TO SCARE ME NOW, RIGHT?
- NO, WE ACTUALLY SAW IT.
- MMM.
- YOU SAW IT?
- Ayeka: YES.
- AHH!
- COME TO THINK OF IT,
DAD AND GRANDPA
SAID THEY SAW SOMETHING--
SOMETHING SIMILAR.
- Mihoshi: STOP IT, PLEASE.
I CAN'T STAND IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF,
TENCHI?
- HEY, DO I LOOK AFRAID?!
- AHH!
- OH! GRANDPA!
- LISTEN.
I'LL TELL YOU THE STORY.
WHEN I WAS A YOUNG MAN,
THE PERSON WHO LIVED
HERE TOLD IT TO ME.
IT BEGINS OVER 600 YEARS AGO.
THERE WAS A HOUSE ON A MOUNTAIN
FAR AWAY FROM CIVILIZATION.
IN IT, THERE LIVED A COUPLE.
PEOPLE RESPECTED AND
ADMIRED THEIR RELATIONSHIP
BECAUSE THEY WERE
SO MUCH IN LOVE.
HOWEVER, THE WIFE
HAD BEEN SICKLY SINCE CHILDHOOD
AND HAD BECOME BEDRIDDEN
FOR QUITE SOME TIME.
IT IS SAID
SHE PROBABLY KNEW
THAT HER TIME
WAS RUNNING SHORT.
THEY DID THEIR BEST
TRYING TO CARE FOR EACH OTHER
AND LIVE THEIR LIVES
TO THE FULLEST
AND TO TREASURE
THEIR REMAINING TIME TOGETHER.
ONE STORMY NIGHT,
THEY HEARD A VOICE
THROUGH THE HOWLING WIND.
IT WASN'T THEIR IMAGINATION.
THE VOICE WAS REAL.
THOUGH THEY WERE SCARED,
THEY WERE COMPELLED TO LISTEN.
AND THIS IS WHAT
THE VOICE SAID TO THEM--
"HEAD TO THE WEST.
GO OVER THREE MOUNTAINS
AND YOU'LL FIND AN HERB
THAT CAN CURE
ANY KIND OF SICKNESS."
THUS THE WIND SPOKE
AND THEN FELL SILENT.
THE HUSBAND
BELIEVED THE WIND'S WORDS
AND DECIDED TO GO SEARCH
FOR THE HERB.
SHE BEGGED HIM TO REMAIN
AND NOT LEAVE HER ALONE,
BUT HE LEFT
AND SET OUT FOR THE WEST.
- HUH?
MMM!
- OW!
- FOR SIX MONTHS,
SHE WAITED FOR HIS RETURN,
HOLDING ON AGAINST DEATH
WITH ALL HER STRENGTH.
BUT HE DIDN'T RETURN.
SHE SPOKE TO HERSELF, SAYING,
"I WISH THAT I WERE HEALTHY.
THEN I WOULD BE ABLE
TO LOOK FOR HIM."
BUT, ALAS,
HER HOPES WERE IN VAIN.
AND ONE DAY, ALL ALONE,
SHE PASSED AWAY.
AFTER THAT DAY
AROUND THIS PLACE,
PEOPLE BEGAN TO SEE AN IMAGE
OF A WOMAN.
THEY CALL HER THE WHITE GHOST.
SO YOU'D BETTER
WATCH OUT, TENCHI.
- HMM?
- HER SPIRIT WANDERS AIMLESSLY,
SEARCHING FOR HER BELOVED,
CONSTANTLY SEARCHING.
SHE MAY EVEN COME FOR YOU.
- HEY!
- AHH!
- ( all shouting )
- HAVEN'T YOU RESTED
LONG ENOUGH?
GET BACK TO WORK!
- All: OH YES, MA'AM!
- OH!
- KIDS TODAY!
EH, THAT GOES FOR YOU TOO,
I HOPE YOU KNOW.
- BUT-- BUT I--
THE WHITE GHOST IS--
- NOT THE WHITE GHOST!
THAT OLD STORY OF YOURS AGAIN?
- YOU-- YOUR STORY?
THEN YOU MADE IT ALL UP?
- ( laughs )
YUP.
NOT MAD, ARE YOU?
- Innkeeper: CUT IT OUT!
- ( laughs )
OH!
GO RIG THE LIGHTS
OR SOMETHING.
- WHEN WILL THEY EVER GROW UP?
WHY AM I THE ONE
WHO HAS TO FIX THIS?
DAD AND GRANDPA ARE ALWAYS
SITTING AROUND DOING NOTHING.
HUH?
SO WHAT IF GRANDPA'S STORY
WAS ALL MADE UP?
I MEAN, WE ALL DID SEE
THAT WHITE IMAGE.
HA HA!
I'D BETTER STOP THINKING ABOUT
GHOSTS OR I'LL PROBABLY SEE ONE.
- ( rustling )
- HEY.  AHHH!
OH!
( groaning )
- ( rustling )
- OH!
- JEEZ!
SILLY ME.
IT WAS JUST A STUPID CAN.
AHHH!
- ( glass smashing )
- AHHH!
( panting )
AAHHH!
OH!
AHHH!
- Ayeka: TENCHI!
- HUH?
- ( moaning )
- ( groaning )
- TENCHI!
HUH?
NOW WHERE DID HE GO?
( groaning )
- YOU'VE SEEN IT?
- YUP.
- ( gasps )
I'M SCARED! ( crying )
- HMM.
I NEED TO KNOW SOMETHING.
WHERE DID YOU SEE IT EXACTLY?
- ( groaning )
- All: HUH?
( all screaming )
- HUH?
HMM!  MY IMAGINATION.
- SASAMI?
- OH!
- SAS-- SASAMI?
- NOT SO TIGHT!  AHH!
- OH.
WELL, SASAMI, IT'S ONLY YOU.
- I CAN'T BREATHE.
- OH.
- ( moans )
- MY, THAT WAS SO SCARY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS--
HUH?
OH!
SASAMI'S REFLECTION IS--
- All: HUH?
- ( gasps )
- TSUNAMI?
- OH MY.  SASAMI.
YOU ARE--
- SASAMI!
- WHOA!
( all screaming )
- AHHH!
- All: SASAMI?
( all calling out )
- ( static over radio )
- AH, SHE'S NOT AROUND HERE
ANYWHERE.
- I LOOKED--
SHE'S NOT INSIDE THE INN.
- WASHU?
- HMM?  NOPE, I'VE CHECKED.
MY INSTRUMENTS CAN'T SEEM
TO FIND A TRACE OF HER.
- OH NO.
- I CAN'T COMMUNICATE
WITH RYO-OHKI NOW EITHER.
- EH! WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO SPREAD OUT
AND SEARCH FOR HER OURSELVES.
- WELL, I'LL GO THIS WAY.
- ALL RIGHT.
- AH, LET'S SEE.
I'LL GO THIS WAY,
THEN... HMM...
- YOU!
GO THAT WAY.
- HMM.
- SASAMI?
SASAMI?
SASAMI, WHERE ARE YOU?
( sighs )
WHERE ARE YOU?
THAT REFLECTION
WAS OF TSUNAMI.
AND WHAT IS HAPPENING
TO SASAMI?
( sighs )
OH?
HMM?
- ( meows )
- HUH?
- WHAT?
- ( grunting )
OW!  OH!
- SHH.
- WASHU.
- LET'S LEAVE THEM ALONE.
- OH, OKAY.
- ( girls moaning )
( muffled protesting )
- HMM?
- I'M SORRY, AYEKA.
BUT I'M NOT THE REAL SASAMI!
- HUH?
WHAT-- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, SASAMI?
WH-- WHAT?
- ( crying )
- ( meows )
- SASAMI?
OH.
UH-HUH.
- 700 YEARS AGO.
YES-- IT ALL HAPPENED
700 YEARS AGO.
- ( laughter )
- THAT DAY WHEN THE SPACE PIRATE
RYOKO ATTACKED PLANET JURAI.
- ( alarm sounding )
- Man: INTRUDER IN BLOCK 194!
INTRUDER IN BLOCK 194!
- PRINCESS SASAMI,
WHERE ARE YOU?
SASAMI!
- ( man continues )
- SASAMI!
AHHH!
- Man: D1, SWITCH TO MODE 4!
- PRINCESS SASAMI!
- ( gasps )
- PRINCESS SASAMI?
WHERE COULD SHE HAVE GONE?
WHERE DID SHE GO?
- WOW!
WOW!
( grunting )
( gasps )
( laughs )
HOW DO YOU DO?
OH!
OH!  AHHHH!
( heartbeat )
- PRINCESS SASAMI!
WHERE ARE YOU?
OH, THERE YOU ARE!
- MAMA!
- PRINCESS SASAMI!
IS MY LITTLE PRINCESS ALL RIGHT?
- YES!
- OH GOOD.
- ( crying )
I TRIED TO TELL YOU MANY TIMES.
THE REAL SASAMI DIED THAT DAY.
THEREFORE I AM--
I AM NOT YOUR REAL SISTER!
- HUH?
- AYEKA!
AYEKA!
PLEASE WAIT!
- ( laughs )
- AYEKA, WAIT FOR ME!
SISTER!
AYEKA, WAIT FOR ME!
WAIT FOR ME!
- ( laughs )
- AYEKA!
- ( gasps )
SASAMI!
ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( wailing )
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, SASAMI.
I'M SORRY, SASAMI.
- ( wailing )
- MMM.
WHY ARE YOU TELLING ME THIS,
SASAMI?
- UM...
- ARE YOU TELLING ME THIS
TO DRIVE ME AWAY?
- NO, AYEKA.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH!
I DO!  I REALLY--
- ( giggling )
REALLY?
- YES, I DO!
YES, I DO!
- YOU DO?
WELL, I LOVE YOU TOO, SASAMI.
WE LOVE EACH OTHER.
THAT'S WHAT COUNTS.
- YES.
- WHOA!
- TENCHI?
- UM, UH, I--
- ( laughs )
- I FEEL THE SAME
AS AYEKA.
- AH.
- SASAMI, WE LIKE YOU
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE.
- RIGHT.
SASAMI, WHATEVER HAPPENS,
YOU ARE MY DEAR SISTER.
- AYEKA!
( sobbing )
TENCHI!
- BE THAT WAY.
THAT'S FINE.
- ( meows )
- ( laughs )
SASAMI IS A LITTLE GIRL
AFTER ALL.
LET'S SEE.
- ( muffled talking )
- LOOKS LIKE
SHE'S FALLEN ASLEEP.
- YES, IT LOOKS THAT WAY.
THE POOR DEAR'S EXHAUSTED.
I GUESS SHE WAS AFRAID AFTER WE
FOUND OUT ABOUT HER SECRET,
WE WOULD LEAVE HER.
SHE-- SHE TOLD ME
THAT THE REAL SASAMI DIED.
BUT IF THAT'S TRUE, THEN--
- OH.
- Tsunami: PRINCESS AYEKA?
SASAMI DIDN'T REALLY DIE,
PRINCESS AYEKA.
( gasps )
- SHE THINKS OF HERSELF
AS MY CREATION.
BUT SHE ACTUALLY SURVIVED
BY ASSIMILATING WITH ME.
SHE'S STILL YOUNG. ONE DAY
SHE WILL UNDERSTAND EVERYTHING.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL HER?
- SHE WOULDN'T HAVE BELIEVED IT,
PRINCESS AYEKA,
EVEN IF I HAD TOLD HER.
BESIDES, SASAMI NEEDED TO KNOW
OF YOUR FEELINGS FOR HER.
RIGHT NOW, THAT'S MORE IMPORTANT
THAN THE TRUTH OF HER IDENTITY.
PRINCESS AYEKA, SHE TRULY IS
YOUR REAL SISTER.
- WOW!
- BEAUTIFUL.
- HERE YOU ARE.
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU.
AHH!
- ( all cheering )
- BEAUTIFUL CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
( laughs )
- ( all laughing )
- OKAY.
- ( meows )
- HEY, WAY TO GO, RYO-OHKI!
- HEY, COME ON, TENCHI.
COME ON, HAVE A LITTLE SAKE.
- I'M STILL A MINOR.
- Both: GO RIGHT AHEAD!
- HUH?!
- LET'S LIVEN THINGS UP.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
MMM!
- YEEEE!  WHOOA!
- OH NO.
SOMEONE FEELING
KIND OF BLUE AROUND HERE?
- MMM.
- HMM.
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT JURAI HAD TREES
THAT COULD TAKE ON HUMAN FORM.
( sighs )
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND ANYTHING.
- MEANING?
- TSUNAMI AND SASAMI
ARE THE SAME.
THERE-- GET IT?
- SO WHAT?
- WELL, THEY ARE ASSIMILATED.
THAT MEANS THAT SASAMI
AND TSUNAMI ARE IDENTICAL.
WHICH MEANS
THAT WHEN SASAMI GROWS UP...
- SHE'LL LOOK LIKE TSUNAMI?
HMM.  IT CAN'T BE.
- Tsunami:
YES, SHE WILL BE LIKE ME.
WE HAVE SEPARATE MINDS
RIGHT NOW,
BUT WHEN WE ARE JOINED
IN ONE FORM...
YOU CAN CALL ME SASAMI
OR TSUNAMI,
WHICHEVER ONE YOU PREFER.
- Both: HUH?
- YOU NEEDN'T WORRY.
WHEN WE ARE UNITED,
SHE WILL HAVE A COMPLETE MEMORY.
- THAT'S NOT WHY WE'RE WORRIED.
- HUH?
- SO SASAMI WILL LOOK LIKE YOU?
- YES, I AM THE IMAGE
OF SASAMI IN THE FUTURE.
- DAMN, I DIDN'T THINK
ABOUT THIS.
SINCE AYEKA IS NO COMPETITION,
I THOUGHT SASAMI
WAS NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
- I DIDN'T PLAN ON THIS.
SASAMI'S BEAUTY
WILL SURPASS MINE.
- ( both grunting )
- WELL, SHE'S A LOT PRETTIER
THAN YOU ARE.  HMM!
- AND AT LEAST SHE'S BETTER
LOOKING THAN YOU ARE.
- WHAT'D YOU SAY?
- I'M SIMPLY STATING A FACT.
- AHEM.
- SHUT UP!
- YEAH, YOU STAY OUT OF THIS.
- ( gasps )
- Ryoko: YOU NEVER
WERE AS PRETTY AS ME, EVER.
YOU NEVER WERE.
- WHAT?!
YOU JUST TRY
AND NAME ONE ADVANTAGE
YOU HAVE OVER ME!
- EVERYTHING!
- OH, DON'T ARGUE LIKE THAT!
OH, WHOA!
- Both: OH!
- OH.
ARE-- ARE YOU TWO OKAY?
- ( both gargling )
- Ryoko: OF COURSE WE AREN'T.
- Ayeka: WHAT DO YOU THINK,
YOU SIMPLETON?
- Mihoshi:
OH, I'M SO SORRY.
- Ryoko:
I'M GONNA GET YOU!
- Mihoshi: AHHH!
- ( splashing )
- ( theme music playing )
♪ I AM LONELY
LIKE THE MOON ♪
♪ YOU ARE FAR AWAY
AS THE EARTH ♪
♪ THOUGH YOU SAY
I LIGHT YOUR THOUGHTS ♪
♪ NIGHT AFTER NIGHT ♪
♪ SOON YOU FORGET ♪
♪ WE ARE DRIFTING
IN THIS DANCE ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL YOU
CIRCLE MY HEART ♪
♪ KEEPING SUCH
A GRACEFUL DISTANCE ♪
♪ SO CLOSE
BUT SOMEHOW APART ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I CRY FOR YOU ♪
♪ KNOWING
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WHISPER
TO THE STARS ♪
♪ UP IN THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT I WANT TO FIND
A WAY TO YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ KISSING THE SUN
WHEN MORNING COMES ♪
♪ YOU DON'T SEEM
TO COUNT THE HOURS ♪
♪ WHEN WE ARE NOT TOGETHER ♪
♪ I'VE SEEN THE TENDER FIRE
IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ YET WHEN I'M GONE,
YOU CARRY ON ♪
♪ I FLOAT IN THIS EMPTINESS ♪
♪ TILL AT LAST
LOVE RETURNS ♪
♪ WITH THE NIGHT ♪
♪ AND THE LONELY MOON. ♪