( sighs )
RYOKO! WE THOUGHT YOU
WERE KAGATO'S PRISONER.
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
WELL, NOW THAT YOU'VE ESCAPED,
PERHAPS WE CAN SAVE TENCHI,
SINCE HE WENT TO SAVE YOU!
- WE MUST GO NOW.
WE MUST CHALLENGE KAGATO.
THAT'S ALL WE CAN DO.
- IS THAT RIGHT?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT WE CAN DO--
WE CAN FIND TENCHI, THAT'S WHAT
WE CAN DO. DO YOU HEAR ME?
OW!
OH!
HUH?
IS HE DEAD?
- IT'S NOT OVER YET.
I WILL KILL KAGATO.
I WILL KILL HIM!
EVEN IF IT KILLS ME.
LET'S GO!
HA!
HAAAAA!
- ( panting )
OH, NO, DON'T DIE, TENCHI!
PLEASE DON'T DIE.
WHOA!
( sobbing )
BY THE ROYAL SEAL
IN MY TRUE NAME,
PLEASE OPEN THE PATH TO OUR
ANCESTORS, THE SPACE TREES.
HEAVEN TO OCEAN,
OCEAN TO EARTH,
EARTH BACK TO HEAVEN,
SHOW ME THE PATH
ENGRAVED BY THE LIGHT.
- Ayeka: NOW WHICH WAY
DO WE GO?
- ALL THE PASSAGES
WILL LEAD TO HIM.
- LET'S GO.
- HEY, WAIT FOR ME!
- ( growling )
- HYAH!
- AHHH!
- EW, PLEASE STAY BACK!
- HMMM.
- ( playing )
- ( pulsating )
- HMM.
THERE MUST BE AN ENTRANCE
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
- WELL NOW,
LOOKS LIKE AN INVITATION.
- SURE DOES.
LET'S NOT BE RUDE.
- HELLO,
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
COULD YOU PLEASE WAIT UP?
WHOA!
OH NO!
WHERE'D THEY GO?
WHAT IS THIS?
WHERE AM I?  HEY!
WAIT A SECOND.
IF I HAD MY CONTROL CUBE...
HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE
TO ASK YOU TO WAIT FOR ME?
- HMM.
- ( song continues )
- WHAT THE--
- WELCOME TO MY CHAPEL, LADIES.
ENJOY THE MUSIC?
- STAND BACK, AYEKA!
- OOOH!
SCUMBAG!  OH!
- IS THAT TERM OF AFFECTION
OR DO YOU JUST NOT LIKE ME?
YOU'RE QUITE POWERFUL,
PRINCESS,
BUT THIS CHAPEL'S FORCE
FIELD COUNTERACTS
ALL ENERGY THAT ATTACKS IT.
NOW ALLOW ME TO TEACH
YOU SOME MANNERS.
- AHH!
- AH!
( sighs )
AHHH!
- SHADOW!
- 700 YEARS IS A BIT TOO LONG
OF A REST FOR YOU, RYOKO.
YOU CAN'T EVEN TELL THE REAL ME
FROM MY SHADOW.
THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
- KAGATO, DON'T-- MY ARM.
( grunting )
AHHH!
- YOU LOOK QUITE NICE IN GRAY.
YOU WILL SHOW ME THE SECRET
OF TSUNAMI UNIT, PRINCESS AYEKA.
- ( beeping )
- THIS PLACE
IS REALLY REALLY WEIRD.
WHERE'D THEY GO?
KAGATO MIGHT HAVE THEM ALREADY.
AND IF HE DOES,
THAT MEANS I'M ALL ALONE.
WELL, THAT'S OKAY
BECAUSE I'M A
GALAXY POLICEPERSON
AND I CAN HANDLE IT.
I'LL JUST CAPTURE KAGATO
ALL MYSELF AND-- AND--
WHAAA!
AHHH!
I ORDER YOU TO STAY AWAY!
HEY, I'M FEELING LIKE I HATE
SNAKES.
YOU HAVE A RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT, YOU SNAKES.
ANYTHING YOU COULD SAY
CAN BE USED AGAINST YOU
AS EVIDENCE IN A COURT OF LAW.
YOU HAVE A RIGHT TO AN ATTORNEY
AND I GUESS IT WILL HAVE TO
BE AN ATTORNEY THAT
HANDLES NO-ARMED SNAKE FACES
AND THEN--
( panting )
AND THEN...
THAT'S ALL.
- ( beeping )
- ( glass shattering )
- HEY.
THE CHARGES AGAINST YOU
WILL BE REALLY BAD
IF YOU TRY TO ESCAPE.
I'M REALLY SERIOUS NOW.
I REALLY AM.
THIS THING ISN'T WORKING.
IT'S NOT POWERFUL ENOUGH.
I SHOULD HAVE
PAID MORE ATTENTION
WHEN THEY EXPLAINED
HOW TO USE THESE THINGS.
MMMM AHHHH!
HUH?
( whimpers )
- OKAY, TAKE IT EASY.
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
THANKS FOR SETTING ME FREE,
BY THE WAY.
THIS IS A DANGEROUS PLACE
YOU'RE IN, YOU KNOW?
- YOU'RE NOT KIDDING.
- LET'S GET THESE
OUT OF THE WAY.
RISE AND SHINE.
THERE SHE IS.
NOW THIS GIRL'S
TOTALLY OUT OF CONTROL.
DON'T YOU AGREE, MIHOSHI?
- WELL...
- LOOKS LIKE NOTHING'S BROKEN.
- UM, EXCUSE ME?
- THAT JERK TRIED
TO DESTROY HER, HUH?
WELL, I'LL SHOW HIM.
- ( sighs )
- EXCUSE ME?  WHO ARE YOU?
YOUR OUTFIT SEEMS TO BE
A SCIENCE ACADEMY UNIFORM
FROM A LONG TIME AGO.
- YOUR BODY IS SAGGING A BIT.
THE DETERIORATION
OF YOUR MUSCLES
DEFINITELY
AFFECTS YOUR ABILITY TO FIGHT.
IT ALSO AFFECTS YOUR VISUAL
PSYCHOLOGICAL TACTICS.
OH!
- OKAY, PIPSQUEAK, WHETHER MY
BODY IS SAGGING OR NOT
IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
WHAT ARE VISUAL PSYCHOLOGICAL
TACTICS ANYWAY?
- YOUR SEX APPEAL, OF COURSE.
- HEY, I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW
MY BODY SHAPE HASN'T CHANGED
FOR THE PAST 700 YEARS!
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT,
YOU BIG FAT SMART ALECK?
- WHAT I THINK IS THAT'S NO WAY
TO TALK TO YOUR MOTHER, RYOKO.
- ( grunts )
- THAT'S RIGHT.  IN FACT,
NOT ONLY DID I CREATE YOU,
BUT I CREATED RYO-OHKI,
I CREATED THE SOJA.
I'VE CREATED SO MANY THINGS,
REALLY.
BUT I USED MY OVA FOR YOU,
SO I'M MORE LIKE YOUR
MOTHER THAN YOUR CREATOR.
- YOU MUST BE THAT
FEMALE STUDENT
THAT WAS KIDNAPPED BY KAGATO.
- A FEMALE STUDENT?
NO, I AM WASHU!
AND I JUST HAPPEN TO
BE THE TOP SCIENTIFIC
GENIUS OF THE UNIVERSE.
I AM CUTE,
I HAVE TO ADMIT!
I LOOK A LITTLE YOUNG
TO BE A MOM, DON'T I, RYOKO?
- HUH?  BALONEY!
I'VE BEEN ALONE FOR 2,000 YEARS,
EVER SINCE I WAS BORN,
EVER SINCE I WAS--
I WAS BORN.
BUT WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS THIS PLACE?
- THIS IS THE REVERSED WORLD.
- REVERSED?
- THIS SHIP HAS TWO LAYERS--
IT HAS A TOP AND A BOTTOM.
BUT THE INTERSECTION
BETWEEN THEM IS ONE WAY,
SO THAT MEANS--
- FORGET ABOUT THAT!
TELL ME HOW TO GET TO KAGATO.
- WANT TO TAKE REVENGE
FOR TENCHI?
- HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT TENCHI?
- AS YOU ARE CONNECTED
WITH RYO-OHKI,
SO AM I CONNECTED WITH YOU,
MY DEAR.
SO I KNOW EVERYTHING.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT TENCHI.
- UH...
- YOU LIKE HIM!  YOU LOVE HIM.
YOU'VE NEVER
FELT LIKE THIS BEFORE,
AND YOU'LL DO ANYTHING FOR HIM.
ON TOP OF ALL THAT,
YOU WANT TO DO THIS AND THAT
WITH TENCHI.
- OH!
- NOW DON'T YOU?
- OH, SHE'S THINKING ABOUT THAT?
- HEY, STOP!
SHUT UP!
- IF YOU WANT TO GO,
I WON'T STOP YOU.
FOR YOU, IT'S A PIECE OF CAKE.
- PLEASE STOP, RYOKO.
SHE IS NOT THE ONE
YOU SHOULD POINT YOUR SWORD AT.
- OH!
- HMM.
- RYOKO, I SHOULD
HAVE STAYED OUT OF THIS.
- RYOKO?  BEFORE YOU GO,
I HAVE TO ASK YOU ONE THING.
I WONDER, COULD YOU PLEASE--
DO YOU THINK
YOU COULD CALL ME MOM?
- ( grunts )
- HEY, RYOKO!
BUT WHY SHOULDN'T WE
GO WITH HER?
- BECAUSE IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
ONCE WE'RE ON THIS SIDE
OF THE WORLD, WE CAN'T GET OUT
UNLESS KAGATO IS DESTROYED.
- BUT SHE--
- PLEASE TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
THAT WAS RYOKO'S ASTRO BODY
I BROUGHT HERE.
HER PHYSICAL BODY
IS ON THE OTHER SIDE.
- OH.
NOW WHERE ARE WE?
- OH!
- Yosho: AYEKA?  AYEKA?
- HMM?
- AYEKA.
- YOSHO!  OH!
- AYEKA,
I NEED TO KNOW SOMETHING.
- TELL ME, YOSHO.
WHAT IS IT?
- AYEKA, TELL ME ABOUT THE POWER
THE MASTER KEY CAN ACTIVATE,
THE POWER EMBODIED IN THE TREES
OF THE ROYAL FAMILY,
THE STRONGEST POWER IN THE
UNIVERSE-- TSUNAMI.
TSUNAMI?
- HOW IS IT THAT ONLY YOUR
RELATIVES CAN CONTROL IT?
TELL ME!
- OH NO!
NO, YOU ARE NOT YOSHO.
OH, LET ME GO!
LET ME GO!
- ( laughs )
IS IT YOUR BLOOD?
- LET GO!
- OR DO I NEED
SOMETHING ELSE, MY DEAR?
- HELP ME!
HELP, PLEASE!
SOMEONE HELP ME!
TENCHI!
- AHHHH!
WELL, I SEE TSUNAMI MUST BE
PROTECTING THOSE OF ROYAL BLOOD.
IN THAT CASE--
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
- WELL, THE SHREW
THAT WAS IN THE WORLD
OF SHADOW HAS RETURNED, I SEE.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I'VE BEEN WAITING.
BUT THEN YOUR TIMING
WAS NEVER PERFECT.
- I'M AT YOUR SERVICE.
- ( grunts )
WHERE AM I?
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
- Woman: YOU ARE ALL RIGHT NOW.
- HUH?
WHO ARE YOU?
TELL ME WHERE WE ARE.
- I AM TSUNAMI,
THE SHIP OF JURAI.
AND WE ARE INSIDE OF MYSELF.
- INSIDE OF YOU?
BUT YOU'RE HUMAN.
WAIT, I GET IT.
YOU OWN THIS SHIP, RIGHT?
- NO.
THE OWNER OF THIS SHIP
IS SASAMI.
- SASAMI?
- YES.
YOU SEE, WHAT I AM
IS THE MIND OF THE SHIP.
- YOU'RE LIKE A HUMAN VERSION
OF RYO-OHKI?
OH MY GOD!  RYO-OHKI!
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
- I CAN DETECT RYO-OH'S KEY
70 LIGHT SECONDS FROM US
AT THIS MOMENT.
- ARE THEY STILL ALIVE?
- I FEEL RYO OH'S KEY
RESPONDING FROM WITHIN SOJA.
- ALIVE?
- THEY MUST BE IN CLOSE COMBAT.
- COMBAT? ARE THEY REALLY
FIGHTING OVER THERE
ON THAT SHIP?
PLEASE TAKE ME THERE.
WE HAVE TO GET IN THERE.
- TENCHI, LISTEN TO ME.
I CANNOT LEAVE HERE.
ON THIS JOURNEY,
YOU WILL HAVE TO GO ALONE.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT WITH YOU?
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT WITH ME.
- WELL THEN...
- Mihoshi: THERE'S NO WAY OUT?
- Washu:
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
YOU SEE HERE
ON THE SHIP'S DIAGRAM,
THAT GOES THIS WAY
AND THIS GOES THAT WAY.
- UH-HUH.
- AND SO THERE IS NO WAY OUT.
ABSOLUTELY NONE.
NO WAY!  THAT'S IT.
GOT IT?
- UM, NOPE. I DON'T
GET IT AT ALL.
- OH!
- SO I GUESS
WHAT YOU'RE TELLING ME
IS THERE'S ABSOLUTELY NO WAY
OUT OF HERE?
- WHERE WERE YOU
WHEN THEY HANDED OUT THE BRAINS?
- BUT HOW CAN THIS BE? YOU
CREATED THIS SHIP, DIDN'T YOU?
- MM-HMM.  AND THAT IS
WHY IT IS SO PERFECT!
- ( banging )
- ( gasps )
- ( sobbing )
- OKAY, YOU PAIN IN THE NECK.
THERE ARE ONLY A COUPLE THINGS
WE CAN DO HERE.
- RYOKO!
AND WHAT SHOULD I DO NOW?
- TAKE THIS AND JOIN IN.
- HURRAY HURRAY, RYOKO!
( blowing whistle )
WATCH OUT.
- AHH!
- HA!
- ALL RIGHT, RYOKO NAILED HIM.
- I SURE HOPE SHE DID.
- THIS PILLAR IS VERY DENSE.
HE MUST HAVE GOTTEN
SERIOUSLY DAMAGED.
( gasps ) AH!
OH!  AHH!
- WHERE ARE YOUR MANNERS,
PRINCESS?
- AHHH!
- ( grunting )
- I AM GOING TO ENJOY
CRUSHING YOU.
- YES, I'M SURE YOU
WOULD IF YOU COULD.
- WHAT?
- JUST WHAT SEEMS
TO BE THE PROBLEM, RYOKO?
- BUT WHY DOESN'T RYOKO
USE HER FULL POWER?
- WOWEE!
YOU MEAN SHE ISN'T?
- IF SHE WAS,
THIS WOULD BE OVER BY NOW.
- WELL, EXCUSE ME.
- RYOKO CAN'T BEAT HIM
LIKE THAT,
EVEN ON HER OWN TURF.
- Mihoshi: RYOKO.
- AHHHH!
- ( grunting )
- AHA.  THAT WAS WHY.
- AHA, THAT WAS WHY WHAT?
- IF RYOKO
USES HER FULL STRENGTH,
AYEKA WILL BE BURNT TO A CINDER
BY THE COUNTER FLOW
OF THE EXTRA ENERGY.
- WELL, YOU SEEM
TO HAVE A LOT OF IDEAS.
WHAT SHOULD SHE DO?
- HAND ME YOUR CUBE.
- AHHHH!
- COME TO ME, AYEKA.
- AYEKA.
- WE CAN'T GET OVER THERE,
BUT THEY CAN COME HERE.
- Kagato: YOU ARE MAKING IT
EASIER FOR RYOKO TO FIGHT, HUH?
EVEN I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
TO AYEKA
NOW THAT SHE'S
IN ANOTHER DIMENSION.
- WHY DON'T YOU LEAVE US ALONE?
'CAUSE IF YOU DO,
I'LL LET YOU GO FREE.
- GO FREE?
- RYOKO AND I ARE NOT
UNDER YOUR POWER ANYMORE.
- AND I AM NO LONGER
YOUR STUDENT, PROFESSOR.
DO YOU THINK
I HAVEN'T LEARNED ANYTHING
IN THE PAST 5,000 YEARS?
- WHAT DID YOU JUST DO?!
- I DIRECTED ALL THE FORCE
OF THE GEMS FOR SOJA.
ALTHOUGH I COULD MAKE IT
AS COMPACT AS RYOKO.
I THINK YOU'LL FIND THE POWER
I CAN PRODUCE AT ONE TIME
IS FAR GREATER THAN RYOKO'S.
- I'M GETTING WEAK.
MY POWER IS DRAINING.
- ( whirring )
- PROFESSOR, I'M GOING TO
SHOW YOU A LITTLE EXPERIMENT
JUST LIKE THE OLD DAYS.
- I FORBID IT.
- PRINCESS AYEKA, YOU'RE IN
NO POSITION TO FORBID ANYTHING.
AND SINCE
YOU'RE NOT COOPERATING,
I'LL INTERROGATE
YOUR BROTHER AND SISTER INSTEAD.
( laughs )
- NO, PLEASE DON'T!
SASAMI!  YOSHO!
- THERE IT IS,
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
IT IS TRULY AMAZING.
HOW CAN IT TAKE UP
SO MUCH ENERGY, HUH?
WHAT? WHOA!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
OH!
- THE 10 WINGS
OF THE NIGHT HAWK,
THE ROYAL FAMILY'S
MOST POWERFUL SHIP-- TSUNAMI.
- IS THAT IT?
- Kagato: MY SHIELD
IS COMPLETELY USELESS.
BUT THAT'S NOT ALL
THE GEMS CAN DO.
NO!
THAT WAS ONLY THE BEGINNING.
- THAT IS THE MOST POWERFUL
OF ALL SHIPS.
- THERE IS ONE FINAL USE
FOR YOU.
WHEN YOU LOSE CONSCIOUSNESS,
ALL THE POWER FROM YOUR GEMS
WILL BE SOJA'S TO USE.
IT'S A PITY, RYOKO,
THAT YOU WON'T LIVE TO SEE ME
AS THE RULER
OF THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE.
- I'M SORRY, TENCHI.
- AH!
WHAT WAS THAT?!
- TENCHI.
- ( gasps )
ARE YOU REAL?
- I'M NO GHOST!
- Kagato: DIDN'T THINK
YOU WERE STILL ALIVE, KID.
- NO, TENCHI, DON'T.
- NOW I'LL BE FINE.
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU PLAN TO DO?
- HUH?
JEEZ!  I CAN'T GET IT OUT!
- AND NOW I'M WORRIED.
- ( grunting )
- Kamidake: TENCHI,
LET US HANDLE THIS.
- WHAT?
HUH?
- HERE WE COME.
- WHAT A COMICAL PAIR
YOU TWO ARE.
- I GOT IT!
- ( both shouting )
- YOU TWO LOOK AFTER RYOKO.
- Azaka: YES, SIR!
- AYYYYY!
WHAT THE--
DAMN!
JUST WHEN I NEED IT MOST.
- JUST A RUSTY OLD PIECE
OF JUNK.
- WHOA!
( grunting )
- THE MASTER KEY IS JUST A TOOL
TO ACTIVATE THE
POWER OF THIS SHIP.
IT'S USELESS WHEN CUT OFF
FROM THE SHIP'S POWER.
- YEEEEAAA!
OOOHHHH!
- TENCHI?
OH, I CAN'T MOVE.
HEY, YOU TWO, WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?! GO HELP HIM.
- WE CAN'T.
KAGATO'S FORCE IS INCREASING
AT AN INCREDIBLE RATE.
WE ARE USING ALL OUR POWER
JUST TO SHIELD IT.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOUR SWORD DOESN'T HELP ANYMORE?
IF ONLY YOU HAD
LEFT THESE WOMEN BEHIND,
YOU COULD HAVE REMAINED ALIVE.
- I WOULD RATHER DIE
THAN FORSAKE ANY ONE OF THEM.
- ( laughs )
- OH!
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT WITH ME
BECAUSE I HAVE ALL THE GEMS!
( laughs )
- ( screaming )
- ( laughing )
MARVELOUS POWER, SPLENDID.
( laughs )
COME TO ME NOW, TSUNAMI!
- ( gasps )
- NO!
THIS CAN'T BE THE END.
- DO SOMETHING BRILLIANT.
YOU CREATED THIS
SHIP, DIDN'T YOU?
- SHE'S RIGHT.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING
YOU HAVEN'T THOUGHT OF.
- WELL, OKAY, SO THERE IS JUST
ONE MORE THING THAT WE CAN TRY.
- WHAT IS IT?
- WE CAN PRAY REAL HARD.
( speaking Japanese )
- ( gasps )
TSUNAMI, I'M SCARED.
- IT WON'T BE LONG NOW.
YOUR POWER JOINED WITH MINE--
WE'LL BE UNBEATABLE
IN THE UNIVERSE.
- TENCHI, I'M SCARED.
- I'M SORRY TO FAIL YOU.
I AM NOT CAPABLE
OF RESCUING YOUR SISTER.
I CAN'T EVEN USE THIS SWORD.
- Tsunami: HAVE FAITH
IN YOUR OWN POWER.
- HUH?
- PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
SOJA IS VERY DANGEROUS.
- AS LONG AS I HAVE THIS SWORD,
I CAN MANAGE SOMEHOW.
- LISTEN.
- WHAT?
- DON'T RELY
ON THE SWORD ALONE.
TENCHI, YOU'LL HAVE TO TRUST
IN YOUR OWN POWER.
- TRUST IN MY OWN POWER?
MY POWER?
- YES.
- Kagato: HOW CAN YOU
HAVE ANY POWER LEFT?
- I HAVE BEEN RELYING
ON THIS SWORD TOO MUCH.
- I WAS GOING
TO FINISH YOU LATER,
BUT WHY NOT NOW, HUH?
SO YOU'RE GIVING UP?
- Ryoko:
TENCHI, RUN!  GET AWAY!
( grunting ) STOP.
AW, PLEASE DON'T.
OH, YOU GOT EVERYTHING
YOU WANTED.
PLEASE SPARE HIM.
- CAN THIS BOY
REALLY MEAN THAT MUCH TO YOU?
WELL, NOT TO WORRY.
VERY SOON YOU AND PRINCESS AYEKA
WILL JOIN HIM--
VERY SOON INDEED.
HE WON'T BE ALONE IN DEATH.
- NO!
- OH!
- AH, NOW IT'S YOUR TURN.
AH, IMPOSSIBLE. I THOUGHT
THE POWER FROM TSUNAMI
WAS COMPLETELY CUT OFF.
IT'S YOU!
- AH!
- IT'S YOU!
YOU'RE CREATING ALL THIS.
- THE TRANSFORMATION
OF OBJECTS.
THE WINGS OF THE LIGHT HAWK!
UNBELIEVABLE.
- AHHH!
NOW!
GET HIM!
- AHHH!
- I'VE GOT YOU!
- YEEEAAA!
( groaning )
- TENCHI.
SAME NAME AS THE MASTER KEY.
WELL DONE, TSUNAMI.
TENCHI CAN'T BE COPIED.
SPLENDID PLAN.
YOU'VE WON, BOY.
- A BOY WHO CAN
CREATE THE WINGS OF
THE LIGHT HAWK, HUH?
I WANT TO MAKE HIM MINE!
- TENCHI!
- All: HI, TENCHI!
All: OH, TENCHI!
OW!
- ( laughs )
TOO BAD!
I'M GOING TO BE THE FIRST
TO GIVE TENCHI A HUG.
TENCHI!
- ( meows )
- I SAID I'M FIRST!
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME IS WASHU.
I WOULD LIKE TO THANK YOU
FOR SAVING ME FROM KAGATO.
- UH, UM...
- I LIKE YOU.
DO YOU WANT TO BE A GUINEA PIG
FOR MY EXPERIMENTS?
- WHAAA!
- LISTEN, MOM!
- WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
- OH, TENCHI!
- ( girls all squealing )
- OOOH!
SHUT UP!
- AH!
- ( all gasping )
- HMMM?
- I GUESS THE SPACESHIP
WAS CUT IN HALF ALSO.
- All:
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
- ( whistling )
- HUH?
- Kamidake: THANK YOU.
- Azaka:
WE APPRECIATE YOUR WORK.
- AHHHH!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH HIM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- Mihoshi: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CUT IT OUT, PLEASE, BOTH OF YOU.
- Ryoko: SHUT UP.
- Washu: LEAVE THEM ALONE!
- Mihoshi: I CAN'T.
- Sasami: BREAKFAST IS READY!
- Ryoko: HEY, YOU GUYS!
- Azaka: JUST ANOTHER
PEACEFUL BREAKFAST, HUH?
- Kamidake: YES.
IT'S GOING TO BE
ANOTHER FINE DAY
ON PLANET EARTH.
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ LIFE IS SO FULL
OF HURRY AND HUSTLE ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I THINK
IT'S PASSING US BY ♪
♪ THE DAYS ARE LIKE HOURS,
HOURS LIKE MINUTES ♪
♪ I'M CAUGHT IN IT
TILL I LOOK IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND TO MY SURPRISE ♪
♪ I FIND THERE IS A HEAVEN ♪
♪ TIME IS UNREAL,
MAKING ME FEEL ♪
♪ FREE AND ALIVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME,
YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
IN SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME,
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE
LIGHT-YEARS AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TELEPHONE LOVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME, YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
TO SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME ♪
♪ WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE LIGHT-YEARS
AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TELEPHONE LOVE. ♪