- ( theme music playing )
- OH.
HUH?
THAT'S A ROYAL TEARDROP.
- Man: AYEKA?
- HUH?
FOR YOU, YOSHO.
( giggles )
- AYEKA, WHY ARE YOU OUT HERE?
- BECAUSE YOU WENT OUT,
LEAVING ME BEHIND.
- ( laughs )
- AH!
ONE DAY,
I WILL BE YOUR BRIDE,
WON'T I, YOSHO?
- WHEN YOU GROW UP.
- IT IS THE COLOR OF YOUR EYES.
- A ROYAL TEARDROP?
- MM-HMM.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- THIS FLOWER
SHOULDN'T BE USED
FOR HAPPY OCCASIONS.
- ( glass shattering )
- ( Ryoko laughing )
- YOU DEVIL!
AYY!  AHHH!
- TAKE ME WITH YOU!
YOSHO, TAKE ME WITH YOU!
YOSHO!
( panting )
WHERE ARE YOU?!
YOSHO?
( gasps ) YOSHO!
( gasps )
- YOSHO?  BUT HE'S DEAD.
- WHAT?
- HERE, TAKE THIS
TO REMEMBER HIM BY.
- AHHH!
( screaming continues )
OH.
( moans )
HE ISN'T DEAD.
HE CAN'T BE.
- ( birds singing )
- I WISH I COULD GO HOME
TO PLANET JURAI.
HMM?
WHAT IS SHE UP TO SO EARLY?
REALLY, WHAT A
DISGUSTING THING TO SEE
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING.
OH, THAT MONSTER WOMAN.
UGH!
- HMM, LET'S SEE.
AHA!
( laughs )
HMM.
- COME ON, AYEKA!
- I DON'T WANT TO.  NO.
I DON'T WANT TO!
- DON'T BE SO DIFFICULT.
LISTEN TO ME, AYEKA.
YOU'VE STAYED IN THIS
ROOM FOR ONE WHOLE WEEK.
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
IT'S VERY RUDE.
THEY'RE GOING TO
THINK WE JURAIANS
DON'T EVEN HAVE THE COURTESY
TO SAY HELLO!
- NO, THEY WON'T, SASAMI!
UM, BUT THE HEAD OF THE FAMILY
IS OUT NOW, ISN'T HE?
- THE FATHER MAY BE OUT,
BUT I CAN TELL YOU THIS--
TENCHI IS AT HOME.
THIS IS VERY VERY HARD ON ME.
- I'M SORRY, SASAMI.
I SHOULD BE THE ONE
TO WORRY ABOUT THESE THINGS.
- ( sighs )
- LET'S GO.
- PHEW!
HUH?
HMM.
- HMMM!
- ( gasps )
I HATE THIS!
- HUH?
COME ON, AYEKA!
- OH.
- WELL, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
IT'S BEEN SO LONG,
I WAS BEGINNING TO THINK
YOU'D DIED, YOUR MAJESTY.
- WHERE'S TENCHI?
- TENCHI? WELL, HE ISN'T HERE,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
- AND I WORKED SO HARD
TO GET AYEKA OUT HERE.
HEY!
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
WHAT IS IT?
- MMM, WANT TO KNOW?
- MM-HMM.
- HMMM!
- WOW!
- IT WAS BORN THIS MORNING.
ISN'T IT ADORABLE?
- DID YOU LAY IT?
- NO, SASAMI!
GET AWAY, DON'T TOUCH IT.
- ( yawns )
WHAT?  MISS AYEKA.
- OH.
PLEASE ALLOW ME TO EXPRESS
MY SINCERE GRATITUDE
FOR THE HOSPITALITY
KINDLY OFFERED
TO JURAI AND MY OWN FAMILY.
AH, ANYWAY,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
- WHAT?  YEAH, SURE.
- HEY HEY, PRINCESS, DON'T YOU
WANT TO KNOW ABOUT THIS EGG?
- I HAVE NO INTENTIONS
OF SPEAKING WITH YOU.
HA!
SASAMI, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'LL GET GERMS FROM THAT.
- BUT RYOKO'S BABY
IS GOING TO BE BORN,
AND THAT'S DEFINITELY SOMETHING
I WANT TO SEE.
SO ARE YOU MARRIED, RYOKO?
WHO'S THE FATHER?
- WELL NOW...
- SASAMI!
- YOU SEE?
- ( gasps ) TENCHI'S THE FATHER!
- WHAT?
- HUH?
WHAT?  MISS AYEKA,
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
YOU SEEM UPSET.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THAT IS CERTAINLY
NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GO OVER THERE
AND HOLD THAT EGG
WITH YOUR MONSTER WOMAN?
- EGG?  WHAT ON EARTH
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- OH, I'M SO HAPPY!
SO HAPPY TO BE ABLE
TO BEAR A CHILD
OF THE MAN I LOVE.
- A CHILD?!
- GO AHEAD, FEEL IT NOW.
IT WON'T BE LONG.
- ( groans )
- HUH?  WHAT?!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- ( egg squealing )
- HUH?
( screaming )
- ( gasps )
( laughs )
- ( meows )
( cooing )
- ( Ryoko laughs ) OH.
COME HERE.
THERE'S A GOOD LITTLE RYO-OHKI.
- RYO-OHKI?
YOUR SPACE SHIP?
THEN THAT'S THE CHILD OF--
- ( laughs )
- IT CAN'T BE TRUE.
- OH, YEAH, PRINCESS.
YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT'S TRUE.
- CAN A SPACE SHIP
HAVE A BABY?
- SURE.
MY SHIP WAS TOTALLY DESTROYED,
SO IT REPRODUCED ITSELF.
YOU MUST BE CRAZY TO THINK
IT'S TENCHI'S CHILD.
- YEAH, I THOUGHT
THAT WAS KIND OF STRANGE.
- THIS IS SO TYPICAL.
YOU'RE ALL MAKING FUN OF ME.
- UH, MISS AYEKA,
WE'RE NOT MAKING FUN OF YOU.
AT LEAST, I'M NOT.
- YOU STOP IT!  LET GO!
I WAS SO FOOLISH.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE DIFFERENT.
WHY DON'T YOU GO HAVE
A GOOD TIME WITH THAT
FOSSIL WOMAN OF YOURS?
- ( Ryoko laughs )
- ( crying )
- WHOOPS.
- I BEG YOUR PARDON.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, MISS?
WHAT IS IT?
- UM...
UM, NO NO...
NOTHING REALLY.
- ( meows )
- ( laughs )
- ( yawns ) YOU KNOW,
I FIND THAT PRINCESS SO AMUSING.
SHE REALLY KILLS ME.
- WHAT KIND OF MISCHIEF
ARE YOU UP TO NOW?
DON'T YOU HAVE
ANY CONSCIENCE AT ALL?
- YOU ARE JUST SO SWEET!
- WHAT?
OH!
- YOU'RE SO SWEET
TO BE SO CONCERNED ABOUT ME.
- ( groaning )
- TENCHI, DEAR,
WHERE'S THE SWORD?
- THE SWORD?
I GAVE IT BACK TO AYEKA.
- YOU WHAT?!
BUT THAT SWORD CONTAINS
ALL OF MY ENERGY SOURCE.
OH, WHY DID YOU GIVE IT BACK,
TENCHI?!
AWWWW!
( gasps )
- SECOND TIME TODAY A YOUNG
LADY HAS RUN INTO ME.
I GUESS I'M JUST LUCKY.
- GRANDPA, I'M SHOCKED.
- YEEEAH!
- THAT'S A SPRY YOUNG LADY
YOU'VE GOT THERE.
- HMM? MMM.  HMM?
- MMM, NOW THEN,
SO THIS IS TENCHI'S BABY,
IS IT?
- NO NO, GRANDPA.
THIS IS RYO-OHKI.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED?
HE JUST HATCHED
FROM AN EGG, GRANDPA.
- I SEE, I SEE.
TENCHI, NOW THAT YOU
ARE A FATHER OF A CHILD--
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
GRANDPA?
- --YOU'LL HAVE TO
BECOME RESPONSIBLE.
YES, YOU'VE GOT A BUMPY ROAD
AHEAD OF YOU.
- IT'S NOT MY CHILD!
OH, FORGET IT!
- ( door slides closed )
- TENCHI, DON'T FORGET PRACTICE
THIS AFTERNOON.
- TENCHI, WAIT!
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT HIM.
HE'S THE SERIOUS TYPE
JUST LIKE HIS MOTHER.
- ( meows )
- RYO-OHKI?
WHAT IS IT, RYO-OHKI?
( gasps )
AYEKA.
HEY, WHERE YOU GOING?
( bangs head )
OUCH!
RYO-OHKI?
- ( crashing )
- ( Sasami gasps )
- HUH?
- ( crying )
- ( meows )
- AHHH!  AHHH!
( screaming )
- ( meows )
- RYO-OHKI!
SHH SHH SHHH!
GO AWAY, YOU DIRTY LITTLE THING.
- ( meows )
- ( gasps )
VERY WELL.
I WANT YOU TO STAY RIGHT THERE
AND I'LL BE THE ONE TO GO AWAY.
HA!
NOW DON'T YOU DARE FOLLOW ME.
I SAID DON'T FOLLOW ME!
- ( meows )
- HUH?
THE ROYAL TEARDROP?
IT CAN'T BE.
IT'S THE SAME COLOR
AS YOUR EYES.
ONE DAY I WILL BE YOUR BRIDE,
WON'T I, YOSHO?
( crying )
- ( meows )
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
PLEASE LEAVE ME ALONE.
- ( whimpers )
OH!
- ( crying )
HUH?
FOR ME?
- ( meows )
- THANK YOU.
BUT DIDN'T YOU KNOW
THAT I HATE YOU,
YOU FUNNY LITTLE THING?
- ( meows )
- ( laughs )
- HMM.
LET'S SEE, HMM.
NOW IF I WERE THAT SWORD,
WHERE WOULD I BE HIDING?
YOSHO!
HMM!  GOOD RIDDANCE.
ALTHOUGH I KIND OF LIKE HIM
IN THAT SIZE.
- Sasami:
AYEKA, WHERE ARE YOU?
- THIS ISN'T
GOING TO LOOK GOOD.
- SHE ISN'T IN HERE.
WHERE DID EVERYONE GO TO?
- SO TELL ME,
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
WITH MY SPACE SHIP DESTROYED,
I CAN NEITHER FLY
NOR COMMUNICATE WITH MY PEOPLE.
- ( meows )
- THE ONLY CLUE I HAVE
IS THE SWORD.
I WONDER...
COULD MY BROTHER REALLY BE...
BUT YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
A WORD I SAY.
- ( meows )
- OH! WHAT IS IT?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
YOU'LL GET LOST!
RYO-OHKI!
I CAN'T FIND HIM ANYWHERE.
- ( sticks clashing )
- Man: HYAH!
- HUH?
- ( grunting )
- TENCHI, WATCH YOUR FEET.
- YEEAAA!
( groans )
- TRY HARDER.
- ( groaning )
- ( laughs )
- OUCH.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S START OVER
WITH THE BASIC PATTERNS.
- OKAY.
- HUH?
- READY?
- HAI!
- ( both grunting )
- THAT'S--
- ( grunting )
- THAT'S JUST LIKE THE
SWORDPLAY ROUTINES
OF JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY.
YOSHO--
COULD HE BE A CLUE
TO HIS WHEREABOUTS?
TENCHI?
WHAAAA!
- HUH?
AHHH!
- WHAT'S WRONG, TENCHI?
YOU'RE A SITTING DUCK.
- JEEZ, WAS THAT PART
OF THE ROUTINE?
- NO.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
( gasps ) HUH?
- WHY?  WHY MUST I SUFFER
FROM THIS KIND OF DISGRACE?
OOH!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING DOWN THERE?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M SORRY.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
- LADY AYEKA?
- I'M ALL RIGHT.  OH!
IT HURTS.
OH.
- RED BLOOD.
- ( birds chirping )
- HUH?
- UH, NOTHING.
NOTHING AT ALL.
- WHAT ARE YOU TWO
DOING THERE?
- UH, SIR?
- HMM.
THAT LOOKS
LIKE A BAD SPRAIN.
- SIR, THAT SWORDPLAY ROUTINE
YOU WERE PERFORMING,
I WAS WONDERING--
- TENCHI, CARRY THIS YOUNG
LADY HOME ON YOUR BACK.
SHE'D BETTER NOT BE
USING THIS FOOT FOR A WHILE.
- HEY!
- SIR? DID I SAY ANYTHING
TO OFFEND YOU?
- I'LL BE ON MY WAY HOME NOW.
YOU TAKE CARE OF HER.
- HEY!
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE, GRANDPA!
HMMM.
- Sasami: RYOKO, IT'S RAINING!
RYOKO, PLEASE STOP THE RAIN.
- ( sighs )
- STOP THE RAIN!
MY SISTER AND THE OTHERS
ARE STILL OUTSIDE.
- WELL, SORRY. ON THIS PLANET,
THEY DON'T HAVE A
WAY OF DOING THAT YET.
HEY, SASAMI DARLING,
DO YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW
WHERE YOUR ADORABLE SISTER
KEEPS TENCHI'S SWORD,
BY ANY CHANCE?
- YEAH, SHE CARRIES IT WITH HER
WHEREVER SHE GOES, I THINK.
- OF COURSE.
- ( grunts )
- OH.
- ( sighs )
HERE, YOU CAN DRY YOURSELF
WITH THIS.
UH, UMM...
- ( shivering )
- UH, I GUESS I'LL GO OUTSIDE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
OH, TENCHI.
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
A-CHEW!
- ( rustling )
- HUH?
OH.
- ( rustling )
- WHAT?
( screaming )
- HUH?  LADY AYEKA!
WHAT'S WRONG?
- SOMETHING--
SOMETHING LUNGED AT ME!
- ( meows )
- OH, DON'T WORRY.
IT'S ONLY RYO-OHKI.
- HUH?
- ( meows )
- OH.
HE SCARED THE DAYLIGHTS
OUT OF ME.
NAUGHTY THING.
- UH, OH.
- HMM?  OH.
- I'M GOING BACK OUTSIDE.
- OUTSIDE?
- YES?
- OUTSIDE IT MUST BE COLD.
- YEAH.
- WELL, I GUESS I MUST HAVE
MISUNDERSTOOD CERTAIN THINGS.
- HUH?
- SINCE YOU WERE WITH RYOKO,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE HER FRIEND.
- WELL, I'M NOT.
BUT I THINK I STARTED ALL THIS
BY OPENING THE GATE.
- THE GATE?
- NEAR HERE, THERE'S A CAVE
AND RYOKO WAS LOCKED UP IN IT.
- MY BROTHER YOSHO DID THAT.
- YOSHO?
THAT'S WHAT THE LEGEND SAYS.
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
- UH, SURE.
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO NOW?
- I'LL SEARCH.
YOU SEE, I KNOW I CANNOT RETURN
TO MY PLANET NOW.
I MUST CONTINUE THE SEARCH
FOR MY BROTHER.
ONLY IT'S HARD FOR ME.
I HAVE NO RELATIVES
ON THIS ALIEN PLANET.
- IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
PLEASE STAY WITH US
AS LONG AS YOU'D LIKE.
I'M THE ONE WHO'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR ALL THIS.
AND BESIDES,
YOU'RE RELATED TOO, I GUESS.
- ( meows )
- YOSHO IS MY HALF BROTHER.
HERE ON EARTH, YOU MAY THINK
IT ODD TO MARRY YOUR BROTHER,
BUT ON JURAI, IT'S NOT.
EVEN THOUGH
MY PARENTS ARRANGED IT,
I WAS HAPPY ABOUT IT.
JUST-- JUST TO THINK
THAT I WON'T BE ABLE
TO SHARE THESE FEELINGS
WITH MY BROTHER,
I-- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO ANYMORE!
( sobbing )
- HIS SHIP-- IT MUST HAVE BEEN
DESTROYED JUST LIKE YOURS WAS.
YEAH, THAT MUST BE IT!
AND HE WAS FORCED TO--
- ( sobbing )
- WELL, UH, SO YOU SHOULD
CHEER UP!
- HUH?
- CHEER UP, AYEKA!
- HMM?
- WHAT IS IT?
CARROT?
SO YOU WANT THIS CARROT?
- ( meows )
- THERE THERE.
HOP.
- ( meows )
- ( laughs )
- CARROTS, HUH?
EAT ENOUGH OF THOSE,
SOMEDAY YOU'LL GROW
UP TO BE A SPACE SHIP.
- ( meows )
- WHEW!
IT FINALLY CLEARED UP.
- HUH?
- WELL, SHALL WE GO NOW?
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO GO SEE RYOKO'S CAVE?
WE MIGHT JUST FIND A CLUE THERE
ABOUT YOUR BROTHER.
- WHAT-- WHAT IS THAT?
- OH, THAT'S THE HOLY TREE
OF MISAKI SHRINE.
WONDER STORIES HANG FROM IT.
THEY SAY IF YOU MAKE A WISH
WHEN THERE'S A FULL MOON,
IT'LL COME TRUE.
ANOTHER STORY SAYS YOU CAN
MAKE RAIN IF YOU PRAY FOR IT.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO SEE IT?
- MMM.
THERE IS NO DOUBT.
THIS IS FUNAHO.
IT IS ALIVE.
- FUNAHO?
- MY BROTHER'S SPACE SHIP.
REMEMBER THERE WAS A TREE
EXACTLY LIKE THIS IN MY SHIP?
THIS TREE IS THE BRAIN OF THE
SHIP, THE HEART OF THE SHIP.
- WOW! THIS TRANSFORMS INTO
ONE OF THOSE GIANT SPACE SHIPS?
- NO.
THIS ONE HAS TAKEN ROOT.
IT CAN'T BECOME A SPACE SHIP
ANYMORE.
- ( hollow echoing )
- WHOA!  WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- THE SHIP'S MEMORY.
- MEMORY?
THAT'S--
- THAT'S MY BROTHER'S SHIP!
- Tenchi:
RYOKO-- SHE LOOKS SCARY.
AND HE MUST BE YOSHO.
THIS MUST BE
HOW THE LAKE WAS MADE.
- ( Ryoko moaning )
- HE IS ALIVE.
I'M SURE OF IT NOW.
SINCE FUNAHO IS ALIVE,
THEN SOMEWHERE ON THIS PLANET,
HE MUST BE ALIVE ALSO.
I'VE BEEN COLD TO YOU.
I'VE BEEN NASTY
AND I'M SORRY FOR THAT.
I BELIEVE THIS IS YOURS.
- WHAT?
- YOU ARE RELATED BY BLOOD
TO JURAI'S ROYAL FAMILY.
AND I AM ASKING YOU
TO PROTECT US UNTIL THE TIME
MY BROTHER IS FOUND.
- BUT I'M NO GOOD
AT HANDLING THAT SWORD.
- AYEKA!
( panting )
- SASAMI!
- WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
YOU'VE BEEN GONE SO LONG,
I WAS WORRIED.
- I AM SORRY.
DID YOU COME ALL THIS WAY
BY YOURSELF?
- OH NO, RYOKO IS WITH ME.
AND RYO-OHKI MET US HALFWAY.
HE BROUGHT US HERE.
- ( meows )
- ( laughs )
YOU ARE
ONE FUNNY LITTLE CREATURE.
- Ryoko:
OKAY OKAY OKAY.
MY, WHAT A FRIENDLY ATMOSPHERE.
- Tenchi: RYOKO.
- HA!  NOW, TENCHI,
HOW COME YOU'VE BEEN WITH THIS
UNWORTHY GIRL ALL THIS TIME?
- BECAUSE I HAD TO.
LADY AYEKA INJURED HERSELF.
- MMM?  WOW, TENCHI,
YOU GOT THE SWORD BACK.
WELL DONE, MY BOY!
- NO, I RETURNED THE SWORD
TO LORD TENCHI.
- HUH?
OKAY!  SO YOU'RE PISSED
WE GOT IT BACK.
AND IT'S NO USE
TRYING TO LIE TO ME.
- BUT IT'S TRUE.
- HMM?
- WE ARE RELATED BY BLOOD,
LORD TENCHI AND I.
AND ANYWAY, IT'S REALLY
NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
- OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
YOU INGRATE!
OH!
AND I CAME ALL THIS WAY
JUST TO HELP YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
DO WHAT YOU WANT.
- RYOKO, COME BACK!
- Both: TO HELP US?
- HEY!
COME BACK!
IT'S ALL A MISUNDERSTANDING.
WE DIDN'T MEAN ANY HARM,
RYOKO!
- FORGET IT.
- BUT YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT SHE'S GOING TO DO
WHEN SHE GETS UPSET, YOU KNOW?
- OH, I SEE.
AND HERE I THOUGHT YOU
WERE GOING TO PROTECT ME,
LORD TENCHI.
LET'S GO, LORD TENCHI.
- HUH?
- COME NOW.
- OH.
- HUH?
- ( meows )
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ LIFE IS SO FULL
OF HURRY AND HUSTLE ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I THINK
IT'S PASSING US BY ♪
♪ THE DAYS ARE LIKE HOURS,
HOURS LIKE MINUTES ♪
♪ I'M CAUGHT IN IT
TILL I LOOK IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND TO MY SURPRISE ♪
♪ I FIND THERE IS A HEAVEN ♪
♪ TIME IS UNREAL,
MAKING ME FEEL ♪
♪ FREE AND ALIVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME,
YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
IN SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME,
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE
LIGHT-YEARS AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TELEPHONE LOVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME, YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
TO SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME ♪
♪ WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE LIGHT-YEARS
AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TELEPHONE LOVE. ♪
- ( silent )