- ( theme music playing )
- IF THAT BOY IS IN YOUR WAY,
YOU MUST OBEY ME.
ELIMINATE HIM.
- Washu: NOW THAT'S CUTE.
- HUH? ( gasps )
WASHU.
IF I TAKE YOU WITH ME...
- ( grunts )
( gasps )
( grunts )
THEN I WON'T HAVE
TO KILL TENCHI.
- Washu:
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO WITH THAT?
- HUH?
- GONNA TAKE THAT
LITTLE DOLLY TO DR. CLAY?
I HAD NO IDEA HE WENT
FOR THAT SORT OF THING.
- ( groans )
- BECAUSE IF IT'S A GIFT,
I CAN PUT A RIBBON
ON IT FOR YOU.
- HOW DID YOU KNOW
ABOUT ALL THIS?
- I THOUGHT THE LINK WITH YOU
WAS CUT OFF FOR SURE.
- I GUESS THE GEMS
ARE REAL, AREN'T THEY?
- HUH?
THAT DOES IT!
- I'M READY.
- ( grunts )
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
NO MORE VIOLENCE.
I WILL NOT ALLOW IT.
NOT IN THIS HOUSE.
- Azaka and Kamidake: OOH!
- HUH?
HEY, THAT'S MY ROOM.
- DON'T GET IN MY WAY.
- HUH?
- IF YOU DO,
I WILL KILL YOU.
- ( floor creaks )
- HUH?
- OH, TENCHI.
- RYOKO, WHAT'S UP?
- IT'S...
NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
- Ayeka: TENCHI!
- ( gasps )
- WATCH OUT!
- Ryoko: NO!
OH, TENCHI.
TENCHI.
- HMM.
- ( crying )
- Both: HUH?
- WE'RE GOING AFTER HER,
RYO-OHKI.
- ( meows )
- OH, DEAR.
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
- BUT YOU'RE GOING
TO COME WITH ME. YES, AYEKA?
- WELL, I GUESS
I COULDN'T LEAVE HER.
NOT LOOKING SO AWFULLY
PITIFUL ANYWAY.
- ( chuckles )
THANK YOU, AYEKA.
- Ayeka: DON'T YOU THINK THAT
COPY HAS A BETTER PERSONALITY
THAN THE REAL RYOKO?
- Washu: ( laughs )
YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
- UH--
- Ayeka: SHE'S UNIQUE.
DON'T YOU AGREE?
- Washu: I AGREE.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- DID YOU SAY THAT
WASN'T THE REAL RYOKO?
- THAT'S NOT EXACTLY
WHAT I SAID,
BUT I DID SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- THEN WHAT ABOUT
THE REAL RYOKO?
- WELL, THOSE GEMS ARE REAL,
SO THE REAL RYOKO'S
PROBABLY STILL ALIVE.
- ( sighs )
- Washu: YOU'RE PUTTING
A TRACE ON RYOKO,
AREN'T YOU, RYO-OHKI?
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- Washu: HUH?!
BATTLE ENERGY REACTION?
- ( Mihoshi screaming )
- IT'S MIHOSHI.
- YES, I WONDER
HOW SHE FOUND HIM.
- SHE'S A GENIUS.
I SWEAR IT.
- NOW, WASHU!
- HUH?
- IF THAT'S WHERE
RYOKO'S PRISONER,
THEN WE SHOULD STORM
THE PLACE AND GET HER.
- Washu:
I'LL FIND THAT BASTARD CLAY.
- WASHU, COME ON!
- WHY DON'T YOU HANG ON
A SECOND THERE
WHILE I PINPOINT
HIS LOCATION?
- ( screaming )
- AAH!
COME ON, WASHU! HURRY UP!
- ( screams )
- AAH!
- ( gasps )
MM, THAT MIHOSHI
REALLY IS HOPELESS.
- ( beeping )
- HUH.
THERE HE IS.
SEE, TENCHI?
HUH?  OH?
UH...
( sighs )
I WISH YOU WOULD TRY
THINKING A LITTLE MORE
BEFORE YOU ACT, TENCHI.
- SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW,
LORD TENCHI?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- FIRST, WE RESCUE MIHOSHI,
AND THEN--
- Mihoshi: WHOA!
- Both: OH?
( shouting )
PLEASE HELP ME,
HELP ME, HELP ME.
OH, NO. WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
WHOA!
( gasps )
I GOT YOU!
TAKE THAT AND THAT!
YES!
- LOOKS LIKE SHE'S
ALL RIGHT, I GUESS.
- ( Mihoshi shouting )
- ( sighs )
WELL, THAT BOY IS
PRETTY GOOD FOR AN EARTHLING.
BUT HE DOESN'T LOOK
GOOD ENOUGH
FOR WASHU TO BE
SO INTERESTED IN HIM.
WELL, AT ANY RATE,
THERE'S NO WAY
THEY CAN GET HERE.
( chuckles )
- Washu: THAT'S WHY I TOLD
THEM TO WAIT FOR AWHILE.
- WHAT?  WASHU?
HOW DID YOU GET HERE?
- YOU CERTAINLY LOOK OLDER,
DR. CLAY.
ALTHOUGH YOUR OCTOPUS HEAD
IS JUST LIKE THE OLD DAYS.
- ( grunts )
HUH?
YOU...
YOU'RE JUST THE SAME,
WASHU.
- ( chuckles )
- JUST LIKE WHEN WE
WERE COMPETING FOR
THE DIRECTOR'S CHAIR
AT THE ACADEMY.
BUT NOW IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO FIND OUT HOW I FELT
WHEN I WAS DRIVEN
OUT OF THE ACADEMY.
NOW IT'S YOUR TURN TO KNOW
HOW THAT FEELS, WASHU.
- HUH?  OHH!
- IT IS MY RECOMMENDATION
THAT YOU DO NOT MOVE.
IF YOU DO, THIS ENTIRE
SHIP WILL BLOW UP
ALONG WITH YOUR
PET GUINEA PIG.
NOT TO MENTION,
DEAR, WASHU,
THAT PRECIOUS GIRL OF YOURS.
- HUH.  OH WELL.
IT'S A GOOD THING IT'S
NOT SOMEONE LIKE AYEKA.
- ( yelling )
- SO PERHAPS
YOU CAN TELL ME
WHAT THOSE GEMS ARE
SHE WAS WEARING?
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
EVEN HER MAJESTY
COULDN'T FIGURE THEM OUT.
WHICH FRANKLY
SURPRISES ME.
- ( imitating Clay )
ACTUALLY, FRANKLY AND HONESTLY,
I DON'T KNOW EITHER.
THEY'VE BEEN AROUND
SINCE I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
- ( groans )
WELL, THAT IS INTERESTING.
BY THE WAY,
I REALLY MUST SAY
I WAS VERY SURPRISED
TO HEAR YOU CALL THAT BOY
A GUINEA PIG.
I THINK IT WAS
THE FIRST TIME
I EVER HEARD A HUMAN
CALLED THAT.
WHAT ABOUT HIM
DO YOU LIKE?
HE DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
ESPECIALLY WORTHWHILE MATERIAL.
ANYONE AS EASY TO TRICK AS HE
MUST BE A BLOCKHEAD.
OH, PARDON ME.
- ACTUALLY, THAT'S WHAT
I LIKE ABOUT HIM.
BESIDES, JUST BECAUSE
I CALL HIM MY LITTLE GUINEA PIG
DOESN'T NECESSARILY
MEAN THAT HE'S
A RESEARCH SUBJECT,
DOES IT?
- ( chuckles )
- HUH?
- OH, SERIOUSLY, THIS MUST BE
SOME KIND OF JOKE BY YOU, WASHU.
SOME JOKE INDEED.
- HMM.
HEY, THERE.
I'M SURE YOU DIDN'T
GO TO ALL THIS TROUBLE
JUST TO REMINISCE
ABOUT THE GOOD OLD DAYS,
NOW DID YOU, DR. CLAY?
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
- THERE WAS NOT A DAY
I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT YOU
THESE 20,000 YEARS.
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW MANY TIMES
I THOUGHT THAT
EVER KNOWING YOU
WAS THE GREATEST
MISFORTUNE OF MY LIFE.
- OLD MEN ARE
SO FULL OF GRUDGES.
- WELL, THAT'S ALL
COMING TO AN END TODAY.
THE BIGGEST PAIN OF MY LIFE
WILL BECOME THE GODDESS
OF GOOD FORTUNE.
- Washu: GOOD FOR YOU.
- I MEAN YOU, WASHU, DEAR.
- UH-HUH.
- UH-HUH?
( stammers )
THERE'S A PLACE
I'D LIKE TO TAKE YOU.
SOMEONE WANTS TO MEET YOU.
- OOH, LITTLE GIRLS
TURN YOU ON, HUH?
- WHAT?!
- AH!  I KNEW IT.
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE ME
TO SOME KIND OF SECRET CLUB,
AND THEN DO
ALL KINDS OF THINGS
TO MY YOUNG AND
BEAUTIFUL BODY.
OH MY.  OH MY!
AND AT THE END,
YOU'RE GONNA DO SOMETHING
ABSOLUTELY UNSPEAKABLE.
WOW!
OLD AGE HAS SUCH
A WAY OF DISTORTING
HOW YOU EXPRESS YOUR LOVE.
- ( shouts )
I NEVER SAID SUCH THINGS.
- WELL, I APPRECIATE
YOUR FEELINGS.
REALLY, I DO.
BUT WHY CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT I'M IN LOVE
WITH SOMEONE ELSE?
- WASHU, CUT THAT OUT!
BESIDES, WHY WOULD I
BE INTERESTED IN SOMETHING
THAT I CAN'T TELL
THE FRONT FROM THE BACK?
- ( growls )
TAKE A LOOK, YOU JERK!
- NOW JUST YOU STOP IT.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU.
THE ONE WHO WANTS TO SEE YOU
IS LADY TOKIMI.
- HUH?  LADY TOKIMI?
- ( chuckles )
SURPRISED, WASHU?
( chuckles )
- YEAH, I'M SURPRISED.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'VE HEARD YOU CALL
SOMEBODY BY A TITLE.
- ( stammers )
DAMN YOU!
- SO, WHO IS THIS
TOKIMI ANYWAY?
REMEMBER I WAS LOCKED UP
FOR THE LAST 5,000 YEARS.
I'M PRETTY SURE I DON'T
REMEMBER HEARING THAT NAME
WHILE I WAS AT
THE ACADEMY.
CAN'T REMEMBER A THING THAT
HAPPENED OVER 20,000 YEARS AGO.
AH, COME ON.
GIVE ME A HINT.
- ( groans )
WELL, YOU'RE STILL A LITTLE
JOKER, AREN'T YOU, WASHU?
YOU MAY NOT KNOW HER,
BUT SHE KNOWS YOU.
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW,
ASK WHEN YOU GET THERE.
- ( panting )
- HUH?
- DAMN IT.
NOW WHERE COULD
RYOKO BE?
- TENCHI, I THINK DIDN'T WE
COME THIS WAY EARLIER?
- WHAT?
- Mihoshi: TENCHI!
I THINK THAT MAYBE
WE SHOULD GO THIS WAY, TENCHI.
- HMM.
UH-OH.
- LET'S SEE.
- OH, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
TENCHI?
( gasps )
- UHH.
- ( gasps  )
- ( both gasp )
- NO!
- OH, TENCHI.
( sighs )
- SOMETHING'S VERY WRONG.
THE STRUCTURE OF
THE PASSAGEWAY
IS DIFFERENT FROM
THE GALAXY POLICE STRUCTURE.
AND I THINK THAT PERHAPS
THIS MEANS...
- PERHAPS THIS MEANS...?
- THIS MEANS THAT PERHAPS
WE'RE TRAPPED IN HERE.
- YES, WE'RE TRAPPED IN HERE!
WE ARE VERY LOCKED UP!
- WE ARE?  OH DEAR.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- ( crying )
- OH, YEAH. BY THE WAY,
DON'T YOU WANT TO KNOW
HOW I KNEW WHERE TO FIND YOU?
AREN'T YOU JUST
THE SLIGHTEST BIT CURIOUS?
- WELL, WHY NOT?
IT'S A LONG TRIP.
WHY DON'T YOU SIT DOWN
AND TALK?
PLEASE, SIT DOWN.
- HUH?
- I AM INTERESTED
IN HOW YOU FOUND
THE LOCATION OF THIS BRIDGE.
BUT ALSO HOW YOU
FOUND OUT ABOUT RYOKO.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
BECAUSE OF THE GEMS.
BUT IT SEEMS I WAS WRONG,
I GUESS.
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
IN ALL THESE THOUSANDS OF YEARS
I'VE NEVER BEEN DETECTED
IN ANY KIND OF SEARCH.
I'M VERY IMPRESSED.
YOU MUST HAVE SOME SYSTEM,
WASHU.
- IT'S SIMPLE, REALLY.
DID YOU KNOW YOU HAVE A HABIT
OF MARKING
ALL YOUR FAVORITE THINGS
WITH YOUR SPECIAL LOGO?
ALWAYS DID.
- WHAT?!
- Washu: THAT'S HOW I KNEW
THAT THE BRIDGE
WAS IN THE STATUE'S HEAD.
- ( stammers )
- AND THIS...
IS YOUR FAVORITE.
- NOW HOW DID YOU GET
YOUR HANDS ON THAT?
NOW STOP THAT!
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH TROUBLE
I WENT THROUGH TO GET THAT?
- WHAT SHOULD I DO
WITH THIS?
- ( groans )
GIVE IT TO ME THIS INSTANT,
OR OTHERS WILL SUFFER.
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
OOH.
- ( chuckles )
- ALL RIGHT.  ALL RIGHT.
- ( gasps )
- ( chuckles )
( gasps )
WASHU?
HUH?
- Washu: AND I DIDN'T FORGET
TO PUT THE RIBBON ON.
- ( murmurs )
- LISTEN UP.
I'D REALLY LIKE TO GET
THE GANG AND RYOKO BACK,
AND I'LL GIVE YOU THIS DOLL.
BUT I REALLY MUST
INSIST THAT YOU
DON'T DO ANYTHING
INDECENT WITH IT, OKAY?
- ( both gasp )
- Ryoko: DON'T MOVE.
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
Z-ZERO?
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
NEVER MIND.
( chuckles )
HOW ABOUT THAT?
YOU FORGOT TO TAKE
ZERO INTO ACCOUNT.
I'M ASHAMED OF YOU.
- WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
- ( scoffs )
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO KEEP UP
THAT ATTITUDE FOR LONG.
- I MEANT YOU TOO,
DOCTOR.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- PAY ATTENTION, DOCTOR.
PLEASE DON'T GET TENCHI
INVOLVED ANYMORE.
- UNBELIEVABLE.
EVEN THOUGH A DIFFERENT
MEMORY WAS PLANTED,
COMPLETE AND ABSOLUTE
OBEDIENCE TO ME
SHOULD BE IN THE DEPTH
OF HER UNCONSCIOUSNESS.
- MY GUESS IS THAT IT'S BECAUSE
YOU MADE A COMPLETE COPY.
- ZERO.
LISTEN TO ME.
THAT IS NOT YOUR WILL.
THE PSEUDO-PERSONALITY
THAT WAS PLANTED IN YOU
IS MAKING YOU
ACT LIKE THAT.
ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS ERASE THAT MEMORY--
WHOA!
- NO, DOCTOR.
I WANT THIS MEMORY
AND BODY.
I WANT TO LIVE AS RYOKO.
- YOU WOULD BETRAY ME?
HOW DARE YOU.
WHY, YOU'RE JUST--
YOU'RE JUST A MARIONETTE
THAT I MADE.
- I-- I AM RYOKO!
- ENOUGH!
- ( gasps, screams )
( grunts )
- ( gasps )
ZERO.
- TENCHI.
TEN--
( grunts )
- RYOKO.
CLAY, YOU'RE AN AWFUL BASTARD.
- EVERYONE'S MAKING FUN OF ME.
- YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED
AT ALL, HAVE YOU?
THIS IS WHY YOU WERE
KICKED OUT OF SCHOOL.
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO STIRRED
THOSE WHO WERE JEALOUS
OF MY TALENT
TO DRIVE ME OUT!
- THERE'S NO ONE LIKE THAT
AT THE GRADUATE SCHOOL.
THE ONES WHO DON'T
LOVE THEIR WORK
ARE THE ONES
WHO ARE DISLIKED.
AND THEY'RE THE ONES
THAT ARE DRIVEN OUT.
- I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT I LOVE.
I LOVE PERFECTION,
AND MY TECHNOLOGY IS PERFECT.
THAT'S WHAT I LOVE.
THERE CAN'T BE ANY
DEFECT IN MY WORK.
THERE CAN'T BE!
- ( laughing )
YOU IDIOT.
- YOU DARE CALL ME THAT?!
( panting )
HUH?
20,000 YEARS AGO
YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
DIDN'T YOU SAY THAT?
I REMEMBER INVESTIGATING
YOUR PAST
A LONG TIME AGO.
OH, YES.  I DO INDEED.
( chuckles )
LET'S SEE WHAT YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH LADY TOKIMI IS
BY MAKING A COPY...
OF YOUR MEMORY.
- HUH?
BACK OFF, YOU IDIOT.
DON'T YOU KNOW A WOMAN'S
AGE AND PAST
ARE BEST KEPT A SECRET--?
- I KNOW THAT I AM
A SCIENTIST.
I KNOW THAT I CAN'T STAND
LEAVING A MYSTERY UNSOLVED,
AND THE SAME APPLIES
TO THAT GEM, WASHU.
I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF
IT REALLY EXISTS OR NOT.
WHAT THE--?
- HER VERY EXISTENCE
IS IMPOSSIBLE.
EVEN THOUGH SHE WAS PRESENT
RIGHT THERE IN FRONT OF US.
- MY GOD!
- WHOA!
HOW COULD THIS BE?
ITS FUNCTIONS SHOULD HAVE
BEEN TOTALLY SHUT DOWN.
- CLAY!
-  ( gasps )
( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- HUH?
- WHEN THIS SHIP DIVIDES,
THE ENERGY REACTOR
OF THE MAIN BODY OF THIS SHIP
WILL BEGIN TO SHRINK
AND THEN IT WILL EXPLODE.
- UHH.
- IF YOU WANT TO STOP IT--
IF YOU WANT TO STOP IT,
THE STATUE OVER THERE
IS THE CONTROL.
- UM...
- YOU'D BETTER HURRY
OR YOU WON'T MAKE IT.
- HA.
THIS MUST BE IT.
TALK ABOUT BAD TASTE,
DIRTY OLD MAN.
- ( funeral march playing
on computer )
- OH, NO.
THIS IS A DUMMY.
DAMN!
- DAMN.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHOA!
- ( all scream )
- TENCHI!
- AAH.
- M-MIHOSHI,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT? ARE YOU?
- ( stammers)
YES, I AM.
OH, TENCHI,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY TO YOU.
YOU SAVED ME AGAIN.
TENCHI, I'M SO--
- ( beeping )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
LET'S SEE.
- OH, NO.
THE FLOW OF ENERGY IS
CONCENTRATING ON ONE POINT ONLY.
- OHH.
- IT MEANS WE'RE GOING
TO BECOME A BLACK HOLE!
- WHAT?!
- WOW.
YOU MEAN IT REALLY?
THIS'LL BE THE FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER COME SO CLOSE TO ONE.
OH!
- I'M SURE IT WILL BE.
- OKAY.
I'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
AT LEAST TO CONTROL THIS SIDE
OF THE SHIP IF POSSIBLE.
- ( groans )
TENCHI?
- ( yells )
- AYEKA.
- I CAN'T!
- ( all shout )
( all scream )
- OH.
( groans )
- WASHU, YOU HAVE
RUINED EVERYTHING.
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT,
WASHU!
HUH?
WHAT?!
THE GRAVITY CONSTANT
OF THE SPACE IS CHANGING?
BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
IT CAN'T BE.
WHAT'S THAT LIGHT?
THE LIGHT HAWK WINGS!
IT'S SAID THEY CAN
ONLY BE CAUSED BY
A JURAI SHIP.
BUT THAT'S NOT
IT'S A PERSON.
( stammers )
IT'S THAT BOY.
HMM.
AND THAT REMARKABLE BOY
IS IN THE COMPANY OF WASHU,
ISN'T HE?
THEN I'LL TAKE THIS INFORMATION
TO LADY TOKIMI.
( chuckles )
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- ( screams )
- WELL, IT IS NOW MY DUTY
TO ESCORT THE PRISONER,
RIGHT?  ISN'T IT?
- Washu: HERE.
- WHOA!
WELL, WHAT IS IT, WASHU?
A GIFT?  WHO FOR, HUH?
- JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR YOU TO WHILE AWAY
THE TIME ON DUTY.
- OH, I SEE.
WELL THEN, I'LL BE SURE TO GIVE
IT TO THE APPROPRIATE PERSON.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
OKAY NOW.
GOOD-BYE, WASHU.
- OKAY, BYE, NOW.
- TAKE CARE.
WHOA!
- ( glass shatters )
- ( groans )
- OH, WASHU?
- DON'T WORRY. I PUT
A TUBE OF GLUE IN THERE TOO.
- I'M SORRY I LIED TO YOU.
- RYOKO.
( chuckles )
- I HAVE WANTED TO BE
CALLED THAT FOREVER.
I ONLY WISH THAT
TIME WOULD STOP NOW.
- ( stammers )
- BUT I AM NOT RYOKO.
- COME ON, TENCHI.
NOW HURRY UP.
- YOU, WHAT IS IT, WASHU?
- PUT RYOKO IN
THE CAPSULE.
- WHAT?
- RYOKO'S GOING BACK
INTO ONE BODY.
- OH.
- BUT...
- YOU KNOW, I GOTTA
TELL YOU CHARACTERS,
IT'S NOT TOO EASY
TO DUPLICATE MY MASTERPIECE.
I TOOK THE TROUBLE
TO DIVIDE HER INTO TWO
BECAUSE I CAN'T CONTROL
THE MIND OF A COMPLETE UNIT.
SO NOW I'M GONNA PUT THEM
BACK TOGETHER INTO ONE.
YEP.
- ( gasps )
OH, I'M-- I'M SO...
- MM-HMM.
- Ryoko: YOU BIG FAT LIAR.
- Washu: DO YOU HAVE
ANY OBJECTION, RYOKO?
- Ryoko: I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE MAKING
THIS KIND OF A DECISION FOR ME.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
SHE'S SO EMBARRASSING.
- Washu: EMBARRASSING?
YOU MEAN IT'S
EMBARRASSING BECAUSE
SHE REMINDS YOU OF YOURSELF?
OR IS IT BECAUSE YOU'RE
REALLY JEALOUS OF HER?
I MEAN, SHE'S SO HONEST
ABOUT HER FEELINGS.
RYOKO.
THAT IS THE OTHER YOU.
THE ONE WITH YOUR
TRUE FEELINGS.
AND I BET YOU KNOW THAT
BETTER THAN ANYONE.
AM I RIGHT?
RYOKO?
RYOKO, I WON'T FORCE YOU TO
IF YOU DON'T REALLY
WANT TO DO IT.
GOOD GIRL.
- Ryoko: DAMN YOU, WASHU.
- D3: WHAT IS THIS ENERGY?
- IS IT WASHU?
OR IS THIS TSUNAMI'S DOING?
- THAT SWORD IS CAPABLE
OF MATERIAL CONVERSION,
AND YET IT ONLY
HAS THREE BLADES?
- I CAN'T SAY.
- YOU CAN'T SAY?
OR YOU WON'T SAY?
BUT THIS DIMENSION SEEMS
TO BE PERFECT FOR YOUR PURPOSE.
WITH NOT ONLY WASHU,
BUT TSUNAMI HERE.
NOW WHAT SHALL WE DO
ABOUT DR. CLAY?
- AS I RECALL, THIS DIMENSION
IS YOUR JURISDICTION.
- YES, YOUR MAJESTY.
- ( giggles )
- Washu: OH, TENCHI?
- ( gasps )
- HUH?
- ( panting )
- ( door opens, closes )
- WASHU, I THOUGHT
TENCHI WOULDN'T BE BACK
UNTIL LATER THIS EVENING?
( giggles )
- ( chuckles )
SO INNOCENT.
- ( sighs )
OH, MY.
WHEN WILL I EVER
GET BACK TO NORMAL?
( giggles )
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ I AM LONELY
LIKE THE MOON ♪
♪ YOU ARE FAR AWAY
AS THE EARTH ♪
♪ THOUGH YOU SAY
I LIGHT YOUR THOUGHTS ♪
♪ NIGHT AFTER NIGHT ♪
♪ SOON YOU FORGET ♪
♪ WE ARE DRIFTING
IN THIS DANCE ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL YOU
CIRCLE MY HEART ♪
♪ KEEPING SUCH
A GRACEFUL DISTANCE ♪
♪ SO CLOSE
BUT SOMEHOW APART ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I CRY FOR YOU ♪
♪ KNOWING
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WHISPER
TO THE STARS ♪
♪ UP IN THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT I WANT TO FIND
A WAY TO YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ KISSING THE SUN
WHEN MORNING COMES ♪
♪ YOU DON'T SEEM
TO COUNT THE HOURS ♪
♪ WHEN WE ARE NOT TOGETHER ♪
♪ I'VE SEEN THE TENDER FIRE
IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ YET WHEN I'M GONE,
YOU CARRY ON ♪
♪ I FLOAT IN THIS EMPTINESS ♪
♪ TILL AT LAST
LOVE RETURNS ♪
♪ WITH THE NIGHT ♪
♪ AND THE LONELY MOON. ♪
- THE KING OF JURAI ARRIVES
TO TAKE AYEKA AND SASAMI HOME.
( chuckles )
NOW I'LL BE ALONE
WITH TENCHI.
JUST THE TWO OF US.
CHECK IT OUT
ON OUR NEXT EPISODE,
"HERE COMES JURAI."