- ( theme music playing )
♪ CAN'T YOU SEE
THAT I AM A PIONEER? ♪
♪ UNLOCKING
THE GREATEST MYSTERIES ♪
♪ MY KEY IS A FEARLESS HEART
SO PURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ YOU CAN'T BE A HERO ♪
♪ HIDING UNDERNEATH YOUR BED ♪
♪ GOT TO LIVE THE LIFE ♪
♪ YOU CREATE INSIDE YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ SO I OPEN THE WINDOW ♪
♪ CAUGHT THE WIND ONE NIGHT ♪
♪ NOW I SAIL WITH THE BIRDS ♪
♪ IN THEIR FLIGHT ♪
♪ SOME WILL SAY ♪
♪ YOU'RE SAFER HERE ♪
♪ NEVER MIND THAT,
BE A PIONEER ♪
♪ CAN'T YOU SEE
THAT YOU ARE A PIONEER? ♪
♪ NOT ONE
OF THE ENDLESS TALKERS ♪
♪ WHO TELL YOU
THE SAME OLD RULES ♪
♪ YOU'VE HEARD BEFORE ♪
♪ WE WILL BE PIONEERS ♪
♪ FOREVERMORE. ♪
- ( phone ringing )
- HUH?
- ( ringing continues )
- HMMM.
HELLO?
MASAKI RESIDENCE.
OH, HELLO, TENCHI'S AUNT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING SO KIND
TO SASAMI.
OH, AND THAT DISH YOU TAUGHT HER
TO COOK THE OTHER DAY.
YES.
WE ALL ENJOYED IT VERY MUCH.
IT WAS DELICIOUS.
WHAT?
I SEE.
YES, I'M ON MY WAY NOW.
- ( hawk squawking )
- WELCOME HOME!
- TENCHI!
OH.
- THANKS FOR
TAKING THE TROUBLE, AUNTIE.
- HMM.
- COMING ALL THIS WAY
TO BRING SASAMI HOME.
WELL, SASAMI,
HOW IS THE BABY DOING?
- WELL, HE WAS CUTE.
- OH.
A GIFT?
YOU'RE SO KIND.
TO CELEBRATE THE BABY'S BIRTH?
- WELL, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- I HAVE TO BE GOING.
- OH.  ALL RIGHT.
WHY DON'T YOU COME BACK WITH
THE BABY NEXT TIME YOU VISIT?
- ( doorbell rings )
- YES?
OH, AUNTIE, I--
- HI!
HERE ARE THE DIAPERS
AND THE FORMULA AND THE TOYS.
- ( grumbles )
- THANKS.
YOU SEE, HIS MOTHER
JUST BECAME ILL ALL OF A SUDDEN.
I KNEW YOU WOULDN'T MIND
TAKING CARE OF THE BABY.
ANYWAY, IT'LL BE
JUST FOR A FEW DAYS.
YOU'LL BE FINE. AND WITH SO
MANY GIRLS AROUND THE HOUSE,
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
- UH, A BABY?
- ( squealing )
- LOOK, AUNT--
HUH?
- BYE BYE!
GOOD LUCK!
- SO IT'S UP TO US TO TAKE
CARE OF THIS BABY FOR A WHILE.
- WOW!
HE'S SO CUTE.
THERE THERE!
- AHH!
- ( laughs )
HE'S TOO ADORABLE.
- HMM.
WELL, TENCHI WAS MUCH MORE
ADORABLE WHEN HE WAS LITTLE.
- WOW, REALLY?
- YEAH.
- WELL,
OBVIOUSLY THEY'RE RELATED.
SEE, HIS EYES
LOOK EXACTLY LIKE TENCHI'S.
- HUH? YEAH?
THEY DO?
- AND YOU SEE, IF HE'S THE
GRANDSON OF TENCHI'S AUNT,
WELL THEN, THAT MEANS
HE'S RELATED TO ME ALSO.
SO YOU'LL GROW UP
TO BE LIKE TENCHI.
- HMM.
- OH, SO CUU--- OH!
- WHOA!
- DARLING, BABIES ARE SO CUTE,
AREN'T THEY?
- HEY, RYOKO!
- NOW LET'S PLAY WITH MOMMY.
- ( cooing )
- ( grunting )
HEY, STOP IT!
STOP IT, BABY!
- ( laughs )
- WELL WELL NOW,
WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
A MONSTER LIKE YOU
CAN'T BE TRUSTED WITH BABIES.
- OH!
- NO WAY!
COME COME, LITTLE ONE.
YOU WERE SCARED.
- HMM.
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
YOU!
- AHHH!
ECH!
- ( laughs )
OH.
- EWWW!
AH, NO!
- AHHH!
- WHHAAAA!
- AAAH.
- Tenchi: WHOA!
- ( gasps ) TENCHI!
- AH.
WELL, HI THERE.
DID YOU ENJOY YOUR TRIP?
- UH-HUH.
- ( baby crying )
- HUH?
LITTLE TARO!
- ( meows )
- ( laughs )
- ( Taro continues crying )
- IT'S A BABY.
HE'S SO CUTE.
- ( meows )
- ( crying )
- MIHOSHI?
WOULD YOU CHANGE HIS DIAPER,
PLEASE?
- HUH?  OH, OKAY.
- OH, MISS AYEKA?
I GUESS YOUR DRESS
GOT A LITTLE WET.
UH, I'M SORRY.
- TENCHI, WHAT'S THAT?
- THIS?
THIS I HAVE TO GO WASH.
PLEASE, MISS AYEKA,
YOU GO AHEAD AND CHANGE.
- REALLY?  YOU MEAN
YOU'RE GOING TO WASH IT?
WHY DON'T YOU LEAVE THAT
UP TO ME, PLEASE?
- OH!
OKAY THEN, THANK YOU.
- MY PLEASURE.
- HOW THOUGHTFUL OF HER.
- HMMM?
- ( Taro cooing )
( crying )
- NOW FIRST YOU TAKE THIS
LIKE SO,
AND-- ( laughs )
- ( cooing )
- ( meows )
- I JUST-- I DON'T THINK
I'M DOING IT RIGHT.
- ( meows )
- NO, I DON'T.
- TENCHI?
HMM.
- MAYBE THIS GOES HERE
AND THIS GOES THERE,
OR THAT GOES WHERE--
I DON'T KNOW!
- I GUESS HE ISN'T HERE.
HMMM?
- ( meows )
( squealing )
- MIHOSHI,
YOU DOING ALL RIGHT?
- UH, UM, YES,
I'M DOING JUST GREAT.
I'LL BE DONE IN A SECOND.
- AH!
OH, AND MIHOSHI, DON'T FORGET
TO PUT THE DIAPER COVER OVER IT.
- HUH?
DIAPER COVER.
OH, I SEE!
SO THIS IS A DIAPER COVER.
THAT'S WHY IT DIDN'T WORK.
( laughs )
- HUH?
- OH.  HUH?
- HERE YOU GO.
- AHH!
- ( mewling )
- THERE YOU ARE.
- Mihoshi: RYOKO!
RYOKO?
HIS DIAPER COVER'S NOT ON YET.
- MMM.
- HE WON'T PEE SO SOON.
- BUT TENCHI TOLD ME
TO PUT THE DIAPER COVER ON
BEFORE I DID ANYTHING ELSE.
- TENCHI WAS MUCH MUCH CUTER
WHEN HE WAS A BABY.
- ( mumbling )
HUH?
OH, SOMEONE MUST HAVE
MADE SOME ALREADY.
- ( Taro crying )
- HUH?
JUST DRINK.
DRINK IT!  DO IT, DO IT, DO IT.
COME ON.
- RYOKO, WAIT A MINUTE!
WHAT KIND OF STUFF ARE YOU
TRYING TO GIVE HIM THIS TIME?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
WHAT KIND OF STUFF?
IT'S THE FORMULA THIS TIME,
I SWEAR.
- AHA!  I THOUGHT SO.
- ANYTHING WRONG?
- OH, WOW!
I DID IT!
- ALL RIGHT!
NOW HE'S OKAY.
- YES!
- ( cooing )
- All: OH!
- WE SURE ARE LUCKY TO HAVE
SUCH NICE WEATHER, AYEKA.
- YES, INDEED.
- Azaka: THE SPRING MIST
IS IN THE AIR.
- Kamidake: WHAT IS IT
WE'RE DOING EXACTLY?
- EXACTLY WHAT YOU THINK
WE'RE DOING.
- AHA!
- WHOOPIE!
- ( squealing )
- ( laughs )
OH! HEY!
OUCH OUCH OUCH!
OW, THAT HURTS.
PLEASE STOP.
- ( blowing )
THERE.  THERE YOU GO.
- ( cooing )
- ECH!
- ( crying )
- OH, PLEASE DON'T CRY.
( crying )
- HEEE-- OH!
- AHHH!
OW!
- ( both grunting )
- TAKE THAT AND THAT AND THAT!
- ( fighting continues )
- HERE, HMM?
- ( laughs )
- ( Taro coos )
- HMM.
I HAD NO IDEA HOW MUCH WORK
IT IS TAKING CARE OF A BABY.
WELL, IT'S NICE TO RELAX.
- Mihoshi: NOW IT'S
TIME TO TAKE A BATH.
- WHAA--
- ARE YOU READY?
WE'RE GOING IN.
THERE, NICE AND WARM.
- ( baby cooing )
- BABIES FEEL SO GOOD--
SO SOFT AND BOUNCY.
- WHAT DO I DO NOW?
- UH UH, SEE? SEE,
THERE'S NO USE IN DOING THAT.
I CAN'T
BREASTFEED YOU, NOT YET.
( grumbling )
- HEY!  OH, NO,
PLEASE STOP IT.
UH UH, OH MY, OH MY.
- ( groaning )
- THERE THERE, TENCHI.
- THANK YOU, SASAMI.
- OH MY, OH MY!
- DIAPERS, DIAPERS.
- MILK MILK MILK.
- OH NO, WHAT SHALL WE DO?
- DIAPERS DIAPERS.
- MILK MILK MILK.
MILK... ( gulping )
- EXCUSE ME?
- ( snoring )
- AHHH!
- ( groaning )
- ( crying )
- ( groans )
OH!
- ( computer whirring )
- WHO'S THERE?
WHO IS IT?
COME BACK LATER. I'M BUSY NOW.
HMM?  HUH?
HMM.
OH!  WHAT THE--
- ( Taro coos )
- ( groans )
HUH?
- ( coos )
- HMM.
AH.
OH, I SEE.
HUH?  OKAY OKAY.
HMMM. EH.
AH, THIS IS NO GOOD.
IT DOESN'T SUIT
YOUR CONSTITUTION AT ALL.
AH, I'VE GOT JUST THE THING
FOR NOURISHMENT--
MAKES YOU BIG,
MAKES YOU STRONG.
YES, THIS IS IT.
THERE.
PERFECT.
WHAT DO I THINK I'M DOING?
- ( laughs )
- ( all snoring )
- UH?
OH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHOA!
THE BABY'S GONE.
WHERE IS HE?
- ( knife chopping )
- HUH?
AH.
LITTLE WASHU.
- WHOA!
UH, I-- I-- I--
- LITTLE WASHU,
YOU'RE TAKING CARE OF THE BABY.
- UH, HE--
HE'S SO ANNOYING, REALLY.
HE JUST CAME INTO MY LAP
WITHOUT EVEN ASKING ME.
SO ANNOYING.
- SORRY, LITTLE WASHU.
- NO ONE ELSE
WOULD TAKE CARE OF HIM.
SO I HAD TO.
- TENCHI!  'MORNING.
- ECH!  STOP IT!
- MMM! HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
MORNING KISS FOR ME?
- STOP! GET AWAY FROM ME!
- ( Taro cooing )
- OH, I SEE.
WASHU'S TAKING CARE OF YOU.
- WELL, SOMEONE HAS TO.
- ( whimpering )
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- MILK, OF COURSE.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW?
- NEVER MIND.
JUST DO IT.
- HERE, HAVE SOME MILK.
- JUST A MINUTE!
HEY THERE, CRAZY GIRL,
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO,
SUFFOCATE HIM?
YOU JUST COME SIT HERE NOW.
PHEW! YOU HAVE TO GIVE HIM
A BREAK SO HE CAN BREATHE.
HMM.
YOU CAN'T EVEN FEED THE POOR
KID PROPERLY, CAN YOU?
SORRY, MOM!
I DIDN'T RAISE YOU TO BE
A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING.
- DIDN'T RAISE ME AT ALL.
- HERE YOU ARE. WOW,
WHAT'S EVERYBODY DOING HERE?
TAKING CARE OF A BABY
OR WHAT?
- OKAY, HE'S ALL YOURS NOW.
- JUST LEAVE IT TO ME.
THERE THERE.
- MISS WASHU?
- THANK YOU, LITTLE WASHU.
- Mihoshi:
COME TO YOUR MAMA, BABY.
- Ryoko: I'LL DO IT.
HE DOESN'T LIKE IT.
- Ayeka: HAVE SOME MILK NOW.
- ( sighs )
I JUST CAN'T WORK TODAY.
- ( Taro cooing )
- ARGH!
YOU GIRLS, REALLY!
AHH!
DON'T PULL, OKAY?
HEY, CALM DOWN NOW.
- ( cooing )
- ( laughs )
HUH?
HMM.
HUH?  HMM.
YEEAAH! AHHHH!
( muttering )
WHY DO I ALWAYS
HAVE TO DO THIS?
HUH?
- ♪ APRIL ROSES,
TINY SPARROWS ♪
♪ COMETS BRIGHT AND NEW ♪
♪ ALL BELONG TOGETHER ♪
♪ WITH THE MYSTERY
THAT IS YOU ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE
YOUR LITTLE FACE ♪
♪ I HEAR A SONG
FROM LONG AGO ♪
♪ I THINK YOU KNOW
THE MANY SECRETS ♪
♪ I'VE FORGOTTEN... ♪
- TARO, NO!
- ♪GENERATIONS THROUGH THE AGES♪
♪ JOINED AS ONE SOMEHOW ♪
♪ LEADING TO THE MIRACLE ♪
♪ THAT I AM HOLDING NOW ♪
♪ FROM THE SKY
AND FROM THE SEA ♪
♪ UPON A BREEZE
YOU CAME TO ME ♪
♪ YOU SEEM TO SEE
A GREATER UNIVERSE ♪
♪ THAN I DO ♪
♪ SLEEP, MY BABY,
SLEEP, MY BABY ♪
♪ DREAM OF SOMEWHERE
FAR AWAY ♪
♪ DO YOU REMEMBER STILL ♪
♪ HOW I HOPE
YOU ALWAYS WILL ♪
♪ KEEP THE MEMORY
OF THE DAY... ♪
- ( sighs )
WELL, WASHU, IT SURE LOOKS LIKE
THE BABY BELONGS TO YOU NOW.
- GUESS I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
- HE'S SUCH AN ANGEL
WHEN HE'S ASLEEP.
BUT ONCE HE WAKES UP--
- THAT'S THE WAY IT IS.
HE DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO TALK YET,
YOU SEE.
SO HE HAS TO SHOW WHAT HE WANTS
WITH HIS BODY.
SAYING, "I'M HERE.
I WANT THIS OR THAT."  RIGHT?
- YOU'RE A SELFISH LITTLE THING,
AREN'T YOU?
- WELL, IT'S ONLY NATURAL.
YOU SEE, THAT'S THE ONLY THING
YOU CAN BE WHEN YOU'RE A BABY.
HMM?
WHAT NOW?
- OH, WELL, YOU SEE,
I LOST MY MOTHER
WHEN I WAS VERY LITTLE.
AND I WAS WONDERING IF THIS
IS HOW A MOTHER AND CHILD ARE.
- OH, YES, THIS IS EXACTLY HOW
YOU AND YOUR MOTHER WERE.
- OH, YOU THINK SO?
- I KNOW SO.
- HUH?
- ( Taro crying )
- OH.
UM, SORRY I WOKE YOU UP.
WELL, I HAVE TO
BE ON MY WAY NOW.
AND, UH...
- TENCHI?
- HUH?
- GOOD NIGHT.
- GOOD NIGHT, LITTLE WASHU.
- ( whimpering )
MAMA.  MAMA.
MAMA.
- NOT ME, LITTLE ONE.
I'M NOT YOUR MOMMY.
- MAMA.  MAMA.
- NO, I'M NOT YOUR MOM.
( humming )
BINGO!
( humming, slurping )
- 'MORNING.
WHAT'S UP?
- OH, TENCHI, GOOD MORNING.
IT WON'T BE LONG NOW,
SO YOU'LL JUST
HAVE TO WAIT A MOMENT.
- ( doorbell rings )
- HUH?
WHO COULD IT BE?
- YES, HONEY, IT'S COMING.
- LITTLE WASHU?
- ( all yawning )
- THANK YOU
FOR TAKING CARE OF HIM.
- THANK YOU.
IT WAS SO NICE OF YOU, REALLY.
- THAT'S OKAY.
- I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
YOU DID A GREAT JOB
FOR YOUR AGE.
- OH, WELL, THERE'S SO
MANY GIRLS AROUND HERE.
SO I DIDN'T HAVE TO
TAKE CARE OF HIM ALONE.
- MA!  MAMA.
- Aunt: OH MY,
THE BABY'S TALKING.
- Father:
WOW, HE REALLY IS TALKING.
"MAMA, MAMA."
- WELL, IT'S TIME FOR US
TO BE GOING NOW.
THANKS AGAIN.
AND PLEASE TELL SASAMI
TO COME VISIT TARO
WHENEVER SHE WANTS.
- OKAY, THAT'S GREAT.
I'LL BE SURE TO TELL HER.
- YEAH!
THANK GOD HE'S GONE.
- YOU WORKED THE HARDEST
OF US ALL, LITTLE WASHU.
IT WAS A LOT OF WORK,
BUT THEN,
WE'LL MISS HIM
WHEN HE'S GONE, I GUESS.
- HE CALLED ME MOM.
OH, BABIES, BABIES.
TENCHI?
- YES?
- I HAD A BABY ONCE.
- WHAT?
- THE FATHER WAS A MEMBER
OF ROYAL SPACE ACADEMY,
LIKE MYSELF.
WE WERE BOTH STUDENTS
WHEN WE GOT MARRIED.
I LOVED HIM
AND FELT SO ATTACHED TO HIM.
ME AND HIM AND THE BABY--
THAT WAS ALL I NEEDED
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
BUT YOU SEE,
HE WAS FROM
A VERY PRESTIGIOUS FAMILY.
WHILE I WAS GONE,
MESSENGERS CAME FROM HIS FAMILY
AND HE AND THE BABY
WERE TAKEN FROM ME.
LINEAGE, SOCIAL STATUS--
WHY SHOULD THESE THINGS
MATTER SO MUCH?
THAT'S HOW GROWN UPS ARE.
IF THAT'S SO, I'D BE HAPPIER
BEING A CHILD,
NEVER EVER GROWING UP.
- THAT'S TERRIBLE,
LITTLE WASHU.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY!
I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD HEEE--
UH, I-- HUH?
- HMM!
- WHAAAA!
- TENCHI, I'LL BE GLAD
TO BEAR A CHILD
IF THE CHILD IS YOURS.
- WHOA WHOA WHOA!
UH, MISS WASHU, REALLY, I--
- NO NO NO, TENCHI.
YOU CAN JUST CALL ME
WASHU NOW.
- WHOA WHOA!
- NOW NOW NOW.
JUST CLOSE YOUR EYES, TENCHI.
- EEEEEK!
- WHOA!
- HMMM!
- OUCH!  YOU SHOULDN'T DO THAT
TO YOUR MOMMY, LITTLE RYOKO.
- ( groans )
MOMMY MY BUTT!
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW
WHEN TO STOP, DO YOU NOW?
- MMM, HONEY, I THOUGHT
I'D MAKE YOU A LITTLE BROTHER
IN CASE YOU'RE LONELY BEING
THE ONLY CHILD IN THE FAMILY.
I KNOW IT REALLY MUST BE TOUGH.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW I FEEL!
I'M SO SAD.
- MISS-- MISS WASHU!
HOW DARE YOU SAY SUCH THINGS
WHEN YOU HAVE A HUSBAND?
HOW DARE YOU?
- THAT WAS 20,000 YEARS AGO
THAT I HAD A HUSBAND.
"HAD" A HUSBAND.
AY, BUT I'M STILL
QUITE SO YOUNG
THAT I'M LONELY
COME BEDTIME.
- ( groans )
- AHH!
I'M SO EMBARRASSED.
- AH!
- HEY, YOU,
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT THAT.
YOU LISTEN TO ME.
YOU DON'T LAY A FINGER
ON MY TENCHI.
- Ayeka: RYOKO, HOW DARE YOU?
- OH MY.
- RYOKO--
- Ryoko: SHUT UP, I'M BUSY NOW!
- PLEASE STOP IT,
BOTH OF YOU!
- ( sighs )
- THOSE KIDS,
THEY ARE SO HELPLESS.
- HUH?
RIGHT, TENCHI?
THEY NEVER GROW UP, DO THEY?
- ...NOTHING MORE!
- Ryoko: I KNOW TENCHI
WOULD AGREE WITH ME.
Ayeka: HE'S BEEN MINE
SINCE BEFORE HE WAS BORN,
I'M TELLING YOU.
- THAT'S WHAT YOU CLAIM,
NOTHING MORE.
- THERE IS A STRONG BOND OF LOVE
BETWEEN TENCHI AND ME!
- ( theme music playing )
♪ I AM LONELY
LIKE THE MOON ♪
♪ YOU ARE FAR AWAY
AS THE EARTH ♪
♪ THOUGH YOU SAY
I LIGHT YOUR THOUGHTS ♪
♪ NIGHT AFTER NIGHT ♪
♪ SOON YOU FORGET ♪
♪ WE ARE DRIFTING
IN THIS DANCE ♪
♪ I CAN FEEL YOU
CIRCLE MY HEART ♪
♪ KEEPING SUCH
A GRACEFUL DISTANCE ♪
♪ SO CLOSE
BUT SOMEHOW APART ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I CRY FOR YOU ♪
♪ KNOWING
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WHISPER
TO THE STARS ♪
♪ UP IN THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT I WANT TO FIND
A WAY TO YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ KISSING THE SUN
WHEN MORNING COMES ♪
♪ YOU DON'T SEEM
TO COUNT THE HOURS ♪
♪ WHEN WE ARE NOT TOGETHER ♪
♪ I'VE SEEN THE TENDER FIRE
IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ YET WHEN I'M GONE,
YOU CARRY ON ♪
♪ I FLOAT IN THIS EMPTINESS ♪
♪ TILL AT LAST
LOVE RETURNS ♪
♪ WITH THE NIGHT ♪
♪ AND THE LONELY MOON. ♪
- ( silent )