- ( theme music playing )
- ( birds chirping )
- ( both sigh )
- Kamidake: LOOKS LIKE
ANOTHER BEAUTIFUL DAY.
- Azaka: SUCH WONDERFUL
SPRINGLIKE WEATHER.
- ( yawns )
- GOOD MORNING.
- AH!
AHHHH!
- TENCHI.
- HUH?  YOU!
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE I TOLD YOU?
DON'T COME
INTO MY ROOM LIKE THAT.
- BUT I WORRY ABOUT YOU, TENCHI.
THINK OF ALL WE'VE BEEN THROUGH.
CAN I HELP IT IF I
WANT YOU TO BE SAFE?
- AW, MAN.
DON'T TELL ME YOU WERE
IN MY ROOM ALL NIGHT.
- MM-HMM.
- THOSE DAYS ARE OVER,
THANK GOD.
- ( moaning )
- RYOKO,
WHAT I NEED NOW
IS MY PRIVACY.
- HUH?  PRIVACY?
- MMM.
- OH.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT IN THERE?
- I'LL MANAGE.
- OH, TENCHI!
TENCHI!
- AT LEAST THERE'S ONE PLACE
I CAN BE ALONE.
- HI.
- DOH!
- ( laughs )
TENCHI?
- STAY OUT!
DON'T NEED THIS ANYMORE.
UH-OH. WHOA!
WHOA!
OH!
UH-OH.
HOW DO I GET BACK
TO MY NORMAL SELF?
WHAT'S THAT?
OH, I REMEMBER.
- ( sighs )
( yawning )
- ( scraping )
- HUH?
RYOKO, SUCH BEHAVIOR.
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED
OF YOURSELF.
- ( grunts )
- HMM?
- TENCHI, GOOD MORNING.
- OH, AYEKA,
JUST WHO I NEEDED TO SEE.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
- THAT IS FROM THE ROYAL TREE.
- TSUNAMI SAID IT WAS FOR YOU.
SHE SAID IT WAS RYO-OH'S SEED.
RYO-OH'S?
- I FORGOT TO GIVE IT TO YOU.
I'M SORRY.
- AHH.
THANK YOU.
OH!
I WANT TO SAY THANK YOU.
- OH, DON'T BOTHER, PLEASE.
REALLY.
- OH, BUT I MUST.
YOU SEE, NOW I CAN BRING RYO--
- ( grunting )
- BACK TO LIFE. THANK
YOU, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.  THANK YOU.
- Tenchi: THAT'S WONDERFUL!
- YOU'RE WONDERFUL.
- TENCHI!
- ( knocking )
- IT'S OPEN.
COME IN.
- ALL RIGHT.
UM, I'M REALLY VERY SORRY
TO BOTHER YOU, MISS WASHU.
- ( computer beeping )
- MISS WASHU,
YOU'RE THE #1 GENIUS SCIENTIST
IN THE GALAXY.
AND THERE'S SOMETHING I'D LIKE
TO ASK YOU TO DO FOR ME.
- NO!  NOT UNLESS--
- UNLESS?
- UNLESS YOU CALL ME
LITTLE WASHU!
- HUH?
EXCUSE ME, MISS WASHU?
- EGH!  NO!
I'M NOT DOING ANYTHING
UNLESS YOU CALL ME LITTLE WASHU!
- HOW CAN I CALL YOU LITTLE
WHEN YOU'RE 20,000 YEARS OLD?
ALL RIGHT, THEN,
LITTLE WASHU.
CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
CAN YOU BUILD ME A UNIT
TO PLANT RYO-OH'S SEED?
- OF COURSE.
I CAN DO THAT. THAT'S EASY!
AFTER ALL,
YOU ARE THE #1 GENIUS SCIENTIST
IN THE GALAXY.
- OF COURSE.  I'M THE #1 GENIUS
SCIENTIST IN THE UNIVERSE!
( laughs )
- ( laughs )
- BUT I'M NOT GONNA DO IT.
( groaning )
THAT WOULD BE MY
STANDARD ANSWER,
BUT FOR YOU, I'M GONNA DO IT
BECAUSE I REALLY REALLY LIKE
YOUR ENTHUSIASM.
- ( gasps )
- HAVE A FLOWER POT.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HUH?
- HEY, JUST KIDDING.
THERE IS SOMETHING WE CAN USE.
KAGATO MADE IT.
BUT THERE ARE
NO FUNNY TRICKS INVOLVED.
AND THE INTERIOR CONFORMS
TO JURAI'S ENVIRONMENT.
IT'S REALLY A GOOD PIECE
OF WORK.
- WHY DID HE MAKE IT?
- WELL, KAGATO'S REASON
FOR HAVING RYOKO ATTACK PLANET
JURAI WAS TO GET TSUNAMI.
- AH.
- SO THE ONLY THING I HAVE TO DO
IS TO ENTER ALL OF THE DATA
ON YOUR KEY.
- AND RYO-OH
CAN BE RESURRECTED.
- ( birds chirping )
- ( meows )
- HMM?
LOOK! ALL THESE CARROTS
WILL BE FOR YOU.
HEY!
HOLD ON NOW.
THEY DON'T GROW THAT FAST.
- ( whimpers )
- YOU HAVE TO WAIT.
- ( cries )
- ( Mihoshi laughs )
- HMM?
- OH, I WONDER WHAT
SHE'LL DO NOW. ( laughs )
FOMI MISSED HER CHANCE WITH KEN.
SHE'S SO CLUMSY.
( laughs )
OH NO.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I JUST LOVE
THESE ROMANCE COMICS.
- ( sighs )
- WAAAAA!
UUU UUU UUU!
- WHAAA!
RYOKO, IT'S ONLY YOU.
- WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING?
HUH?
- WELL, WE ARE READING COMICS
FOR GIRLS.
- COMICS FOR GIRLS?
WHAT IS THAT?
- STORIES ABOUT A BOY AND GIRL
FALLING IN LOVE.
- HUH?
- THEY'RE ABOUT THE ART OF LOVE.
IT'S A HANDBOOK ON HOW TO WIN
THE LOVE OF SOMEONE YOU LOVE,
EARTH-STYLE.
- EARTH-STYLE?
HMM. YOU MEAN,
LIKE HOW TO GET TENCHI'S LOVE?
- MM-HMM.
- ( sighs )
- I THINK.
- AHH!
( squealing )
- I HAVE TO MAKE BREAKFAST.
- ( laughs )
- ( humming )
- SASAMI, I'M HOME.
- OH, HELLO, TENCHI.
BREAKFAST TIME.
- AH, THEN I'LL GO GET EVERYONE.
- GOOD.
UH, AYEKA IS WITH WASHU.
THAT'S WHERE YOU'LL FIND HER,
TENCHI.
- SHE'S AT WASHU'S?
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO--
WELL, BE RIGHT BACK.
- ( meows )
- LITTLE WASHU?
- YES!
- 'MORNING.
BREAKFAST IS READY.
OH, WHERE'S AYEKA?
I THOUGHT SHE WAS WITH YOU.
- UM, NO, I'M PRETTY SURE
AYEKA IS IN THE UNIT
PLANTING CARROTS
OR SOMETHING.
- ( meows )
- HEY, RYO-OHKI!
- DON'T WORRY.
SHE'S JUST ON HER WAY
TO GET AYEKA.
BUT I NEED TO SEE YOU.
- AH, YOU'RE UP TO SOMETHING,
AREN'T YOU?
- BINGO.
- I KNEW IT.
- ( singing )
- HUH?  AH!
AHHH!
- ( squeals )
- THIS IS NOT A CARROT!
- ( growling )
- ( computer scanning )
- HMM.  BLOOD, BODY FLUIDS,
HAIR SAMPLES.
THAT'S JUST ABOUT ALL
OF THE PHYSICAL SAMPLES.
ORGANIC PATTERN,
ASTRO PATTERN,
PSYCHO LAYER PATTERN,
OVER DIMENSION,
PARALLEL PATTERN.
YES, THEY'RE ALL
PRETTY WELL NORMAL.
- ARE WE DONE YET?
HAVE YOU GOT ANYTHING?
SASAMI'S GOT BREAKFAST FOR US,
YOU KNOW.
- I HAVE ALL THE SAMPLES
I NEED FOR ANALYSIS.
AHH!  EXCEPT FOR
THE MOST IMPORTANT ONE.
- High-pitched voice:
DA DUM DUM DUM! ( indistinct )
I'M READY NOW!
UH, WHAT'S WITH THE
NURSE'S OUTFIT?
- I'M AN ANGEL OF MERCY, TENCHI.
( laughs )
- YEEEAAAA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I JUST NEED
SOME SPERM SAMPLES.
- WHAT?
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT? STOP IT!
- DON'T WORRY.
STRICTLY MEDICAL, RIGHT?
HELLO!
- NO!
- I'VE GOT MAGIC FINGERS.
- I DON'T CARE.
- YOU WANT ME TO STOP IT?
- THAT'S WHAT I JUST SAID.
- NAH, YOU DON'T WANT ME
TO STOP IT.
- YES!  I DO TOO.
OH NO!  AHHH!
- LET'S SHAKE THE DEW
OFF THIS LILY, SHALL WE?
- AHHH!
- Mihoshi: EXCUSE ME?
- Both: HMMM?
- EXCUSE ME.
- OH!
HOW-- HOW THE HELL
DID YOU GET IN HERE?
- UM, I CAME TO GET EVERYONE
'CAUSE EVERYONE WAS LATE,
BUT, UM, I GOT LOST
AND FOUND MYSELF HERE.
- GOT LOST, HUH?
THIS IS NOT SOMEWHERE
YOU CAN JUST WALK INTO.
- SO, WASHU,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ANYWAY, HUH?
- UH, UMMM, UH...
UH, WE WERE JUST PLAYING DOCTOR.
- OH, I SEE!
PLEASE CONTINUE.
- OH, DON'T SIT THERE.
- ( whirring )
- OH, UH...
- DON'T TOUCH IT.
- OH, THIS IS--
- NOW GO AWAY!
GO ON!
WHAT'D YOU TOUCH?
- THIS, I THINK.
- AHH! NO, GO AWAY!
- OH, NICE.
- NO, THAT'S--
- ( stomach growling )
- I JUST WANT TO EAT.
- WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
- I DON'T GET IT.
BUT IF THAT'S
WHAT EARTHLINGS DO,
I GUESS I'LL GIVE IT A TRY.
- ( laughs )
LET'S GO WATCH THIS.
- ( meows )
- OH BOY! HERE WE GO.
- WHOA!
- OH!
OOH, I'M SORRY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( groaning )
WHAT?
RYOKO, WHAT'S THE IDEA?
- I'M SORRY,
I WASN'T PAYING ATTENTION.
I'M SO CLUMSY.
- HUH?
- MY NAME IS RYOKO AND I'M--
- ( laughs )
-OH, EMBARRASSED.
- WOW!
- Ayeka: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- UH, AYEKA!
- WHAT?  WHAT IS IT?
- UM, CAN I ASK YOU YOUR NAME?
- HUH?
RYOKO, ARE YOU SICK?
I MEAN, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- OH, UM...
( gasps ) OH!
- OH!
- OH, TENCHI,
YOU ARE A BOLD ONE, AREN'T YOU?
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- RYOKO, YOUR FACE IS RED.
WHAT'S WRONG?
DO YOU HAVE A COLD?
- GO AWAY.
I'M AT THE IMPORTANT PART.
- I'VE GOT
SOME GREAT COLD MEDICINE.
- I DON'T WANT IT.
- SURE YOU DO.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF.
- HEY, WOULD YOU STOP?
- THEY KEY IS TO CURE IT EARLY.
- LET ME GO.
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME.
- YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A CHILD.
- MIHOSHI, STOP!
LET ME GO!
( fighting continues )
- Ryoko: STOP IT, STOP IT!
- ( fighting continues )
- WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
- ( laughs )
RYOKO READ TENCHI'S
FATHER'S BOOKS FOR RESEARCH.
- RESEARCH?
HMM.  I SEE.
- OH!  AYYYYY!
- OH, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH MY GOD, YOU'RE HURT.
- HMM?
- PLEASE, USE THIS.
AND DON'T WORRY
ABOUT GETTING IT DIRTY.
OH!
EXCUSE ME.
OH, AND MY NAME IS AYEKA!
REMEMBER, IT'S AYEKA!
- HMM?
- ( birds chirping )
- "HANGERS ON,
THOUGH YOU BE FRIENDS,
BE MORE HUMBLE
WHEN ASKING FOR SECONDS."
ONE OF MY VERY BEST SO FAR.
TENCHI?  TENCHI?
- YES, I'M COMING!
- DO YOU KNOW WHAT THOSE GIRLS
ARE DOING OVER THERE, TENCHI?
- HUH?
- ARE THEY PLAYING SOME SORT
OF A GAME?
- I REALLY DON'T KNOW, GRANDPA.
- HEY, GIRLS,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OVER THERE?
WHY DON'T YOU COME OVER HERE
AND TALK WITH ME AND TENCHI?
- GIRLS?  WHAT GIRLS?
YOU! HOW DARE YOU USE MY
GUARDIAN WITHOUT MY PERMISSION?
- YOU!  WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
COPYING ME?
- ARGH.  HOW UNPLEASANT.
LET US LEAVE.
- Kamidake: YES, MA'AM.
- THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
- Azaka: YOU'RE WELCOME.
- THEY'VE BEEN ACTING WEIRD
ALL MORNING.
- HMM.
SPRING FEVER.
- ( laughs )
- HMM.
- HMMMM!
- THAT'S IT.
AH, GREAT TENCHI.
- WHAT IS IT, AYEKA?
YES?
- I'VE BEEN WORKING.
I MADE IT FOR YOU.
- WHAT, FOR-- FOR ME?
- YES.
- AYEKA.
( laughs )
OOH!  OH NO!
WHAT HAVE I DONE?!
- MMM, GOOD.
- OH, REALLY?!
I'M SO HAPPY!
( laughs )
MMM.
I CAN'T TELL ANYTHING.
- ( meows )
- COME ON.
TASTE IT.
- ( growls )
- HMMM!  GREAT.
I WONDER WHAT IT'S MISSING.
HMM.
ARGH!
( singing )
OH!
( groans )
- I'M HOME!
- Both: WELCOME HOME, TENCHI.
- OH, WHAT IS IT NOW?
- Ryoko:
LISTEN, LISTEN, TENCHI.
WE'RE A PERFECT MATCH
FOR EACH OTHER.
- THAT'S DAD'S BOOK, ISN'T IT?
IT'S REALLY--
- TENCHI!
TENCHI, LOOK RIGHT HERE.
RIGHT HERE-- "THE LOVE YOU
FIND NOW IS AN ETERNAL LOVE.
TREASURE IT."  OW!
- TENCHI, FEBRUARY
IS THE BEST MONTH.
AS OUR RELATIONSHIP DEEPENS,
WE WILL HAVE THE BLESSINGS
OF THOSE AROUND US.
- WOULDN'T BLESSINGS FOR A MATCH
WITH A MONSTER BE
POINTLESS, TENCHI?
- IT WAS FATE--
FATE THAT BROUGHT US TOGETHER.
WASN'T IT, TENCHI?
- TENCHI!
- Ayeka: HE'S A BETTER MATCH
WITH ME.
- YOU KNOW, THOSE BOOKS
ARE 10 YEARS OLD AT LEAST.
- Both: WHAT?!
- BUT THIS ONE HERE
IS HOT OFF THE PRESS.
NOW LET'S SEE.
OH, BOTH OF YOU ARE THE ABSOLUTE
WORST MATCH WITH TENCHI!
- Both: EH?
- I, ON THE OTHER HAND,
AM, UM, OH!
A PERFECT MATCH.
- OH NO. OH!
- I'M SO HAPPY!
- ( all grumbling )
- FINE, ON TO MY NEXT OPTION.
I'LL JUST WORK ON THE OLD MAN
AND MAKE MYSELF THE FIANCEE.
GRANDFATHER?
I WOULD LIKE
TO BUILD A FAMILY WITH TENCHI.
PLEASE HELP ME.
- HMMM.
YOU HAVE BEEN THINKING
FAR AHEAD.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAVE MY BLESSING.
- ( laughs )
PIECE OF CAKE!
OOH!
- YOU ARE SUCH A HARDWORKING
YOUNG LADY, MIHOSHI.
- WELL, I MUST DO SOMETHING
IN RETURN FOR YOUR KINDNESS.
- I THANK YOU.
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
DO YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND,
MIHOSHI?
- OH.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK OF TENCHI?
- OH, THIS--
THIS IS SO EMBARRASSING.
- IF YOU WERE HIS GIRLFRIEND,
I COULD REST EASIER.
- BUT, UH,
WE'RE BOTH SO YOUNG.
AND WE HAVE TO FIND OUT
HOW HE FEELS ABOUT ME.
( laughs )
- YOU UNDERSTAND?
YOU MUST DELIVER THIS TO TENCHI.
THEN I WILL GIVE YOU THE CARROTS
THAT YOU LOVE SO MUCH
WITHOUT TENCHI KNOWING.
- ( meows )
- OH!
NO NEED FOR SUCH HASTE.
- ( meows )
- NOW I MUST LEAVE ALSO.
- HEY! HELLO.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
- ( meows )
( meows )
- WHAA--
WHAT'S THE BIG HURRY?
- ( meows )
- "I AM BUT A HUMBLE SCHOOLGIRL.
THERE IS SOMETHING I WOULD LIKE
TO DISCUSS WITH YOU.
I WILL WAIT FOR YOU
AFTER SCHOOL"?!
- OH, TENCHI!
GREAT TIMING!
CAN YOU GET ME SOME VEGETABLES
FOR DINNER?
- OH, SURE.
- I CAN'T GET AWAY RIGHT NOW!
- ( creatures beeping )
- ( floor creaking )
- HEY!
IS THAT RYO-OHKI?
OH.
WHAAA!
THEY'RE GONE!
THEY'RE EMPTY!
OH, I KNEW IT!
IT IS RYO-OHKI!
YOU STUPID LITTLE--
AYYY!
( shudders )
- TENCHI?
- UH UH UH...
- SO THIS IS THE
REASON FOR THE WEIRD
ENERGY REACTION I DETECTED.
COME ON, COME ON,
BACK TO THE POND.
- ( meows )
- UH, ALL RIGHT THEN.
BUT ONLY ONE
FOR EACH OF YOU.
- ( meowing )
- TENCHI, DON'T YOU
HAVE THE VEGETABLES YET?
HUH?
WOW!
SO MANY RYO-OHKIS!  WOW!
- SUCH NAUGHTY CRYSTALS.
- ( all meowing )
- UH, CARROTS ALL GONE.
BETTER GET BACK TO WORK.
- OH, WHERE IS TENCHI?
ISN'T IT AFTER SCHOOL YET?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
TENCHI NEVER SHOWED UP.
( coughing )
NO MORE GIRLS' COMICS FOR ME.
OOOHHHH!
- YOU AWAKE NOW, PRINCESS?
- AWAKE AND FROZEN, THANK YOU.
- DON'T YOU THINK THERE ARE
TOO MANY PEOPLE IN THE WAY,
LIKE WASHU AND MIHOSHI?
- ON THAT ISSUE,
I WILL COOPERATE WITH YOU.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
- ( both grunting )
- FIRST WE'LL CREATE
A FORCE FIELD
AT THE DOOR TO
LOCK WASHU INSIDE.
AND THEN WE'LL MAKE MIHOSHI
GO BACK TO THE GALAXY POLICE
FOR A WHILE.
- MY, YOU'RE SO DEVIOUS,
AREN'T YOU?
- ( both laugh )
- EARTH STYLE OR WHATEVER--
BOY MEETS GIRL.
AFTER ALL, TENCHI AND I
ARE BOTH HUMANOID TYPES.
WHAT WE WANT
HAS GOT TO BE THE SAME THING.
- I'LL WASH AND WASH
AND PRESENT MYSELF TO TENCHI
IN THIS BEAUTIFUL SKIN.
AND HE'LL SAY,
"AYEKA, YOU'RE SO BEAUTIFUL."
- NO NEED TO BE AFRAID,
TENCHI.
I'M THE HUMANOID
OF YOUR DREAMS.
- ( both laughing )
- ( clapping )
AHEM!
UH, HONORABLE--
HONORABLE SIR,
COULD I HONORABLY HONOR--
UH, HUMBLY--
COULD I USE YOUR PHONE?
- MM-HMM.
- ( ringing )
- I'LL GET IT!
HELLO?
MASAKI HOME.
OH, THAT SOUNDS AS IF
I'D MARRIED INTO THE FAMILY.
HOW EMBARRASSING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU THINK IS SOUNDS THAT WAY?
- ( grumbling )
GET A GRIP!
AND LISTEN UP, DETECTIVE.
- AH!
- ( panting ) ARGH!
THIS IS YOUR VERY NASTY SUPERIOR
AT THE GALAXY POLICE, MIHOSHI.
- OH MY!  HELLO.
BUT HOW ON EARTH
DID YOU KNOW I WAS HERE?
- AN UNIMPORTANT DETAIL.
NOW COME BACK QUICKLY
TO MAKE YOUR REPORT.
- YES!  DETECTIVE MIHOSHI
IS ON HER WAY.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME, SIR!
- GOOD.
( laughs )
GULLIBLE IS AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
- ( slurping )
- HMMM?
- HMMM.
WHAT DO I DO?
I NEED A SPACESHIP.
HMM?
OH, AYEKA.
- DON'T WORRY.
LET'S TALK TO WASHU.
I'M SURE SHE WILL BE ABLE
TO GET YOU A SPACESHIP OR TWO.
- REALLY?  REALLY?!
OH, THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
- YOUR SHUTTLE FELL INTO
SUBSPACE AROUND HERE, RIGHT?
SO NOW
WE JUST NEED TO FIND IT.
- CAN YOU DO THAT?
- POLICE SHIPS ARE RARE
IN THIS AREA,
SO IT SHOULD BE EASY
TO LOCATE.
NOW LET'S SEE.
THERE IT IS!
- OH, WONDERFUL!
THANK YOU.
- ( beeping )
- ( clapping )
- THERE IT IS.
THERE'S MY SPACESHIP.
- ( both gasp )
- ( both screaming )
- OH NO!
WHAT DO WE DO?
- ( roaring )
- HAVING A FOOLISH DAUGHTER
IS MORE WORK FOR MOM!
- WELL, THAT WAS SURE SIMPLE.
- SHUT UP.
IF ONLY I HAD ALL MY GEMS.
- BYE, MIHOSHI.
- TENCHI, THANK YOU!
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
AND GOOD LUCK, MIHOSHI.
- I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU
OR THE TIME I SPENT HERE.
SO I--
- MIHOSHI,
ARE YOU REALLY GOING HOME?
- YES, I HAVE TO
BECAUSE MY WORK--
- NO, I DON'T WANT YOU TO!
( crying )
- I'M SORRY.
I DON'T WANT TO.
I-- ( crying )
- SASAMI, LET'S NOT
MAKE IT DIFFICULT NOW.
- ( sobbing )
- MIHOSHI, YOU CAN COME BACK
ONCE YOU'VE FINISHED, CAN'T YOU?
- YOU MEAN YOU DON'T MIND
IF I COME BACK HERE?
- DO YOU REALLY, TENCHI?
- YES, OF COURSE.
REALLY, YOU'RE WELCOME
TO COME BACK HERE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THAT'S SO NICE.
I WILL COME BACK
AS SOON AS I FINISH MY WORK.
I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN, TENCHI.
- WELL, HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT?
- WELL, AT LEAST
SHE WON'T BE BACK FOR A WHILE.
- COME BACK SOON, MIHOSHI!
COME BACK SOON!
- Both: BYE BYE NOW!
DON'T COME BACK
FOR A LONG TIME.
- ( whimpering )
- THAT'LL DO IT.
THE LAST OF 'EM
IS OUT OF THE WAY.
- ( grunting )
- WHAT? WHAT'S THAT YOU SAY?
GOOD LUCK TO ME?
- YOU--
- AND THAT I'M PERFECT
FOR TENCHI?
WELL, THAT'S AWFULLY NICE
OF YOU TO SAY.
PRINCESS, YOU'RE THE GREATEST.
- ( Ayeka whimpering )
- MIHOSHI, WE WILL
REACH THE RENDEZVOUS POINT
WITH THE MAIN SHIP SHORTLY.
DOCKING COMPLETE.
SUPER INTERSPACE HOTLINE
NOW OPEN.
MIHOSHI,
YOUR PASSWORD, PLEASE.
MIHOSHI?
MIHOSHI, YOUR PASSWORD.
- OH!
( laughs )
- MIHOSHI?
- YES?
- WE ARE READY
FOR SUPER INTERSPACE HOTLINE.
PLEASE SAY YOUR PASSWORD.
- UM, I DON'T KNOW.
THERE WAS AN OLD WOMAN
WHO LIVED IN A SHOE?
- PASSWORD CONFIRMED.
- WOW.
- THE LINE HAS BEEN CONNECTED.
- ( scanning )
- REPORT TRANSFER COMPLETE.
- GREAT, THEN LET'S GO BACK.
- YOU STILL HAVE TO MAKE A
VERBAL REPORT TO YOUR SUPERIOR.
- OKAY.
- YOU DID IT,
DETECTIVE MIHOSHI!
OH, I HAD A FEELING IT WAS YOU!
I HAD A FEELING.
TWO DAYS AGO,
THERE WAS A REPORT
FROM THE SPECIAL UNIT
ASSIGNED TO RESCUE YOU.
THEY DETECTED A SHOCKWAVE
AND AN ELECTROMAGNETIC WAVE
BELIEVED TO BE CAUSED
BY A HUGE EXPLOSION.
THE HEADQUARTERS
DID AN ENERGY SPECTRUM ANALYSIS
AND CAME UP WITH A RESULT
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO.
THE EXPLOSION
WAS FROM SOJA.
THEN I RECEIVED YOUR REPORT.
OH, YOU DID IT!
CONGRATULATIONS.
NOW MY JOB IS SAFE
AND YOU CAN GO BACK PROUDLY
TO THE CENTRAL OFFICE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
UH, WHAT'S WRONG, MIHOSHI?
- OUCH.
- WHAT?!
YOU'RE NOT GOING BACK?
- RIGHT.  I,
FIRST CLASS DETECTIVE MIHOSHI,
WISH A REASSIGNMENT
TO PATROL THE SPECIAL AREA
OF THE SOLAR SYSTEM.
- BUT--
BUT WHY?
WHAT FOR?
YOU'RE TURNING DOWN
THE CENTRAL OFFICE?
CENTRAL COMMAND?
YOUR GRANDFATHER--
I MEAN THE MARSHAL--
IS LOOKING FORWARD
TO SEEING YOU AND--
- NO, I'M NOT A CHILD ANYMORE
AND PLEASE DO NOT WORRY
ABOUT MY GRANDFATHER.
- UH, WON'T YOU RECONSIDER?
BESIDES, THE EARTH
ISN'T OUR TERRITORY.
GALAXY POLICE CAN'T GO THERE
WITHOUT JURAI'S PERMISSION.
- I ALREADY
HAVE THEIR PERMISSION.
WHAT?!
- HE SAID
THAT HE WANTED ME TO COME BACK.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- WHAT I MEAN IS--
WHAT HE SAID IS--
TENCHI ASKED ME
TO COME BACK AND HE--
OH, HOW EMBARRASSING!
OH, CHIEF, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE MAKING ME SAY THIS!
OH!
( laughs )
THEN I-- UH--
- YUKINOJYO, WHO IS TENCHI?
- HE IS RELATED
TO THE JURAI ROYAL FAMILY.
- HUH?
- HOWEVER,
DUE TO SOME MISSING DATA,
EVEN I CANNOT BE CERTAIN.
- MY GOD!
DETECTIVE MIHOSHI!
- ( blabbering )
- HEY YOU!
LISTEN, MIHOSHI!
- HUH?
I'M SORRY,
MY REPORT IS FINISHED.
FIRST CLASS DETECTIVE MIHOSHI
IS ON HER WAY.
- WAIT, MIHOSHI!  NO!
- ( computer tone playing )
- LET'S GO, YUKINOJYO.
- YES, MA'AM.
- HEY, MIHOSHI!
MIHOSHI!
OH GOD.  HMM.
OH, WELL, I GUESS
THIS TAKES PRIORITY FOR NOW.
- ( floor creaking )
- FINALLY.
TENCHI, TONIGHT I CAN FINALLY--
( laughs )
TENCHI, YOU AWAKE?
ARE YOU?
- UH, WHAT'S UP?
IT'S REALLY LATE AT NIGHT.
- ( sighs )
TELL ME, TENCHI,
WHO DO YOU LOVE?
ME OR AYEKA?
- WELL...
- PLEASE ANSWER ME, TENCHI.
- UH...
- YOU LOVE AYEKA.
OH!
YOU DON'T LIKE ME
BECAUSE I DO THINGS
LIKE PUNCH HOLES IN THE CEILING
AND GO THROUGH WALLS
AND FLY IN THE AIR.
IS THAT IT?
- I DON'T MIND
ANY OF THAT.
- THEN ANSWER ME, TENCHI.
- I LOVE YOU, OF COURSE!
- ( gasps ) TENCHI!
- RYOKO!
- Both: ALL RIGHT!
( both laughing )
Both: SHHH!
- OKAY.
YOU WON'T GET ANY SLEEP,
TENCHI.
- ( pulsating )
- TONIGHT WE ARE GOING
TO GET REAL WET.
OH YEAH.
- ( croaking )
- AYEKA!
- I'M GLAD I HAVE
THAT FORCE FIELD SET UP.
CALLOUS PERSON,
TRYING TO GET INTO HIS ROOM
WITHOUT EVEN KNOCKING.
- YOU'RE CHEATING, AYEKA!
- CHEATING?  YOU'RE A FINE ONE
TO TALK ABOUT CHEATING.
- THAT REALLY
WAS A CHEAP TRICK.
- AND WHO FELL
FOR THE CHEAP TRICK? HUH?
- HMM!
- YOU JUST TRY AND LAY
A FINGER ON TENCHI.
I WON'T LET YOU!
- ALL RIGHT, YOU WIN.
YOU CAN GO FIRST.
I DON'T CARE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, GO FIRST?
- WELL, YOU'RE TRYING TO GET HIM
INTO THE SACK TOO, AREN'T YOU?
- WHAT?
- WELL, AREN'T YOU?
IT'S OKAY, I DON'T MIND.
- I AM NOT A WOMAN
OF LOOSE MORALS!
- REALLY?
HMM.
- WHAT?  WHAT IS IT?
- I SPY A LITTLE LIGHT MAKEUP,
A NEW NIGHTIE...
( sniffs )
AH, I CAN ACTUALLY
SMELL YOUR HORMONES.
"MY MIND AND BODY ARE PURE!
MAKE LOVE TO ME!"
THAT'S THE MESSAGE
YOU'RE TRYING TO GET ACROSS.
- NO, YOU'RE A LIAR!
- YOU LOVE TENCHI, DON'T YOU?
- OF COURSE I--
( whimpers )
- THEN WHY? IT'S ONLY NATURAL
TO WANT TO BE WITH HIM
AND MAKE LOVE WITH HIM
IF YOU LOVE HIM.
- BUT IS HE-- I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW HE FEELS ABOUT ME.
AND-- AND IT'S--
AND IT'S--
- AND IT'S--
- AND IT'S JUST TOO EARLY
FOR US.
- OH, WELL,
IN THAT CASE,
I'LL GO FIRST.
- HMM. HUH?
NOW HOLD IT! THE POINT IS
NOT WHO'S GOING TO GO FIRST!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU!
YOU!
YOU WON'T GET PAST ME.
- FINE. WE'LL DO THINGS THE WAY
YOU LIKE TO. WE'LL FIGHT!
- ( both grunting )
- Sasami: TENCHI?
AYEKA?
RYOKO?
ARE YOU HERE?
ARE YOU?
RYO-OHKI?
WHERE DID EVERYONE GO?
TENCHI?
- ( glass shattering )
- AHHH!
OH, TENCHI.
TENCHI, YOU--
I'M HURT.
TENCHI, WATCH OUT.
WAIT, DON'T TAKE HIM AWAY.
TENCHI-- DON'T TAKE HIM AWAY!
NO, DON'T TAKE HIM AWAY!
NO, STOP!
DON'T TAKE HIM!
NO, WAIT.
PLEASE DON'T.
DON'T TAKE HIM AWAY, TOKIMI.
AYEKA, WHERE ARE YOU?
RYO-OHKI?
WHERE ARE YOU?
AYEKA?
- ( grunting )
- LISTEN UP, PRINCESS.
YOU LEAVE TENCHI TO ME.
HE'S TOO MUCH TO HANDLE
FOR A LITTLE GIRL LIKE YOU.
- ( grunting )
- I'M NOT SHUTTING UP
OR GIVING UP!
- ( Sasami crying )
( knocking )
- HUH?
- TENCHI?  TENCHI?
- ( door closes )
- WHAT'S WRONG, SASAMI?
- I HAD A SCARY DREAM.
CAN I SLEEP WITH YOU?
- WHERE'S AYEKA?
- SHE'S WITH RYOKO.
- Washu: FIGHTING AGAIN,
I'M SURE.
- Both: HUH?
- Tenchi:
THOSE TWO ARE SO IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- Sasami:
THERE YOU ARE, RYO-OHKI.
I'M SO GLAD.
- Both: HUH?
- Washu: LET'S FORGET ABOUT THEM
AND WE'LL ALL SLEEP TOGETHER.
- ( door slides closed )
- NOW JUST A MINUTE.
- Ryoko: WAIT WAIT WAIT WAIT!
- ( beeping )
- I WONDER WHAT THAT WAS
OUT THERE.
- ( Ryo-Ohko meows )
- TWO WET FOOLS
WHO FORGOT TO KNOCK.
- HUH?
- OH, NOTHING.
COME ON, LET'S GO TO SLEEP.
- ( meows )
- ( laughs )
- Tenchi: SO, SASAMI,
WHAT WAS YOUR DREAM ABOUT?
- LET'S SEE.
A WOMAN TOOK YOU AWAY, TENCHI.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHO SHE WAS.
- DON'T WORRY,
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
- OKAY.
- ( both sigh )
- ( ship passing )
- Both: HUH?
- WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
- SOUNDS LIKE
MIHOSHI'S SHADOW.
- OH!
- AND IT DOESN'T SOUND GOOD.
- Tenchi: HUH?
- MIHOSHI?  MIHOSHI?
- YES, YUKINOJYO?
- MIHOSHI, WE SHOULD BE APPLYING
THE REVERSE BRAKE.
- THE AUTO CONTROL
SHOULD DO THAT.
SO DON'T WORRY.
- AND I STILL DON'T SEE
ANY BEACON
FROM THE EARTH, MIHOSHI.
- OOPS, I FORGOT.
- FORGOT WHAT?
- THEY HAVE NO SUCH THING
ON PLANET EARTH.
- WHAT?!
- ( ship screeching )
- ( both laughing nervously )
- ( both groaning )
- Azaka: LOOKS LIKE
ANOTHER BEAUTIFUL DAY.
- Kamidake: SUCH WONDERFUL
SPRINGLIKE WEATHER.
- ( Ryo-Ohki meows )
- MMM. HUH?
HUH?  OH.
AHHH!
- All: HUH?
- GET AWAY FROM THERE!
- ( meows )
- I TOLD YOU THAT
WASN'T A CARROT.
- ( meows )
- AH, RYO-OH!
- OH, I SEE.
YOU'RE TALKING
WITH RYO-OH.
- ( meows )
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ LIFE IS SO FULL
OF HURRY AND HUSTLE ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I THINK
IT'S PASSING US BY ♪
♪ THE DAYS ARE LIKE HOURS,
HOURS LIKE MINUTES ♪
♪ I'M CAUGHT IN IT
TILL I LOOK IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND TO MY SURPRISE ♪
♪ I FIND THERE IS A HEAVEN ♪
♪ TIME IS UNREAL,
MAKING ME FEEL ♪
♪ FREE AND ALIVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME,
YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
IN SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME,
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE
LIGHT-YEARS AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TELEPHONE LOVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME, YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
TO SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME ♪
♪ WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE LIGHT-YEARS
AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP
THIS TREASURE FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TELEPHONE LOVE. ♪