- ( theme music playing )
- ( groans )
TENCHI.
TENCHI!
NOW WHERE DID HE GO?
HMM.
- ( bones crack )
- ( groans )
WHERE DID HE PUT THEM?
HMM?  LET'S SEE.
WHOA!
HUH?
- IT WAS CURIOSITY
THAT KILLED THE CAT, TENCHI.
- ( screams )
- I BET YOU WERE
LOOKING FOR THESE.
- SO THAT'S WHERE
THEY ARE-- OOPS.
- YOU WEREN'T TRYING
TO SNEAK IN THERE
AGAINST MY ORDERS,
WERE YOU?
( chuckles )
- NO, I WASN'T.
- IT IS THE ANCIENT LAW
OF THIS MISAKI SHRINE.
AND YOU ARE NO EXCEPTION
TO THAT LEGACY.
( chuckles )
BUT REALLY,
YOU WANT TO SEE
WHAT'S IN THERE, DON'T YOU?
- MM-HMM.
- HERE THEY ARE, TENCHI,
IF YOU CAN
TAKE THEM FROM ME.
LET'S SEE HOW GOOD
YOU REALLY ARE.
- HMM.
HUMPH.
HYAH!
( strains )
WHOA!  WHOA-AH-AH!
- HMM.
WORK HARDER.
AND REMEMBER, YOUR CHORES
ARE PART OF YOUR TRAINING.
- HMM?
CURIOSITY KILLED THE CAT.
LUCKY FOR ME, I'M NOT A CAT.
( laughs )
AAH.
OH.
- Katsuhito:
TENCHI!  BOY!
- ( gasps )
- WHY MUST YOU COME HERE
TIME AFTER TIME
WHEN YOU KNOW
IT'S NOT ALLOWED?
- BUT WHY IS THAT, GRANDPA?
- I'LL TELL YOU WHY, MY BOY.
A DEMON SLEEPS HERE.
- A DEMON?  NO.
- IT'S TRUE.
NOW, LISTEN CAREFULLY
FOR WHAT I'M ABOUT
TO TELL YOU REALLY HAPPENED.
IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
A DEMON CAME HERE
FROM THE SKY.
ITS STRENGTH WAS
ENORMOUS AND TERRIBLE.
IT DESTROYED VILLAGES,
BURNED EVERYTHING,
AND OUR PEOPLE
SUFFERED GREATLY
BECAUSE OF
ITS EVIL POWERS.
- Young Tenchi:
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE DEMON?
- Katsuhito: ONE DAY,
A SHIP LIKE A DRAGON
APPEARED FROM THE SKY.
ON ITS BACK,
RODE A MIGHTY SAMURAI.
HE FOUGHT THE DEMON
USING A SWORD WITH
GREAT SPIRITUAL POWERS.
NOW THE DEMON SLEEPS,
HELD PRISONER
IN THIS SHRINE.
THE SWORD
PLANTED IN THE GROUND
KEEPS WATCH OVER IT.
THAT SAMURAI WAS YOSHO,
YOUR ANCESTOR, TENCHI.
REMEMBER YOUR NAME
AND WHAT IT MEANS--
"HEAVEN AND EARTH."
YOU MUST REMEMBER
AND RESPECT YOUR ANCESTOR.
REMEMBER.
- HUH?
OH!
( strains )
( grunting )
HMM.
( straining )
HUH?
WHA-- IT'S JUST A RUSTY
OLD PIECE OF JUNK.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
"THE SWORD THAT CUTS
THROUGH A ROCK"?
HA!
UH-OH!
WHAT?
- ( rumbling )
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
OH.
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
OH, THINK, GENIUS.
HMM?
OH, A PASSAGEWAY.
AH, THAT'S COLD!
OWW, MY HEAD!
I-- WHOA-AH-AH!
WHOA!  OH, BOY,
I THOUGHT--
( gulps )
HUH?
( groans )
( screams )
( crashes )
OUCH!
( groans )
HUH?
OH.
HMM?
( gulps )
OH, IT'S JUST A GIANT
GLOWING LIGHT.
NO PROBLEM.
AHH.
W-- WHAT'S THAT?
( gulps )
A DEMON SLEEPS HERE.
IT WASN'T
JUST A LEGEND.
- ( sword clangs loudly )
- AAH!
WHEW.
TIME TO GO HOME.
AH.
I'M ON MY WAY.
OKAY, I'M OUT OF HERE.
( screams )
HUH?!
( grunts, strains )
LET ME GO!
- ( raspy breathing )
- ( both scream )
- OH.
( whimpers )
( yelps, growls )
HUH?
- ( demon groaning )
- I'M GIVING THOSE KEYS
BACK TO GRANDPA
AND DO AS MANY CHORES
AS HE SAYS!
( panting )
- ( bell tolls )
- HEY, TENCHI.
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
- OH, UH, NOTHING.
JUST AN OLD
PIECE OF JUNK.
- OH.  SO, UH, HOW WAS
YOUR SUMMER VACATION?
- OH, DON'T ASK ME.
JUST ME AND GRANDPA
AT WORK ALL DAY LONG AS USUAL.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE ALL
PART OF THE TRAINING, I GUESS.
- OH, MAN,
WHAT A BIG DRAG.
DIDN'T YOU GET TO MEET
ANY GIRLS EVEN?
- IF YOU WERE A GIRL,
WOULD YOU COME
TO A SHABBY SHRINE
DEEP IN THE MOUNTAINS?
- HMM, HELL NO.
- RIGHT.
PLENTY OF GIRLS 82 YEARS OLD.
- OH, SO YOU DATED
MUMMIES ALL SUMMER LONG?
( chuckles )
- YUP, DRIED UP,
FURLING OLD MUMMIES.
( laughs )
( continues laughing )
A MUMMY?
- HEY, WHAT'S WRONG, TENCHI?
- HUH?  OH.
- TENCHI, DON'T TELL ME
YOU WERE SO HARD UP
YOU SLEPT WITH A MUMMY?
- ( grunts )
- ( students gasp )
- GET A LIFE, CLOWN!
- OH.
- I'VE GOT
TO GET A GRIP.
GRANDPA NEVER
MENTIONED ANYTHING.
MAYBE NOTHING
HAPPENED AFTER ALL.
( sighs )
JUST RELAX, TENCHI.
- ( bell jingles )
- OH.  HUH?
WHAT?
OH, GREAT,
I FELL ASLEEP.
I MISSED ALL MY CLASSES
AND EVERYONE'S GONE.
- ( bell jingles )
- ( cat meows )
- KITTY, HOW THE HECK
DID YOU GET IN HERE?
- ( meows )
- ( bell jingles )
- HUH?
- ( giggles )
- ( bell jingles )
- OH.
- RYOKO.
- HUH?
- ( giggles )
THAT'S MY NAME.
- NO.  NO WAY!
- ( growls )
- YOU CAN'T BE--
YOU CAN'T BE THAT...
THAT-- THAT--
THAT-- THAT
FREEZE-DRIED DEMON!
AAH!
- IT WAS COLD IN THERE
AND DARK.
YOU KNOW HOW LONG
I WAS TRAPPED IN THAT CAVE?
700 YEARS.
AND I DIDN'T LIKE IT.
I DIDN'T LIKE IT
AT ALL.
ALL I WANT NOW
IS REVENGE!
- HEY, IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
- NO?
- NO, NO WAY.
IT WAS MY ANCESTOR,
SOME GUY NAMED YOSHO!
- I DON'T CARE.
I JUST NEED TO LET OUT
MY ANGER ON YOU
RIGHT NOW!
- WHY ME?
IT'S NOT FAIR!
- ( cackling )
WHAT'S THE MATTER, TENCHI?
- WHOA!
( panting )
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO RUN
A LOT FASTER THAN THAT,
EARTHLING.
- AAH!
OKAY, NOW!
- MM-HMM.
- READY OR NOT,
HERE I COME!
AAH!
HUH?  WHOA!
WHOA.
( shouting )
HUH?!
- ( laughs )
( laughter continues )
- ( screams )
- HEY, TRY NOT
TO HURT YOURSELF.
I'D LIKE TO DO THAT
FOR YOU.
- ( groaning )
OWW.  HUH?
UH-OH.
( screams )
( breathes deeply )
( holds breath )
( strains )
( exhales loudly )
THAT WAS CLOSE.
I'LL JUST HIDE HERE
WHILE I FIGURE OUT A PLAN.
WHAT IS THAT--
THAT SMELL?
OH, GAS FUMES.
GAS FUMES?!
- ( gas hissing )
- Tenchi: OH, GREAT!
I'VE GOT A GOOD PLAN!
I'M GONNA GET OUT OF HERE.
- Ryoko: TENCHI.
- WHAT NEXT?
- ( groans )
- ( hissing )
- ( gulps )
- HELLO, THERE.
- HUH?!  WHAT?!
( grunts )
- IT'S TIME FOR
TODAY'S LESSON,
SCHOOLBOY.
- ( screams )
THERE'S LEAKING GAS!
YOU'LL START A FIRE!
- GAS?  WHAT IS GAS?
- ( groans )
I CAN JUST SEE
THE HEADLINES.
"BRILLIANT STUDENT
BLOWN TO BITS."
OH, MAN, IF I'D KNOWN
I WAS GONNA DIE TODAY,
I WOULDN'T HAVE DONE
ALL THAT HOMEWORK
OVER VACATION!
I-- I THINK I MIGHT
JUST HAVE AN IDEA.
- HMM?
- HEY, WHAT'S THAT
OUTSIDE THE WINDOW?
I JUST USED THE OLDEST
TRICK IN THE BOOK.
- OOH, WHAT IS IT?
I WANT TO SEE.
- ( door slides )
- HMM?
HMM?  HEY, I DON'T
WANT TO MISS ANYTHING.
- YEAH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE BOUGHT IT!
I'M OUT OF HERE.
- NO, I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
I THINK-- ( gasps )
WHAT?
- ( whimpers )
- ( growls )
I'LL GET HIM!
- ( static crackles )
- ( screams )
THERE SHE GOES.
YOU KNOW,
SHE WAS KINDA CUTE.
HUH?
OH, OLD SHRINE HABIT.
( laughs )
HUH?!  AAH!
- ( coughs ) HEY, THAT'S NO
WAY TO TREAT A LADY!
- OH, BIG TROUBLE.
SHE'S ALIVE AGAIN.
- ( shouts )
( gasps )
LOOK AT ME.
MY HAIR IS A MESS.
- THANK GOD.
- OH!  OH OH.
- ( sighs, pants )
OKAY, OKAY.
SO SHE'S GOT INCREDIBLE
SUPER POWERS AND I DON'T.
SO FAR SO GOOD.
SO-- SO NOW WHAT
DO I DO?
- ( giggles )
YOU ARE ONE
BEAUTIFUL DEMON.
LET'S GO.
- ( fire alarm rings )
- ( screams )
TAKE IT EASY.
IT'S ONLY
THE STUPID FIRE ALARM.
- ( ringing continues )
- OF COURSE HALF THE BUILDING'S
GOT TO BE ON FIRE
BEFORE IT RINGS.
WELL, I GUESS IT'S JUST
ONE OF THOSE KIND OF DAYS.
HUH?
WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT JEWEL ON HER WRIST.
THAT'S GOT TO BE
THE SOURCE OF HER POWERS.
YEAH, THE LEGEND SAYS SO.
THREE GEMS FOR POWER.
WITHOUT HER POWER,
MAYBE I CAN GET HER
BACK IN THAT CAVE.
I'VE GOT TO TRY.
COME ON.
YOU CAN DO IT, TENCHI.
( laughs )
I CAN BEAT HER.
IT'S EASY!
- EASY?
- ( grunts )
WHAT THE-- UH.
- DON'T BE SO SCARED,
SWEETIE PIE.
- HUH?
- I WON'T HURT YOU...
TOO MUCH!
- ( screams )
- ( grunts )
- HUH?
WHOA.
- ( gasps )
IMPRESSIVE.
CATCH.
I GOT YOU!
HEY, NO FAIR.
CHEATING!
- WHAT?  GIVE ME A BREAK.
THIS SWORD HAS
A MIND OF ITS OWN.
IF I'D HAD MY WAY, I WOULDN'T
FIGHT A MONSTER LIKE YOU.
- MONSTER?!
TELL ME JUST EXACTLY
WHAT MAKES YOU CALL
A PRETTY YOUNG LADY
LIKE ME A MONSTER?!
- OH, COME ON.
YOU WALK THROUGH FIRE.
YOU WALK THROUGH WALLS.
YOU RIP HOLES IN THE ROOF.
AND YOU CAN EVEN FLY!
- VERY GOOD REASONS,
BUT NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
- OH.
- OH WELL,
ANOTHER BATTLE LOST.
THAT'S THE STORY OF MY LIFE.
( sighs )
HUH?
- OH, THE SWORD DID IT.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO CUT OFF YOUR---
I'M SORRY.
- ( giggles )
TA-DA.
- WOW.
- GOOD NIGHT.
- ( clapping )
( laughing )
( screams )
- ( siren wailing )
- UH-OH.
OH, NO!
I BETTER GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE I GET INTO
REALLY BIG TROUBLE.
WHAT A MESS!
( panting )
( sighs )
HOME.
( exhales )
THIS SWORD
SURE IS POWERFUL.
I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED
TO THAT DEMON GIRL?
TRY NOT
TO THINK ABOUT HER.
IT'S OVER.
( yawns )
HUH?
- ( moans )
- ( babbles )
( yelps )
- HMM.  MMM.
WELCOME HOME, TENCHI.
- ( groans )
( whimpers )
- ( end theme playing )
- ♪ LIFE IS SO FULL
OF HURRY AND HUSTLE ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I THINK
IT'S PASSING US BY ♪
♪ THE DAYS ARE LIKE HOURS ♪
♪ HOURS LIKE MINUTES ♪
♪ I'M CAUGHT IN IT
TILL I LOOK IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ AND TO MY SURPRISE ♪
♪ I FIND
THERE IS A HEAVEN ♪
♪ TIME IS UNREAL ♪
♪ MAKING ME FEEL ♪
♪ FREE AND IN LOVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME,
YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME
HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET ♪
♪ IN SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME ♪
♪ WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK
OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE
LIGHT-YEARS AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP ♪
♪ THIS TREASURE
FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TALENT FOR LOVE ♪
♪ YOU TOUCH ME,
YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ AND TIME
HAS NO MEANING ♪
♪ I'M ON A ROCKET
TO SOME OTHER ZONE ♪
♪ BABY, YOU THRILL ME ♪
♪ WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ DON'T THINK OF STOPPING ♪
♪ UNTIL WE ARE
LIGHT-YEARS AWAY ♪
♪ ALL ALONE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT TO KEEP ♪
♪ THIS TREASURE
FOR MY VERY OWN ♪
♪ YOUR TALENT FOR LOVE. ♪
- ( inaudible )