(suspenseful music)
(heroic music)
- [Voiceover] Golden scales
can't be kept in a pond.
When Wind meets Cloud, the
golden fish becomes a dragon.
Conquerer, the leader of the world's
best martial arts school,
The Conquerer's Clan,
tries to bring the martial
arts world together
with Mud Buddha's words on his mind.
If he could get Wind and Cloud together,
he could unite everyone under his rule.
Acting on his wild ambition,
Conquerer kills Wind and Cloud's families
and adopts them himself,
teaching them in the arts.
But, the hearts of the young
Wind and Cloud reap revenge
and while they study under Conquerer,
they await the chance to kill him.
(suspenseful music)
- [Wind] Conquerer taught
us all the kung fu we know.
So to beat him, we'll need
the Flame Kylin's blood
to gain power.
- [Cloud] But, you could be possessed.
No, Wind, it's too risky.
(ominous music)
- [Voiceover] So, Wind,
you better prepare yourself
and be ready to sacrifice your life.
I drew all the devilish
Flame Kylin's blood.
You'll need to use your
ice heart technique
or else you'll lose your mind
and become possessed by an
uncontrollable killing machine.
- [Cloud] Wind, don't.
- [Voiceover] You can't stop this.
You and Wind are the only two people
who can fuse with the Flame Kylin's blood.
To call upon its power, you must allow
yourself to be possessed
by the Flame Kylin.
(tearing)
(dripping)
(shouting)
(chirping)
Now, Cloud, remember
this, Wind's devil blood
and your own is connected.
When Wind is using the powers granted
by the Kylin's blood, you must cease.
If not, he'll lose control.
- [Cloud] No, Wind.
(chirping)
(shouting)
- [Wind] Listen, Cloud,
if I ever lose control
of the demon please kill me.
- [Cloud] Conquerer, it's time you've paid
for all you've done.
- [Conquerer] Wind and Cloud
will make and break me?
Ridiculous.
(shouting)
(exploding)
(fighting)
(thrilling music)
(shouting)
- [Cloud] Quickly, Wind,
the ice heart technique.
- [Wind] The heart is cold as ice.
Nothing can stand in my way.
With a heart as clear as ice,
nothing can stand in my way.
(breaking)
(shouting)
Listen, Cloud, if I ever lose control
of the demon, please kill me.
(clanking)
(rumbling)
(shouting)
(fighting)
(running)
(shouting)
(fighting)
- [Conquerer] Run with me.
- [Wind] I'll go with you.
(apprehensive music)
(shouting)
- [Voiceover] Stormriders.
Clash of evils.
(drumming)
(foreboding music)
- Archers!
(crashing)
Fire.
(shouting)
(crumbling)
(suspenseful music)
- Jue.
You dreamt about your revenge again?
Wait, Jue.
We can't, Jue.
I promised our master.
- [Voiceover] Master Jue,
there's a man outside
called Duen Long.
He's got a letter for you.
- I wanna see him.
- Come with me.
- Long, isn't this the famous House of Ao,
from the Sword Worship Villa?
Why are they hiding underground now?
- The clan from Sword Worship Villa
was the Emperor's appointed swordsmiths
but due to false charges of rebellion,
the Emperor had the whole clan executed.
There are only two survivors
from that massacre.
Jue and Kay are the only
remaining members of that clan.
To survive, they went underground.
(banging and clanking)
I'm Duen Long, I'm here to see Master Ao.
I see from your forge that
your clan's swordsmith's skills
are not exaggerated.
They remind me of Sword
Worship Villa's glory days.
- Please get to the point, sir.
- I heard you've been searching for
the Flame Kylin's blood.
If that's true, I come bearing good news.
- The Flame Kylin's
been extinct for years.
So how can there be any Flame Kylin blood?
- There are only two people in this world
that carry the beast's blood.
The Linien Cave, the Flame Kylin.
The stories say that
one day Wind and Cloud
entered the cave, fought
with the Flame Kylin.
They killed him and took its blood.
- Why should we believe you?
- Because the Duen family and
the Flame Kylin are linked.
- The Kylin Sword.
- If you want the blood
from Wind and Cloud,
you'll need the Duen's family Kylin Sword.
- And, what do you want?
- What I want is the Conquerer's Clan.
- How dare you, Quail, you can't go
through Mr. Chao's things.
- Please, everyone has to
follow the rules and cooperate.
- What rules?
If anything breaks, can you compensate us?
- Oh, no, no, no,no, no, I can't.
- Where's your self-respect?
You're a guardsman.
So, what's this expensive thing, huh?
Let me take a look.
(elephant roaring)
There's a whole circus there.
What's going on?
Oh, Mr. and Mrs. Chao, I hope you're well.
- Oh, come on, Captain, it's my husband's
50th birthday today,
so we've hired a circus
for the big occasion
and everyone's invited.
You don't really need
to search them, do you?
- Thing is, we've received
news that the Bat Gang
is gonna ambush the city.
- The Bat Gang coming here to attack us?
We should go hire some
bodyguards to protect us.
- Don't worry, with me
here, it's more than enough
to take on the Bat Gang.
- Okay then, leave all the knives
and swords and weapons here.
- Stay vigilant everyone.
(people talking)
(exciting music)
- Hey mom, look, it's the elephant.
- Excuse me, sir, get out of the way.
(barking)
- [Mrs. Chao] Quickly
men, get my dog back.
- [Men] Yes, ma'am.
- Quickly, there he is.
(funky music)
- Give that back.
- Hey, doggie, come back.
- Hurry, I saw the dog go that way.
Go, go!
- Well, maybe, I should help her out.
- Ay, watch out.
- Wait, give me back my money.
- Come on, this way.
(giggling)
- Captain, there's no
trace of anyone there.
- They must've gone the other way.
Hurry up, after them, come on.
- [Men] Yes, sir.
- You pervert.
- That's the first sign of her love.
- Didn't I tell you to work
harder on your kung fu?
If I'm not there, who'll
save your butts next time?
- Hey, Mrs. Chao really
seems to care about that dog.
It must be worth a lot.
- Well, the dog's mine now
so don't even think about it.
- Hey, Ying, you're not going to try
and sell my little doggie, are you, huh?
- Well, that depends on
if he's a good boy or not.
Hey, what are you barking at, huh?
Keep barking and I'll sell you, you hear?
Oh no, now I'm all wet.
- Oh no, doggie.
Hey, doggie.
- [Ying] Hey, Yam, come on.
Forget about that mutt.
Come back.
- Doggie.
(barking)
Doggie, where have you gone now?
(whimpering)
(barking)
- Come on, Yam.
Forget about him.
Come back out, please.
- Doggie, what are you growling at now?
(growling)
(barking)
(yelling)
- Get out of here quickly.
- Come on, Yam, we gotta help.
Leave that guy, he's
probably dead already.
- He's still breathing.
We've gotta help.
- Right, don't move.
- Get outta here.
(roaring)
Okay, hold him still.
(yelling)
Yam, hurry up with that.
- You know, Ying, he could be abandoned.
- Let's talk about that when he wakes up.
(grunting)
- Hey, look at this.
Who's arm do you think is
bigger, his or mine, huh?
Yeah?
- Wow.
Check that out.
His arm's as big as your head, Juno.
(suspenseful music)
(somber music)
- Cloud, I promise I'll find you.
(shouting)
(roaring)
You dodge me.
(shouting)
(somber music)
- Hello, sir, is there
something I can help you with?
- Where are your best grave stones?
- This way, sir, follow me.
This is Ku Young white marble.
It's top grade.
- This will be fine.
- And, what should I
engrave on the headstone?
- The grave of Brother Cloud.
- [Voiceover] As you wish.
- This headstone is the last thing
I can do for my good brother.
Make sure you do the best job you can.
- [Voiceover] Table for one.
Please, come right this way.
- He's got a sword!
- [Voiceover] This guy's
disrespecting Captain Xi.
- [Captain Xi] Where's
the man with the sword?
- [Voiceover] Upstairs, Captain.
- Hey, you with the long hair,
I've not seen you around before.
Where did you come from?
- Are you deaf, boy, Captain Xi's
asking you how you got in the city.
- From the South.
- You think I'm some kind of idiot?
The South is nothing
but cliffs and ravines.
- Yeah, that's true but
that's where I came from.
- I don't care if you
were born from the rocks.
You can't bring weapons in here.
I'm taking it.
(gasping)
(struggling)
Please, sir, there's a weapons ban
being enforced on the city.
Nobody's allowed weapons
within the city walls.
Knives and swords could hurt good people.
We don't want people to get hurt.
- Blades ruin lives but so does revenge.
- We're just following orders
and keeping your sword temporarily, sir.
Oh man, that long haired guy's good.
I wonder where he's from.
And you, you idiot, you
almost chopped my arm off.
- [Quail] Sorry, Captain,
that was an accident.
(foreboding music)
- [Voiceover] What's Wind doing here?
He's so drunk.
- [Voiceover] I don't care.
Anyone from Conquerer's
Clan needs to be dealt with.
- [Voiceover] The master's coming.
(mysterious music)
- [Men] Mistress.
- Miss Dream, he's the
renowned Whispering Wind
from the Conquerer's Clan.
Should he awaken, we will
not be his equal in battle.
We should kill him before he wakes up.
(monkey chattering)
- I want to know exactly why he's here.
Quickly, bring him inside.
- We're only hiding here because
we're trying to escape
from the Conquerer's Clan.
His presence might expose us.
- No, you're wrong.
We're only hiding her because we want
to get away from senseless violence.
Just tell everyone to stay alert.
(thunder booming)
- Friends of the martial arts world,
members of the Conquerer's Clan,
in defending the clan, our
Lord Conquerer perished,
killed by his own
disciples, Whispering Wind
and Striding Cloud, the
whole of Conquerer's Clan
is sad and mournful now.
Our kingdom needs his
king and ours is gone.
Today, we shall announce that Tun Wong
will ascend to the
position of clan leader.
- Huh, Tun Wong as clan leader?
(laughing)
- [Duen Long] You're all right.
So, why don't you let
me be your new leader?
(whispering)
- What are you doing here?
You were thrown out of
the Conquerer's Clan.
- How rude.
I'm your new leader.
How dare you speak to me like that.
I'll make an example of you.
- You don't have the skills, boy.
(yelling)
- Oh, you deserve that.
You should've just let him be.
(clanking)
- This is why you have no
idea how to treat a lady.
We don't often get such
a beautiful girl around.
(whinnying)
(wind howling)
(birds cawing)
(mysterious music)
- Hmm, Conquerer, you
always did look down on me.
But, you still met your end at
the hands of your disciples.
Well now, have a good look at
who's succeeded your place.
It's me, Duen Long.
(bird cawing)
(wind blowing)
(suspenseful music)
(birds chirping)
(clinking)
- [Voiceover] A fish in a boiling cauldron
knows its days are numbered.
Why would the bird who knows the nest
is dangerous wait for the wind?
- I never knew Conquerer's
Clan had such a poetic master.
You are?
- Names are useless, hence, I am Nameless.
- Ao Jue, honored to meet you.
- Ao Jue?
So, you're from the Sword Worship Villa?
Well, Jue, it seems you
haven't caught any fish today.
- I've only caught small
ones but I want big game.
- If you're looking for big
game, you should be weary,
another bloody storm
could erupt at any moment.
A storm such as this could be devastating.
- Master Nameless, you worry too much.
Look, the sky is clear.
The big fish is here.
- Once the big fish leaves,
other fish can loose their bearings
and things will turn to chaos.
- The weak are nothing
but prey for the strong.
This is simply nature.
And, definitely me.
- Violence is in human nature
but it disrupts the peace.
(exploding)
(shouting)
(somber music)
Didn't Sword Worship
Villa make their weapons
to uphold justice?
- Justice, righteousness and
evil are all scholarly lies.
Sword Worship Villa pledged
their loyalty to the Emperor,
yet, why did he do what he
did and slaughter my family?
The Sword Worship Villa of old is gone.
They were eliminated.
My new clan is the Blade Manor.
- Hate is the foundation of all evil.
Young Master Jue, why
can't you leave behind
that hate and live a life worth living?
(clinking)
- My nature is so merciless,
I have to be cold, too.
Not everyone appreciates my music.
(epic music)
Ah, the Sword Shadow Technique.
- [Nameless] This stubbornness
will do you no good.
Let go of your anger.
(crashing)
- No one in the world can stop me.
- Hey, Ying, the Chao
Family's bodyguards are here.
- I'll go deal with them.
- Wait, Wood, stay calm.
- You got nowhere to run now.
Brat's pretty brave.
How dare you steal Mr. Chao's dog.
(thumping)
(barking)
- There's a martial arts master in there!
Run!
- Wow, Ying, he's good at martial arts.
- So, what's your name?
- I don't remember.
- You don't remember your own name?
- It doesn't matter if you don't know.
You can work for me, now.
- You're the youngest here.
Why should he work for you?
- What about now?
- [Ying] Well, you're gonna need a name.
Seeing as you're so good at martial arts,
we'll call you Expert.
You're one of us now, okay?
- [Yang] Yeah, Expert's a great name.
- [Voiceover] Mr. Chao is looking for
some great bodyguards today.
He'll choose the winner of
these martial arts contests.
(fighting)
We have a winner.
It's Chen Dong of the Chen Fist Clan.
Next fighter.
- Are they hiring bodyguards?
- Is that wine?
Is it the Drunken Fist?
- But, we've already
chosen eight bodyguards,
we don't need you.
Move along.
- Well, I'll take all eight of 'em on.
- [Voiceover] How dare he?
- [Voiceover] Rat.
- Let's get him.
(fighting)
(exploding)
- Whoa, great!
He'll do for me.
- The Wind Kick.
- That means he's Wind.
We should go tell the boss right away.
- [Voiceover] Here's the money I owe you.
- Mistress wants him
alive, what should we do?
- Kill him first, we'll worry later.
- But, the Mistress
won't look kindly on us.
- Well, let's prepare some poison first.
I'll convince Miss Dream it's for the best
after we've killed him.
(crickets chirping)
(somber music)
(glass breaking)
(thrilling music)
- Stop.
Look at that.
It was he and Cloud who killed Conquerer.
You almost killed a good man.
(fire burning)
(wind blowing)
(horse whinnying)
(crickets chirping)
(owl hooting)
- [Duen Long] Ghost Healer, stop now.
(chuckling)
- Long.
(ominous music)
- That smell.
She smells so delicious.
She's a woman?
Well, what a waste.
(horse whinnying)
- So, where is it?
(chuckling)
- This toxic leech can
poison any human blood.
This poison will work within a day
of entering your victim's body.
No matter how good his
martial arts powers,
he'll still become fatally poisoned.
He'll lose his strength
and won't be able to fight.
- Ah, you're just as good as they say.
If you need anything, let me know.
- Another mild horse.
- He's yours.
I didn't tell you because
I didn't want to scare you.
- But Long, can you really trust this guy?
- [Duen Long] The Ghost
Healer's about as crazy
as they come but as long as you give him
what he wants, he'd even
betray his own parents.
(growling)
- You want to turn the Flame
Kylin's blood into poison
with these leeches so
it'll destroy Jue after
he extracts it from Wind
and Cloud and drinks it?
- It's a necessary step to
kill two birds with one stone.
- Hey, Expert, come here.
What are you waiting for?
You'll have to earn your keep here.
So, let me show you how we do it.
(funky music)
- Excuse me, coming through.
- [Wood] There's so many
people, hey, excuse me.
(laughing)
- Ow, that hurt, why you hitting me?
- You're so useless.
Watch me.
- Let's see you do it.
- I give up.
How can you still see while
you're still blindfolded?
(laughing)
- So, you think you're good, huh?
Try and steal my money bag.
Come on.
(wind blowing)
(jingling)
You pervert.
- [Juno] Don't do it.
- [Yam] Stop it, Expert.
(calm music)
(jingling)
- Hey, Expert, as I saved your life,
you owe me a big favor.
- Sure, tell me what you want me to do.
- We're here.
Let's go get the doggie.
Cool, that was so much fun.
(clanking)
- Shhh.
(suspenseful music)
- Okay, you guys, go look for the dog.
- Right.
- Be careful though.
You come with me, Expert.
(suspenseful music)
(creaking)
(gong ringing)
(struggling)
- [Expert] Let me do it.
(smashing)
(crumbling)
- Look at all that gold.
You know what, all this
stuff is dirty treasure.
- Dirty treasure?
- Let's take it all.
(fire burning)
Expert, be careful.
(rumbling)
(screaming)
(water splashing)
(banging)
Are you okay?
- What a coincidence.
Take them away.
- Captain Xi.
This has nothing to do with the kids.
Let them go.
- Look, Miss, we caught the
thieves red-handed this time.
But, I guess, as it's your first offense,
you were all coerced.
You may all leave.
But, you stay right here.
- Wait, what do you want with him?
- Well, that's men's business,
woman should keep their noses out.
I've never seen you before.
So, tell me, where are you from?
- The South.
- Huh, the South, again.
That big tattoo means
you're in a gang, right?
Resisting arrest?
- Oh, he's still breathing.
- Why is everyone from
the South so darn strong?
(ominous music)
- [Young Jue] Father, why are we called
the Sword Worship Villa?
- A long time ago, our
great ancestors came
across a piece of superior metal.
They wanted to use it to create
a completely invincible sword which they
would call Jue.
But, it was cursed.
Whoever tried to forge this sword
would die a sudden and violent death.
The sword's spirit was
uncontrollably fierce.
- But, isn't a fierce sword a good sword?
- True but a man should
never be controlled
by the sword he uses or he
will lose all his humanity.
- Of course, Father.
- Our ancestors considered
the evil of the sword
was too great so they buried
it inside a stone cavern
before any more trouble
could be brought upon them.
They decreed that none
of their descendants
should learn how to use it and each year
they made sure to worship the
sword to protect the family.
- [Voiceover] Master, the Emperor says
Sword Worship Villa was
planning a rebellion.
The army's here already.
- I should never have
worked for the Emperor.
(shouting)
- Master, Master.
- Kay, I don't have much time.
I know Jue loves you.
But, your martial arts is
derived from a negative power
while Jue's skills are derived
from a positive energy.
For the sake of Jue, promise
me you'll never marry him.
Now hurry and get him outta here.
Get outta here.
- Master.
- Father.
I know where I can find
the Flame Kylin's blood
to awaken the Sword Jue.
And soon, I'll get revenge.
(somber music)
You killed my father.
You destroyed my home
and you even desecrate
the land of my ancestors?
You despicable emperor.
(epic music)
(yelling)
(rumbling)
(struggling)
It truly is an evil sword.
Just what I need.
(exploding)
(thunder booming)
- From the Conquerer's Clan.
If we let him stay here,
it'll just bring us trouble.
- But he killed Conquerer.
That severs any ties he had with the clan.
- Mistress, can you really
bet all our lives on it?
(thunder booming)
- What I'm about to do isn't
anything personal, Wind.
We're trying to avoid any trouble here.
(fighting)
(glass breaking)
- Master Wind, please, spare his life.
(monkey chattering)
That fire monkey.
- Mud Buddha?
- Ah, this is fate.
Master Wind, it seems fate has
brought us together, again.
(thunder booming)
(elephant roaring)
(festive music)
- Great!
- Excuse me.
Excuse me, please.
Excuse me.
- Expert, come with me.
After what we've been through,
I guess I can trust you.
This is all the money we've
managed to save so far.
- What are you going to do with it?
- All of us are orphans.
And, nobody's looking out for us.
So, in order to survive, we have to steal.
I hope
Wood, Bymie, Juno and Yam live good lives.
I heard once, if you keep
heading towards the East,
you'll get to the sea and if you continue
traveling East by boat, after
a month you'll find an island.
The beautiful Peng Li Isle.
When I've saved enough money,
I'm going to take those
kids and go to that island.
(owl hooting)
(fighting)
(creaking)
(horse whinnying)
- [Men] Master.
- Are you certain Wind is in the city?
- Yes, he's at the winery.
- I'm dying to meet him.
The rest of you go to Chao's mansion.
Go!
(crickets chirping)
(horse snorting)
- No, don't open the door.
(suspenseful music)
Oh, Evil Fang.
- So, Wind, do you remember this scar
you gave me 10 years ago?
I'm gonna give it back to you tenfold.
(fighting)
(horse neighing)
(crashing)
(fighting) 54 42
- Someone help us!
(yelling)
- Take everything with us, men!
(horse snorting)
- This is our chance, we
should get some as well.
- Please, I beg you, leave me and my wife
enough to retire.
- Well, I would.
But, you won't live another day
so you won't need retirement money.
- Actually, take it all, I don't mind.
Just don't kill us.
Please help!
- Let's go save 'em.
(suspenseful music)
(fighting)
- Stay still.
- Miss Dream, are you okay?
(fighting)
(crumbling)
(banging)
(fighting) 59 18
- It's Striding Cloud!
- Wind!
(yelling)
(water splashing)
(growling)
- What the?
(squishing)
(gasping)
(water splashing)
(shouting)
- Good sir, thank you for
helping us last night.
If not for you, our whole
city would've been wiped out.
- [Voiceover] Thank you.
- Well sir, I've discussed this with
the Elder Council of the
City and we would like you
to be the captain of our
guard and protect us.
- Captain, so that means
he'll have to arrest us?
- [Yam] But, he still works
for me so he can't arrest us.
(somber music)
- What we witnessed just now,
it seems the devil blood of the Kylin
is taken over Wind's body.
If the demon inside him attacks again,
we will all meet our doom.
- Mud Buddha, please guide
him to the right path.
- I live my life in seclusion
because I can't face the world anymore
and I don't want to see the future.
- But, he saved your life
before, you have to help him.
- He lives to fight fate.
I don't know if there's
anything I can do to help.
- Mud Buddha.
- Wind is now seeing dreams are not real.
Hesitation can bring long regret.
(mellow music)
- [Wind] Where's the Bat Gang?
- You defeated them.
- Did I?
(water splashing)
- You're here!
Please sir, take me as your disciple.
- Captain Xi, what's the matter?
- I'm so pathetic.
I'm a disgrace to the whole city.
I'm just a useless, gutless coward.
- Captain Xi, please, get up first.
- Mr. Long Hair, teach me kung fu.
The man with the Kylin tattoo on his arm
has taken everything from me.
I have to get it back.
- What did you say?
A man with a Kylin tattoo on his arm?
(thunder booming)
- Fish!
- Yeah, it's a big one.
We should catch it.
Hey look, it's gone over there.
- You know what I think?
There's no reason for you
to give up being a captain
just to be a thief.
You should just go, okay.
You can be the captain of the guard
and not have to hang out with us thieves.
- I'm not going to be the captain.
But, all of you should
stop stealing from people.
Let me take care of you all.
We'll find Peng Li Island together, okay.
- That'll be great.
But, the first thing we should
do is help you get better.
You need to get your memory back.
(giggling)
- Hey, Ying, what's with
that look on your face?
What are you laughing at?
- What look on my face?
- Expert, come over here.
(bird squawking)
Look, the little mama bird is hurt.
(birds squawking)
(thunder booming)
(crashing)
(ominous music)
(wind blowing)
(somber music)
- Cloud.
(crashing)
(suspenseful music)
- Help me!
(banging)
(smashing)
(heroic music)
(crashing)
- Hold on tight.
(shouting)
(cheering)
(breaking)
- [Yam] The baby birdies!
(birds chirping)
- [Ying] Are we all ready?
- Get him.
(laughing)
- Wind, how did you and Cloud meet?
- We both had an unhappy childhood.
Our parents were killed by Conquerer.
We both thought the same thing.
For revenge, we first
had to look at our fight.
- My name is Wind.
(somber music)
- Wind, Cloud.
Fate has delivered you both to me.
(laughing)
- [Miss Dream] So, what
was he like before?
- [Wind] Our personalities
were totally different.
(growling)
(shouting)
(whimpering)
(gasping)
- Why did you have to kill them?
- They can't protect themselves like this.
It's a blessing for them to die young
rather than suffer a life of pain.
- The Cloud I've known for all these years
is not the same man now.
- [Miss Dream] Are you going
to tell him about his past?
- No, I've never seen him
smile like this before.
- It's a blessing for him.
He seems happy.
I hope my father can be
happy where he is, too.
- Your father?
- My father left our family to become
the best martial arts expert.
Even when my mother passed away,
he didn't come back.
I hated him for it.
But, when my mother died,
she said she felt no hate or regret.
It changed the way I thought.
In my heart, I know my mother was hoping
I would give my father another chance
and forgive him.
(somber music)
(laughing)
- Revenge is a vicious cycle.
Cloud and I spent half our
lives planning revenge.
But, neither of us knew
revenge doesn't bring peace or joy.
Cloud was known as the God of Death.
I never could've imagined this.
The moment his past is forgotten
marks the beginning of his happiness.
It seems if you leave the anger behind,
a new life begins.
(yelling)
- [Yam] Hey, Mr. Wind, come play with us.
(peaceful music)
- You know, this is the first time
I've seen you happy since I met you.
- We've never really
played like this before.
So, I feel quite happy.
- I'm happy for you, too.
You've finally found your good brother.
- And, someone else who cares for me.
(romantic music)
Dream.
I'll stay with you and wait
for your father's return.
(banging)
- Life is always full of
ups and downs, Master Wind.
At this moment, do you feel as
though life has blessed you?
If you wish for your brother
to feel the same happiness,
you should leave this place immediately.
In your blood runs the spirit of the Kylin
and the Kylin's nemesis
is none other than Cloud.
Wind and Cloud will make you.
Yet, Wind and Cloud will break you.
See, the lives of Wind
and Cloud are intertwined
in life but also with death.
If you both want good lives,
you'll have to live apart from each other
and stay away from the martial arts world.
(pleasant music)
- He died because of you?
If you're brother knew you
lived with such regret,
I'm sure he would forgive you.
- I know he'd forgive me.
I just hope he's found a better place
and can live in happier times.
Will you please have a drink
with me and my brother?
- Sure.
- I'll be leaving soon.
- Why's that?
- I have to find my place in the world.
The promise my brother made me,
if it were you, would you have killed me?
- Yes, because we're
brothers and you asked me to.
Take care.
(ominous music)
- Dream.
- It's Kay.
- Deal with her.
(yelling)
(growling)
- Wind, are you okay?
- Striding Cloud!
(breaking)
- Wind!
Wind, please stop!
It's me, Wind.
- [Shadow] Stop there.
- We can't let her get away.
- You two really think you can stop me?
(foreboding music)
(breaking)
- [Quail] Quickly, get Captain Xi.
- I'm only here for Wind and Cloud.
Get out of the way or die.
(gasping)
- You.
- Shadow.
(fighting)
- You wanna die?
- I'm the captain of the guard.
I have to protect this city.
(ominous music)
Oh, Quail, you fool.
Why on earth didn't you wait for me.
I'm the captain of the guard.
You wanna fight, then fight me.
(gasping)
(rattling)
- The blood of the Flame
Kylin's almost mine.
- Please, Master Jue, help me.
- Look, it's Wind.
- Take him alive.
(epic music)
(fighting)
- How do you like this?
I designed this Kylin
lock especially for you.
- [Juno] We have to help Wind.
- [Wood] Yeah, shoot him.
(breaking)
Yam, watch out!
(yelling)
(somber music)
- It really doesn't matter
if I'm this Striding Cloud
or not.
What's most important right now
is that we're friends.
After I save Wind, I'll come back
and we'll go to Peng Li Isle, okay.
(horse galloping)
(ominous music)
- Master Jue, I'm sorry, I was too slow
and I couldn't stop Wind from killing Kay.
But, as soon as you drink
the Flame Kylin's blood,
not even Nameless can stop you.
Soon, the whole martial arts world
will bow before you.
A blood leech.
- Kay's would was inflicted
by the Kylin Sword.
You think a master swordsmith
is so easily fooled?
Are you thinking about
the Ghost Healer now?
I invited him earlier.
(laughing)
Did you think I wanted to drink the blood
of the Flame Kylin?
I wanted the blood for one thing.
To break the seal binding this sword.
I don't just want the martial arts world,
I want everything under the sky.
(foreboding music)
(shouting)
(epic music)
- Take him alive!
(fighting)
You wanna save him?
I'll trade him for the
Kylin blood in your body.
- Wind.
- Let him go.
- With the Ao ancestors as
witness, I shall release
the Jue Sword from the
Flame Kylin's blood.
I'm not afraid of a
curse on my descendants.
To achieve my revenge, I have no regrets.
(laughing)
Man and sword unite.
- Release my friend now.
- Yes, a great blade
and it will taste your blood.
(epic music)
(fighting)
This sword is truly
the king of all swords.
(fighting)
Nameless.
- Ao Jue.
Turn back from evil.
(ominous music)
(epic music)
That sword is beyond evil.
It would even kill its own master.
Give it up.
- Shut up.
After I kill you I'll be the
greatest fighter in the world.
(fighting)
No one.
No one can kill me.
(shouting)
- The Devil Shadow Technique.
- Ao Jue's makes you a saint
but evil only begets evil.
My Sword of the Heavens will break
the Sword of the Devil.
(awe-inspiring music)
Be careful.
Drop the sword.
(screaming)
If the Jue Sword's demon
soul gets into your body,
you'll become the Kylin Devil.
(shouting)
- The devils of the storms.
Wind and Cloud will fight to the death.
They won't stop until
one or both are slain.
If you wish to save them,
then I suggest you release me.
(fighting)
- Tell me how we can save them.
- Use that sword.
Use the Kylin Sword to
draw out the Kylin Blood
in their bodies.
Only then can they return to normal.
(fighting)
(epic music)
(crumbling)
(shouting)
- Ying, Wind's over here.
Come help me.
- [Ying] If you wanna kill
her, you have to go through me.
(shouting)
(yelling)
- Oh no, Ying!
- I'm just glad you're fine.
- You have to kill Wind now.
He's lost all his humanity.
There's no turning back for him.
- No.
I'll save him, I will.
There has to be a way to save him.
This won't end unless you kill him.
(birds squawking)
- But, Cloud, don't you wanna
find out about your past?
- That day, when Wind
asked me if I were Cloud
would I have been able to kill him,
the old me would've said yes.
But, I've changed.
Now, I'll never give up on a friend.
From now on, I'll only
remember happier days.
- Huh, Cloud, Ying, I can see the island!
(happy music)
(soulful music)