Let's see, is everybody here?
Toucan's late,
surprising no one.
I've called him several times,
but he won't answer his phone.
That Toucan.
We were abundantly clear
about what time to meet up.
He'll make us all late!
Do you think it's possible
he got the date wrong?
I highly doubt that.
He's been counting down the days
like his life depends on it.
[TOUCAN] Loco Moco
is a total tourist thing.
Any pro will tell ya that
poke's the way to go!
[LION] His heart's been
in Hawaii for weeks now.
That's it.
If we have to wait any longer,
we'll miss our flight.
We might as well
just board without him.
[ukulele playing]
Is that...?
♪ Aloha. Oe oe oe! ♪
[whistle blows]
You're so late!
Where have you been?
What kind of employee
can't keep to a schedule?
Oh, that's what
you're all upset about?
That ain't no biggie, my man!
We're on island time;
we can't be stressin' out
about schedules!
Relax! Hang loose!
But we're not there yet.
Ainokea.
You should care!
Look.
Times have changed, old man.
I'm a part of the relaxed
generation, remember?
Sadly, I'm still a victim
of the corporate machine.
Right. Well, if you want
to make it to Hawaii,
you'd better start
caring about schedules.
All right, I'm late because I
went to a daytime hostess club!
[LIZARD]
Didn't need clarification.
[POLAR BEAR AGENT A]
Hmm...
[TOUCAN]
Hmm...?
[POLAR BEAR AGENT A]
Yup, you're good to go.
Ah, good morning to you, sir.
Thanks.
I apologize, but I'm
afraid I can't let you
go out of the country
with this passport.
There has to be some mistake!
I just used it not too long ago,
and everything was fine!
What's up, Lizard?
You in trouble?
They aren't
accepting my passport.
Sorry, what's wrong, exactly?
You tell me.
I'd know Toucan's
handwriting anywhere.
We can't confirm your
identity from this, sir.
Let's go for a swim
as soon as we land!
[LIZARD yells]
Oh, man. I'm here! I made it!
Hawaii!
It's even prettier
than the pictures!
I gotta document everything!
Will you be quiet?
Phew.
It's awfully hot, isn't it?
It's that mane
of yours, Big Cat!
Probably doesn't breathe well.
Yeah, I'm dying.
'Kay, our tour guide is
supposed to be meeting us
around here.
Let's see.
Aloha, dude!
[laughs]
That means "hello,"
in case you guys didn't know.
[CARACAL]
I take it you're here for us?
You betcha!
The name's Nene.
Let me show you around!
You'll be livin' like
locals in no time!
If you're a tour guide, then you
shouldn't be showing up late
to meet your guests.
I would hate for you to
throw our whole itinerary
out of whack!
Bro, bro, bro.
You came to Hawaii to recover
from the daily grind
of the corporate world,
isn't that right?
I suppose that's true, yes.
[NENE] The number-one rule
in this island paradise
is to never let yourself
get bogged down in something
as petty and pointless
as a schedule.
Take it from a native, brah.
It's just not how
we do things here.
[CARACAL] Oh...
I'm not too sure about that.
[LIZARD] Maybe because
of where you heard it first.
Party time!
Hey. I know you. Nene?
Wait a minute.
[gasps] It's Toucky!
Long time no see, old bird!
[TOUCAN, NENE]
Gimme some wing.
And, pound it!
One more. Ay!
[LION]
Oh, is he a friend of yours?
Yeah, from the old neighborhood!
[LION]
Wow, that's wonderful!
What a small world!
But, he just said
he was a native.
Toucan's from Kobe.
Aw, it's no big deal, buddy,
let's not cloud the issue
with facts, all right?
So anyway, what are
you doin' in Hawaii?
Like I told ya before,
I'm a tour guide.
Yeah? When did you start that?
--Today.
--You're kidding me!
[NENE] I'm sure you guys
must be exhausted
from the long flight over here.
I'll show you to your hotel
so you can kick back.
I respect that he's your
friend and all, Toucan,
but do we want him
as our tour guide?
Absolutely not.
That guy is a joke!
Let's just dive in
and expect the worst.
[LION]
Oh, no. If Toucan says that...
Listen up, friends!
Let's all meet back here
after you've had a minute
to put your bags in your rooms.
We've got lots of sights to see!
It's time for your
Hawaiian adventure!
Everybody on the bus!
Check, one, two. Hello?
Okay, good, now let's
go see some landmarks.
Come to think of it, my Uncle
Green Anole lives in Hawaii.
I wonder if we're anywhere
near his house.
Ooh, this Wolf Yakuza
steakhouse looks delicious.
I hope we go there!
Yo!
Here I am on the bus.
Lucky me, right?
I gotta be sure to capture
every last moment!
First stop. Ta-da!
The beach!
Yes. We can see that.
Got any information?
It's a beautiful beach!
You're not much of a tour guide!
This is Waikiki Beach.
It wasn't always
a beach, though.
Apparently, the sand was brought
over from somewhere else.
Ooh, yay, trivia!
Wait, wha--?
That shark's real close.
Shark?!
Let me see!
Hey, didn't you die
in the last episode?
You idiot!
Nobody can kill
the Honey Badger!
Oh, yeah?
Cool, that makes sense.
Know what doesn't make sense?
You're afraid of
a dumb little shark!
I'm way tougher than that thing!
I'll turn you into
fish fry, punk!
[vocalizing]
[SHARK]
Shark!
[HONEY BADGER gasping]
Oh, my god,
Bossman really is easy to kill.
This gag never gets old!
And if you turn your
attention this way,
you'll see... a mountain!
[LIZARD]
Thank you, Captain Obvious.
It's probably famous
for something.
[LIZARD] I assume so, since it's
on the famous landmark tour!
[LION]
According to the literature,
this place is called
Diamond Head.
It got its name a long
time ago because sailors
used to climb it,
thinking the calcite
crystals near the mouth
were diamonds!
Oh, boy, I bet they
were disappointed
when they got there!
Ha! What did they expect?
It's not like there'd be
a bunch of free diamonds
sittin' out in the open.
Wow, this mountain
may not be very tall,
but it's still scary to look
down from the summit.
[HONEY BADGER]
What are you scared of now?
You're still alive?
You are resilient!
That's 'cause I'm
the Honey Badger!
Honey Badger don't care!
Now, what's so scary here?
Oh, I was just steppin'
back from the railing,
talkin' about how I'd hate
to plummet to my death.
You really are a chicken,
Toucan, you know that?
Watch and learn, I'll show
ya how unstoppable
you can be when you're
not afraid of anything!
Check it out!
If I was afraid, could I do
somethin' as awesome as this?
[HONEYGUIDE]
Woohoo!
You're so cool, Bossman!
Yeah, work it!
[HONEY BADGER yells]
[HONEYGUIDE laughs]
What an idiot!
[NENE] Last but not least,
we have this thingy!
Ah, yes, the famous
"rock with a turtle on top."
Behold.
This is King Kamekameha,
who was a lot like
King Kamehameha,
except he was a turtle.
Made in Italy to celebrate the
centennial of Hawaii's discovery
by Captain Cook.
The original statue fell into
the sea on its way over here,
so this one is
actually a recast.
The spear in his left
hand symbolizes peace,
while his right hand is
open to represent Hawaii's
everlasting prosperity.
[LIZARD]
Now you know something?!
And this statue
was modeled after--
This statue was modeled not
after King Kamekameha the First,
but a particularly handsome
turtle hand-selected
by the ruling king at the time!
Crazy, right?
[LION]
Hey, I wanted to say that!
Where did you get so much
energy all of a sudden?
Oh, I'm glad you asked!
I'll explain everything tonight!
What's goin' on dude?
Dude, you're gonna be so rich.
Whoa, really?
Absolutely. Be there.
But I already have plans
with Lizard tonight.
I'll buy the drinks.
Say no more.
I'll meet you in the hotel
lobby right after dinner,
and don't you dare be late.
Roger that, old buddy!
Ah, pinch me,
I must be dreaming!
Free drinks! The best kind!
That's weird.
I just finished a thought.
Isn't this the part where Honey
Badger comes crashing in?
Hey! Where's your friend?
Huh? I checked the
site of his most recent
life-threatening injury,
and he was gone.
But if I know Bossman,
he's probably doing just fine.
[HONEY BADGER yelling]
He's gotta be dead.
That scream was way too long.
Don't be so sure!
He'll shake it right off. Watch!
[NENE chuckling]
[TOUCAN, NENE]
Cheers!
This rules!
Even the free drinks are
way yummier in Hawaii!
That's right,
everything's on me,
so drink as much as you want.
We gotta celebrate
our reunion, after all!
Oh, Nene, where have
you been all these years?
Gimme a highball, wouldja?
Does this mean you're
not mad at me anymore?
What do you mean,
what would I be mad at you for?
[TOUCAN]
You know, back in grade school?
The first lunch period we
had after summer was over?
[TOUCAN] Whoa! This is
from before we left for break!
Ew, gross, the bread's
hard as a rock!
Nene!
I'm not super hungry today.
You want my roll?
I mean, if you're
offering, Toucky, yeah.
It's yours. Say "Ah."
[NENE]
Ah...
[NENE gags]
Oh, yeah, the whole bread thing.
Well, I did have to get dentures
for my front teeth after that,
but it's water under
the bridge, no worries.
Right, it's like it
never even happened.
Cool, cool.
And there was that
other matter, too.
Uh, which one?
[NENE] Don't pretend you
don't remember Bunnie.
Come on, who have
you got the hots for?
What? I can't tell anyone that.
My beak is sealed, I promise.
Trust me, dude.
It's Bunnie.
So then he tells me
he thinks eggplants
are better than cucumbers.
Oh, really?
Hey, what are you
two talking about?
Wanna know something crazy?
Yeah, of course.
Earlier, this silly goose
told me that he's, like,
totally in love with you.
[BUNNIE]
Oh, uh... That's nice.
But I really like Impala. So...
So... so... so...
You said you wouldn't tell
anyone how I felt about her,
but you did.
You told her.
[TOUCAN chuckles]
Um. You're not by chance still
mad about that little slip.
Also under the bridge.
I forgot about it
until just now.
Phew, that's good.
Time heals all
wounds or whatever.
Yo! Another highball!
How 'bout we cut the chit-chat
and get down to business.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Something about me
getting filthy rich.
Remember my suspiciously
detailed rundown
on that turtle statue?
Yeah, of course, it was weird
you actually knew something.
Ha, well, I wouldn't
go that far, but okay.
Prepare to be titillated.
Feast your eyes on this.
[TOUCAN]
Let's see here.
"King Kamekameha's hidden
treasure." What's this?
[NENE]
Exactly what it sounds like.
There's tens of billions
of dollars in riches buried
underneath Iolani Palace
waiting to be claimed.
Hold on.
You saying we can just walk
in and clean the place out
ourselves?
[NENE]
Yup.
So how'd you like
to live a life of luxury
from now on, Toucky?
It would be ridiculous
to come here
and not drink Blue Hawaiians.
I'm so relaxed.
I could do nothing here all day.
I agree.
It's like this sunshine
is driving every ounce
of exhaustion out of my body.
Toucan is missing out.
I wonder what he's doing.
No idea.
I haven't seen him since
he bailed on our plans
last night and disappeared.
Let's not worry about it.
He's enjoying his free time.
Fair enough.
He can take care of himself.
Uh, probably.
With these supplies,
we should be good to go.
Are you sure we need
such hardcore gear?
We're kind of storming
a fortress, bro,
so if anything happens
and we get caught,
we need to be prepared
to defend ourselves.
I guess when you
put it that way...
So the plan is, we meet
at Iolani Palace at midnight,
and then by morning
you'll have more cash
than you know what to do with.
[NENE]
Cut to midnight.
I can already smell
that sweet bread.
We'll be living like
kings in no time flat.
So, what's our first move?
Just watch.
We're gonna walk right
through the front door.
You sure? Sounds risky.
[TOUCAN]
What, with the guards and all.
[NENE chuckling]
Comin' in hot!
[RHINO GUARD A]
Whoa! What's going on?
[RHINO GUARD B]
Huh? Why am I so sleepy?
[NENE]
Nighty, night! Let's go.
[TOUCAN]
Pretty fancy schmancy.
Looks like they spared no
expense on the decorations.
[NENE]
And, jackpot.
Our destiny awaits
just beyond this door.
I'm talking bank accounts with
more commas than you can count.
Treasure in a throne room.
Talk about cliché.
[TOUCAN]
Whew!
Yup, those are some chairs.
Whoa. Pretty nice digs.
Come on.
I know that panel's
around here somewhere.
What the--?!
A secret staircase?!
Quick. We're wasting moonlight.
So lame.
Isn't there an elevator?
Just a little bit further.
[NENE]
And then...
[TOUCAN screams]
I'm just guesstimating here,
but I'm pretty sure we
could both live ten lives
with this haul and still
never run out of gold.
[TOUCAN] Yahoo! Holy crap
I'm quitting my job, like,
yesterday.
Goodbye, office! Woohoo!
Toucky!
Get a load of this shiny statue!
Hm? Yeah, what is it?
Does it look like something
that might be priceless?
Sure does!
Step closer and look!
Yowzah.
I can't imagine how much
that gaudy thing weighs.
Much less the fat stacks
of cash I could get for it.
[NENE]
And, scene.
This got weird.
Did I mention I'm
the only one who knows
about this place?
So, you gigantic pain,
you have no hope
of being rescued down here.
Uh... What do you mean?
[NENE chuckling]
You really think
I would forgive you?
The bird who made my days
as a student a living nightmare
and left me
traumatized for life?
You have to be held accountable,
and I've finally got
my chance for revenge.
When I heard your
company was planning
a business trip to Hawaii,
I became a tour guide just
so I could get close to you!
[chuckling]
Let's take it down a notch.
This is nuts. Calm down.
We can talk about this.
You can't leave me here!
Oh, I'm perfectly
calm right now.
You can have the
treasure, just let me go!
I'm sorry!
[NENE] Who needs treasure when
you can destroy your nemesis!
[laughing]
Toodle-loo!
[TOUCAN screams]
You can't!
You've made your point,
so please let me go!
How about this for an idea!
We'll go to hostess
clubs, on me!
[TOUCAN] You'll regret
walking away from me, Nene!
[NENE]
Beg all you want.
Nothing will cha--[screams]
Wait! What do you
think you're doing?!
What's it look like?
If you're gonna leave
me here to rot...
...then we're both dying in
this stupid treasure room,
you conniving moron!
Say your prayers!
Yeah, baybay!
[NENE screaming]
Huh, so...
Still no word from Toucan?
Where on earth could he be?
He probably decided
to stay in Hawaii
and found some poor local
girl to shack up with.
[RABBIT REPORTER A] Breaking
news regarding the explosion
at Iolani Palace.
Police have apprehended
two suspects, seen here.
[GROUP gasps]
[RABBIT REPORTER A] One of
the alleged arsonists refuses
to talk, but the man known as
Toucan keeps repeating things
like "My dead grandma
was waving at me
from across the river!"
We don't yet know
how any of this might
factor into their crime.
Word is...
We're still getting on the
plane and leaving, right?
Oh, yes.
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Africa High-School Girls!
Hey, didn't your dad just
get back from a work trip
to Hawaii?
Oh, yeah.
I can't believe he left his
darling daughter behind.
I was made for the beach!
I dunno, I'm not sure you're
supposed to take your kids
with you when its business.
Meh. I guess that's true.
Did he at least bring
you back some souvenirs?
Uh-huh. But, like, check it.
Yikes. Not cool.
Where would you even put that?
No idea.
And besides, what's a moai
got to do with Hawaii?
It makes no sense.
Pretty lame gift.
Ugh, jeez.
I just wanna take
a romantic trip.
Enjoy some Hawaiian sunsets.
Lay out on the beach with
my smokin' hot boyfriend.
Perfect!
Or, like, stargazing while
cuddling with a stud.
That sounds great!
Aw, man.
Why aren't there any hunks here?
I would totally pounce
if I saw one.
Don't worry.
I bet we'll both get a
boyfriend at the same time.
You're right!
It'll be so cute
when that happens!
[GORIMI, SHISHIMURA]
A hunk!
Hey, hold on, what's
the meaning of this?
Am I being mugged by students?
Not so fast.
I saw him first, Gorimi,
this guy's my catch!
[GORIMI]
Get your filthy paws off him!
I got here before you did!
That means this
reptile belongs to me!
Ow! Ow, ow.
Stop twisting my body
in directions
it's not supposed to go!
Please, if you're not careful,
you're going to
break my spine
or pull my tail off.
No, seriously,
you're about to rip it off!
[LIZARD screams]
Ow!
[HONEYGUIDE]
Next time on Africa Salaryman.
"Africa Post-Vacation."