[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Africa Fairy Tale.
Little Red Toucan Hood!
[TOUCAN]
Once upon a time,
Toucan was terribly
stressed and got a bald spot.
Ugh, my head is freezing!
I hate this!
Ah, corporate drone.
Perhaps this'll help you.
Ooh, a hood! Yay for me!
And, there!
♪ Now I get to be
Little Red Riding Hood, ♪
♪ 'cept I'm a Toucan! ♪
[PRES. TURTLE] Actually, it's a
loin cloth I got for my 60th,
but whatever makes him happy.
Little Red?
Take this to Granny
for me, would ya?
Come on, can't you
see I'm busy here?
Who's Granny? Jeez.
If you do it, I'll take you
to a host club after work.
Scratch that, Granny's awesome.
Great. I knew I could trust you.
Back in a flash!
Don't be gone too long, now.
I get paid, right?
Keep your receipts.
You got it!
Oh, yes, and you might
run into a ravenous wolf,
so be careful on your way there.
Hang on, what did you just say?
'Kay, so I think I'm supposed
to take a right up here.
[rustling]
[yells]
Yikes! A wolf!
[screams]
I got tired of the
corporate life, so now...
Bang! I'm a hunter!
Where's them wolfs at,
boy, I'mma get 'em!
You scared me!
What in tarnation?
I just stuck the
dern thing back on!
[TOUCAN]
Who cares?
Anyway, what are you doing here?
I reckon that
oughta be obvious.
[TOUCAN] I reckon you'd
be wrong about that.
[LIZARD] I'm on the hunt
for a big bad wolf.
[TOUCAN] 'Kay. Well,
good luck then, pardner.
It's mighty dangerous out here,
so I'll come with ya.
Say thank you, boy.
Yeah, yeah, "thank you, boy."
Now giddy-up, already!
So, turn left up here,
then what do we do?
Rawr, I'm a wolf!
Oo-oo, I'm just me!
Wow, he's hot!
[LIZARD yelling]
[TOUCAN] Okay, well, that's
definitely not the answer.
Maybe it's a left
and then a right?
Ugh, now I'm confused.
--Oh, I see, it's a left!
--[LIZARD] Help me!
Hey, Granny!
How's the hangover?
Huh? Who's Granny?
I brought you your work!
But I took the day off, so...
Eh, just do what I do
when I work from home.
Stay clocked in
the whole weekend!
This isn't fair.
My, Granny, what a big
mouth you have.
Well your mouth is
a lot bigger than mine.
[TOUCAN]
Nuh-uh!
Oh. He's right.
Why's that?
[LION]
Hmm. I'm not sure, either.
Hey, Dad, I brought
you some meat!
You need your nutrients! Here!
[LION chuckles]
You didn't have to do th--
[LIZARD groaning]
[TOUCAN]
Huh. That's weird.
I didn't know lizard necks
could bend that way.
[OL FENNEC FOX]
It's so hot in here!
[OL MOUSE]
I know, right?
Hey, do we still have
that carton of ice cream
in the freezer?
'Sup, babes!
Got any spicy plans
for the summer?
What the--?
Don't do that! You scared me!
[TOUCAN]
Wanna go for a ride in my Lexun?
Like, to the beach, or a
fireworks show by the Nile?
That's right, summer's
almost here!
It's the most anticipated season
for adults and kids alike!
Time to hit the beach!
Watch the fireworks!
Go to the beach!
Enjoy a barbeque!
And don't forget the beach!
And yes, I said it three times!
As the tides rise,
passions and hormones
begin to rise as well!
What's shakin', pretty ladies?
Dig the bathing suits.
Come hang with us!
[OL FENNEC FOX squeaks]
[OL MOUSE]
They're scary!
Aw. Don't be scared, we just
want to have a little fun
with you two!
Yeah, what he said! Relax.
We promise that we're good guys.
Heh-heh.
[TOUCAN]
Stop right there, ruffians!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[CROCODILE]
What's your problem?
[TOUCAN]
I am here!
Wah!
Nailed it!
Hey, screw you, birdbrain!
We ain't done squat!
You ruined our fun!
Now you'll pay!
[TOUCAN]
Awesome flip!
And, punch!
You've done it now,
you pipsqueak!
I'm gonna knock your beak
straight through your--
[CROCODILE]
Whoa! Hang on! Not so fast!
Huh? Why did you stop me?
Look at that thing he's holding!
What do you mean, bro?
I--Oh! That thing!
Whoa. It can't be!
[TOUCAN chuckles]
[BOTH]
It is! It's baked sweet corn!
[TOUCAN chuckling]
You scared them off
with a corn cob?
Jeez, Lizard!
Don't just barge into
somebody's dream sequence!
Ugh. Who cares?
Listen here, Toucan--
No way!
This beach trip is not
open to married people!
And since you had a shotgun
wedding, that's a double-no!
That's not what I wanted to say!
I know you're ready
for summer break.
We've been really
busy here lately.
Ha! You're tellin' me!
I've been workin' overtime
on top of overtime
for as long as I can remember!
I mean, the burnout
is gettin' to me
like you wouldn't
believe, buddy!
If I don't focus on
summer vacation,
this job is gonna destroy
my mental health!
[LIZARD] I'm not sure
how you hit overtime
since you always go home the
second you're scheduled to,
but yes, that must
be very stressful.
Wait, you're leaving
early today!
Ooh! I should go
abroad this year!
Heck yeah!
Maybe I'll find a
couple of cute blondes
and embark on a whirlwind
tropical adventure!
[LIZARD]
Adventure? What are you, five?
[TOUCAN]
Ah, summer!
That magical time of
year when all of your
wildest dreams and
fantasies come true!
I hate to interrupt
your childish reverie,
but I guess I have no choice.
Yeah, what's up?
About summer break...
Uh-huh.
[LIZARD]
It's canceled.
[TOUCAN screams]
How can they do
something so terrible?!
This company is
morally bankrupt!
Bankrupt, I tell you!
This is employee abuse,
no, animal abuse!
I promised my dead granny
I'd take a summer break.
They can't stop me!
Then go to your
granny's grave and say,
"Sorry, Granny, in this economy,
a salaryman doesn't
get a summer break."
But my doctor says
it's medically necessary
to go to the beach
and see the babes!
I see. Well, guess you'll die.
[TOUCAN] Stop actin'
like it's no big deal!
This is the most unspeakable
thing that's ever happened
to any animal of any species
in the entire history
of the planet!
[LIZARD] Worse than
deforestation and extinction?
Okay.
[TOUCAN]
This will not stand!
Time to march into the
President's office and give him
a piece of my mind!
[LIZARD]
So loud...
Monster! Do you want
to become turtle soup?
That doesn't sound
good to me. No.
Then gimme back my break!
Aww.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
We're too busy.
This is exploitation!
The government's gonna
come shut you down!
Well... I can't give
you a summer vacation,
but I'll let you come with me
on my business trip instead.
How's that?
Sweet talk won't
save you, old man.
Where are you goin' anyway?
It's prob'ly someplace stupid
without any beaches
or hot chicks, right?
[PRES. TURTLE]
Hawaii.
Uh.
There's gotta be somethin'
wrong with my ears.
Why did I just hear
the word "Hawaii"?
That's what I said.
I don't tell you this enough,
President Turtle,
but I have so much
respect and admiration
for the way you run
this fine company...
But just a minute ago,
you said you were gonna
make me into turtle soup!
Aw, come on, buddy,
I was just pullin' your leg.
You know how much we like
to joke around the office!
Anybody who would
say somethin' like that
about our amazing President
Turtle would have to be
total and absolute garbage,
which I am not!
No, sir!
[grunts]
Oh, goodness,
that chair's a doozy.
Now then, there are
some conditions.
[TOUCAN]
Conditions?
Yes.
If you want to come with me,
you'll have to make sure
all your work is done first.
Oh, dear, what's wrong?
You sick?
Work's my friend! I love it!
All right, let's get productive!
Hmm. That's good.
Now, if only I could
get my employees
to be this motivated
all the time.
[HIPPO] Oh, great,
did somebody do something
to break the paper shredder?
[OL MOUSE] Aww, rats,
I was really looking forward
to that ice cream!
[LION]
Huh? Oh, crap!
The paper's out!
Someone help me!
[HONEYGUIDE chuckling]
[toilet flushes]
Jeez.
Something wrong?
It's just one of those days.
Oh, that reminds me,
is your tail okay
after that stalker
cut it off earlier?
[LIZARD] Yes, it's much
better now, thanks to you.
Who would use pasta
to force somebody
into a double suicide?
I'm just thankful it
happened before you took
your lunch break, Big Cat.
You're the only
reason I'm still alive.
[LION] Well, I suppose
everything worked out
in the end, didn't it?
[LIZARD]
Yes, yes. That's true.
'Cause I almost pasta way.
Ha, get it?
[LIZARD screaming]
Ah! Are you okay, Lizard?
[LIZARD] Please, Big Cat,
tell me you get it.
I said "pasta way," because it
sounds like "passed away."
It was a good joke, wasn't it?
[grunting]
Um, yes, I get it!
I just didn't laugh, is all.
[HONEYGUIDE chuckles]
[TOUCAN humming]
Hey!
Check out that fella
who's lookin' hella cute.
It's Mr. Toucan in a new suit!
Oh, boy, I sure can't wait
to take off for Hawaii.
[TOUCAN] Ooh! This pattern
makes it even fancier!
...is what a dummy would say!
[HONEYGUIDE] Squeak, squeak.
Squeak, squeak, squeak.
[chuckles]
Causing misfortune brings
me such sweet joy!
I mean, really, when
you're forced to work
for an incompetent buffoon,
you gotta have some kind of
outlet for all
the stress, right?
Well, it's about time
to post a blog update.
[HONEYGUIDE]
Dear Diary.
Today I witnessed 15 incidents
of other people's misfortune.
I don't care if
I can't be happy,
as long as
nobody else is.
[HONEYGUIDE laughing]
[LION]
Who is that?
[TOUCAN]
Ugh.
It's that one guy who
transferred to our department
last month.
He's got quite a reputation
for being nasty.
He likes to trash-talk
our female coworkers
on social media.
And if there's a
male he doesn't like,
he'll fake a photo of that
person having an affair
and then text it to
the poor guy's wife.
[PRES. TURTLE grunting]
Mr. President, sir!
[TOUCAN]
That's it.
Oh?
I didn't think you'd get worked
up about something like this.
[TOUCAN]
Not fair!
Wait, what's not fair?
[TOUCAN]
He'll get what he deserves!
Hey!
[HONEYGUIDE]
Huh?
What's your deal?!
You just went number-two
on my brand-new suit,
ya jerkwad!
Huh?! Hey, coworker!
Nice to meet you!
Gimme your money!
I'm sorry, but I don't
have any money!
If that's true, then let
me see inside your wallet!
[HONEYGUIDE yells]
Hey, Boss, come and help me!
What?!
[roars]
This crazy penguin
just assaulted me, sir!
And I was minding
my own business!
Beat him up!
What did you call me?
What's the matter with you?!
You stupid bird!
I thought I told you
not to ask for my help
unless there's
somethin' in it for me.
Was that too complicated for
you to understand, or what?
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
I won't do it again, I promise!
You graduated from
a top university
and you can't
remember one thing?
I tell ya, if your stupid
head wasn't screwed on...
I know!
You got some honey stuck
in your brain, don't ya?
Lemme stick a straw in
your ear and suck it out!
[HONEYGUIDE]
No! Anything but that!
[HONEY BADGER] Better yet,
I'll cut you into chunks
and make yakitori out of ya!
Is that what you want, huh?
[HONEYGUIDE]
Please, sir, I'm not a chicken!
What am I watching here?
It's looks like workplace
harassment to me.
[HONEY BADGER]
Huh?!
I'm Honey Badger.
He's my subordinate, Honeyguide.
Was he botherin' you guys?
He used my new suit
for toilet paper, so yes.
I ripped it apart
myself, though.
Hm. I see, that's a shame.
Please accept our
humble apology!
How dare you?!
Just wait till my buddy
Big Cat gets a hold of ya.
Nobody messes with me
when this guy's around!
That tough guy act
ain't gonna save ya
from the king of the jungle--
No, thanks. I'd rather not.
What are you talkin' about?
Don't you think you oughta
defend my honor?
I'm your precious subordinate!
[LION]
Yes, but what can I do?
Guess I'll call HR!
[tambourine rattling]
[LIZARD]
Why a tambourine?
[CARACAL]
You called?
It worked!
Do something, would ya?
[CARACAL]
What's the trouble?
[whistle blows]
Hm? Who, me?
Button your jackets
right now, please!
What do you think this is,
a high school?
This guy is useless, Big Cat,
you have to take
care of it for me!
[LION] Please don't pull on
my suit like that, Toucan,
you're going to stretch it out!
[TOUCAN] Hit 'em with
your scary face attack, hurry!
[LION] It's not an attack.
It's just my face.
[HONEY BADGER]
So that's Lion, huh?
Come on! Use your
tapetum to spook 'em!
[NARRATOR]
Let me explain!
The tapetum is a layer of tissue
in the eye that reflects light.
It's because of this layer
that cats can see so well
in the dark.
But remember, kids,
never point a flashlight
into an animal's eyes!
Ha! Now you look really scary!
Were you not listening?
How 'bout that?
I'll bet you're freaked out now.
You want the laser eyes to stop?
Pay me back for my suit!
Cut that out, it hurts.
[HONEY BADGER]
Oh, yeah?
That doesn't scare me at all!
[TOUCAN]
What?! But how?
[HONEY BADGER] You're talkin' to
the Guinness World Record holder
for not bein' afraid of
anything, so suck on that!
They really do have those
for everything, don't they?
Not only that, but he
also bears a striking
resemblance to the famous
Nazca lines in Peru.
I couldn't stand up
to somebody like him!
[TOUCAN]
Wow! That's uncanny!
[LIZARD]
How's this?
[HONEY BADGER]
Eh, not scary.
[PRES. TURTLE]
And this?
[HONEY BADGER]
No way, didn't even flinch!
[TOUCAN]
How's this?
[HONEY BADGER]
That the best you can do?
Figured it out yet, fluff-nuts?
You may be the
king of the jungle,
but this Honey Badger doesn't
give a you-know-what!
I'll use my nails to
slice you to shreds!
Shping!
And then...!
I'll use my fangs to crush
your skull like it's nothin'!
Squawk! Get him, Boss!
He may be an idiot,
but he's useful when I need
some muscle.
Hey, quick question.
Are you not scared of that
huge elephant outside?
Of course not!
Eh which one of you
would win in a fight?
Don't run your beak
off at me, bird boy!
Honey Badger don't care!
That's my whole thing!
[HONEYGUIDE]
Tweet, tweet. Tweet, tweet.
Huh? Tweet, tweet.
Where did my boss go?
He's gone! Tweet tweet!
[HONEY BADGER yelling]
He just rammed straight
into a wild elephant,
which stomped him to death.
Squawk! I'm not surprised!
[TOUCAN]
Now, pay for...
...my...
[TOUCAN]
...suit!
[HONEYGUIDE]
Okay!
[TOUCAN chuckles]
So we managed to
get him to reimburse me
for the suit that he ruined.
[HONEYGUIDE chuckling]
This pasta's nice and slippery!
But he's still just
as insufferable as he was
to start with.
Hey, write him up or something!
Nah, if we make
a big deal out of this,
then the recruiter's gonna
get yelled at for hiring him
in the first place.
[SHISHIMURA]
Africa High-School Girls!
[NARRATOR]
In the wild plains of Africa,
the key to survival is speed.
[SHISHIMURA humming]
[NARRATOR]
Three minutes for makeup.
[SHISHIMURA]
Perfect!
[NARRATOR]
Ten for clothes.
Oh, my god. I'm like, so cute.
Now, off to class!
[munching]
Ooh, a hottie!
What school do you go to?
Carnivore High!
[SHISHIMURA]
Oh, there's another one!
[munching]
I'm dead, aren't I?
[SHISHIMURA]
Three in a row? Lucky me!
Woof. Woof. Don't eat me.
You're such a fast
runner, so why do you
always show up late?
Sorry. I'm just crazy
for cute boys!
Like for real!
[GORIMI]
Africa High-School Girls!
[NARRATOR]
In the wild plains of Africa,
the key to survival is strength.
A hundred push-ups.
An hour of squats.
[NARRATOR]
And breakfast for energy.
[GORIMI]
Off to class!
[NARRATOR] Training on the
way to school is a must.
[GORIMI]
A pull-up bar!
When I see... [grunts]
...one of these... [grunts]
...I can't resist! [grunts]
Woohoo, oo, oo, oo!
Fitness is important,
but this is beginning
to be a big problem.
At least I'll always
pass P.E, right?
[PROF. GIRAFFE]
Please study, Gorimi!
[HONEY BADGER]
Next time! On Africa Salaryman!
"Africa Business Trip."