[ZEBRA A] Back off, jerk.
Quit pushin' me!
[IMPALA A] What'd you say?!
How 'bout you quit pushin' me!
[ZEBRA A]
You wanna go?
[IMPALA A] You better
get off at the next stop.
[ZEBRA A]
Like hell I will, pal!
[IMPALA A] Well, you
can't say I didn't warn ya.
Ha! Now that was exciting!
What a lucky day.
I just love witnessing a fight
first thing in the morning!
And I'm the first
one here again!
Nothing like peace and quiet.
Since the boss man died,
this place is a paradise!
Now, time to start
the day by slacking off!
Whoa. Those are tasteful.
Oh, boss!
I didn't see you there!
Flowers are so nice.
Like Mother Nature's kisses.
Hey, wait.
You said somebody died?
What the hell is that?!
Me dyin' makes you wanna
throw a party, huh?
Hang on, Mr. Honey Badger, sir.
I can explain, see?
The party is to make sure
you're not lonely in heaven.
Isn't that thoughtful of me?
Yeah, except I ain't there!
Besides. I ain't gonna
be lonely when I die.
You'll die too!
[laughing]
[HONEYGUIDE] I thought this
would make you happy.
[HONEY BADGER]
Sure made you happy, didn't it?
Well, you won't make
this mistake again.
You screwed up the wall,
which means I'll be takin'
the cleaning fee
straight outta your salary.
[HONEYGUIDE] Gah! But I spent
so much money putting this
death party together for you!
Not to mention, I had
to pay that penguin back
for goin' number-two
on his suit.
At this rate, I won't
have enough money
to pay for my bills!
And forget about
upgrading my cell phone
like I was planning to!
Oh, why must I suffer?
Because you're a crappy person.
Just go take out a loan!
[BOTH arguing]
They're so loud.
This is an office!
You're not wrong, Toucan.
But I don't think
a full drum set belongs
in the workplace, either.
Why?!
Aw, man.
How am I supposed to
get 300 million yen?
Hey.
Slot machines.
Let's see, which one of these
babies is the luckiest?
[RAT yells]
Huh?
What's the big fuss?
[SLOT MACHINE]
Come try your luck!
Your chances are
one in 3,276,800!
[RAT yelling]
Oh, my god, what do I do?
This is so intense!
Big money, baby!
Help me out!
[SLOT MACHINE]
The Golden Choice!
Am I a man or am I a mouse?
I mean I'm both, I guess.
But, anyway. Whatever I am,
I've come too far
to throw in the towel!
I gotta win big!
This fellow seems to be
having quite a lucky streak.
[RAT panting]
My heart, it's about to explode!
Okay!
Just clear your mind
and concentrate!
Yes! I won!
See that? Look! I did it!
[HONEYGUIDE laughs]
So how big was the jackpot,
if you don't mind me asking?
Well, there's a
guaranteed payout.
It's ten thousand yen!
Cool, right?
That's great, but how much money
are you going to walk away with?
Oh, yeah, that!
Over 200,000!
That's incredible! 200,000, huh?
Maybe I'd better
try my luck here.
Well, that's that.
200,000 yen down the drain.
All of this month's expenses.
I need a loan.
But how do you even
get one of those?
A lot of good it did
me to graduate
from a national university.
Excuse me, but I think
you forgot something!
Interesting.
Welcome, sir!
Are you looking
for some financing?
Yes, that's exactly what I need!
Just 300,000 yen,
for starters!
Uh, I wouldn't call
that "for starters."
One moment, please,
I'll ask him.
Mr. Gnumann!
We have a customer!
Pardon me.
So, how much money?
300K, please.
Yeah, that ain't gonna happen.
30K, then.
Wow, that's quite a jump.
The problem is,
my boss is a monster.
He beats me senseless
every day and takes my money,
so I can't pay my bills!
Plus, he reduced my salary
because of a totally unfair
evaluation!
[GNUMANN]
Well, that is a problem.
[HONEYGUIDE] And today, he said
he was gonna dock my pay
for destruction of property,
can you believe it?
I mean, I did do it, but still!
I graduated from
a national university.
You'd think he'd
overlook it, right?
[GNUMANN]
And you're okay with all this?
[HONEYGUIDE]
No, weren't you listening?
But if I reported him,
he'd fire me.
The guy's made it clear that he
doesn't give a you-know-what!
I don't ask for much.
I'd be happy for the rest of my
life if he would just disappear!
Oh, and 300 million yen
wouldn't be bad, either.
[GNUMANN]
I'd love 300 mil myself.
Finish him.
Huh?
[GNUMANN]
Finish him.
Uh, sorry,
that wasn't quite clear.
[GNUMANN] Take out an insurance
policy on this boss of yours,
and then kill him
so we can collect.
Oh. That makes sense.
[CROW]
A few days later! [squawks]
[HONEYGUIDE] "I built the
bomb just like you told me."
Man, this Gnumann guy is pushy!
[phone ringing]
Yeah? What is it?
[GNUMANN]
The insurance is paid, correct?
Yup, it's all taken care of.
[GNUMANN]
Good.
Now, all you have to do
is go and place the bomb
inside your boss's desk.
I guess it's showtime.
Doo-dee-doo-dee-doo.
I can't wait to blast
that creep to smithereens!
It's a bee.
Whoa! And free honey!
I gotta go find a jar
to put it all in!
[laughs]
Gee, what a lucky break!
Now come to Honeyguide.
[HONEY BADGER]
Hey, you!
Oh, god, he's here!
Only a matter of time.
And hup-a-doodle-doo.
All right, this is the moment
we've all been waiting for.
[HONEYGUIDE chuckles]
Well, Honey Badger.
In a few seconds, your bullying
days will be over for good!
I hope it's worth it to you
in the end, boss man!
Now rest in pieces,
you big meanie!
[HONEYGUIDE]
And, boop!
[screaming]
[HONEYGUIDE]
Got him!
That was a death scream
if I ever heard one!
[TAIL]
Twitch, twitch, twitch, twitch.
Gross!
What is that disgusting thing?
I think it got in
my mouth for a sec!
[HONEY BADGER]
Cut the racket!
[HONEYGUIDE] What?
How is he alive after that?
[LION] Oh, no! Lizard's desk
exploded for no reason!
Those clowns are
always so noisy!
[HONEYGUIDE]
Crap!
Did I really plant the bomb
in the wrong department?
[LION] Ah! Now the apology
dumplings we got
are on fire, too!
[HONEYGUIDE yelling]
Eh. Whatever.
[TOUCAN, LIZARD growl]
[HONEYGUIDE yells]
Drumsticks to the face!
And Lizard on the bass! Yeah!
[CROW squawks] You're halfway
through the episode!
[squawks]
Morning, coworkers!
Hey, Toucan.
Have you read this
month's Comiczine yet?
[TOUCAN]
Lizard.
Comics aren't work-related!
You should read the Daily Afbiz!
Where'd that come from?
Real adults don't waste
their time on manga and anime.
Be a professional, would ya?
I'm ashamed of you.
Wait. You're the one telling
me to act like an adult?
You're doing the same thing!
Take that back!
For busy guys like us,
I suggest this.
Oh. HR!
Ya know, no one called you.
Correct! I was not summoned.
I came here because
I have business with Lion.
Lemme guess, we're makin'
cutbacks and Big Cat
got the axe.
What's that on
your screen there?
Only the best app ever!
It's a free manga reader!
[TOUCAN]
Oh, sweet!
I'll bookmark it on my
phone and start readin'!
I take it you've
already changed your mind
about that whole
responsible adult idea, then.
Excuse me, Lion,
would you please do me a favor?
[LION] If it's about early
retirement, I'm not interested.
Well, somebody's gotta go!
Guess we'll just have
to draw straws, won't we?
[LION]
To see who gets fired?
That's not the reason
I'm here, though.
I want you to join me
at a speed-dating event!
Sorry, but I'm happily married.
Don't get so wrapped
up in the little details!
Just think of it as a favor
to your dear coworker!
But it's a big detail.
Come on, I need you!
These things are
really competitive!
What if there's a fight?
You can't miss that! Let's go!
[LION] But if they're
competing for dates,
then I can't even participate!
What would my wife say?
[HONEY BADGER]
Competing?
Fine. Then all you have
to do is get a divorce!
[LION]
I don't want to!
We gotta go, Lion!
Yikes, it's him!
Oh, you startled me there!
Let's see who can make
it past the most people
before time runs out!
Um, that's not
really how it works.
Oh, well.
I'm not going,
so it doesn't matter.
Somehow, I got
roped into it anyway.
This should be fun!
Get ready to eat my dust!
Welcome, we've already begun.
Please fill out your profile
cards so you can join us.
[LION]
Uh, sure.
He asked me to come and he
hasn't even shown up yet.
Hey, Lion, sorry I'm late!
There wasn't a good
stopping point in my manga,
so I just finished
the whole thing.
Ah! Here's another
new participant!
Please fill this card out for me
if you'd be so kind.
[CARACAL]
You got it!
I don't want to
disappoint anyone today.
So I'll tell them I'm married.
[LION] I can only imagine
what Honey Badger put down.
Awesome's not an occupation!
Is everyone finished?
Excuse me!
Yes, can I help you
with something, sir?
[LION] Would you mind
telling this gentleman
what speed-dating is?
Yes, the shadow-boxing fellow.
I don't think he gets it.
What is he fighting?
Pardon me, sir.
But this is my
first time, as well.
How exactly do we progress
from date to date?
I'll explain the rules.
Each one of our beautiful
female participants
will be seated like so,
which will leave a spot open
for a man to join her.
Each gentleman will
take a vacant seat,
then chat for a little bit while
perusing the profile cards.
And then!
The gentlemen will move
to the next empty seat
until two people find that
they have a mutual attraction,
at which time a couple
will be born!
Now then!
If everyone's ready,
get in there and date!
Right!
So we just keep looking
until we find who we want?
You know what, guys?
I understand now!
Speed-dating is exactly
like conveyor-belt sushi!
That's kind of a problematic
metaphor, but sure.
Hey! No, Honey Badger, wait!
[HONEY BADGER growling]
Honey Badger!
[LION]
Are you all right?
You're frustrated, aren't ya?
Well, get good
before I kick your--
I think you're the only one
who's frustrated around here.
Something just occurred to me.
Is it possible that
this thing was a scam?
[HONEY BADGER grunts]
[LION]
A scam?
[CARACAL]
Yeah, I mean, there's no way in.
[LION]
Good point.
Not just that, but the
women get in for free,
and we had to pay 5,000 yen.
Then there's the job
and salary restrictions.
Not to mention, they're selling
people soap and detergent.
They almost sold
that pot earlier, too.
[LION]
Hmm...
The only beverage they
offer is tap water,
and all the cakes are
extremely dry and tasteless,
to put it lightly.
They can't be that bad
if you keep scarfing them down
like that.
[CARACAL]
And look at that shady egret
who's running the operation.
He's clearly a grifter.
[LION] I've never seen
a species like him in Africa.
[CARACAL]
You know what he thinks we are?
[LION]
Huh?
Leekaducks.
What's that?
[CARACAL] A leek-duck fusion
that doesn't exist in nature.
Rumor has it there's
a secret food plant
that breeds masses
of them for profit.
Even though they're
genetically engineered,
they still have a living
animal soul at the core.
They're dumb, so they're
synonymous with suckers.
Oh! Goodness!
That sounds like
a terrible thing to be!
Yeah, it's bad.
You sure this place is legit?
[CARACAL]
Hear that?
They're talking about
the same thing!
The guys here are so low-level.
Latecomers, poorly educated,
and worse than that,
some of them are
even married, too!
[LION, CARACAL]
Uh...!
Oh, no, that's us!
I mean, I can't introduce a
person like that to my parents!
Huge waste of time, right?
[FENNEC FOX A]
Right.
And if he didn't go
to a top school,
how would we even talk?
We would be way too different.
[HONEYGUIDE] Someone call for
a national university grad?
What can I do for you, sir?
[HONEY BADGER]
Bullseye!
[HONEYGUIDE]
Why?!
That's enough. Let's go.
You're done too? I'm so glad.
Yeah, for what it's worth,
I do appreciate
you tagging along.
See ya.
I'm gonna head back to the
office to read some more manga.
[LION]
Read it at home!
[CROW squawks]
The next day! The next day!
[squawks]
Hey! Thanks for yesterday!
[LION]
Morning.
Kind of a doozy, wasn't it?
So, did you get
some tail, or what?
Not really.
There was this, that,
and the other, so...
Uh, that's a bit vague.
That makes sense.
Too bad you couldn't
even get a seat,
but them's the breaks, right?
[LIZARD]
How did you get all that?
[CARACAL]
I'll never win.
Not with that attitude, bro!
It's fine.
It's good practice.
For what?
[CARACAL] Well, the next one
is a town mixer, I think.
So now I'll be better
prepared for it.
[TOUCAN] Nah, the bar's
a lot higher at one of those.
You're screwed.
Oh, yeah, Toucan!
I brought something for you.
Really? Huh. There's soap
and a little detergent.
Soap, detergent, soap,
detergent, detergent,
soap, soap, detergent.
What the--?
I got swindled
into buying those.
But I'm not gonna use that many.
Let's see here. We got more
soap, more detergent, more soap,
more detergent, even more
soap and detergent,
with a bonus helping of...
oh, great,
more soap, detergent,
soap, detergent,
soap, detergent.
When does it end?!
You want one of these?
[LIZARD]
Hell no!
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Africa High School Girls!
Ugh, this blows.
What's wrong?
You look like you missed
feeding time or something.
I have plenty of
reasons to be bummed.
Like how tragically
single we are.
Yeah, we suck.
[SHISHIMURA] What if we graduate
high school without ever meeting
one cute guy?
It's enough to break your heart!
Letting our sweet
youth pass us by.
What a shame!
For sure! We gotta hunt
down some hotties, quick!
And the fastest way to do
that is to organize a mixer!
In that case...
Let's go find us some boys!
Welp. I saw that coming.
I know!
Huh? What's up?
There'll be tons of
cute guys at a town mixer!
Well yeah,
that's totes obvi, Gorimi,
but only adults can go
to one of those things.
That's no problem.
I betcha with enough makeup
we could fake our way
through it!
Or would you rather turn into
an old maid and die alone?
What? No, that'd be like,
literally the worst.
That's the spirit!
I'll go and sign us up
right away then!
[BOTH chuckle]
Perfect!
We're so mature and so classy!
Yeah, good thing my mom
had all this retro stuff
crammed in the
back of her closet!
Glad you could make it, Lizard.
I'm sorry to drag you along.
Well, you did threaten
to relocate me
to the Alaska branch, so...
Don't be silly.
All I said was that
we have an opening
and you'd be a great fit,
and that I have the power
to make you go at any time.
Talking to HR feels like
negotiating with the yakuza.
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
What a hunk!
I'll find myself a soulmate
this time, wait and see!
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
'Scuse us!
Ooh!
Looks like we're already getting
some attention from the--
[BOTH yell]
You seem friendly.
I'd like to know more about you.
Hey there, handsome,
wanna go get a table
and have a nice chat?
[GORIMI]
Hey, I was talking to him first!
[SHISHIMURA]
Yeah, but I saw him first, so...
[GORIMI]
Who cares? He's mine!
[BOTH arguing]
[LIZARD]
No, don't do that!
My body is not that stretchy!
Oh, hey, maybe it is.
Oh, no, here we go.
Okay, I guess I'm a snake now.
Boing! So flexible.
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Next time on Africa Salaryman:
"Africa Play-by-Play
Commentator."