[JOB HUNTER 5A]
I'm so nervous!
[TOUCAN yawning]
You know, I've been getting up
a little earlier recently.
Oh, that's good.
Do you go for
a run or something?
[TOUCAN]
No way.
I've been spendin' my time
at a local host club.
[LIZARD]
I should've known.
[TOUCAN] It sucks, though,
'cause I can't take a girl out
afterwards if I'm
headin' into work.
[LIZARD] Well, the solution
seems pretty obvious.
Hey, I know!
I can just take her
into the office with me!
That's a unique
date idea, isn't it?
Uniquely stupid.
Just for argument's sake,
what would you two do there?
Oh, my!
What kind of question is that?
Toucan! That disgusting!
Remind me not to go
near your desk anymore!
[JOB HUNTER 5A]
Today's the day!
[TOUCAN] Wow, look at all these
students huntin' for jobs.
Yeah.
I've seen them
all over the place.
It's that time of year, I guess.
That brings back some memories.
Now that you mention it,
our company's conducting
interviews today too, isn't it?
[TOUCAN] Hot damn, these
strawberries are good.
Anyway, is the president
interviewin' people himself,
or what?
Nah, he's not gonna be around.
Apparently, Big Cat is the
one in charge of the operation.
[TOUCAN]
With that face?
He'll scare people away!
[LIZARD] I dunno, he's still
a good conversationalist.
Do you have a favorite candy?
I'm just sayin', I would hate
to walk into a job interview
and see that huge, hairy
carnivore starin' me down.
Your strawberry was good, too.
If it were me, I'd probably
jump out the window!
[chuckling]
[JOB HUNTER 5B screams]
[TOUCAN]
The weather's nice, huh?
[LIZARD]
Heh. Yes, it is.
[TOUCAN]
Oh, no! I'm so late!
I'm a Toucan. Just your
average salaryman! Hehe!
I stayed up too late last night
watching illegal videos.
Ain't I a stinker?
It sucks that I owe money to
three different loan companies,
but my three girlfriends
are covering my expenses
for as long as I need them to.
So it's all good! Hehehe!
Maybe I'll use my bonus to
buy myself a brand new watch!
Ugh, I wish I didn't have to
go to that dumb meeting today.
I'd much rather take the
day off and go to Hawaii!
Hehehe!
Anyway, if anime's
taught me anything,
I'll have a fateful meeting
when I turn this corner!
Just thinkin' about it
makes my heart race!
[grunts]
[TOUCAN grunting]
[choir singing in Japanese]
[LIZARD] Time for our 36th
cost-reduction meeting.
And to all of our board members,
we really appreciate you all
being here with us today.
The goal of this meeting is for
us to cut our annual expenses
by ten million yen, so let's
come up with some ideas
and put them up on the board.
Oh! Lizard! Pick me! Me!
Go ahead, Big Cat.
I noticed that Toucan
isn't here yet.
Have you heard from him?
He sent me a message saying
that he was running late,
but it's Toucan, so I
assume he's not coming.
Oh, is that so?
I don't know.
He was supposed to be at work
a whole three hours ago.
I wonder if he got into some
sort of terrible accident
on the way over, though.
[BISON, OTTER laugh]
[LIZARD]
Trust me, he's fine!
This isn't the first time
he's played hooky, after all.
I mean, the guy would rather
die than sit through a meeting.
I'm sure he'll roll in at
the last minute like usual.
Although I can't overlook
this, I won't fire him.
I'll just dock his pay.
[LIZARD] I suppose it's possible
he got into a fender-bender,
but I'm sure he's not dead.
It's Toucan!
We can't be rid
of him that easily!
[laughing]
I'm really worried.
--Hey, what's that?
--Was there an accident?
[MOB 5B] You don't look
so good. You okay?
[TOUCAN GHOST]
♪ Ahh! ♪
[LIZARD] So, picking up from
where we left off last time,
do we stop replenishing
the Lethal Hamster's seeds?
Or should we find
a less expensive feed?
Are you talking about
those sunflower seeds
in the rooftop garden?
Yeah, can the Lethal Hamster
even get onto the roof?
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
If it can fly or
use the elevator,
it can easily get onto the roof.
If it can fly, you say?
Oh, Mr. Sheep.
It's not a bird,
so obviously it can't fly.
FYI, Owl, we've had
several employees report
that they've seen the
Lethal Hamster flying.
Ridiculous!
And this is a business meeting.
Please keep your tall
tales and cigarette butts
to the smoking room!
--But it's the truth, I--
--I've heard enough.
I've seen the Lethal
Hamster fly before.
--Me too.
--So have I.
Is that so?
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
Fair enough, since there
appears to be heated
disagreement about
the capabilities of
the Lethal Hamster,
it might be prudent to rethink
the location of the feed
for right now.
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
Are those seeds only there
for the Lethal Hamster?
Why are we spending our
company funding on this?
Right, they should be
a snack for employees
and customers instead!
The nameplate says they're
for the Lethal Hamster,
so that's that!
[OWL]
Look. Lizard.
I know you reptiles
are simpletons,
but could you at least try
to think outside the box
once in a while?
Take that back right now!
It's blatant discrimination!
[LION yawns]
[LION]
Still no Toucan.
I wonder if he's okay.
[TOUCAN GOD 5A]
Toucan.
[TOUCAN]
Where am I?
Um, am I dead?
[TOUCAN GOD 5A]
My child.
Huh? Someone talkin' to me?
Oh, that's bright!
[ANGEL 5A]
Flap flap flap.
Welcome, Toucan.
[TOUCAN]
Damn! Who's that handsome devil?
Listen well.
I'm the Almighty God, and you
must heed my holy wisdom.
[TOUCAN]
No thanks.
Baked avocado with cheese
is quite delicious!
[TOUCAN]
That's random.
Oh, and when you store them,
add an onion so they
won't brown as quickly.
[TOUCAN] Thanks, that'll be
real helpful in the afterlife.
[ANGELS]
Flap flap flap...
[TOUCAN GOD 5B]
Toucan, my child.
What is it this time?
My name is God.
[TOUCAN]
Yours too?
[TOUCAN GOD 5B] Coffee and
shortcake are a heavenly combo.
[TOUCAN]
Great, more pointless wisdom.
[TOUCAN GOD 5B] Then again,
sugar with caffeine
is detrimental to your health,
so keep that in mind.
[TOUCAN] That's a weird thing
to tell somebody who's dead,
but thanks, I guess.
[TOUCAN GOD 5C]
Ah, foolish mortal.
It was so pathetic
of you to be killed.
[TOUCAN]
Jeez, turn the light down!
I am the Almighty God.
[TOUCAN]
I don't feel very blessed.
I have descended from
on high to bring you to life
once again.
[TOUCAN]
Whoa, really? Sweet!
I don't think so!
I'm the one who's going
to bring him back to life.
Thou shalt not steal my points!
[TOUCAN]
Wait, what? Points?
[TOUCAN GOD 5B]
You're both wrong.
Those points are
rightfully mine.
After all, I only need
a few more before I get
another chance to
spin the prize wheel.
[TOUCAN] What is this,
some kinda corpse casino?
You two clearly don't
understand the rules.
First-come-first-served,
remember?
[TOUCAN GOD 5A] Well then, let
us hold a meeting to determine
which of us deserves
custody of the carcass.
[TOUCAN GODS]
Sounds good to me!
[TOUCAN GODS chattering]
Man, you'd think gods would
have better things to do.
Enough fighting!
The points belong to me,
and that's the end of it!
And besides, I don't approve
of your hand positions.
They're all wrong!
Mine is classic!
Yeah, well, this one is more
popular with the young people!
Ah. I just love
a good cup of tea.
[TOUCAN GODS arguing]
Turns out gods
have meetings too.
And, of course,
they're a huge waste of time.
Oh, yeah. I guess
I had a meeting today.
Hey! That's right,
all meetings are pointless!
It looks like he's bringing
himself back to life!
I nearly spat out my tea!
No, wait! Come back!
[GIRAFFE 5A]
Hey, look, he's okay!
I'm back! Thank gods!
I have to go in to
the office right now!
What are you saying, sir?
How 'bout you go
to the hospital?
Let go!
You guys don't understand,
there's no time to lose!
I need to get over to
the office immediately!
Now that's real determination!
That guy is a model employee!
[OTTER] I know I should've
brought this up a long time ago.
But those horns
you've got there--
Can't you take them off please?
They scrape the doorframe
every time you walk
through a room!
Think of all of the money
we'd save on repairs!
You've got some nerve!
If you want to be that way,
then let's talk about
your stupidly long torso!
What are you?
Some kind of eel with fur?
Nice compliment,
eels are delicious!
Back me up! C'mon!
You know,
I don't see why anyone would
count sheep to fall asleep
when they could
be counting owls!
I mean, we're far
more intellectual!
I don't know about intellectual,
but you're disgusting for sure.
Your heads turn a full 360!
Ha! Wrong! You buffoon!
It's 270 degrees. So eat that.
Everyone! Calm down!
This is about cost reduction!
Please stay on topic!
No more chit-chat!
You know what?
You're not running a
very productive meeting.
We don't have all
the time in the world
to discuss these
things, you know!
I see. In that case...
Enough of this!
Now, time to clean out
those ears and listen up!
The best way to cut costs
is to stop having meetings!
[GROUP gasps]
Some of you suits make five
to ten million yen per year!
When you crunch the numbers,
how much do you think that
sets us back every hour?!
And this!
Why is every employee
allowed to print
as many documents as they want?
And in full color, no less!
Hmph!
We've had the same
exact meeting 36 times,
and we're still talkin'
about sunflower seeds?
What are we, kindergarteners
in the sandbox?!
And that's not all.
I'm only gettin' started, baby!
The cost of drinks after work
comes to ten thousand yen!
Then we need cab rides!
And hotels when
we miss the train!
[LIZARD] Could you stop using
me for the bad examples, please?
You're a better fit anyway.
These are all paid for by the
company entertainment budget!
We can slash it
and save tons of cash!
I'm not sure if you know this,
but you're bleeding
profusely from your head.
You might want to relax--
I might be hemorrhaging
blood from my skull,
but it's nothing compared
to the way this office
is hemorrhaging
money left and right!
The worst part is,
you think you can reduce costs
by having a meeting
about reducing costs,
which only costs you
more in employee hours!
You've got a head injury.
We need to take you to the
hospital before you die again!
Let's go!
[TOUCAN]
I'm done with the rat race!
You can't take any
of this crap with you
when you bite the big one!
[EMERGENCY BEAR 5B] You have
blood coming out of a lot of
places it shouldn't be!
[TOUCAN]
Shut up!
If I didn't have a concussion,
I wouldn't be spitting
all this truth!
[laughing]
Oh! I know, the obvious
solution to overspending
is reducing employee wages!
If we cut ten people's salaries
by one million yen per year,
then we would be saving
a whole ten million yen!
Lowering our
entertainment costs, huh?
That's not bad.
It makes a lot
of sense, doesn't it?
[OWL]
We completely overlooked that.
[SHEEP]
Silly us!
I guess Toucan's not a total
waste of space, after all.
Doesn't anybody like
my pay-cut idea?
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
[CARACAL]
Snappy suit. Check!
Big smile. Check!
Today's my final interview.
I bet the president'll
be there too!
I took lots of seminars,
practiced interview questions,
and now, I'm an hour
early with time to kill!
I'm ready to go!
There really are a lot of
students here looking
for jobs, though.
I wonder if they all have
their eyes on that same
big company I do.
Well, no matter how
fierce the competition is,
I've worked hard for this,
and I'm not gonna lose!
[LION]
Oh, no.
I forgot my writing utensils.
[CARACAL]
Typical.
[LION]
And my application form.
[CARACAL]
Wow! That's not a good sign.
[LION] Uh-oh. I didn't bring
my cover letter, either.
[CARACAL]
What's wrong with this guy?!
[sighs] Come on!
Be more professional!
[LION] Excuse me, do you
have a pen I could borrow?
Sure. I brought several,
so don't worry about
giving it back.
[LION] Wonderful!
Thank you so much!
[CARACAL] I don't have
time for these amateurs.
Twenty minutes left.
I should head over.
I know my interview strategy,
and I made a good
impression as an intern.
So I have absolutely
nothing to fear.
Unless, of course...
Oh, no, what if I run into
some trouble on the way there?
[TOUCAN] Hey, old man!
Goin' somewhere?
[PRES. TURTLE]
Stop it! That hurts!
Darned kids.
[CROCODILE]
Stupid turtle!
You're frickin' ugly!
[CARACAL]
That poor turtle.
They're assaulting him!
[HYENA] Let me see ya
lay an egg, grandpa!
[PRES. TURTLE]
Ow, that makes no sense!
Listen, I swear
I'll buy you youngsters
anything you want,
just leave me alone!
[HYENA] I don't think
I can crack his shell open,
dude, it's way too thick!
Let's pretend like it's (bleep)
and throw him into traffic!
[TOUCAN] Oh, man, that'd be
such a good prank, let's do it!
[HYENA] Okay, so if we want
it to be just like the game,
then we need to find
a way to make him
stick his head in and
legs inside so he slides
like a hockey puck!
Come on, you old fart,
you better do what we say
if you know what's good for ya!
[TOUCAN]
...we ain't got all day!
[PRES. TURTLE]
I can't do that!
Stop heckling me,
I'm begging you!
[GROUP] Slide for us!
Slide for us! Slide for us!
[laughing]
Cut it out, you brats!
You're wasting my time!
I've got a very important
interview, I'll have you know!
[BOTH groan]
Another mouthy old guy?
You came down the wrong street!
Aw, yeah, this is gonna be good.
Teach him a lesson, dude!
[CARACAL] I'd rather not
resort to violence.
But if I must...
Face me.
[HYENA]
Quit actin' all tough!
[CARACAL yelling]
[HYENA]
"Face me," really?
Who even is this nerd?
That's it, rearrange his face!
Yeah, make that loser pray
for the sweet release of death!
[BOTH grunting]
[CARACAL] Well, at this rate,
I doubt I'll make my interview
in one piece, much less
in a timely manner.
Maybe I'll use my savings
to go to graduate school
and put off job-hunting
for a little while.
Ooh, or better yet,
I could pursue my
childhood dream of becoming
a manga artist!
Ya had enough yet,
stupid pussycat?
[panting]
[LION] Excuse me, but could I
ask you for directions?
[HYENA]
What do you want, you old--
[BOTH scream]
[CROCODILE]
Holy crap! He's really scary!
[HYENA]
We should run!
[TOUCAN]
Don't blame me!
I'm just a sweet,
innocent little kid!
[CROCODILE] Hey wait,
don't leave me all alone
with the big scary lion,
come back!
[LION]
Um, so, can you help me?
[CARACAL]
That really smarts.
[LION]
Oh, hey!
You're that nice gentleman
who lent me a pen earlier,
aren't you?
[LION]
Um, thank you so much again!
What? Oh. Mm-hmm.
Omigod! Look at what time it is!
I'll never make it now.
[LION]
Gosh, are... are you all right?
My, you really came
to my rescue there,
young fellow!
[LION]
What's wrong?
[CARACAL]
I had a job interview today,
but I fought a bunch
of kids instead.
Boo-hoo-hoo, life is suffering.
That sounds like a predicament.
Well, if it's any consolation,
I'd be happy to let you come
work at my office instead.
[CARACAL]
Huh?
[PRES. TURTLE] I'm president of
a company that's housed inside
that wastefully tall skyscraper.
[CARACAL gasps]
[PRES. TURTLE chuckles]
At my firm, you'd
have a chance to make
ten million yen a year,
even in your twenties!
If you work 200 hours
of overtime, that is.
[CARACAL]
What?!
[PRES. TURTLE] And you there
with the scary face.
You're hired too!
[LION]
Really? Thank you, sir!
That's great!
And that's the story
of how I landed this job.
I guess the president's
never been strict
in his hiring practices.
And it sounds like Lion's
always had a scary face.
Indeed I have, and that
was 20 years ago,
before I started growing this
intimidating beard of mine!
The boss hasn't
changed much, though.
He was born old.
Well, in my honest opinion,
this story isn't quite
appropriate for the job fair
for a lot of reasons.
Aw, but we don't have
any more material.
It was heartwarming,
if you ask me.
[TOUCAN]
Twenty years ago, huh?
I used to play all over
this neighborhood as a kid,
and I seem to remember
havin' a lot of fun
with a local
senior citizen, too.
[GROUP laughing]
[TOUCAN] Break his shell,
maybe candy'll come out!
I wonder whatever happened
to that sad, old geezer!
[laughing]
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Africa High-School Girls!
[SHISHIMURA] Nom, nom, nom,
nom, nom, nom! Mmm!
What's wrong?
Why do you look so serious?
'Kay. Don't freak out, but
I think I may have just had
a stroke of, like,
supreme genius!
I'm gonna be rich!
Really? Omigod, you have
to tell me your idea!
Hmm! We could totally
sell yakisoba bread filling
without any bread!
Oh, yeah, everyone
would buy that stuff.
Ya, I know!
Since it's literally
just yakisoba.
[SHISHIMURA]
Right.
[GORIMI] But hey, you know
that pastry that's basically
a banana with bread
wrapped around it?
If you got rid of the bread
and whipped cream,
you could make
bank selling that!
Mmm. I mean yeah, I guess so.
[GORIMI] Yay, I can't wait
to be super rich and stuff!
Um, you do know that's
just a banana, right?
[GORIMI] Um, do you
think we might be...?
[SHISHIMURA]
Don't even finish that sentence!
You were like,
getting ready to call us dumb,
weren't you?
[GORIMI]
No. I was gonna say stupid.
[SHISHIMURA] Dumb is just
another word for stupid, stupid!
But yeah.
I think you might've just
proved we're not the brightest
of the bunch.
[CARACAL]
Next time! On Africa Salaryman!
"Africa! Nasty Coworker!"