[LION screaming]
Gross! Is that a C-word?
Ew, where's the bug spray?
[COCKROACH]
I have a name, you know.
Don't tell me we're out!
I know I put in a supply order!
[COCKROACH]
It's my office now.
[TOUCAN screams]
[TOUCAN] I'll cut you to pieces,
even if I end up
killing myself too!
[COCKROACH] This is a whole new
level of workplace harassment.
Oh, Lizzie, thank
goodness you're here!
[LIZARD]
Hm?
Best buddy!
[COCKROACH]
Resistance is futile.
Everybody knows
cockroaches are unkillable!
We are legion.
[TOUCAN] You gotta snatch 'em
up with your tongue, right now!
No, thanks.
Why not?
You love those things!
Because I am doing
a juice cleanse today.
So we're fighting off
the insect apocalypse
and you're more worried
about your girlish figure?
Juices are full of nutrients
and anti-inflammatory compounds!
Do you poop?
[MEERCAT panting]
[NURSE RABBIT] Um, that's
a lot of sweat, Doctor.
Should we call it off, or...?
[MEERCAT]
No. [panting]
It'll be all right.
The patient's waiting.
[NURSE RABBIT]
But, Doctor!
[MEERCAT]
We can't afford to waste time.
It's best if we go
ahead and start.
Well, here we go, then.
So please open up as wide
as you possibly can,
Mr. Lion, sir!
[LION humming]
This Haagen-Duck
ice cream is so delicious!
Hey, it's that new flavor
they've been advertising!
Looks yummy.
I sure wish I could have
a little taste of that.
No, this is my special treat,
you go get your own!
Aw, but that's not fair!
It's hot outside and
I don't wanna walk.
The sweetest rewards
in life are reserved
for those who've
overcome great hardships.
If you really want something--
[LION grunts]
[roaring]
[TOUCAN]
Mm-hmm.
Oh. That's a cavity.
[LION]
That can't be right.
I brush all the time.
You'd better go to the dentist
before the pain gets any worse.
Nope. Hard pass.
Now what's so terrible
about goin' to the dentist?
[LION]
It's scary, that's all.
Wait, Toucan,
that's my ice cream.
Oh, you're right,
how silly of me.
Say ahh!
[LION yells]
Out of concern for your health,
I'm gonna have to take
this off your hands.
How noble.
All right, fine,
I'll go right now.
Oh, and Toucan?
Please don't eat the flan
in the fridge while I'm gone.
No flan. Sure!
[LION]
This molar's killing me.
[MEERCAT yelps]
I haven't even done anything
yet and he's furious!
Okay, sir, go ahead and
open up real wide for me.
[LION]
Ah...
[MEERCAT]
Um, maybe it's here.
Oh, god, I hope he
doesn't eat me!
Now, if you start to
feel any pain at all,
just raise your hand.
Go to dental school, they said,
it's the safest job
there is, they said.
They never had to reach into
the gaping maw of a carnivore!
[MEERCAT screams]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Please let me go!
I swear I won't do it again!
[MEERCAT]
Oh, god, the pain is unbearable!
[NURSE RABBIT] Would you
please open your mouth?
[LION]
Oh, I'm sorry.
My, that's salty.
Wait, why is it salty?
[MEERCAT] This is it. Everything
tastes better with salt.
This guy's gonna
eat me for sure!
Um, salty?
Well, when you fix cavities,
sometimes there's, uh,
--tooth juice?
--[LION] What? Tooth juice?
That's horrifying!
[MEERCAT]
Um, so?
Yes? What is it now?
[MEERCAT] Could you tell
me if it tasted good?
[LION] It did not, and what kind
of question is that?
You know, I think I see a little
something stuck in your molars.
[NURSE RABBIT] Are you aware
that you're bleeding, Doctor?
[TOUCAN humming]
[MEERCAT] Let me get a
better look at that please.
[LION roars]
[LIZARD] That scream
sure sounds like Big Cat.
Look at that! He did go!
[MEERCAT] I'll be right back
with some medicine for you.
Just sit tight for me, okay?
[TOUCAN]
Big Cat!
Hey.
[LIZARD]
Aw, what a trooper.
Now's my chance!
[humming]
[MEERCAT screams]
Ow, why?
Let me go, it hurts!
[MEERCAT] I suggest you start
brushing more consistently.
If you don't brush twice a day,
every day, tartar will--
--[MEERCAT screams]
--[NURSE RABBIT] Doctor!
[MEERCAT yelling]
If you've got any difficult
confessions to make,
now's the best time.
Toucan! Would you please
stop fooling around?
Dental hygiene
is extremely serious!
[MEERCAT yelling]
[LION]
Not the cheesecake!
[NURSE RABBIT]
Doctor!
[yelling continues]
[LION]
Oh, is that all?
[MEERCAT screams]
[NURSE RABBIT]
Doctor! No!
Doctor? Someone help!
[CROW]
It's the next day!
Good morning,
did everything go well
with your cavity, or...?
Thanks for asking.
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
It turns out I just
had the Lethal Hamster
lodged between a
couple of molars.
[LIZARD]
Ah, that's no big deal.
He fished the little
bugger out, though.
Wow. I'm glad to hear that, man.
[TOUCAN screams]
You've got it all wrong!
I don't need any dental work!
I don't have teeth!
[LIZARD] Tap tap tap tap
tap tap tap tap tap tap.
Hey there, Wallabea.
I'm sorry about the other day,
and I was wondering
if I could make it up
to you with some dinner.
Greetings, corporate drones!
A moment of your time?
Sir!
Oh, sorry, I'm at work.
One second.
Jeez, would it kill ya
to keep it down?
I'm tryin' to talk to my
woman over here, gawd!
[LIZARD growls]
[TOUCAN yells]
Someone stop this madman,
he's outta control!
You think you're
tough now, huh?
What the hell is your problem?!
The president is talking.
Now then, if you're
done slacking...
[LION, LIZARD]
A mascot character?
Yes. I would like the company
to come up with its very own
animal mascot to spice up
our corporate branding.
I think something fun
and colorful like that
would enhance the
Cinema Café project, too,
if you haven't forgotten
about it already.
Isn't that the same
project you mentioned
offhandedly a few
days ago, Big Cat?
I'm sorry, I wasn't
sure if that was actually
happening or not.
Of course it is.
I hope it's been progressing
smoothly so far.
Well, "progressing"
is kind of a strong word.
But, in our defense,
we haven't heard any
other details about it
since the day you
first assigned it to us.
Some information would be nice.
Hm, anyway, the first step is to
rustle up a mascot character
for the company.
All right, good meeting.
See you later.
Typical upper management
move for you.
Okay, how are we going to
put this thing together?
Well I'm probably not
the best person to ask.
I don't know the first
thing about mascots.
Do you have any ideas?
I've seen mascot characters,
but I'm just as
in the dark as you.
Yeah that's what I thought.
Huh?
You say you want to know
about mascot characters, do ya?
[LION]
Are you familiar, Toucan?
Sure, I could lay a
little wisdom on you guys.
Your smug attitude
is infuriating as usual,
but yes, please do.
[LION]
Start at the beginning.
What exactly is a mascot?
Sweet summer child!
Your innocent naivete
is adorable.
I would be more than
happy to educate
and enlighten you morons
in any way that I can.
On second thought,
we've all got phones,
let's just Khookle it.
Hey!
All I wanted to do was help you
two out with your problem!
[LIZARD] I dunno where
you got the idea that this is
only our problem, but whatever,
educate away, Toucan!
It makes no difference
to me, but!
If you really want
to know that badly,
then fine, I guess I will.
Okay, for someone to
qualify as a mascot character,
there are three key
attributes they must possess.
First off, they should have
a powerful message of love
and appreciation for
whatever place they live.
Number two.
They're unique, yet adaptable
to any marketing scheme.
And three, they need
a carefree personality
that's equal-parts lovable
and motivational!
Huh, I never knew mascot
characters were subject
to that kind of scrutiny.
These days, it's pretty
common to only have
one or two of those.
I mean, even big corporations
use company mascots,
so the requirements
can't be that strict.
I guess the president wants
to jump on the bandwagon too.
That said, I think the best
way to get the inside scoop
is for us to meet up
with my mascot friends
and see what they have
to say about the whole thing.
Wow, I didn't know
you had friends
in that industry,
Toucan. That's great!
[TOUCAN] You guys probably
have a few of 'em, too.
Look up some of your
old contacts on Fakebook.
I'm willing to bet at least
one person you know
is a mascot.
Trust me, they're everywhere.
Look at that, I have an
old friend from college
who became a mascot character!
[LIZARD] Ah, and apparently
someone I knew in high school
did the same thing.
[TOUCAN]
Told ya!
Now let's go hit these
guys up for intel!
Oh, yeah, and we're gonna
be discussing everything
over drinks, so remember
to save your receipts!
[LIZARD] He just wants an
excuse to drink on the clock.
[LION, MELONBEAR]
Cheers!
[LION]
I guess old habits die hard.
[MELONBEAR growls]
There's nothin' I like
better than knockin' back
an ice-cold beer!
I have to ask you.
Why do you have a melon
for a head now?
You were a normal bear
back when I knew you.
I'm glad you wanna know!
It's a sad tale, sad enough
to make you cry!
All right, thanks
for the warning.
Tell me everything, then.
Here goes.
After I graduated college,
I was unemployed without
a worry in the world!
Every day, I'd go and sneak
a taste of the local specialty.
Jubari melons! Until...
[MELONBEAR grunting]
It sounds like the universe
was punishing you for stealing.
Another beer please!
The authorities found me
and took me into custody,
so it was either face criminal
charges or become a mascot.
You've been through a lot
in your life, haven't you?
Got that right.
Not to mention, my hometown's
under federal supervision
for some financial
complications,
so that kinda puts a
damper on everything, too.
[LION] I'm not sure
how to respond to that.
But hey, it's not all
doom and gloom for me!
I'm a pretty popular character,
so I get invited to all
kinds of special events
all over the country!
I mean, yeah, it's work,
but basically I just goof
around with kids all day long,
so it's nice and easy!
Lots of people love me.
I'm a local hero!
[LION] I would expect children
to run away from you.
[MELONBEAR]
Let's rekindle our friendship
over a few more
drinks, shall we?
Uh, you'll have to pay
for them, though.
[LION]
Not shy, are we?
--[LIZARD sighs]
--[ice clinking]
[LIZARD]
I'm not so sure about him.
[COW]
Lizard, let's go eat.
[FOX] The school lunch
looks super good today!
Rad!
--[LIZARD] 'Sup, Bunzo.
--[BUNZO] What'd I do?
So would you like to
come and have lunch
with me and my friends today?
[BUNZO] Um, I appreciate
the invite. Really!
But I'm kind of a
slow eater, so I can't.
I'd only slow you guys down.
Just go without me.
But, bro!
[COW] Hurry before
everything sells out!
No, yeah, for sure.
Well, I guess
I'll catch ya later.
[LIZARD] So that guy
became a mascot, huh?
Didn't see that coming.
He mostly kept to himself
back in those--
It's Apple time!
I APPLE-ogize for the wait!
[LIZARD]
What the--?!
Ow...! [groans]
Is that... Is that you, Bunzo?
Ah-ah-ah!
That tired old moniker doesn't
APPLE-y to me anymore!
Because I'm Apple Bunny now!
[LIZARD]
I know it's been a long time,
but I'm already sick of you.
[APPLE BUNNY laughs] Aw, don't
act like such a sour apple!
[LIZARD] Boy, you sure
have changed quite a lot.
A nice compliment like that
makes me happy to the core!
[LIZARD]
Uh, wow, that's positive.
You were the only person
who ever acknowledged
my existence back when
we were in high school.
[LIZARD] I see, you drop
the apple thing
when you're being serious.
[APPLE BUNNY] I hated myself,
so I got plastic surgery
as soon as we graduated.
Surgery?!
I didn't know surgery
could do all that!
[APPLE BUNNY]
That's when I began my new life.
As an apple-tastic mascot!
I'm so happy we got
reAPPLEquainted!
Do you mind if I show you
something apPEELing?
[LIZARD]
Sure, why not?
[APPLE BUNNY] It's trick that
made me popular and stand out
from the bushel!
[LIZARD] I don't know why, but I
have a bad feeling about this.
[APPLE BUNNY]
Ha...!
It's the Apple Splash
Jump, Kersploosh!
You can't just--Ah!
[APPLE BUNNY] Let's go!
This apple's got a strong core!
[PATRONS screaming]
[APPLE BUNNY]
Bukkake.
[LIZARD] I really, really
hope I misheard that.
Hey, waitress, can I get
a refill on everything,
starting with the
most expensive stuff?
Yeah!
Same thing goes for me,
and make it snappy, would ya?
[TOUCAN, PENZABURO sigh]
Overpriced meat
and a nice cigarette.
Can't beat that combo!
[PENZABURO laughs]
You can say that again!
I like your style!
Anyway, you said you
had somethin' you wanted
to talk to me about today?
Oh, yeah, I almost
forgot about that.
I was wondering if
you could tell me how
you mascot characters
are faring these days.
You're really askin' me
the tough questions,
aren't ya?
I assume you're talkin'
about money,
which is the only reason why I'm
doin' this gig to begin with,
which is why I got myself
a cushy job as a mascot
for a hotshot baseball team.
The work's pretty mediocre,
but in this business,
it's all about makin'
that dough, baby.
So do you ever get
a chance to interact
with any of the other mascots?
[PENZABURO] Mm, I mingle with
them every now and then
during fan events with other
teams and stuff like that,
but nah, they're not really
part of my personal life.
This is fascinating.
It sounds like it would be
kinda fun to do what you do.
I wonder if I could get a sweet
gig as a mascot character too.
It's probably a
low-stress deal, huh?
Ah. Surprisingly, there's a
whole lotta stress involved.
Oh, really, what do you mean?
Are you sure you're
ready for this?
[TOUCAN]
Mm-hmm.
Truth is, my
money-grubbing ex-wife
is demanding a
buttload of alimony.
Which means I'm gonna
wind up losin' half
of all the assets I've worked
so friggin' hard to build!
[TOUCAN]
That's not really related.
That damn gold-digger
only cozied up to me
so she could be a
celebrity trophy wife
and reap the
benefits my success!
Oh. That sucks,
why'd you get a divorce?
Oh, cause I cheated on her.
Oh, so it was
entirely your fault.
Yeah, I actually had
three separate affairs,
with her older
sister, her younger sister,
and even her mother.
Are you okay in the head, dude?
I think the stress is really
starting to get to me.
I mean, what's gonna happen
if I take it out on the kids
who come to see my games?
How am I gonna come back
from a scandal like that?
Wait, I thought actin' like
a jerk was your whole thing.
[PENZABURO sighs]
Well, you're half-right.
My fans have always
called me "Heelguin"
because I play such a
mischievous character,
so it would be on-brand.
But if I were ever
to harass a kid in public,
then it would
be curtains for me.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
You can't let anyone see
how crappy you actually are.
What kind of mascot hits
the slots four times a week?
And what's worse, you literally
take candy from babies!
You're right, my
personality is a disease.
You don't have to explain
anything to me, Penzaburo.
Stress really does a
number on the old body,
doesn't it?
Thinkin' about how
stressed I am is gettin' me
even more stressed out.
Hey, now that we're done eating,
why don't we go to
a shady massage parlor?
That sounds good. Yeah!
I'll even falsify the receipt
so my boss thinks it came
from a restaurant!
Hot damn,
what are we waiting for?
Let's go blow off
some steam, buddy!
Gotta love work outings!
The sexy kind!
[PENZABURO]
Here we come, ladies!
Hey, Lizard?
Did you learn anything good
about mascot characters?
Nope. I fully intended
to ask him about it,
but I got so overwhelmed
with all his foolishness,
my brain turned into
applesauce and leaked out
through my ears.
I see, that's too bad.
At this point, I don't feel
like I could even tell you
what a mascot
character is though.
Did you collect
any intel, Toucan?
If I had to sum it up,
I'd say that mascot characters
have a pretty
complicated lifestyle.
Yes. I agree. Ugh.
What'll we tell the president?
Ah, my corporate drones!
I'm glad you're all
in one place!
Hello, sir.
If you're here to ask
about the mascot project...
Mascot? I'm sorry, I haven't
the foggiest idea what you mean.
What?
But, President, you said
you wanted us to create
some kind of character to
represent the company, remember?
Oh, yes, of course.
I've lost all interest.
[LION, LIZARD]
Really?
[PRES. TURTLE] Never mind that!
Our new goal is to organize
some club activities
and team-building games.
When people see that,
they'll think we're
one of those companies
that values its employees!
So this place is doomed, huh?
Oh, well.
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Africa High-school Girls!
Hi! What's up, guys?
Thanks for coming!
[AUDIENCE]
Hello!
Whoa, is something
going on over there?
[GORIMI]
Yeah.
[SHISHIMURA] Hmm.
"Mascot Character Trade Fair."
We should go check it out.
I've always thought mascot
characters were neat.
Really? I'm not super up-to-date
with which ones are popular,
but sure, let's go for it.
[CROWD chattering]
Now, Apple Splash Jump!
Kersploosh!
Huh? What do you want?
Keep movin', punk!
[MELONBEAR]
Rawr! I'll eat you up!
[OBSEQUIOUS RABBIT grunts]
[PENZABURO growls]
I'm sorry, sir!
What? There's no need
to apologize.
It was just an accident, right?
[OBSEQUIOUS RABBIT] Ah!
Thanks, I'll be more careful!
[PENZABURO growls]
[OBSEQUIOUS RABBIT yells]
Hey! No violence allowed!
Don't like it? Fight me!
[APPLE BUNNY]
Juice, anyone?
Kersploosh! Kersploosh!
Kersploosh!
[yelling]
[DEER] Everyone, please
calm down! Security!
Huh. The deer's cute.
I think she's the
best mascot here.
This thing might
not be for kids.
That's it! [yells]
Time to show
these boys and girls
what bear guts look like!
Next Africa Salaryman:
"Africa Job Search."