[CROW caws]
Vacation's over!
[PHONE VOICE]
Five combo! Six combo!
[LIZARD snores]
[LIZARD]
Come on!
G'mornin', Lizard!
Hey.
And I oop!
It's always hard to get outta
vacation mode, huh?
You know they're gonna
make you pay for that.
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
My fake blog needs
to be updated.
[TOUCAN]
"Today my boss got so mad at me!
And all because I
didn't have some stupid
paperwork ready fast enough!
Time for some soul detox.
In other words, a smoothie
and a walnut galette
at my favorite café!
I'll be fine!"
That's a winner!
Gah! Big Cat's giving
us a nasty glare!
Excuse me, you two.
Ah! I screwed up!
Now he's gonna know I've
been goofin' off at work!
I think he already knows that.
[LIZARD, TOUCAN]
Um... Yes? What is it?
Tell me.
Uh, how do you insert
a new cell again?
[LIZARD, TOUCAN] "How do
you insert a cell again?"
Oh, boy, here we go!
That's our Big Cat!
What a goofball.
After every vacation, the guy's
memory does a hard reset!
[LIZARD]
Let's take a look.
Why are you in WordPad?!
And what's a macro?
That's where you use the
Schrödinger equation
from quantum mechanics, right?
No, I'm afraid that's
not what macros are,
or if that's even a real thing.
And what am I?
He broke himself!
I guess we're all
in the same boat then.
[startup sound]
Ah. Well, it's time
to get at it.
Okay, then.
I'd better start on
today's assignments.
[LION]
I don't get it! Gah!
[TOUCAN] Why do you think
we're all such slackers
after vacation?
[LIZARD]
You're a slacker 24/7, Toucan.
I guess after you've been
doing this job for a while,
it takes longer to
get yourself going.
Kinda like my old computer.
[PRES. TURTLE]
Enough of this lazy shoptalk!
Back to work!
[LIZARD] Ow!
I'll report this one day!
Log off your social
media and get busy!
Stay all night! And don't
think you're getting paid!
[TOUCAN] You tell him, boss!
I love this shady company!
Hello, my corporate drones!
Still working hard?
Ah! What happened here?!
A messy desk is bad enough.
But look at all this
trash on the floor!
This isn't a frat house!
Well duh, that's what
the cleaning crew's for.
We need more than that!
What's wrong with you?
Stop that shedding!
I-I'm sorry, sir,
but I can't control it.
The heat is making
it fall right out.
You're molting and balding!
Ugly buzzard.
Say that again.
My soup threat still stands.
You three. Honestly.
Lizard! Stop that!
Don't shed your skin here!
[PRES. TURTLE]
There's got to be a better way.
That's why I purchased
a robot vacuum!
Huh? A bug? Why?
[PRES. TURTLE] This little
fella's got top-of-the-line AI
that responds to my voice!
In other words, it's smarter
and more obedient
than you lot have ever been!
[laughs]
[VACUUM] I'll clean anything
at your request, Master.
Good! Now suck up all
the dirt and garbage in here.
[VACUUM]
Understood.
[LIZARD]
Wow, i-impressive.
[LION]
This is great!
[laughs]
Thank you so much, President!
Eh, it's fine.
It came out of your paychecks,
so you might as well
enjoy it, right? Slobs.
[LIZARD]
Gee, thanks!
Big Cat. Be strong.
[LION]
Let me touch it.
Just the tip!
[LIZARD]
You can't.
And please don't
phrase it like that.
[TOUCAN screams]
What is it?
Turn this thing off!
It's gonna eat me alive! Help!
[VACUUM]
Oversized garbage detected.
Initiating
elimination procedure.
[TOUCAN screams]
Lemme go!
I promise, I'm not garbage!
[VACUUM]
Commencing secondary scan.
Scanning. Scanning. Scanning.
Scan is now complete.
Confirmed.
The target is garbage.
Help me! Please! No!
[VACUUM]
Status update.
The target is double garbage.
[TOUCAN]
Hey, that's not nice!
Ah. It's like that little
doohickey can read my mind.
Money well spent!
[TOUCAN yelling]
This is really going to improve
things around the office.
[TOUCAN] Don't just ignore
a friend in need!
I'm sorry, which friend is that?
[TOUCAN]
Kersplat!
[screams]
What the heck is that?!
I'm gonna die!
[screaming]
[LIZARD]
Don't do it, Big Cat.
[TOUCAN]
I don't wanna die!
[PRES. TURTLE] Aw, rats!
Now look what you did!
Go to your desk!
Go!
Y'know, I don't think
the world's ready
for cleaning robots yet.
Well, I'm buying a new
one out of your salaries.
Could you not?!
[LION sniffing]
What's the matter with Big Cat?
Kinda looks like he's in heat.
Nah. I heard he's been
tryin' to quit smoking. See?
Oh, so he's just
smelling the smoke.
Let's let him agonize in peace.
Whoo, I love blind dates!
The girl who set
it up is a cutie!
[LIZARD]
You know I'm married, right?
[TOUCAN] But just because she's
cute doesn't mean I'll end up
with a looker.
We'll have to leave
that one to fate.
Whatever happens, I'll take it!
[TURACO]
Hello, boys!
There they are.
[TOUCAN growls]
[TOUCAN]
The world!
Stop time!
Gimme a break.
I mean, I didn't expect
the club leader to set us up
with anybody cuter than she is,
but this ain't gonna
work for me.
What, you wanna duel?
Pick a card!
Meh, if you say so.
[TOUCAN]
Eeny, meeny, miney, mo.
Catch a lizard by his toe.
If he hollers, let him go.
Eeny, meeny, miney, mo!
'Kay. Oh, yeah, I can
work with this one.
[TOUCAN]
Time started moving again!
[LIZARD imitating phone]
Ah! Sorry, I gotta take that.
Yeah, what's up?
Right. Right. Uh-huh.
No kidding. Really?
Sorry! Gotta go.
I messed up at work.
I was just so eager
to see you ladies.
Guess I rushed
through some stuff!
And after you set
all this up, too.
My bad!
[TOUCAN] That's how you
ditch a double date!
You are so mean.
Turnin' down a gal without
hurtin' her feelings
is a skill only the greatest
of players can master.
I understand the organizer
didn't want to upstage herself,
but why should me and
Lizard have to look at that
all night long?
So, the club leader
isn't angry with you?
Oh, she is;
she blocked my number.
[LION]
Sensible woman.
[TOUCAN] Ugh! Look, you didn't
see the other chick!
[LION] Well, she's
better off without you.
[TOUCAN humming]
Laundromats are dangerous.
Where'd that come from?
It's so cozy.
Now I won't want
to go in to work.
[TOUCAN]
Pick a filter, and got it.
Trust me, as soon
as this goes viral,
you'll never go to work again.
[LION]
Don't post that!
[PRES. TURTLE humming]
What brings you here today, sir?
[PRES. TURTLE]
Oh, Lion!
Have you heard of these
events they call sports days?
They improve office
communication and efficiency,
which is precisely what
we need around here!
Huh?
[PRES. TURTLE] And you
know I love a passing fad.
That's for sure.
All right, everyone!
Our first company
sports day starts now!
Do your best, corporate drones!
I feel like a show horse.
Nope, you're a show lizard.
And I'm a show bird!
Here's the list of events.
Baobab-eating race,
electric eel tug-of-war,
a hedgehog ball toss.
[TOUCAN] Sweet, sounds
like all the old standbys!
I feel like I'm a schoolboy
again! This is awesome!
Last chance to back out
before I make you losers
eat my dust!
Oh, my goodness,
I forgot to bring a towel...
[PRES. TURTLE] So that's the
kind of worker who benefits
from a sports day!
It turns out, when you
hold a company event
without any alcohol,
employees like Toucan
will turn their energy in a
completely different direction!
Think of the possibilities!
So corporate teambuilding
actually works!
Great!
[LETHAL HAMSTER] From then on,
the salarymen bravely tackled
each event, building up
trust along the way.
[LETHAL HAMSTER] And
after the festival was over,
as they rested beneath
the setting sun,
all three of them were left
with the same question.
[GROUP] Will I get paid
for working on a day off?
[TOUCAN yawns]
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
Hey, what's up, Lethal Hamster?
Oh, what did I do
over the summer?
Let me see here.
I went to a cookout
with my girlfriend.
Then I ran into one of my other
girlfriends while we were there,
so that didn't go too well.
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
[TOUCAN]
Yeah, I know.
Like they say,
pimpin' ain't easy.
[LIZARD]
You could always drop dead.
What about you, little friend?
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
Oh, you're lookin'
for someone to marry, huh?
[LIZARD]
How'd you get that?
Come on, it's so early!
--Not for love!
--What?
Sitting still for a long time
makes my butt fall asleep.
You're flexible, Toucan!
Uh, Toucan?
Whoa! Hey, what's the
big idea? Get off!
You should've pulled the
chair away; that'd be funnier!
So, how are the new employees?
You think they're
settled in yet?
They're fine, I suppose.
[LION]
How's the one from Japan?
[LIZARD]
Ugh, that guy.
[LION] What, is there
a problem with him?
I don't know if I'd call
it a problem, exactly,
it's just that he's, uh...
Go on, you can say it.
[LIZARD] Well, you know
our daily reports?
[LION]
Yes, of course.
[LIZARD] For some reason, he
always completes them in code.
[LION]
He's serious about security!
[LIZARD] And I can't
say I get the whole
dressing-like-a-ninja thing,
but I guess we can let
that slide since he's new.
[LION]
I think it's unprofessional.
Plus, it makes Toucan
act even sillier.
[LION] Is he's dressing
like a ninja, too?
[LIZARD]
No, it's nothing like that.
He does all his paperwork
in Portuguese.
[LION]
Maybe it's a rebellious phase.
[striking]
[LIZARD]
Ow!
Caltrops? What the hell?
That's why you
shouldn't drag your tail.
Oh, and I stabbed the
Lethal Hamster too.
Wow, really turned the tables
on the little rascal, didn't ya?
Listen-- Oh, god!
Is the new guy here yet?
It's noon.
Don't ask me.
[LIZARD] I asked him
to do something in Excel,
and he gave me this.
Wow, really?
Oh, man, he's so freakin' cool!
This is useless. It's going
straight into the shredder.
[TOUCAN]
What?!
No, that's a work
of art, give it here!
It's garbage!
It's awesome!
Garbage!
Oh, he's still not at work?
I'd better call him.
[phone ringing]
Ah! This dude is legendary!
Hang on. Where's that
new Toucan guy at?
[GIRAFFE 8A]
Mm... I'm not sure.
Good grief.
Hmm?
[TOUCAN snoring]
Yeah, I'd say the cutie
on the right is my type.
Hey, baby.
Oh, wow, déjà vu.
[TOUCAN]
Come on, show me your ways!
Ooh, got me again! That hurts!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Yeah, shurikens hurt, bud.
[TOUCAN yelps]
I used to go to MoocDonald's
all the time back in college.
Yup, you don't find
yourself coming in here
as much as an adult.
That's because we
know greasy food is bad.
Yeah, I'm more
careful about that now
than I've ever been.
[CLERK 8A]
We'll see you next time!
[LION]
Oh! You guys are here too, huh?
Somebody's feelin' young.
Even at my age,
sometimes you just have to
chow down on some
yummy junk food!
There's somethin'
magical about it.
You know, I used to work at
a Moocky D's at one point,
but that was ages ago.
Avogado?
We don't have that, sir,
this is Moocdonald's,
not Smooshburger.
[TOUCAN] Do you have to make
everything about you?
[LION]
And it's pronounced avocado.
I've had some pretty
bad part-time jobs, too!
[LION]
Let me go!
I'm a male lion,
we don't hunt anything!
Yeah, same here.
I'm no chicken!
Look at me! I'm a Toucan!
Where's my lawyer?
Let me go!
[LIZARD] Getting arrested
is not a part-time job.
I wish they'd eaten you.
Ay! Lickety-split, forgot
to grab my shi-- Wait.
[screams]
Big Cat's scary
when he's workin' late!
His pupils are huge!
They don't look like
that during the day!
[LIZARD]
Well, it's night.
This should help.
[BOTH scream]
[LION]
Ack. So bright.
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Africa High-School Girls!
[SHISHIMURA sighs]
Oh! Just looking at a cute
guy gets my heart pumping!
Ugh I know, right?
But I wish we could meet
some hotties in person
instead of ogling them on TokTik
all the time, don't you?
Big mood.
Plus, the guys at our
school are so shrimpy.
I want a real hunk of a man!
Yeah!
Enough with the pictures.
I want a boyfriend I can hug
and squeeze and cuddle!
[GORIMI]
What's wrong?
Girl, I think I just
solved our dilemma.
We just have to upload
a super-adorable video
to TokTik.
Then the boys will
slide into our DMs!
That's like the best idea ever!
Okay, let's do it.
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
We love pancakes!
Hashtag foodies!
[laughing]
Omigod, look we're so pretty!
Wow, Shishimura!
We're e-girls now!
[GORIMI]
Gimme bananas!
[SHISHIMURA]
C'mere, zebra boy!
You know what?
Extra's good, but
we're, like, too extra.
Yeah, we overdid it, didn't we?
Let's reshoot.
Uh-huh.