Social media?
Well, in this day and age,
I would consider it
an irreplaceable business tool.
For example, it allows me
to connect with my colleagues
and get their perspective
on work-related issues.
Then, I can improve my
negotiations with my clients.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Hmm. Mm-hmm.
Ah! My kid has that!
Actually, I happened to
peek over her shoulder
while she was checking
her Fakebook the other day,
and boy, did she get angry!
Oh, Fakebook? Duh!
I'm on that thing 24/7!
It's the best way to
meet babes in my area!
If you ask me,
in this industry,
mixers are less about dating
and more about the networking.
In a way, they're part
of the job description.
What? Mixers?
Oh, no, I'm much too
old to get invited
to those things anymore.
But listen to this!
I've noticed that my
precious little princess
has been attending an
awful lot of them recently.
As her father, it's
concerning to say the least!
Huh?
To hook up with
chicks, obviously.
Why else would you go to them?
Mixers are no joke, man!
Oh, no.
I certainly wouldn't
call it earnest.
[BAR PATRONS chattering]
[TOUCAN humming]
I need to get some
kind of gimmick.
Now what should I order?
Oh, that one looks good.
Hey there, Pops. I'll take
a beer, a savory omelet,
ooh, and how 'bout a maxau?
[SEALION BARTENDER]
Comin' up!
Are you listening?
Nah, I usually tune out when you
start whining about work stuff.
Makes my drink taste bad.
But if you cover the bill,
I am all ears.
[LIZARD grunts]
[LIZARD] I was drinking
with some clients recently.
Oh, yeah, and a yakitori
plate with necks,
hearts, and thighs, please.
You got it!
Sorry for the wait,
here's your beer, mister!
[TOUCAN chuckles]
Ah, there we go!
Now that hits the spot!
There's nothin' like
an ice-cold brewski!
I was talking.
Yeah, yeah, back to
your boring work story.
[SQUIRREL] You're all business,
aren't you, Lizard?
[BABOON] Come on,
do something funny for us!
Uh...
[LIZARD]
"Do something funny?"
What am I, a clown
at a birthday party?
I'm terrible at this stuff!
Ugh! But I really
have to make this sale.
Of course.
And here I thought you
gentlemen would never ask!
[LIZARD]
Uh... whoa, whoa...!
[chuckles]
So anyway...
That thing that
happened the other day.
How did it go?
What thing?
Oh, right, that thing!
Needless to say, the whole
evening was a disaster.
Hey, toots, wanna
come drink with me?
What're you havin?
A piss-off margarita?
Sounds gross,
but I'll get you one!
Listen to me!
[TOUCAN]
Hey, magic tricks are okay,
but you picked
the worst one ever.
You gotta be able to whip
somethin' out any second.
And it has to be
super flashy too.
Whip something out?
That seems hard.
That's what she said.
Anyway, I guess I can
show you one trick.
[LIZARD]
Ah, yes, yes, please do!
Check this out!
I made a regular nosebleed into
a delightful water feature!
Gah, get away from me!
What's the matter,
you don't like it?
You're making a huge mess!
Trust me, it's a
real crowd-pleaser.
The lightheadedness is
a serious downside, though.
Please put on a bandage.
[TOUCAN laughs] Look at me,
I'm one of those fancy fountains
with a naked angel in it!
Better yet, just bleed out.
[SEALION BARTENDER]
Come on in!
I didn't know
you two were here.
Great, it's Big Cat.
[LION]
And-a HUP-a-doodle-doo!
Heh.
Look, don't take
this the wrong way,
but it's kinda weird to
drink with a superior,
so if you could just,
you know, get lost.
Could I get a cassis orange?
And a skewer sampler,
too, please.
Are you listening?
[SEALION BARTENDER]
Okay, sorry for the wait, folks!
Here's that yakitori!
[TOUCAN]
Ooh, looks delicious!
Can't wait to chow down!
[LIZARD] Wait.
Isn't that made of chicken?
Toucan!
Beer and yakitori,
it's the perfect combo!
I'm sorry, but a toucan
eating yakitori?
That must be some
form of cannibalism.
Oh, it doesn't offend me.
[LIZARD]
What?
Most chickens have a sense of
humor about this kinda thing.
Like my favorite
manga character says,
this is a dog-eat-dog world.
And chickens eating yakitori
is basically a trope now.
[LIZARD]
I doubt that.
Here's a question, Big Cat.
[LION swallows]
What is it, Toucan?
Do you know any good party
tricks for impressin' clients?
[LION laughs]
Where'd that come from?
[TOUCAN] Lizard the loser
wants to learn somethin'
before he embarrasses
himself again.
[LION]
Ah, I see. How about this?
Fuegeot!
Oh, yeah! Like the car!
One more beer.
[SEALION BARTENDER]
Sure thing!
[LIZARD] That's great,
but their logo is a lion,
so only you can do it.
Do you know any
other good tricks?
Well, let me see here.
Oh, this one's a classic.
[LIZARD]
Tiny rabbits?
[TOUCAN]
Aw, that's adorable!
Let's get a tenderloin
and shoulder over here!
[SEALION BARTENDER]
Gotcha!
I think it would be
more impressive if you got
a real rabbit and swallowed
it all in one bite, though.
That's frowned upon
in a business setting.
But I can do it.
You can?
Ew.
You know...
All this party-trick talk is
taking me back to my days
as a new employee.
Oh, really,
what did you do then?
[LION]
Me? I'm glad you asked.
A few of us would dress up like
pop stars and put on a show.
[SUPERIOR 3A]
Stop that!
And we really gave it 100%, too!
If you want to make
a strong impression,
you should do the same thing.
And it's even better
if you're naked.
Public nudity is a little
more difficult to get away
with these days, though.
I'd probably get
arrested if I did that.
[LION] Ah, I suppose
that's a fair point.
Times sure have changed.
And speaking of time, it's
cherry-blossom-viewing season.
We should get a group
together and go out soon!
You never know,
maybe you'll pick up
party-trick inspiration
from somebody else.
Excellent idea!
We all did a trick
at last year's party.
And I'll never forget it!
Wow, Toucan!
Turns out you're actually
useful sometimes!
I know you're setting
me up to say,
"What do you mean, sometimes?"
but this show's more
original than that.
It's settled!
Let's put together
a flower-viewing party
this weekend!
All right!
Hey, this is the most
stereotypical "anime" moment
we've had so far!
What'd I just say?
This spicy cod roe
latte is... the worst!
And why isn't
Toucan at his desk?
[LIZARD]
You forgot already?
[LION]
Huh?
[LIZARD] He's saving
our flower-viewing spot.
Okay, this is the kind
of thing we have interns for.
Ugh.
I thought the plan was
for all of us to come
save the spot together.
Excuse me.
[screaming]
[CAT 3B]
He's gonna eat us!
[LIZARD]
Shping! Hup!
[LION]
Hup! There we go!
Well, we should
get back to the office!
[LION]
Thanks for your help, Toucan.
[TOUCAN] Am I the only person
in the company who's qualified
to sit?
Hoo boy.
[gulping]
Ah.
Can't believe I gotta
stay here till tomorrow.
But, if I left for five minutes,
some other firm or
a group of college kids
would snatch it up.
I still don't understand
why I had to get stuck
with the grunt work.
Why am I so undervalued?
Because this is a gag anime
and I'm the character
you love to hate?
That's discrimination.
Who do I report this to?
HR? The writers?
So much for my plans to call
in sick and go see a movie.
Lest we forget,
the point of this party
is so Lizard can learn how to
be less of a boring buzzkill.
Why is his lack of personality
my responsibility?
Right, it's not, but I
shouldered the burden anyway.
I really do have the
generosity of a saint.
Wait, saint?
No, more like God, or Buddha.
Whoa, hold on.
Does that mean I'm a god?
No, I'm the God!
Which makes me...
...the world.
[NARRATOR] Eventually,
Toucan stopped thinking.
Wow, time sure flies when
you're achieving enlightenment.
Now that it's dark out,
it's kinda scary.
Gah, who's there?!
Listen, you don't want
to eat a toucan;
we're nothin' but beak,
I promise you!
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
[TOUCAN] Oh, it's just
the Lethal Hamster.
You scared me, little guy.
[TOUCAN] Could you put those
down before you hurt someone?
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
What was that?
You want somethin' to eat?
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
I should have some
drinkin' munchies.
Ah, here we go.
All I got is this dried squid.
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
Why's everyone in this
show such a messy eater?
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
[TOUCAN]
Aw, you want to thank me?
Don't mention it,
that's what gods do, so...
Oh, jeez, you've got
a killer grip, dontcha?
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
[TOUCAN]
Hm?
[gasps]
What the hell?!
That's thoughtful of you,
but a dead toucan
is not what I want for
a thank-you present!
God, that's gross.
I think we should call somebody!
Oh, great.
He's framing me for a murder.
Guess I better stash the stiff.
[gasps]
Oh, man!
In my infinite and
godlike wisdom,
I've just come up
with a brilliant idea!
[chuckling]
[TOUCAN]
That oughta do it!
Hold down the fort, would ya?
As for me...
...the dance floor awaits.
[CLUB music playing]
[CUSTOMER 3A]
How long till Square Twin?
[CUSTOMER 3B]
We should have about an hour.
[TOUCAN] EDM events are
full of thirsty women
who hit on guys like me
left and right.
[NARRATOR]
This is Toucan's opinion.
[TOUCAN] All these guys
are walking trainwrecks.
Just keep your cool, bro!
Don't go after every chick you
see; you gotta be strategic!
[chuckling]
Perhaps it's time to
demonstrate my secret technique!
Toucan Eyes... Activate!
Shping!
[NARRATOR]
For the uninitiated,
"Toucan Eyes," the envy
of men the world over,
can only be attained by reaching
the peak of masculine suavity.
It allows one to spot all women
in the immediate vicinity
who are open to flirtation.
[TOUCAN]
Target identified.
Club Flirting Rule Number One.
Casually get closer so that you
can dance right next to her.
[NARRATOR] Toucan invented
this rule himself.
[TOUCAN] Good. Now we can
move on to Phase Two.
[TOUCAN vocalizing]
--[TOUCAN] Aw, yeah!
--[WALLABEA] Oh, yeah!
This beat is hella sick.
Gets me every time!
Big mood!
They play some really
good jams here!
[BOTH]
Whoo!
[TOUCAN]
Club Flirting Rule Number Two.
Don't let on that you're
there to flirt with her.
[NARRATOR]
Again, he has no basis for this.
[TOUCAN grunting]
[TOUCAN vocalizing]
Oh, my god! Sorry!
I was so into it
that I spilled my drink!
[WALLABEA laughs]
It's fine, really!
Sometimes the music takes over!
It's not even that noticeable,
don't worry about it!
I feel so guilty!
I can't take it!
[TOUCAN]
Club Flirting Rule Number Three.
Become an obligation.
The trick is to do something
that's not crappy enough
to turn her off,
but annoying enough
that she can't ignore you.
[NARRATOR]
If you hadn't guessed,
he invented that one, too.
[TOUCAN] Seriously,
you are such an angel!
But please, let me buy you
one more drink after this song.
It's the least I can do!
[WALLABEA]
Oh, that's okay, really.
[TOUCAN] Come on,
you'd be doing me a favor.
I'll never forgive myself
if I don't fix this!
[WALLABEA] I told you,
it's not that big a deal!
Ah, what the heck?
Fine, you can buy me one more,
but only because
you're so funny.
[TOUCAN] At this point,
you're 70% there.
[NARRATOR] This is conjecture
on Toucan's part.
[BOTH]
Cheers!
[WALLABEA]
Thank you again for the drink.
[laughs]
Oh, you're welcome.
And I'm sorry again
for spilling mine.
[WALLABEA] I told you,
there's no need to apologize!
Ma'am, yes, ma'am!
[WALLABEA laughs]
You're so weird!
[TOUCAN laughs]
My old man always made me salute
whenever I screwed up as a kid.
So, uh, who did you
come here with?
Ugh.
Well, at first, I was here
with a friend of mine,
but she went home
with some random guy.
Yeah, random guys suck.
Can't say I mind, though.
After all,
if she was still here,
then I wouldn't have been
lucky enough to hang out
and have drinks with you!
[WALLABEA]
You're such a smooth talker!
Actually no,
I'm honest to a fault.
Lawyers aren't allowed
to tell lies.
Little-known tidbit for ya.
[WALLABEA]
Oh, really, is that so?
Yeah. Like, someone
was lying today in court,
so I yelled, "objection!"
And, "You're out of order!"
[NARRATOR]
It probably goes without saying,
but every word
of that was a lie.
Wow. Crazy.
[TOUCAN]
Huh? Is she listening?
In case you missed it,
yeah, I'm a lawyer.
So, not only am I honest,
but I'm super trustworthy too.
And filthy-stinkin'-rich.
[WALLABEA]
Uh-huh, that's interesting.
[TOUCAN] Come on!
What else could she want?
I'm sorry, but...
Don't women go nuts for lawyers?
You seem bored.
Eh, that's not really my thing.
Why? Lawyers rule!
Well, a man's profession
doesn't determine
what kind of person he is.
Um, okay.
[WALLABEA] If you think you
can reel me in by telling me
about your cushy job,
it's not going to work.
That's pathetic.
Uh, no. I wasn't.
[WALLABEA] I mean, the fact
that you even brought it up
is a clear indicator you think
I'm either shallow or stupid.
You're speechless now?
Guess I hit the nail
on the head.
You must've pegged me
for the kind of woman
who only cares about money.
Better luck next time, loser!
Bet you spilled your drink on
purpose, didn't you?
Oldest trick in the book!
You just wanted me to
feel responsible for you...
[NARRATOR] As his pride
was reduced to dust
and his very existence
faded into oblivion, eventually,
Toucan stopped thinking.
Oh, my!
The weather's outstanding!
Isn't it, though?
Toucan! Thank you
for securing the spot!
We've brought plenty
of food and beverages!
We're ready to party!
Hey. What's wrong?
Um.. Toucan?
Ugh. All right,
enough playing around--
[LION]
Lizard.
He's dead.
I'm beat!
After all the craziness that
went down at the first club.
I partied my sorrows
away at another one.
Huh?
Sweet, the gang's all here!
I can't wait to check
out the flowers!
Wait... Excuse me?!
Um...
Sorry, but could you please
tell me who passed away?
It's me!
Oh...
Taken long before his time.
We were just acquaintances at
best, but I'll never forget him.
[TOUCAN]
Hey, you're doing it wrong!
Damn, did I really leave such
a weak impression on Big Cat?
Oh, god!
Toucan's dead. That idiot!
[TOUCAN]
Look at Lizard.
He's taking the
news pretty hard!
[LIZARD]
He's gone!
This is such a tragedy.
That moocher owes me money!
[TOUCAN] That's what
you're choked up for?!
I've always wanted
to play one of these.
Now let's bury this bird!
Bye-bye!
[TOUCAN] Is this the
best funeral you jerks
could put together?!
When I am dead, I'm comin'
back to haunt all of you!
It's flower-viewing
season again,
and folks are coming
out in droves today!
The cherry blossoms in
Ueno Park are in full bloom!
What's this?
For some reason,
this group over here
is behaving like
they're at a wake.
Let's go and check in!
What brings you here today?
Our coworker is dead!
[RABBIT REPORTER 3A] Oh, my
gosh, it really is a wake!
I'm so sorry!
Oof.
This whole thing is an
absolute dumpster fire.
[TOUCAN groans]
Toucan was a loudmouth,
but I know I'll miss him!
Yes, I agree.
[gasps]
Like my favorite
manga character says,
this is a dog-eat-dog world.
And chickens eating yakitori
is basically a trope now.
[LIZARD]
That rascal!
He was trying to teach me a
party trick from the beginning!
[TOUCAN]
That's a hell of a stretch!
[crying]
Thank you for your sacrifice.
I read you loud and clear.
You wanted me to feed
your dead body to a bird!
[TOUCAN]
Nope, that's not a thing!
There's a bird right over there!
Hey!
[TOUCAN yells]
Now that I look closer,
you seem a little familiar!
Who, me? No way, man!
Come with me, please!
Whoa, hang on, what's happening?
Colleagues! Listen up!
Toucan told me that
he'd like to be made
into yakitori and
eaten by a bird!
No one said that!
And so today, I will see that
his final wish is granted!
This man, who kind
of resembles our Toucan,
has graciously agreed
to do the honors!
[TOUCAN]
Hey, I never agreed to jack!
[grunts]
[LIZARD]
Go on, don't be shy! Eat!
[WORKERS]
Eat him up! Eat him up!
Eat him up!
[TOUCAN]
Forget it, you psycho!
[LIZARD]
He's running away!
Catch him!
[TOUCAN] Fine, you win!
This is all my fault!
[LIZARD]
I'll kill you!
[TOUCAN] What's with the
classic cartoon outro?
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Africa High-School Girls!
Social media, huh?
That's a stupid question.
I can't live without it duh!
My dad looked over my
shoulder when I was checking
my Fakebook profile
the other day.
Like, totes invasive right?
Ugh, that guy has no concept
of personal boundaries.
It's honestly tragic.
[GORIMI grunting]
Social media?
I know what your
game is, mister.
This is your way of
asking for my contact info.
Omigosh, you media
people are so smooth.
It's like, majorly romantic!
If you insist.
I guess I can add you.
[TOUCAN]
Next time on Africa Salaryman:
"Africa Mascot Characters!"