[PRES. TURTLE]
And so, as we reap the benefits
of the excellent profits
we've seen this year,
we acknowledge that the
company's success is owed
to the daily efforts
of our fine employees.
Ugh.
When bonus time comes around,
the boss never misses an
opportunity to blather on.
And, as the company's
continued growth
is in everyone's best interest,
I expect we'll achieve even
more impressive results
as we move forward.
Bravo! I'm so moved!
You know that won't
double your bonus.
Okay!
I'm gonna be responsible and
put all of that sweet moolah
to good use!
[RABBIT CLERK 11A]
Thanks, enjoy your purchase!
[TOUCAN humming]
[CROW squawks]
It's the next day!
Let me guess,
you're feeling guilty
for wasting your bonus
on video games?
No. They're awesome.
Well then,
what's wrong with you?
I wanted to go to a health
spa for some shady fun,
but then I chickened out!
[LIZARD] Ah, so, the games
were a smart buy.
It's hard to get away with stuff
like that in anime anyway.
I mean, what if somebody
showed this to their kids?
Think of the bad press!
You're right,
that is worth considering.
Wait, what's with that pose?
Please buy the home video!
Don't talk to them!
[LIZARD] Oh, god.
Why am I so far off the ground?
Wow. What a small car.
Oh, dear.
Whoa! That was close.
Oh, look out.
Did you get that
with your bonus?
Oh, hello there, Big Cat.
What'd you blow
your money on, bro?
Paying back loans, of course!
Hey, buddy?
Uh, yes, Toucan?
Use your bonus to treat
us to some Instadram-worthy
sushi, please!
What's Instadram? In-star-dram.
Oh, Star?
I understand what you mean now!
[chuckles]
Sure thing.
I can afford that much!
Woohoo!
How do you turn this
crazy thing off?
Hey, chef!
Two fatty tuna, one tiger
prawn, one sea urchin!
And I'll take a
locust roll, please.
[SUSHI CHEF 11A]
Got it!
Not what I thought.
[CROW]
It's Crow, comin' at ya!
[squawks]
[LIZARD] Tappity tappy tappity
tappy tappity tappy...
Hello, my corporate drones,
time for a barbecue!
You scared me, sir.
A BBQ?
Seems a bit sudden.
Kinda like your entrance.
[LION]
Ahem. I agree.
I assume that you'll
be in attendance, Lizard,
since you enjoy being employed.
[LIZARD] Only safe choice
is to say "yeah."
You're paying for
it though, right?
Indeed. It must happen,
at all costs.
Why are you so determined, sir?
There's a manga
I've been reading.
--Oh!
--That one's an anime now!
Sometimes the characters
have a barbecue,
and it makes me want to
try doing one for myself.
So...
That's a silly reason.
Hey, why am I on there?!
[LION]
So, when will it be?
It's happening this Sunday,
and I expect to see
every one of you there.
Well, great.
It sucks that it's on a Sunday,
but it is free food.
And I'll bring a tent along!
[CROW squawks]
At the barbecue!
[LION]
And there! All finished!
Hey, what's up, newbie?
You coming to the thing?
[dial tone]
[TOUCAN]
Psh.
Where's Crane?
Says he's busy today.
I set up the tent, guys!
Come see, 'kay?
Oh, thanks.
Right on!
The weather's nice today.
That's good.
Yeah, it's perfect.
Stupid new guy.
Flakin' out on us.
There we go.
'Sup, guys?
I'm in my secret hideout.
Do you like it?
Nin-nin! Nin-nin!
I was stoked about
all the feedback I got
on my last vid,
but I got caught.
Not very ninja-like of me,
now was it?
[chuckles]
I'll be sure to try
harder next time, guys,
how 'bout that?
Okay, so check this view.
It's a beautiful day outside!
There's a spot here where
you can have barbecues,
and let me tell you,
it is busy! Dang.
You won't catch
me there, though.
I was supposed to go
to some work thing,
but I blew it off 'cause I'm
a free bird! Heh heh!
Now!
Today I'm gonna try
my hand at bomb-making.
Believe it or not,
I've never made a bomb,
so this'll be interesting.
It looks like the first step
is finding a plastic
toy capsule thingy.
Lemme see.
The veggies are ready!
Thank you, Lizard.
You can set them right there.
Here you go.
You having some trouble?
I can't get the grill to light.
[LIZARD]
Is there any kindling in there?
[LION] Actually, could you
grab some pinecones?
Oh ho ho ho ho!
Cash is the best kindling,
not that you poors
would know that.
First of all,
what the hell, dude?
And second of all,
give me a pay raise!
Don't put your nasty
bugs on top of the grill!
Hey, don't knock it
until you try it, okay?
No way! C'mon, don't you dare
let it touch the pineapple!
Is it hot enough now?
[TOUCAN]
Ugh, I'm gonna puke!
Come on, Big Cat eats them, too.
[TOUCAN]
Huh?
Where'd you get that idea from?
The Li-- (bleep)!
That's a cartoon!
So are we!
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
Nin, nin, nin, nin, nin.
Nin, nin, nin. Nin, nin. There!
Yo!
And just like that,
we have ourselves a bomb.
Next step, we're gonna make a
whole bunch more of these guys!
Now, this one needs a few turns.
[TOUCAN] Can you stop
with the creepy-crawlies?
I mean, what if people
are watchin' the show
while they're tryin'
to eat their lunches?
Well, you shouldn't eat while
watching TV, so uh, good!
Need more heat?
Try it, it tastes
just like shrimp.
Then eat shrimp!
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaking]
[TOUCAN]
Oh, that's fantastic.
It's burned to a crisp.
You torched the bug! Nice!
It wasn't me!
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
[CROW squawks]
Well, back to the grind!
[squawks]
I think that's
everything you missed.
[TOUCAN]
Monday already? No!
It's not fair!
I don't wanna be
just a cog in the...
You say that all the time.
We've heard it.
You should definitely
come to the next barbecue,
new guy.
This whole cookout was my idea,
so why did I barely
get any screen time?
[CROW squawks]
This part's about flyers!
[squawks]
[LION]
Maybe this piece rotates.
Or not. Does it face outward?
The neck is right there.
I think it'll be a little bit
more clear after we do
the next few steps.
[LION] Isn't it supposed to
open out from the chest
like Obtimus Prine?
You gotta twist it.
Look closer at the neck part.
Careful, or you'll break it.
Nothin' else works.
Greetings, my--
[GROUP yells]
Oh, it's just the boss.
Don't scare us like that!
What kind of leader
doesn't strike fear
into the hearts
of his followers?
[LION]
What brings you here, sir?
[PRES. TURTLE] I have a favor
to ask of you three,
not that I'm giving you
any choice in the matter.
Just wait till we're finished
playing with this Transvormer.
[PRES. TURTLE] Ah, this
belligerent side of you
is refreshing.
Anyway. I need you to
distribute something.
The money?
I told you, that's
just for showing off.
Oh, these flyers.
[PRES. TURTLE] Yes, hand them
to people on the street.
Why now, of all times?
The company's reputation's
been in freefall
ever since the news
of my gross indiscretion.
Er, which one?
[PRES. TURTLE]
"Let's Positive!
Our company is of the
positive, by the positive,
for the positive!
A positive company!"
Don't ask questions,
just go hand 'em out would ya?
'Scuse me.
[RABBIT A screams]
--[LION] Here.
--[RABBIT B screams]
--[LION] For you.
--[RABBIT C screams]
Ugh. No one's taking
any of mine. Why?
This time it's not
your scary face.
Nobody wants this lame paper.
I guess not.
By the way, Toucan,
what's that you've got
in your hand there?
Oh, you mean this?
I had all the flyers
bound into a book.
That way I only need one taker!
[LION]
That's so smart!
It's hardcover and everything!
Oh, and if I see a missionary,
I can just swap it out
for their Holy Bible!
[LION]
Oh! Okay?
[TOUCAN] You need to
think of a strategy too.
[LION sighs]
Easier said than done.
You could at least give 'em
a piece of candy with it.
[GIRLS scream]
[LIZARD]
Oh, god, I can't breathe!
Er, excuse me...
Please let me through.
[TOUCAN]
Lizard?
There you two are! I did it!
[LION]
Did what?
[LIZARD] I got rid of half of
them by including bugs!
[LION, TOUCAN]
That's your gimmick?
I bet that all of
them would be gone
if you left out the stag beetle!
Typical hot guy.
[LIZARD] What would be better to
hand people than stag beetles?
[LION]
Maybe something everybody likes.
[TOUCAN] Ooh, how 'bout
Transvormer parts?
[LIZARD]
We're not made of money!
Those are too expensive!
[LIZARD]
Oh, hey, new guy.
[TOUCAN]
Ooh!
[LION]
Sushi!
[TOUCAN]
Man, I love tuna!
[LIZARD]
Well, everyone does like sushi.
[LION]
Let's go get some more!
[LIZARD, TOUCAN]
All right!
[LION]
I'm not paying, though!
Well, why don't we find out
if they're doing a good job?
Hold on, where'd my
corporate drones go?
And what's this thing?
I even sent that
rookie Crane out here
and he's disappeared, too!
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
Not that Crane, dummy.
[sighs]
And look at this mess,
nothing but flyers
and Transvormer pieces
scattered all over the place.
Those good-for-nothings!
Hold on.
Isn't this the same Transvormer
they were fiddling with before?
Maybe this piece rotates.
Or not.
Does it face outward?
You jerks!
Did you forget to
include your poor boss?
Oh, would you
like some too, sir?
Salmon roe, please.
[LIZARD]
One more salmon for me.
[TOUCAN]
Extra-fatty tuna!
[SERVER A]
Coming right up!
Oh, hey, you finished
the Transvormer!
Nice work!
It looks great!
You're so smart, sir!
Oh, you think so?
[chuckling]
Phew, I'm stuffed!
Here, boss!
Ah yes, I always get
tense in my shell area!
Sushi's on you, right?
Of course not; the president
is a total cheapskate.
[PRES. TURTLE]
I got it.
Wow, really?
Yay, free sushi!
Thank you very much, sir!
That's very kind of you.
Well, of course.
It's only natural for
a president to treat
his employees.
I usually hate it when
you flash your money around
like you're better than us,
but if it means I get free food,
then you can flex on us
all you want, baby!
That's enough praise, my boy!
I do appreciate it, though!
Your job is to work
hard for the company,
and my job is taking good
care of my corporate dro--
er, my employees!
[LION]
That makes sense.
[LIZARD] Wait, why stop calling
us corporate drones now?
[PRES. TURTLE] By the way, I
have a new assignment for you.
Of course, I knew there
had to be a catch.
I'm sure you all remember
the Cinema Café project
we discussed a while back.
[TOUCAN]
Oh, yeah, that old thing.
[PRES. TURTLE] Well, there'll be
a competition for it next week.
[GROUP]
What?!
I know it'll be difficult
with so little time left,
but there's always overtime!
Unpaid overtime, of course.
[LION]
We can't finish by next week!
[PRES. TURTLE]
Oh, you'll be fine.
Just pull a presentation
out of your butts!
Do you know what company
we'll be competing against?
Well... Let me see.
Well, just pull it
out of your butt.
Ah. Yes.
Tiger and Leopard, I do believe.
No. Not them.
What is it?
Well, it's just that my
old college classmates
are working at Tiger
and Leopard these days.
That's perfect,
you can call 'em up
and ask 'em to
go easy on us, then!
Uh...
Unfortunately, I think that
would have the opposite effect.
Huh? Why's that?
Well, uh, it's complicated.
Those two guys...
They're probably still
holding a grudge.
[TIGER growls]
How is it? The presentation?
[LEOPARD]
It's flawless. No weaknesses.
We're going to blow those
losers out of the water.
[TIGER sighs]
Looks like we're finally
getting our chance
at revenge, partner.
[LEOPARD] That's right. That
Lion will pay for betraying us.
And with interest,
too, of course.
[LEOPARD, TIGER laughing]
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Africa High School Girls!
[SHISHIMURA]
Y'know, Gorimi,
I've been thinking.
[GORIMI]
Uh-huh?
[SHISHIMURA] The sushi here
is super delicious,
and a lot of the toppings
aren't even seafood!
Yeah, you're right!
I love this place.
There's so much variety!
I've got a great business idea!
[GORIMI]
Like for us?
Yup!
Who better to design a
brand-new line of sushi toppings
than a pair of hip
teenage girls?
I mean we do eat
a lot of sushi, after all.
We'll make millions!
Totally! Wow, you're so smart!
[SHISHIMURA]
No time to lose!
Let's hurry to my house
and start creating!
[GORIMI]
Right behind ya!
Okay! Now let's try out
every ingredient we can get
our hands on!
Got it, chef!
Gorimi?
What's up, girl?
You think this thing is edible?
Maybe. Or maybe not.
Cool, well...
Rock-paper-scissors,
loser eats it.
You're on.
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[SHISHIMURA screams]
Woohoo, yeah!
Omigod.
What kind of creature is this?
I found it near
my house in a ditch.
[LION]
I'm home!
How's my baby girl?
Oh, and you have
a little friend over!
[SHISHIMURA]
Daddy?
Huh? Yes, cupcake?
We worked very hard
and made some sushi
just for you.
Will you please try it?
Oh! Just for me? How sweet!
[SHISHIMURA]
Okay, Daddy, open wide!
[LION]
Ah...
[SHISHIMURA]
Now's my chance!
Eat this abomination, old man!
[LION gags]
[LION grunts]
Girl... Did I kill my dad?
He doesn't look too good.
[SHISHIMURA]
Um... Daddy?
You okay?
Speak to me!
Hello?
Uh-oh.
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI scream]
That's delicious!
[SHISHIMURA, GORIMI]
What?
It's a little off-putting
when you first put it
in your mouth, but it
gets tastier and tastier
the more you chew!
That's right, viewers.
It may look kind of bizarre,
but it's a huge hit!
Customers are flocking
to try this trendy new sushi!
[LION]
Huh! How 'bout that?
It's really taking off, cupcake!
Well, you won't catch
me eating any of it.
[LION]
Next time on Africa Salaryman:
The heartwarming final episode!