[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaking]
Um... That's all you're
eating for lunch, Big Cat?
[LION]
Yes, I'm on a diet.
I got scolded by the higher-ups.
That can affect your evaluation
these days, you know.
[LIZARD]
Oh, I see.
[LION] I'm starting out by
watching my portion sizes.
In that case, I'm sorry for
eating right in front of you
like this.
Oh, it's fine,
I love salad. Really.
[TOUCAN] Aw, man, this
unhealthy food is delicious!
Mmm. It's goin' straight to
my thighs and I don't care!
Hey. Y'know what?
Can I get one more?
Actually, I don't remember you
eating very much to start with.
I didn't, and that's what
makes it so upsetting.
[LION growls]
[LION yells]
As I get older, I keep eating
the same things I always have,
and somehow, every morning
I wake up heavier.
Yeah, totally know
that feel, bro.
Hm? Really?
Sure, it's just like...
[FOX]
Rustle, rustle, wiggle, wiggle.
Who--?
[FOX]
Your girlfriend, silly.
Every morning I somehow
wake up with a new girlfriend.
You just wanted to say that.
You look like you're in
pretty good shape, Lizard.
What do you do to stay so fit?
Ah, well...
Nothing. I couldn't
get fat if I tried.
[TOUCAN]
Yah!
[LIZARD grunts]
Whoa!
My hand just slipped
for some strange reason!
Anyway, that's bull.
You've gotta work out
or something, right?
Fine, I hit the gym on
the way home from work
to make up for sitting
at a desk all day long.
[LION]
A-ha. Lizard's a gym rat!
[LIZARD] A lot of people
lose weight that way.
And I hear that a low-carb
diet is more effective
than counting calories.
[TOUCAN] Oh, yeah,
that's what the ugly old hag
at Reception does.
[LIZARD] Pay attention to your
meals at home, though.
My wife took it upon herself
to replace all my snacks
with fruit!
[LION]
Hm.
There sure are a lot of ways
to improve your health!
[LIZARD]
True.
But if you want my opinion,
sports are the best
weight-loss plan!
Say. Let's have
a run after work!
Toucan, you come too!
Running?
I don't wanna!
You can't make me!
[LION]
That's it!
I bet with you two,
exercising would be lots of fun!
Now I'm feeling motivated!
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
[LION]
Let's do our best!
[LETHAL HAMSTER squeaks]
[LIZARD]
The weather's terrible.
[LION]
Yes, tomorrow, then?
[TOUCAN]
Sounds good.
[LION]
Can I... say something?
Please don't.
[LION]
My daughter's at that age.
She doesn't want to use
the bathtub after me anymore.
[TOUCAN]
Cool, guess we're doing this.
[LION humming]
Bath's open!
Ew, Dad, I'm not going
after you, that's nasty!
Seems like only yesterday
she took baths with me.
You can't really blame her.
I'm sure the tub's full
of hair after you get out.
[LION]
They grow up so fast.
You're lucky that
you even have a family
to be all sad over.
That makes me jealous!
You don't think you'll
ever get married?
Eh.
I want to play the
field a little more.
Plus my current girlfriend
has me on a pretty short leash,
so there's no rush.
And I have plenty of friends
with benefits anyway, so.
[LION] Uh, I think you
should consider treating
your girlfriend better.
The point is,
I envy people with families
for a different reason.
[LION]
Are you listening?
With a family, you have
to fill up the bathtub
so that everyone
can use it, right?
[LION]
Mm-hmm.
But that feels like such
a waste for just one person.
[LION]
Ah! I understand that.
I felt the same way back when
I was a bachelor like you.
The water's still super clean
when I'm done with my bath,
so it seems like a shame
to send it all down the drain,
you know what I mean?
If only I could find
a good use for it.
Let's see here.
You've got water...
and a bird.
I know!
Just cook with it!
I'm sure a toucan broth
would have a delicious flavor,
don't you think?
[TOUCAN]
I'm not eating broth made of me.
Hey, Big Cat and Toucan.
Hey.
[TOUCAN coughing]
You sick? Sounds awful.
That secondhand smoke
is a silent killer, buddy.
Put out your cancer stick before
it blackens all our lungs.
[LIZARD]
But this is the smoking room.
Ugh! My poor plumage!
I'll never be able to get that
nasty cigarette smell out!
Don't listen to him, Lizard.
He's trying to quit smoking,
so he came in here
to catch a whiff.
[LIZARD]
Moron.
So, baths, huh?
My wife really enjoys them,
so we always fill up the tub.
As for the leftovers, though...
There's water and a bird.
Use it for broth.
Old joke. Try somethin' else.
[TOUCAN] Whew, another long
day in the corporate jungle.
Time to fire up the old bathtub!
Here's a tease for my lady-fans!
Oh... oh...!
Lizard and Bigs really
crossed the line today
with all that insensitive
talk about toucan broth.
It was so inappropriate!
I mean, one of
'em's a carnivore!
I should've gone straight
to HR with that.
Hmm...
[TOUCAN]
Ta-da!
I made cabbage rolls
with my bathwater,
and they came out pretty good!
You guys want some?
That's disgusting.
I agree.
Haters.
I need a friend, man.
My remote cohabitation setup
turned out to be a disaster,
and now I'm really
depressed over it!
I'm sorry, remote what?
Remote cohabitation.
It's when you're in a
relationship with someone
who doesn't live with you so
you stay on the phone with them
all day so it feels like you're
doing everything together.
All right, how did
you manage to ruin it?
Here's what went down.
[TOUCAN snoring]
--[phone buzzes]
--[GIRLFRIEND 2A] Hey, Touc.
Touc?
[TOUCAN]
Hmm?
Oh, g'morning, honey.
[GIRLFRIEND 2A]
Good morning.
Morning, babe.
[GIRLFRIEND 2B]
Good morning, Can-Can!
That hot springs getaway
sure was relaxing, huh?
I'd love to soak in
each other's juices again
sometime soon, gorgeous.
[GIRLFRIEND 2A]
What are you talking about?
We've never had a hot
springs getaway together.
Oh, crap!
[GIRLFRIEND 2A] You'd better
explain yourself, mister!
There's another woman,
isn't there?
[GIRLFRIEND 2B]
Um, whose voice is that?
[GIRLFRIEND 2A] I hear you
over there, you little
homewrecking weasel!
I guess he didn't tell you
he had a girlfriend!
[GIRLFRIEND 2B]
Who are you calling a weasel?
I am a rabbit,
thank you very much!
You're the weasel here,
you tramp!
[GIRLFRIEND 2A] For your
information, I am not a weasel.
I happen to be a northern
hairy-nosed wombat, missy!
[GIRLFRIEND 2B]
The hell is that supposed to be?
[arguing continues]
Aw, yeah!
A long-distance catfight,
right here in my living room!
Anyway, I'm totally
traumatized now.
Yeah, I get it. Drop dead.
This must be so hard.
Serves you right.
Hard for the women, I mean.
You jerk!
[LION growling]
Looking busy...
I'm looking busy...
[PRES. TURTLE] Hello there,
my corporate drones!
How are you all today?
Oh, hey, President Turtle!
You need something?
We're pretty busy
over here, so...
You were literally petting
a stack of paper just now.
By the way, I wanted to ask you.
What do you always carry a fat
wad of cash on your head for?
That old thing?
Easy, pride!
I'm so filthy rich.
It's fun to do stupid things
with it and make you poors
feel like trash!
Hey. Who's in the mood
for turtle soup?
As appealing as that may be,
we can't kill the president.
[LION chuckles]
Well?
What can we do for you, sir?
I'm here because I have
a special assignment
for you three.
Special assignment, you say?
Tell me more.
It's very simple.
I would like you gentlemen to
locate the Mokele Mbembe for me.
[TOUCAN]
Moke what now?
It's a mysterious thing.
Wow, thanks, so helpful!
It's a rare and legendary
creature, but real!
[LIZARD] The Mokele Mbembe
is a mysterious cryptid
that is rumored to, but doesn't,
make its home in
Africa near the water.
Theories abound as to
what this being truly is
and how it should be classified.
Is it the last living dinosaur?
An alien lifeform?
A case of mistaken identity?
A mascot character for
(bleep) Village, perhaps?
Eyewitness accounts
are inconclusive,
so the Mokele Mbembe is a UMA,
or "unidentified
mysterious animal."
And why are we searching for it?
Because, well, she's my wife!
[chuckles]
What?! Is that true?
[PRES. TURTLE]
Course not, it's a joke!
[LIZARD]
Lying geezer!
That I am. Now quit your
bellyachin' and say yes already,
before I dock your pay!
[LIZARD] Gah, this has to be
against HR rules in some way!
Gah! As soon as I find
out what number to call,
I'm reporting you
for workplace violence!
Okay, so if this is
a work-related trip,
I'm assuming we're allowed
to expense transportation
and food?
Absolutely.
Up to 100 yen for transportation
and 300 yen for meals.
Total.
[TOUCAN]
Hello, is this Jobfinder?
Yeah, I need to find a new
position starting immediately.
Sure, I'll hold.
[LION]
Well.
We made it to the jungle.
Uh-huh.
So why don't you lead the way?
[grunting]
Hey, why are you pushing me?
You never know what
kinda terrifying predators
we might run into, and you've
got the most fighting potential,
--so get movin'! Go!
--[LION] Fighting potential?
What was it called again?
Moke...
Mo...
Uh, anyway, is there
any particular area
we should look at?
The details are a bit murky.
Says here its current rarity
is comparable to that
of the lethal hamster.
You mean the one that
shows up at the office
wielding carving knives?
That doesn't help us much!
So, in Animal Crossroads,
it'd be tuna.
[LION]
I love that game!
That you get.
Ah!
Look, there's a pond!
I bet it's close by, right?
Wow, that sure is
a good-sized pond!
No animals, though.
Not even one.
[TOUCAN screams]
Did you find it?
Yeah!
I caught a tuna!
And look!
I've never seen one this big!
Ah. Nice catch, Toucan. Slacker!
[TOUCAN yells]
Hey, you two!
I see something!
[TOUCAN]
Just a kappa.
[LION]
Yeah. That's nothing.
[LIZARD]
Kappas are mythical creatures!
If you're going to get
excited about something,
it should be that, not your
dumb little video game!
Yeah, well, I'm only
gettin' paid to worry
about the other thing,
so it's kinda hard to care.
[LION] Hmm. And I want to
get home by sundown,
so can we speed this up?
[LIZARD]
Ugh.
Looks like I'm in the minority.
Let's just see what
this thing has to say.
Excuse me, but could I ask
you a question, please?
Sure! Ask all you want!
[LIZARD] That is not the
voice I was expecting!
Er... You see...
My friends and I are looking
for something called
the Mokele Mbembe.
I don't suppose you've
seen it somewhere?
You mean Mbembe?
Yeah, I can definitely help you!
Wonderful!
Um... In that case...
Where is it now?
I'm not gonna tell you
for free, silly.
Er, fair enough.
We don't have much money,
but maybe we could work out
a payment plan?
Oh, I don't need any money.
[LIZARD]
N-No money...?
I'm afraid to ask...
The only thing I want from
you is for you to introduce me
to a nice man who's my age!
Right, of course you do.
Uh... That's no problem!
How about... him?
[TOUCAN]
Sorry, I was playin' my game.
What's goin' on now?
This one's a real catch.
He looks like a monster
with that big ugly beak.
You're not much to look at
either, ya plate-head!
[TOUCAN]
Uh, rude!
What sort of man
did you have in mind?
Well...
I do have a type.
[LION]
Really? [laughs]
So, what qualities does
Miss Kappa expect
in the ideal boyfriend?
Uh... Let's see.
Hairy all over with
bright red eyes.
Plus a row of sharp spines on
his back in a regular pattern.
[TOUCAN]
Dude, that's a monster!
I know.
Something like that can't be--
Oh. There it is!
Hey. T-Toucan.
Turn around slowly.
[CHUPACABRA growling]
[TOUCAN screams]
[LIZARD]
A chupacabra!
[TOUCAN]
It's hideous!
Kinda looks like
an old man, though.
Wait a minute.
She wants a guy who's hairy
all over with bright red eyes,
doesn't she?
And look, he's got spines on
his back in a regular pattern,
as well!
This person checks
all the boxes!
[TOUCAN]
That's no person!
[CHUPACABRA growling]
Pardon me, sir.
I hate to ask this, but...
Hola.
Is there something
I can do for you?
[LIZARD]
Why the accent?
Say, while I've got you here,
could I ask you
for a small favor?
I would like a companion.
Preferably one with
a high-pitched voice
and a plate on her head.
[LIZARD]
Uh, uh...
[CHUPACABRA]
Muy bien!
I can't thank you three enough.
This beauty's one in a million!
Yeah, I'm really grateful, too!
[CHUPACABRA]
Say, "Te amo!"
[LIZARD]
Right. Now, uh...
Can we get back
to the Mokele Mbembe?
[KAPPA]
Oh, Mbembe?
He's been right over
there this entire time,
licking the sap off that tree.
[MOKELE-MBEMBE]
Shping!
I don't know what I
pictured, but that wasn't it!
Either way, we might
as well capture the thing
so we can go home soon.
Er... Right!
I say we all split up
and corner it!
[LION]
Oh, no, it got away!
--Hey! Stop!
--[LIZARD] Here, boy.
[LIZARD]
Slow down!
[LIZARD, LION panting]
[LIZARD]
So... fast...
[LION]
Whew.
I can't run another step.
[LIZARD]
Hey, Toucan.
I think you dropped your--
[PRES. TURTLE] Ah! I knew you
young fellows could do it!
That'll be all.
You can return to your work now.
Of course, sir, right awa--
[MOKELE-MBEMBE screams]
No! I don't want to!
Listen, you!
Put your clothes on
and clock in!
Telling me you needed sick leave
and then disappearing
to the jungle.
You're nothing but a wage thief!
Get to your desk!
Right now!
[MOKELE-MBEMBE] I'm begging
you, for the love of God,
someone help me!
[yells] If I go back to
the Admin department,
I'm as good as dead!
Do something!
[PRES. TURTLE]
Hush up!
[MOKELE-MBEMBE yelling]
[MOKELE-MBEMBE]
Please, I belong in the wild!
I guess he was
an escaped employee.
Things must be brutal in Admin.
Makes you wonder what kind of
shady crap this company's into.
[LION, LIZARD, TOUCAN]
Ah, yes, hello?
Is this Jobfinder?
I need a new position,
starting immediately.
[SHISHIMURA]
Africa High-School Girls!
[SHISHIMURA snoring]
--[phone rings]
--[SHISHIMURA screams]
Oh, no!
I forgot to silence
my phone before class!
The teacher's
gonna confiscate it!
[GORIMI grunting]
[PROF. GIRAFFE]
Gorita? What's wrong?
Do you have a problem?
[GORIMI] Now's your chance
to hide your phone. Wink!
[SHISHIMURA] Wow, Gorimi,
you're a true friend!
[PROF. GIRAFFE] Oh, and give
me your phone, Shishimura.
[GORIMI]
Africa High-School Girls!
[SHISHIMURA slurping]
Okay, here's the tea, Gorimi.
Oh, yeah?
What happened?
Well, I went to take
a bath, but turns out,
like, my dad's fur was in it.
So I drained it out.
[GORIMI]
Mm-hmm.
And then he
totally flipped over it!
"We don't waste perfectly
clean bathwater here,
young lady!"
Crazy, right?
Totes! That was
super uncalled for!
Yeah, I knew you'd think so.
I can relate.
Mine did something
dumb yesterday.
[SHISHIMURA]
Yours, too?
What did he do, tell me?
--So, at dinner...
--Yeah?
...my dad ate my second helping!
--No!
--Sucks, right?
--For sure!
--It was so unfair.
I only got 300 bowls' worth!
Hold on. What? 300? Wow.
Uh, I mean, sounds like both
of our dads kinda suck.
[LION sneezes]
Hey you gettin' a cold, Big Cat?
Uh... [sniffs]
No, I don't think I am.
I guess someone must be
talking about me somewhere.
Yeah. I've heard
that old saying.
Toucan! Don't wipe snot on me!
I'd like to think it's
my little girl bragging
on her dear old dad.
[LIZARD]
Next time on Africa Salaryman:
"Africa Flower-Viewing Parties."