[CROW squawks]
It's the last episode, moron!
[LION groans]
This is terrible.
Hey there, Big Cat! Yikes.
What's the matter
with you today?
Why does your
face look so scary?
I'm just kidding,
you always look scary, ha!
I'm in a world of trouble here.
Better not fret too much,
or you're gonna go bald.
[LION] Is there really
no way out? Oh, dear.
[TOUCAN]
Wah!
I tried to help him,
but he ignored me!
Lizard. Hello?
One of you has to
gimme some validation
or I am gonna drop dead!
Don't you hear me?
Hey, hey, Lizard? Come on.
Dude. I'm right here.
What gives?
[LIZARD]
Big Cat.
We need to decide on a direction
for the presentation right now.
I have a few ideas.
I say we sit down and
go over the details ASAP.
You're right,
it's time to buckle down.
We won't get anything
done if we don't have
some kind of meeting.
Wait for me!
Do you guys even
realize I'm here?
The presentation is
only five days away.
Sadly, we still haven't
made any solid decisions.
And if we don't
win the contest,
then we can all kiss
our jobs goodbye.
No biggie, we'll bomb
so hard that the president
won't have the heart to fire us.
Obviously someone didn't
bother to read the email
he sent us yesterday.
Email? What's it say?
Let's see here.
"If your presentation isn't
chosen, the three of you
are fired.
So please work as though your
pathetic lives depend on it.
Love, President Turtle."
Oh, god!
[screams]
Whoa, watch the equipment!
What are you two
idiots sittin' around
twiddlin' your thumbs for?
We have to think
of a direction...
I'm happy to see you
finally understand
the severity of
the situation, Toucan.
We never stood a chance!
I can't believe I'm gonna
have to sell my Lexun and...
I think they should fire
you, regardless.
And the worst part is,
if I lose this job,
I won't be able to pay
back my loan shark!
Your motivations are stupid,
but I'm glad we're on
the same page, at least.
You're the smart one.
Got any brilliant ideas?
Yeah, Lizard, I mean Mr. Lizard,
I mean Dr. Lizard!
Can you save our asses
with your supreme genius?
Why is this whole thing
riding on me?
Hey, it's not riding on you!
Well, it is, but don't let it
go to your head, all right?
[HONEYGUIDE chuckles]
Looks like you three
are taking the bad news
pretty well!
Whatever you want,
I'm certain that it can wait.
Sorry. I'm not going anywhere!
I hear you have a presentation
next week, is that correct?
And if you guys don't
win this for the company,
then you're going to be
fired immediately?
My goodness,
I don't know what to say!
[HONEYGUIDE crying]
[LION] Are you trying
to be encouraging?
Oh, god no, I'm just
organizing your farewell party.
How's your schedule
looking for Friday?
[LION]
We're not officially fired yet.
Well, that presents a problem.
Why's that?
[HONEYGUIDE chuckles]
I already got everybody
to sign this goodbye card.
If you don't get fired,
then how am I supposed
to explain to them that
they wasted ten seconds
of their time?
Er... Toucan?
Way ahead of ya.
[HONEYGUIDE whimpers]
[HONEYGUIDE yells]
[glass breaks]
This is awful.
Not even our own
coworkers want us to succeed.
Gah! Hey!
You guys havin' a wimp
convention in here?
[LIZARD]
Ugh, not again.
So, a little birdie
told me President Turtle
trusted you with an
important assignment.
Is that right, pussycat?
Well, I ain't gonna let you
take any credit for it!
I wrote my own proposal!
But you can't get credit
for this; you're not even part
of our division.
Seriously?
Let's lure him into the car
so we can drop him off at
the looney bin.
I'm on board with that plan.
Fine, then there's only
one thing left to do!
[cymbals crash]
Gah, son of a--
[HONEY BADGER laughs]
At this rate, you chumps
won't get anything done!
I can't wait to see you fail
at your precious contest!
[laughs]
Huh?
I'll be docking your pay.
[yelling]
Hold on, President!
It was a dumb joke!
Honey Badger does
care this time, honest!
I was just stoppin' by
to give my good pal Lion
a kick in the pants, is all!
Ha ha, ha ha...
I sure hope this job
doesn't turn me into a prick.
Oh, that ship's sailed.
[CROW squawks]
It's the next day, dumbass!
[LION]
Good morning, you two.
I wouldn't call it good.
'Sup, buddy?
I'm glad we at least
thought of a direction
for our presentation.
I agree. It's nice to know
we have one obstacle
behind us now.
That's not near enough, though.
It's nowhere close
to being finished yet.
So negative!
Either way, our situation's
definitely improved
from yesterday, right?
[sighs]
We're gonna be workin'
round-the-clock, huh?
It's better than having no job.
Time to put our heads
together and win this thing!
Look, someone's
coming over here.
Hello, Lion. It's been a while.
Why, we've been so excited
to see you again,
we're trembling
with anticipation!
[TOUCAN]
Doesn't look like it.
Why are you here?
Is that any way to greet
your old friends?
We traveled all
this way to a firm
that we're competing against
just to cheer you on.
Say, "thank you."
Oh, really, you did?
That's so very generous of you.
I appreciate it!
[BOTH gasp]
Hey, are you messin' with me?
Huh?
It's sarcasm.
How did you not realize that?
[LION]
Okay, then why?
Why? To tell you
that this is war!
Oh, that's pretty
straightforward!
Don't tell me you've already
forgotten about
that rotten thing you did.
How could he?
He committed a heinous
crime against humanity that day!
Does that matter
if we're all animals?
If you just listen, I can
explain everything.
We didn't come here for excuses!
We've been counting
down the days until
we could exact our revenge!
Yeah! It's time for you to
face your punishment, bub!
[LION]
Oh, my.
[OL FENNEC FOX]
Um, excuse me, sir.
There's no smoking in here,
so if you could please
put that out...
Huh? You got a problem, shrimpy?
[OL FENNEC FOX]
No!
Face it, Lion.
Everyone knows your
presentation doesn't have
a snowball's chance in hell
of outdoing the one
our company whipped up.
You might as well surrender now
before you embarrass yourself.
[TIGER grunts]
Don't say that!
We want Lion to be humiliated!
[clears throat]
Uh, what I meant was,
we're not gonna
let you back out!
Exactly.
We're looking forward to your
pitiful performance next week.
See you then, loser!
Were those two supposed
to be scary, or...?
Well, they scared him.
Big Cat...
What did you do to hurt them?
[LION]
Ugh, I can't say it.
They're right, it was
unspeakably terrible of me.
It's so terrible you
can't even tell us?
Don't worry, bro.
What's done is done.
Uh, que sera sera!
And all that good stuff.
Thanks a lot, Toucan.
That helps.
Wow. You're surprisingly--
[LIZARD]
Don't you dare give up now!
[TOUCAN]
And, kablam!
[TOUCAN screams]
I can't do this!
I'm sleepy!
And hungry! And bored!
I wanna go home!
You are such a baby.
What's that yummy smell?
Hey there, I'm from Eweber Eats.
[TOUCAN]
Pizza!
Great, it's here!
You can just set
it down anywhere.
[PIZZA RABBIT]
All right, thanks!
Wow, this looks
incredibly delicious!
I figured we'd be getting
hungry right about now.
You really are a good
superior, Big Cat.
God, I'm starving.
Hey, pizza. Get in my
belly before I pass out!
[LIZARD]
Stop drooling on the table.
[LION laughs]
Let's eat quick
and get back to work!
--[TIGER] Cheers! Bottoms up!
--[LEOPARD] To the firm!
Isn't a bit early for this?
You saw them.
I think it's safe to assume
we have this competition
in the bag.
You're right, that bird
had "bumbling idiot"
written all over him.
[LEOPARD] Should we look
over our materials?
There's no need for that.
The corporate drones can
just brief us the day before.
I suppose so.
If that's the case,
then let's hit the club
and find some ladies.
[TIGER]
Sounds like fun.
Well, Tiger,
what are we waiting for?
Let's go! Time's a-wastin'!
[LEOPARD chuckles]
We're finally finished.
Guess we pulled
it off after all.
Ugh. The sun is
beginning to come up.
Ugh. Just five hours until
we give our presentation.
[LIZARD]
Maybe we'd better sleep.
[yawns]
You're right. We should catnap.
Where did Toucan go?
[TOUCAN snoring]
He's been like that
for a solid hour now.
Poor fella.
This is probably the most
he's had to apply himself
at work since the day
they hired him.
Bet you're right,
but if it wasn't for
Toucan's hard work,
there's no way we could've
pulled this thing together
before the deadline.
That's true.
[yawns]
[LION]
Let's rest up while we can.
Yeah, I'm bushed.
[LION yawns]
Well, goodnight, Lizard.
[LIZARD]
Good night, Big Cat.
[snoring]
[TOUCAN grunts]
Is it morning yet?
[TOUCAN yells]
Wake up, you two!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
It's almost ten o'clock!
You've had enough
beauty sleep, hot guy,
now let's get moving!
The time has come,
the walrus said.
[TOUCAN] The time's already
come and gone, pal!
We're about to be late!
Where am I?
What's for breakfast?
Hey, sleepyheads,
look up at the clock!
[BOTH yell]
Listen, God, I know
we don't talk enough,
but please let us make it
to our presentation on time!
Excuse me, sir.
We're kind of in a hurry, here;
don't you have a nitro boost
or somethin' you could use?
Throw a banana peel! Somethin'!
I guess the guys from
Africa Trading are running late.
It sure says a lot about
them if they can't show up
on time to something
this important.
We're terribly sorry for cutting
it so close, gentlemen!
Talk about an embarrassment.
I didn't realize the hiring
standards at Africa Trading
were so low.
[LEOPARD]
That's right.
Every professional knows
that early is on time,
and on time is tardy.
I'm so sorry.
Hmph. If sayin' you're sorry
could fix everything,
we wouldn't have
any use for cops.
[AFCADO CHIEF]
Now, now, they weren't late,
so why don't we get
down to brass tacks?
If that's what AfCado wishes,
then that's what
my firm'll do, sir.
[AFCADO CHIEF]
Very good.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to hear
the presentations from each
of your companies, please.
All right, we might
as well go first,
since ours is the best.
[LEOPARD] We'll turn out
the lights so you can get
the full effect.
All set.
Now sit back and enjoy.
Thank you.
We expect you'll choose
to do business
with Tiger & Leopard.
[AFCADO CHIEF]
This is spectacular.
Are you sure you can
do it on this budget?
[TIGER]
Of course, it's simple!
We use in-house creators
to keep the cost low,
and our scheduling is flexible,
so we don't worry about
rush-ordering anything.
[LEOPARD] We look forward
to your decision, sir.
That was quite an
impressive performance.
I know.
Now, I'm even more afraid.
Guys.
Even though they are great,
we have to hold
our heads up high.
We worked hard.
And without faith, we can't win.
Heh. I never thought you would
be the voice of reason.
I agree. Thank you, Toucan!
In our hearts,
we're already winners today!
[AFCADO CHIEF]
Let's keep the ball rolling.
Africa Trading?
Now then, without further ado,
here is our presentation.
Thank you.
This concludes our proposal.
They had good energy and
their ideas were creative,
but our plan is more efficient,
so we're the obvious choice.
I knew we had this in the bag.
[LIZARD] Is he mad at us
because we threw it together
so quickly?
[TOUCAN] If he yells at me,
I'm jumping out the window!
[AFCADO CHIEF]
That was incredible!
[GROUP]
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
[AFCADO CHIEF]
I'm quite impressed!
AfCado would like to proceed
with Africa Trading's
proposal for the project!
We're so happy to
have your business!
--[TOUCAN] That's great!
--Are you kidding?!
But sir!
We had much lower costs
and our schedule was better!
[AFCADO CHIEF] I do agree
that Tiger & Leopard's plan
was superior in every way.
However, your plan
lacked a certain "fire"
that we felt was crucial.
Fire? I don't believe my ears!
[AFCADO CHIEF] It's just that
you seemed somewhat detached
from your message.
Was your slideshow
created by someone else?
[BOTH gasp]
[AFCADO CHIEF]
I'll take that as a yes.
[LEOPARD]
Well, even if we didn't make it,
the content is what matters!
[AFCADO CHIEF] We've taken
content into consideration.
[TIGER]
This is an outrage!
[AFCADO CHIEF]
We wanted a proposal that really
got to the heart
of the Cinema Café project,
and Africa Trading delivered.
If the cost is a little higher,
then so be it.
[BOTH gasp]
It was touch-and-go for a while,
but luckily, we managed
to strike a deal with them!
I'm so happy
everything worked out.
Now I won't get
fired or divorced!
[LION] You really had a lot
on the line, didn't you?
By the way, Big Cat,
you never told us why
they hate your guts.
[LION]
Well, I uh...
[TIGER] 'Cause he ate the
flans we were lookin' forward
to havin' later that day.
Yeah, he did us real dirty.
Wait.
You almost ruined our lives
over a couple of stolen flans?
No, they weren't just
any old flans!
They were for
a super special treat!
That was a classic
Toucan move, buddy.
I'm so proud.
Sorry. I'm the worst.
Grudges are one thing,
but food grudges
can run especially deep.
We may've lost this battle,
but we'll be back to get
our revenge someday!
[LION whimpering]
Hang on, what kind
of flan did he take?
Afaf Flan, the best kind!
And the most upsetting
part of it is,
the company that used to
make it went out of business
forever after that!
[TOUCAN]
Huh. You sure?
It says here they're
up and running again.
Really? That's amazing!
In that case,
I'll treat both of you
to some Afaf Flan next week!
Now that sounds like a plan.
Looking back on it,
I don't know why we got
so bent out of shape
over some silly flan.
Ten cups each!
Whoa, is that really
what it's like to be
an awkward old guy?
I hope I don't
turn out that way.
Attention, please,
let's raise a glass
in celebration of these three,
who won a major client for us.
I hope the rest of you
corporate drones
will follow their example.
Now for a few words from them.
I have to say,
this victory belongs
to my dearest colleagues,
Lizard and Toucan.
I could never have
accomplished this feat
on my own.
Although it's tempting
to revel in the successes
we've achieved,
I believe that this is only
the very beginning.
I plan to work hard
and make the Cinema Café
project the best it can be!
Ugh. I always hate
these long speeches.
[phone ringing]
Oh, AfCado's calling me.
Hello? Sure, I can talk.
Wait. Huh?
What?! You don't want
to work with us now?!
Oh, no!
Gah! Hundreds of millions,
out the door!
Did they happen to mention what
made them change their minds?
LOL! Just kidding!
[GROUP growls]
Okay, now that I've
got your attention,
I say we should propose a toast!
Um, you guys look angry.
Come on, this is a party,
we're here to have some fun.
[LIZARD] You're about to learn
the difference between
a good joke and a bad one!
[TOUCAN]
Hey, not the feathers!
Uh, cheers!
Hey, it's Shishimura!
And me, Gorimi!
Okay, real talk.
What did everybody think
of Africa Salaryman?
Really? It wasn't funny?
What? You don't like it?
If there wasn't
a screen between us,
I'd murder you!
Hey, calm down, Amber,
it's not worth it.
But Monica...
Okay! Africa Salaryman is over!
Yup, we'll see ya later!
Bye-bye!