‐ [Karen Voiceover] On the
night that I told the truth
to Mr. Mike.
Ms. Miina left our
house without telling us
where she was going or anything.
She just disappeared.
Mr. Mike spent the entire
night out looking for Ms. Miina
and when he came back.
‐ I’m sure she’ll come back,
as soon as she gets hungry.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] Well,
at least that’s what he said
but it was painfully
obvious to me
that he was just acting tough.
Ms. Miina, what’s going on?
Mr. Mike and I, I mean
my big brother and I
are really worried about you.
So would you please
please come back home?
Please?
(upbeat pop music)
‐ Karen!
(singing in Japanese)
‐ Hey Miina, you
really had us worried.
You leave us wondering
where you are
and then you just
pop up at school
like nothings happened.
Can you at least look at us?
So what is it?
What, what do you mean?
Hey, Miina.
Fine, suit yourself.
‐ Ms. Miina.
But, it was a good thing.
‐ Karen, what are
you talking about?
(insects chirping)
‐ Ms. Miyafuji?
‐ Oh hello.
‐ What’s wrong?
Your face is all red.
‐ Oh, its nothing, really.
‐ Perhaps you asked
Kamishiro to go steady?
‐ No I didn’t!
‐ You don’t have to
get so upset about it.
‐ This is just about the
worst time for all this.
‐ I don’t get it.
What’s up with her?
‐ I have a very strong feeling
love is in the air.
(soft romantic music)
‐ What the heck is going on?
Miina decided that she
would ignore me all day
until she left school.
‐ Well I’m sure she had
a good reason for it.
‐ What kind of reason?
‐ I really don’t know.
Girls can get
rather complicated.
‐ No kidding, what she
says and what she does
are two totally
different things.
While we’re on the subject,
where’s Miina staying?
‐ She’s staying with
one of her classmates.
Her name is Haruko Shido.
‐ Haruko?
‐ Yeah, she’s just a
girl who’s in her class.
She has a rather
unique big brother.
‐ I’ll be really nice.
I promise to do
everything you want!
‐ No!
‐ I’m bringing her back.
‐ What is it that you
were just imagining.
‐ I really can’t say it.
‐ Please wait, Mr. Mike.
I’ll do it.
I think it would be best
if I just go and see Ms. Miina.
At times like this,
its often better
to keep things just
between us girls.
‐ You have a point.
‐ Haruko, I’m sorry
to barge in like this.
‐ It’s perfectly alright.
In fact, I’m really
happy because it feels
like I have a sister.
‐ And I’m happy
cause I feel like
I’ve got a new little sister.
It just feels like it, you know.
It just feels like it.
‐ Haruko, do you
think that maybe
I could stay here
for a little while?
‐ Oh great, that’s perfect.
This will be so fun.
‐ Just pretend that
this is your house
and then do whatever
you want to do
and then I’ll do the
same as well, okay.
Well, I will stay within
certain boundaries.
‐ [Woman] Haruko, you
have another friend here
to visit you.
I’m sending her in.
‐ Okay.
‐ Wow.
Now there are three
little sisters.
‐ Oh its alright, Karen,
don’t worry about him.
My big brother won’t
act on what he says.
‐ Hey, you brought me
a change of clothes.
Thanks a lot.
‐ You’re welcome.
Ms. Miina, can we go
somewhere and talk for awhile?
‐ Sure, Karen.
Why did we come
to a public bath?
‐ You know what they
say, naked people
bear their hearts right?
Besides, whenever I’ve
had a really important
conversation with you,
it’s almost always
been in the bathtub.
‐ It was like our own
secret room where Mike
couldn’t hear what
we were saying.
‐ Yeah.
‐ So you seem like
you’re doing okay.
I thought you’d be
depressed because
of what’s been happening
over the last few days.
‐ I am depressed, Ms. Miina.
But there’s a part of me that’s
really happy I found out.
That I’m the one
related to Mr. Mike.
‐ Yeah.
‐ And then last night when
you left the house, Ms. Miina,
I realized something.
I love Mr. Mike like
a little sister should
and I really love
having you as my friend
and I love the three of us.
I love us all together.
‐ Karen.
‐ I want the three
of us together.
I want us all together
living in that house.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Would you mind telling me?
What made you decide
to leave the house?
‐ I left because I’m a stranger.
Its not my home.
‐ If you really meant that,
you wouldn’t of chosen
Haruko’s house to run to.
I think you would of
gone much farther away.
You have another
reason, don’t you?
‐ Well I.
‐ You know that you
can stay in the house
and you can stay in love
with Mr. Mike if you want.
You can even tell him
you’re in love with him.
Right now, Ms. Miina,
you’re not even talking
to Mr. Mike.
Oh my, that’s not
because of me, is it?
‐ Its not that.
Well, part of me may think that.
But that’s really
not the reason.
‐ But Ms. Miina, love
alliance rule number three
is still fully active.
Whoever ends up being
related to Mr. Mike
must support the others
romance with him.
‐ But, Karen.
‐ I wouldn’t want anyone else
to be Mr. Mike’s girlfriend
but you.
You’re the one for my brother.
‐ Thanks Karen, I appreciate it.
But can you hold off on
the idea of me going back
to the house for a bit?
‐ Why do you want that?
‐ Well because.
‐ Please tell me.
Ms. Miina?
‐ I can’t look.
‐ What?
‐ I can’t look at him.
Ever since I found out that
Mike wasn’t my brother,
I haven’t been able to
look him in the face.
Its strange but I can’t.
My heart just starts to
race when he talks to me.
I can’t believe I’m
feeling this way.
I just, I just can’t see
anyone other than mike
but if we, if I.
‐ Ms. Miina.
‐ Both of them are so innocent.
Its so cute.
‐ Yeah it is.
‐ Its so nice to be young.
(laughing)
‐ You sound like an old woman.
‐ You.
I’ll do something dreadful.
(screaming)
‐ [Haruko] I’m sorry.
Somebody help me.
I’m in trouble.
Stop it.
‐ Tsubaki, I’m so
lonely here without you.
Who is that?
‐ [Mike] So it didn’t
work out with Miina, huh?
‐ [Karen] I’m sorry, but
she said she’d come back
so she’s not gone forever.
‐ Well, its’ alright.
As long as we know where she is.
We’ll be fine.
To think that ruined
house had records in it
that answered questions
about our past.
You know, Karen, the weird thing
its so run down it
doesn’t look like anyone’s
been living there for
at least 20 years.
‐ There’s no way.
According to the information
in our mother’s notebook,
the house that the
three of us lived in for
the first couple years of
our lives was this one.
So this really is our house.
‐ Yeah.
Guess you’re right.
You know even after we
read that entire diary,
we still have no real
idea of who our mother is
but the diary should serve
us some sort of clue.
So if you want me to, I
can begin a full search
for our mother.
‐ I don’t know, Mr. Mike, what
do you think we should do?
‐ I think we
shouldn’t do anything.
‐ You’re right,
I agree with you.
‐ So it doesn’t bother you?
‐ I’d be lying if I said
it didn’t bother me at all.
But I think that you
said it best, Mr. Mike.
All that really
matters is now, right?
You and I, in that house.
Miina, you and I in that house,
the three of us living
together as a family,
that would be my perfect now.
‐ But that’s not
the case for Miina.
‐ But Mr. Mike.
‐ Isn’t that right?
As soon as she found out
that she wasn’t related
she put a lot of distance
between her and us.
I don’t care if she’s a
relative or a stranger
but I guess it must
be important to her.
‐ No that’s not it.
I promise you that Ms.
Miina isn’t worried
about any of that at the moment.
She’s looking at
what’s happening now.
I can tell, I’m sure of it.
‐ Alright then, what
is now for Miina?
‐ That’s really not for
me to say, I’m sorry.
But please don’t stop
believing in her.
Right now, Ms. Miina is.
‐ You know, now I know for
sure that I’m your twin brother
but it really
hasn’t sunk in yet.
From my standpoint, you
and Miina act a lot more
like your twins
then we ever have.
‐ But we are twins.
‐ Oh?
‐ Even though we’re not related.
She and I are
still twin sisters.
‐ Karen!
‐ Haruko, what’s wrong?
‐ Karen.
Mii, Mii, it’s Miina.
‐ What’s wrong with Miina?
(soft instrumental music)
‐ Miina said she
was leaving town.
I tried to talk her out of it
but she wouldn’t listen
and before I knew it,
she had disappeared
from our house.
‐ [Mike Voiceover]
Why damn it, why?
‐ Mr. Kamishiro.
‐ Ms. Kasami.
Have you seen Miina around here?
Miina Miyafuji?
‐ Yes, I was just going
to tell you all about it.
I saw her, she was walking
towards Umino Kutchi station.
Did something happen to her?
‐ [Mike Voiceover] Miina.
‐ Miina!
‐ Its Mike.
Why is he here?
‐ Hey where do you think
you’re going, Miina?
Tell me why.
Why aren’t you coming back home?
Why aren’t you talking to me?
Its pretty strange.
Don’t you think
its strange, Miina?
The fact that you’re not
related to us bothers you.
Did you think we’d kick you out?
Do you really think
I’m that narrow minded?
Even if we’re not
related by blood,
even if we’re strangers,
we can still be a family.
You and I could just go
somewhere and get married,
then there’d be no
reason for you to leave.
‐ Oh Mike.
Are you proposing to me?
‐ Well no.
Its an example, you
know, just an example.
‐ I’m happy, I’m so happy.
‐ I, oh Miina.
‐ But I’m scared.
‐ Scared?
What’s with being scared?
What are you scared of?
‐ I want to be in that house.
I’m more than
happy to stay there
but I’m scared that
there may come a day
when we won’t be able to
communicate with each other.
If that happens, I won’t
be able to stay there.
I won’t be, be able to...
‐ Miina.
Miina, you’re worrying way
too much about the future.
I told you, the only thing
that really matters is now.
If you don’t concentrate on now,
there will be nothing
for you later.
So what do you want to do now?
Answer me.
‐ I want to stay.
I want to be with you.
I want to be with you
and Karen, all together
in that house.
‐ Then lets do that.
‐ What about?
‐ We’ll talk about
us another time.
(soft romantic music)
‐ No, stop, you can’t do that.
Stop wait.
‐ Karen?
(screams)
(groans)
(shouts)
‐ Oh my.
‐ You sure know how
to entertain us.
Hats off to you.
‐ Oh, Mr. Kamishiro.
‐ This is sure to
get you suspended.
‐ I think I’d rather
pretend as if I hadn’t
seen anything.
‐ Shimazaki, Senpai,
madam president.
I don’t understand.
‐ What are you all doing?
‐ Well, you know me.
I’m pretty much always
on the side of girls
who are in love.
‐ That’s not really
a reason to be here.
What does this all mean?
‐ Don’t ask me what it means.
All I know is that Haruko
told me I should come here
and wait for a little while.
‐ I’ve been busted.
‐ Come on everyone,
let’s go home.
‐ Hey, not so fast!
What did you think
you were doing.
Damn you.
‐ [Shimazaki] Ouch
that hurts, Mike.
Why are you attacking just me?
‐ [Mike] I can’t possibly
raise my hand against senpai
or my teacher.
You’re the representative
for all of them.
‐ [Shimazaki] Help me, Tsubaki.
‐ [Tsubaki] I’m sorry, Kousei.
‐ [Kasami] I’ll just
pretend I’ve never
seen any of this either.
‐ You’re wonderful, Kamishiro.
‐ Kousei.
‐ I envy them.
I want to fall in love, too.
‐ No way, you can’t
do that, Haruko.
‐ My big brother is a, well
he’s a really big time loser.
(soft romantic music)
‐ Gees, what were
those guys thinking?
I don’t believe them.
‐ You’re so cruel, Karen.
I thought you were going to
support me in my romance.
‐ Oh but I do, Ms. Miina.
Of course, I hope you’ll
try and understand
that Mr. Mike is my new
big brother after all.
I want to be babied by him
for a little bit longer.
(laughing)
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Well I’m your little sister.
Its alright if I walk arm
in arm with my big brother,
don’t you think?
‐ Yeah, well you know.
‐ Mike.
(giggling)
What do you want
for dinner tonight?
‐ You’re acting like
a newly wed wife.
‐ Is that bad?
‐ Of course it is.
Mr. Mike is my big
brother and mine alone.
‐ Yeah but he’s my Mike.
‐ So what, he’s my big brother.
‐ Does anyone here
care what I think?
‐ Yeah, what is it Mike?
What do you think we should do?
‐ That’s right, please
tell us, big brother.
‐ Well I think.
That’s something pretty obvious.
We’re gonna live in
that house, our house,
all three of us together.
‐ [Miina] Oh gees, that’s
not what we’re talking about.
‐ [Karen] But its just
like you to say, Mr. Mike.
(soft romantic music)
‐ [Karen Voiceover] I’m sure
there will be many things
up ahead for the three of us.
‐ [Miina Voiceover]
But for right now.
We’re all going
back to our house.
‐ [Mike Voiceover] The
three of us are going
to live together
and if we keep repeating it.
Someday we’ll be a real family.
(soft instrumental music)
Hey Miina, did you know?
‐ [Miina Voiceover] Know what?
‐ [Mike Voiceover] That photo
from when we were babies
it was actually you and
me in the little pool.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] Apparently
I was off taking a nap.
‐ [Mike Voiceover] So
Miina, even back then
the three of us were together.
So, that’s how it is now
and how its gonna
be from now on.
‐ [Both Voiceover] We’ll
continue to be twins forever.