(gentle music)
‐ The one thing I had with me
when I was abandoned
by my mother and
entered the orphanage,
was this photograph
showing me when I was a kid
and this girl who I
thought was my relative.
Even though I hold this
photo dear to my heart,
I’m not overly
obsessed about the past
and I’m really not emotional
enough to cherish something
that I have absolutely
no memory of.
But I had the fait hope
that I might be able
to meet the girl that I
took this picture with,
that I might be able to
meet a real relative.
That’s why when I
got into high school,
I decided to live alone
here near this lake
where the photograph was taken.
It didn’t take long to find
that house in the picture.
The place was all torn up
and it was very cheap to rent
so I didn’t hesitate
signing a rental agreement.
This is where I will be living,
in this beautiful
place that is so calm,
it gives me this
wonderful illusion
that time is just
standing still.
But then, as both my
work and school life
were starting to get settled,
something drastic happened,
I met them, the girls
who may be my relatives,
Miina Miyafuji,
Karen Onodera.
These two girls had the exact
same photograph as I did
and both of them had the
same color eyes as me.
I instinctively felt
that one of these two
girls was my relative,
a real relative bound by blood.
But there were three of us.
There were only two
people in the photograph,
but there were three of us here.
One, a stranger.
One, a blood relative.
In that very strange
relationship,
all three of us started to
live under the same roof.
Summer had begun.
From that day, when I met Miina,
from that moment
when I met Karen,
our summer had begun.
Our strange, uncertain summer,
swaying between a
relative and a stranger.
(upbeat music)
(sighing)
‐ Miss Miina, I don’t know
if it’s such a good idea
to bring job opportunity
booklets into the bath.
‐ But the businesses in this
area aren’t offering many jobs
and you need to be 18 or
older to get most of them.
If I find anything, I
have to call right away.
‐ Yeah, that may very
well be the case but‐‐
(water splashing)
‐ Hey, Karen, tell me the truth,
do you think I look 18?
‐ Not really.
‐ [Miina] You’re so cruel!
How could you say that to me?
‐ I’m so sorry.
‐ And with your chest,
you’re the last person
I wanna hear that from.
‐ Why are you so mean?
That really bothers me.
‐ It’s all right, Karen, flat
has it’s way of being wanted.
But being halfway in between
is really the worst
place you ca be.
‐ [Karen] Really, is that so?
‐ Well, yeah.
(gasp) Wow!
‐ [Karen] What is it?
‐ [Miina] Oh I see, you’ve
already found someone, huh?
I understand, sorry
to bother you, bye.
I missed out.
‐ Huh?
What’s this?
(sighing)
(whimpering)
‐ [Miina] No, Mike, you idiot!
You pervert, you sicko!
‐ A job, you say?
‐ Yeah, of course,
let’s face it,
we can’t rely on you
forever, right, Mike?
‐ I feel the same
way as Miss Miina.
‐ [Miina] Do you any
good leads for jobs?
‐ No, of course, I don’t.
I only just moved here
a couple of months ago
and I really don’t know that
many people around here.
‐ Oh, gee, why am
I not surprised?
‐ [Mike] Hey, shut up.
Anyway, Miina, what
about high school?
‐ High school?
‐ [Mike] Don’t you wanna go?
‐ (laughing) Well, you
know, I’m kinda dumb
so that’s really impossible.
‐ Miss Miina, is it possible
that you haven’t attended
high school, at all?
‐ Well, um, it’s
kind of complicated.
‐ I know you don’t
wanna talk about it
but at least tell us
if you’ve ever been
to high school or not.
‐ [Miina] I was planning to go,
but things sort of fell through.
‐ So, what happened?
‐ No comment, I’m sorry.
‐ So, you’re looking for
leads for part‐time jobs, huh?
‐ That’s right.
‐ You know, the very
fact that you would
come to me looking for help
is such a pleasant surprise.
‐ Look, it’s the top
two cute freshman guys,
Shimazaki and Kamishiro.
Oh, a beautiful couple
is such a nice thing.
‐ I’d say Kamishiro
has to be the cat,
I’m certain of it.
‐ A cat, wait, I don’t get it.
‐ (gasp) I can’t believe
it, my little Haruko.
My little sister’s
about to begin her climb
up the long ladder of maturity.
‐ A part‐time job?
Don’t you think that’s
a little strange?
‐ [Mike] What?
‐ Oh, come on now, Mike,
you’re already working
as a programmer.
‐ Hey, wait a minute, how
do you know about that?
‐ Oh, I know everything
about you, Mike.
(smack)
‐ [Mike] I’ll smack you.
‐ [Shimazaki] Yeah, well my
head’s already throbbing.
So then, what kind of
jobs are you looking for?
‐ [Mike] Ones that
girls could do.
‐ I see, these leads
are for those relatives
that have recently
moved into your house.
‐ I’m asking you, how
do you know about that?
‐ Yes, and I’m telling you,
I know everything about you.
(smack)
‐ [Mike] I’ll smack you.
‐ [Shimazaki] Yeah, my head.
Mike?
‐ Hm?
‐ If what you want is money,
I’ll give you as
much as you want
if you’ll just spend
a night with me.
(smack)
‐ [Mike] I’ll smack you.
‐ That was the
third time already.
‐ [Auburn Haired Girl] Look,
the cute couple is
flirting with each other.
‐ [Brunette Girl]
But when Kamishiro
is on the aggressive side,
it’s not as fun.
‐ I really don’t get
what’s going on at all.
‐ Oh, my Haruko.
(sobbing)
‐ The scenery is so beautiful.
It’s easy to feel peaceful here.
‐ You think so?
Of course, no matter
how peaceful or
pretty the scenery is,
it doesn’t give us
any money to live on.
‐ Miss Miina, how
about you try choosing
whether you’re gonna
read that paper or eat.
(gasp)
What’s the matter?
‐ [Miina] The high
school that Mike goes to
is looking for an
office assistant.
‐ An office assistant?
Are you really going to go
apply for that, that job?
‐ [Miina] You think I shouldn’t?
‐ I really don’t know
but looking at this ad,
it says that you’ve
got be at least
a high school graduate to apply.
‐ [Miina] That’s okay, I’ll
make up some bogus resume.
‐ [Karen] But, isn’t
that a bad thing to do?
‐ [Miina] We’ll be
a burden on Mike
if we don’t make some money.
‐ [Karen] Yeah, I
suppose so, but‐‐
‐ So, what do you think?
Do I look like I’m 18 now?
‐ I really don’t know
about you being proud
of stuffing your bra.
‐ Why are you just
sitting there?
Hurry up and go put
on a decent outfit.
‐ Huh?
‐ That’s right, for Mike.
‐ For Mr. Mike?
‐ Yeah.
‐ For Mr. Mike.
(sweet music)
‐ I’m shocked, to think
that you of all people
would actually come
to work at my school.
‐ But does it trouble
you that I took the job?
‐ Why would it?
I’m thrilled that you’ll
be at school every day,
because then we can
always be together, Karen.
‐ [Simpi] Kamishiro.
‐ Simpi, please, stop that.
‐ Hey, Simpi, back off!
You shouldn’t be trying
to seduce underclassmen!
‐ Okay, I won’t do it anymore.
‐ (sigh) Oh, Miina, thank you.
Oh, Miina, you saved me.
‐ I did it just for you, Mike.
(sighing)
‐ Miss Miina, I’ll do
my best, I promise.
‐ Yeah, me too.
‐ [Simpi] Leads
for part‐time jobs?
‐ [Mike] Don’t you have any?
I’m helping out with the
student counsel work and all.
I’m not saying it’s
in exchange for that,
but if you have any leads,
please, let me know.
‐ It’s for those
two girls who are
staying over at your
place, right, Kamishiro?
‐ [Mike] Well, yeah, it is.
But please don’t tell
everyone about it.
‐ Don’t worry, I’m one to
keep my mouth shut. (chuckles)
You doubt me, don’t you?
That’s a shame.
I was about to
introduce you to a lead.
‐ Really, that’s great!
‐ Yes, my best friend’s family
runs a local grocery store.
She has entrance exams
to study for this year
so she was looking for someone
to help out with the store,
in her place.
‐ That’s great!
Please, introduce me to her.
(bells ringing)
(door opens)
‐ I’m so sorry to
have kept you waiting.
The one in charge of
hiring is absent today.
I’ll be filling in for him
and conducting the
interview instead.
I’m one of the teachers
here and my name is Kazami.
I’m sorry, is something wrong?
‐ [Both] No, nothing
at all, Miss Kazami.
‐ Oh, I see.
‐ [Miina] Oh, it looks lik
she didn’t recognize us.
‐ [Karen] That’s a good thing.
‐ I’ve only been able
to take a quick look
at your resumes.
You are Miss Kikoko Inowe
and Miss Yayoi Inowe.
You have the same last name?
‐ Yes, you see, we’re twins.
‐ We have the same
eye color too.
‐ Oh wow, very impressive.
Both of you graduated from
Tokyo University Magnet School?
‐ [Karen] Miss Miina, there’s
no such school in Tokyo.
‐ [Miina] What, really?
‐ Is something the matter?
‐ [Both] Nothing at
all, Miss Kazami.
‐ Wait a second, you
two look familiar.
Have I met you somewhere before?
‐ [Both] No, I don’t
believe you have, mam.
‐ Really, are you sure?
‐ Yes, mam.
‐ [Loud Speaker] Miss Kazami,
you have a telephone call.
Please, come to the teacher’s
office as soon as possible.
‐ I’m sorry, would you mind
if I stepped out
for a few minutes?
I won’t be long.
‐ [Both] Yes, please, go away.
‐ What did you say?
‐ [Both] Oh, nothing.
(gasp)
Oribe and Kamishiro.
‐ Mam.
‐ Hello, Miss Kazami.
‐ It’s Mr. Mike.
‐ And I’ve heard that
voice somewhere before.
It’s that Simpi that came
to our house the other day.
‐ [Karen] I don’t get it.
What is Mike doing
all alone with her?
What’s the meaning of all this?
‐ Listen, Kamishiro, regarding
that thing we talked about?
‐ [Mike] Yeah, I was gonna
have a chat about that
a few minutes ago, but
I got a great answer.
I’m planning on visiting
the parents later
and giving them my greetings.
‐ What does he mean, greetings?
‐ What does he mean, parents?
‐ So they’re that important?
Kamishiro, you just met
them a few days ago,
these people may
be total strangers.
‐ That’s true but they
could be my real relatives.
‐ [Miina] Can you hear them?
‐ [Karen] Yeah, barely.
‐ Look, you really don’t know
enough to be certain, do you?
How about you have
them take a blood test
and then you can
find out for sure
if they’re really
relatives or not.
‐ Simpi, I’ve already done
some research about that.
The only way to know
for sure is DNA analysis
and that cost 100,000 yen.
I don’t have that kind of
money laying around anywhere.
Besides.
‐ Yeah, besides what, Kamishiro?
(angelic music)
‐ It’s like this, I
have something right now
that I’ve wanted my whole life
and it amazingly appeared
right in front of my face.
‐ Oh, Kamishiro, I‐‐
‐ Stop, right there!
All interior relationships
are forbidden!
‐ Miss Miina, no!
‐ [Miina] And when I
say it’s forbidden,
I mean it’s forbidden!
‐ Who was that?
‐ [Miina] I’m a teacher!
‐ I don’t know any teach
here who sounds like that.
‐ Hey, this is kinda suspicious.
‐ It was coming from
that room, wasn’t it?
‐ [Mike] Should
we open the door?
‐ Of course, we need
to inform the teachers
if there’s someone
suspicious in there.
‐ [Miina] This isn’t good.
‐ Well, no, of course it isn’t.
‐ Who is it?
(whimsical music)
Simpi, there they are!
‐ [Simpi] Escaping
from the window
makes them all the
more suspicious.
‐ Miss Miina,
didn’t we come here
so that we could interview
for a job opening?
‐ You don’t mind my
framing you here?
‐ No, that’s unacceptable.
‐ Then you better keep running.
(whimpering)
‐ [Karen] Miss
Miina, what’s wrong?
‐ I think I twisted my foot.
Don’t worry, I’m all right.
‐ All right, I’m back.
I’m sorry to have kept
you waiting so long.
(sighing)
‐ [Both] One, two, three, four.
Two, two, three, four.
Three, two, three, four.
‐ They’re not in there.
‐ They’re not over here either.
I better go inform the
student body president
about all this.
‐ I’ll go with you.
‐ Looks like we were
able to fool ’em.
‐ I can’t believe we
stole these gym clothes.
(sobbing) I’m turning more
and more into a bad girl.
‐ Someone stole all my gym
clothes out of my locker.
‐ Someone took mine too.
‐ Mine are all right, see?
‐ What happened, Haruko?
(girls gasp)
(screaming)
It’s a misunderstanding,
I was just!
‐ [Female Student]
Two suspicious people
are running around campus?
A couple of freshman girls
had their gym clothes stolen?
‐ [Male Student] I heard
one guy got caught.
‐ [Female Student] And
I heard the other one
is still on the loose.
‐ [Girls] Oh no!
‐ Call out the Manners
Committee Members,
you’re to work together
with the teachers
to blockade every entrance
and exit to this school.
‐ You really think we need to
go that far, Madam President?
‐ I do, we need to be
thorough about this.
(dramatic music)
‐ [Female Student] Should we
check this room just in case?
‐ [Male Student] Yeah, I got it.
‐ What do you see, Miss Miina?
What’s going on now?
‐ [Miina] It looks
like they’re doing
a search at the school.
‐ Oh no, this isn’t happening.
We’re really gonna
end up as criMiinals.
‐ Na!
(gasp)
Mr. Marie.
‐ Now, how did this
one get in here?
‐ Na, na, na, na‐‐
‐ I don’t get it,
what’s it doing?
‐ It always moves
around in strange ways.
‐ So you girls were here?
(gasp)
‐ But how, when
did she get here?
‐ You mean, how
(giggling)
(bells ringing)
‐ [Student] So what did
happen to their gym clothes?
‐ [Simpi] Kamishiro.
‐ Good work today, Simpi.
See you later.
‐ Oh, so I gather you’re
not going to help me?
‐ No, I have something
I need to do.
‐ Oh, I see, are they really
that important to you?
‐ They are, now if
you’ll excuse me.
‐ Oh, Kamishiro.
‐ [Kazami] Here you go.
‐ [Karen] Thanks,
I’ll have some too.
‐ To think that the two of you
would go to all the trouble
of dressing up and
writing false resumes
just so you could come
to a job interview
to be office assistance.
Do you really want to be
with Kamishiro that much?
‐ Well, uh.
‐ I guess.
‐ I see, but if he had found out
that you guys were
doing all of this,
don’t you think he
might have gotten angry?
Of course, deep down, he
might be happy about it.
You see, I was able to learn
quite a lot about Kamishiro
from the headmaster of
the government orphanage
that he had been in
most of his life.
Apparently, he didn’t make
any friends while he was there
and spent most of
his time all alone.
Although, he’d always be nice
and cordial and say hello,
he would never play together
with any of the other orphans.
Even after he started
coming to this school,
he would always try to be
alone as much as possible.
But you see, the real
reason why Kamishiro
behaves the way he does,
is so that he doesn’t
have to feel responsible
for showing any
kindness to anyone.
He can’t possibly
abandon the people
who become deeply
involved in his life.
That may come from the fact
that his parents
had abandoned him.
But then you two appeared and
were suddenly in this life
that Kamishiro had built.
Suddenly, after being
alone for all this time,
relatives showed up.
In other words, now
that he knows you,
Kamishiro will never
be able to abandon you.
I know he may act king of
cold or aloof towards you
but I’ll bet you anything that
he’s accepted both of you.
That’s the way which
he shows his kindness.
Do you understand?
You two are the ones
that opened the door
to the kindness that’s
been hiding inside of him.
It looks like it’s safe
for you to go home now.
You make sure you wash and
return those gym clothes, okay?
‐ [Karen And Miina] Yes, mam.
(train rumbling)
‐ [Miina] Uh‐oh,
the door is locked.
‐ [Karen] But, Mr.
Mike’s motorbike is here.
‐ [Miina] Well,
the lights are on,
so Mike has gotta
be inside, right?
‐ Hey, who’s out there?
‐ Oh, it’s me, Miina.
‐ And Karen, too.
‐ [Mike] Where
have you guys been?
Just wandering around
for all this time?
‐ Well, I.
‐ [Mike] Have you guys
never thought about
the feelings of those
who worry about you?
‐ But nobody has ever really
been worried about me before.
‐ [Karen] Oh, Miss Miina.
‐ Idiot!
Well, there’s someone
worried about you right now.
I’m worried about you.
If I’m being pushy,
just tell me,
and I won’t care anymore.
(somber music)
‐ No, Mike, you’re
not being pushy.
‐ Yeah, I don’t think
you’re being pushy at all.
‐ Thank you for looking
out for the two of us.
‐ I like it when people
are a little pushy.
‐ [Miina] I’m sorry, Mike.
‐ [Karen] I apologize.
‐ Then while I’m being pushy,
I guess I’ll let you know
that I managed to find
a couple of jobs
for both of you,
store clerks for a nearby market
called Harry Kouwa Groceries.
They know about
our situation too.
‐ Oh, Mike.
‐ Mr. Mike.
‐ Also, I made it so that you
work in the late afternoon.
You two will be going to
school during the day.
You fine with that?
(gasp)
Why are you dressed like that?
(sobbing)
Could it be that the strangers
who were at my school today
were you two?
‐ [Karen] I’m so sorry.
‐ What were you idiots doing?
Why at school of all places?
‐ We went there
for job interviews
and while we were there, Mike,
we saw you flirting
with that Simpi.
‐ Wait a second, what
are you talking about?
‐ [Miina] You were
flirting with her!
Right?
‐ Yes.
‐ Hey, I wasn’t
doing any such thing.
‐ [Both] Yes, you were!
‐ [Mike] Look, don’t try
to change the subject.
I want you to explain to me
why you’re dressed like that.
‐ [Karen] It’s kind
of complicated.
‐ [Miina] Hey, you’re the
one tryna change the subject!
‐ [Mike] Answer my question!
(smooth music)
‐ [Karen And Miina] Next
episode, more twins.
‐ [Miina Voiceover] We
ended up transferring
into the same school as Mike.
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
I’m a bit nervous,
this is the first time I’ve
attended a coed school.
‐ [Miina Voiceover]
All that aside,
I heard from someone in my class
that Mike always
seems to be clinging
onto one of his guy friends.
And he doesn’t show any signs
of being a guy living
with us, either.
Could it possibly be that
Mike is actually gay?
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
That is a big problem.
We gotta do something about it.
‐ Please Twins, episode five.
Do you like girls?
Make sure to watch it.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] Next
episode, more twins!