(tranquil piano music)
(upbeat electronic music)
(singing in Japanese)
(school bell rings)
‐ [Haruko] Mina, hey Mina!
We’re over here!
‐ [Mina] Sorry to
keep you guys waiting.
‐ Hey wait, what
happened to Karen?
I thought she’d be with you.
‐ She’s just gonna watch today.
It’s that time of the month.
‐ Amazing, girls get
such special privileges
when it’s their girly
time, that’s cool!
I didn’t know about that!
‐ [Koishi And Yuuka] You
mean you don’t get it yet?
‐ Uh, I don’t?
‐ You don’t?
Oh Haruko.
‐ [Teacher] Hi everyone,
let’s get started.
Today we’ll move on
to the sample shown
on page 76 of your textbook.
The sample is where
Mi meets Kumihiko‐
(sighs)
‐ What’s wrong?
‐ [Teacher] And acknowledges
that he is fuming from
conversing with him.
‐ Nothing, it just suddenly felt
like there was
someone in the hall‐
‐ [Teacher] Mr. Kamishiro
and Mr. Shimazaki.
‐ I’m sorry.
‐ [Teacher] As I was saying
before I was interrupted,
this part of the excerpt
is a good example
of a process by which we‐
(birds chirping)
‐ [Koishi] Mina, I’m
heading to school now.
I can trust you to take
care of the shop, right?
‐ Of course you can,
have a good class.
‐ Bye Karen, I’m going now!
Karen?
‐ Oh yes, one serving
of chicken soba noodles!
Thank you very much.
‐ What was that about?
‐ A bit of over dingy‐ness
‐ [Mike] Karen’s been
acting strange lately?
‐ [Mina] Yeah, I mean a
different strange than normal.
I don’t know.
(plate breaks)
She’s been in ultra
clumsy mode lately,
and I don’t think it’s her
time of the month either.
‐ Time of the month?
‐ [Mina] Nevermind, I’m worried.
She’s been taking her baths
lately all by herself.
So I‐
‐ Talk to her, see if she’s
got something on her mind.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Miss Mina Myafuji
and Karen Onodera.
Love alliance rule number one,
neither of us asks Mr. Mike out
until we figure out which
one of us is his family.
Love alliance rule number two,
if one of us finds out
she’s family with Mr. Mike,
we inform the other right away.
Love alliance rule number three,
whoever turns out to be
the relative will support,
the relative will support
the other’s romantic
relationship with Mr. Mike.
And so‐
‐ [Mina] Karen!
Hey, can I come in?
‐ (gasps) Miss, Miss Mina!
‐ Sorry, did I come
at a bad time for you?
‐ No, I was, I was just
about to get out anyway.
I’ll head out now Miss Mina.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] I’m so
sorry Miss Mina, I’m sorry.
(faucet drips)
(gasps)
‐ Hey.
What is it?
‐ Oh, it’s nothing, really.
‐ [Mike] No, I don’t
buy that for a second.
(Karen sighs)
I can see it right on your face.
You know Karen, you saw
how Mina was acting, right?
Don’t forget, if
there’s anything
you would like to
say to us, then‐
‐ [Karen] I know that.
I know that, so‐
‐ [Mike] So?
‐ But I’m a completely
different person from this Mina.
I’m me, I’m unique.
My name is Karen Onodera.
‐ [Mike] What are
you talking about?
Of course you are.
That’s not what I
was trying to say.
‐ [Karen] (sobs)
I’m not Miss Mina!
‐ Karen?
‐ [Karen] I’m not Miss Mina.
‐ [Mike] Karen.
‐ [Karen] I’m sorry, I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to say
something like this.
‐ No, I’m sorry.
‐ [Karen] I’m going to go
walk outside for a bit.
I’ll make sure to come back,
so please don’t worry about me.
‐ Hey!
(whines)
‐ [Mina] How did it go?
‐ I have no idea, but I’m sure
there’s something going on.
‐ I see.
‐ There’s just one thing though.
I really don’t know
how girls feel.
‐ [Mina] That’s not true, Mike.
Actually, a girl’s feelings
are a whole lot simpler
than you probably
think they are.
See, we worry about things
because we’re too
simple, you know?
‐ Is that so, huh?
‐ Uh‐huh. For instance,
what would you do
if you found your mother, Mike?
You already know the
answer to that, right?
‐ [Mike] Yeah, but I’d
still ponder about it.
‐ [Mina] It’s the
same thing as that,
although I really hate to see
her all sullen and worried,
and I am very concerned
about her and her well‐being,
I’d like to trust
that Karen’s fine.
I’m sure she’ll work it out.
‐ Guess you’re
right, she’s fine.
Yeah.
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
What am I gonna do
when I can no longer
say that anymore?
Because...
because the answer
is already out.
I know that Miss Mina is
really worried about me,
and I also know how Mr.
Mike feels about things too.
And so, I’ll become,
I’ll become stronger.
Karen Onodera will become
stronger, and walk with a smile.
And then...
and then...
(dramatic music)
We will be disbanding.
Miss Mina,
I’m going to disband
our love alliance.
‐ I went and put my work on hold
in order to come all the
way out here for this.
I’m gonna hate it if
it’s some sort of prank.
‐ [Karen] I’m sorry to
keep you waiting, Mr. Mike.
‐ Karen!
‐ I’m sorry, it took me a
little bit of time to get ready.
‐ That’s okay, but that dress.
‐ Yes, it’s the one that
you bought for me, Mr. Mike.
(giggles) How does it look?
‐ Um well, it looks great.
‐ [Karen] Thank you very much.
‐ Oh yeah, Karen. About
this letter that I got.
‐ Right, I sent that to you.
‐ Why go to the
trouble of all this?
‐ I have a favor to ask you.
Could you please go
out on a date with me?
‐ A date?
‐ [Karen] Yes, a date.
A date between Karen Onodera
and Mike Kamishiro. (giggles)
(calm, upbeat music)
‐ [Mike] Hey, what’s with
this all of a sudden?
What’s it all about?
‐ Is it bad for us
to go out on a date?
‐ Well, I’m not
saying that, but‐
‐ Then I think it’s
perfectly all right,
because after all, we
just might be strangers.
‐ [Mike] Karen, you
really shouldn’t say‐
‐ [Karen] I’m sorry, but I,
I just wanted to go on a date
because this’ll
be the first date
I’ll have been on in my life!
(calm, upbeat music)
‐ [Mike] Here.
‐ Oh, thank you very much.
‐ [Mike] We’ve
walked quite a bit.
‐ [Karen] Yes.
‐ [Mike] Did it seem
enough like a date for you?
‐ [Karen] Well yeah,
of course it did.
‐ [Mike] Good. But to
tell you the truth,
it didn’t feel
like a date to me.
In fact, it wasn’t any different
from when the three
of us go out together.
‐ [Karen] It was
different, it was.
I’m sure that it was.
No.
‐ So Karen, looks like
you found the answer.
‐ Um yes, yes I have.
‐ [Mike] I see,
then it’s all right.
You don’t have to say anything.
If you’re satisfied with the
answer, then it’s fine with me.
(bell rings)
Karen, I‐
Karen?
(gasps) Karen!
‐ Please let me say this.
I know the answer, and so...
Mr. Mike, are you listening?
I love you.
Oh, I love you, Mr. Mike.
And not only that,
I’m in love with you.
‐ Karen, oh Karen.
‐ [Karen] It’s, it’s
only natural that I
love you, Mr. Mike.
It was bound to happen.
(gasps) And that’s because
you’re my one and only
big brother, Mr. Mike.
(Mike gasps)
Mr. Mike, you and
I are, we’re twins.
Brother and sister, family.
We now know that no matter
how much I love you,
you and I will
never have a romance
because we’re blood related,
because we’re twins.
Because we’re siblings.
I’m very happy that we’re
related, I really am.
I really‐ (sobs)
‐ [Mike] Karen.
‐ I’m so sorry.
I probably shouldn’t
have told you how I feel,
but I couldn’t, I
couldn’t help it.
I just couldn’t help it!
(sobs)
‐ [Mike Voiceover]
I see, I get it now.
It seems it’s true that
Karen and I are twins,
and that the girl in this
photograph is, no, no way!
Hey, you know what, Mother?
You abandoned me.
After 16 years, I’ve finally
become my own person.
Then Mina came along
and Karen came along.
And then the three of us
started to live together.
Good things were about
to get started, until‐
‐ Just don’t leave, put this
stupid stuff behind you.
(Mina hums)
‐ Oh.
‐ Ah!
‐ I’ll give you
pretch later, okay?
‐ [Karen] I’m home.
‐ Hi, welcome back!
I was getting worried, what
were you doing out so late?
And you’re all dressed up like
you’re going out on a date.
(laughs) You weren’t
by any chance
off breaking love alliance
rule number one, were you?
‐ [Karen] Love alliance rule
number three, to be exact.
‐ What?
‐ Miss Mina, Mr. Mike’s sibling
has turned out to be me.
‐ Huh?
‐ Mr. Mike is actually
my older brother.
‐ That means that you and Mike
are really the twins
in the picture?
‐ Uh‐huh.
‐ You found out.
‐ Wow, I just can’t believe it!
Oh my goodness gracious,
that changes things.
I guess I’ll have
to move out of here.
‐ [Karen] What are you
talking about, Miss Mina?
There’s no way that Mr. Mike
would ever kick you
out of this house.
You know that’s true,
don’t you Miss Mina?
‐ Yes, Karen.
‐ This house is home
for all three of us.
You belong here Miss Mina,
just as much as I belong here.
We belong together.
‐ Do you, do you really mean
that I’m not related to Mike?
‐ That’s right, you’re free.
You’re finally free to
fall in love with him.
It’s all right for you to, to
tell him exactly how you feel.
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
I’ll head home first.
Mr. Mike, I’ll head
head home first.
I’m sorry to have given
you so many worries.
Have you had a chance to read
from our mother’s diary yet?
It’s about our mother
and about the two of us.
I’m going to tell
Miss Mina myself.
We promised each
other a while ago
that whoever found out which
one of us was the relative
would tell the other
one right away.
I’m sure that Miss Mina will
be confused by all of this,
so please, Mr. Mike,
please be kind to her.
Please surround her with warmth.
To my dear brother, love, Karen.
‐ [Mike Voiceover]
Nothing is gonna change.
I won’t let it no
matter what happens.
I’m not gonna let things change.
We won’t‐
‐ [Karen] Miss Mina?
Miss Mina!
‐ Karen!
‐ Mr. Mike, it’s Miss Mina.
‐ What’s wrong?
‐ She’s not at home,
and her bags are gone.
‐ What? Mina!
(Mina sobs)
Hey Mina!
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
Why, why Miss Mina?
You can stay here and
fall in love with him.
‐ Mina!
‐ [Karen Voiceover] Why?
‐ Come back Mina, please!
‐ Nice to meet you.
I know you’ve never heard of me,
but I’m actually
a blood relative.
‐ See, here it is.
I have the same photo.
‐ They really are, we’ve
got the same eye color.
‐ [Mike] What matters is now!
You can stay here, it’s all
right to stay here, really.
Senpai, there was something
that I always wanted,
and it suddenly appeared right
in front of me, like magic,
and I don’t know
why that happened.
So why, why is that?
Why did that happen?
Mina!
(singing in Japanese)