(dog barking)
‐ [Miina] Hey, don’t you think
you should call the
police or something?
‐ You’re kidding me, right?
I finally got permission
from the orphanage
to live on my own.
If they see any problems
at all they’ll just come
and take me back.
‐ You could have a problem.
‐ [Mike] Yeah,
because of you guys.
(Miina yawns)
‐ I’m getting really sleepy.
Do you have a spare futon?
‐ Do you think a
young guy living alone
would have a spare futon around?
‐ Don’t tell me that!
‐ I’m the one who wants to cry.
You’re better off,
at least you can
sleep next to her.
‐ Oh, you’re so right.
Excuse me.
(door scrapes)
(upbeat pop music)
‐ [Mike] Geez, did I do
anything wrong to deserve this?
(singing in a foreign language)
(light orchestral music)
‐ I’ve been waiting for
all this time to find
the twin brother that’s
in the photograph with me.
He might be a bit
older than I am
or he may be younger than I am.
And I believe that I would
be able to meet him someday.
Maybe he’s someone like this,
or he could be someone a
little bit more like this.
‐ [Boy] Karen, Karen.
‐ You, who may be
my older brother
or even my younger brother.
(Karen yelps)
(towel whooshes)
(Mike chuckles)
(Karen screams)
(Miina groans)
(door slams)
‐ What’s the matter?
Are you guys okay?
(Karen grunts)
(birds chirping)
(Miina moans)
‐ Nyu.
‐ Nyu?
(Miina grunts)
(girls thud)
(birds chirping)
‐ I’m terribly sorry about this.
I’m sure I’ve caused
a lot of trouble.
You see I,
I have this habit of passing
out when I get too excited.
Oh yeah, before
we talk about that
I should probably
introduce myself.
How do you do?
My name is Karen Onodera.
‐ My name is Miina Miyafuji.
And the guy next to me is‐‐
‐ I don’t wanna be rude
but that doesn’t
matter right now.
The problem we all have
to consider right now is
that there are three
copies of this photograph.
‐ Maybe somebody made
some extra copies.
‐ What I wanna know is why
the two of you have ’em.
‐ Well, apparently this
photograph was handed over
to the orphanage on the
day my mother gave me away.
At least that’s what I was
told by my foster parents
who raised me.
‐ That’s the same
thing I was told.
‐ [Mike] So, what was
your mother’s name?
‐ I have no idea.
‐ We are the same
on that front too.
Just like best buddies.
‐ I guess that’s true.
‐ Don’t get so chummy.
The problem is that
the three of us
have a photograph,
and that there are only two
little kids shown in it.
‐ Maybe the third
one is out of frame.
‐ [Mike] I’m sure
that’s impossible.
What this means is that one
of you is a complete stranger.
‐ Maybe you’re the
stranger here, Mikey.
‐ Hey, don’t call
me Mikey, got it?
(Karen yelps)
I’ve gotta go to school now.
We’ll finish this
when I get back.
You can stay here
in the meantime
and eat whatever’s around.
But listen, don’t
set one foot outside.
And don’t answer the
door, no matter what.
And don’t touch my computer
under any circumstances.
And that’s final!
‐ Why so bossy?
‐ I’m the master of this
house and I am the boss.
‐ You’re right, sorry.
‐ [Mike] I’m going now.
‐ [Karen] Um.
‐ [Mike] What?
‐ I hope you don’t mind but
I’d really appreciate it
if you would tell me your name.
‐ Mike.
My name’s Mike Kamishiro.
(cicadas chirping)
(upbeat music)
‐ [Karen] I used your shampoo.
Thank you very much.
‐ No problem.
Hey, Karen, what’d
you think about him?
‐ [Karen] What do you mean?
‐ [Miina] What was your
impression of Mike Kamishiro?
‐ Actually, I found him to be
more than a little bit scary.
‐ [Miina] Really?
‐ I’ve only gone to
all girls schools.
I don’t have much experience
when it comes to
dealing with males.
‐ You really don’t have to
be afraid of him, you know?
Mike is pretty rough with words
and likes to act tough
but, let’s face it,
he’s letting us stay
in his house right now.
I’m beginning to think that
he’s a pretty good guy.
Besides, he’s a little
bit on the clumsy side.
Trust me on this.
(laughs)
‐ [Karen] Oh yeah?
How do you know?
(Miina screams)
(Miina thuds)
(Karen shrieks)
(chalk tapping)
‐ [Teacher] Now, in
this sentence we can see
how the ancient Japanese
grammar is used to express
the word bloom.
‐ You left your schoolbag?
That’s a pretty dumb
thing to forget.
Don’t you agree?
‐ Just shut up.
‐ Is something going
on back at home?
‐ Would you shut up?
‐ When we’re like this,
don’t you think we
look just like lovers?
‐ Don’t talk to me.
‐ Anyone?
(breath whooshes)
‐ Oh wow, I’m getting kinda wet.
‐ Back off!
(teacher gasping)
‐ Kamishiro you’re that way?
‐ No way, you can’t believe him.
(upbeat music)
‐ [Matagu] Wow, Haruko,
the lunches you make
are so delicious.
‐ [Haruku] But I get
them ready‐made, brother.
‐ [Matagu] Oh, so that’s
why they’re all so tasty?
‐ [Haruku] I won’t bring
them for you anymore.
‐ [Matagu] No, wait, I’m sorry.
(Mike slurping)
‐ Senpai, I’m really sorry.
I promise I’ll pay
you back tomorrow.
‐ So, what happened anyway?
‐ Nothing, I just forgot
my wallet at home.
‐ [Tsubaki] Would
you like a bite?
I don’t mind.
‐ No, thank you.
I never really liked pumpkin.
(Mike slurps)
‐ [Miina] Hey, Mike!
There you are!
‐ Hmm?
‐ We’ve looked
everywhere for you.
(Mike spits)
(Tsubaki groans)
‐ Who’s that?
‐ Dunno.
‐ Here, you forgot
your bag this morning.
I also thought you’d be
hungry so I made you lunch.
Here, it’s my very
own special, toasty,
warm, pumpkin box lunch.
‐ Stop harassing me!
‐ So, you don’t like it?
‐ Who are these girls?
‐ Mr. Kamishiro.
(camera shutter snapping)
I need to ask you why your‐‐
‐ Duties as the student
body president‐‐
‐ Duties as student
body vice president.
‐ I understand.
‐ Wow, she bought that.
‐ Would you just be quiet?
‐ Mr. Kamishiro, you do
know that it’s a violation
of the school regulations
for you to bring
outsiders onto
this campus, right?
‐ [Mike] Yes, it was a mistake.
‐ Mr. Kamishiro, just
exactly how are you related
to those girls?
‐ I was just about to ask that.
‐ Those two are your
girlfriends, right?
‐ They’re not, senpai.
‐ [Tsubaki] So they
are your girlfriends!
‐ I just said they’re not!
And I really don’t
understand why
that’s any of your
business anyway!
(Tsubaki gasps)
‐ Whoa, that boy is dense.
‐ Yeah, you really think so?
‐ So, Mr. Kamishiro, what
exactly is the truth about them?
‐ [Miina] They...
They’re distant
relatives of mine.
The other day there was a
tragedy in their household
and I was the only person
they could turn to so.
‐ [Ichigo] That’s a lie.
‐ [Tsubaki] That’s a lie.
(Miina sighs)
‐ So, that’s what’s going on?
On top of living alone
you have to take care
of these two mow.
‐ [Both] Oh brother,
she bought it.
‐ You’re a wonderful person.
If you have any problems at
all don’t hesitate to call me.
I want to support
what you’re doing.
‐ Okay.
Thanks a lot.
‐ This teacher is a total ditz.
‐ Oh, you really think so?
(upbeat music)
‐ [Tsubaki] What?
You’re saying one of those
girls is your twin sister?
‐ Well, there seems to
be a strong possibility.
‐ How can you really be certain?
Maybe they’re just trying to
fool with you or something.
‐ Well, there’s nothing
they can take from me
by lying about this.
Senpai, I’m going to
try to do something
about this situation on my own,
so please don’t tell
anyone about it.
‐ Sure.
‐ [Miina] That was a pretty
modern school, don’t you think?
‐ [Karen] Yeah, you’re right.
‐ [Miina] What’s the matter?
‐ [Karen] Well, he
scolded us again.
‐ Mike can be a little
too short tempered.
I really wouldn’t
worry about it.
‐ No, I think anyone
would be upset.
He was living an ordinary life
and suddenly two total
strangers show up
and get in the way.
‐ We’re not just strangers.
There’s a pretty strong
possibility that we might be
related to Mike by blood.
‐ But it’s also
possible that we’re not.
At the very least I
think that’s going to
end up being the
case for one of us.
‐ [Miina] Can I
ask you something?
Are you regretting meeting Mike?
‐ [Karen] I don’t really‐‐
‐ [Miina] Was he different
from what you imagined?
‐ [Karen] Oh, no,
that’s not what I meant.
I mean, he is different but‐‐
‐ But you had a reason
to come here, didn’t you?
You knew this would happen,
but there was a reason you
went ahead and came anyway.
Am I right?
‐ Yes.
But, yeah, I understand.
‐ That we both have our reasons
and we just can’t
be so reckless.
I guess I knew that but...
When I thought Mike
might be my relative
I wanted to be spoiled.
‐ Yeah, me too.
‐ Hey, do you think
our mother lived here?
Do you think she gazed
across this lake too?
‐ Well, I don’t know about that.
But, it’s wonderful here.
‐ Then I think we should
take a good look at it.
We should engrave
the image in our eyes
and make memories of it.
I know.
(calm piano music)
‐ Great, I wonder where
they wandered off to.
They should be here.
Fine, who cares?
(keys clicking)
(calm orchestral music)
(thunder rumbles)
(rain patters)
(light orchestral music)
(Karen knocks)
‐ Excuse me, it’s Karen.
Mr. Mike, can I come in?
This won’t take
up too much time.
I’d like you to listen
to me for just a minute.
I’ve decided that I’m
going to go back home.
Ms. Miina told me that she
was going to go back home too.
I’m really sorry if Ms. Miina
and I caused you any trouble.
But I’m glad I got to spend
the night in the house
from the picture.
And I’m happy that I
got to meet somebody
who might be a relative.
Is it all right with
you if I come in?
Since there’s a
chance we’re related
I would like to
say goodbye to you.
(heavy piano music)
(Karen gasping)
Little Wonder.
(heavy piano music)
‐ I’m sorry, Mike.
Sorry, I’m just sneaking out.
It’s just that I’m no
good at saying goodbye
and I never have been.
(heavy piano music)
(door slides)
‐ Ms. Miina!
(Karen gasping)
(scooter hums)
Ms. Miina, look out!
(Mike gasps)
(tires screech)
‐ Why don’t you watch
where you’re going?
‐ What were you doing there?
‐ Huh?
‐ What’s this?
Are you going somewhere?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ [Mike] You just showed up
here, did as you pleased,
and now you’re sneaking away?
Don’t you think
that’s a bit much?
‐ I’m sorry for barging
in and staying here.
But just a little bit.
I thought I wanted
to rely on you
but I guess that was wrong.
See ya.
(scooter humming)
(light piano music)
‐ Why did my mother abandon me?
(Miina grunts)
When I was young I thought
about that all the time.
I really wanted to find out why.
But now, I just don’t care
about all that stuff, you know?
It’s not like I’m
gonna go and change
anything about my
life at this point
just because I find out
the reason why she left me.
‐ [Miina] What do you mean?
‐ So your saying
you don’t get it?
‐ No, I don’t get it!
‐ What matters is now!
(dramatic orchestral music)
You see, if the two
of us are actually
related by blood somehow,
I just don’t wanna let you go.
I don’t wanna abandon
someone I’m related to.
‐ Even though we
might be strangers?
‐ There’s a chance that
you’re a relative, right?
‐ That’s different than what
you were saying this morning.
(vibrant piano music)
So it’s all right?
‐ [Mike] Yeah.
‐ Do you really mean it?
‐ You’re rubbing it in now.
‐ I really wanna...
I really wanna thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for doing this.
(Miina sobbing)
(vibrant orchestral music)
‐ This is all gonna work
out for the best, Ms. Miina.
‐ [Mike] I have work so
I’m going back to my room.
I’m leaving getting dinner ready
and all that stuff to you.
‐ Okay, me too?
‐ Same for you, all right?
‐ All right.
‐ [Mike] We might
be related too.
(light orchestral music)
(scooter hums)
‐ You know what?
I think Mr. Mike was
out looking for us.
‐ I’m kind of upset though.
‐ Why do you say that?
‐ ’Cause he acted all cool.
‐ (laughs) I take
back anything I said
about him seeming a bit scary.
He’s not good at communicating
but he is very kind.
I found that out tonight.
‐ You did?
‐ Yes.
I saw it in his room.
‐ Mike!
I’m coming in!
‐ Why don’t you try
knocking instead?
(Miina chuckles)
What is it?
‐ I’ve come here to
pick up the lunch box.
(Miina giggles)
Oh, there it is.
Looks like you ate all of it!
(Mike groans)
(Miina laughs)
Hey, I thought
you hated pumpkin.
‐ Yeah, I do.
‐ Was it tasty?
‐ It was terrible.
‐ Whoa, you’re horrid!
(laughs) Just kidding.
(Mike grunting)
‐ [Mike] I told you
it was horrible.
‐ [Miina] But you ate it.
You ate all of it.
There’s not a crumb left.
‐ [Mike] I didn’t
wanna waste it.
‐ [Miina] Wasn’t it tasty?
‐ [Mike] I’m telling
you it was horrible.
‐ [Miina] You’re
not being honest.
‐ [Mike] I am too.
‐ [Miina] Oh, no, you’re
going to eat me, aren’t you?
‐ [Mike] What are
you talking about?
‐ [Miina] Danger, danger!
‐ [Mike] Shut up!
(singing in a foreign language)
‐ [Karen and Miina] Next
episode, more twins!
‐ [Miina] I, Miina Miyafuji,
had a dream about Mike.
I was worried about Mike’s
senpai who came to visit.
It’s that because
I’m his relative?
Or because I’m a stranger?
‐ [Karen] I, Karen Onodera,
had a really good reason
for coming all the way
here to Mr. Mike’s house.
I had a vague idea about it
but I was way too
afraid to confirm it.
And that reason is‐‐
‐ [Miina] Please
Twins! episode three,
We Might Be Strangers.
Be sure to watch it!
Next episode, more twins!