(rain pattering)
‐ It’s raining.
The Ballgame Festival’s been
canceled because it’s raining.
‐ No way!
You’ve gotta be kidding!
All my efforts were‐‐
‐ A complete waste of time.
(exasperated sigh)
‐ You don’t have to
be so blunt about it.
(door sliding)
‐ Everyone, listen up!
The Ballgame Festival’s been
canceled ’cause of rain!
Mr. Yamada said we
could all go home!
‐ Hey, that’s great!
‐ No!
I spent a week
helping my brother
with the secret training
he did for today!
‐ Wait, secret training?
‐ What kind of stuff did you do?
‐ Well, let’s see now.
(bright music)
We did some close‐contact
exercises and stretches
and other stuff like that.
(bell dinging)
(coy giggling)
‐ No!
Your brother is a pervert!
‐ Yes, she is!
(Karen giggling)
‐ It’s a shame that
the Ballgame Festival
was canceled, Miss
Miina, don’t you think?
‐ Yeah, I guess.
‐ Is there something the matter?
‐ No, I just, I hate rain.
‐ Well, your clothes
do get pretty wet.
‐ Oh, why do I even try
for a serious conversation?
(uptempo J‐pop music)
(bold music)
‐ [Mike] What’s with
the sudden blue sky
as soon as the Ballgame
Festival was canceled?
Damn it, I just don’t
feel like working today.
‐ [Miina] Well, then
how about we go out
and have some fun for a change?
It’s still before noon,
and Karen and I don’t have
to work today, so we’re free!
‐ Oh, Miss Miina,
that’s a wonderful idea!
‐ [Mike] Okay, I guess
we could do that.
(whimsical music)
(exasperated sigh)
‐ I’m sorry, I don’t
like scary things.
‐ You know what, Karen?
Something just occurred to me.
Your tastes are so
different from ours.
Maybe you are the stranger.
‐ Oh, Miss Miina, no,
please don’t say that!
‐ Miina!
‐ Relax, I’m only kidding!
‐ Hmm!
‐ Oh!
I’m sorry, but do you mind
if I go look at some clothes?
‐ No, of course not.
‐ [Karen] Oh, I love that brand!
‐ [Mike] Yeah, I see.
Hey, Karen, I’ll just be
waiting outside, okay?
‐ Thanks, Mr. Mike!
‐ I’m going too!
(crowd chatter)
(gentle whimsical music)
‐ Hey, Mike, I’m sorry!
‐ Damn, you’re late!
So how long do I
gotta wait out here?
‐ Actually, Karen’s still
kinda looking around.
(Mike sighing)
She seems to be the
indecisive type.
‐ So what?
You gonna make me
wait even longer?
‐ Don’t be silly!
I told her to meet
us here in an hour
so we can go do
whatever we want.
‐ Oh, okay.
You wanna go and have some tea
while we’re waiting for her?
‐ That’s such a
big waste of money!
Why don’t we just
buy some drinks
and head out to the park?
‐ Sounds good, all right.
‐ [Miina Voiceover] I
gotta thank Karen for this!
‐ Sorry, did you say something?
‐ Uh, no!
No, nothing at all!
(quiet sigh)
‐ Well, miss, have you decided?
Miss, oh, miss?
‐ [Miina] And now that
Shimazaki has started dating
Vice President Tsubaki,
Akina’s group has
gotten really depressed!
They totally had
it in their heads
that you and he were
some kind of an item.
Let me put it this way,
they were so sure that
Haruku actually came up to me
and said, "You do know that
Shimazaki is bi, right?"
You know, I don’t think she
even knows what that means.
You don’t like
talking much, huh?
‐ It’s not that.
It’s just that I’m
really not used to it.
You know, spending so
much quiet time like this.
‐ Yeah, well, I’m not sure
this place is all that quiet.
(crowd chatter)
(quiet gasp)
Oh, Mike, look over there!
It’s Miss Kazami, and
she’s with her boyfriend!
‐ [Mike] Isn’t that her husband?
You really shouldn’t
stare at them.
‐ I can’t stop!
Oh!
(can clanging)
(disappointed groan)
‐ You’re so stupid.
‐ Oh, fine, call me stupid.
But I still had a
lot of ice tea left.
(surprised gasp)
‐ Here.
You take it.
‐ Okay.
(pensive music)
(quiet gasp)
‐ [Mike] And don’t
drink all of it.
(surprised gasp)
‐ Well, of course I won’t!
You ruined it!
‐ I what?
‐ Nothing, okay?
‐ How come you’re pouting, then?
So let me see your face.
‐ No way!
‐ Do what I said!
‐ I won’t!
‐ [Mike] Miina!
(quiet gasp)
(awed gasp)
(quiet gasping)
‐ I...
(quiet gasp)
I...
(tense music)
‐ [Karen] Miss Miina?
(blade sheathing)
Oh, Miss Miina!
I’m afraid you’ve violated
Love Alliance rule number one.
I can’t forgive such action!
(heavy slice)
(anguished scream)
‐ She’ll cut me up!
‐ Huh?
What are you saying?
‐ Oh?
(crowd chattering)
‐ [Mizuho] Mr. Kamishiro?
(coy laughter)
‐ Well, hello there.
(nervous giggling)
Thanks a lot, Miina.
I really didn’t need
that embarrassment
you put me through.
‐ [Miina] I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, Karen.
I very nearly kissed Mike.
If I hadn’t suddenly remembered
about you and the Love Alliance,
I’m sure that I would have.
I would have.
Oh, what should I do?
I can’t seem to control myself
when I’m alone with Mike!
‐ [Radio] Inter‐high
school tournament
to be held in Matsumoto this
year is only a week away!
From all over the country,
many of the nation’s
finest young athletes
have begun to gather‐‐
‐ Oh, right.
It’s that time of year again.
‐ In preparation
for the opening ceremonies
and the start of competition.
‐ Huh, hey, Mike?
Where are you?
Did he just go ahead without me?
It’ll be okay, as long as
I get back to the boutique.
So while...
Hey, wait, where
is the boutique?
(quiet sigh)
‐ [Mike] Karen!
‐ Mr. Mike, I’m sorry I kept
you waiting for so long.
‐ Don’t worry about it.
Has Miina shown up here yet?
‐ I haven’t seen her in a while.
Is something the matter?
‐ I think she got lost.
But I’m sure she’ll show up
if we stay here for a while.
I don’t want to miss each other
by going off to look for her.
(pensive music)
‐ Tsubaki, can’t you just try
to be a little bit friendlier?
I mean, this is supposed
to be a date, you know.
‐ Would you please stop
assuming that this is a date?
‐ But I thought that, I
mean, I didn’t think I was‐‐
‐ Ah‐ha!
Oh?
This is no time for me
to be snooping on anyone.
(crowd chatter)
‐ Miss Miina still isn’t here.
‐ Nope.
Hey, you didn’t buy any clothes?
‐ No, I found
something that I liked,
but it was kinda over my budget.
‐ You know, I could help
you a bit if you want me to.
‐ No, no, thank you.
I’m already freeloading
at your place.
I couldn’t take
any more from you.
‐ Hey, don’t be so standoffish.
It’s quite possible that you
and I just might be family.
‐ Yeah, and it’s possible
we might be strangers.
‐ Hey, stop saying
things like that.
‐ If we were strangers...
‐ Yeah?
‐ What would you do
if weren’t related?
(exasperated sigh)
‐ I wouldn’t do anything,
just normal stuff.
Like I’ve always done, I guess.
‐ I just don’t think...
(pensive music)
I would be able to act like
nothing had changed between us.
‐ Of course I’m
sure that it’d be
a little bit awkward
for us at first.
‐ That’s not what I
was talking about.
I mean I didn’t...
I’m sorry for saying
such weird things.
(surprised gasp)
He must’ve really hated
what I was saying.
Oh?
‐ Here.
‐ [Karen] Mr. Mike!
‐ I asked the salesperson,
so I’m sure this is it.
This is the new outfit
that you wanted, right?
‐ Oh.
(surprised gasp)
(quiet crying)
‐ What’s wrong?
Karen, how can you cry?
‐ You can’t keep
being so sweet to me,
or I won’t be able to
restrain myself any longer.
‐ [Mike] What are
you talking about?
‐ I mean I‐‐
I mean I‐‐
‐ Karen!
(pistol cocking)
Karen!
You realize you’re
in clear violation
of Love Alliance
rule number one!
I’m sorry, I can’t
let that slide.
(loud bang)
(anguished scream)
(Karen squealing)
‐ Hey!
Yeah, this is ridiculous!
Why are you passing out now?
Hey, Karen, wake up!
(crowd chattering)
‐ Uh, don’t mind us,
everything’s fine!
She gets lightheaded sometimes!
(nervous laughter)
(sighing) Gimme a break!
(crowd chattering)
(footsteps patting)
‐ Oh?
Uh‐oh.
At least I finally
found the boutique,
but I’m so late,
they left without me!
(gentle music)
‐ What am I gonna do?
I can’t just leave Karen
alone when she’s like this.
But what about Miina?
She can be so clueless.
‐ [Haruko] Oh, look, it’s Karen!
Hey, so what’s wrong with Karen?
Is she asleep?
‐ I’m glad that you’re here.
Can I ask the two of you to
watch Karen for a little while?
‐ Uh, yeah.
‐ Great, thanks.
‐ Whoa, wait a second!
We were just about to
go in and watch a movie!
‐ Ah, come on, Senpai!
This is important!
‐ Well, since you
put it that way.
(crowd chatter)
‐ Where in the hell
could Miina be?
Yeah.
(bright music)
(quiet grumbling)
(tired gasp)
‐ [Karen] Mr. Mike?
‐ No, silly!
It’s me, Matugu Shido!
(surprised gasp)
(loud scream)
‐ Mr. Pervert!
‐ How dare you say that!
‐ Oh, calm down, Karen!
He’s quite safe!
My brother is more of a
closet pervert, you know?
‐ You too, Haruko?
(crowd chattering)
(birds singing)
‐ They’re not here, either.
Karen wasn’t at the
boutique when I checked.
It’s possible that they
might have already...
(romantic music)
‐ Hey, Miina.
We’re gonna head on home
now in lovey‐dovey mode.
‐ Oh, Miss Miina, I hereby
disband the Love Alliance.
(quiet sigh)
‐ It’s just a fantasy.
I can’t believe I’m
thinking this way.
This is just ridiculous!
I’m stupid like Mike said I was.
(crowd chattering)
‐ Mr. Mike must be
with Miss Miina.
(romantic music)
‐ Hey, Karen.
We’re gonna head on home
now in lovey‐dovey mode.
‐ Oh, Karen, I hereby
disband the Love Alliance.
‐ Oh, no!
Please take me with you.
Don’t leave me all alone!
(sentimental music)
(slide whistle)
(loud slurping)
(quiet sobbing)
‐ Hey, guys, where’s Karen?
‐ She’s gone off.
I don’t know where.
‐ Man.
Darn it.
(video games beeping)
‐ Oh, Mike, Karen.
‐ Mr. Mike, oh, Miss Miina.
(phone ringing)
(phone receiver slamming)
‐ Terrific, they’re
not home, either.
Well, is it possible
something bad happened?
Miina, Karen.
(sinister music)
‐ Help me, Mike, please!
‐ Oh, Mr. Mike!
‐ Why don’t you ride
with me ’til the morning?
Come on!
(loud slam)
(surprised gasp)
‐ Hey, you’re that
guy in the red Chaser!
(girl screaming)
You bastard!
‐ What?
What did I do?
‐ [Miina Voiceover] I hate it.
I hate being alone.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] I really
don’t like being alone.
‐ I hate it.
‐ [Mike] Don’t you
be popping up on me
at a crazy time like
this, you got it?
‐ Wha, what the hell?
I don’t know what
your problem is,
but you’re making a big mistake!
(exasperated sigh)
‐ Damn it, I just don’t
get how it’s come to this.
(melancholy music)
‐ [Miina Voiceover] Mike.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] Mr. Mike.
‐ [Mike] Miina, Karen.
Miina.
Karen.
Miina and Karen.
Miina, Karen!
I’m standing right over here!
Mike Kamishiro is right here!
Where are you,
where have you gone?
Hey!
Hear me!
I’m standing right here!
Miina!
‐ Oh, is that Mike?
‐ [Mike] Karen!
‐ Oh, Mr. Mike?
(bright music)
(rapid breathing)
‐ Mike!
‐ Mr. Mike!
(surprised gasp)
‐ [Mike] Miina!
Karen!
‐ Karen!
‐ Oh, Miss Miina!
‐ Oh, no!
(surprised gasp)
(worried gasp)
(all screaming)
‐ Where have you been?
‐ Mr. Mike!
‐ Oh, Mike!
(both sobbing)
‐ Oh, geez.
(pained grumbling)
Oh?
‐ Kamishiro!
How could you in
such a public place?
‐ Well, my hats
off to you, Mike.
You know even I couldn’t
possibly top anything like that.
‐ You can see their undies!
(joyous crying)
(nervous gasp)
(exasperated gasp)
‐ Today is the worst day.
(crickets chirping)
‐ Hey, Karen, I’m envious.
Mike was really nice and
bought you some clothes.
‐ I’m so sorry.
‐ [Miina] Oh, well.
‐ So it’s all right with you?
‐ Actually, I...
I very nearly kissed Mike.
Out in the park.
‐ What?
No fair!
‐ I’m telling you this
per our Love Alliance
rules and regulations.
‐ Okay, but that’s not
really the point, is it?
‐ No, but he bought
you those clothes!
(sentimental music)
(quiet gasp)
‐ All right, no
more cheating, okay?
‐ You too, Karen.
(coy giggling)
‐ [Both] Hey, why don’t we agree
that everything that happened
today never really happened?
(quizzical gasp)
(coy giggling)
(both laughing)
(birds singing)
(bright music)
‐ Hey, Mike!
Let’s go out and
have some fun again.
‐ [Karen] Yeah, let’s all
go out together again!
‐ [Mike] Nope,
never gonna happen.
‐ Ah, what?
‐ Mr. Mike, that’s terrible!
‐ [Mike] Terrible’s fine by me.
(Miina giggling)
(exasperated sigh)
‐ [Miina] If we stay
like this next time‐‐
‐ [Karen] We’ll never lose
sight of each other again!
(frustrated gasp)
‐ [Mike] You think I’d be able
to walk around town like this?
Let me go!
‐ We’ll lose sight
of each other.
‐ It’ll be bad if
someone gets lost.
‐ Like that would happen when
we’re just going to school!
‐ [Miina] Oh well, it might!
‐ [Karen] You know, there
is a chance that it would.
‐ [Mike] Ah, geez.
‐ [Girl] Miyafuji?
‐ Huh?
‐ Oh?
‐ It is you, right?
‐ [Miina] Yuka?
‐ Miina, to see you again
in a place like this!
What a coincidence!
‐ Yuka.
‐ I was so worried about you.
You disappeared so suddenly.
I’ve missed you.
(Yuka giggling)
(birds singing)
(uptempo J‐pop music)
‐ [Both] Next
episode, more twins!
‐ [Miina] To think that I’d
see Yuka there, of all places.
‐ [Karen] She’s a person that
knows about Miss Miina’s past.
The past that we
don’t know about.
‐ It’s all right.
I’m all right.
‐ [Karen] Tell us what
happened, please, Miss Miina?
‐ I don’t want them to know.
Not Mike and not Karen.
I don’t want them or anyone
else to know about me.
‐ [Karen] Oh, Miss Miina.
Please Twins episode
10: I Want To Run Again.
Be sure to watch it.
Next episode, more twins!