(soft whimsical music)
‐ My dearest uncle, I
know that its been awhile
but I’m finally writing.
By the way, this
is Karen Onodera.
Right now I am happy
and doing well,
living in Mr. Mike’s house.
Its very nice here.
During the day, I’ve
spending my time
studying for entrance
exams with Ms. Miina
so that we can transfer
into the same high school
that Mr. Mike goes to
and then in the afternoon,
I have a job working at a store
called Harikawa Groceries
that’s not too far
from our house.
Of course, Ms. Miina
is with when I work.
I think Mr. Mike might of
taken on too many programming
jobs because he looks like
he’s very busy all the time.
There are so many things
that I’m not used to here
and I do make mistakes sometimes
but please rest assured
that I’m doing my very best.
Uncle, although I am writing
this to you right now,
I don’t think you
will ever receive it
but I just had to write
something to someone.
(low electronic music)
Because from today on,
to the school that
Mr. Mike attends,
the three of us
will go together.
(upbeat electronic music)
(singing in Japanese)
‐ Well um, uh.
Transfer students.
Try to be nice to them.
‐ I’m Miina MiyaFuji.
How do you do?
‐ Um, my names Karen Onodera.
(kids shouting and cheering)
‐ Very cute is right.
(low tense music)
‐ Hey, Mike, heck of a
greeting their getting,
isn’t it?
Are you worried?
‐ I’m worried they
might cause problems,
that’s all.
‐ Oh I see.
(bell ringing)
(kids shouting)
‐ Mr. Yamada!
(bell ringing)
‐ Um I uh, hi hi hi.
Hey there.
So, where you guys from?
If you need anything, just ask.
I’ll help you out.
‐ You know, my house
is real close to here
so you guys‐‐
‐ Now you guys
leave them alone.
‐ [All] Welcome to our school.
‐ My name is Akina Sagawawa.
‐ I’m Futaba Mashita.
‐ And I’m Haruko Shidou.
‐ Nice to meet you.
‐ I’m very happy to
meet you as well.
‐ Hey wait, MiyaFuji
and Onodera,
you’re the two girls
who are somehow related
to Mike Kamashiro
over in the next class
aren’t you?
‐ Yeah that’s right.
‐ Wait, how do you
guys know that?
(giggling)
‐ Well the entire school
knows about it by now.
‐ Well then, there’s
something I would like
you to tell us.
It’s about Kamishiro
and Shimazaki.
Do they hang around at home too?
‐ Shimazaki?
‐ What do you mean by that?
‐ I mean the two of
them are always together
and they always seem to be
having such a good time,
you know?
‐ We couldn’t help
fantasizing about them.
‐ Hey guys, we’re
not fantasizing.
They’re gay!
‐ [Both] No!
‐ No way.
‐ I don’t get it.
‐ What?
Am I couple with Shimazaki?
You mean you guys
called me out here
just to ask an idiotic
question like that?
‐ Well yeah, the girls in my
class were spreading rumors.
Right?
‐ Yes.
‐ This is stupid.
Its totally untrue, of course.
‐ But Mike, don’t be silly.
There is no smoke where
there is no flame burning.
‐ Don’t just show up
here out of nowhere
and start saying
things that add fuel
to the fire.
‐ So there really is a flame?
‐ No there isn’t.
‐ Hey, are you the one?
‐ I’m afraid that I’m the guy
that’s rumored to have a
special relationship with Mike.
I’m Kousei Shimazaki.
‐ How do you do?
I’m Miina Miyafuji.
‐ And I’m Karen Onodera.
‐ A pleasure and no need
sticking to formalities,
you can just call me Kousei.
‐ Sure.
I mean.
‐ Nice to meet you, Shimazaki.
‐ Just what I expected
from Mike’s relatives.
When it comes to
not being honest,
you’re all alike.
‐ What do you mean by that?
‐ I mean that its pretty
obvious to me, Mike,
that these two are
in love with you.
‐ What?
‐ Stop saying ridiculous
things like that.
I mean it.
Hey, I want you two to
stop blushing right now.
(girl meows)
Ah, stop with the mews.
‐ Well I trust
that the two of you
will take good care of him.
‐ Don’t you ever
listen to anyone?
‐ As long as you two girls
are living here with him
I can finally relax.
It will keep anyone
strange from approaching
our little Mike.
‐ What are you talking about?
‐ About the future,
the one between you and me.
‐ I should just.
‐ We can’t.
People are watching.
‐ [Mike] Don’t you understand?
‐ [Shimazaki] Of course I do.
‐ [Mike] Stop that.
‐ You know, this
is the first time
I’ve seen someone like
that in real life.
‐ And this is the first
time I’ve seen one
outside comic books.
‐ [Girl] Wait, do you mean
Mike Kamishiro in class B?
‐ [Girl] Yeah.
‐ [Girl] Well I do think
he’s really attractive
but you know, he can be
rather hard to approach.
I even think Shimazaki
may be his only friend
at this school, so all in all.
From what I’ve heard,
he doesn’t accept
any gifts from girls
and has never even
been seen with a girl.
So maybe those rumors
about him are true.
‐ You know I think its just
like what Mike’s homeroom
teacher was saying
the other day,
he lives sort of an
outlaw life at school.
‐ But maybe.
‐ Maybe what?
Karen?
‐ Well um, maybe Mr.
Mike isn’t interested
in girls at all, if
you know what I mean?
‐ What?
‐ I mean, boys are always
flirting with girls right
and they’re always trying
to get girls to notice them?
‐ Well I think that’s
right but I’m not sure.
‐ On TV, boys are always trying
to steal the girls laundry
and peek into their baths
to see them naked.
‐ But that’s against the law.
‐ Oh no, Mr. Mike.
He may not be a
normal boy anymore.
‐ Well I think Karen’s
really starting to lose it.
‐ [Girl] Kamishiro.
‐ Ms. Miina, no
please you can’t.
I’m just not mentally ready yet.
‐ Hey you, over here.
‐ Oh, hi Sinpai, are
you on the swim team?
‐ No I’m not.
‐ You see, this
afternoon the pool area
has been rented out just
for the student council.
‐ Hey wait, that’s a total
abuse of power isn’t it?
You sure its alright?
‐ Its perfectly fine.
I gave them permission.
‐ Ah, Ms. Kasumi, hello.
= what’s wrong?
‐ Well I.
I guess I’m starting to think
that I just can’t believe
in you anymore, ma’am.
‐ Really?
Really?
‐ He seems to be having
a normal conversation
and like you said before,
poor Mike may not
be a normal boy.
‐ Its bad to have a
normal conversation?
‐ Look at who he’s talking to.
I hate to say this
because it irritates me
but he’s talking to
a high school girl
with a great figure.
(sultry rock music)
A beautiful teacher with
tons of sexy adult charm.
And a super Lolita
that could easily pass
for a grade school girl.
He’s surrounded
by beautiful women
of the same caliber as
the three sacred trashers
but he shows no interest.
‐ Oh my goodness, this
really is a problem.
‐ I know.
‐ Ms. Miina, I think we
should do whatever we can
to help Mr. Mike rediscover
the normal feelings
of being a boy.
‐ How do we do it?
‐ It doesn’t matter how.
Working hard for the
sake of a relative
is just what families do.
‐ You know you’re right.
‐ And so?
‐ And so could you please
come up with a plan?
‐ Hey, Kamishiro, would
you care to join us
in the swimming pool?
‐ No, thank you.
I don’t have a swim suit.
‐ We can lend you
one if you like?
‐ Thanks a lot but I got to go.
‐ You don’t have to swim
if you don’t want to.
‐ No thanks.
I have work to do.
‐ Well.
‐ You got to admit,
Kamishiro’s a tough opponent.
‐ As a teacher here, I
would just like to say that
he’s a serious guy.
‐ Calm down, calm down.
Calm down.
(giggles)
‐ Oh.
Dear Mike, my heart
races at the thought
at just how stoic you are.
(soft instrumental music)
‐ [Miina] We will
execute these plans
the day after tomorrow.
‐ We’re really doing
this, Ms. Miina?
‐ Yes, for Mike.
‐ yeah, this is for mike.
I’ll do it.
I’ll do it for Mr. Mike.
‐ If I can keep this up.
‐ Mike.
‐ What do you want?
‐ I start swimming
classes tomorrow.
So I thought I’d try it on.
What do you think?
How do I look?
‐ I, I think that you
look perfectly normal.
‐ Oh I’m glad.
‐ Calm down, I just
said it was normal.
‐ Mr. Mike, would you
tell me what you think
about mine?
‐ There’s nothing
strange about it.
‐ Oh thank you so much.
‐ Karen, did you know your
strap is flipped over?
‐ Ms. Miina, could
you please fix it?
‐ [Miina] Wow Karen, your
skin is so white and smooth.
‐ [Karen] Wait a minute,
if you lower it too far.
‐ [Miina] Maybe I’ll
touch something important.
‐ [Karen] No, don’t.
‐ Hey!
Please do things like that
back in your own room, alright?
‐ Hey, Ms. Miina, I
think I’m starting
to get sleepy.
‐ Oh then lets take a nap.
‐ Okay.
‐ [Mike Voiceover]
It’s not even noon yet.
Damn it.
‐ [Miina] Goodnight, Mike.
‐ What?
Wait?
You are not sleeping in my bed.
‐ What?
What’s the matter?
‐ [Mike] Get out.
You’re interrupting my work.
‐ Mike, wait a minute.
‐ Mr. Mike.
‐ [Mike Voiceover]
Just calm down.
(soft instrumental music)
(grunting)
(groaning)
‐ I’ve about had it.
I can’t believe all
the embarrassing things
we’ve had to go through
and Mike hasn’t reacted
to a single one.
‐ Ms. Miina, I’m
no longer confidant
that I’ll lead a
normal life as a woman.
‐ Yeah, well.
Our plan didn’t work
out like we thought.
We need a drama.
Something that will
heighten his emotions.
‐ Drama?
Are you sure?
‐ Yes, a drama.
‐ Hello, can I buy this?
‐ We’ll go through with
it at school tomorrow.
‐ Um, yes.
‐ Hello?
‐ One of thems a relative.
One of thems a relative.
(groaning)
‐ Oh Mike, you look exhausted
or are you sexually frustrated?
‐ I beg you, just
leave me alone.
‐ As you wish.
‐ Girls from Class A
are having swim class
fourth period.
‐ [Boy] I can’t wait to
see those transfer students
in swimsuits.
(overlapping chatter)
‐ Alright ladies, since
the phys ed teacher
is home sick with the flu today,
I will be teaching the class.
‐ Do you get the feeling
that there are really only
two teachers working
this high school?
‐ Yeah, very much so.
‐ Why don’t we take this
time to freely play around
in the swimming pool?
(blows whistle)
(upbeat pop music)
(kids laughing)
‐ Okay, me first.
‐ Hey, what are you
doing over there?
‐ [All] Crap, crap.
‐ What am I doing here
is the real question.
‐ Yup, yup you’re
so cute, Haruko.
(groaning)
You’re so cute, Haruko.
(bell ringing)
‐ I’m so tired right now.
I want to go home.
‐ Mr. Mike!
‐ Look, I’m sorry Karen,
would you leave me alone?
‐ Ms. Miina’s been hurt.
‐ What happened, Karen?
Is Miina alright?
‐ Ms. Miina was accosted
by one of the boys.
(somber instrumental music)
And she was dragged
into the locker room.
I couldn’t move.
I was just so scared.
‐ Are you serious?
Damn it!
Miina!
(somber instrumental music)
Are you okay?
Miina.
‐ Hi, Mike.
I’m sorry, I’m sorry.
‐ Are you hurt anywhere?
Miina, did they do
something to you?
‐ It was awfully close but no.
I fought, I fought
as hard as I could.
‐ I see.
I’m really glad.
Yeah, I’m glad that you’re okay.
‐ Mike.
‐ Yeah, I’m really glad
that you’re alright.
Oh Miina, I’m so glad.
‐ Mike, I, I wanna.
‐ It’s alright.
You don’t have to say anything.
‐ I’m sorry.
‐ Miina, why are
you apologizing?
‐ Because I didn’t think
you’d be so worried.
I didn’t realize.
I’m so sorry.
‐ Miina?
‐ Mike I, I just.
I want.
‐ Uh I.
(gasps)
‐ No, you got to stop.
Don’t go any further than that.
(shouts)
(groaning)
‐ Karen, what’s your problem?
‐ No.
(mews)
‐ Karen?
‐ No!
‐ Did something bad happen?
‐ What’s the matter, Mike?
‐ [Miina] No!
‐ What is the meaning
of all this, Mike?
I thought you
understood you have me.
‐ That’s not the point, Kousei,
so why don’t you be quiet?
Mike Kamishiro, these young
girls are your relatives.
Its a crime what you’re doing.
A big crime.
‐ This was an accident,
just an accident.
(mews)
‐ Yeah but, she looks
like she’s really happy.
‐ But I don’t know why.
‐ No!
‐ Oh my handsome darling, Mike.
‐ What in the world are
you guys doing in here?
‐ Ms. Kazami.
‐ Madam President.
‐ [Mike Voiceover]
So I get slapped
with a three day suspension.
What kind of excuse
am I gonna be able
to make for the
orphanage director?
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
Me and Mr. Mike
with Mr. Mike.
‐ [Miina Voiceover] I.
I.
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
Mr. Mike and I,
we might just be relatives.
‐ [Miina Voiceover] I
might just be relatives
with mike.
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
But then, I would like
to believe that it was
fate that made it possible
for me to finally meet
Mr. Mike like I did.
‐ [Miina Voiceover] It was
sheer luck that I met Mike
but to me it was pure fate.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] I
want to be with Mr. Mike.
‐ [Miina Voiceover] I
want to be with Mike.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] Is
this feeling of mine
really selfish?
‐ [Miina Voiceover] Am I being
selfish feeling this way?
Is it selfish?
‐ [Karen Voiceover] But I,
but I can’t stop it anymore.
‐ [Miina Voiceover] I
can’t stop it anymore.
‐ [Both Voiceover]
I can’t stop it.
I can’t stop this feeling.
(energetic pop music)
(singing in Japanese)
‐ [Both] Next
episode, more twins.
‐ [Miina Voiceover]
I really kissed Mike.
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
I experienced a
kiss with Mr. Mike.
We might be relatives.
[Miina Voiceover] We
might be relatives
but then if we’re strangers?
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
If we are strangers.
‐ [Both Voiceover]
We can fall in love.
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
This feeling that I have
can no longer be stopped.
‐ [Narrator] Please Twins
episode six, Love Alliance.
Be sure to watch it.
Next episode, more twins.