‐ [Mike] What really matters
to us is the present,
not the past.
(birds chirping)
Miina, if you and I are
truly related by blood,
then I don’t ever wanna let
you go, Miina, understand?
I don’t ever wanna
abandon a relative.
‐ But, Mike, what
if it turns out
we’re nothing but strangers?
What would you do then?
(gasps)
‐ You know what I’d do.
‐ Mike, no, this
is embarrassing.
‐ It’s all right.
‐ But.
‐ [Mike] All right.
‐ [Miina] There.
Stop it!
Oh.
(eyes clicking)
It was a dream, a
silly little dream.
But to have a dream
like that, I must.
Oh.
Ew!
(gasps)
I’m sorry!
I was having a strange dream!
I don’t swing that way!
Really.
(popping)
(gasping)
That’s a.
I’m so sorry, I’m
sorry, I’m so sorry.
I gotta get a hold of myself!
(grunting)
‐ Shut up!
(Please Twins! Opening Theme)
(singing in Japanese)
♪ Kitto meguriawaseta ♪
♪ Tenshi no hon no
kimagure da yo ♪
♪ Sanpomichi de
fuita suna kaze ♪
♪ Kokoro ga hayatteku ♪
♪ Setunasa Hagurakasu no
ni wa nareteru no ni ♪
♪ Konna toki dake namida
ga tomerarenai no wa ♪
♪ Naze darou ♪
♪ Aimai na kisetsu dakara koso ♪
♪ Kasuka na tezawari
Kokoro de kanjite ♪
♪ Kagirareta toki
wo ikiru kara ♪
♪ Tatanda tsubasa wo
ima sugu hirogete ♪
♪ Tatoe niji ga kowaretemo ♪
♪ Sora wa matteiru ♪
(upbeat music)
(cicadas singing)
‐ One set of futons
are the minimum items
needed for everyday
life, 43,560 yen.
Total, including
sales tax, 45,738 yen.
The two of you can pay me back
for all that by taking care
of all the household chores
for as long as you stay here.
You can decide between
yourselves who’s
gonna do what chore.
And I will use the time you
guys are doing your chores
to get all of my
programming work finished.
Any questions?
‐ No, none at all.
‐ None over here.
‐ Okay, I’ve got
one more condition,
we call each other by
first name, no titles.
I just don’t want anyone
making a big deal about this.
‐ In other words, "Karen"
and "Mike" and nothing else?
‐ Yeah, that’s exactly it, good.
And I’ll just call you
"Miina" and "Karen."
‐ Oh, I, I mean, I get it.
Miss Miina, Mister Mike.
‐ Lose the Miss and Mister part.
‐ I’m sorry.
‐ What’s that on your neck?
‐ Oh, that’s just something
that you shouldn’t ask about.
(laughs)
‐ Right, whatever.
Well, I’ll be up
workin’ in my room.
I’ll just leave you
two deal with the rest.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
If the phone rings,
don’t answer it.
‐ Whatever you say.
(phone ringing)
(gasping)
‐ I got it!
Coming!
‐ I just told you
not to answer it!
‐ Oh.
‐ Yes, I know that.
I’ll make sure to
send the data today.
Yes.
Yes, goodbye, and thank you.
(beeping)
Guess I should start.
‐ I just made some coffee,
would you like some?
‐ I’d really
appreciate it if you
would knock before coming in.
And you don’t need to bring
me coffee and stuff like that.
‐ Okay, but since I went
ahead and made you a cup
I can leave it here
for you, right?
‐ Sure, fine.
‐ What kinda program is that?
(softly gasps)
‐ You wouldn’t
understand if I told you.
‐ Why do you have to be so mean?
‐ You know, I’ve really got
a lotta work to get done.
‐ Oh.
‐ Miina, why are you
blushing like that?
‐ Uh, what, it’s
nothing, really!
Nothing at all.
I’m sorry I bothered you
while you were working.
I promise it’ll
never happen again.
‐ What was that all about?
(ice cubes rattle)
(gasps)
(sips)
(softly gasps)
This is good.
‐ This can’t be, I’m.
That’s impossible!
Oh.
You didn’t happen to be there
watching for a while were you?
‐ Uh, yeah, pretty much.
U‐Um, Miss Miina,
about Mister Mike.
(gasps)
‐ It’s, It’s not what you think!
This is the first
time I’ve met a
relative and I’m
just on cloud nine.
See, I had a lot going on,
and I haven’t had a lot of
happy things happen to me.
Well, it is true that
I think Mike is a
rather dependable guy,
and I’ve got to admit,
I was really surprised when
he showed up in my dreams,
but it’s not at all
what it sounds like!
It’s nothing like that at all.
‐ There’s a chance Mister
Mike may be your relative.
‐ Yeah, that’s right.
‐ But, then again, he
might be just a stranger.
‐ Uh.
‐ Miss Miina, if Mister
Mike was a stranger,
what would you do?
‐ Oh, well, I don’t know.
‐ Your mind is set, isn’t it?
‐ I haven’t even
thought about it!
‐ But if we are strangers,
we’re gonna have
to leave this house right away.
(spring bouncing)
‐ I get it.
Our conversations
aren’t meshing.
‐ What isn’t meshing?
(doorbell ringing)
(gasping)
‐ Coming!
‐ I’ll get that.
Wait a second, what
are you guys doing?
‐ Well, uh.
‐ A secret meeting.
(doorbell ringing)
‐ Hello there,
who’s at the door?
‐ It’s Senpai.
‐ Kamishiro, can I come in?
(cicadas singing)
(bell chiming)
Kamishiro, the promise we
made about those club budgets
was that you would have
them done last week.
I remember we were
really clear about that.
So I was wondering if something
might be wrong with you.
‐ I’m sorry, my paid job
has got me kind of busy.
Is there any way at
all it could wait?
I could have it Monday evening.
‐ That’s fine, I really
don’t mind waiting.
‐ That’s a big help.
‐ Uh, who?
‐ Hm.
‐ Oh, I’m so sorry.
My name is Tsubaki Oribe,
and I’m one year
ahead of Kamishiro.
So are you getting accustomed to
life here, Miss Miina Miyafuji?
‐ Hey, wait a second,
how do you know my name?
‐ [Tsubaki] Our student
body president has
an amazing information network.
It’s a secret as to why
it’s so amazing, though.
‐ I’d really appreciate
it if you would
tell President Morino
to take it easy on me.
(laughs)
‐ Okay, Mike, I’ll tell her.
‐ Excuse me, can I assume you’re
done with your business here?
‐ Yes.
‐ Good, ’cause Mike has
a lot of work to do.
‐ So it’s just Mike is it?
‐ Hey, it’s all right because
Mike and I are relatives.
Right?
‐ Not so close!
‐ It’s all right, if you
really are his relative.
But there’s a chance that
you’re just a stranger.
And if you’re just a
stranger, then Miss Miyafuji,
it seems that all
you’re doing is unfairly
imposing yourself
onto Kamishiro.
‐ Oh.
That’s, that’s
really not the case!
‐ So you say.
‐ Anyway, if you’re
through her then‐‐
‐ Um, I thought everyone
might be a little thirsty.
‐ Oh, don’t mind me, but
since you so kindly offered,
I’ll be happy to
have some, I guess.
(groans softly)
‐ Oh, sure, of course.
There really isn’t
very much to it.
‐ Is something wrong
with your neck?
(gasps)
‐ That’s something you really
shouldn’t ask me about.
Miss Miina, your face
looks very scary.
‐ Well, I was born this way!
‐ Oh, I see, I’m sorry.
‐ What the heck are they doing?
‐ That’s delicious.
Wow, what’s the source
of this mineral water?
‐ It’s nothing but
plain tap water.
‐ That’s right,
’cause we’re poor.
‐ Yeah, ever since
you two moved in.
(dinging)
‐ Uh.
‐ Wait, Kamishiro,
that’s just not
something that you say
to a potential relative.
Well, maybe they’re
strangers after all.
(groans)
‐ U‐Um, I know, how about
something nice to snack on?
I’ve already eaten a bit of it,
but would you like to try some?
‐ [Tsubaki] Oh, Prech?
‐ Yes, it’s an old
favorite of mine.
(whining)
Uh, Little Wonder!
‐ Where did this
thing come from?
It’s so cute!
‐ Yeah, he sure is.
‐ How is it you’re
so familiar with it?
This is strange, in fact,
this is really strange!
‐ Oh, come on, you
don’t know about it?
This little thing appears all
the time around this area.
‐ Don’t make it sound so simple.
‐ Well I’d expect nothing less
from a place that
had a big UFO craze!
‐ I’ve heard that everyone
at school calls it "Marie."
‐ So it’s Mister Marie.
(whining)
‐ Oh, it reacted!
‐ This is absurd,
don’t you think so?
‐ Oh, I don’t know.
‐ It’s holding a floater!
‐ Yeah, so what,
it’s still cute.
‐ But it’s eating Prech!
‐ He must be an omnivore.
‐ A what?
Oh, no, I gotta work!
‐ Kamishiro, I’m fine, you
don’t have to worry about me.
‐ But first I’ve gotta deal
with this strange thing.
‐ But, Mike, you’re
gonna miss your deadline.
‐ Yeah, I know that.
(whining)
Don’t wave at me!
Dammit.
(cicadas singing)
‐ I guess Mike has
gone back to work.
‐ I suppose that means
you’ll be going home now/
‐ Oh my, I’d nearly forgotten.
When my mother heard I was
coming here to visit Kamishiro,
she insisted that I bring
these buckwheat noodles.
‐ Oh, I see.
Thank you, that’s very nice.
Well, then.
‐ She also wanted the noodles
cooked in a special way.
(sighs)
‐ She planned this.
‐ What was that?
‐ Oh, nothing.
‐ Miss Miina, isn’t that nice?
It’s a free lunch!
(laughs)
‐ So it is.
(typing)
‐ Man, I only have
one hour left.
But what’s goin’ on downstairs?
(phone ringing)
What now, another bad day?
Yeah, hello, Kamishiro here.
Wait a minute, are you possibly?
(crunching)
(whining)
(playful music)
‐ Hm.
Miss Morino, is that
you standing there?
‐ Oh, hi, Miss Kazami.
‐ What are you doing here,
and what’s with the telescope?
‐ Just doing some bird watching.
‐ [Kazami] Ah.
Hold on, that’s a lie, right?
‐ [Morino] Yes, of course.
(cicadas singing)
‐ Thank you, we’ll gladly
take all these noodles,
but I really insist on
doing all the cooking.
‐ You know, I was
taught a really tasty
way of cooking them.
‐ Are you trying to imply
that my cooking is awful?
‐ Oh, are you good at cooking?
‐ Not to brag or
anything, but Mike
ate my cooking yesterday
and the day before,
and he said it was tasty!
‐ Oh, is that so?
‐ Lose the "I wasn’t
expecting that" look.
‐ Well, you don’t
have to get so mad.
It’s almost as if you were
kinda jealous or something.
‐ Well, even if
that was the case,
what’d be the big deal anyway?
‐ There’s a chance you
might be his relative,
wouldn’t that make this a
dangerous train of thought?
‐ It’s all right.
There’s also a chance
we could be strangers.
‐ Well, it wouldn’t
be right for you
to live in this
house as a stranger.
‐ It’s just as likely
we’re relatives.
‐ Which way would you prefer?
‐ Before I answer that,
why don’t you tell me
which way you would
prefer, Senpai?
‐ Well, who really knows?
‐ It’s obvious that this
is getting us nowhere
so why don’t we just split
the noodles in half, okay?
(electric shocking)
‐ [Tsubaki] Sure, that’s fine.
Do you have a pot
that I can use?
‐ All we have is that
little one there.
‐ Well, I only need to
make enough for one.
‐ Um, ’scuse me.
‐ What?
‐ What is it?
(roaring)
‐ Nyu.
Nyu.
‐ Hey, come on, hey.
Haruko, I can come
with you, right?
I mean, that’s okay with you?
‐ Sorry, Matagu.
I’m going to a friend’s
house today, so nope!
‐ Why don’t you have dipping
sauce for the noodles?
‐ Maybe because we’re poor.
‐ [Matagu] Come on,
don’t be so stubborn.
‐ [Haruko] No means no!
(groans)
(knocks softly)
‐ Um, uh.
‐ [Mike] Who is it?
‐ It’s Karen, may
I please come in?
‐ Sure, good timing anyway.
Karen, I.
‐ Um, see.
Oh, Mister Mike, your
Senpai and Miss Miina
are cooking your noodles
in a very worrisome way!
I see auras of a
tiger and a lion!
‐ What are you talkin’ about?
‐ I’m telling you, it’s
a tiger and a lion.
‐ There aren’t any lions
or tigers around here.
‐ I suppose that’s true, but.
‐ Look, just calm down a bit.
I wanna talk to you.
Why don’t you sit
down over here.
‐ Okay, excuse me.
(chair squeaking)
‐ Now, you know, Karen,
you called and gave the
telephone number to your,
uh, what do you call them?
Oh yeah, to your foster
parents, is that right?
‐ Yes, I found a pay
phone yesterday and
called my uncle and
told him where I was and
then I gave him the phone
number for this house.
Was that a bad thing?
‐ Karen, he called.
(gasps)
I said that your uncle
called the house.
‐ [Karen] Are you
sure it was my uncle?
‐ Yeah.
He said he wanted to talk
to me, so I took the call.
‐ Mm.
‐ [Mike] I heard the basic
gist of things from him.
Your uncle’s company
is in trouble, right?
(laughs)
‐ Don’t you hate recession?
‐ Yeah, really.
So I finally understand
why you came here
mid‐semester despite
the fact that you
had attended a private
all‐girls school.
‐ I should have
told you, I’m sorry.
‐ [Mike] There’s no
need to apologize.
‐ But.
‐ Look, I don’t
think that your uncle
told you everything
he should have.
This is a lousy
way of putting it,
but your uncle has
gotten into trouble
trying to keep his
company afloat.
Apparently he sent you
here because he was afraid
that his troubles might
become your troubles, too.
‐ I thought it had to be,
or something like that.
See, my uncle always
said it was too dangerous
for me to travel too far
from home all by myself.
He said I walked
around in a daze.
(laughs)
But then he changed his mind
and let me come, so I did.
‐ [Mike] He told me that
he was leaving home and
that he trusted me with you.
He also said he would do
whatever he could to‐‐
‐ [Karen] Mister Mike, my uncle.
‐ Don’t worry yourself, Karen.
He said to tell you
that he was all right.
‐ I understand.
‐ [Mike] But he also
said that he might
not be able to
call here anymore.
‐ But why?
He can’t.
‐ One more thing.
He said sorry.
‐ I don’t believe it.
Uncle’s gone.
(sobbing)
(piano playing)
‐ Your uncle, was he a kind man?
I’m sure this isn’t very
convincing, but it’s all right.
It’ll be all right.
You can stay right here.
It’s all right for you to stay.
‐ Yeah, but, what
if we’re strangers?
There’s still that chance.
‐ Yeah, well, I suppose
that’s true, but.
You and I have the
same eye color, Karen,
so it’s all right.
It’s all right for
you to stay here.
(sobbing)
I won’t, I won’t abandon you.
Never.
‐ Mike.
‐ Kamishiro.
‐ Uh.
(crashing)
‐ Wha?
‐ What is going on here?
‐ Yeah, I was gonna
ask you the same thing.
You didn’t knock first and
then you dropped all the food.
‐ What do you expect?
(moaning)
(shouting)
(sniffling)
‐ I’m sorry.
Oh!
Nyu!
(steam releasing)
‐ Huh, hey!
‐ Kamishiro.
(dramatic music)
‐ What were you two doing?
‐ Wait, you gotta
let me explain this!
‐ Yeah, she was crying.
‐ You didn’t force her.
‐ Now. wait, would you just
listen to me for a second?
Senpai!
Miina!
(gasps)
‐ I can’t believe it!
I can’t believe that you of all
people would do such a thing!
‐ I feel so stupid that I
ever thought highly of you!
‐ [Mike] Would somebody
please listen to me!
‐ (together) No!
(cicadas singing)
‐ Kamishiro, you’re wonderful.
(laughs)
(groans)
(humming)
(cicadas singing)
(splashing)
‐ Boy, I really
was surprised about
what happened this afternoon.
But then when I
really think about it,
there just couldn’t be
something like that going on.
‐ No, of course there couldn’t.
‐ That’s so true.
‐ Uh.
(splashing)
‐ Hey, cheer up, okay?
‐ Sure.
‐ I think it’s a good thing
Mike’s letting you stay.
‐ Yeah.
(splashing)
‐ Well, I guess the
same goes for me.
‐ Miss Miina, there’s
a chance Mister Mike
might be a relative, right?
‐ Could be, for one of us.
(piano playing)
‐ So he might be a stranger.
(laughs)
‐ Oh, is that you, Miss Kikuchi?
It’s Mike Kamishiro.
Um, about the data I was
supposed to send today,
can it wait until
tomorrow morning?
No, I’ve been really
doing my best trying
to get it done for
you, but there’s this
one part I’m having a
little trouble with.
I am working hard on it!
And, no, I am not goofing off!
Look, you are the one who...
[Mike Voiceover] We might be.
[Miina Voiceover] Relatives.
[Mike Voiceover] But.
[Karen Voiceover] We
might be strangers.
(Please Twins! closing theme)
(singing in Japanese)
♪ Ano hoshi wa ♪
♪ Onaji matataki de ♪
♪ Kawarazu ni watashi wo mite ♪
♪ Taikutsu na yume
wo nageki fuseta ♪
♪ Yokogao wo sotto terashiteta ♪
♪ Asu ni wa chiisana
nimotsu seoi ♪
♪ Kouya wo tobitatsu
tori ni naru kara ♪
♪ Mukai kaze no naka ♪
♪ Mukau basho wa mada ♪
♪ Itsuka tadoritsuku
hoshi ni nareru ♪
♪ Matsuge ni nijinda
shizuku wo nabikase ♪
♪ Kesshite owaranai tabi wo ♪
♪ Tsudzuke ni yuku yo ♪
‐ (together) Next
episode, more twins!
(playful music)
‐ Miss Miina, you
know that you and I
can’t keep relying on
Mister Mike forever.
‐ Oh, look at this magazine
with part‐time job listings
The school that Mike goes
to has a part‐time opening!
‐ But you don’t qualify.
They’re looking for
people who are over 18.
‐ Don’t worry,
I’ll be all right!
‐ [Karen] Where does all
that confidence come from?
‐ [Miina] Wait, what
do you mean by that?
‐ [Karen] Oh,
nothing, nevermind.
‐ [Miina Voiceover]
Please Twins! Episode 4!
‐ [Karen Voiceover]
"Kind to You."
‐ [Miina Voiceover]
Be sure to watch it!
‐ [Karen Voiceover] Next
episode, more twins!