(students chattering)
‐ [Mike] We eat our
meals together back home
so don’t you think that
eating together here
is a little much?
‐ But food tastes better
when we’re together.
‐ You don’t want to eat with us?
‐ It’s not that I don’t want to,
I’m just worried
about all the staring.
From over there too.
(Kousei slurps)
‐ Those girls are being so
open about their feelings.
‐ [Ichigo] That
makes me wanna smile.
‐ What are you talking
about, Madame President?
You, who has an information
network as good as the Echelon
should certainly know by
now that one of those girls
has no blood relation
to Kamishiro at all!
‐ Yes, of course
I know all that.
‐ If you leave them all alone
there could be some
sort of mishap.
And, in fact, I
guarantee there will be.
‐ [Ichigo] Are you jealous?
‐ I really don’t care if you
want to think of it that way.
‐ All right then.
I agree to help you out.
If you’re saying
you won’t regret it.
(upbeat music)
(singing in a foreign language)
(birds chirping)
(bell chimes)
‐ [Student Announcer]
An announcement
from the Student Council.
Mike Kamishiro in 1‐B,
please report to the Student
Council office immediately.
If you don’t come soon I’ll
do something really dreadful.
(speaker buzzes)
‐ What was that?
‐ [Student] Hurry up, Kamishiro.
I heard President Morino’s
something really dreadful
is something really dreadful.
‐ Okay.
(upbeat music)
So let me get this straight,
for the duration of
the ballgame festival
you want me to be on
the executive committee
as an interim member?
‐ That’s right.
I think very highly
of your work ethic
and your information
handling capabilities.
‐ Look, I appreciate that
but I already have a job.
‐ Yes, I know.
We’re prepared to pay you
a very generous salary
fitting your work.
It will pay better than writing
computer programs at home.
‐ I’ll do my best for you.
‐ Good, I’m counting on you,
Kamishiro. (laughs dryly)
(students chattering)
‐ I’m Tsubaki Oribe,
committee member.
‐ I’m Mike Kamishiro,
an interim member.
(bell rings)
Wait,
are there really only two
of us on this committee?
‐ Everyone’s short
of people these days.
‐ Come here, froggy!
Come here, froggy!
‐ You know, I just
can’t believe that.
What in the world‐‐
‐ President Morino has
left us her orders.
She wants this ballgame
festival to be organized
and held in secret.
‐ Well, that’s stupid.
Why hold a festival in secret?
‐ [Tsubaki] Oh, I
don’t really know.
‐ I thought something was
fishy so I came over here.
‐ Oh, Ms. Miina, I think
the situation falls
under Love Alliance
rule number four.
‐ We’ve gotta stop them.
‐ I’m right with you.
‐ [Ichigo] You can’t.
‐ [Miina and Karen]
Starting council president!
‐ The student council
office forbids entry
of those other than
committee members.
‐ What?
That’s not fair.
‐ Then Ms. Miina and
I want to volunteer
to serve on the
committee, right now.
‐ Request denied.
‐ Why?
I don’t understand.
‐ Feng shui.
Dr. Kopa told me about it.
‐ That is not a valid reason!
‐ [Ichigo] Then I’ll make
it a presidential order.
If you violate my order
I’ll do something dreadful.
‐ Dreadful?
What exactly are you
planning on doing?
‐ The school forbids
part time jobs
for its students.
The Jomon‐style roasts
at Harikawa Grocery
are rather tasty.
You know what I mean?
(girls gasp)
I’m glad the two
of you understand.
‐ How ’bout we switch this
one with that one over here.
‐ Oh yeah.
That’ll work out a lot better.
‐ [Tsubaki] Of course.
‐ [Mike] How ’bout
we take this one
and group them altogether?
‐ [Tsubaki] That’s great.
I knew you’d do a
good job, Kamishiro.
(Kousei groans)
(crickets chirping)
‐ [Miina] You are not going
to quit the committee?
‐ But why aren’t you, Mike?
‐ Because no matter
what the work is,
I still need the money.
We used up quite a bit
of it on that last trip
we took, you know?
‐ So, you wanna hang out
with the vice president, huh?
‐ It’s not that.
‐ [Miina] You’re being fooled
by a woman’s seduction.
‐ That’s right because
it’s really true
that boys prefer girls with
good figures, isn’t it?
‐ Please don’t jump
to conclusions.
Senpai and I are
just doing paperwork.
I’ll have to be staying at
school late from now on.
So make sure both of
you get to work on time.
You got that?
(girls huff)
(light orchestral music)
‐ Oh, Miina, what do
you think we should do?
It’s a big crisis for
the Love Alliance.
‐ I guess we have to
count on Mike being stoic
through it all.
‐ Yeah, you’re right.
Mr. Mike would be the last
person to make a big mistake.
‐ But if we just do nothing
then something like that
might really happen.
‐ I’ve never felt
this way before.
I’ve gotta have you.
I can’t stand just
working together with you.
My heart races every day.
But I want it to race even more.
‐ Senpai, no.
‐ I love you.
‐ That’s not good at all.
‐ We need to keep an
eye on him after all.
‐ We can’t, we have a
job we have to go to,
don’t you remember?
(Marie humming)
(girls gasp)
‐ [Marie] Huh?
‐ [Both] Yeah, that’s it!
(Marie coos)
‐ [Mizuho] Marie is gone.
I wonder if he’s at
Kamishiro’s house again.
(birds chirping)
‐ [Tsubaki] You think it’s
all right for the 12th graders
to stand on the west side?
‐ That’s kind of
close to the tent
where all the teachers
will be resting.
Do you think they
might complain?
‐ You’re right.
Maybe it’d be better if
we thought about moving
the teacher’s tent as well.
(Marie coos)
‐ I wonder if Mr. Marie
is keeping a good watch
on them right now.
‐ We have to have faith in him.
We don’t have a choice.
(bright orchestral music)
(monitor beeping)
(crickets chirping)
(Marie warbling)
‐ Oh, that’s good,
it looks like Mr. Mike
was all right again today.
I just wish the ballgame
festival would arrive soon.
Right?
Don’t you agree?
‐ Huh?
Oh.
(water splashes)
Yeah, you’re right.
(students chattering)
‐ [Student] Here goes!
(Marie coos suspiciously)
‐ Sorry to make you wait.
Look, I bought you some.
(Marie shrieks)
Let’s rest for awhile.
(monitor beeps)
‐ Oh, thank you.
‐ I hope that was
what you wanted.
‐ Yeah, it is.
(Marie groans)
‐ Hey, Kamishiro, how’s life
going with those two girls
you’re living with?
‐ What?
Well, there are a lot
of things that go on.
But I feel like we’re
getting by somehow.
‐ Isn’t it stressful?
‐ Yeah, sometimes it is.
But it’s a different
kind of stress
than I used to experience.
You know, senpai,
not that I wanna go into
a lecture about this,
but I faced a lot of
hardships in my life.
I was in a facility I hated,
and did everything
I could think of
to try and get thrown out.
And I’ve been living
my life until now
thinking that I was
living only for myself
but then, after they came here,
I think something inside
of me changed somehow.
‐ I think you’re
just getting soft.
‐ I can’t really tell
about that, you know?
‐ Well, I can tell if you can’t.
‐ You’re being fooled
by a woman’s seduction!
(light orchestral music)
‐ Kamishiro, you’re really
a different kind of guy.
‐ [Mike] Huh?
What do you mean by that?
‐ [Tsubaki] You’re
mature for your age.
‐ That’s not true.
I’m just a kid, desperately
holding back what I wanna say
or what I wanna do.
And what I really wanna do is
say everything that I
feel inside my heart.
(light orchestral music)
(Marie cooing angrily)
(Tsubaki screams)
(can clinks)
Senpai, are you okay?
(Tsubaki gasps)
‐ No!
(hand cracks)
So you’re the type of guy that
does that kind of stuff too?
Idiot!
(door slams)
(Tsubaki stomping)
(Marie coos)
(cicadas chirping)
(chair rattles)
‐ [Kousei] Mike.
‐ [Mike] Shimazaki.
‐ What did you do to her?
‐ [Mike] What?
‐ What did you do to Tsubaki?
‐ Huh?
‐ [Miina] Mike, you pervert!
‐ [Karen] Mr. Mike,
you’re disgusting!
‐ Hey, what’s going
on with you two?
‐ Oh, now he’s just
gonna play dumb.
‐ Mr. Marie was
watching all day.
Right?
(Marie grunts)
‐ Something happened
at school, didn’t it?
‐ [Mike] Yeah, it did.
But it’s nothing like what you
guys are probably thinking.
It’s nothing like that.
(cicadas chirping)
‐ [Kousei] I see, it
was an accident, huh?
I’m sorry, Mike, I shouldn’t
have gotten so awfully excited.
‐ It’s all right.
But I’m just a
little bit curious,
did something happen
with you an senpai?
‐ Yes, Mike, about
six months ago.
‐ When Kousei came to the campus
while preparing for
his entrance exams,
someone introduced me to him.
For awhile I would just
give him basic advice
about what he should
do in preparation.
And then, after a few
weeks, I began to tutor him.
‐ Then you guys started
to see each other?
‐ That’s right.
‐ And so, I went on a
few dates with Tsubaki
to take a breather
from all the studies.
But then one day.
‐ No, Kousei, I can’t here,
it’s too embarrassing
in a place like this.
‐ But I just can’t hold back.
‐ [Tsubaki] Kousei.
(light orchestral music)
(Tsubaki gasps)
‐ No!
(hand cracks)
You idiot.
And because of that incident
I started to keep my
distance from Kousei.
‐ You are an idiot.
Why have you never told me this?
‐ There are times when
a guy just hold back
and I guess I was embarrassed,
but I guess it’s true that
I’ve hurt Tsubaki’s feelings
and I was wrong.
And so I’ve tried to hold back
and suppress any interest or
feelings I’ve had toward woman,
and made myself believe
deep in my heart
that you were much more
to me than just a friend.
‐ [Mike] Well, that seems
to be succeeding for you.
‐ [Kousei] Well, it’s
the fruit of my labor.
‐ So are you in love
with senpai?
(light orchestral music)
‐ I suppose you’re probably
still in love with
Shimazaki, right?
‐ Not anymore.
Mike Kamishiro is
who I currently‐‐
‐ [Ichigo] Liar.
Kamishiro is a serious guy
and would never
lay a hand on you.
That’s why you were able
to approach him so easily,
wasn’t it?
But let’s face it,
that’s not love.
‐ [Tsubaki] President Morino.
‐ If you keep acting out
on your mistaken emotions
you’ll come to a standstill.
I was so close to you, Tsubaki,
and yet I couldn’t see through
to your true inner feelings.
I still have a
ways to go myself.
‐ You mean all of that.
‐ Happened in the past?
‐ That’s right.
And you guys were so worried.
In the first place I.
‐ You what?
‐ What were you saying?
‐ Nevermind.
‐ [Miina] What?
Now you’ve got me curious.
‐ [Karen] Please
tell us, Mr. Mike.
‐ [Mike] I said, nevermind.
‐ Aw.
‐ [Mike] Shimazaki,
you’ve got to catch the
one you love, right?
I really understand
how that feels.
But a feeling can sometimes
break up a relationship
with that person.
I won’t do it.
I don’t wanna let go.
Because this house has
what I’ve wanted so much.
(birds chirping)
(pencil scraping)
(door scrapes)
(Tsubaki gasps)
‐ Kamishiro, I’m
sorry about yesterday.
‐ [Student] What happened
yesterday was an accident.
‐ Yes, I know.
‐ Mike didn’t mean to
touch you in that way.
I want you at least
to understand that.
‐ [Tsubaki] Why are
you here, Kousei?
It’s awfully early in
the morning for you.
‐ It seems I’m an interim
committee member now too.
I got the permission of the
student council president.
‐ Oh, that president.
‐ Tsubaki, do you
mind if I sit here?
‐ Just as long as you don’t
try to get any closer.
‐ Of course.
I understand.
(light piano music)
(moves into bright
orchestral music)
I’m sorry I’ve hurt you.
‐ Yes, I was hurt.
‐ I’ll never do it
again, I promise.
‐ I don’t believe you.
‐ So, you don’t have
feelings for me anymore?
Does that mean that
you’re in love with Mike?
‐ What if I said that I was?
‐ I wouldn’t do anything.
‐ I see.
‐ But there’s just one thing.
I’m still in love
with you, Tsubaki.
‐ It’s a little late.
‐ I can never figure out
why you thought you had
to slap me like that.
I thought that it was all
right if we loved each other.
‐ [Tsubaki] It was embarrassing.
It was really embarrassing.
‐ I’m sorry.
‐ You see, it was my first kiss.
I always dreamed it
would be more gentle.
I hate you for what
you did, Kousei.
I hate you.
‐ [Kousei] Don’t pout.
‐ I’m not pouting, I.
‐ Please don’t.
(cicadas chirping)
Let me start from the beginning.
From a simple kiss
that got so confused.
‐ No fair.
‐ You’re right about that.
I’m sorry.
‐ Okay.
I forgive you, Kousei.
Because I’ve always.
(cicadas chirping)
(Tsubaki moans)
(hand slaps)
Idiot!
(door slams)
Kousei, you pervert!
You can’t be delicate at all!
‐ Senpai, are you?
(upbeat music)
Hey, Shimazaki, what
did you do to her?
‐ Well, Mike, it
seems I did it again.
I’m a guy who can’t
suppress any desires.
‐ Go after her and stop
acting like a jerk!
‐ She just slapped me again.
‐ So, go after her anyway.
If you love her, chase her!
(upbeat music)
‐ I can’t brush you
aside, Shimazaki.
(camera shutter snaps)
Oh well, I guess this is
all right the way it is.
(upbeat music)
Tsubaki, you should accelerate
straight into the
right direction.
‐ I’m so sorry, Tsubaki, really.
‐ Don’t touch me,
you sick pervert.
‐ Tsubaki.
‐ You really are the worst
of the worst, you know that?
‐ Hey, senpai!
All lovey‐dovey, huh?
‐ Yeah, you guys look cute.
‐ [Tsubaki] Are you mocking me?
‐ Of course not.
‐ [Both] We’re both
jealous of you.
‐ I don’t get it.
‐ You’ve gotta be more
honest with yourself.
‐ Or your love will run
away from you. (laughs)
‐ [Kousei] I can’t win.
‐ Oh, Kousei.
Next time try to
keep things proper.
(bright orchestral music)
‐ [Miina] I’m jealous that
they can be so honest.
‐ [Karen] I’m jealous that
their love can bear fruit.
‐ [Miina] Oh, Mike.
‐ [Karen] Mr. Mike.
‐ [Miina] Tell me,
where is our love?
‐ [Karen] Where is our
love headed towards?
(singing in a foreign language)
‐ [Miina and Karen] Next
episode, more twins.
‐ [Miina] I went out into town
with Mike and Karen today.
‐ [Karen] The three of
us are together, but.
‐ [Miina] It’s all
right if I pretended
I was on a date
with Mike, right?
‐ [Karen] It’s all right
if I pretended too, right?
‐ [Miina] Hey, Mike, Karen,
where did you guys go?
‐ [Karen] Where are you,
Mr. Mike, Ms. Miina?
‐ [Miina] I don’t
want this to happen.
I don’t wanna be alone.
‐ [Karen] I don’t
wanna be alone.
‐ [Miina] Please
Twins! episode nine.
‐ [Karen] Don’t Leave Me Out.
‐ [Miina] Be sure to watch it.
Next episode, more twins.