(soft music)
‐ [Mike] Karen.
‐ [Karen] Mr. Mike.
‐ Where’d Miina go?
‐ [Karen] I don’t know,
she isn’t back yet.
‐ I see.
‐ I suppose it can’t be helped.
This is the first time
she’s seen her friend
in quite a long while.
‐ That’s true.
I think so too.
‐ Yes.
A vague sense of worry
was starting to wrap
itself around me.
Most likely, Mr.
Mike was feeling
the very same thing.
Miss Miina had kept
her past a secret
from us for all this time.
And both Mr. Mike and I
had been very
careful not to touch
that issue for her sake.
However, now that Miss
Miina’s friend had appeared,
something was going to change.
At least, that’s what
I started to think.
There were only supposed
to be two of us,
but we decided to stay
together as three.
And we finally started to
feel that it was all right.
And yet, I couldn’t seem to
shake the worries away.
(upbeat music in
foreign language)
‐ What?
‐ Nothing.
I was just wondering.
What kind of conversation did
you have with your friend?
‐ This and that.
But she seemed like
she was very happy
to hear that I had
found my relatives.
‐ Oh, I see.
That’s wonderful.
(sighs)
‐ It was.
(soft music)
So you run on the
inner high school team?
‐ Mmhmm, my last race
was the best I ever ran.
I was like, so excited.
Though I could say my
mother was more excited.
‐ Good for you.
‐ Sorry, how inconsiderate.
I shouldn’t talk about it.
‐ Oh, don’t be ridiculous.
I know you’ve been working
hard for a long time.
You should be proud.
I’m very happy for you.
‐ Thanks a lot.
Aren’t you ever
coming back, Miina?
‐ But I told you.
I found my relatives
so I’m staying.
So you don’t have
to worry about me.
I’m very happy with my life.
‐ [Yuuka] Should I keep this
a secret from my mother?
‐ [Miina] If that’s possible.
‐ Can I assume that everything’s
finally cleared up now?
That we’re okay?
I mean, I was able to meet
my mother’s
expectations at last.
And Miina, you were able
to locate your family.
‐ Yeah, that’s right.
I guess that’s good enough.
(water splashing)
‐ Miss Miina, it’s
time for us to,
Miss Miina!
‐ [Mike] Idiot, you
should know better
not to soak until
you’re hard boiled.
‐ [Miina] There goes my dignity.
‐ Oh yeah, well, you
didn’t have too much.
‐ [Miina] That
hurts my feelings.
‐ [Mike] Karen, I trust you
take care of Miina, okay?
‐ Sure, I’d be happy to.
‐ [Miina] Hey, Mike?
‐ What do you need?
‐ It’s fine for me
to stay here, right?
‐ Oh, Miss Miina.
‐ I can stay here.
I can, right?
‐ Of course you can.
What are you talking about?
(crickets chirping)
Of course you can.
(bells chiming)
‐ Hey Miina, hi Karen.
All of us are going
over to my place
to hang out after school today.
‐ So then, would
you like to join us?
‐ We’ll have a blast.
‐ So Miss Miina,
what should we do?
‐ Oh, I’m sorry.
I have a lot of stuff I
have to get done today.
‐ That’s too bad.
‐ Oh, that’s really a shame.
This morning my
brother was saying
that he was going to
volunteer to cook for us.
‐ [Girls] Huh?
(giggles)
‐ No way, you can count me out.
‐ Me too.
‐ Huh, why not?
It’s my brother cooking for us.
‐ So Miss Miina, you
gonna go see your friend?
‐ Yeah, I guess.
‐ [Mike] Hey, Karen.
‐ Hi, Mr. Mike.
‐ Where’s Miina?
Isn’t she with you?
‐ [Karen] No, she’s
going to get together
with her friend this afternoon.
She already left.
‐ I see.
Hmm?
‐ Something the matter?
‐ Well, isn’t that girl
over there Miina’s friend?
‐ Excuse me.
If I’m not mistaken,
you’re Miss Miina’s
friend, aren’t you?
‐ Yes, yes that’s right.
Are you friends of hers?
‐ Sort of, we’re Miina’s family.
‐ [Yuuka] Family?
(gasps)
(soft music)
‐ Even if I do something
like this here,
it’s still not gonna
make any difference.
But Karen always looks
so worried all the time.
I’m happy Mike pretends
to look the other way.
I appreciate it.
But for now at least,
I really don’t
want to see Yuuka.
No, I can’t say that.
(squeals)
Oh, Ms. Kazami.
‐ Good afternoon.
‐ What are you
doing here, ma’am?
‐ Well you see, I
noticed that you were
walking towards Mount Kokama
on your way home from
school, Miss Miyafuji,
so I thought that I
should follow you.
It’s not safe for
a girl like you
to be in such an isolated
area by yourself.
‐ I’m sorry, ma’am.
‐ It’s not that I’m
upset at you or anything.
May I join you for awhile?
‐ Yeah, of course.
(moans)
‐ It feels so nice.
It’s been quite awhile,
since the last time.
‐ Can I ask you a question?
‐ [Mizuho] What is it?
‐ Well.
How can I put this?
Oh that’s right, I know.
You’re married,
right, Ms. Kazami?
‐ Yes, to a wonderful man.
‐ [Miina] Did you
have lots of dramas
before you got married?
‐ [Mizuho] Mmhmm,
there were lots of them
after we got married too.
‐ Really, afterwards?
‐ That’s right.
I think I can finally
say it with a smile now.
But there were times
that I felt as if
my body and soul had been
ripped apart at the seams.
‐ What did you do when
you felt that way?
‐ I verbalized it all.
‐ Verbalized?
‐ Yes, just about everything.
I verbally expressed
everything that I was feeling.
Sad things, happy things.
Even things I didn’t
want to think about.
‐ [Karen] Excuse me, but if
it’s not too much trouble,
would you please tell me
what you can about Miss Miina?
‐ About Miyafuji?
‐ Yes, something happened
to her, didn’t it?
‐ You mean, she hasn’t told you?
‐ Miss Miina doesn’t
say much about herself.
‐ Well, I‐‐
‐ Oh please, I really
want to know about her.
You gotta tell me.
‐ Karen, stop it.
‐ Mr. Mike?
‐ I said stop.
‐ Why would you say that?
Don’t you care about her?
Doesn’t Miss Miina worry you?
‐ Just because you’re worried,
does that make it right for you
to pry information
out of a stranger?
To me it seems like you’re just
trying to lessen
your own worries
in spite of what Miina wants.
I don’t want to find out
about Miina this way.
Especially if it’s something
that she doesn’t wanna tell us.
‐ Mr. Mike.
‐ I think, I think
he’s absolutely right.
‐ Yeah, me too, I’m sorry.
‐ Don’t worry about it.
‐ I’m sorry, I
shouldn’t have asked.
‐ I’m relieved.
I’m glad that Miyafuji’s
living with people like you,
because you care about her.
‐ Well sure, we’re family.
‐ Ms. Kazami, there
are times in your life
that you know you’re
making a mistake.
But no matter what you try,
there doesn’t seem
to be anything
you can do about it, right?
What should you do
in times like that?
‐ [Mizuho] There’s
always something that
you can do about it.
You’ve probably already
found the answer
and just don’t know it yet.
‐ [Miina] What do you mean?
‐ Well I think of it this way.
When we’re feeling sad,
we spend all of our
time thinking about
and wondering how
not to feel that way.
Even when we don’t realize it.
I guess what I’m saying is that
we find the answers we need
before we know we have.
I know you’re looking for
the right way to avoid mistakes,
just as you realize
you’re making one.
You can’t see it now
because you’re still
really uncertain
about all your feelings.
The answer is already
inside of you.
All you have to do
is move forward.
Just move forward.
(crickets chirping)
‐ Hi, I’m home.
‐ Miss Miina.
‐ [Miina] Karen?
‐ Oh you’re home, Miss Miina.
I was so worried about you.
‐ I asked you not to make
us worry but then you did.
‐ I’m very sorry.
‐ [Mike] Don’t you have
anything else to say?
‐ I do.
‐ Miss Miina?
‐ Karen, Mike.
Tomorrow after school,
could you guys plan to spend
a little bit of time with me?
Please come, all right?
(whistle blowing)
‐ [Mike] You wanted
us to spend time
with you at the track?
‐ [Miina] You know
about the inner
high school track and
field competition, right?
This is the training field.
‐ I didn’t know
about a competition.
‐ Hey, wait a minute.
I saw something about
this on the news.
‐ [Miina] You know
that girl over there,
the one who’s talking?
‐ [Karen] Oh yeah.
‐ [Mike] So is she
one of the competitors
in the tournament?
‐ Mmhmm, distance runner.
Her name is Yuuka Yashiro.
She was in my class
in junior high.
‐ [Karen] Were you
two close friends?
‐ Yeah, I think so.
You see, I kinda stayed with her
and her parents
during junior high.
‐ So the two of
you lived together?
‐ Yeah.
But I, I ran away from there,
right before I came here.
‐ Ran away?
‐ Well, I left without
saying anything.
That’s running away.
‐ But how come‐‐
‐ You see, just like Mike did,
I lived in an orphanage
from when I was a baby.
When I went to junior high,
I got to know Yuuka
pretty quickly,
and I started to practice
with the track team.
At first it was just
to hang out with her,
but then I got to like it.
It feels silly to
be saying this,
but I was a fast runner.
I started for a simple reason.
But the more I did it, the
more I really enjoyed it.
Not too long after
I started training,
Yuuka’s mom came
and talked to me.
It seems she’s a famous
track and field athlete.
And she told me that I
had a lot of potential.
At first, I turned her down.
I didn’t have any
money to pay her.
That’s when she offered
to be my legal guardian
until I grew up.
She said that I could live
in her house with Yuuka,
and that she would train me.
I was happy.
I ran really hard all the time
because I never
wanted to go back
to that awful orphanage again.
I had nothing but bad memories
of living in that place.
I entered competitions, set
new records, and won awards.
And then one day,
I received a recommendation for
a certain high school.
If I got a scholarship,
I thought I’d be able to run
without troubling anybody.
But then, I injured myself.
So as an athlete,
I became no good.
And I just couldn’t meet
everyone’s expectations.
The scholarship offer
was canceled too.
As soon as I became unable
to run, I lost everything.
I just couldn’t stay at
Yuuka’s place anymore,
so that’s why I left.
The only thing that
I could rely on
was that photograph.
I was such a horrible person.
From the moment my
scholarship offer
was received in the mail,
all I could think about
was setting a new record.
Even Yuuka, who lived
with me, was my rival.
On top of that,
I never understood why Yuuka
always insisted on calling
me by my last name.
All I could think about
was how to protect
what I thought I belonged to.
You see, I desperately
wanted a place to belong.
‐ Oh, Miss Miina.
‐ [Miina] I, I‐‐
‐ Idiot, what are
you talking about?
Miina, you’ve got a place.
Our place is yours
and you belong there.
And so, there’s no need
to force yourself to run.
If you want to run, you
can go ahead and do it.
And if you don’t want to
run, that’s fine as well.
No matter what you say or do,
Karen and I will not change
how we feel about you.
But that’s not the point.
Don’t you have something
you need to do?
Wasn’t there a
reason you came here?
‐ [Karen] There was,
wasn’t there, Miss Miina?
‐ Karen, I,
I, I’m sure that, I
mean I, I’m certain.
(soft music)
Yuuka.
‐ Miyafuji, doesn’t
your knee hurt?
‐ Just a little.
Let me run with you
for a little while.
‐ I’m fine with it
if you are, Miyafuji.
‐ Thanks.
Yuuka, you know, I’m fine now.
I really am fine.
I finally found a
place where I belong.
A place where I can be myself
without overexerting myself.
Please make sure to tell
your mom about it, okay?
And Yuuka, I’m sorry
about so many things.
That’s what I wanted to say.
That’s what I’ve
always wanted to say.
‐ Miyafuji, I was
jealous of you, you know.
I was jealous that you
could run faster than me.
I’m so sorry.
‐ Yeah.
Thanks for being
so honest with me.
‐ You know, I think
of you as a friend.
(gasps)
I really do.
‐ Yeah.
(soft music)
(screams)
‐ Miina!
‐ Miss Miina.
‐ Are you all right?
‐ [Mike] Miina.
‐ Miss Miina.
Did you hurt yourself?
(laughs)
‐ I just tripped.
‐ Oh good.
‐ You had me so worried.
‐ Me too.
‐ [Miina] Yeah, that’s right.
This is where I belong.
(birds chirping)
Hey Karen, is Mike still asleep?
‐ It seems he was working
rather late last night.
‐ Do you mind if I leave
you to do the chores?
‐ It’s all right.
You should feel
free to go and help
Miss Yuuka out for
as long as you need.
‐ Thanks a lot.
I’ll be back in plenty of
time for us to go to work.
‐ Okay, have a good day.
‐ Thanks, you too.
(birds chirping)
‐ I’m so glad the three
of us can stay together.
The three of us in this house.
There’s something
not quite right here.
Now I see it.
The difference is
that there’s a road
in between the
pool and the house.
That means the photograph
wasn’t taken from the place
where we all thought it was,
but from the other side.
(soft music)
There’s no doubt about it.
This photograph was
taken from this location.
But why did someone need to come
all the way up here just
to take a photograph?
(soft music)
‐ Good morning.
Hmm, that’s weird.
The two of them have
gone out already?
‐ No way, it can’t.
Could this possibly be the house
where our mom used to live?
Could this really be
where I came from?
(upbeat music in
foreign language)
‐ [Girls] Next
episode, more twins.
‐ [Karen] I will no longer
ask myself what I should do.
I understand how Miss Miina
and Mr. Mike are concerned.
So I, Karen Onodera, am
going to let them know
the feelings I
have inside of me.
I have to express
these strong feelings,
even though it could mean
a possible breakup
of the love alliance.
Please Twins, episode 11.
I Want To Tell You I Love You.
Be sure to watch it.
Next episode, more twins.