(bird chirping)
‐ [Man] What are
you doing Karen?
‐ Just laying here with you.
It’s perfectly alright
because we’re twins.
I don’t understand why
you still act so distant.
After all, it’s
already been two weeks
since we found out
we were related.
‐ Not already, but
only two weeks.
‐ By the way, when
do you think we’ll be
able to start taking
baths together?
‐ What are you talking about?
That just isn’t normal.
Are there any brothers and
sisters who actually do that?
Have you even seen it on TV?
‐ FCC regulations keep
that stuff off of TV.
Okay, how about a wake up kiss?
‐ No.
‐ If you won’t,
then I guess I’ll just have
to intrude on your bath.
‐ You know, your
personality has changed.
‐ That’s because I wanna be
pampered by my big brother.
‐ Oh brother.
Miina.
‐ You two sure seem
to get along well.
‐ Well we are twins you know.
‐ Oh yeah?
Well even twins have their
limits, you know what I mean?
‐ What are you
yelling at me for?
‐ Because you give
her the opportunity!
‐ So it’s my fault?
I’m sorry.
‐ You can’t get into
that mood you guys!
Big brother is my big
brother and mine alone!
(man yells)
‐ [Man] Hey!
‐ Big brother!
‐ Wait!
‐ Karen, wait a sec.
‐ Karen?
‐ Hey!
‐ Get off of me!
‐ [Girl] Watch where
you’re touching him!
‐ [Man] Hey!
(upbeat music)
‐ I see.
In other words Mike.
(long beep)
‐ Meow!
Meow.
Meow!
Meow, meow, meow.
‐ That’s how it is
with Karen right now,
and it’s started to affect
your ability to do your work?
‐ Yeah.
You pretty much got
it all down Kousei.
‐ You’ve still got
tons of problems,
even though you’ve figured
out who your relative is.
You’ve got a lot
going on Kamishiro.
‐ That’s true.
Karen’s really
happy about all this
and I understand how she feels.
I’m pretty happy about
finding a relative
that I never thought
I’d meet too,
but you guys know
that we have to
make our own living, right?
Well, if I can work as much as
I can during summer vacation,
it’ll be easier on us later.
‐ Alright then.
We’ll just have to do
something about that.
‐ What?
‐ Just leave it to us.
(birds chirping)
(girls yelling and giggling)
‐ Hey, wait!
‐ So I found all
the ingredients and
made a very special dish,
just for my big brother
and he loved it.
‐ Cool!
‐ [Boy] I’m jealous.
‐ And I also get
to scrub down his
back in the bath, you know.
‐ Wow!
‐ [Boy] I’m really jealous!
‐ And at night, we sleep
together in the very same bed.
‐ Amazing!
‐ [Boy] It’s just too much!
I can’t resist it anymore!
‐ [Girls] Resist what?
‐ You know, stuff.
‐ [Woman] Karen’s
clinging all over
Kamishiro every day then?
‐ I understand that
Karen is happy now,
but it’s affecting
Mike’s ability to work
so I thought something
needed to be done.
‐ Is that all?
‐ Is what all?
‐ Well let’s see,
Karen is clinging
all over Kamishiro,
and so you haven’t
asked him out yet.
Let’s face it,
isn’t that why you’re
getting irritated Miina?
‐ That may be right.
‐ Well you need to hurry
up and ask him out.
You should go for it.
‐ [Girl] What if
I don’t know how?
‐ Wow!
This is great!
It’s got all the basics.
I could absolutely get
all of my work done here.
‐ [Girl] You’d get worried
about Miss Miyafuji
and Miss Onodera if you
were too far away, right?
That’s why I set it up
relatively close to your house,
and it won’t cost you any
money because it’s a tent.
‐ You guys are lifesavers.
‐ Of course,
I was the one who got all
the equipment together.
‐ Thanks Shimazaki.
I owe you one.
‐ [Girl] I’m worried.
Mike is late.
‐ [Girl] Maybe he’s
just really busy.
‐ Then I have to
make sure to soothe
and comfort him
when he gets back.
‐ Karen, you’re making
too big a fuss over Mike.
‐ You think so?
‐ I do.
I’m holding back the urge to
fawn all over him too you know.
‐ You can’t!
The only one who
can hang all over
my big brother is
me, his sister!
‐ Yeah, yeah, so you said.
Geez, I guess you’ve
forgotten all about
the rules of the love alliance.
‐ Rule number three,
the relative will
support the other’s
romantic relationship
with Mr. Mike.
You see, I still
remember that Miss Miina.
‐ Well then?
‐ But Miss Miina,
don’t you remember?
We disbanded the love alliance.
‐ [Miina Voiceover]
Someone who I’d thought
was a friend yesterday is
now acting more like a foe,
or rather like a
wicked mother in law.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] Big
brother is my big brother
and mine alone and that’s that!
‐ [Miina Voiceover]
It’s me who can be
romantically involved with Mike.
‐ [Karen Voiceover] Oh yeah?
Well it’s up to him to
answer to your feelings
or not Miss Miina, and not me.
‐ [Miina Voiceover]
You just said something
you shouldn’t have.
(doorbell rings)
‐ It’s Mike!
‐ Big brother!
‐ [Girls] Hi, welcome back!
‐ I’ve got some information that
I’m sure you two will
find very interesting.
(girl laughs evilly)
(boy yawns)
‐ I got a lot of
stuff done yesterday.
If I can just finish
that module today.
What?
When did this get here?
‐ Hooray!
It’s up, it’s up!
The tent is up!
My little tent is
up and standing!
Isn’t it great?
‐ I’m so hard.
‐ You’re kidding, but why?
‐ [Man] Alright, it’s done!
‐ [Boy] Magumo senpai?
‐ Oh!
Hey Kamishiro.
‐ Hey, good morning Mike.
‐ [Woman] Oh Mr. Kamishiro!
‐ [Boy] Miss Kazami.
‐ Mike!
Big brother!
‐ Wait, you guys too?
‐ Morning Mike.
‐ [Boy] Shimazaki?
‐ I don’t get all this senpai.
What’s going on?
‐ I’m really sorry Kamishiro.
I just don’t know how it
could’ve happened but,
somehow that person
found out about this.
‐ That person?
‐ [Girl] Now, let’s start
the fun little summer camp
sponsored by the
student council.
(girl laughs evilly)
‐ Sorry I’m late!
Hey, what’s wrong with him?
‐ It’s nothing really.
(girl laughs evilly)
(couple giggling)
(upbeat guitar music)
‐ [Mike Voiceover] What was I
doing kicking back like that?
I got a lot of work to do, work!
‐ He’s hold up in
there big time.
‐ I’m just gonna
go check up on him.
‐ Karen, don’t bother him now.
‐ But Miss Miina,
you were playing with him until
just a few minutes ago yourself.
‐ I know, that’s true.
‐ Now, now, why
don’t we just leave
him alone for a little while.
‐ Okay.
‐ Alright everybody,
you’re free now to
do what you want.
I suggest that you
work hard to make
wonderful memories this summer.
(girl laughs evilly)
‐ That was a pretty
suggestive announcement.
‐ I was planning on doing
that from the very start.
‐ Yosuke, you’re so
silly, you know that?
‐ Madam President,
is it really alright?
‐ Yes.
‐ However, as a student
council President.
‐ Subaki, if you’re going to
be all worried about Kamishiro,
then you should spend
more time with Shimazaki.
(girl laughs evilly)
‐ [Boy] Come on Kaede.
(girl giggles)
(boy giggles)
‐ Hey Haruko, let’s
head back to our tent.
‐ What about Mike?
‐ But Mike, big brother.
‐ [Girl] It’s alright.
‐ Shall we Miss Kazami?
‐ [Girl] Yes, let’s.
‐ [Girl] Let’s go Kousei.
‐ [Boy] Subaki.
‐ [Girl] Koishi,
you can go visit
Mr. Himaru right now you know.
‐ [Woman] What are
you talking about?
I know you’d be
lonely by yourself.
(girl chuckles)
(girls giggling)
‐ My big brother.
‐ Are you gonna keep
whining about that Karen?
‐ Miina, Karen, I almost
forgot, have you heard?
‐ Heard what?
‐ Well I heard that
there’s a ghost out here
that appears every night.
‐ What?
‐ There’s a ghost?
‐ I wonder if
everybody out there
is going at it right about now?
‐ We’ll find out later.
Oh nothing at all.
(girl laughs evilly)
‐ [Boy] Miss Kazami.
‐ Yes Kei?
Let’s make a memory, shall we?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Now!
Study, study, study!
Go to Tokyo University!
(boy laughs)
‐ [Girl Voiceover] Good
memory of the summer, huh?
‐ I won’t try anything.
I give you my word.
Trust me, please.
‐ Hey, Kousei.
You’ve gotta understand,
it’s not that I’m afraid
of being touched by a man,
but since it’s my first time,
I want it to be a
wonderful memory.
A memory I could carry
my whole life, you see?
Would you be gentle with me?
‐ Subaki.
Yeah, I promise.
I promise.
‐ Then it’ll latch
on to a guy and
won’t let go no matter what.
After that, it just sucks
the life out of the guy.
‐ Oh my!
‐ What is the ghost like?
Is it horrid looking?
‐ I’d heard that
she’s really pretty
with long flowing hair, a
beautiful face, and glasses.
I also heard that
her skin is so white
it’s practically
transparent and that
her build is slender yet
she’s really got big boobs.
‐ A gorgeous older
woman with glasses!
‐ Oh yeah, for some
reason she only goes after
younger boys who
are the loser type.
(boy yells)
Oh no, Karen!
‐ [Girl] That voice.
‐ Hyosuke, I heard
a strange voice.
‐ [Boy] I’m sure
it’s just Matagu
making a big fuss again
’cause he’s lonesome.
(couple giggling)
‐ No, don’t.
‐ [Girl] But it’s
dangerous Miina.
‐ I’m just gonna go
look around the area.
Please take care of Karen.
(girl yells)
Mike!
‐ Sorry.
Did I frighten you?
‐ No, I’m alright.
Did you hear that strange
voice a few minutes ago?
‐ Yeah.
I got worried and went to
look around for a little bit,
but I didn’t see
anything out there.
You know, I’m sure
it’s just Shidou senpai
making a fuss again.
‐ Okay.
I got it.
I guess that means you’re
going back to work, right?
Okay.
‐ Miina!
You wanna have some
coffee with me?
‐ Really?
‐ For the moment,
work has settled down.
I’m taking a break right now.
‐ Then I’d be
happy to come over.
‐ [Girl] I’ve been able
to get a lot of fun shots,
but the climax
has yet to happen.
(girl laughs evilly)
‐ [Mike] How’s Karen doing?
‐ When she heard that scream,
she had one of her
fainting spells.
‐ [Mike] Uh oh, is she alright?
‐ Haruko is staying
with her right now.
‐ [Mike] Okay.
Then it’ll be alright.
‐ Worried about
your little sister?
‐ [Mike] Don’t put it that way.
I’m just worried in
general, you know?
‐ Sorry.
I didn’t mean it
to sound that way.
I have so many other things
that I wanna say to you Mike.
You know, it’s
probably inappropriate,
but I’m really
thankful there was
all that commotion earlier.
‐ [Mike] Why is that?
‐ Because it gave
me the chance to
finally be alone here
with you tonight.
‐ [Mike] Miina, we
live in the same house.
‐ That’s not it.
You see Mike,
there’s something that I really
wanna tell you, and just you.
(slow piano music)
I decided a long time ago,
and I’m prepared to
take the consequences.
The only thing left is to
tell you how I really feel!
‐ [Mike] You can’t!
‐ And why not?
‐ ’Cause I’m saying it.
Sorry.
I knew how you were feeling and
I actually know how I feel now,
but I’ve been
really reluctant to
talk about it with you Miina.
‐ But why?
Because Karen’s around?
‐ No.
The thing is Miina,
you and I are living
together in the same house.
If I told you how I felt and we
ended up in that kind
of a relationship,
I wasn’t sure if I
could hold myself back.
‐ [Miina] Mike.
‐ Are you okay?
‐ Yeah.
Where’s Miss Miina?
‐ She stepped out for awhile.
(girl yells)
‐ [Mike] Hey Miina.
‐ Tell me Mike.
Tell me how you feel.
I won’t regret it.
If it’s with you,
I don’t mind what we
do with each other.
It’s alright.
Tell me, please Mike.
‐ Miina I feel like what
I’m trying to say is‐.
‐ No!
Miss Miina!
You can’t do that!
You can’t Miss Miina.
Don’t take my big brother
away from me, please.
Big brother is my big
brother and mine alone.
That’s absolutely,
definitely how it is.
‐ But why Karen?
Why can’t I be with him?
You don’t think we’d
make a good couple?
Do you hate me now?
I just don’t understand.
‐ No that’s not it.
See, if you become my
big brother’s girlfriend,
he’ll cherish you
over everyone else
and he’ll even
forget about the fact
that he has a little sister.
His girlfriend will be the
nearest and dearest to him
and all family will
come a distant second.
I couldn’t take that.
‐ Karen, do you honestly
think that would happen?
‐ And is that the
reason why you’ve
been so clingy to me lately?
‐ Idiot.
‐ [Mike] Yep.
You’re an idiot.
You know Karen, both my
family and my girlfriend
are dear to me at the same time.
More than one thing can
be dear to my heart.
Understand Karen?
‐ Karen, Mike is a big brother
to you and you alone but,
if you can, could you maybe
make him our Mike too?
The three of us are one when
we’re all together, right?
You were the one who said that.
‐ I’m so sorry Miss Miina.
Please forgive me, but I
was so worried Miss Miina.
I was really, really worried.
I’m sorry!
Miss Miina!
(man yells)
‐ Hot, hot, hot!
(girls yell)
‐ Mr. Mike!
‐ What is it?
‐ What’s going on?
‐ Miss Miyafuji,
your attire is...
(girl yells)
‐ Is there something
wrong, well Mr. Kamishiro?
‐ I think that was a great
punch line Kamishiro.
(girl laughs evilly)
‐ President Morino, why
do you have a camera?
What are you photographing?
‐ [Girl] Everything that
you guys have been doing.
‐ No way.
‐ Wait, that means.
(girl laughs evilly)
‐ A wonderful summer memory.
‐ [Mike] Madame President?
‐ [Karen] What’s
the matter with her?
‐ What the?
‐ What just happened?
(boy chuckling)
‐ This is just so perfect!
Glasses, all the woman, the
forbidden play of the masochist!
‐ A dramatic photo of the ghost
on the shore of Lake Kazaki has
been revealed to the public.
We have proceeded
with an undercover
investigation to verify
its authenticity.
After overcoming many obstacles,
we are pleased to
be able to introduce
you to a special guest,
the beautiful high
school girl who
managed to capture the
sinister ghost on film
as it was assaulting a
boy, Miss Ichigo Morino.
(girl laughs evilly)
‐ [Group] What a
summer break this is.
(upbeat music)
‐ [Boy] Hey, did you
see that horror special
on TV over summer vacation?
‐ [Boy] Yeah, the one where
our student council President
took a photo of
the ghost, right?
‐ [Girl] I heard that Haruko’s
big brother was the victim.
‐ [Girl] Yeah, and I heard that
he’s still in the hospital.
(girl yawns)
‐ I’m so sick of it.
Everyone in town is
talking about it.
‐ What is it Miss Miina?
‐ It’s Mike.
‐ [Karen] Who’s that
girl he’s with I wonder.
‐ [Miina] I don’t know.
I can’t really see her but,
he’s just accepted a letter.
‐ [Karen] No way!
‐ Karen.
‐ Miss Miina.
‐ [Girls] It’s time to
reform the love alliance.
‐ [Miina] Hey!
That’s my Mike!
‐ [Karen] And that’s
my big brother!
‐ [Girls] You better not
lay one finger on him!