[SOLDIERS yelling]
Hey, get up!
We're under fire,
we need backup! Radio!
Radio!
I'm looking forward to
our time together.
[KYOKO]
Such boldness!
[CHIDORI] Make out to
your heart's desire!
[MARDUKAS] Now, Sergeant Sagara,
if you should happen to commit
some sort of shameless
act against the captain,
I will tear you limb from limb!
[SOUSUKE yells]
[SOUSUKE]
Just a dream...
No, Mr. Sagara.
We shouldn't...
Please...
[SOUSUKE screams]
Okay, what's all the
racket in her-- Wah!
[SOUSUKE]
K-Kaname!
When... When
the heck did she--?
[SOUSUKE] I-It's not
what it looks like!
--I didn't do any--
--Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Hey, Tessa, I
thought you promised
that you'd stay
out of this room!
You broke the rules
that we agreed on!
No thanks, I couldn't
eat another bite.
Look, I'm not falling for it!
Now wake up, will ya?!
Kaname, don't be so rough.
[CHIDORI] Shut up!
It's your fault, too!
You left yourself open!
No, I don't mind.
Just go ahead and fire.
[SOUSUKE]
Fire what?
[inaudible dialogue]
[MAO]
It's your last weekend here.
Let's see... what should we do?
[TESSA]
Oh, I've already made plans.
I'm spending two days
and one night
at a hot spring in Okutama.
Miss Kaname and her
friends are invited, too.
[MAO &amp; SOUSUKE]
A hot spring?
Yes! No trip to
Japan is complete
without a hot spring visit.
He strongly recommended it.
He recommended it?
You don't mean...
[KURZ]
Hi! Good morning to everybody!
[ALL]
Good morning to you, too.
[KURZ] I'm Kurz Weber, and
I'm gonna be your coordinator.
I'm a student of Tessa's
dad at the college.
Let's be good friends.
Just call me Kurz-baby.
[SHINJI]
Excuse me, Kurz-baby?
I didn't say the boys could--
[KURTZ screams]
Sorry about that.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Melissa Mao, a
research student at the college.
It looks like I've
already met some of you.
If you have any problems,
just ask me, okay?
This is one heck of a party...
Three whole hours
cramped in a car
with three other guys...
it's torture I tell ya!
Oh, you don't have to tell me.
I know all too well.
--Who asked Mao to take charge?
--This is gonna be so much fun!
Hey, Sousuke, you look
awfully relaxed back there.
[SOUSUKE garbles]
[KURZ] Okay, all I hear
is a mouth full of jerky.
Not a problem. I appreciate
the lack of female disruption.
[KURTZ &amp; ONO D sigh]
Yeah, in any case,
as you know, gentlemen...
we'll be staying at the
hot springs lodge tonight.
[BOYS]
Yeah!
[KURZ] A bunch of young
guys and girls on a trip to
the hot springs.
You know what that means?
[SHINJI]
Un-unh.
Huh? You don't...
Y-You don't mean "that"?!
That's right, I mean "that".
--A trip to a hot spring
--Hey, you want some of these?
--isn't complete without "that".
--Oh, yes, they look delicious.
--[ONO D] Oh, I get it!
--How about you guys?
--Not doing "that" would be rude
--No thanks, I'm on a diet
--to the girls.
--right now.
[KURZ] Exactly Ono D! I think
we'll get along just fine.
[ONO D]
Yes, I think we will.
[KURTZ &amp; ONO D laugh]
[SOUSUKE garbles]
[KURZ]
Again with the jerky?
[KYOKO]
Wow! It's gorgeous, huh?
Yeah, it's a fantastic view!
Well, it looks like
we have a fair amount
of time before dinner.
Hey, Kaname, you feel up to
going to the open air bath?
Mmm, I guess so, but--
Are you worried about something?
Well, Kurz is here and
all, so I was wondering
if they might be
plotting something sketchy.
Oh, you don't need
to worry about that.
[TESSA] It'll be okay. Even
Mr. Weber wouldn't be that lewd.
Actually, I would be
that lewd, Miss Tessa.
[KURTZ chuckles]
Our prey's on the move,
heading for the open air bath.
Alright, we should
get moving too.
Um, Kurz, are you
sure about all this?
Don't worry.
Let's get going, okay?
[SOUSUKE]
Kurz. Going to the bath?
Oh, you want in? Then get ready
for a little taste of Heaven.
That's not what I meant.
[KURZ]
Huh?
[SOUSUKE] Enjoy your bath
like normal. Nice and normal.
Hey, what does that mean?
Kurz, let's go!
I'm comin'.
[SOUSUKE]
What peaceful scenery...
Wow, what a pretty
view out here!
You see? Didn't I
tell you, Kaname?
Hey, look over there! A river!
[KYOKO]
Oh, wow!
Better not lean over too much,
or you're gonna fall.
[CHIDORI]
We're fine.
[REN] This certainly is
a rather nice hot spring.
And the water
temperature is perfect, too.
I could just relax here
in the open air.
Here's to sweet freedom.
By the way, do you know
what benefits this spring
is supposed to have?
I think it helps headaches
and stiff shoulders.
[MAO]
Huh? Nothing for pretty skin?
But you shouldn't have
to worry about that.
You have pretty skin already!
[MAO] Really? But my skin
gets some rough treatment
in my line of work.
Oh, that's right. Hey, Tessa!
Stop being so shy and
get out here, will ya?
[TESSA] I-I'm sorry. I guess
the thought of stepping out
into the open air bath just
makes me a little nervous.
You're sure it's alright?
Look, don't worry, it's fine.
Come over here, and I'll
wash your back for you.
[TESSA]
Oh, thank you.
[TESSA screams]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
You really are one
hardcore klutz, aren't you?
Tessa, you alright over there?
[TESSA] Yes, but my butt
hurts a little bit now.
[MAO]
Where, let me see?
[TESSA] M-Melissa! Stop! Please
don't stare at me like that.
[MAO] It looks like you
just scraped it a bit.
But you have really nice skin.
[TESSA]
Th-That's off-limits!
[MAO] Oh, come on.
Lemme see there, too.
[TESSA]
Th-There too? Wah!
[MAO]
What if I do this? Does it hurt?
[TESSA]
No. That's fine...
[TESSA squeals]
Kazama! Hey, come on,
man, snap out of it.
Oh, man, she's the best ever.
[ONO D]
What are you blabbering?
Hey, Kurz, Kazama
collapsed over here.
[KURZ] That proves he's
nothing but a kid.
We're just gettin' started here!
[ONO D]
Uh, your nose.
Anyway, what now?
We can't see over unless we
get on each other's shoulders.
That's where these come in.
An electric drill and
a fiber-optic scope?
Oh, I see.
You carry around the
same kinda stuff as Sousuke.
Don't worry. Well, here we go.
[KYOKO] Hey, Mao,
Tessa says you know a bunch
of foreign languages.
How'd you learn 'em?
[MAO]
Men. M-E-N.
[KYOKO]
Men?
[MAO] Well, the
secret to improving
is to learn while you're in bed.
[GIRLS giggle]
Isn't it done yet?
Wait a sec,
something's not right.
There's a metal plate
behind the wall!
Maybe to keep guys from peeking?
[KURZ] This metal... it's what
the military uses for armor.
[KURZ]
Fine. If that's how it is...
[ONO D]
Can you reach yet?
[KURZ]
Almost.
[ONO D]
How 'bout now?
[KURZ]
Almost...
I don't like having THAT
on the back of my head.
Almost there...
[KURTZ shouts]
[yelling]
[splashing]
[GIRLS]
Huh?
Okay, why's there
a security gun?
What kind of inn is this?!
What's he talkin' about?
I guess it must be the latest
security system or something.
What if I try to go
around this side?
Damn, there's no opening!
[BOTH]
Whoa!
[MAO]
This is like a feast!
[KYOKO]
Yeah, you're right!
[MIZUKI] It was worth
coming all this way,
and the path was so relaxing.
[REN]
Yes, it was nice!
[MIZUKI]
Wanna go back in later?
[KYOKO]
Oh, I'll go, too!
[MIZUKI]
Sounds like a plan.
[REN]
I agree.
Looks like we still
have a chance.
We do, but normal methods
won't break through
that security system.
So we'll have to come
up with a good plan.
I agree, rookie, but
first let's eat while we can.
We'll have to attack
from a distance.
We can get them with
night vision scopes
from the summit
facing the inn.
The best observation
points are here and here.
How 'bout here? It's faster
going in a straight line, right?
No good,
that's in the west,
and the topography
makes it sunny there,
so the vegetation will be thick.
There's no way we'll be
able to capture our target.
Oh, I see. You're pretty
smart, you know that?
I'm a sniper. Knowing
how to read a map
--is a specialty for me.
--A sniper?
Alright, prepare to move out.
[SOUSUKE]
Kurz. Going to the bath again?
That's right,
something wrong with that?
There's nothing wrong.
It's just that...
It's just what?
[SOUSUKE] Enjoy your bath
like normal. Nice and normal.
[ONO D]
Kurz let's go!
I'm comin'.
[TESSA]
Um... this one!
Oh yeah!
Ah! The joker again?
I guess he must really like you.
Funny, I think the
joker fits you better.
What did you say?
Hey, now...
[KYOKO] Hey, don't you
think Ono D and the guys
were acting kind
of down earlier?
Oh, you were thinking that, too?
[KYOKO]
I wonder why...
[MIZUKI]
I don't know...
Let's go, Ren.
Be right there!
[KYOKO]
Shinji didn't look too good.
[MIZUKI]
Think he got the chills?
[SHINJI sneezes]
You have the chills?
[KURZ]
Be careful where you step.
[SHINJI] Hey, Kurz, at least let
me use a flashlight, come on.
Not a chance. We'll be
spotted by the enemy.
[ONO D] But we gotta hurry.
They'll be outta the bath
by the time we get there.
[KURZ]
Ono D, Kazama, it's a trap.
[SHINJI gasps]
[SHINJI screams]
What's wrong, Kazama?
[SHINJI] I think I stepped...
on a landmine.
You think what?
Landmine?! You mean
that kind of landmine?
Wait a second.
What the hell kind of inn
is booby-trapped
with landmines?!
No way, this has Sousuke
written all over it!
[KURZ] Yeah... that bastard.
Did he come here yesterday?
He must have won
over the innkeeper
and then set his traps.
And Mao...
Pl-Please help me...
Don't worry,
we won't abandon you.
[KURZ]
There it is.
Alright, Kazama, shift
your weight slowly now.
Got it. Very... slowly.
[ONO D whimpers]
[SHINJI sobs]
[KURZ]
Just a little more...
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[SOUSUKE hums]
What fools they are.
That's it, I can't
take it anymore!
Even with infinite
lives I couldn't!
Yeah, that's right. I mean,
why are we still alive anyway?
[KURZ]
Kazama...
[BOYS]
Huh?
[KURZ] I won't force you
to do anything, but...
are you sure you
wanna run away now?
[KURZ] See, even
I'm afraid of dying,
and sometimes
I wanna run away,
but I believe there are
some things in this world
that you just can't give up,
even if you have
to risk your life...
Something that
makes you feel
"as long as I can
get through this,
I can live my whole
life with pride."
Having something you can
get that passionate about
is important, don't you think?
That's why I'm not
going to give up.
That's why I'm going to fight.
My hero...
It's not like me to say stuff
like that, but well anyway...
I'm going to go on alone.
Maybe you two should...
Huh?
Wait, you mean you guys...?
[KURZ]
Time is running out.
This is our last chance.
I'm only going to tell
you this once, so listen good.
--There's only one way
--[KYOKO] UNO!
to attack this situation:
We have to climb this
slope and get our eyes
on the target directly.
[SHINJI] But they have
that security system.
[ONO D]
Yeah!
[KURZ] Right. That's why you two
are going to climb the slope
first as decoys.
[SHINJI]
Huh?
[ONO D]
Hey, no fair!
[KURZ]
There's nothing to worry about.
There's about a two
second delay between
the time those guns
identify their target
and the time they fire.
And in those
two seconds...
I'll find where they are
and finish them off...
with this.
[SHINJI] A VSS Vintorez?
But something like that
is almost impossible.
[KURZ]
I can do it. Trust me.
[ONO D &amp; SHINJI whimper]
[KURTZ breathes deeply]
Now!
[SHINJI &amp; ONO D scream]
[KURZ]
Where are you? Come on out!
Gotcha!
[BOTH scream]
Don't stop, keep going!
[KURZ]
Crap.
[ONO D screams]
Damn, another landmine?!
Kazama, get down, now!
[KURZ screams]
[KURZ]
Hey, are you alright Ono D?
[KURZ screams]
Son of a...
[SHINJI]
Kurz!
Kurz, are you alright?
I messed up.
Come on, you
can't wimp out now,
your butt just got
burned that's all.
It's alright. I know
the limits of my body
better than you
can imagine, so...
[KURZ grunts]
[SHINJI]
Kurz!
[KURZ] What are you hanging
around here for?
Hurry or you'll miss the target!
[SHINJI]
But...
Go, Kazama! Don't let
our deaths be for nothing!
If you don't move it, I'll lose
any respect I have for you.
Now go! Go and burn the image
of those girls into your mind.
Pass it on to
the next generation.
Tell them the tale of the
victory we earned here!
Go on. Go!
Don't just stand there.
Run, now! What are
you doing? Hurry!
And you call yourself
a man, Kazama?
[SHINJI screams]
Yes, that's it. Now run, Kazama.
Go run up that slope.
[SHINJI screams]
[SHINJI] I can see it! I can see
it! Kurz, I can see the enemy!
[SHINJI screams]
[SHINJI] I got it! The target!
It's right in front of meeee!
The men's and women's
baths switch places at ten.
It seems like only yesterday
that Miss Testarossa
came here as an
exchange student.
But it's time for
her to go now.
Well, I know it was
only for a short time,
but did you have fun
while you were here?
[TESSA]
Yes!
[KYOKO] Um, excuse me!
All of us have prepared
something for you today.
What is it, Kyoko?
[KYOKO]
This is for you!
Best of luck back home, too!
[CLASS cheers]
[GIRL]
It was great to meet you!
[cheering continues]
[GIRL 2]
I'm so glad I got to know you!
[GIRL 3] Thanks for coming,
it was great to see you.
[cheering continues]
Thanks so much.
I'll do my best...
Really, thank you...
everybody...
I'll never forget this...
[cheering continues]
[TESSA] Thank you everyone.
I really, really mean it.
Good work. I'll be
taking command now.
Aye, aye, Captain.
The Captain will now
resume command.
Start the engine.
[SOLDIER]
Starting engine.
[SOLDIER] Run a performance
check on all leaks!
[MARDUKAS]
Captain.
[TESSA]
What is it?
[SOLDIER]
This is damage control...
[MARDUKAS]
How was your R&amp;R?
[TESSA]
It was nice. Very nice.
I will endeavor to
do everything I can
to protect them, no matter what.
[WOMAN] Initiating final
check. A group - check.
--Well I'm glad to hear that.
--B group - check.
C group - check.
Awaiting XO approval.
All checks complete, ma'am.
Very well. Ahead at
one-third top speed.
Aye, ma'am. All ahead
at one-third top speed.
[SOLDIER]
Ahead at one-third speed.
[TESSA] I will protect them,
no matter what.
And that's everything.
Well, she's gone, huh?
Yeah.
You feel relaxed?
I guess so.
[CHIDORI] But... you're actually
gonna miss her a little,
aren't you?
N-No, not really.
[CHIDORI] Me too.
I think I'm gonna miss her
a little bit, too.
[CHIDORI] Duty and humanity!
A world of manly chivalry.
[KURZ] Hey Missy, you
better watch your tongue.
[CHIDORI] Patience, patience,
and more patience!
[KURZ] What? Give up
without a struggle?
[CHIDORI] A light snow
that soaks the heart.
[KURZ] You gonna let me
handle this or what?
[CHIDORI]
Shut up!
[SOUSUKE] Next time: "A Fancy
Without Honor or Humanity."
We dedicate this story to the
late director, Kenji Fukusaku.
[CHIDORI] Stop it! I don't think
he'd appreciate that.