[SOUSUKE] So the problem's with
this gym equipment shed?
[KYOKO] Yeah, the door's
locked from the inside,
and we can't seem
to get it open.
It's creepy. We can hear
noises and voices from inside,
so we came to you
to check it out for us.
Yes, you made the right
decision. I can handle this.
[BOY 1]
Isn't it ready yet? Hurry up!
[SHINJI]
Right. Okay, finished.
[BOY 2]
Whoa, this is awesome.
[BOY 2] It's so good. It was
risky, but man was it worth it!
Too bad it's only
us enjoying it.
We could make a killing selling
this stuff under the table.
[SHINJI]
No way, we'd get caught.
[SOUSUKE]
Narcotics. I'm sure of it.
--Narcotics?!
As head of security and adjunct
to the student body president,
I can't let this slide.
Stand back.
Hey, um, Sousuke, what are you--
[GIRLS scream]
[explosion, screaming]
Hold it right there!
Don't attempt to resist.
Just surrender.
Huh?
Sousuke, wait a sec.
What's going on?
Hmm?
[SHINJI screams]
[SHINJI] Look what you did!
They're all ruined!
They're all what?!
He's right!
Okay, what were
you doing in here?
--We were developing pictures!
[BOY 1 sobs]
It was hard enough just
trying to get these shots!
Yeah, thanks a lot, Sousuke.
What did we ever
do to deserve this?
I had no idea this is
what you were doing in here.
So you decided to shoot
off a freakin' stun grenade?!
So why are you
developing film out here?
The softball team
needs this shed.
[GIRLS]
Mm-hmm.
We're sorry for all the
trouble we caused you.
But it's just that
the photography club
doesn't have its own clubroom.
What was that for?
You can't just use
rooms without permission.
I'm tired of telling you!
[GUITARIST]
Yeah, we know, but...
[DRUMMER] We don't have
any place to practice.
[COOK GIRL]
Miss Chidori!
[CHIDORI]
What?
The biology club's doing
an experiment on cockroaches
right next to
where we're making lasagna.
[COOK GIRL]
Tell 'em to stop!
[CHIDORI] What are you doing?!
We have a biology
room, go use that!
Yeah, well
the thing is...
the amateur karate club
is in there right now.
[ISSEI yells]
Tsubaki!
Chid--
[crash]
Captain!
Tsubaki!
You okay?
Oh, hi, Chidori, what's up?
[CHIDORI]
Stop playing around in here!
We're not playing!
Me and the other karate club
members were just studying
how to fight in a
space full of obstacles.
--Mm-hmm.
Well stop it. You're
bothering other people.
Go find somewhere
else to practice.
[KARATE BOYS] What are you
complaining for, girlie?
I mean, you're the one
who kicked us out
of our dojo in the
first place, ya know.
We're the victims here. We're
like poor lost little lambs.
You should feel sorry for us.
[blows landing]
[KARATE BOYS]
Now what did you do that for?
Shut it!
Stop taking so much pride in
how miserably pathetic you are.
[KARATE BOYS groan]
Anyway, I do feel bad for you,
but you can't practice in here.
Alright. Chidori, we're sorry.
Thank you. As long
as you understand.
Tsubaki, you're a
real sensible guy.
You... think so?
[CHIDORI]
Yeah. Okay, thanks a lot.
[KARATE BOYS chuckling]
[ISSEI] Hmm...?
[blows landing]
Just what the heck
are you grinning at?!
Man, it's just been one
thing after another today.
The photo club's
had problems, too.
[CHIDORI]
Hmm?
They don't have
a clubroom,
so they were using the equipment
shed as a darkroom.
Somehow our school
never has enough rooms
for our clubs to meet in.
Then what if we were
to construct a new clubroom
up on the roof of the school.
I have no problem
aquiring temporary barracks
from the U.S. Army really cheap.
Really? That's a great idea!
But there aren't any windows,
so the air circulation is bad.
In the summer it would
be like a steam sauna.
Then that idea's rejected!
Excellent work, Miss Chidori.
And where have you been?
I was having a
discussion with someone.
Oh, really.
Well, we've been here
trying to figure out what to do
about the shortage of clubrooms.
Yes, as was I.
One of the clubrooms
has just become available.
There are only two members
in the social science club,
so they've graciously agreed
to give up their room.
[CHIDORI]
Oh, that's great!
That being said, they gave us
a rather unusual demand...
regarding how to
decide which club
would get to use the newly
available room.
And what is it?
Each club is to
attract as many people
of the opposite sex as it can.
The one that draws
the most wins.
But that sounds like...
Flirting!
This is the perfect
weather for flirting.
We from the social science club
would like to thank you all
for supporting our
project today.
[ALL]
Yeah...
Please allow me to
introduce myself.
I am the president of the social
science club, Shiro Nanba.
I'll go over the
rules one more time.
Each club will select three
members to do the flirting.
Whichever club is able to draw
in the most people will win.
We will count the number
of people who are present
at this square at
four o'clock PM.
Bring 'em, or tell 'em
to be here.
Be creative, okay? We'll
start registration now.
[CHIDORI] I can't believe
it's actually starting...
[KYOKO] I guess they all
really want a room.
Are we supposed to
participate as well?
No, we're just observers
for the student council.
And I'm just a rubber-necker.
Huh?
Hold it. Just what do
you think you're doing?
You're going to be
taking part, too?
Affirmative.
But wait, Sousuke, you're
not a member of any clubs.
That's incorrect.
I joined the school
photo club just yesterday.
I'm already listed
in their records.
We asked Sousuke if
he'd give us a hand,
because he's a pretty
good-looking guy and he's brave.
Plus he owes us for
completely ruining our film,
so he agreed. Right?
[SOUSUKE] Mm-hmm. Affirmative.
[ISSEI] You asked him? Damn!
I should've thought of that.
Well it's too late
to realize that now.
Since I've signed on
to this fight,
you have no chance to win.
The new room belongs
to the photography club.
What's that? Just how
far are you gonna go
to try and get in
my way, Sagara?
Uh... Wait...
You won't get in my way.
What does that mean?
Oh, nothing, best of luck to ya.
[laughing]
What's so funny?
Well, because.
Sagara, you think you're gonna
get any girls in that getup?
It's quite functional,
and I think that you are
the ones who look foolish.
Oh really, you think so, huh?
Then why don't we make a bet?
If you're able to
get even one girl,
then I will treat you to
lunch for two whole weeks.
But if you can't
get any girls...
Let's see...
You have to swim in that lake
totally naked. How's that?
Fine with me.
[crowd chattering excitedly]
We're holding you to it.
Whoa, hold it, Sousuke.
I know you're tough,
but are you sure about this?
No problem.
Sousuke, do you even
know what flirting means?
Yeah, I explained it all to him.
It's just a girl hunt, right?
Shouldn't be hard.
"Shouldn't be hard"?
Correct. Given my
strength, getting women
will be a pretty simple job.
Gentlemen, let the
contest begin!
[NANBA] This is a
part of social science.
"Social science"?
Right. Tell me,
what kind of person
does someone of the opposite
sex find easy to trust?
An honest person, a
liar, a frivolous person?
Or is there a completely
different theory behind it all?
I thought I'd take a little
sample and find out for myself.
Uh... Oh.
Hi, excuse me, Miss,
would you like to-
[grunts]
[CHIDORI]
Whoa, that was rough.
Hey, look.
Isn't that Sasaki, the
one in charge of supplies
for the student body?
[CHIDORI] Yeah, and I think he's
also a member of the model club.
[GIRLS laughing]
[SASAKI]
Um, excuse me...
Huh? What?
[SASAKI chuckles nervously]
S-Say, Miss...
would you like to have
a cup of tea with me?
Huh? You with some cult?
Or are you trying to pick us
up to... to make fun of us?
[SASAKI] Then how 'bout
karaoke or something.
What a dork.
You wanna sing anime songs?
[GIRL 2]
I think you're right!
[GIRLS laugh]
Man, that's gotta sting.
Sasaki, hang in there.
Listen, jerk, stop staring
at me with those nasty eyes!
You give me the creeps!
I'm-I'm sorry, Miss.
Turn three times
and bark like a dog.
Then we'll let you take
us out for some tea.
Damn lousy... Screw you!
Who would ever want to talk to
stuck-up snobs like you anyway?
I just want a room
where I can take my time
and make my models.
All the model kits
I haven't finished yet
cry out to me every
single night begging me,
pleading me to complete them!
Can one-to-one perfect
grade ugly figures
like the two of you possibly
understand their burning,
all-consuming anguish?
Oh, stop it, Sasaki!
Okay, you made
your point already!
Let go! I'm not done!
I'll fix them
with poly putty!
That's right, you selfish
old-type bitches...!
That won't get
them any points...
[NANBA] It would appear that the
model club's case is hopeless.
[GUITARIST] Then we'll
see you babes
at the plaza at the park
at four o'clock.
[GIRL 3]
Okay, we'll be there.
[GIRL 4]
But why can't we just go now?
Well, there's uh...
circumstances.
Wow, they're as
good as I thought.
That deserves
about an 80, right?
[NANBA] The music club
is taking this too easy.
The secret is to
ask enough girls.
You'll eventually get one.
Well, that sounds easy enough.
Look, any guy can dress up nice.
And if he tries to talk
to, say, 10 girls,
then in the very worst case,
there will be at least one
girl who will listen to him.
And most times, the one
girl who does bother to stop
and listen will stick it
out with him to the end.
If he walks around
for a whole day,
then one girl is sure to give
him her real phone number.
All a guy needs is a
little bit of fortitude.
Oh, so that's how it works.
I take it he speaks
from experience, huh?
[CHIDORI] Hey, aren't they
from the karate club?
[KYOKO]
Are they cosplaying?
Here's some pretty
cute chicks, huh?
When you look at
me with those scared,
bunny rabbit eyes, it gets
me even more charged up.
[KYOKO] Looks more like
kidnapping than flirting.
[ISSEI]
Stop right there!
[GIRLS sigh]
[ISSEI whimpers]
Listen, can't you tell
they don't like you?
So let them go, now!
Huh? Who the hell are you?!
Stupid brat!
We're gonna beat your ass!
[yelling]
[ISSEI] Hmph.
What?!
[KARATE BOY 2 yells]
Justice prevails!
It's no use, he's too tough!
We won't forget this!
Oh, so the ally of
justice strategy.
So, are you ladies okay?
[GIRL 5]
Yeah, we're okay.
[GIRL 6]
You saved us.
That's good.
Well, um, if you
wanna thank me,
then I have a favor to ask you.
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[ISSEI] Could you um,
come to the stage of that park
at four o'clock this afternoon?
All of you.
[GIRL 7]
But why?
Uh... I'll, uh,
I'll tell you then.
Just make sure you come, okay?
See ya!
I think I'd give that a 60.
If he's gonna do this,
he should make sure the girls
say they'll actually come.
Oh, look, it's Kazama.
[CHIDORI]
Ugh! Look at her!
[KYOKO] I wonder if Shinji
likes that kind of girl...?
So his strategy
is to beg and plead?
[CHIDORI &amp; KYOKO gasp]
Down here.
[PROSTITUTE]
Yeah, sure.
It'll be quick.
Gedor calling Ascheros, code
six, delta, bravo, sierra, over.
[SOUSUKE]
Ascheros, roger. Proceed.
[PROSTITUTE]
Hey, what are you doin'?
S-Sorry, it's nothing.
Just got a call
from a friend of mine.
Yeah? What kind of
friend? He a foreigner?
[SHINJI]
Yes, something like that.
Okay, how 'bout right here?
[PROSTITUTE] I don't
care where ya do it,
just take the picture,
you little pervert.
--If you make me wait,
--[SHINJI] This is Gedor,
--I'll add an extra charge.
--guidance complete. Go.
--Thirty-thousand is too cheap--
--[SOUSUKE] Ascheros, roger.
Wh-What the hell is this?!
[PROSTITUTE screams]
Ascheros success.
This makes six now.
[PROSTITUTE] Bastards,
what's going on here?!
Let me out of this thing!
[SOUSUKE]
Quiet down.
Yelling will only
shorten your lifespan.
[SHINJI] Sousuke...
I think we may have gotten
on the wrong track here.
Using money as
bait to lure them
is the most reliable way
to ensnare them.
Well, yes, I do want the room,
but... I don't know about this.
[SOUSUKE]
What are you talking about?
You're the one who told me
that flirting is a girl hunt.
[GIRLS yelling]
[SHINJI] I didn't think you'd
hunt girls for real, though!
It might be too late
now to say this...
but I think we've
committed a big crime.
[SOUSUKE]
No, we'll let them go tonight.
It's catch and release.
No problem.
[CHIDORI]
There's a big problem!
[SHINJI]
K-Kaname!
Kaname, what's wrong?
Why you stupid...
[CHIDORI]
Let them go! Now!
R-Right!
[GIRLS screaming]
[slap]
[SOUSUKE]
That hurts you know.
[CHIDORI] Shut up right now!
Didn't you ever stop and think
what you were doing was
just a little strange?!
Sorry, I still don't
get this flirting thing...
[CHIDORI growls frustratedly]
Fine. Let me explain it to you:
[CHIDORI rambles
unintelligbly in fast-forward]
[CHIDORI]
Got it? That is flirting.
I can't do that...
Well, don't look at me!
[SOUSUKE grunts]
You're hopeless. I can't
believe you didn't know that.
[SOUSUKE] This is bad.
I didn't expect this.
What are you gonna do, Sousuke?
You made that promise, you know?
Hey, Kaname, can't you let us
trap just one girl like before?
Not even. What makes you
think I'd even consider it?
Well, our club
needs the room,
but more importantly,
Sousuke's in trouble.
And why am I supposed
to care about that?
You think I'm his keeper?
But Kaname...
It's an opportunity to
think about what you did.
You're always
going out of control,
and then you leave me
to pick up after you.
If something had gone wrong,
you wouldn't be the
only one in trouble...
You would have gotten
everyone in school involved
due to your lack of judgment.
[SOUSUKE]
Sorry. You have a point.
Sousuke?
I'll use a frontal attack
and try to talk to
girls like normal.
There's a possibility
at least one of them
will have an uncommon
interest in military affairs.
Pardon me,
would you like to hear
about the new Javelin missile?
Do you wanna know the real names
of defense agency spies?
Would you like to
know an efficient way
to shoot your target?
[CHIDORI]
This will be good for him.
If he keeps going
like he has been,
he'll never fit in
with Japanese culture.
Would you like top-secret
data about the Soviet Navy?
Oh, yes, thank you.
I'll be 88 this year.
No, um, what I meant to say--
[OLD WOMAN] I came
to buy something
for my grandson's
birthday party today.
He looks a little like you.
He... looks like me?
He's a very sweet,
honest good boy.
I just don't know
what kind of gift he'd like...
[SOUSUKE] How's this?
It's a French army tank,
called a Leclerc,
and it's equipped with,
among other things,
an innovative
modular shielding system.
Thank you very much
for all your help today.
[SOUSUKE]
No need to thank me.
Be careful on your way home.
[CHIDORI sighs]
Hi, Nanba, is that you? Kaname.
I'm not feeling all that well.
Yeah, I'm going home early.
I'm sorry. Thanks, bye.
Well, see ya. Best of
luck to you, Sousuke.
[OLD WOMAN]
Thank you, dear.
[NANBA] We've added
up the totals.
First off, in third place,
with a total of three girls
is the fishing club.
Next, in second place,
with a total of five girls
is the music club.
Frankly, I thought they
would do a little better.
And finally,
in first place
with an incredible
total of eleven girls...
it's the amateur karate club!
[KARATE BOYS cheer]
Look, I came all the
way out here with you,
because I thought you were cute,
so what's the deal with
this big ol' mob.
Tsubaki, is this why you told
us to meet you at this park?
[NANBA] Which means our old room
now belongs to the karate club!
[crowd applauds]
[GUITARIST] Hey, Sagara,
how many girls
did your club pick up?
Zero.
Zero, so in other words,
you couldn't even
get one single girl.
Affirmative.
Then I guess you gotta
take your clothes off and
go swim naked.
[DRUMMER laughs]
Sousuke...
[GIRL]
Yeah! Take it off!
I told him so...
[SOUSUKE sighs]
Alright fine. A promise
is still a promise.
[CROWD] Take it off.
Take it off. Take it off.
[chanting continues]
[GIRLS squeal]
[WOMAN] Pardon me
for interrupting.
I apologize for keeping
you waiting, Mr. Sagara.
[MUSIC CLUB whimpers]
Uh... Who are you?
Stop. Don't speak.
Weren't you the gentleman
who insisted I come out to
the park this afternoon?
It was so difficult to slip out
without my husband noticing.
Husband?
Oh, she's someone's wife.
I believe you promised...
that we would share
a dinner together, correct?
Y-Yeah...?
I've... been looking
forward to this.
Well, shall we go then?
Huh? I, uh...
[WOMAN]
So long everyone. Take care.
[crowd murmurs in disbelief]
[GIRL]
I can't believe it!
[BOY]
Look at that hot chick!
[SOUSUKE] Who... Who is she?
I don't remember talking
to a girl like this.
It seems you had a
narrow escape, Mr. Sagara.
Yes! Who are you?
[WOMAN]
My... don't you remember me?
We see each other every day...
It makes me so sad...
I-I-I'm very sorry, ma'am.
But I don't remember.
What, you really don't know?
N-No, ma'am, I'm afraid I don't.
[giggling]
[WOMAN]
I can't take it!
[laughing]
I did it! Am I amazing or what?
In other words, success!
[SOUSUKE]
K-Kaname?!
Mm-hmm. You couldn't tell?!
You really didn't know?
Yes! It was perfect!
[CHIDORI giggles]
[CHIDORI]
You know, you should thank me.
I went all the way
back to my house
and took out my
mother's kimono to wear.
Oh, so that's it.
Mm-hmm.
You know, you always
manage to surprise me.
Don't I? But I think
there's something else
that you're wanting
to tell me as well.
Yes. Um, thank you.
Try again.
[SOUSUKE]
I'm very sorry.
[CHIDORI]
Idiot...
[SOUSUKE] I'll definitely pay
you back for this.
[CHIDORI]
Wrong!
[SOUSUKE]
I'll be more careful.
[CHIDORI growls]
You look quite... lovely.
Heh!
That's the first time
you've told me...
[CHIDORI] A lot's happened,
but now it's almost over,
and the last show's about
a biological weapon?!
[SOUSUKE] Affirmative.
A tragic even suddenly
befalls a peaceful school.
Young lives
disappear one by one.
[CHIDORI]
Hold it, isn't this a comedy?!
[SOUSUKE
You're being naïve!
The slaughter will
win its acclaim
as a controversial story.
It's a surefire
strategy for victory.
[CHIDORI]
No, I don't wanna die!
[SOUSUKE]
Next time: "5th Period Hotspot."
A shocking ending which
is sure to be a milestone
in Japanese anime history.
Stay tuned until
the last moment...