[KAGURAZAKA]
Yes! Good morning, class!
[STUDENTS]
Good morning, Ms. Kagurazaka.
Today, we're holding
a sketching event.
As this is an activity
outside school grounds,
I ask that all of you act
in an appropriate manner.
[STUDENTS]
Yes ma'am.
Especially Sagara.
Is that understood?
Yes, I will put my
skills to good use
and defend the safety
of our cherished school.
It's a privilege, ma'am.
I mean do you understand
the word "appropriate"?
[SOUSUKE] Yes, I'll be sure to
use the appropriate weapons.
[KAGURAZAKA]
No!
[STUDENTS scream]
[KAGURAZAKA clears throat]
And now we'll hear a few words
from Mr. Mizuhoshi,
the Art Teacher!
Our theme is
"humans and nature."
It's been quite some
time since the cry went out
over environmental issues.
So, capturing the relationship
between humans and nature
with your youthful sensibilities
and within the boundaries of
a frame is an activity fraught
with all kinds of meaning.
If we assume that the
word "frame" could hold
negative value, in view of our
reckless courage and daring
to refer to superficial
philosophical problems
and cognitive theory,
this would truly be a ladder
meant to be thrown away.
The limitations of the so-called
structuralistic approach
have been happening for
some time now--
--Excuse me, Mr. Mizuhoshi...?
--[MIZUHOSHI continues rambling]
Yes, what, Ms. Kagurazaka?
[KAGURAZAKA] Since we don't
have time, please summarize.
Oh, right, I forgot.
[STUDENTS sigh]
Put simply, our theme
is "humans and nature."
It's been quite some time
since the cry went out
over environmental issues.
So, capturing the relationship
--between humans and nat--
--[STUDENTS groan]
In short, we just draw a person
and the scenery together.
And we have to choose a
model from one of us here.
[GIRL] That's it?
What was the lecture for?
[BOY] What can you say?
He's an idiot.
So, do we have any
candidates for the model?
[STUDENTS grumbling]
Well, how 'bout Sousuke then?
He looks like he'd be
good at standing still.
Since you consider me good
enough, then I will volunteer.
[STUDENTS applaud]
Okay, let's decide on a pose.
Mmm?
[MIZUHOSHI]
And now for Class 4.
Look, you guys, making him
stand on his head all day
would be unreasonable.
No more unreasonable than
doing the Reverse Bridge
like you said.
[ONO D]
He can do it if he tries.
[KYOKO]
No he can't.
You're Class 4, aren't you?
Have you selected a model?
Yes, it's me.
[MIZUHOSHI]
Your name?
[SOUSUKE]
Sousuke Sagara.
Then Class 4... is Sagara.
Sir, this is my first time
serving in this capacity.
In order to carry
out my mission,
I wish to receive
your instruction
on what a model must do.
That is a great question!
Questioning the very
essence of such a thing
is not something your
average student could do.
I'm honored, sir.
[MIZUHOSHI clears throat]
The role of the model
is very important.
And by that, you mean...?
[MIZUHOSHI] You are to
become one with nature!
Blending with the plants,
you cause accepted ideas
to break down.
You mask them, and
thus ensnare them.
To express this process plainly,
[MIZUHOSHI rambles
incoherently in high-speed]
I will do my best to apply this.
[ONO D]
No, he bats right!
[CHIDORI]
I said no!
Uh... Okay, we'll just go
ahead and have the model
sit underneath that tree.
[KYOKO]
That's so boring.
Sousuke, come sit down by--
Uh? Uh... Huh? Where is he?
Um, does anyone know?
Now that you mention it...
He's probably off
to the bathroom.
[phone ringing]
[SOUSUKE]
Sagara here.
Sousuke! You come back
here right now!
[SOUSUKE]
I cannot do that.
What?
[SOUSUKE]
I'm a model.
For the sake of art,
I must blend in with nature,
become one with it,
and mask it or something.
I don't know what
you're talking about,
but unless you're here,
we can't draw.
[SOUSUKE] I'm the
paradoxical symmetry,
or the anti-tank missile,
or the electronic
jamming pod or--
I'm not sure, but I think
it's something like that.
You are the model!
That's it! You hear me?!
[SOUSUKE] Anyway,
draw your pictures.
I'll be watching you
secretly from here.
Wait... a sec...
Man.
Well?
Once again he
got the wrong idea.
We'll pick another model.
No way, no way, no way!
You shall not change your model!
But our model's gone missing.
We can't find him!
That excuse is not acceptable.
To remove that model who openly
accepted my enthusiasm--
What exactly are you up to?!
It's always the same.
My own critically-accepting
craft simulation
in containing the
transparent sublimation
of things as they are,
the masses fail to see
a reality on the
verge of despair...
[ALL]
What?!
You're saying he won't take
anyone other than Sousuke?
We have no choice.
So, let's all go
start looking for him.
[SOUSUKE] So,
you came after all,
to interfere with my modeling.
Your information and
movements are uncoordinated.
A march of raw recruits.
Just give it your best shot.
[screams]
What the--?!
There's a hole!
Is... Is this glue?!
Did Sagara do that?!
Th-This path's not safe!
[screaming]
Someone help us...
We can't move...
Who in their right mind
would do this?
Huh? What's that?
I can't hear you!
[BOY] I said Sagara's
been laying traps for us
all over the place!
Fine... Then just get back here.
Damn that idiot...
He seriously is
trying to lose us!
Kaname!
Shinji's Bravo Team
has been wiped out, too!
[CHIDORI growls]
Sousuke, you--
[cell phone ringing]
[ONO D]
Miss Chidori, we found Sagara!
Way to go, Ono D!
Now grab him!
[ONO D] Leave it to us!
Four against one can't--
[ONO D screams]
[explosion]
[birds cawing]
Ono D! You alive?
Answer me!
[ONO D coughing]
[ONO D]
A landmine... he got us...
Say... Kaname...?
Remember awhile back
I told you I liked you
and you turned me down...?
Well, I still feel the
same way right now...
[ONO D coughs]
[CHIDORI]
No, don't die!
[ONO D] If-If I make it
out of this alive...
would you reconsider...?
No. Not on your life.
[ONO D]
You're so mean!
[ONO D croaks]
Sousuke!
You, I will never forgive!
If it takes any longer
for us to catch Sousuke,
it'll definintely
be the end of us.
But! We will capture Sousuke!
For the sake of
our lost comrades!
For the sake of our
own human dignity!
And above all, for the
sake of everybody's grades!
[STUDENTS] yeah!
[CHIDORI] We are now engaged
in a tough battle.
If you see a man, kill the man.
If you see a god, kill the god.
No questions asked.
No mercy shown.
Never mind the casualties;
just move forward.
Now, follow me!
[STUDENTS] Yeaah!
[screaming]
Don't let it phase you! Go!
[grunting]
Come on! Keep charging!
[screaming]
That was nothing!
[grunting]
[screaming]
I... won't lose to you!
[CHIDORI panting]
Almost there.
[CHIDORI gasps]
[SOUSUKE]
So it's over.
Art is such a cruel thing.
[CHIDORI]
Sousuke!
You know, you've given
us a lot of trouble today!
No way!
So, we finally found you.
Ready to say your
prayers, Sousuke?
[KAGOME]
Wait! Come back here, loser!
[MIZUHOSHI'S MOM]
Here you are.
[KAGURAZAKA]
Thank you very much!
It's so peaceful here.
I have to say, I'm
honestly quite surprised
that your house is located
this close to the venue,
Mr. Mizuhoshi.
Yes, I have always
found in the atmosphere
of this garden an active silence
--and a flickering image of--
--[CHIDORI] Hey! Wait!
[TEACHERS]
Huh?
Sa-Sagara?
--Now you wait just one minu--
--Miss Chidori?!
[CHIDORI]
Sousuke!
[MIZUHOSHI grunting]
[MIZUHOSHI'S MOM whimpers]
Don't move! If you value
this woman's life,
then you'll do as I--
[SOUSUKE grunts]
[STUDENTS yelling]
Well, well... We finally
caught up with you, Sousuke.
K-Kill me.
Oh, we still have a use for you!
We'll kill you after that...
--Say, um, Miss Chidori...?
--Now, take him away,
and get your sketchpads!
Huh? Now wait a minute!
[PRINICPAL]
Brilliant works of art.
The sensitivities
of adolescence.
Their youthful
vitality...
each one has such
fresh brush work.
Thank you, Principal.
Like these, Class 4, 11th grade.
They're so... uh...
They're-- what are they?
Uh, the students here,
appear to have taken a
very avant-garde approach.
You can see the
influences of T. Orester.
One can say they
evoke the emptiness
a human feels when
stripped of power.
Upon further examination...
[CHIDORI] For crying out loud,
is that war nut ever going
to adjust? Seriously!
Well, it's not like
he means any harm.
That doesn't make
it okay for him
to let a hand grenade
off in class.
But, Kaname, when
you're with Sousuke,
it always looks like
you're having fun.
I don't know how you see that.
Lately, now, I've
just been tired.
Huh?
[train honks]
[CHIDORI] See, he just doesn't
get the strain I'm under.
I think it's best to put
some distance between us.
Kaname?
Senior Fuwa?
[ONO D] That's a lot
of stuff you got...
Hey, Sagara, what's this?
It's a smoke grenade.
Oh, huh...
[ONO D gasps]
[STUDENTS scream]
Why didn't you tell me
the thing was loaded?!
I figured you knew better.
Kaname! Hey, listen to this:
Sagara brought another
weird thing to...
[ONO D] Kaname?
[CHIDORI]
Well, all things in moderation.
All right, class,
today we will learn
about the subjunctive.
Open your books to page 24.
Please take a look at the
first example sentence,
"If I could fly,
I would fly to you."
The subjunctive mood
is used to indicate
that the speaker is making
a hypothetical insertion.
[SOUSUKE]
Miss Chidori.
W-What?!
[CHIDORI laughs]
[SOUSUKE]
Something's wrong.
Like what?
Chidori... is a
student or faculty member
threatening her or something?
Or do you think it
might be drug abuse?
Hard to say...
Good job, guys.
I've got plans today,
so I 'm gonna be leaving early.
Bye.
O...kay.
Chidori?
Yeah, what?
Well, is there anything that's
been bothering you lately?
If you're in some
sort of trouble,
I could be of assistance.
It's nothing.
I'm all right, really.
So don't worry.
See ya!
This is bugging me.
I am worried.
Say, Sousuke, would...
would you be free Sunday?
I could leave that day open.
So... do you wanna go somewhere?
[FUWA]
It's been three years.
Brings back memories.
You sure it's okay? 'Cause
you've got entrance exams.
Hey, I need to relax, too.
Besides, I couldn't pass
up a date with you.
Oh!
Anyway, let's just
have fun today.
[CHIDORI]
Okay.
And that's the situation.
That guy used to be Kaname's
senior in middle school.
They were close friends.
He must be enrolled
at another school.
If we assume he's
gotten close to Chidori
in order to steal
our school secrets,
that would explain things.
Hey, don't be ridiculous!
I guess we'll have to
put the screws to him!
No, Sousuke, we can't!
If you went and did
something like that,
Kaname would hate
you for sure.
Watch them first,
and then think it over.
Okay?
If you feel that strongly,
I'll leave him for now.
[screaming]
Now what?
Well, so far he doesn't seem to
be a spy or threat of any kind.
The two of them are... I
believe... h-having a good time.
Are you okay?
Yes, now I understand the
relieved. I feel very situation.
Your words are all mixed up.
No problem.
Our recon here is over.
Secure an escape route and
thoroughly cover your tracks.
Leave your explosives
and rations here.
Our rendezvous is point alpha.
Tokyo, reconfirm the
chopper's eta.
You know, you look
rather flustered, Sousuke.
Anyway, we're going home.
[KYOKO]
What?
[YAKUZA]
Hey you!
It'sa middle of day you
two lovebirds.
Good students should be
at home hittin' their books.
I don't need advice
from a person
who starts drinking at noon.
Would you leave us alone?
[FUWA]
Kaname?!
--What'd you say, brat?
Professional yakuza! Not good!
[SOUSUKE] No problem,
I'm a professional soldier.
It really doesn't
make any difference
who she's become friends with.
I will protect her.
Sousuke, I'm so impressed!
But if you
jump out like that
they'll find out we
followed them here.
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo?
You think you can mess
with adults, kid?!
Buzz off! Your
stupidity is catching.
[YAKUZA]
What did you say?
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu!
It's Bonta-Kun?
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu Fumoffu Fumoffu!
Shut up.
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo... mofu!
[YAKUZA]
Ow! What the hell was that?
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu...
Get down here now!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo... Fumoffu!
Fumofu!
B-Bro!
Here, take this!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo-mo-mo-mo!
How the hell can a plushie...?
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu!
[YAKUZA B]
Why you--
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo! Fumoffu!
Fumo-fumo-fumo-fumo!
[YAKUZA B]
Stop... stop...stop!
Kanam--!
Stay where you are, or else--
[YAKUZA C grunts]
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu...
Fumo!
Uh... Hey, Bonta-kun...?
[SECURITY GUARD A]
What happened?
[MAN]
That's him!
He's the one that took
my costume by force!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu!
[SECURITY GUARD A]
This way, follow him!
[SECURITY GUARD B]
Hey you, wait!
[FUWA]
What the heck was that, anyway?
I mean, there's no way
it can be an attraction.
[CHIDORI laughs]
But you know, your outbursts
were also way out there.
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
I guess I put you in a dangerous
position there, didn't I?
It's fine.
I... I even like that
about you, actually.
Huh...?
[FUWA] Uh, Kaname, look...
will you go out with me?
See, to be honest...
I... I really like you.
So... Kaname?
Senior!
[CHIDORI]
That idiot!
I'm sorry.
I see...
So, there's someone
else that you like?
Huh?
It's just that sometimes
you get this look on your face
as if you were thinking
about somebody.
Oh! Well, uh... Well I, uh...
Well, knowing your
taste, he's gotta be
an extremely mature,
reliable person, huh?
No, he's not!
He isn't like that at all!
Huh?
Oh! I, uh... I mean...
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu, fumoffu, fumo...!
Go hide in there, quickly!
[SECURITY GUARD A]
Come on!
Young lady,
did you happen to see
a Bonta-Kun carrying a gun?
[CHIDORI]
Uh, he went that way!
[SECURITY GUARD A]
Okay, let's go!
[CHIDORI]
You can rest easy, Bonta-Kun.
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu.
Thank you for your help.
Now, I know you've
already helped me...
But could you spare a
minute to hear my story?
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo...?
[CHIDORI] Today, I went
on a date with a guy
I used to kinda like.
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo...
He was my senior from my
days back in middle school.
And he really was a good guy.
Then, just
the other day,
I ran into him taking the
train home from school.
A minute ago he asked
me to go out with him.
But I said no.
You know why I told him no?
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo?
I don't really know, either.
Although, while all
this was bugging me,
there was someone
worried about me.
Even though he usually
doesn't have a clue,
For once he asked me:
"Is there anything
that's bothering you?"
That made me happy.
Well, that's it!
Tomorrow, I'll be right
back to my usual self.
So just rest easy, "Bonta-kun"!
See ya!
[SECURITY GUARD A]
There he is! This way!
You give us back
that costume right now!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu!
[SECURITY GUARD A]
Get back here!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu!
[SOUSUKE] At last,
some fierce fighting!
An unknown enemy
suddenly appears.
Undertaking a special mission
from the student council,
I'm attacked by
a violent storm.
At the end of this desperate
struggle, do we find tears?
Love? Or broken dreams?
[CHIDORI] I couldn't care less!
Just clean up after yourselves.
The student body president will
chew me out too if you don't!
Tune in next time for:
"The Pure Yet Impure Grappler"
and "Trespassing on Good Faith".
[SOUSUKE] The school janitor may
be my strongest opponent yet...