[CHIDORI] A student
council announcement?
What's this?
"Starting with last weekend,
there have been many
attempted assaults
within the school district.
Of those, 7 involved
a sex offender,
likely a single perpetrator.
Some reports mention
a pony, but it's unclear
what that may mean.
What to do when you
meet a sex offender:
A: Engage and
annihilate the enemy.
B: If A proves difficult,
obtain what intelligence you can
and withdraw.
Air and artillery cover
will not be provided."
Look, Sousuke,
you aren't gonna get
your point across with such
an unfriendly writing style.
A pervert? Scary...
Well, it appears she
understands it.
At any rate,
starting next time
try using simpler language
like normal people use.
Understood.
Huh?
Pony!
What?!
Pony, pony, pony pony!
Oh no, go away!
Ponyyyy!
Somebody help me!
[KYOKO screams]
Pony!
[screaming continues]
Oh, hey, Sousuke.
Good morning.
Huh? What's going on?
Kaname... Actually I've
got some bad news for you.
The sex offender...
What'd he do this time?
Last night he assaulted Kyoko.
N-No way! Not Kyoko!
Well, what happened to her?
Is she all right?
I'm sorry... I'm not quite
sure how to explain it.
It... can't be.
It seems she met a pervert in a
strange costume on her way home.
He seized her before she
could make a counterattack
And forced her down on the
spot despite her struggling.
After combing her hair
meticulously with a brush...
Oh no...
[SOUSUKE]
He gave her a ponytail.
That's just so-- He what?!
[KYOKO]
Oh, it's Kaname!
Good morning!
[KYOKO laughs]
What is this?
The pervert's signature.
A ponytail!
My hair was pulled back
with wire and glue.
I've washed it like 5
times but I can't get it out!
That's all?
Mm-hmm. That's it!
Although, it was scary.
It's odd, huh?
Defies description...
Ya know, that's smarts.
Shut up! You really
had me worried there!
I swear, Sousuke!
[CHIDORI]
It's too bad about Kyoko.
[SOUSUKE] Yes, since one of our
school's students was a victim,
We should capture
the perpetrator,
torture him severely,
and extract from him
his true intentions.
[CHIDORI]
Don't be creepy.
At times like these, we
should let THEM handle it.
Excuse me?
Yes?
[CHIDORI] I'd like to report
an attack by a sex offender.
[OFFICER grunts]
Sex offender?!
I'm afraid we can't talk here.
Come with me!
[CHIDORI] Huh?
Hey-Hey wait a minute!
[WAKANA]
C'mon!
[CHIDORI]
Ms. Yoko Wakana?
[WAKANA] Yeah! I'm really
in the traffic division,
but I ditched that to
investigate a sicko.
I've even cut down on sleep!
And look at this!
There've been 8 reports
of similar attacks
appearing alternately
in the north and south.
If it follows the pattern,
he'll show up around here.
So tonight, I'd like you
to go out and act as a decoy.
What? Why should
I have to do that?
Heh.
Wouldn't you like to settle
the score for your friend?!
Plus, a little while ago,
I made a big mistake
and as a consequence, I got
reassigned to deskwork.
But, you know, a big arrest
could put me back
on active duty. So...
[CHIDORI]
A big mistake? Like what?
Well, it's pretty
embarrassing...
I was in my patrol car
chasing two students
riding double on a bike
but they were tough.
And not only did
I not catch them,
I slammed right into the
guardrail at full speed.
I wasn't hurt at all, but
the patrol car was totaled.
How terrible...
I'm sorry to hear that.
Of the two, I remember
the guy's face very well.
And when I find him,
he'll get all kinds of
corporal punishment,
Officer Wakana style.
No, don't!
[WAKANA] Why shouldn't I
put the hurt on him?
Oh, no, that isn't--
Now, look, would you
just knock it off?
Uh... What's wrong?
[CHIDORI]
N-Nothing!
Sometimes I can
hear radio waves.
Strange whispers...
it's a chronic ailment.
Well, that's all
for now, civilian.
I'm counting on you tonight.
Uh, wait a sec...
If you don't show up,
I'll arrest you too.
[WAKANA laughs]
So does this mean I gotta pay?
[SOUSUKE] Chidori,
are you really accepting
this decoy assignment?
Mmm. I wanna settle
the score for Kyoko.
And besides,
it really is our fault
for making that lady as
agitated as she is.
[SOUSUKE] All right, then as
a precaution, I'll cover you.
If she should threaten
you, I'll subdue her.
[CHIDORI] No, you can't! Your
face is the one she remembers!
[SOUSUKE] In that case,
I'll use my new equipment.
I've made several
improvements to some gear
I acquired recently.
It's a type of reinforced
suit with a sensor array,
a digital communication device,
and bulletproofing that can stop
even rifle bullets.
If all goes well,
it can radically change
the face modern warfare.
[SOUSUKE]
Okay, they're moving out.
[BONTA-KUN]
Fu...
[WAKANA gasps]
[BONTA-KUN]
...moffu!
Fumo? Fumomo!
I heard you were a guy
in a horse costume.
I never figured
you'd be Bonta-kun.
Wait!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumomo!
Eat this!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumomomo!
Stop!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu... Fumo!
You can still move!
I'll change that!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo!
So, you're gonna put up
a fight, you pervert?!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo!
There's no clear shot!
[WAKANA] Here's to
saving my career
by turning you into
a spec of dust!
[WAKANA]
There's no escape!
Now, who's the predator?!
There's still some
practicality issues...
[CHIDORI] I wonder if
he'll really show up...?
[bushes rustling]
[CHIDORI]
Huh?
[CHIDORI whimpers]
Pony!
Someone! There's a pervert!
And a really weird one, too!
Please help me!
[PONY MAN]
Pony pony pony pony pony!
[CHIDORI]
Nooo!
[WAKANA laughs]
This is fun! This is
really fun, Bonta-kun!
Let's you and me
have some more fun!
You won't beat me!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo!
[WAKANA yells]
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo?
[WAKANA]
Take this!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo!
Fumo...
[WAKANA laughs]
[BONTA-KUN]
Fu!
Man, you're irritating!
Drop already!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumomo.
Begging won't help you, furball!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo...
[WAKANA grunts]
You're strong for a rat!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumomo. Fumo!
Fumomomoffu! Fumo!
Fumoffu! Fumo!
Fumomo! Fumoffu fumo!
[WAKANA yells]
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoooffu! Fumo!
[WAKANA]
I win!
Someone! Help me!
[PONY MAN]
Pony... p-pony.
[WAKANA]
That's the perp?!
So, then, who the heck is this?!
Oh! This is my friend.
Right, Bonta-kun?
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu.
Yeah? Well, you have a
really strong friend there.
Man, I can't believe
she's actually buying it.
Pony.
Pony pony pony pony pony pony.
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumomo?
Pony pony pony pony pony.
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu fumoffu.
Pony! Pony...
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo...
So you guys are bonding
over weird noises?!
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumo?
In any case,
it was my active role
that led to the
suspect's arrest.
But all you did was
go on a rampage.
[WAKANA] Okay, now is
when you get to tell us
exactly why you did this.
I didn't mean to
be so hard sell,
but ponytails
totally rock!
The bare neck of short hair...
The gentle femininity
of long hair...
The ponytail
perfectly combines
these two
contradictory elements.
In spite of this, lately,
I just haven't seen girls
with ponytails around anymore.
It makes me so sad
to think about it.
That's why you turned
to this bizarre crime?
Yes, but officer... I'm happy.
I lived in a way that
was true to myself.
Well, you'll be put
away for a long time.
So you take care of
yourself in prison.
I will. Sorry for
all the trouble.
[BONTA-KUN]
Fumoffu fumoffu.
This is wrong. There is
something very very wrong here.
[CHIDORI]
The old man trembled...
"It can't be...
it simply can't be!"
With that thought, he
opened and closed the lid
of the shumai box
again and again...
And so, one... by one...
the shumai disappeared...
In the end, all 12
of them... vanished...
When he lifted the lid
for the last time,
he realized the shumai
that had disappeared
were all stuck to the bottom...
[KYOKO &amp; MIZUKI scream]
[CHIDORI]
It's too early to be scared.
There's still more to the story!
[CHIDORI] One day,
the old man died,
and this is what
happened at his funeral.
Before they carried
the coffin out of the house,
they had a viewing of the body.
"It's the last time we'll
see him," they said.
So the mortician opened
the lid of the coffin
in front of everyone.
Now the coffin
was open,
but the old man was...
stuck to the bottom of the lid!
[KYOKO &amp; MIZUKI scream]
[CHIDORI] Well, how was
that story, Sousuke?
[SOUSUKE]
I dunno.
[ALL sigh]
So, c'mon, Sousuke. Nothing?
Look, it's pointless.
I'm telling you,
he has no imagination.
[SOUSUKE]
Hmm.
Maybe Sousuke'd
get a little scared
if you showed him some real
examples of ghosts and goblins.
Speaking of which, there's a
hospital that went under nearby.
There was a big fire
10 years ago.
A hospital that went under...
Hey, that sounds like fun!
Kaname, you don't mean...
That's right!
How about we go take Sousuke
to that hospital right now!
You'd better not do it, Kaname.
I've heard all kinds of scary
rumors about that hospital.
Even better! If it'll scare
the crap out of Sousuke...
[MIZUKI]
Kyoko's a scaredy-cat, huh?
[CHIDORI] She ran into a
sex offender the other day.
Let's give the girl a break...
[MIZUKI]
Yeah...
Uh... So this is the hospital?
[CHIDORI] Now, this is
what I'm talking about.
Looks like the
aftermath of a bombing.
[MIZUKI gasps]
What's wrong, Mizuki?
Th-There! Over by the window!
There was a strange old lady
watching us just now!
I'm not buying it.
She was there just now!
She was smiling
and looking at us!
Ha! Very funny!
You're a natural-born
actor. Really.
Yo-You idiot!
What are you saying?!
This place is way too dangerous!
I'm going home!
Honestly, between
her and Kyoko...
It's rather illogical.
I just don't understand why
Mizuki would be that frightened.
I know! Being like that
before we go in
takes all the
fun out of it.
[SOUSUKE] The old lady
was just standing there.
What was that...?
[SOUSUKE] I said,
the old lady at the window
was just standing there.
What? So you saw her too?
[SOUSUKE] There's no way she'd
spot it without me noticing.
Now, if the old lady
were equipped with a gun
or rocket launcher, I could
see her being scared, but--
What's wrong, Kaname?
Are you feeling sick?
Aren't you... Aren't you,
like, scared at all?
Scared of what?
[CHIDORI] Of what?!
Don't you think it's weird
for an old lady to be
out here at this hour?!
[SOUSUKE] Perhaps the old lady
is from the neighborhood
and got lost.
Don't worry, if we find her
we'll take her to the police.
[CHIDORI] I-I guess that sounds
like a reasonable explanation.
[SOUSUKE]
So, aren't you going in?
[CHIDORI]
Huh?
[SOUSUKE] I don't see why...
but if you're scared,
you can go home.
[CHIDORI]
I-I'm perfectly fine, okay?!
All right, I'm going in!
[SOUSUKE]
Why're you so mad?
[CHIDORI]
I am not mad!
[SOUSUKE]
What's wrong?
Uh... um... why don't
you go in first?
[CHIDORI] Ugh, how 'bout now?
Aren't you scared?
[SOUSUKE]
Scared of what?
[CHIDORI] I guess atmosphere
alone isn't enough...
[CHIDORI screams]
Well, that's odd.
That's it?
You just think it's odd?
C'mon, don't you, like,
feel anything else?
A-A child was--
Yes, that's why
I said it was odd.
That's scary!
It's scary, right?!
Despite what you say,
it's only a child.
He couldn't defeat
someone who's familiar
with all sorts of
weaponry like I am.
[CHIDORI]
Oh, come on!
You're so abnormal
to act that way
in response to
something like that!
Could anyone be
more obtuse than you?!
I'm not entirely sure,
but what you're saying
sounds quite rude.
What are you going to do?
I'm concerned about the
old lady on the fourth floor.
But if you're getting cold feet,
I don't mind if you go home now.
What're you trying to say?
I do not have cold feet!
[SOUSUKE]
Then let's go.
D-Don't you feel nervous coming
to a place like this at all?
Not at all, because as long
as you stay on the lookout,
you should be able to spot
any landmines or booby-traps.
Uhh... That's not
quite what I meant.
[phone rings]
[CHIDORI screams]
Please stand back.
[phone continues to ring]
[CHIDORI]
Why did you do that?!
[SOUSUKE] There's a booby-trap
that triggers an explosion
when you
pick up the phone.
One of my comrades
fell victim to such a trap
in the ruins of Lebanon.
Hello? This hospital's
been closed for many years
so if this is an emergency,
please call 1-1-9
to obtain an ambulance
and medical assistance.
I don't think that
they're listening... huh.
Uh, is someone there?
[CHILD]
I can't breathe!
It's so hot!
--[screaming]
--The pain! The pain! The pain!
What?! What the heck?!
Somebody needs help.
They probably called
not knowing this
place went under.
No, that's not the problem!
Don't you think this
is all too weird?
It's like one unnatural
thing after another!
Wouldn't it be better if you
went home after all?
You're probably tired right now.
[CHIDORI] Somehow, the look
in your eyes pisses me off.
I'm just concerned for you.
Well, you don't have to be!
Why do you keep saying I'm the
one who's scared, anyway?! Huh?
I'm not, you know!
[CHIDORI]
What about that?
[SOUSUKE]
I'm just glad it's not a bomb.
Forget it. Next!
--And this?
--[CHILDREN laughing]
--It's only voices.
--[CHIDORI] Scratch that! Next!
--[CHILDREN laughing]
Go back home...
Or drop dead.
Go home! Drop dead!
A-A-And this... what do
you think about this, huh?!
Despite what you think, with
only a hammer she couldn't--
[CHIDORI screams]
[CHIDORI]
It's not her weapon!
She's soaked in blood!
That scary, isn't it?!
And you!
Can't you do anything
cooler like spit poison gas
or do some kind of
mysterious dance?!
And wipe that smile
off of your face!
Kaname! Get back here!
Be quiet!
--[crashing]
--[KANAME gasps]
[CHIDORI screaming
[CHIDORI]
Where am I?
Oh, that's right, I fell
through the floor or something,
didn't I?
[CHIDORI] That's a lot of
blood... am I gonna die?
[SOUSUKE]
Kaname! Get up! Answer me!
No, hold on, don't move!
Don't talk! Stay there.
I'll come to you! Just wait!
[CHIDORI]
Sousuke!
Why are you... so jittery?
Are you hurt, Kaname?
Kaname, are you all right?
I don't really know...
What's this?
Paint can?
[CHIDORI]
What's going on?
[KID] Excuse me...
are you all right?
Hey, that's Mr. Sagara!
[SOUSUKE]
Yoshiki?
Are you injured?
[CHIDORI] In other words, you
guys were putting on an act
like that to help out
Mr. Gen who lives here?
[YOSHIKI] Yeah, what happened
was a lot of couples
and delinquents kept coming
here and picking on him!
We thought maybe if people
heard the place was haunted,
they would stop wanting
to come bother him.
It seems to have
worked pretty well.
The number of people
coming has dropped off.
Thank goodness for that.
That explains a lot.
I mean, Mizuki got
scared and ran off
after seeing that
old lady in the window.
An old lady?
The old lady you propped up
next to this one window.
What was it? A mannequin?
What are you talking about?
[CHIDORI] Huh...?
Oh... that lady.
It's probably someone who
died in the fire 10 years ago.
She's been showing up on
and off for awhile now.
[screaming]
[OLD WOMAN]
So, they've finally gone home.
[GEN laughs]
[GEN] Mom, I have a
feeling those kids won't be
coming near here ever again.
This place was dad's
pride and joy
when he was
hospital director.
And now that he's gone,
he'd want us
to live a peaceful life here.
You said it, Son.
Are you awake?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'll walk now.
[CHIDORI]
Hey, Sousuke?
[SOUSUKE] Yes?
[CHIDORI]
Were you scared?
[SOUSUKE]
Scared of what?
When I fell and it looked like
I was all covered in blood.
[SOUSUKE]
Yes.
[CHIDORI]
Huh?
[SOUSUKE]
Oh, nothing.
What's that? I had trouble
hearing what you said.
[SOUSUKE]
Don't worry. Forget it.
Nope! So, what was it you said
just now? What was it, huh?
[CHIDORI]
N-Nothing! Kaname, I--
[CHIDORI] Tell me! If you
don't tell me what you said
I'll give you something
to really be afraid of.
So let's hear it.
[SOUSUKE]
Keep steady!
[CHIDORI]
Cleaning a rugby ball?
What's up with that, Sousuke?
[SOUSUKE] It looks like next
time we're doing a rousing,
touching sports story.
[CHIDORI] Can you make these
crybabies into tough guys?
[SOUSUKE]
Leave it to me.
Mao has supplied me with a
recruit training manual.
In one week, I'll transform them
into heartless war machines.
[CHIDORI] Tune in next time for:
"The War Cry of Excessiveness".
Gung-ho, gung-ho, gung-ho!
[SOUSUKE] By the way, why are
you wearing naval attire?