[phone ringing]
[RECORDING] Hello, you have
reached Brilliant Safetech.
We're sorry, but no
one is currently here
to take your call.
Please leave your
message after the beep.
And may the fortunes
of war smile upon you.
[message tone beeps]
[SAGARA] Beart, it's Sagara.
The package arrived,
but you sent me the wrong item.
I ordered a
special gun sight.
The only thing I got
was a strange bottle.
I glanced over the manual, and
it looks extremely dangerous.
How could you even think of
shipping something like that
through Air Mail?
Are you insane?
Call me as soon as you can.
Who'd ya call?
[SAGARA] An old friend of
mine... weapons dealer.
He can get you almost
anything, for the right price.
Huh...
While I ordered a
special part for my gun,
but it seems there was
some kind of mix-up.
[CHIDORI] Looks like
one solid water bottle.
[SAGARA] Of course! It's
designed not to break easily.
[intercom bells chime]
[KAGURAZAKA] Sousuke Sagara
from class 2-4,
I have something to ask
you about the clubroom
that's under
construction!
Come to the
faculty room, now!
[intercom bells chime]
So what'd you do
this time, Sousuke?
Uh, nothing really
comes to mind.
You sure?
Well, yesterday I saw
some "Do not enter" tape
around the
construction area,
so out of the
kindness of my heart,
I setup a high-voltage
trap. That's all.
You don't think she's
mad about th--
--Of course she's mad!
--Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Some construction
worker probably fell
into your stupid
trap. Come on.
Nobody should touch that bottle.
Well, in any case,
she's a good baby-sitter.
Sure is rough though.
Yes, I got one!
Got what, Ono D?
This is a Flaming Hot
God-of-Curry Bread.
It's always been sold out.
[KYOKO]
That's the new kind, right?
[MIZUKI]
I heard it's really spicy.
[ONO D]
I thought I'd try it out.
Well, here I go.
That's hot!
--Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
--Gee, what a surprise.
--[ONO D] Water!
--I'm sorry, that's empty.
[ONO D] Water?!
♪ Empty. ♪
[ONO D]
Water!
Ono D, no! That's
Sousuke's bottle!
[ONO D chokes]
Here, have this!
[ONO D gulps]
Haah!
Thank you, Kyoko,
that was too hot!
Man, what was
that baker thinking?
[MIZUKI] The name said
it was hot, right?
Of course it's gonna be spicy.
[SHINJI] Guys... I
think you should
--take a look at this!
--You're such a scatterbrain.
--[SHINJI ranting]
--Well, try it again tomorrow.
--No way, forget it!
--[SHINJI ranting]
--I've had enough super-hot
--stuff for the year!
--You guys, are you listening?!
--Yeah, that's probably wise.
--Hello?!
[laughing]
--This is really important!
Honestly. You will apologize
to that worker, later on.
You hear me?
Understood.
[MIZUKI]
Huh? Lunch break's over?
[MIKIHARA]
That was fast.
Bye, Kyoko!
[KYOKO]
Okay, later!
[SAGARA]
Hold it!
Someone! Please tell me what
happened to the contents
of this bottle!
Give me a straight answer!
I promise I won't get angry
or make you pay me back for it.
Just tell me
who's responsible.
[ONO D]
Sorry, Sagara.
I thought it was a water bottle.
And the contents?
I cleaned it up, and
threw it in the trash.
Sagara, class is
already started!
Listen everyone!
From now on,
you're forbidden to
leave this classroom.
That means you,
too, so don't move!
Huh? What do you mean?
We need to get back
to our class, Sagara.
Doesn't matter,
whatever the circumstances,
whoever enters this
room from this point--
[ISSEI] Sagara! I sent a letter
challenging you to a fight
on the roof today during lunch.
Where were--
[ISSEI shouts]
This is an emergency.
What's that?!
Now we can't get out!
That's quite enough,
Sagara, just what are you...
Uh... Doing...?
[CHIDORI]
What's with that outfit?
[SAGARA]
It's an NBC Protective Suit.
[CHIDORI]
Uh, NB what?
[SAGARA]
Wait, first things first.
[CLASS murmuring,
ISSEI groans]
Now what are you
doing? S-Sagara?
[SAGARA]
I will explain.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I must ask that fifth period
be suspended immediately.
What did you say?!
[SAGARA] A serious disaster
has occurred here.
This bottle contained a
bacteriological weapon,
and releasing it from
its special capsule
has created a biohazard.
B-Biohazard?
[SAGARA]
Affirmative.
An extremely
dangerous bacteria,
created with the latest
biotech has spilled out.
It's insatiable,
ferocious, airborne,
and once it infects someone,
it will not stop until it
devours its entire prey.
That's what the manual said.
So is it right
here in this room?
[SAGARA]
Yes.
Are we infected? A-Am I?
And what about my students?
[SAGARA]
I'm afraid so.
[CLASS begins
screaming, panicking]
[SAGARA]
Calm down! She just fainted.
But how can we calm down?!
Infected? W-What do you mean?
[SAGARA] Don't panic!
Running around and
shouting won't help anything!
[MIZUKI]
Well, don't be so selfish!
Once you're infected,
you die, right?!
But you've got
the fancy suit.
It's easy for you to say,
"Don't panic!"
[SAGARA] But I'm the only one
here who knows anything
about bacteriological weapons.
To come up with an
effective strategy--
I get it, you're just trying
to save yourself, Sagara.
You've got some nerve!
What the hell's wrong with you?!
What do you think
you're doing to us, huh?!
You're just thinking
of yourself...
[CLASS panicking]
[SAGARA]
Fine...
[ALL gasp]
Now do you all understand?
I'm not giving you instructions
simply to save my own life here.
As an expert in war,
I'm only trying to prevent
the situation
from getting worse.
[CLASS sighs]
Everyone, please
forget your hatred.
[CLASS begins sobbing]
[SAGARA]
And don't hold any grudges.
That way we can think
about our next step.
This tragedy isn't
anyone's fault.
[sobbing continues]
Sousuke...
You all understand that, right?
[blows landing]
[CHIDORI] Honestly,
guns and bombs, fine.
But biological weapons?!
What kind of dangerous stuff
are you packing, you bastard?
Hey, guns and bombs are
dangerous, too, you know!
What was in there?
Just knowing it's a
biological weapon won't help us.
Mmm... Does anybody feel sick?
[CLASS murmurs]
Maybe we ought to go
to the school nurse.
[SHINJI] I don't think
that's a good idea.
Why's that?
Sousuke gave us
strict instructions
not to leave the classroom,
because he didn't want
the infection to
spread any further.
He said it was
transmitted through the air.
If we were to leave the
room, the entire school
would turn into one,
big infectious hotspot.
But Shinji,
nobody here feels sick.
One of the features
of these weapons
is that after
someone's infected,
it takes some time before
the symptoms appear.
But they're very
deadly nonetheless.
Sometimes they're
even referred to
as the "poor man's
nuclear bomb."
I've heard that some
country in the Middle East
is studying the Ebola
virus for military use.
That could even be what this is.
--[CLASS gasps]
--Ebola?
You mean the one where you bleed
all over your body and die?
Right. Known as the
flesh-eating virus.
If that's what this is,
then none of us
will get out of here alive!
--[SHINJI cackles]
--What? N-No way!
I don't wanna die!
[CLASS screams]
[CHIDORI] Hold it, guys!
Stop it! Calm down!
We can't leave the room,
didn't ya hear?!
Damnit! I told you people!
--Calm down now!
--[chalkboard screeching]
--[CLASS groaning]
One more time!
Stop acting like this!
You'll just create more victims!
But...what about us?
Look, everyone, think
about how history
is gonna judge this tragedy.
If we lose
ourselves in a panic
and spread the infection
throughout the entire school,
rest assured, people will
despise us for all eternity!
Is that what you want?
[CLASS sighs]
Hey, I'm scared too, you know.
Before I have to die,
I would've liked to at
least go to Ohio
and eat all the
trident yaki I could.
Or go to the soba shop by
the station one last time
and gorge myself on
Super Deluxe Soba,
piled high with all the
toppings I could want.
Then I could die
without regrets.
That is how I feel.
It doesn't cost much
to please you.
However! We can't
let it get to us,
even with death
staring us in the face,
we must confront it with reason!
We should bravely
offer our lives,
on the sacrificial altar of fate
and pray for our
countrymen's safety.
Isn't the brilliance of
such a noble spirit
what humanity is all about?
[CLASS gasps]
It's just like
you said, Chidori.
She's right, let's stop
behaving so shamefully.
It won't be easy, but we
should just face our destiny.
Thank you, everyone. I am
truly proud of each one of you.
I'm sorry for being
so harsh with you.
What are you talking
about, Kaname?
We're the ones who were wrong.
It'll be okay, we're all
friends here, aren't we?
We won't be dying alone, so
there's no reason to be afraid.
Thank you.
[CLASS cries]
[SAGARA]
What are you people crying for?
Quiet, you! We're
all busy reflecting
on the human
conscience right now.
You just stay over
there and die.
That's right, Sagara.
You mustn't bother them now.
[SAGARA]
Not an option.
I haven't informed
them of the vaccine, yet.
[CHIDORI]
Vaccine?
The vaccine for the weapon,
it was included for emergencies.
See, it's right here.
But there's only one dose.
[growling, panting]
What's the matter?
Oh, Sousuke. Oh, Sousuke,
you're a genius at making
things more complicated,
you know that?
[growling &amp; panting continues]
[CLASS gasps]
We'll draw for it!
No hard feelings!
[whimpering]
[groans]
[crying]
[BOY]
We're all gonna die. All of us.
Hi, Mom, it's me.
Yeah, well, I just
wanted to say goodbye.
[crying, sobbing]
[CHIDORI gasps]
Kyoko...
[KYOKO giggles]
It's hard, but it's okay...
I had fun going to
school with you...
It's so cruel...
How could this happen?
How could this have happened?
Who's next? Mizuki?
Yeah, me.
[MIZUKI gulps]
[MIZUKI whimpering]
No! No! No, no, no, no!
--Mizuki!
--I don't wanna die before
I meet some wonderful guy!
There must be some mistake!
I demand a re-draw!
You know what--
[ISSEI]
Stop embarrassing yourself.
--Huh?
Now look, it's not like
I don't understand how you feel,
but you're making a
total ass of yourself,
and that puts a stain on
the life you've lived so far.
Why can't you see that?!
If this is to be your
destiny, accept it
and decide how to use
the rest of your life.
[CHIDORI sniffs]
That was beautiful, Issei.
It's your turn, now...
[ISSEI] I have no regrets
in my heart.
So, even if I did
draw the winner...
[ISSEI]
You take this, Chidori.
[CHIDORI]
Issei... no I couldn't.
[ISSEI] You will live...
along with my love.
Too bad. Okay, next!
Hey, your name's
Issei, right?
I just got so choked up
when you yelled at me.
N-Now look, woman!
You seem like a nice guy,
and we're gonna die anyway,
so why not, ya know, be with
me till then, huh? Huh?
--Alright...
--[ISSEI] Hey, stop it!
--So how 'bout you,Ren?
--Stop touching me!
Oh, whatever, I don't
mind drawing last.
Hey, Sousuke, you need
to draw a paper, too.
Yes, then I guess I'll draw.
[SAGARA]
Oh, it's the winner.
Winner?
Yeah. I guess I win.
[CLASS gasps]
Well, that's the
way it is. Sorry.
[MIZUKI giggles]
[ISSEI]
Of all the people... why you?
No way... There is no way
that I'm just going to accept
something like this...
Normally I can handle
pretty tough situations...
but this is too much...
[CHIDORI] This universe
is so absurd.
I'm going to die from insanity
before the bacteria kills me.
I understand,
but I promise you,
I will never forget
this tragedy.
I will send the data directly
to the weapons maker,
and warn them strongly to
prevent such occurrences
from happening in the future.
That's why...
[CLASS]
Why?! Why what?!
You should all accept
your fate calmly.
[CLASS]
We're gonna kill you!
[screaming]
[SAGARA]
Wait! Everybody calm down!
Violence won't solve anything!
Let's talk this over!
[BOY] That's what you say,
but you're still fighting back!
[CHIDORI] Everyone stop!
Stop this ugly fighting!
We can just redo the drawing.
Please don't give
me anymore grief!
Oh, who cares?!
[CHIDORI screams]
[ISSEI]
Sagara, die!
[ALL screaming]
[FUJISAKI] Quiet down!
What is going on in here?!
This isn't some
disorderly elementary school!
Why can't you take your
education more seriously, huh?!
[SHINJI] Oh no, he opened it...
even though it spreads
through the air....
Yes, how dare he...
[BOY] Oh, you've
done it now, Fujisaki...
D-Done what?
Who cares how far the
stupid thing spreads now!
[CLASS screams]
[SHINJI] I need to get rid of my
naughty pictures before I die...
[ONO D]
Man, I gotta go to the bathroom.
[KYOKO]
Yeah, so do I.
What do we do now?!
Everybody left!
The bacteria, Sousuke!
--The bacteria!
--[SAGARA] I know.
[CHIDORI whimpers]
Just what kind
of life did I have
for it to come to
an end this way?
But then again,
when I die,
I won't have to deal with
or clean up after
all the messes you
cause ever again.
If I look at it that way,
then maybe I can be happy.
[ISSEI]
Well I'm not happy.
There still happens to
be one certain matter
I have to settle once
and for all before I die.
Confessing to
the woman I love
or telling my family goodbye
is my least concern.
The only thing I have
to do right now is...
Knock it off, woman!
Lighten up. I've decided to
live for love 'til the end.
Anyway, what
I want to say is...
I can't go off and die until
I settle my score with you.
Really?
That's right,
so say your prayers.
[ISSEI roars]
Oh, life, burst
into flames.
Show it to me, your
final fiery glimmer.
Now, I put all my
strength into this!
Daidomiyaku
Final Technique: Rin!
[MIZUKI giggles]
I won.
Wow, I have no strength left
to yell at you for that.
[CHIDORI]
Ren, where are you going?
You see, I understand how
grave this situation is now.
Whatever time I have left,
I'd prefer to spend with
the one I love...
But it's just not to be...
So now that things
have come to this...
I think I will enjoy a
final cup of tea, alone.
[CHIDORI]
I'm sorry...
[MIKIHARA] Everyone,
thank you for everything.
Well then, take care.
Uh-huh. See ya...
[SAGARA]
Kaname.
Huh?
Come with me, immediately.
W-Wait!
[SAGARA]
There's no time!
[CHIDORI]
Sousuke, where are we going?
[SAGARA] I said there's no time.
Don't worry, just come.
[CHIDORI]
The nurse's office, but why...?
[CHIDORI screams]
Hey, wait! What are
you doing, Sousuke?
Alright, get undressed.
Huh?
Strip down.
Wh-What are you saying?
You don't mean...
"that"? What?
Because we're going to die?
But it's all so sudden.
I-I'm not even prepared.
And to do it in a
creepy place like this?
I can't. I just can't.
[CHIDORI gasps]
It's alright. You don't
have to say anything.
Now I can die and
not have any regrets.
[door slides open]
Mikihara, what's going on?
But Senior, why are...
why are you here?
[ATSUNOBU] I finished
my work in study hall,
so I came to tidy up
some business I had here.
You mustn't be here.
Please, you must leave me.
If you don't, then I...
I can't leave you.
Steady yourself.
Oh, Senior...
I feel so hot. I wonder
if this is the end...
Oh, hey there, Kyoko...
Ono D, hang in there...
Hang in there?
That's a pretty tall
order right now.
My head's starting to
get all clouded and fuzzy,
and I can't move a single
muscle in my body...
[KYOKO]
Oh no...
But you know what, Kyoko?
I finally realized how
beautiful the world is.
Ono D...
Ono D!
I guess... it's finally
come to the end...
Looks... like I'll
be the first to go...
[KYOKO gasps]
No! Don't you die on me!
You know, Kyoko... this is the
first time I've seen you cry.
No, please, just hang on.
[ONO D] This is the end...
There's something I want to say.
I just...want to tell you...
To tell you that...
T-Tell you that...
[ONO D gasps]
You wanted to tell me...
what now?
Oh, nothing,
I feel really good.
It's weird, my shoulders
and hips feel fine now...
[KYOKO &amp; ONO D scream]
[KYOKO]
What's going on?
I don't know. Ah! Kyoko!
[KYOKO gasps]
[KYOKO squeals]
[KYOKO]
Nooooo!
[BEART] Listen, Sagara,
that's not a deadly virus.
[SAGARA]
Explain.
[BEART] You know all the
attention on bacteria
that can break down
petroleum products?
Well, our researcher was trying
to put them to military use,
but he ended up
creating an odd strain.
And the result is this weapon?
That's right, it's called
the Full Monty Bacteria.
Around 36 degrees Celsius,
in other words, at
human body temperature,
it multiplies at an incredible
rate and becomes active.
When it does, it
completely devours certain
petroleum products, specifically
polyester and nylon.
That's what makes it
such a ferocious bacteria.
[SAGARA]
Are there counter measures?
[BEART]
None. Just a vaccine.
It dies after about two hours,
but until then, wear nothing
--but natural fibers.
--Here, put this on,
--Everyone around you will
--it's made of wool.
--become a victim.
--Oh, senior...
Oddly, as a side-effect,
it relieves
stiff shoulders and hips.
We'll have to settle this later.
Well, what's the word?
What's going on here?
At the very least,
it means this wasn't
a strain of deadly bacteria.
You don't say...
[CHIDORI exasperatedly laughs]
[sighs]
But, whatever the case may be...
[ENTIRE SCHOOL BODY screaming]
I doubt that I'll live
for much longer...
[indiscriminate
screaming continues]
[BOY 1] I heard Sagara's
behind this whole thing!
[BOY 2]
It's Sagara's fault?
[BOY 3] Let's get him,
that lousy son of a--
[KYOKO]
Looks like he got away!
[BOY 1] Find him!
Get out here, you bastard!
[screaming continues]
[CHRIS] Hey Luci, good job,
that was fun, huh?
[LUCI] Um, yeah,
but you're not done yet,
you still have another
line, Chris Patton.
[CHRIS]
Oh, wait, there's still more?
[LUCI]
Hello, turn the page, goofball.
This is Urzu 7. HQ, I'm
surrounded by ferocious locals.
Need immediate evacuation.
Repeat, immediate evacuation.
[BOY 1]
There he is!
[GIRL]
Rip him to shreds!