[VICE PRINCIPAL]
Principal! Principal!
Principal!
Yes, what is it,
vice principal?
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
Please take a look at this!
[PRINCIPAL] An estimate for
school repair... Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
So, 435,000 yen
total for last month?
Last week! And it's all the
work of that Sousuke Sagara.
He's a chronic property
wrecker, a class nuisance!
Vice principal, you are aware of
his circumstances, aren't you?
He's traveled from one
foreign hotspot to another
since early childhood.
We cannot expect him to
just embrace a life of peace
in Japanese society.
[VICE PRINCIPAL] Even so,
his actions are too erratic!
That is why we,
as instructors,
must accept our duty
to guide young Sagara.
So, you're overlooking this?
Yes, I am.
Principal, rumors of
a charitable donation
that came with his transfer
have been circulating, and--
That is irrelevant.
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
A rather sizeable donation...
[PRINCIPAL]
Like I said... irrelevant.
[TESS] Sergeant Sagara,
you aren't causing any trouble
for the people at
school, are you?
[SOUSUKE]
Negative, Captain.
[TESS] We cannot
have any trouble.
We are a top-secret unit
of mercenaries, after all.
[SOUSUKE] Don't worry.
I'll remove any enemy
that gets close to Chidori, even
if they're on school grounds.
[TESS] That's...
not quite what I meant.
My sincerest apologies, Captain,
but it's time for school.
Have a nice day. This is
Sergeant Sousuke Sagara
ending transmission.
[TESS]
Mr. Sagara, wait a--
[GIRL]
I love you...
[GIRL] Your sincere gaze
and manly profile...
I've always watched you
from afar... and sighed.
Feel free to laugh at
this coward who can
only express her feelings
in a letter like this...
But whenever I think
of you, I feel as though
my heart would burst.
If only I could make
my heart stop beating,
my soul could rest in peace.
Please accept my
feelings for you.
I'll wait for you behind
the gymnasium after school.
[CHIDORI yawning]
[camera shutter snaps]
You look sleepy, Kaname,
were you up late?
[CHIDORI] Yeah, the Stallone
movie that was on last night
was so good.
[KYOKO]
Did you watch the whole thing?
[CHIDORI] Yeah, it had some
spectacular explosions, ka...
--...boom!
--[STUDENTS screaming]
Wh-What's happening?
[CHIDORI growls]
Ah! Kaname!
Alright.
[CHIDORI]
It's not alright!
Exactly why are you
blowing things up already?
Explain yourself, Sousuke!
You see, Miss Chidori,
I discovered evidence
of someone tampering
with my shoe locker.
Due to the possibility that
this "someone" rigged a bomb...
Rigged a bomb?
[SOUSUKE]
I detonated it, just to be safe.
Of course. Yeah, I see.
What kind of weirdo in
this peaceful country
would rig a bomb in
someone's shoe locker?!
[SOUSUKE]
You're so naïve...
There was an incident
recently where some
Islamic fundamentalist terrorist
blew up a high-ranking
U.S. military official by
rigging a bomb in his mailbox.
I cannot be careless.
[CHIDORI] That's no reason
to do something like this!
Miss Chidori,
the most appropriate way
to dispose of suspicious
materials is detonation.
No, it's not! Each and every
day, you just constantly...
[BOTH] Huh?
[CHIDORI]
What is that?
[SOUSUKE]
It appears to be a letter.
[CHIDORI]
Hey, you're right...
[STUDENTS chattering]
[COUNCIL SECRETARY] Thirteen
wounded, three shoe lockers,
40 pairs of slippers, and
29 pairs of shoes destroyed
are the total damages.
Many thanks, Miss Mikihara.
Now, then, would someone please
care to make an explanation?
I will, your excellency, sir.
[COUNCIL PRESIDENT]
I'm listening.
Sir! Today at 0815, I
had just arrived at school,
when I noticed something
wrong with my shoe locker.
[COUNCIL PRESIDENT]
A suspicious article?
[SOUSUKE] Affirmative.
Because of the potential threat,
I implemented the most reliable
means of disposing of it.
[COUNCIL PRESIDENT]
And what means was that?
[SOUSUKE] Destruction by means
of a high-yield explosive.
[COUNCIL PRESIDENT]
Explosion you say?
Yes.
Uhh...
[CHIDORI gulps]
I see, that is most commendable.
What's wrong, Miss Chidori?
You certainly are
quite the noisy one.
Upperclassman Hayashimizu,
don't you think it's abnormal?
Where on earth would a
high school go and blow up
a school shoe locker?!
[ATSUNOBU]
Here, apparently.
Oh, come on!
It seems you fail to grasp
the severity of this situation.
Imagine this for instance:
Let's assume that a
package from a stranger
has arrived at your house.
When you pull it out,
you hear the sound
of something
rustling inside.
It could have a foul stench
or be slightly warm.
It's that kind of package.
So, would you still open that
package and take a look inside?
No, I wouldn't. I'd toss it.
[ATSUNOBU]
You would, wouldn't you?
And if it were a shoe
locker, you'd have no choice
but to blow it up.
Oh really, is that how it goes?
Yes, it is.
And I will explain this to the
teaching staff. That is all.
[CLASS chattering]
Can you... make out anything?
[SOUSUKE] Judging from the
contents, this is a letter
from a hostile third party.
[CHIDORI]
Are you serious?
[SOUSUKE] Well, if you
piece it together...
[GIRL] Sousuke Sagara, I've
always watched you from afar...
...you coward.
I'll make your heart
stop beating.
And then you'll rest in peace.
Wait behind the
gymnasium after school.
I'll kill you.
I'm almost certain
that's what the letter says.
Nice! And how did you
come up with that?
First off, it's a
girl's handwriting!
[SOUSUKE] A feint, to foil
handwriting analysis.
This guy may be a pro.
[CHIDORI]
That's one creepy pro.
Anyway, I really think
it's a love letter.
And what is that?
Huh?
It's a... Um, it's a...
There must be some girl
out there who likes you
or something.
Um, so... does that
make you happy?
I don't follow, but
it's not a problem.
Where you going?
Pre-emptive strike.
Wait! Class is about to start!
Hey, Sousuke!
Aww...
[COACH]
Jin High!
[TEAM]
Let's go! Let's go!
[COACH]
Jin High!
[TEAM]
Let's go! Let's go!
[CHIDORI]
Looks like no one's here yet.
[KYOKO] Tell me, Kaname,
why are you here checking up
on Sousuke anyway?
Well, because I'm the vice
president of the student council
here... and our class rep,
so I gotta keep an eye on him.
[KYOKO]
Mm-hmm...
What's that supposed to mean,
Kyoko? Why are you following me?
[KYOKO laughs]
Because it looked
like it might be fun!
Yeah, well, you've really
got a lot of nerve, you know?
There she is.
Huh?
[KYOKO] That's Miss
Ena Saeki from Class 1.
They say she came in second
at the Miss Jin High pageant
at the school
festival last year.
Oh, really...?
She does have a face
that any man would fall for,
but she's probably an airhead.
[KYOKO] No, I hear
she's good at school, too.
I think on the end of the year
tests, she was ranked fifth.
[KYOKO] But our subject
Sousuke has yet to arrive.
[COACH] Alright, see you later.
[TEAM chattering]
[KYOKO]
I guess Sousuke's not coming.
[CHIDORI]
Yeah, it's been two hours.
[KYOKO yawns]
I think I'll go home now.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to...
wait here a little longer.
Okay, see ya!
[CHIDORI]
Mm-hmm.
Man, that Sousuke
is such a jerk,
--standing her up...
--[PUNK 1] Ooh, that hadda hurt.
--It's so thoughtless...
--You gotta real death wish.
No big deal.
Hey, it's a girlie.
[PUNK 1]
Wow, she's a cutie.
[PUNK 3] Whatcha doin'
out at a time like this?
Nighttime's scary, see? 'Cause
there's lowlifes like us around.
Real scumbags who
do things like this.
Stop it, please.
[PUNK 1] Ooh, she said,
"Stop it, please!"
[PUNK 3] Why does
that turn me on so much?!
[CHIDORI] Okay, this
isn't good. Is anyone...?
Dammit!
[CHIDORI grunts]
Hey, stop right there!
Huh?!
[CHIDORI gasps]
She-She doesn't want you to
do that, so you let go of her!
Don't get mad.
We're just joking around,
babe, that's all.
I bet you're feeling
left out, aren't ya... babe?
Get your hand off me, now!
[PUNK 2 grunts]
Why, you...
What's your problem, you bitch?!
Who do you think
you're messin' with?!
Oh crap, I'm, uh, I'm
really opposed to violence.
Let's open up our hearts
and talk things over.
Where are you goin'?
Hey, this one's
pretty cute, too.
--N-No! Stop!
--[PUNK 3] Take it off!
Let's see what
you got in there!
--[CHIDORI] Let go of me!
--[PUNKS laughing]
[PUNK 1 grunts]
Huh...?
[PUNK 3 grunts]
[PUNK 2 grunts]
[PUNKS grunt]
What... was that?
[SOUSUKE]
Miss Chidori, are you okay?
Ah?
[CHIDORI screams]
S=Sousuke, I thought
you stood her up?!
[SOUSUKE]
No, I was lying in wait here.
Lying in wait?
[SOUSUKE]
Yes.
For Miss Saeki?!
[SOUSUKE]
Correct.
You mean... you were hiding
there under all that grass
the whole time between
lunch and now...?
Pointing your gun at her?!
[SOUSUKE] Affirmative.
My camouflage was perfect.
Had that girl made
one suspicious move,
I would have knocked her out.
You could have saved us earlier!
[SOUSUKE] Yes, but
I'm not so stupid
as to blow my cover
that recklessly.
[CHIDORI] You are stupid!
In fact, you're an imbecile!
Is that... you, Sagara?
Yes, I am Sousuke Sagara.
But... why all this...
this... uh...
But Sousuke, my love letter...
you did read it, didn't you?
[SOUSUKE]
Oh that? I detonated it.
Y-You detonated my letter...?
[SOUSUKE] It appears
you aren't an enemy,
but just what was
your purpose here?
What... was my purpose?
[SOUSUKE]
Hiding will only make it worse.
[SAEKI gasps]
[sobs]
You're... you're terrible.
[SAEKI cries]
Poor thing. There she goes.
What an odd girl.
Is she the paranoid type?
No! That's you!
[STUDENTS talking]
Not again...
Miss Chidori, what was that--
Morning! No detonations.
No! It's not safe!
[CHIDORI]
Really?
[SOUSUKE gasps]
[SOUSUKE grunts]
Huh...?
See? It's fine. Catch you later.
Hmm?
[CHIDORI] Thank you for
saving us yesterday.
Take a break
and enjoy this.
You'll wreck your body
if you don't eat right.
From the "Mysterious Terrorist."
[SOUSUKE]
A terrorist, huh?
[COMPUTER]
Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload.
[whimpering]
I was just reacting
under pressure.
[CHIDORI]
Don't!
[blow lands]
[CHIDORI] Aw man, now we
can't go back to that arcade.
I have to say,
that was incredibly uncool.
Why?
Who in the hell
would shoot a real gun
into a video game screen?!
I ran out of ammo.
I told you to reload!
All you have to do
is point the gun outside the
screen and pull the trigger.
That's not safe. What if
the gun should go off?
So you use a real one?!
[PUNK 2] Hey, we owe ya
for the other day.
You again?
[PUNK 2]
We ain't here for you.
Huh?
Hey, your name's Sagara, right?
You, come here!
You... want me to follow you?
[PUNK 2]
What do you think, clown?
Come on!
Sousuke...
Be right back.
Kaname, you're really worried
about Sousuke's safety,
aren't you?
Uh-uh. I'm worried
about them surviving.
Huh?
[PUNKS yelling]
[gun cocks]
[machine gun fire,
PUNKS screaming]
Sorry for the wait.
Y-Y-You didn't really
kill them, did you, Sousuke?
No, peaceful solutions
are the best solutions.
[PUNKS whimpering]
You let 'im go home,
just like that, huh?
Well, yeah...
How pathetic.
Miss Akutsu,
that guy's got a gun.
Come on, there ain't no way
we can win against him.
Yeah, right, it's
probably nothing but a toy.
Huh? What are you talkin'
about, huh?! It's a real gun!
It's Austrian-made.
The Steyr SPP-9MM caliber.
Holds 30 rounds.
Fires 900 rounds per minute.
It's a machine pistol
developed for security.
Its reinforced polymer
frame is extremely light.
Plus, it has superior control
in full auto mode, so you can--
[PUNK 1 screams]
[AKUTSU] Enough of your
lame-brain trivia.
Yes, ma'am...
Anyway, if that guy
Sagara's packin' weapons,
why not try using your
heads for once, huh?
How's that? Use our heads?
He's got a girl,
doesn't he? Well, then.
[PUNK 2] No, they're more like
a rabid dog and his owner.
[AKUTSU] Anyway, if you
take the girl hostage,
he can't use his weapons, right?
That makes sense.
Bring in lots of people.
I'm talkin' bout the whole gang.
[PUNKS]
Everyone?!
They've been looking
a little bored lately.
Okay, I'm heading off.
Uh... Already?
Yeah, my younger
brother asked me
to do some
shopping for him.
[SOUSUKE] You wanted to
see me, your excellency.
What happened to Miss Chidori?
[SOUSUKE] She's been absent
since this morning, sir.
Oh, is that so? The video arcade
in the shopping district
filed a complaint,
which I wanted to discuss.
[door slides open]
Hmm?
Hey, which one you Sagara?
State your business.
Look you, I got some
my boys what owes you
big time for jackin'
'em up yesterday.
They're dying to
show their appreciation.
Oh, you think you're hot shit,
huh?! I'm gonna kill ya ass!
Now, now, wait a minute.
Sagara, it sounds
as if our visitor
harbors some
hostility towards you.
He's holding a substantial
grudge for what you
did to his friends yesterday,
and says he wants to exact
his revenge upon you.
I see. Then please convey
this to him, if you would:
"My military might exceeds yours
by an overwhelming margin,
so attempts at revenge would
be a mere waste of efforts."
Hmmm.
Now listen you punk. There's no
way you'd beat me. So step off.
'Cause you ain't even got
one chance in a billion,
you loser biotch.
Your language skills are
outstanding, your excellency.
[ATSUNOBU] Oh, it's nothing.
Only what I've
gleaned from books.
I'm not certain he'll understand
my translation though.
[DELINQUENT]
What'd you say?!
[gun cocks]
[SOUSUKE]
Resorting to violence?
Wait, man. Alls I gots
is a message for ya.
[phone beeping]
Here.
Hello?
[AKUTSU] So you're the
one called Sagara, right?
[SOUSUKE]
And you are?
[AKUTSU]
Come see me after school.
[SOUSUKE]
Negative.
[AKUTSU]
Let this persuade you.
Sousuke?
[SOUSUKE]
Miss Chidori! What happened?
They grabbed me this morning
in front of the train station.
Ya get the picture?
You don't come, who knows
what'll happen to her.
Come to the abandoned factory
in Sengawa at five... alone.
[reciever clicks]
So you're holding
Miss Chidori hostage.
Heh! So there ya go.
Whatcha think?
Don't matter how many guns
you're packing,
'cause you... you can't...
What's that for?
[ATSUNOBU] You made
a foolish mistake.
We wanted to avoid
resorting to violence.
[DELINQUENT]
Wh-What the hell are y--?!
[DELINQUENT screams]
Now you will tell
us about your leader.
[DELINQUENT whimpers]
[CHIDORI]
So these are all your flunkies?
Yeah, and if your
friend doesn't show up,
I'm gonna let them
take care of you.
How... unpleasant.
[GANG MEMBER]
Miss Akutsu! He's here!
[CHIDORI gasps]
Time to let her go.
First, you drop your
weapons... all of them.
[weapons clattering]
[GANG chuckling,
weapons clattering]
[GANG whimpering]
weapons continue to clatter]
There. I've complied.
Where the hell
did you fit all that?!
Oh, nevermind.
Alright, guys, show our
guest some hospitality.
[GANG chuckls]
Hey, that isn't fair!
Right. I'm not a fair person.
Sousuke, run away!
Eat lead, bastard!
Hey, look up there.
[GANG MEMBER 2]
Dude, that's her brother.
[AKUTSU gasps]
Yo... Yoshiki!
Yes. Your younger brother.
I kidnapped him
from the school yard
and hung him up there
when you weren't looking.
It seems he's the only
person you open up to.
[AKUTSU]
How do you know that?!
[SOUSUKE] I have my sources...
[DELINQUENT] I'll tell
you everything!
I believe he should be
waking up fairly soon...
[YOSHIKI screams]
Yoshiki!
Sis, please! H-Help me!
D-Don't struggle!
Stay still!
Don't worry, these
ropes won't break
from the mild tension
induced by struggling.
However...
[YOSHIKI screams]
Yoshiki!
[YOSHIKI] Come on, Sis, help me!
There are five
ropes remaining.
How many do you
think it will take
before your brother falls?
[YOSHIKI screaming]
[AKUTSU gasps]
--[YOSHIKI] Help! Save me!
--[SOUSUKE] So, what now?
Just stop it! Or I'm gonna...
[SOUSUKE]
You're gonna what?
[YOSHIKI screams]
[YOSHIKI]
Hurry!
Don't you care what
happens to this girl here?!
[SOUSUKE]
Will you kill her?
Very well.
What?!
Chidori, I'm sorry,
but I'm afraid
you must share the
same fate as the boy.
No deals with terrorists. That's
the international standard.
What are you talking about?!
[SOUSUKE] Don't worry.
I'll write your next of kin.
You'll do what?!
[SOUSUKE]
Make your choice, Mari Akutsu.
You can save both of them,
or you can kill both of them.
[AKUTSU] If I give in, it'll set
a bad example for the boys,
but if I don't...
Yoshiki... Yoshiki will...
Everyone has something
important to him.
For instance, like you!
Yes, you. Your name
is Seiji Takayama.
An 11th grader at
Garasayuma High.
You adore your little sister
who is in middle school...
The sister who takes
Benton Street home every day
at 6 PM. That's a
fairly deserted street.
I'd be worried that someone
bad might go after her...
[TAKAYAMA screams]
And then there's you, Yuta Date.
You own a love bird.
You begged your parents to buy
you one when you were eleven.
They say love birds
die easily...
Simply spraying insecticide into
the room through a window crack
would send them into fatal,
writhing convulsions of pain.
Stop it! Please, no more!
There's no need for you
to be frightened, Mr. Date.
I was only talking
about your parakeet.
You're Koichi Igarashi.
You have a bike that
you worked hard to buy.
And let's see...
you are Keiji Endo.
You live alone with
your dear mother.
Shigaru Subaru.
Recently you got a girlfriend
who's a year younger than you.
And Shintaro Nakajima,
your older sister gave birth
to a child a week ago...
[GANG screaming]
[CHIDORI grunts]
There. Are you satisfied?
Now you let my brother go.
Are you alright?
Uh, thanks, but...
Yes, I know what
you're about to say.
"You should've killed them all
the minute you saw them..."
That's not it! I can't
believe you did that
to an innocent child!
Oh right, that.
[AKUTSU &amp; CHIDORI] Huh?!
That was good, right?
It was. You performed very well.
But it was pretty scary.
Hey, don't forget
your promise, okay?
[SOUSUKE]
A radio controlled car, right?
You mean you tricked me!?
[YOSHIKI chuckles sheepishly]
His excellency offered
me his full support.
He told me
not to hold back
and to match the enemy's
methods, stride for stride.
After all, peaceful solutions
are the best ones, right?
That was peaceful...?
Whatcha wanna eat?
[SOUSUKE]
Curry rice sounds good.
What, again?
He just burst into the
classroom all of a sudden
and came to me and said,
"I need you to help me!"
Then he pulled a gun on Teach.
"It's an emergency!"
I guess he was really
worried about her, huh?
Wow, you know, maybe he's not
quite the nut I thought he was.
[YOSHIKI]
Huh?
[AKUTSU]
Nothing. Let's go home.
[SOUSUKE] The action series,
Full Metal Panic: Fumoffu,
has finally begun!
Next time, you'll witness
heated battles between
the human-shaped mobile
suits the arms slaves, and--
[CHIDORI]
Oh, there aren't any this time.
[SOUSUKE]
What?!
[CHIDORI] There aren't any.
None, not even at the end.
[SOUSUKE] But when will
I get to show off, then?
[CHIDORI] Next time on the
classroom love comedy,
Full Metal Panic: Fumoffu...
Tune in for
"Hostility Passing-By"
and "A Fruitless Lunchtime."
[SOUSUKE] Wait, I wasn't
briefed on any love comedy!