♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the Mystery Disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled Mystery Disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Ah, it's a wonderful
day to be alive,
especially if you
happen to be a genius.
Tough job, but
somebody's gotta do it.
(laughing)
Hare, if you're a genius,
we're in a lot of trouble.
Yeah.
Enough already!
When are we gonna find
another Mystery Disk?
Soon, soon.
Yeah, finding disks
isn't a piece of cake.
Mocchi hungry!
Cut it out, it's
only an expression!
Remind me not to call
Suezo a turkey.
(all laughing)
♪
Well, look who I found.
Anyway, the Mystery Disk
is supposed to be
in this direction.
Let's go get it!
Yeah!
♪
This direction?
Excuse me.
How do they know where
to find Mystery Disks?
Holly, I think we should check
the stone, just to be sure.
Okay.
Stone?
♪
Magic, if you weren't
a stone, I'd kiss ya!
All right,
the Mystery Disk is here!
(cheering)
How do they know that?
♪
Huh?
(grunting)
♪
Chi, Chi, Chi.
Tiger!
Are you a monster
or a gopher?
Watch what you're doing!
Then get out of the way, Hare.
Back at ya, Tiger!
(groaning)
(laughing)
You look like Tiger
of the Dirt to me.
‐You've been warned!
‐Any time, punk!
(growling)
(shouting)
Stop!
Fighting is bad.
(clanking)
♪
Chi!
Disk, Chi!
Mocchi, you're the best!
‐Mocchi!
It's about time!
Wish I'd found that.
This is your lucky day, Weed.
Looks like
an excellent opportunity
to get in solid with Moo.
It's a strange‐looking
Mystery Disk.
Maybe it holds the Phoenix.
This is unbelievable!
Hurry, hurry!
♪
Prepare for takeoff.
(groaning)
♪
Oh, where's one
when you need one?
Come on, come on!
Just the littlest, tiniest...
Ha, excellent!
Ready...
(wind gusting)
Liftoff!
I'm in clover now!
Ha!
Master Moo, here I come!
(grunting and whimpering)
♪
Higher!
(groaning)
Holly, I'm an eyeball,
not a baseball.
But we're counting
on you, Suezo.
Go for it, you can do it!
Wait, wait, wait, I'm not ready!
(grunting)
♪
Hmm?
Got one!
All right, Suezo!
Incoming!
(grunting)
♪
Okay, all ready, Holly.
Mocchi all ready, too.
‐Mm‐hm.
‐This could be it.
♪
Unlock.
(electricity zapping)
♪
(gasping)
It's a Monol!
♪
(whirring)
I am Monol.
My story is my purpose.
♪
(all gasping)
So, what is your story, Monol?
It's about a mistake.
What do you mean, a mistake?
The mistake of
the ancient beings.
We don't have time
for storytelling.
We got stuff
we gotta get done.
You must listen
to my story!
Who's gonna make us?
Watch it, Monol.
I'm not listening to any
story unless I want to!
We must free the Phoenix.
That's my story.
Let's listen!
‐Yeah.
‐It better be good!
Suezo, please!
Your story is about the Phoenix?
Please tell us what you know.
It's a long one.
Gather around.
Waste of time.
Come on!
Maybe it'll help us
beat the Baddies.
Well, in that case...
Me, too.
(exclaiming)
♪
(clearing throat)
Uh, Monol?
(Monol breathing sleepily)
(snoring)
Hey, wake up!
Huh?
Ah, sorry.
I‐I do that sometimes.
Close your eyes.
I'll make a direct‐access
image to your brains.
Chi?
What's this direct‐access thing?
He's going to send the story's
pictures into our brains.
Sounds like a scam to me.
Come on, this could help us.
♪
Concentrate.
Open your hearts, wider.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it and claim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Phoenix soars
like Master Moo ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Everybody wants 'em,
how about you? ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Moo is the giant
baddest of bad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Nagas fight form,
to resist would be mad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Four hundred monsters,
all shapes and sizes ♪
♪ You can't predict 'em,
they're full of surprises ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Oh!
Oh, wow, that's cool!
Once long ago,
there was a planet,
and on that planet,
only one continent,
a land called Vangea.
The people of
Vangea had created
an advanced civilization.
No, in fact, an extremely
advanced civilization.
These Ancients
developed a technology
that allowed them to create
monsters in the laboratory
and then store the
genetic information,
sealing it in CD‐ROMs.
♪
When the world
was one continent.
I almost feel like
I'm right there,
back in that
ancient civilization.
In time, this technology
became commonplace
and was taken for granted.
And the monsters,
the miraculous result of
this wondrous technology,
became household pets,
created and used for
people's amusement.
But not only monsters
were created.
The technology
was used to create
whatever people believed
would make them happy,
whatever they believed
would please them.
At the peak of
this civilization,
its people believed
they were gods.
But despite their technology,
they were not able to foresee
the great disasters
that attacked the land.
♪
(rumbling)
(wind howling)
(waves crashing)
♪
(exclaiming)
(lightning crashing)
♪
All their advancements
and civilized conveniences
were soon forgotten.
The thin veneer
of civilization
was stripped away,
and the people became savage.
Fights became battles,
and battles became wars.
At first, it was
called the Final War.
(zapping)
(explosions)
But as it went on,
thirty, fifty,
one hundred years...
♪
...the cause of the war
faded from memory.
No one remembered
why they were fighting,
only the bitter
feelings transferred
from one generation to the next,
and the war continued.
♪
One day,
countless years after
the war had begun,
a new monster was created.
♪
It was called Moo.
(roaring and stomping)
(laser zapping)
♪
Tiger, is Moo really that big?
He is huge and he is terrifying,
someone to stay away from.
(whimpering)
♪
Moo's strength
could not be matched.
(laser zapping)
♪
Although he was a living being,
he had been created
for no purpose
but to destroy the enemy.
It was thought that whoever
achieved control of Moo
would win the war,
but Moo became his own master.
He obeyed no commands
but his own.
He learned how to draw forth
and amplify the darkness
in the hearts of other monsters.
♪
The scientists who had survived
turned their efforts
to the creation of a creature
capable of stopping Moo.
That creature was the Phoenix.
♪
(Phoenix screeching)
(whimpering)
♪
When Moo and the
Phoenix did battle,
the scientists
completed the Final Gate,
the way to separate
Moo's mind from his body.
It was a dangerous machine,
one that would
affect all monsters,
but the people believed
they had no choice.
It was the only way to stop Moo.
(exclaiming)
♪
The ancient people of Vangea
had a terrible decision to make.
If they were to rid
themselves of Moo,
they knew their solution
would harm all monsters.
(Phoenix screeching)
♪
But they had no choice.
(whirring and zapping)
Otherwise, they would
all be destroyed.
And so, Moo's body
and mind were separated.
He was destroyed.
But so was the Phoenix...
♪
... and all the other creatures.
The cost was incomprehensible.
♪
(rumbling)
And that is my story.
♪
(exclaiming)
It happened a long,
long time ago.
I didn't know,
no one ever told me.
That's a story.
Chi.
There are some things
about that story
that remind me of my world.
Now just hold on a minute here.
If the Ancients destroyed Moo,
why is it that we're still
struggling against him today?
Yes, Tiger is right, Monol.
Obviously,
his work is not yet done.
What does that mean?
Perhaps Moo's mind
has attached itself
to another body.
Attached itself?
That doesn't sound good.
So, Moo existed a long time ago,
then he was sort of destroyed,
but not really, and now he's
trying to start it again,
is that it?
I am not going to let him do it!
Chi!
Well, that's why we're
looking for the Phoenix
so we can revive it and put
an end to Moo's evil ways.
What she said!
Now, here's a question for you.
If Moo's mind has
been floating around,
what does that mean
for the Phoenix?
Get outta here, Hare!
You mean even if
we find the Phoenix,
we won't be able
to retrieve him
because his mind
won't be there, too?
Come on, that's
just too depressing.
Well, what do you think, Monol?
Patience.
You will find out
at the right time.
Hey, what's your problem?
It's your job to tell us!
My story is my purpose.
‐I...
‐Huh?
Monol?
(snoring)
♪
Hey!
Cut that out!
♪
What?
The Magic Stone?
That's right, I saw it all.
The stone looked bright red,
and then they found
a disk close by.
It's not possible
for an ordinary person
to use that stone.
There was some girl usin' it.
What?
Oh, yes, a human girl
if I'm not mistaken.
I think I heard them
call her Holly.
Holly.
Is something the matter?
Holly, is it?
(chuckling deviously)
We'll see about that.
I would like nothing more
than to be at your service,
Your Majesty.
I will take care of the girl.
No, I will find the girl myself.
You're... going yourself?
(laughing deviously)
♪
Hey, Monol, why don't
you come along with us
to find the Phoenix?
I cannot.
Monol, Chi?
My purpose is to tell my story.
I understand.
But I have one more
thing to tell you.
Monol, I don't know...
That last one
was a little heavy.
We're listening.
♪
(screaming)
I hate it when
you do that, Monol.
(popping)
(grumbling)
Take care of yourselves.
(exclaiming)
Is that your big message?
(laughing)
You take care of yourself, too.
Bye‐bye, Monol!
Thanks for telling
us your story.
Be careful.
♪
If you see Moo,
tell him to watch out for us!
Yeah, me especially!
Very nice meeting you.
Good luck, Monol.
Goodies rule!
♪
Well, I guess we know what
we gotta do for sure now.
We have to find the Phoenix.
Mocchi, Mocchi, Mocchi!
(Golem laughing)
Okay, let's get rollin', yeah!
♪
Master Moo, I know
where the girl is.
Bring her here.
Yes, yes!
Just wait.
(laughing maniacally)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪