♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
They're headed for Yellow River,
and I'm quite sure
they'll cross it.
That would work in
our favor, Master Naga,
because no one is more powerful
underwater than us Arrowheads.
(clank)
All right, finish them off,
but you must watch out.
Of course.
(metallic twinkling)
(rushing water)
Man, this river's enormous.
River's yellow, 'Chi.
The soil's just
clouding the water.
What does the stone say, Holly?
♪
It's pointing to the
other side of the river.
(collective inhale)
Golem hates water.
Golem will sink and drown.
What should we do then?
Hm, how about we walk upriver
and find a place that's narrower
where we can cross it?
Let's get rolling.
All right, let's do it!
(twanging)
I don't see any
narrow part, Hare.
Now this is getting
worse all the time!
Ah, looks like I've taken
you on the scenic route.
Hm?
Hey, look, it's a big house.
Oh, I can make out a sign.
"Rest‐au‐rant," hey, grub!
Looks like a family restaurant.
Mocchi hungry!
Hm?
♪
(yawning)
Oh, we've got customers!
Wake up, Captain,
hey, Captain Jim!
We've got customers!
(clanking)
♪
What's all the racket?
Why did you have
to disturb my sleep?
(deep sigh)
♪
Customers?
Up until now, only
the baddies came.
(grunting)
♪
Hey guys, I can't see
a baddies crest anywhere!
Well, that goes without
saying, we're not baddies.
Yes, but do the
baddies have this area
completely under their control?
That would be impossible,
the area is too big
to have total control over it.
So there are other people
and monsters around
besides the baddies?
Guess so, after all, I'm
living here with the Eared Mew.
Let's stop it right there
and save it for later!
Come on in and have some food!
(humming)
(sizzling)
♪
‐Here it comes!
‐Got it!
Here you are, one large order
of spaghetti and meatballs.
(eating noises)
‐Huh?
‐Ah!
(chomp)
(sounds of struggle)
♪
Hey, who stole the meatballs?
Huh?
You were taking too long,
so I had to use the Tiger
spinning meat attack.
That'll teach you
to play with your food.
So, are you folks travelers?
Yeah, we're on a quest
to find the Phoenix.
And what exactly
is this Phoenix?
I've never heard of it,
are you sure it exists?
Of course, it's a
legendary monster!
Tell us, what's your story?
I'm a simple man,
just a short order cook.
But didn't the Eared Mew
call you Captain?
That's 'cause I
have a small ferry.
A ferry?
Well, you've got yourself
some passengers.
♪
(collective inhale)
Ferry shmerry, that's
practically a cruise liner!
♪
Wow!
What do you think?
This is my ferry
the SS Raspberry.
We got lucky one day and found
an engine nearby so we went
and scooped it up and the
rudder's top of the line,
it can handle even
the harshest current,
and the body's so tough
it won't even get scratched
if you crash into the rocks!
Oh!
So, what's it gonna set us back?
♪
300 golds per person.
300 times 7 makes 2,100 golds
and if you figure in
our group discount rate,
then that will
come to a total of,
what do you saw we settle on
a rate of 200 golds per person?
You trying to whittle us down?
I'm the only man around these
parts who can cross the river.
I don't care who asks for a
ride, even if it's a baddie,
I'll get them there as
long as I get paid in full.
I guarantee it.
(sigh)
So the full meal deal.
That's 2,100 golds then, please.
Uh‐oh, wait a sec, I think
you've forgot to take in
the ferry's age
and its depreciation, hm.
Which would make
a grand total of 1,100.
Then the deal's off, bunny.
All right then,
we'll go up to 1,500.
Not enough.
Oh!
2,100 and not one gold less.
Look, don't you know a good
offer when you see one?
Nope, wanna take it or leave it?
We'll take your deal.
At last, someone with brains.
The deal's set then and
I'll even throw in lunch
on the house.
Hmph, better be good!
(thud)
Hey, how about lending me a hand
packing up the boat, big guy?
Huh, me?
♪
Captain Jim, I can help,
what do you want me to do?
That's all right, just stand
back and keep out of the way.
Huh, oh, come on, what do you
take me for, a kid or something?
Hey, I may be little,
but I can pull my own weight
around here, you know.
(grunting)
(chuckling)
I thought you said you
could pull your own weight.
You can't even handle that rope.
♪
There, now stay out
of the way, kid.
I'm not a kid!
If you weren't you
wouldn't be so mad.
Forget I ever
offered to help you
and don't bother
asking for any favors.
(grunting)
Right, ready to push?
‐Go.
‐On the count of three!
One, two, three!
(grunting)
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it and claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Find the Seed Sisters,
charming but frightening ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Or the Usaba quicker
than lightning ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ There's Evil Hare
and his Captain ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ They love to fight
like Pirate Dragons ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Mighty they battle,
mighty they fall ♪
♪ These monsters rule,
unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Monster's rule ♪
(grunting)
♪
They did it, everyone on board!
'Chi!
(laughing)
Huh, hey, what about Golem?
Have a great trip,
sorry I can't join you!
(whimpering)
Golem scared, hate
river, Golem sink.
Hey, chill out, Golem.
It's just a ferry.
Huh?
♪
(buttons tapping)
Everybody on board?
(in unison)
Aye, aye, Captain!
♪
I'm counting on you, Raspberry.
‐Now, let's cast off!
‐Aye, aye!
(bell ringing)
And we're off!
♪
(laughing)
(sinister chuckling)
They're falling
right into our trap.
Move out!
(squawking)
Hm.
How's it looking there, matey?
Let's see.
Uh‐oh!
There's rocks up ahead, Captain!
Roger, hard to starboard!
♪
(grunts)
You don't make
for a very good spy.
What makes you think
I was trying to spy?
You want to take a tour
of the wheelhouse?
Yeah!
Uh, no way, that's boring.
Come on, I'll let
you steer the boat.
Hey, but I thought you said the
kid should stay out of the way.
Nnnnnng!
Gee, I think that kid's
really taken to me.
(loud crash)
(screaming)
Something's out there!
What?
(splash)
It's the baddies!
♪
Ah!
You take the rudder!
Aye, aye!
♪
(splashing)
Eared Mew, head
for the shallows!
Aye, aye!
♪
Here they come!
No, kid, it's dangerous!
What?
Ah!
(crash)
Jim!
‐Genki!
‐I'm coming!
(grunt)
Genki!
♪
It's you!
(metal scraping)
Captain, we're on the sandbar!
Good, this will work out fine.
Get us on land.
Retreat!
(squawking)
♪
Oh, something
smells scrumptious!
Wieners, my favorite!
Sure looks good!
Dinner tonight is on the house!
♪
(sighing)
Genki, you hurt, 'Chi?
No, I'm fine.
Cheer up, 'Chi!
Whatever.
I'm sorry, Captain, it's all
our fault for dragging you
into this mess.
What do you mean?
She means Moo is going to
come after you two as well.
No problem, I don't care
who my customers are.
As long as I get
my money in the end,
I'll get you
to your destination.
Genki, Mocchi!
Dinner's on!
Food, 'Chi, 'Chi!
Come eat!
No, thanks, you go.
'Chi?
You did good back there.
Huh?
Thanks, what's wrong?
How come you're
sitting out here?
Nothing.
Hey, you still mad 'cause I was
treating you like a kid before?
Then I apologize.
I don't need your apologies.
Maybe Captain Jim was right,
maybe I am just
a self‐centered kid
who always winds up getting
my friends into trouble.
You're thinking about
things a little too much.
When I was your age I did
a lot of foolish things,
and I got my friends into
quite a bit of trouble.
Did you really?
Sure, I was cocky and
I used to charge around
like some kind of loose cannon,
nothing could stop me,
I wasn't afraid of anything.
Like me?
Yup, but because
I was like that
I learned a lot
of lessons, Genki.
People can learn a lot
from their past mistakes.
Important things, things
that make them stronger.
You mean, I could grow up
to be strong like you?
So when any baddies
come to get me,
I'll be able to blow
them out of the water!
That's the attitude!
Keep that up, and you'll
be much stronger than me.
Well, I've got to get a move
on and make some mistakes,
so I can start learning!
That's not quite what I meant.
(laughing together)
Ah, Genki's happy again.
'Chi!
♪
Everything's ready!
Right, let's do it, gang!
Yeah!
(grunting)
♪
You're such a wimp, Golem.
Can't you help us?
(whimpering)
♪
Eared Mew!
Yes, sir, starting the engine.
(engine winding up)
Now, let's get out of here
before those crawfish come back.
You said it!
♪
Rock, move out!
Keep the speed up,
we've almost made it!
I hear you!
(rushing water)
♪
‐They're here!
‐Ready!
‐Me too.
‐Don't let them near the boat!
‐Right!
‐(grunt)
‐Where are they?
‐Look!
They went into
deeper water!
We've got to pass by them
to make it to the other side.
(whimpering)
Come on, Raspberry, don't
let those baddies get ya!
(crash)
♪
(groaning)
Everyone, jump in the river!
Golem not know how to swim!
Do you want to go down
with the ship then?
If you can't swim,
use the harpoon floats.
The rest of you try
to swim to shore.
What about you?
I'm staying right
here with my ferry.
You can't do that,
it's going down!
Not if I can help it!
‐Don't stay!
‐Get going!
(grunting)
(whimpering)
Eared Mew!
‐Look after our passengers.
‐Aye, aye!
♪
(creaking)
No!
(splashing)
(squawking)
♪
We don't stand a
chance against them.
Keep swimming
as fast as you can!
No, Jim!
(squawking)
♪
(bubbling)
What?
(groaning)
(crash)
Jim!
♪
Answer if you can hear us!
Jim?
Are you there?
Captain?
(grunting)
We've been searching
for the captain for hours
and still no sign of him.
Captain.
(crying)
Can't be, he must be there!
Hey, Jim, yo!
Hey, Jim!
(glittering metallic sound)
♪
I'm not that easy to get rid of.
I got caught
in the down current.
I had a long ways to walk back,
so it took me quite a while.
Captain?
Jim?
You know, you people sure
got your money's worth today.
‐Jim!
‐Captain!
Okay, that's enough,
what's gotten into you guys?
(laughing)
♪
You sure overreacted.
(laughing)
♪
(wind blowing)
This job would be so much easier
if we could just use
the humans to do the work.
Master Moo said he didn't want
to go to all that trouble,
so stop your whining.
You said it, brother, and
anyway, the job's almost done.
♪
That's impossible.
Oh!
♪
(deep growling)
No, I can't believe
what I'm seeing.
That's Moo's original body!
♪
You folks take care now.
Thanks, I really hope
we see you again.
Sure!
Bye!
Captain, I hate to
bring this up but‐‐
What do we owe
you for the boat?
Don't worry about it,
I'll build another one.
(deep sigh)
Genki, I'm not good at goodbyes,
so why don't we just go
our own separate ways?
Um, Jim...
Yeah?
Do you think we'll ever
see each other again?
♪
Hm, of course, we will,
we're friends after all!
(chuckling)
We're friends, 'Chi!
That's right, friends!
Then I'll see you
when I see you!
‐Hey, what for us!
‐'Chi!
‐Well, thanks again!
‐Take care.
Bye!
♪
Genki cry, 'Chi?
I'm sweating, all right,
haven't you seen sweat before?
Oh.
♪
(laughing)
Come on, guys,
we've got work to do!
Let's go and find that Phoenix!
Yeah!
(laughing)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monster's rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪