♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disc ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disc ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(twinkling sound)
(lights flicker on)
♪
(crowd cheering)
And now with the scores
all tied up,
the Monster Rancher
Grand Tournament's
Final Battle!
(crowd cheering)
For Team Big, it's Michael!
For Team Roars,
it's Genki!
The final battle is between
the two team captains.
(chuckles)
'Huh' yourself.
And now without
further adieu, begin!
♪
(mechanical clink)
(grunting)
Mike's Magna starting
with a Rock Assault!
And Genki's pink Suezo
counters with a tongue slap!
Rock, no, tongue slap!
Oh my!
(crowd roaring)
♪
(grunting)
(score buzzer ringing)
♪
(zapping)
Oh, Genki's pink Suezo's
gaining ground, folks!
Do it!
Wait a minute‐‐
What's this?
(mechanical beeping)
Oh ho, Magna's famous
spinning attack
with little time
left in the game!
(laughs)
Things don't look good
for Genki.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
...six, five,
four, three, two‐‐
Now!
He's getting up!
He's‐‐
(score tally ringing)
(crash)
Genki pulled it off!
Ye‐heah!
(crowd cheering)
And the winner is
Genki and the Team Roars!
Besides the winner's plaques,
Genki's special prize
is software so new,
it's not even on the market!
Monster series 200x!
Awesome!
In fact, the software
is still in development,
but you'll get it first, Genki!
Watch your mail!
(crowd cheering)
Yeah, Monster Battle rules,
thank you everyone,
I love being here,
thank you!
‐Genki?
‐Monster Battle rules,
‐thank you.
‐Genki!
Monster Battle!
(confused murmuring)
♪
Ugh, oh boy, that teacher
has no imagination.
♪
Same old.
Nothing changes.
Boring.
♪
But just maybe, somewhere...
(whooshing)
(digitized beeping)
♪
I'm here, I'm not
dreaming this time!
It's real, it's the world
of the monsters!
Hey, Genki!
Ugh, what am I supposed
to do with you, child?
Look!
Three, two, one, begin!
(bell ringing)
School's out!
(whooshing)
Genki, your homework!
(whistle blowing)
(background traffic)
♪
Let it be there,
let it be there,
let it be there!
(panting)
Huh?
♪
Yeah, it's here,
it's here, it's here!
Come on, hurry, hurry,
hurry, come on, hurry!
Ah, I'm not waiting, not today!
♪
(laughs)
Genki, is that you?
‐Can't you even say you're home?
‐I'm home!
I've got sweet cakes
for your snack.
‐Thank you?
‐Oh, uh, thank you!
(munching)
Yes!
(ringing)
(kissing)
Time to play!
♪
(disc spinning)
(mechanical beeping)
♪
(beep)
Long ago, when the world
was still one big continent,
a great disaster occurred.
The disaster left an emptiness
in the world.
An emptiness
that was soon filled
by new life forms.
Over time, battles erupted
and some of the new life forms
were hidden away, imprisoned.
Humans were entrusted
with their guardianship.
Hmm.
Many generations have passed,
and some of the
imprisoned life forms
have been released,
many more remain hidden,
waiting for the moment
they will come to life.
♪
(panting)
‐Stop!
‐Return the mystery disk!
Not to you guys, no way!
(slobbering)
Ugh!
(splash)
Oof!
I could be wrong, but I think
I just got spat on!
‐Suezo!
‐Huh?
Hurry, they're coming!
(humorous grunting)
♪
A shrine, of course!
Let's do it!
(buzz)
♪
(panting)
There it is up ahead!
♪
(beeping)
(fire whooshing)
(bubbling)
Gotta load CD Rom.
♪
(beeping)
(whoosh)
♪
Ha!
(high‐pitched buzzing)
♪
Unlock!
(zap)
♪
(yelling)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disc, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it and claim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Captain Black Dino,
one who moves best ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Lead the black dinos
on every conquest ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Little Spot Dino,
harmless enough ♪
♪ To unlock a Kuro,
you gotta be tough ♪
♪ Captain Kuro
will stomp and brawl ♪
♪ Monsters rule,
unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it
unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(whooshing, zapping)
♪
(yelling "ow")
(yelling)
Ugh, you're a Suezo,
you look so real,
you almost scared me!
If I wasn't real,
could I do this?
(grunting)
Ew, oh.
♪
(yelling, laughter)
You are for real!
Where did you come from?
Oh man, you're never gonna‐‐
I was trying to get
this new game software,
‐but all of a sudden‐‐
‐There they are!
Don't try to escape!
Oh no, they found us, run!
(yelling)
(stomping)
♪
Those were black dinos,
weren't they?
But they're just
a little different
from the ones
I'm used to seeing.
‐I see.
‐Well, I mean, I know
a lot about
monsters and everything,
‐it's just‐‐
‐Do you know
a lot about monsters?
Of course I do!
Don't like to brag,
but maybe you've heard of me.
I won it all at
the Monster Battle.
‐Make sense to you?
‐Not at all.
(stomping)
(yelling)
(panting)
♪
(chomp)
(zap)
(commotion, yelling)
Get out, Tail Slash!
Ugh, huh, haha!
Beat the baddies!
(grunting)
♪
(yelling)
(metallic buzzing)
♪
Oh, sure, right,
I'm just an eyeball!
Oh, whoa!
♪
Oh, that was great,
I can't believe it,
it was so fun!
(sighing)
It's okay, Holly,
you win some and you lose some.
‐Oh.
‐Yeah!
♪
Ha ha!
Yeah!
My dream come true.
(birds hooting)
♪
Wow!
Yee‐haw, I'm the champ,
champ, champ, champ,
champ, champ, champ!
We were hoping for the Phoenix,
but then that kid appeared,
I don't blame you
for being blue.
(laughs)
I did it!
I did it, I did it,
I knew this place was for real.
(crickets chirping)
(laughing)
What do we do with him?
Nothing to do, he's just a kid.
If there's one thing
I can't stand,
it's people who call me a kid.
Tantrums are also
a sign of immaturity.
You may be stuck here, kid.
You should try to make
as many friends as you can.
I'm not stuck here,
no sir‐ee!
I'm a champion monster player
and I'm where the action is,
so get used to it!
But how could you be
playing a game in your world
and then all of a sudden
end up in ours,
it just doesn't make much sense.
Yeah, I know, but that's
what happened, look.
Is that the game?
‐Show me.
‐Catch!
(struggling)
‐Huh.
‐Hmm?
A mystery disk.
It's just a CD Rom.
In this world,
it's a mystery disk
and may hold the Phoenix.
Moo loses again.
You aren't making
a lot of sense.
But you're an expert,
you just said so.
Well I am, but
I still don't know
what you two are talking about.
What kind of an expert
has never heard of Moo?
Moo?
No one knows for sure
what he looks like.
But he's gathering mystery disks
from everywhere,
and he changes good monsters
into baddies.
(roaring)
What for?
To conquer this world.
Conquer the world?
That's right.
Just like the ancients did.
Moo makes goodies into baddies
to conquer the world.
Well, I am the champ,
and I say Moo
shouldn't be allowed
to get away with that.
It's just not right!
Oh, really?
(evil laughter)
Black dinos!
Well, well, well, so how
do you plan to do that?
There's only one way!
(grunting)
And that made you champ?
There's always plan B.
(whoosh)
‐That really worked!
‐Well, I tried!
Some champ you turned out to be!
(roaring)
Punks!
Let's go back to the shrine!
Why, what are you
gonna do there?
Let's give the CD Rom a shot.
Do what?
Maybe there really is
a Phoenix inside.
Yes, and then he'll change
all the baddies
into goodies again!
Well, it's gotta be worth a try!
Let's get ready
to pull some air!
(whoosh)
(yelling)
(crumbling rock)
(grunting, rocks crumbling)
♪
(grunting in anger)
I can make
my own monster for real!
I'll be able to meet
my own monster!
(whooshing, wind blowing)
(springing)
♪
Set the mystery disk.
(fire whooshing)
(grunting)
(mechanical whirring)
‐Let's do it!
‐Right!
Unlock!
♪
‐Ugh.
‐Nice going, champ.
(grunting)
I'm getting very, very tired
of this little game,
now hand over that disk!
Turns out we don't have
that particular disk anymore.
It disappeared when
this boy was unlocked.
Nice try, I can see it
from here.
No, that one's a fake.
But you can take it
if it makes you happy.
‐Hang on!
‐Huh?
I want to try again,
let me try one more time.
I can do it!
I know I can.
Okay.
What?
(whirring)
No, you don't!
Uh‐oh, now you've got her mad!
(yelling)
♪
Focus my thoughts.
Think only
of creating a monster.
(breathing)
(whirring)
(whooshing)
(grunting)
(roaring)
(yelling)
Unlock!
(zapping)
♪
‐It's the Phoenix!
‐All right, champ!
♪
(whooshing)
(whirring)
♪
(bouncing)
Huh?
(popping)
♪
Chi.
‐And this is a Phoenix?
‐Huh, some champ.
(yelling)
Too bad.
Mocchi, mocchi, hungry mocchi!
♪
Sorry excuse for a monster,
but I am partial
to this shade of pink!
I think I'll keep it as a pet.
I'm your master now, understand?
(grunting)
♪
(springing)
(zapping)
(boom)
(rocks crumbling)
♪
Come on!
(yelling)
(grumbling)
(rocks crumbling)
♪
(wind blowing)
(panting)
♪
That was truly awesome, huh?
Not my idea of fun.
Heh, here.
You did pretty good back there.
You weren't too bad yourself.
How about if I come with you?
Going against Moo is dangerous.
‐Are you ready for that?
‐Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Genki, my name means energy
and no one can compare to me.
I've got lots and lots of it.
♪
Genki, I'm Holly.
Hey, I'm in!
(laughs)
♪
But I'm the one you're gonna
have to answer to here, Genki.
‐Understand?
‐Suezo, right?
Huh, that happens to be
Mr. Suezo to you, kid!
(peep)
We have to give
your monster a name.
Chi‐chi.
Genki the second!
‐Chi.
‐Pinky sound good.
‐Chi chi.
‐Siggysame?
Chi.
Okay, okay, how about this.
Montezuma.
No, no, it doesn't suit 'em.
‐I like Pinky Peach.
‐No, something simple,
‐like Trevor, I think.
‐Chi, chi!
(grunting)
♪
(whooshing)
Yeah, that's it!
It's sweet cake!
Huh?
‐He's sweet?
‐Chi, chi!
Mocchi!
Ha, ha, I guess that's it then.
‐Your name is Mocchi!
‐Mocchi!
I guess it's Mocchi.
Yep, that was my next idea.
Sure, Suezo.
My adventure,
it's beginning right now!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(twinkling)