♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(zapping)
(roaring)
♪
(crash)
What happened, it's
completely destroyed in here!
The magic stone
is gone as well.
Uh, who are you?
My name is Monol, and I was
born to relay the past.
What do you mean?
(crash)
♪
(rocks crumbling)
Move, troops!
(whooshing)
(zapping)
♪
(roaring)
(fire crackling)
♪
Huh?
It's the Dragon Army!
Yeah, they've come back!
Oh.
Hey gang, long time no see.
Monol!
What are you doing here?
Moo captured me and
locked me up on Mt. Kairus.
He saw the whole thing.
The magic stone disappeared
when they use the final gate.
(group reacting in shock)
Even the final gate itself
was destroyed by
the time we got there.
Probably 'cause the final gate
was the key to
resurrecting the Phoenix.
No wonder he destroyed it!
Phoenix can't be brought back?
Hang on, there's
still another way
that we can do it.
‐Chi!
‐That's right,
it's too early to give up!
That's exactly what
I came here to tell you.
Huh?
I came to fill you
in on everything.
What are you talking about?
Concentrate on
opening your minds.
(ethereal humming)
♪
That's it, now clear
your minds of all thoughts.
Good, that's the way.
(mechanical whooshing)
♪
Think back to the ancient war,
when Moo and the
Phoenix were battling.
(smashing)
(zapping)
The final gate
absorbed the energy
from one of the magic stones.
(zap)
Moo's soul and body
were separated.
(oscillating metallic whoosh)
At the same time,
the Phoenix's soul and body
were also separated.
The Phoenix's soul split
into five separate entities
and flew off in all directions.
(zapping)
♪
It fused with
five mystery disks.
What, the Phoenix's soul split?
And if it bonded
with five mystery disks‐‐
Then the Phoenix's
soul is inside.
Five monsters!
So, it wasn't inside
Genki after all!
(gasp)
Into five?
Hmm?
One, two, three...
...four, five!
(joyful cheering)
Ha, ha, ha, just a coincidence.
No kidding,
but it'd sure save us
a heck of a lot of searching
if we had the Phoenix's soul
right here inside of us!
This is no coincidence.
Pardon me?
The magic stone led Holly
to each of you.
Then it guided you to Falcon,
myself, and many others.
The magic stone was
giving you experience,
so that you would develop
into the Phoenix.
Then the five of us
are the Phoenix.
The Phoenix's soul
is inside us?
Yes.
(all gasping)
(roaring)
(zapping)
♪
Huh?
Up there, the whole
mountaintop's on fire!
(fire whooshing)
♪
(zapping)
It looks like Moo's
attacking Mt. Kairus!
What's the point of that?
He's going to use the
magma under Mt. Kairus
to split the earth open
so that he can destroy
every living being
on the planet.
Not if we can help it!
Well, what can we do?
The final gate and
the magic stone are gone.
You have your courage.
The magic stone's
energy never waned,
even in the most
difficult of times.
It is the energy of courage.
Courage?
The magic stone was
manmade, so it wasn't able
to revive the Phoenix.
What the Phoenix needs
to be resurrected
is pure courage,
the kind of courage
that comes from experience.
And Genki, you are
crucial in all this.
Because it is your
boundless courage
and your love for
the monsters here
that will ignite their courage.
It will?
Yes, that's precisely why
Mocchi passed through
the time portal
and brought you here.
That's why Mocchi came
out of Genki's CD Rom!
Exactly!
(zapping)
♪
(bouncing)
(popping)
♪
(blinking)
Chi!
Now Genki, you must
summon up their courage
and unite them as one.
♪
(explosion)
(rocks crumbling)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock and claim it
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Phoenix soars
like Master Moo ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Everybody wants them,
how 'bout you? ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Moo is a giant
baddest of the bad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Nagas fight form,
to resist would be mad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ 400 monsters,
all shapes and sizes ♪
♪ You can't predict them,
they're full of surprises ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(roaring)
Let's do it, Genki!
Huh?
Not many other options.
Let's fuse together
with the Phoenix!
Stop Moo.
Mocchi try hard, Chi!
‐But‐‐
‐Wait, if everyone fuses‐‐
It'll be just like when
Big Blue and I fused.
Their bodies and
their consciousness.
‐They'll disappear.
‐I can't do that to you!
Huh?
Chi?
I couldn't stand it
if I couldn't see you.
Genki...
Hmm.
Genki, remember what you said?
You said that you were
gonna destroy Moo
and turn the world into
a peaceful place again.
Huh?
I came all this way
because I believed
in what you said.
Tiger?
Golem feel same, your
determination gave Golem hope.
You know, you were the best
motivation ever, Genki.
You guys, really?
So even if it means
that we disappear‐‐
Hold on!
I want to be the one to say it.
We'll have no regrets
if we can become the Phoenix.
Suezo!
Mocchi too!
Mocchi?
(grumbling)
(all sighing)
You guys...
Come on, let's go!
(cheering)
Hmm.
♪
Okay, let's do it!
To our new journey!
Out with a bang!
Have no fears, Chi!
Hmm.
(whooshing)
♪
(grunting)
(zapping)
♪
(loud zap)
Huh?
♪
(whoosh)
(roar)
We're not through yet!
Soldiers, I'm counting
on all of you!
Sir!
We're with you 'til the end!
‐I'm going, too.
‐Thank you.
Move out!
(whooshing)
♪
(screeching)
(roar)
(zap)
Here we go, Big Blue.
Big bang!
(boom)
(zap)
(oscillating metallic tone)
♪
Give me your courage, everyone!
Now!
(zapping)
♪
(grunting)
(whoosh)
♪
Take this, it's our hope,
and it's our tears!
This is our courage!
(boom)
♪
(loud whooshing)
Genki!
♪
See ya.
Uh, Tiger?
Be seeing ya, kid.
Huh, Suezo!
‐Don't be sad.
‐We'll be right here.
Golem, Hare!
You guys!
‐Genki!
‐Huh?
I'm glad I met you, Genki.
Mocchi?
No, Mocchi, don't go!
I love you, Genki.
Chi.
(whooshing)
Oh.
(metallic oscillating tone)
♪
(ice cracking)
(gasp)
♪
(crash)
(screeching)
♪
(gasp)
(grunting)
♪
(zap)
(screech)
(boom)
♪
(screech)
(zap)
(boom)
♪
(roar)
Phoenix!
Use all the courage
that we have given you!
(zap)
(boom)
♪
(screech)
(fire whooshing)
♪
(boom)
(roaring)
(screeching)
(zapping)
♪
Oh.
What are you doing to me?
♪
Now I understand.
You and I are destined
to eternal battle
for as long as we live!
In that case,
I cannot let you exist!
Nor myself!
(grunting)
♪
(whooshing)
(twinkling sound)
♪
(zapping)
(wings fluttering)
Father, my friends!
And Tiger, and Hare.
Golem, and Suezo.
Mocchi.
(zapping)
♪
(twinkling sound)
(zapping)
♪
(ethereal whooshing)
The mystery disks
are turning back.
And look at the baddies' crests!
(high pitched humming)
♪
(yelling)
Genki's falling!
Holly!
(all yelling "Genki")
(whooshing increases in pitch)
♪
Huh?
(grunting)
I'm back in my world now.
♪
Or could I have been
dreaming this whole thing?
Huh?
No, I'm sure it had to be real.
I did it, I actually did it!
I actually did it all!
♪
I guess it's time for home.
(grunting)
(rain rushing)
♪
(grunting)
(panting, coughing)
♪
No use, I feel so empty inside.
Who am I trying to kid,
I can't do anything
without my friends,
not a thing!
♪
And they all said that I
was the most courageous kid
that they'd ever met.
(sobbing)
♪
Genki.
(gasp)
♪
Huh?
Holly?
What's the matter,
that's not like you,
getting all depressed.
He's right.
Crying doesn't suit you, kid.
Huh?
That's right, be happy
like your name.
Full of energy,
with lots of courage.
Don't give up, Genki!
Thank you, Mocchi.
You guys, I miss you so much.
We'll meet again.
Just think of us
whenever the wind blows.
We'll always be nearby.
Can meet anytime.
We'll be waiting for ya.
Our hearts always as one.
♪
(whoosh)
(zapping)
♪
(twinkling sound)
(laughing)
♪
Whoa!
(laughing)
Yeah!
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪