♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(mystical ringing)
Come on!
Give me some concentration room.
Okay, guys?
Ha‐ha, very funny.
♪
The mystery disk
closest to us is...
♪
...in this direction!
Looks just like
the Wild West.
You mean a cowboy movie?
Yup, I reckon I do, partner.
Uh, partner?
Yippee ki‐Chi!
You've had too much sun.
(Genki grunts)
Listen up...
you pilgrims have got
a mighty long ways to go,
but I aim to get you there,
so saddle them up
and let's move 'em out.
Definitely sun stroke.
Chi!
♪
What's the matter?
I thought I saw something.
Mm‐hmm.
Well, we didn't see anything.
Whatever.
Genki, let's go.
Chi!
♪
(growling)
There's five of them in all.
They spend their
time playing games.
This is nothing
we can't handle.
I'll come too.
It'll pass the time.
♪
What's that?
(growling)
(group whimpers)
♪
N‐nice doggies.
Chi.
(growling)
This doesn't look good.
Maybe they're okay?
Looks like
the Wild Bunch.
‐Wild Bunch?
‐Chi?
They're monsters who
escaped from their masters
and became wild.
Wrong, human.
We became free.
♪
(wind swirling)
We are now our
own masters,
free from orders,
free from masters,
free like the wind.
You're Tiger of the Wind.
Oh, boy, this gets
worse and worse.
Tiger of the Wind, huh?
Well, listen,
I'm Genki of the Air,
and you don't scare me at all.
Mind your matters, Genki.
You've been warned.
We are on a mission here,
and you're not
going to stop us.
Kiss the sky, Mocchi!
Mocchi!
(grunts)
You don't understand, Genki.
He's Tiger of the Wind.
I think we should
surrender now
or we'll be lost in
a tornado of destruction.
So, I see even small
children have heard of me now.
Well, Mr. Monster of the Wind,
we've come a long way,
and we're not going to give up.
We've got no
quarrel with you
unless you stand in our way.
Chi!
‐Genki.
‐Oh, great.
Foolish boy.
You don't know
when to stop.
Come on.
‐I'm there!
‐Chi!
(growls)
(wind surges)
♪
Genki!
It's not smart to go
against the Tigers of the Wind.
I went easy on them,
the wind could've
been much worse.
(growling)
I don't see it here.
Oh, well, we don't...
have much of anything.
Mm‐hmm.
Huh?
Are you sure?
There's nothing more?
‐Mm‐mm.
‐Open up.
♪
Lift up your tongue.
Stick out your tongue.
♪
Under again.
Now out again.
♪
Under again.
Now, show me under!
♪
Hey, that's not fair!
This is what we wanted.
Nice try.
Huh?
(mystical ringing)
Why is the magic
stone glowing?
Please return the stone to me.
Well, it's a matter of face.
You see, we can't
just walk away
and take nothing.
Sure you can!
(growls)
♪
One more time.
And this time
it's personal.
♪
Genki, Mocchi, please don't!
Listen up, punk,
and listen up good.
Tiger, please let him go.
Why don't you just
get on with it?
I'm not afraid of you.
Well, maybe you should be.
You're a very brave and
very foolish little human.
You rush in head first
not bothering to even
think of the consequences.
You don't understand that
sometimes in this world
bravery isn't enough.
Life can be hard,
little human,
hard and unfair,
and you must know this.
Don't be reckless.
You're young, brave,
and you have a good heart,
but in this world,
that isn't enough.
I know that better
than anyone.
Let's go!
♪
Genki?
I, uh, I must've had
a piece of sand in my eye.
(Suezo nervously chuckles)
Now, let's find Mocchi
and get out of here.
He's probably off
sleeping somewhere.
♪
I can't see anything.
I see them!
Oh, it's a whole
bunch of them.
Where are they headed?
♪
Must be their home base.
Hey, who's that?
One of the baddies.
Huh?
What's this?
♪
(shouts)
Super torpedo!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Gali is one of
Moo's Big Bad Four ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Big Blue a monster
with power and more ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Pixie's a mystery,
who's side is she on? ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ She's one of Moo's Four,
but for how long? ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Flips and tornado,
without 'em, within ♪
♪ 400 monsters,
someone will win ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Listen up!
You tigers should
realize who you're
dealing with here.
Super torpedoes
won't harm that net.
You're working for
Moo, aren't you?
Never mind who we work for.
I'll ask the
questions around here.
Where is the mystery disk?
We have no mystery disk.
Have you so soon
forgotten who it is
you're dealing with?
Whatever happens to you,
good or bad, is up to me.
(growling)
We mean no disrespect to Moo,
but I'm telling you
that there is no
mystery disk here.
You better leave.
Aren't you forgetting something?
♪
All right then, puh‐lease.
Very nice.
But I don't think so.
(roar)
Tigers run!
(grunts)
I said run!
♪
(smug chuckling)
(shouts)
♪
(growls)
Well, well, well,
look what I just found.
Huh?
Oh, have you forgotten, Tiger.
Tears are not enough.
Dangerous practice
to mock what you
cannot know, Captain.
Perhaps you have forgotten why
I am called Tiger of the Wind.
Ooh, I'm so scared.
Say goodnight, Gracie.
(snaps, grunts)
Write if you get work!
(malicious laugh)
♪
What's this?
I've never seen it before.
‐Oh.
‐I don't like this.
Chi!
Huh?
Oh, no.
It's that Tiger guy.
‐Oh.
‐Chi.
♪
(heavy breathing)
Huh?
Where am I?
(fire crackling)
♪
Hold on, you have
to take it easy.
Hey!
♪
If you're looking for
the magic stone, Genki,
the Dinos took it.
There, now you can
leave me to my fate.
Just be still.
It's time to change
your bandages, okay?
Here...
I have some medicine.
(grunts)
(Suezo groans)
That wasn't nice!
I don't accept
help from humans.
Humans?!
My name is Genki.
Remember when you gave me
that speech about being
reckless a while ago?
Well, Tiger,
it's your turn to listen.
Please allow us
to be your friends.
(Tiger growls)
Maybe we can help each other.
Maybe we aren't who
you think we are.
There, that should do it, okay?
Thank you, human.
Thank you, Genki.
♪
(snoring)
There you go.
♪
Why are you journeying?
Good, you're awake.
Answer me.
This is not your world.
These are not your battles.
If we can revive the Phoenix
from the mystery disk,
all of the bad monsters
will become good monsters,
even Moo.
So, you plan to
battle Moo, do you?
Uh‐huh.
Once I was as
reckless as you, Genki.
Huh?
Once I had a younger brother.
(water running)
We did everything together.
Had every sort
of adventure,
always together.
Life was hard.
We did what was
needed to survive.
(growling)
♪
Time passed,
and many miles passed.
We joined with others,
all of us cast out by humans.
Together we became
a family until...
Moo.
(growling)
♪
And your brother?
Gone forever.
It's not fair.
♪
Let's get going!
Mocchi!
Hey, Tiger,
join up with us.
What do you say?
♪
Help us, Tiger.
It's your chance
to battle Moo.
There are some fights
you cannot win.
My friends,
do not confront Moo.
It will go badly for you.
♪
Listen to him,
it's like he's
completely given up.
His reasons are his own.
We must respect them.
Chi.
Now, we must find
the baddies who still
have the magic stone.
But where do we start?
(Suezo laughs)
Guess what?
I learned an
interesting new trick.
Hmm?
Come on, we're waiting.
Golem!
Ready!
Aim!
Fire!
♪
They went that‐a‐way!
(bang)
Thanks for the catch!
Sorry.
Never mind.
Ha‐ha.
Great trick, guys.
Hah.
And now that we
know where they're going,
we can recover
Holly's magic stone!
(rattling)
♪
This is your special
skill testing question.
I need a mystery disk!
Anybody?
Mocchi, Golem.
Chi!
♪
What?
See you later alligator.
(growls)
Get them!
♪
Catch!
Got it.
Meet you at the edge
of the village!
You bet!
Oh!
♪
Yoo‐hoo!
Bye‐bye.
♪
Aah!
Uh‐oh.
(man shouts)
Alley‐oop!
♪
Hah, better luck next time.
(Mocchi and Genki shout)
♪
How nice of you
to drop in, kid.
(grunts, groans)
♪
I'll take you all
on at once, come on.
(roars)
(wind surges)
♪
What's this?
Another piece of
unfinished business for me?
You've had your way around
here long enough, Dino.
The party is over.
For you!
(roaring)
♪
(straining)
(Dinos whimpering)
♪
Are you okay?
Uh‐huh, thanks
to our friend Tiger.
Chi!
(Tiger groans)
Huh?
Tiger!
♪
You came back
to save us.
Even if it is reckless,
a tiger's gotta do
what a tiger's gotta do.
♪
Tiger, please Tiger.
You've got to get better.
You've got to!
Don't worry, I'll
stick with you, Genki.
♪
Mocchi!
Six is such
a nice, round number.
(mystical ringing)
♪
I wonder...
is the magic stone
leading us to mystery disks
or to each other?
♪
(wind blows)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪