♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Master Moo, the boy,
Genki, and his group
have entered the forest!
But Gali has ordered
the Dokoos to pursue 'em.
I feel it.
Sir?
The voice,
my voice, calling me.
We're getting closer.
♪
Okay!
All I see is jungle
and more jungle.
♪
So, I suppose the map
was right, huh?
Looks to me like
we got a lot more walking
to do before we
can get outta here.
Incoming!
(groans)
The Mystery Disk awaits us;
we must continue.
Right, Golem!
The Mystery Disk and the Phoenix
are waiting somewhere ahead!
Mocchi, Mocchi!
Hey, hang on a minute!
I have the beginnings
of very good plan here, Genki.
You do, Hare?
A river!
What we need is a river!
Huh?
Yes, sir!
Then, we build a raft,
float downstream,
and get outta this
jungle in no time!
That sounds great!
Hey, that's not
a bad idea, Hare‐‐
(laughing)
‐‐compared to most
of your suggestions.
On a river?
Don't worry, Golem,
we'll all make sure
you don't fall in.
And if you do fall in, Golem,
we'll pull you outta there
really quickly.
Really quickly!
Okay.
That a boy, Golem!
Now, let's get outta here!
(all cheering)
Hey, guys!
Guys?
Oh, guys?
A little help here?
I'm sorry, Suezo.
We're just excited;
we didn't mean to walk away.
Yeah, come on,
just laugh it off.
We've got a great plan!
(laughing)
Not funny!
It seems to me
like you've all
been ignoring me lately.
Well, you do have a basic defect
that naturally excludes you
from some of our activities.
A "basic defect"?
Suezo, you have
no specialty attack!
What?
Yes, just think back,
think back to all the battles
we've been in and where
you were at the time.
(all grunting)
Lightning attack!
(zap, grunting)
♪
(laughing)
Come on, I can fight!
I fight just like anyone else!
Yeah, but, here's
the thing, Suezo;
you don't really have
a specialty attack
of your own.
"Specialty attack"?
Maybe that's why sometimes
we don't really notice you.
I attack!
Yeah, come on,
I'm sure we've seen
lots of Suezo's attack modes.
Name two.
Absolutely!
There's, um‐‐
Lots of 'em!
You've got your Slobbery Kiss
and then you've got
your Staggering Slap
and your Spin Attack.
Perfectly fine techniques.
Second‐rate.
They're half‐baked.
Excuse me, did I hear
you say "half‐baked"?
Got that right.
Don't, Suezo, Tiger!
Come on!
(growls)
Huh?
You give up?
You want a‐‐
♪
That wasn't fair!
(growling)
More of Moo's
baddies, I presume?
Dokoo, the mighty Gali
has sent us to deal with you!
Dokoo!
(grunting)
They're mine, all mine!
♪
All right!
(grunting)
♪
Watch it!
Dokoo!
(grunts)
(screams)
♪
(all growling)
Let's get out of here!
(all whimpering)
Now that is what
I call teamwork, right?
Yeah, that was excellent!
(sighs)
Hey, look down there, a river!
Yahoo, race ya!
(laughter)
Hey, Suezo, Hare found a river!
I can't believe I couldn't
take care of those Dokoos.
You guys were right,
I'm nothing but extra baggage.
Ow!
(grunting)
Oh, no, Suezo!
Are you all right?
Does it matter?
I'm useless anyway.
(yelps)
Think good thoughts, Suezo.
Hmm.
Just leave me alone!
Sure, if that's what you want.
See ya.
Write if you get work.
Hey, I didn't mean
completely alone!
Thinking, Suezo!
Thinking?
It's like Golem said, you've
got to think the thoughts;
that can be your
attack specialty.
Mocchi!
You mean thinking
can be an attack mode?
Yeah!
Okay.
Hmm!
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Use telepathy
to deflect the fruit.
All right, take your best shot.
Mm‐hmm!
And think fast!
♪
(grunts)
(yelping)
'chi!
No, Mocchi!
'chi?
Leave Suezo alone!
He has to learn
how to do it himself.
♪
He's right, Mocchi.
I'm in training.
Give it all you've got, Genki!
Now, think about it!
Mind over matter, Suezo!
Suezo just doesn't
have the discipline.
(grunts)
Again!
(grunting)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, you claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Phoenix soars
like Master Moo ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Everybody wants 'em,
how about you ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Moo is the giant
baddest of bad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Nagas fight form,
to resist would be mad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ 400 monsters,
all shapes and sizes,
♪ You can't predict them,
they're full of surprises ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(grunting)
Okay, now try to send Mocchi
a telepathic message, Suezo.
Yeah!
Stand by, Mocchi, okay?
Standing by!
Are you ready?
Okay!
♪
Mocchi, are you
receiving his message yet?
Uh‐uh‐uh.
Come on, now,
concentrate hard!
♪
(grunting)
Well, Mocchi?
Uh‐uh.
Keep trying!
(grunting)
'chi!
♪
'chi.
Mocchi?
Suezo, come on!
Huh?
(groaning)
Suezo?
♪
No, Tiger!
I'm telling you
that's not right;
you're pulling it too tight!
(groans)
(growls)
I'm doing fine!
I told you!
It's your design that's wrong!
I don't get it.
Boy, Suezo just doesn't seem
to know how
to concentrate at all.
It figures.
Hmm?
I don't know why,
but he was never any good
at that stuff,
even when he was little.
He always made the excuse
that he preferred to feel
his opponent getting hit,
but I'm not too sure.
I just don't get it.
Does it really matter?
♪
After all, Genki,
this journey we're on
isn't really about
fighting baddies, is it?
You know, Holly, you're right!
It's about finding the Phoenix
and turning all the baddies
into goodies.
♪
Mm‐mmm.
'chi?
Suezo!
Hey!
Hmm?
How are ya?
Okay?
♪
I'm hungry.
That's good because I just
finished cooking dinner.
Let's eat up.
♪
(laughter)
Good‐looking raft, guys!
Way to go!
Boy, we were up all night,
but I guess it was worth it.
(laughs)
Cool.
'kay, let's go!
(all cheering)
♪
Golem!
Don't like water,
have a good voyage!
We aren't leaving you, Golem.
We're a team, remember?
(grunting)
Better hang on, everyone!
(nervous tittering)
(yelping)
♪
Help!
Golem, hang on!
Hold on, Golem,
I'm coming for ya!
(yelping)
(grunting)
♪
Hang on, Golem,
I'll help you up.
(grunting)
♪ Row, row, row your boat
gently down the stream ♪
♪ Merrily, merrily,
merrily, merrily,
life is but a dream ♪
(laughter)
Boy, that was
a great idea I had.
At this rate, we'll be
out of the jungle in no time!
Yeah.
♪
Aw, Suezo, come on, cheer up!
Okay, I'm cheerful!
Why wouldn't I be?
I mean, come on!
(laughs forcefully)
(groans)
♪
Having a specialty
attack mode isn't everything.
You know that.
Maybe I know that,
but I don't believe it.
I just feel like a real loser.
Aw, Suezo, you're not a loser.
I wish it was
just you and me again.
The new guys all have
great specialty attacks.
I could never
measure up to that.
Maybe...
but none of us
would have made it
this far on our own, Suezo.
We're a team.
Everybody here contributes
whatever they can;
as long as you do
your best, it's okay.
No one really expects
any more than that
from you, Suezo.
Really?
And you know what else?
Sometimes you have to
let go before you can have
the thing you want.
Sorry, I've been a drag.
It's okay, no big deal.
Attention, Suezo is back!
No more Mr. Gloom!
It's good to have
you back, Suezo.
Huh, Mocchi needs a rest.
(laughs)
Nothing like a little nap.
Huh?
What is that?
♪
Gee, I haven't got a clue!
Huh?
♪
Dokoos!
Dokoo!
♪
Now what?
I don't believe it!
They're taking us off‐course!
♪
Huh?
Hare, what do you
think they're up to?
Given the velocity angle
I'm sure the probability's good.
Good for what, Hare?
Huh, what is that?
Something's wrong!
Waterfall.
(yelping)
♪
My probability projections
were certainly right.
Please don't mind if I
don't congratulate you!
(grunting)
Everyone, paddle upstream!
It's pulling us back!
No use, the current's
too strong for us!
Well, quit your useless
yammering and do something
about it, Hare!
Come on, keep at it!
(grunting)
Yes, we're gaining!
♪
No!
We're losing it!
♪
Look out!
(grunting)
Mocchi!
♪
This is it, it's been
nice knowing you all!
Come on, guys, don't give up!
It ain't over till it's over!
♪
Not when you can
give 100 percent!
No point in giving
up until we...
what on Earth is that?
(screaming hysterically)
♪
(sighing)
Gotta do something.
Concentrate, concentrate!
Teleport!
♪
Well, that would
appear to be that.
Time to report back
to Master Gali.
(laughing)
Huh, whoa!
(screaming)
♪
Well, that seemed to defy
the laws of logic, eh?
Didn't we just go over
a waterfall, guys?
Teleported.
Suezo.
(screaming)
Some things never change.
You rule!
(yelps)
What is going on here?
Let's rip it up!
Let's do it!
(grunting)
♪
Dokoo!
Mocchi!
Teleport!
(grunting)
Mocchi.
Tiger!
Just leave it to me.
♪
(zapping)
(grunts)
Hey, Dokoo, say hi to Gali!
Dokoo retreat!
Let's go!
(yelping)
We did it!
I got myself a special attack!
That was great, Suezo!
You saved us;
thank you, Suezo.
I sure did, didn't I?
And no one else
has a specialty attack
like that, Suezo.
It's unbelievable.
Well, if you've got it,
you've got it and if
you don't, you don't.
Show us one more time,
one more time!
Yeah, Suezo, one more
time for the Gipper,
come on, old buddy.
Well, I'm gonna have
to charge for this, you know?
But, you're my friends,
so the first one'll be
a freebie on me.
And now, watch this.
Teleport in three, two, one‐‐
Huh?
♪
Hmm?
Well, I am still
a little new at this,
'cause, after all‐‐
This time, for sure!
(grunts)
Teleport, teleport,
come on, teleport.
Hang on, one more time.
Teleport, teleport!
(grumbling)
Teleport!
I'm getting hungry.
Hey, wait‐wait!
Wait, I can do this!
Mocchi.
Hey, wait, I really can.
Really.
♪
(wind howling)
What, you failed?
Yes, we beg your forgiveness.
They are insects!
I will stomp
them out personally,
once I am joined
with my ancient self.
(laughs maniacally)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪