♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(wind howling)
♪
(growling)
Did that problem with Master
Moo's body get fixed yet?
I don't know, but there isn't
much more we can do to help.
‐Commence.
‐Right away, Master.
♪
(yelling)
Are you all right, Master?
Continue.
Of course, Master.
♪
(roaring)
Master!
‐Stop the engines!
‐Right away.
♪
Master!
The laser beam's ready, Master.
‐Try it.
‐Yes, sir.
(screaming)
♪
It seems you can't withstand
any kind of light yet.
All this power ruined by
a sensitivity to light!
‐What shall I do, Master?
‐Call Durahan.
Ah, you mean the one
who controls the East?
The evil general called Durahan?
Yes, now stop wasting time,
and summon him!
'Kay, come on you guys!
Let's move out!
‐Yeah!
‐Yay!
‐Let's go!
‐Genki.
‐This is where we part.
‐What, how come?
Because of what I saw
in Moo the other day.
Once he merges perfectly
with his new body,
we'll never be
able to defeat him.
But that's the whole
point of the Phoenix.
‐Must revive it.
‐I'll leave that in your hands.
Big Blue and I are
going to round up others
to help us fight Moo.
We'll meet up again once
you have the Phoenix,
and then we'll defeat Moo.
Pixie?
Thank you both.
I can't tell you what a great
help you've been to us.
Hare's right, thanks a lot.
Golem miss you.
Mocchi, Mocchi!
Tiger, aren't you
even gonna say thanks?
‐Gonna miss Pixie?
‐No!
Let's promise.
We'll meet again for sure.
‐It's a deal.
‐We promise.
‐Yeah!
‐'chi!
Pixie, don't forget our promise!
Take care!
♪
Well, we're all alone
again now, aren't we?
Maybe for now, but soon
there'll be new people to meet.
‐'chi!
‐'Kay, let's get rollin' gang!
(indistinct remarks)
♪
Perhaps you've forgotten
that I feed off of grudges.
The bigger the grudge,
the more evil I become,
and the more evil I become,
the bigger the grudges
I need to devour.
‐What's wrong?
‐Oh, nothing really.
You seem kinda down, Holly.
Just a little tired, that's all.
Well, that shouldn't
be any big surprise.
Yeah, for starters,
we defeated Naga.
‐And Moo got his super body.
‐And that's just the beginning.
Yeah, like how we found
out that Moo's true identity
is actually Holly's father.
Guys, I'm sorry.
I thought Father might become
normal again if we found
the Phoenix before Moo
merged with his super body.
Holly?
'chi?
I shouldn't feel
sorry for myself.
It's good to talk to
your friends, Holly.
I mean, hey, that's
what we're here for.
(grunting)
♪
I got the feeling we're
forgettin' something!
‐Huh?
‐Uhhh.
♪
‐What is it?
‐I remembered.
Today is actually
Holly's birthday.
Hey, that's perfect timing!
‐'chi?
‐What do you mean?
Uh, don't worry about it,
could you all come here?
Oh, except for you, Holly.
Okay, what?
I've just learned that
today is Holly's birthday.
So what do you say we have
a birthday party, guys?
That'd cheer her up,
don't you think?
‐That's a good idea, Hare.
‐But here's the thing.
We can't let her
find out about it.
‐Mhm.
‐Good idea, considering.
‐Would you lay off?
‐Is everybody in?
‐Mocchi, 'chi!
‐What's up?
Hey, Holly, we were
just talking about
calling it quits for the day.
‐What do you think?
‐That's fine by me.
Why don't you just
sit back and rest
while we get dinner ready, okay?
You're making
dinner on your own?
'chi, Holly's‐‐
We, uh, thought that we would
give you a break
from, uh, cooking.
‐Nice.
‐Holly need break.
‐He's right.
‐'chi!
♪
Here's a nice place
for you to relax.
Thanks, Suezo.
See ya!
Okay, let's figure out who's
gonna get which ingredients.
‐So you're in charge?
‐Absolutely.
This is kind of
nice for a change.
That just about does it then.
Tiger, you're a master when
it comes to digging holes,
‐so you get the potatoes.
‐Hm.
Golem, could you
get the peaches?
‐No problem.
‐Mocchi, you get the fish
‐for our entree.
‐Mocchi!
Suezo, you're in
charge of dessert.
And Genki, you get the mangos.
‐'Kay.
‐Sure.
And that'll take care of dinner.
‐What are you bringing, Hare?
‐I'm gonna be very busy
getting Holly's present ready.
I'll believe it when I see it.
‐What's that?
‐You heard!
Just wait till
you see my present.
‐You'll be impressed.
‐Whatever.
'Kay, we'll meet back at the
river bank before nightfall.
Right, good luck everyone!
‐'chi!
‐Move out!
All right, time to work.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Here come the Arrowheads,
fighting with claws ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Not like Eared Mew
who only has paws ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Tainted Cat Brothers
are quick and they're bad ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ They're whirlwind fast,
so don't get 'em mad ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ So many monsters,
so little time ♪
♪ Check 'em all out, they're
still in their prime ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(groaning)
It's a big one, 'chi!
Oh, 'chi.
♪
(grunting)
'chi, my only
fishing line, 'chi.
(water splashing)
Fish, 'chi!
♪
(water gurgling)
Wait, come back, fishies!
♪
(screaming)
(panting)
♪
'chi, I caught 'em.
Heavy fish, 'chi.
♪
Over there.
These must be huge.
♪
Torpedo attack!
I'll get ya!
♪
(crashing)
Yeah!
I rule!
Now I gotta get
'em home somehow.
(grunting)
♪
Golem not see any peaches.
(bird chirping)
Small bird, don't be scared.
Your wing is hurt?
Golem take you to your nest.
♪
You safe now.
Ha, okay.
Huh?
Peaches!
♪
Mangos, mangoes, where
am I gonna find mangos?
(screaming)
Yow, yow, hey!
‐What is this?
‐Oh, Suezo.
What do you mean
by stepping on me?
Aren't you supposed to
be out finding mangos?
Still lookin'.
(laughing)
Sure, I knew you wouldn't find‐‐
Well, what about you?
Found your dessert yet?
‐You've got some nerve.
‐Throw me a bone!
Who do you think
you're talking to?
‐An ultra dense monster.
‐Thank you.
Thank‐‐hey, what'd you call me?
Bet I can find my
stuff before you!
Sure, you're on, Mr. Big Kahuna!
♪
Now, where can I
find my dessert?
There's gotta be some
around here somewhere‐‐
Weee!
How lucky can a guy get?
♪
Mangos, mangos, come
out wherever you are!
(shouting)
♪
Fruits for dessert.
(chuckling)
♪
You got my mangos!
You got my dessert!
(laughing)
Nothing like good friends.
Except good desserts.
Check it out, what
a feast this'll be!
'chi!
Hey guys, where's Hare?
Don't worry, he'll come.
Yeah, let's get cookin'.
♪
(explosion)
(gasping)
(screaming)
‐Hare!
‐'chi!
Did someone attack you, Hare?
(chuckling)
Don't mind me, guys.
Bye!
‐Huh?
‐What's with him?
This is all the fire
starter and charcoal
I have left for tonight.
I'm getting kinda
worried about Hare.
He said that he was working
on the present, right?
You guys, why don't we
make our own present?
‐Present.
‐'chi.
♪
(humming)
I'm home.
‐Hi, Daddy!
‐Hi, honey.
Sorry I'm so late tonight.
‐What do you have there, Daddy?
‐This?
Why it's a present for you.
♪
Hm, looks a little too big.
No, it's perfect
'cause I'm growing up!
Thanks, Daddy!
(laughing)
♪
Thanks, Daddy.
Where am I?
Where is everyone?
♪
Where are you, Daddy?
Holly!
♪
‐Holly!
‐We're all done.
Grub's up, bub!
♪
Right this way.
There, you can take
off the blindfold.
♪
What do you think?
Not bad for a bunch
of monsters, huh?
Oh, wow!
‐Ta‐da!
♪
(in unison)
Yay, happy birthday, Holly!
♪
You guys remembered,
even a cake!
‐So how old are you, Holly?
‐Me?
Turning 15.
‐Twelve, thirteen.
‐What's that you're doing?
These will be our candles, done.
Back where I come from, we put
the number of the person's age
in candles on the birthday cake.
If you blow out all the
candles in one breath,
your wish will come true.
Time to make your birthday wish!
♪
(cheering)
Holly's birthday wish come true.
Holly, flowers, 'chi!
‐Thank you!
‐'chi!
‐Mocchi,
‐Flying Kissy!
♪
(gagging)
'Kay, I think it's
time for the feast.
(laughing)
♪
Holly!
I caught that fish,
so try some, 'chi!
Here you are, Holly!
‐Thank you.
‐We made this too.
You gotta try
some of this stuff.
‐'chi!
‐Thanks, you guys.
Here.
Holly try a peach?
'Kay, thanks.
Mmmm.
I peeled these fruits
for you all by myself.
And I found the
potato for the cake.
Thanks, Tiger.
Oh look, the brave Tiger's
proud of his cakey‐poo.
(growling)
No fighting, 'chi.
‐The present!
‐What present?
♪
What's this?
One, two...
♪ Today is‐‐
your day, Holly ♪
♪ Your birthday today ♪
♪ Holly ♪
♪ Happy birthday ♪
(in unison)
♪ Holly ♪
♪ We love you so ♪
Yeah!
(chuckling)
‐Happy birthday!
Oh, guys, thank you.
Da‐da‐da‐da!
And now, the star attraction.
Holly, this is
my special present,
so sit back, and enjoy!
♪
‐Huh?
‐'chi?
Your present is holes?
But they're no ordinary holes.
Voila.
(whistling noise)
♪
Wow.
‐Whoa.
♪
(mixed cheering)
Not too shabby, Hare.
Thank you, this is wonderful.
It's great.
You're the best.
♪
‐Don't be sad, be happy.
‐'chi!
Holly's smile is pretty.
Ain't it true.
♪
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I'm
gonna light one too!
Whoa!
(screaming)
♪
‐Suezo!
Happy birthday, Holly!
Lookin' good, Suezo!
♪
Beautiful.
‐Holly, it's not too late.
‐Huh?
You made a wish about
your father, right?
Uh, yeah, I did.
He'll return to normal
once we revive the Phoenix,
so don't give up, Holly.
♪
Isn't General Durahan here yet?
(engine whirring)
♪
At last, there he is!
Evil General Durahan.
♪
(evil laughter)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪