♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Okay!
Mocchi!
Genki!
Where are you going?
To find the‐‐ whoa!
Well, what do you think?
The Mystery Disk, of course.
Mocchi.
Clumsy kid!
Hey, I know, the magic
stone will tell us.
Great idea!
Mystery Disk, show us.
♪
Cool, let's see!
Watch where you're going!
Can't you see she's trying
to work a little magic here?
But, we want to find
the disk, too, Suezo!
Mocchi.
You have no idea
what that disk is.
Holly's stone is a relic
from the dawn of time.
Its power is unimaginable.
♪
The Phoenix has shown the way.
Holly, let me give it a try!
Magic Stone, which way
to the mystery disk?
Help us out, here!
♪
Oh Genki, it's not going to
work for you right off the bat.
I guess it doesn't
like me very much.
♪
(mumbling)
(laughing)
I fooled you, let's go!
I'm hungry, feed me!
Mocchi, we got stuff
to do, you know!
(crying)
♪
I just hate that.
Don't cry, Mocchi, we'll go
into town and get you something.
Mocchi!
She's turning him into a softie.
♪
(screaming)
Mocchi.
Suezo, any water?
Look like a camel?
Mocchi wants to be carried.
Uh, uh.
You're walking
like everybody else.
Mocchi.
Chi?
Don't look at me.
Okay, Mocchi.
Chi!
Holly, you spoil
him way too much!
Oh calm down, Genki,
he's just a little baby.
Mocchi is my monster, thank you.
I'll decide how to raise him.
Which part don't you understand?
He's a little baby,
and he's hungry.
So we're going to town.
Is that so?
And while we're at it, we're
getting you some shoes, Genki.
Got a problem with that?
Don't need 'em.
♪
Wow!
Easy now, easy now.
Would you look at
all these monsters?
Oh wow, this is so cool!
♪
Hey look, I'm a...
Food Monster!
Mocchi, Mocchi, Mocchi!
Are you happy, Mocchi?
Here!
So what is it?
It's an ancient calculator.
Now, let's see, the stew,
that's about five gold...
The fishy thing,
another seven...
The bread, the rice,
turnips, you owe us 20 gold.
Right, don't forget
what I owe you.
After all, I am going
after Moo with you.
♪
Did you say you
were going after Moo?
I am Genki, and I have come
to your rescue, my friends.
I'm going to show that
Moo what's what, yeah!
I'm out of here!
♪
What's going on?
(mumbling)
Everyone is frightened
of Moo, Genki.
Yeah? Well, this is one
kid who isn't frightened.
You should be, Moo is not
a game to us, you know?
♪
Not sure when it started.
Moo's and his thugs began to
attack village after village,
stealing crops
and Mystery Disks.
They stole young monsters and
trained them to their evil ways.
Once, several years
ago, a brave king
sent his troops to destroy
Moo, but they never returned.
No one knows where
Moo lives for sure.
What we do know is,
Moo is collecting all
the Mystery Disks.
Come on, there's got to be some
way to defeat this Moo guy!
Yes.
When the Phoenix rises,
everyone he took will come
back over to the good side.
♪
I'm sure Moo will too.
This Phoenix thing,
does it really exist?
Who knows.
It's a legend they
told in my village.
If we are gonna fight
this Moo character,
we won't stand a
chance unless we find
the mystery disk that
the Phoenix is locked in.
Hey, you.
Your dinner time is over.
But we're not
finished eating yet.
That's too bad, but this
restaurant is closed.
Forget it, we're still eating!
Sorry, but you must go, now!
All right, then, we're leaving.
♪
They're going to fight Moo!
They must be nuts.
Don't they know?
Don't even look at them,
it'll just mean trouble.
Oh, man, I guess they've
never seen heroes before.
Hey.
Excuse me, could I
see those blue shoes?
No, no, we're closed up.
Get away from here!
Mocchi!
Hey, I don't sell
to your kind, pal!
Mocchi!
Cowards, does Moo
scare you all that much?
♪
Let's go.
Yeah.
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Visit a Jell,
slippery fool ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Or Captain Jell,
these monsters rule ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Worm from below
explodes with force ♪
♪ Unlock them all ♪
♪ Clays and their
captain have no remorse ♪
♪ Unlock them all ♪
♪ Jump smash and more,
get off the floor ♪
♪ These monsters fight,
unlock them today ♪
♪
What'll we do,
we don't even have
enough camping
gear for everyone.
Mocchi sleep.
Oh no, you're sleeping
on the ground with me!
Mocchi stays!
Come on!
Hello.
What a cute little
monster you are.
Here, let's have a look at you.
Uh, hello there, sir.
I'm Matthew, were you
planning on sleeping outside?
Why don't you all come
and sleep at my place?
What, are you sure?
Why, of course, I just need
a little favor from you first.
♪
This is fun!
So, tell me, Suezo, what
is wrong in this picture?
♪
They went east?
Thank you.
♪
Mocchi!
Cute little fella.
Lily and I are so
pleased to know you.
Welcome.
Mocchi!
And I'm Genki, the Champion!
I'm Holly.
Suezo's the name.
Thanks for having us.
It's not much, but it's home.
You're very kind.
(chattering)
Boy, am I stuffed.
I gained ten pounds.
Mocchi, mocchi.
(laughing)
He is so sweet.
He sure is, having this little
monster around is so relaxing.
Do you two have any
monsters of your own?
No, we've always
dreamed of having one.
Some day.
And now that the
Mystery Disk excavations
are tapering out, and...
He's a bit lonely.
Lily!
Today was such a pleasant day.
It was so much fun
having you all here.
We would really
like to thank you
for helping us out
and everything.
You're so soft, so cuddly.
♪
That way!
Oh, so that little
necklace points you
in the direction of
the Mystery Disk.
Uh‐uh.
And, speaking of the stone.
Mocchi.
Bye bye, chi.
Bye bye.
Matthew.
Oh.
Good bye!
Thank you!
You're welcome back any time!
Genki!
Oh, I, um...
♪
Thank you, and thank you
very much for having us, bye!
Hey, wait up, guys!
That poor boy has no shoes.
(chattering)
Genki, what's wrong?
You look kind of sad.
(laughing)
You're imagining it, sad is for
softies, and I'm one happy dude!
Sure.
♪
We're close!
The mystery disk...
We're almost there.
And guess who's
gonna find it first!
It should be somewhere
around this tree.
One, two.
♪
Nothing here.
How am I supposed
to get out of here?
Mocchi.
Are you sure it's here?
Yes, I can feel its presence.
♪
Oh, great, up to my eyeball
in dirt, and now this.
♪
(screaming)
Holly, are you okay?
I'm okay, just a bit scared.
Mocchi, mocchi!
Chi!
You found it!
And where I thought it would be!
Thank you.
Mocchi!
♪
Mocchi.
I think it's...
best you leave us.
Chi!
I want you to go back
to Matthew's house, okay?
I don't want to!
Mocchi!
What's your problem?
Maybe he doesn't like
being shown up by a baby!
That's not it, Matthew and
Lily are really cool people.
Hey, Mocchi, listen, I
just want you to be safe.
Mocchi.
Mocchi, you gotta
do what I tell you!
No!
I won't, I won't, I won't!
Mocchi, mocchi, I‐‐!
But mocchi!
Come back!
Mocchi!
Oh, don't run away
on a sunny day.
Mocchi!
Hey, Mocchi!
Mocchi, come back!
♪
Mocchi.
(screaming)
♪
So, we meet again.
Kid, did you find
a new mystery disk?
Well, even if I did, I wouldn't
tell you, lizard breath!
Tell me, where is your
little monster friend?
I'm not saying anything!
It's just that I'm
feeling a little hungry.
It's snack time, boy!
Just try it!
He's still just a baby, and I‐‐
He may be just a
monster, but he's...
He's a good friend of mine,
and you're not getting
anywhere near him!
(gasping)
How nice, the little
boy loves the monster.
Take him!
Mocchi!
♪
Sushi?
Mocchi!
Mocchi, Mocchi, Mocchi.
Come back!
Where are they?
Hey, over here!
Look out below!
♪
Mocchi!
(screaming)
♪
Genki!
Mocchi!
Oh, Mocchi, I'm so sorry,
you're my best friend!
Mocchi, Mocchi.
Genki, Genki.
I love happy endings.
Yeah, almost makes me
want to shed a tear.
♪
(crying)
It's Spot Dino!
Mocchi!
Oh, great, crying
babies everywhere.
How about if we go find
another mystery disk?
♪
Matthew, Lily!
We figured we'd find you
here at the monster gate.
Is everything all right?
Oh, sure, and we
brought a gift for Genki.
These boots are old
but they're still good.
And a cloak to keep you warm.
Matthew, Lily!
They're awesome,
thank you so much!
You're welcome.
Look at that, what a
sweet little fellow.
You kids come up with the
sweetest little monsters.
He's so cute.
♪
Matthew, Lily, would you
like to take care of him?
Looks to me like that would
make the spot dino pretty happy.
So, you want him?
Oh, yes, thank you.
It's a dream come true.
♪
He's all yours.
Mocchi, Mocchi, Mocchi, Mocchi.
You're staying with me, Mocchi.
Remember? We're best friends.
Mocchi!
Genki and Mocchi,
friends forever!
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪