♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
♪
Bring it up on the monitor.
(Durahan cackles)
Time for the final battle.
He who possesses
the Magic Stone
will control the world.
My troops will soon be
arriving at the battleship,
and when they do...
(evil chuckle)
...Moo will be finished.
♪
(groaning)
Come on, Mocchi,
you can make it.
This is no time
to start complaining.
Yeah, that's right.
Moo could perfect his new
body just about anytime now.
We must find Phoenix.
Yeah, I know, it's just
the direction that worries me.
But Hare, the Magic Stone
told us to go north.
My point exactly.
First it says east,
then all of a sudden,
it says west.
Then it's south,
and now it's north.
But it's way too dangerous
to keep going north.
‐Well, I'm going.
‐Huh?
If the Magic Stone says north,
then that's where I'm gonna go.
Wait!
♪
Thanks a lot.
But what are you gonna
do if the Magic Stone
changes directions again?
What do you want us to do,
just sit here and wait?
Safer than going north.
At least this way
we stand a chance
to beat Moo before
he perfects his new body.
Ooh, stop fighting, 'chi!
I'll make the decisions!
About what?
About the Magic Stone,
we have to get it back.
It's not that simple.
He's right.
For starters, we don't even
know where the Magic Stone is.
And that's exactly
where I come in.
I want everyone to join hands
and focus their energy on me.
Energy, what for?
'Cause I'm gonna use my
unparalleled mental powers
and teleport us to the stone.
(gasping)
That makes sense.
I call it "Suezo's What Have
We Got to Lose" strategy.
Yeah, let's do it.
(cheers and approval)
‐Everyone ready?
‐Yeah, let's go for it.
Hm.
Hm!
Mm‐hm.
(straining)
♪
Teleport!
Where are we?
About ten meters
from where we started.
Well, at least we moved a bit.
Rats, not enough power.
Let's try it again.
Hm.
♪
(straining)
Teleport!
♪
Oops, nope, still not enough.
Let's keep on trying.
Teleport!
♪
Didn't work.
We're just warmin' up.
Don't give up, 'chi!
Teleport!
Oh, it's still not working.
It'll never work if
we start giving up.
That's right,
we're just starting.
Teleport!
Didn't work that time either.
Try again.
(Suezo muttering)
Teleport!
(crickets chirring)
♪
Master Moo, General
Durahan has arrived.
Master Moo, I have returned.
Weed went out with glory
on the battlefield,
and I, General Durahan,
feel honored to have
fought with him.
This is cause for celebration.
Your suffering
is about to end
and then you can unleash
your greatest power.
(laughing)
And now, the time has come
for your immortal powers
to be revived once again.
The stone!
Now, if you'll just
hand it over...
‐Stand back.
‐Huh?
I will personally
present the Magic Stone
to Master Moo.
Oh.
Master Moo!
I bring to you
the Magic Stone.
♪
(guttural moan)
(gasps)
♪
Master!
Moo, your reign is over!
Durahan, you traitor.
Farewell!
(roaring)
♪
(clanking)
(sparking)
Oh no!
♪
You will never defeat me.
A battle wound is
one I wear with honor,
and this battle
has just begun!
You won't escape me, Durahan!
(roaring)
(restraints snapping)
Master Moo, it's too dangerous!
♪
(chuckling)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim
it, you can tame it ♪
♪ Think of a square,
stand it on end ♪
♪ You got a Color
Pandora, watch it defend ♪
♪ Lilim is cute, but
this one's no fun ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ She wants all the
marbles for her honey bun ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ General Durahan
demands it all ♪
♪ He sees the world
at his beck and call ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
All hands prepare for battle!
What?
My cockpit.
Who has destroyed my cockpit?
Huh?
♪
(Moo roars)
Moo!
Durahan, you will
never escape me!
♪
(rumbling)
Durahan!
♪
Huh?
Excellent timing.
My main troops have arrived.
What?
♪
All ships attack!
(beams whiz)
(explosion)
You fools!
Moo is the target, not me.
(chuckling)
Lilim, what are
you laughing about?
Well, isn't it obvious?
I'm laughing because no one
will listen to your orders.
What?
The troops here are all
on Master Moo's side now.
I had quite a time
convincing them, though.
How could you?
All the Baddies on your ship
are gone for good this time.
Lilim, you traitor!
I've got a thing
for strong men.
And no one is stronger
than Master Moo
now that he has this stone.
(cackling)
(click)
(screams)
My stone!
You fools!
Did you honestly think
I would hand over
the real stone?
Feast your eyes on this.
You tricked me!
(growling)
I leave you now,
but I'll be back.
(engine roars)
♪
Don't let him escape!
Destroy me if you
wish, but remember,
you'll also be
destroying the stone.
Durahan!
The Magic Stone belongs to me.
♪
(rumbling)
Durahan, you rat.
Don't worry, Master.
I'll get the Magic
Stone for you.
Master Moo, are you all right?
After Durahan!
Yes, Master.
♪
Teleport!
That's the spirit.
‐Nice try.
‐"Nice try," he says.
(groaning)
Maybe teleporting
us all at once
is impossible.
Throw me a bone here,
I just know we can do it.
Suezo's right.
This isn't the first time
we've been in trouble
and it certainly
won't be the last.
That's right.
We've just gotta believe
in ourselves, people.
We must never stop hoping.
Full speed ahead!
We've made it too far
to give up now.
Okay, you've convinced me.
Let's give it another try.
Hm.
♪
Hmph!
Hm...
Let's do it!
(straining)
♪
Teleport!
As long as I possess
this Magic Stone,
Moo cannot perfect
his new body
and I will be the new leader.
What?
(all gasping)
(thud)
Hey!
Your ship's in the way.
You!
Ohh, where are we?
'chi!
Durahan!
(gasping)
The Magic Stone!
What are you doing here?
(growling)
Finally, my teleport worked!
Please, I need that stone.
I'm afraid that I
need it even more,
so if you want it, you'll
have to steal it from me.
(all growl)
♪
(shouting)
No, they must have
caught up with me.
Durahan, we have you surrounded.
Turn over the Magic Stone.
I don't think so, Weed.
Those planes are the Baddies!
Wonder what's going on?
Why are the Baddies
fighting each other?
I don't know, but I bet
it has something to do
with the last fight
they were having.
(panting)
Huh?
(clanging thud)
Genki!
♪
Huh?
(gasping)
(chuckling)
Wait a sec.
(grunting)
♪
(gasps)
You disappoint me, Lilim.
This Magic Stone
now belongs to me.
(beams whiz)
♪
(roaring)
Dragon Kick!
Mocchi!
Tail Attack!
(beams whiz)
♪
(electricity crackles)
No one can destroy
the evil General Durahan.
I will reign supreme
over the Baddies
and the entire
eastern continent!
No you won't,
not if we have
anything to say about it.
We'll stop you and Moo as well.
'chi!
You overestimate your strength.
You'll never destroy me.
Tornado Attack!
♪
'chi!
You can do it!
♪
Mocchi!
(screaming)
♪
Yeah, do it, Mocchi!
(gasping)
♪
I finally realize the
source of your strength.
It's...your friendship.
(shattering clink)
(thud)
♪
Is it over?
What'd you do that for?
It's a wake‐up call.
This isn't a dream!
Yeah!
The Magic Stone!
(screaming)
‐Holly!
‐'chi!
(gasping)
Looks like I'm the one
who gets the last laugh.
No way!
(buzzer sounds)
That's just the self
detonation device
which is set to go
off in five minutes.
She's got the stone!
Golem, take care of Holly.
Go!
♪
(fingers twitch)
(panting)
♪
(gasping)
Huh?
Thanks for the stone!
No you don't!
♪
Run!
Run, run, run!
♪
I almost had the stone, too.
Let's just get outta here!
Seems like a great
time to teleport.
(explosion)
(screaming)
No...can't concentrate.
Go!
How did that Weed
get my Magic Stone?
We've retrieved the stone.
Open fire now.
(beams whiz)
(explosion)
(panting)
♪
(gasping)
Come back to say goodbye?
♪
(roaring blast)
We're trapped, 'chi!
Don't give up, gang.
Everyone concentrate on Suezo.
♪
Let me go!
You're not my master anymore.
I serve under Moo.
Have you forgotten
who you are speaking to?
I am the immortal
evil General Durahan!
How dare you betray me, Lilim?
(beams whiz)
(flames crackle)
Teleport!
(explosion)
♪
How 'bout getting off, Golem?
Sorry.
So, where are we?
Where'd we end up landing?
Who cares, as long as
we're off that Iron Bird.
Huh?
(gasping)
♪
In the end, we weren't able
to get back the
Magic Stone, were we?
But at least we
got rid of Durahan.
You're right.
That's one less enemy.
Somehow, we'll find Phoenix.
Yeah.
'chi!
♪
We'll just have
to do it ourselves.
Okay, gang.
Come on, time to move 'em out.
'chi!
Then let's head north, guys.
The way the Magic Stone
last pointed, 'k?
Yeah!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪