♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(wind blowing)
♪
(evil laughter)
It won't be long now.
And I'll be
my own self again.
(evil laughter)
♪
Yes!
Master Guji!
(growling)
(swords clanging)
Master Guji is resting.
Wait, Zilla.
It's urgent,
it can't wait, Zilla.
When I say wait,
you wait.
And when I say it can't wait,
it can't wait, got it?
(growling)
♪
Quiet!
What's going on here?
Guji, I have come
with orders for you
from Master Gali.
Oh, from Master Gali.
The rebels who are causing
trouble for Master Moo
have set out to sea on
Pirate Horn's ship, Master.
What?
Guji, your orders
are to find them.
You must not
let them get away.
Leave it to us,
we will find them, Guji.
(growling)
All right, and make sure
you get that pirate, Horn.
Depart, Zilla.
(growling)
(evil laughter)
And so, Horn, we will
finally meet again.
Ya‐hoo!
♪
(giggling)
Chi, it's big!
And wide, chi.
This is a promise, Phoenix,
we're gonna find you this time.
Chi!
(laughing)
Uh, now how did they
get off work when we can't?
Yes, well Mocchi's
never seen the sea, right?
How long does this deck
swabbing business go on anyway?
Suezo, you big lug!
Are you slacking off again?
You pirate, we're
passengers here, remember!
Where do you get off
ordering us around, Horn?
Captain‐‐I'm the
captain of this ship!
You're a pirate!
You're an eyeball!
Come on, Suezo, stop it.
Ahoy there, sweetie.
Oh, she doth teach the
torches to burneth bright.
Beauty too rich for use.
‐For there‐‐
‐Hey, knock it off,
you one‐eyed, no‐good,
sea slurpin' pirate!
Look, landlubber,
it's like I be tellin' ya,
Captain Horn be
an honorable pirate.
Watch, swabbies?
Aye‐aye!
(laughing)
Yes, sir, I've always said
Captain Horn is a fine fellow.
Come on, let me see.
Wow, awesome!
Well now, this old treasure?
It just be a small indication of
my esteem for Miss Holly here.
Horn, it's nothing
but a box of garbage.
Cheap, trashy garbage.
Huh, what'd you say?
Hah, you heard me!
Please, stop arguing!
(sail flapping)
‐Listen.
‐Huh?
It's awful quiet out there.
Too quiet.
♪
Uh, I hate to bring this up,
but what do you want to bet
that Moo controls
the ocean too?
What?
Horn, it's safe, isn't it?
I'm not one to brag,
but there's not a safer
captain on these waters.
I'll get the seven of you
to where you're going.
Hmm‐‐one, two, three,
four, five, six...
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
Hold on, a swabbie's missing!
Chi.
♪
Say there, I'll keelhaul ya!
Swab the decks!
The ocean's
not my thing, Captain.
(laughs)
Well, blow me down
and shiver me timbers, matey.
All hands aloft.
Ho!
He's afraid of the water.
(laughing)
Horn, put him down!
♪
One, two, three!
(yelling)
♪
(splash)
Golem, no!
(laughing)
Face your fears, that's
what me mother always said.
And‐‐hmm?
Uh‐oh.
Hold on, Golem,
I'll save you.
Alley oop!
♪
All right, now pull!
And pull, and pull, and pull.
Are you two all right?
Ugh.
That wasn't
a good idea, Horn.
Ah, I see, rock.
Well then, you just
stay here and rest a while.
Thanks.
No need to thank me, lad.
Besides, Suezo will take
your share of the chores.
Hey, no way!
There's penalties
for mutiny aboard my ship!
Make my day.
Oh, all right, but just know
that this is under duress!
♪
Hard to starboard.
Aye‐aye, Captain.
♪
Some monsters do anything
to get out of work.
♪
♪ Get a disk,
take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Captain Black Dino,
one of Moo's best ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Leave the Black Dinos
on every conquest ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Little Spot Dino
is harmless enough ♪
♪ To unlock the Kuro,
you gotta be tough ♪
♪ Captain Kuro
will stomp and brawl ♪
♪ These monsters rule,
unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Okay, everybody.
(chewing)
Not hungry, Suezo?
No, I think I'll just go up
and get a breath of fresh air.
Hey, what's wrong?
‐Nothing.
‐Nothing?
Karma.
What do you mean?
Ah, he had to
work for a change.
Nope, Suezo's seasick.
(grumbling)
‐Golem.
‐Hmm?
Holly.
Hey, do you want some dinner?
No.
Oh.
Well there's some
yummy rocks and stones
for you to eat down below.
Golem likes it right here.
'Kay.
♪
The stars are beautiful.
A lot's happened since we
started this adventure,
hasn't it, Golem?
Yes.
I hate to admit it,
but sometimes I worry
that we're never
going to find the Phoenix.
Hmm?
The land across the sea
is a strange place
where they say Moo's
rule is even stronger
than where we've been.
The powers of the baddies
are probably stronger, too.
Don't worry, Holly.
We will find the Phoenix.
Huh?
We have learned
something important,
that when we work together
as a team, we can win.
We will find the Phoenix.
You're right, yes we will.
You feel better now, Holly?
Thanks, Golem, I certainly do.
♪
(snoring)
Oh, here we go again.
Suezo?
(waves crashing)
Ah!
♪
(yelling)
Zilla!
♪
Zillas off the
starboard bow, Captain!
I can see that!
Send your lads, Guji?
(ship creaking)
♪
Time to settle this yourself,
you skylarking hooligan!
(growling)
Let the games begin!
Argh!
More of Moo's baddies!
(growling)
And fire!
(cannon fire)
♪
Ready?
Chi.
(cannon fire)
Can't swim.
♪
It's okay, Golem.
This ship's not going down.
Thank you, Holly.
We're a team,
remember, Golem?
And that's what teammates do.
Because we can
do things together
we can't do by ourselves.
Right, Holly.
Hmm.
Give it all you got, men!
Defeat those Zillas!
♪
Zilla troops move forward,
don't let up!
Attack, attack, Zillas!
It's no good.
The enemy is stronger
than we are.
We are Zillas!
We never retreat!
We must attack now!
(cannon fire)
Yeah, right.
Come back, you‐‐here.
Still want to attack?
Grrr, what do you think?
What are your orders, Zilla?
Retreat!
(grumbling)
(laughing)
♪
We did it!
Mocchi!
♪
(trembling)
Looks like I'll have to
take care of this myself.
Well, blow me down.
Hey, Captain, what's going on?
I can feel it.
Me horn is telling me that
Monster Guji is on his way here.
(all together)
Gugi!
The foulest scourge
to ever swim the briny deep.
He'd sink a ship
as soon as to look at it
and he's tried
to sink many of mine.
We'll take care of him.
Chi!
♪
(yelling)
You've come
at last, Guji, hey?
That's Guji?
He's enormous.
That's a really big monster!
So, Captain,
nice to see you again.
Zilla!
♪
And blast 'em!
(cannon fire)
And blast 'em again,
me hearties.
♪
(yelling)
(evil laughter)
Difficult to believe
a puny creature like you
could upset
Master Moo so much.
♪
Don't worry, Holly,
Captain Horn will protect you.
Argh!
Captain Horn!
(screaming)
Holly!
Oh no, you don't!
Pick on someone your own size,
‐you bully.
‐Don't you know
you're messing with
the monster champ, Guji?
Alley oop!
Rip it up!
♪
Arrgh!
Agghh!
♪
Genki, you okay, kid?
Sure, I'm the champ, remember?
You just got me
real mad, Guji,
and you really don't
want to see me mad!
Yah, and I'm with him,
you scurvy‐faced hooligan!
Hey, put her down!
I must help her.
♪
Would some of you
bothersome gnats
care to join
the young lady, perhaps?
(yelling)
♪
Chi!
It's Golem!
One for all,
and all for one.
(struggling)
♪
Tornado!
(screaming)
(together)
Holly, I will catch you!
(screaming)
♪
Tornado!
Rope 'im, me lads.
♪
Arm the halyards,
full speed ahead, me hearties.
♪
You'll get off here.
Then we'll decide
this once and for all.
This Monster Guji
must be stopped.
(yelling)
♪
(yelling encouragements)
Chi!
♪
Hard to port!
We'll drop him
into the whirlpool.
♪
Now then,
cut the blighter loose.
♪
I'm not finished
with you yet!
♪
Zilla!
(yelling)
Never underestimate
your enemy, Horn.
♪
(yelling)
Fill the main sails!
That whirlpool's close!
♪
Yeah!
(celebrating)
Golem, you saved us!
It's just like
you said before,
All for one
and one for all, right?
(laughing)
Congrats.
Look what else
you've done, Golem.
You've overcome
your fear of water.
Oh?
Aargh!
Golem?
Well, I suppose you can lead
a golem to water but maybe not.
Ugh.
♪
(laughing)
Look, there it is!
♪
Thanks a lot
for your help, Horn.
Ah, we couldn't have
stopped Guji without you,
so thanks yourself, me boy.
And here...
What?
♪
Wow!
It may be of help.
♪
It's great!
Horn, where'd you go?
That map is a farewell gift
for you all, Miss Holly.
We'll treasure it, Horn,
thank you very much.
(yelling)
Come on, Miss Holly,
how about this side too, ah?
Horn, just back right off!
♪
(all together)
Bye!
♪
And now, on with our search.
All right, you better
look out, baddies,
'cause we're gonna
find the Phoenix!
(all together)
Yeah!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪