♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(lightning cracks)
♪
I no longer have a choice.
I must use my last resort
to conquer those fools!
Not your last resort!
You mean the fierce warrior?
♪
Come to me, my great warrior!
Awaken, Bajarl!
♪
Bajarl!
Destroy the seven
pests who oppose us.
That is the mission
I bestow upon you.
Bajarl.
♪
Hang on to your hats, people!
‐All right.
‐Gotcha.
♪
(groaning)
Full steam ahead, teleport!
♪
(chuckling)
'kay?
Hey, what happened?
Let me try it again.
Teleport.
Teleport!
Teleport, teleport, teleport,
teleport, teleport, tel‐‐
(panting)
Something's wrong.
That's for sure.
The problem is you don't
ever come through for us
when we need you
the most, Suezo.
Got a complaint?
File it at
the complaints desk!
I'm thirsty!
Water!
You've already polished
off the canteen.
'chi?
Hey, gimme, let me see!
Let me‐‐let me see!
It's gone, the water's gone,
I'm gonna die of thirst.
That's strange.
According to this map,
there should be a town
somewhere around here.
Yeah, but unless
we find some water,
we're not gonna
make it very far.
This is the end.
The sun's getting hotter
and pretty soon the vultures
are gonna start circling in.
(wailing)
Whatcha talkin' about?
The seven of us are a team
and if we pull together,
we'll make it outta here.
That'd practically
take a miracle.
There's no food,
there's no water,
and there's no road in sight.
According to my
calculations, it's hopeless.
We're all doomed, I tell ya.
(crying)
Maybe we are.
But we can't just sit around!
We've got to keep
our spirits up
and try to get outta here.
Yeah, you're right.
Mocchi agree!
We don't give up, 'chi!
Go.
♪
Hm?
Look, something
coming this way.
♪
Huh?
It's a dragon, 'chi!
Can't be, it doesn't have wings.
I got it, it's an Iron Bird!
No way!
It's too small for that.
Then what is it?
♪
Well, it looks
pretty harmless to me.
All right, let me see.
It's only a jar.
Huh‐‐ah!
Be careful.
It's smoking.
I don't like the looks of this.
♪
What's going on?
(sinister laughing)
He's a Baddie!
Sure doesn't look it.
He's little, 'chi.
(laughing)
What are you supposed to be?
I'm Master Naga's servant
and I go by
the name of Bajarl.
One, two, uh, three,
three, two, one.
That's funny.
There's seven of us here!
Seven of us!
Then you must be
the seven people
who are opposing Master Naga.
And if we are,
what are you gonna do?
Hmm, then I'll just
have to get rid of you.
(laughter)
♪
You made me laugh.
No kidding.
The little feller can't
even count up to seven
and he figures he
can get rid of us?
Come on, let's go
call his bluff.
Sounds good!
(chuckles)
♪
‐Whirlwind!
‐The jar's gonna suck us in!
♪
Hare, Suezo,
what's happening?
(sinister chuckling)
♪
(all gasp)
You'll pay.
♪
Unreal.
Tiger, no!
♪
Now how many left
does that make?
(whimpering)
♪
Mocchi!
Cannon!
♪
(exclaiming)
Golem!
Genki!
Stay back!
You can't get sucked in too!
So stay back!
We'll be okay!
Get the Phoenix!
But, Genki...
Can't go.
Mocchi, no, no, can't go!
Mocchi, you go!
Holly!
Okay!
We're counting on you, Holly.
♪
Take this.
Uh‐oh.
Bajarl!
♪
Pretty good thinking, big guy.
However, I can
counter it with this!
♪
Ha, how many does that leave?
Let me see now.
One, two presents for Moo.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Niton, snail,
fast talking and bold ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ He'd give up his mother
just for some gold ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ This one comes back
each time as an ape ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Sweet Baby Bossy
just can't escape ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Stone Dragon spewing
crackling fire ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all 'cause
they're all for hire ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(sighs)
(panting)
I'm tired, 'chi.
Mocchi!
(yelling)
♪
Mocchi, are you okay?
'chi...
Huh?
Houses.
♪
This must be the town
we saw on the map.
Must be, 'chi.
It's completely deserted.
I wonder why it's turned
into a ghost town.
(sinister laughing)
(gasps)
It's Bajarl!
Run, Mocchi!
You can run but you can't hide!
Might as well save
yourself the energy!
♪
Did we lose him?
Sorry to disappoint you.
(laughing)
♪
Is it safe to come out?
Coast clear, 'chi?
♪
(yelling)
Found you.
Not very imaginative
at Hide‐and‐Seek, are you?
♪
Run, Mocchi.
I'm coming to get ya.
Faster!
♪
‐Go!
‐Bajarl!
Oh?
(yells)
♪
(screaming)
Holly!
♪
Where are you?
Over here, 'chi!
(sighs)
I'm glad you're safe.
It's sure a good thing
we fell when we did.
Look at that, 'chi.
A door.
I wonder where it leads.
♪
It looks like some kind
of library or office.
♪
'chi?
'chi.
Huh?
'chi?
♪
It looks like the mayor's diary.
Diary?
"The day we feared
has finally come.
The day when fear
and destruction
overcame our beautiful city
and the people
all ran away."
♪
We lived in this peaceful
and prosperous town
built by our ancestors
until one day...
(crowd commotion)
(Bajarl laughing)
♪
"Bajarl took everything from us.
The lush greenery of our city,
our prosperity."
'chi.
Most importantly, he stole
our precious citizens
from our town.
There was only
one way to fight back.
It was a tough decision to make
but if we didn't
stop Bajarl,
the damages would just increase.
He'd move on to other towns
and steal their people as well.
So we had to do something
to stop Bajarl.
♪
It took a long time
but the citizens set
up some explosives.
Unfortunately,
Bajarl outwitted us.
(laughing)
(yelling)
Oh no!
Now I'm the only
person left in the city.
Sooner or later,
Bajarl will find me too.
♪
'chi...
'chi.
A map, 'chi.
♪
'chi!
"My one last hope is that
someone comes across this diary
and finds it in his heart
to carry out our last wishes."
Give you one guess
who's behind ya.
(screaming)
(laughing)
That about wraps up our
little game of Hide‐and‐Seek.
Ha.
Uh‐oh.
Huh?
Bajarl?
Let me outta here,
on the double!
‐It's Genki!
I want outta here right now!
(groaning)
This jar's hard to break.
Tail attack!
(yelling)
♪
Thanks for the big hand.
Don't just stand there,
my tail's on fire!
Are you guys
all right in there?
We're okay for now!
Perhaps, but not
for very much longer.
Whoa!
I've got you now!
♪
Hurry!
'chi!
♪
(yelling)
(grunting, groaning)
So I guess this
means you're it.
Oh, whoa.
♪
Time for you to
join your friends.
♪
'chi!
No, Mocchi!
No more games for Mocchi, 'chi!
Oh, this is going to be good,
going head to head
with the marshmallow baby.
Mocchi get him, Holly.
You go now, 'chi!
Okay, Mocchi.
♪
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe,
now who's first?
Puffball.
Why you...
♪
This looks like the place.
A‐ha.
♪
There it is.
This is your last chance
to say uncle, little fella.
♪
Bajarl?
(shivering)
How do I get myself
into these situations?
Stop your shivering,
we'll be back in the
desert before you know it.
Go.
(yelling)
♪
Where's this icy
air coming from?
Now is my chance.
Mocchi!
(yelling)
♪
You're stronger
than I took you for.
How could that be?
♪
I really underestimated you.
Huh‐‐Bajarl,
Bajarl, Bajarl!
(grunting)
♪
(Mocchi giggling)
Mocchi!
Run for it!
♪
Follow me!
‐'chi!
‐No, wait!
You can't leave me here!
(grunting)
♪
Wait for Bajarl!
(loud explosions)
♪
Bajarl, Bajarl!
(yelling)
♪
(sighing, whimpering)
Look!
♪
Hey, you guys!
(shivering)
Okay, okay, c‐cold now.
♪
What a waste.
What's wrong, Holly?
I know we didn't
many choices back there
but even still...
‐Aww.
‐... I destroyed a whole town.
I'm so sad.
Uh, Holly‐‐
Golem think mayor
and townsfolk,
they would forgive you.
You took care
of Bajarl for 'em.
You and Mocchi just
finished up the job
that they set out to do
in the first place, you see?
Gotta agree with him this time.
You guys did a great job, Holly.
Don't even doubt it
for a second.
Hm.
'chi!
Well, gang...
let's blow this joint
and get going.
Hm?
Hey, someone's coming.
Huh?
♪
Oh no, not another
Baddie is it?
♪
No, that's no Baddie.
Huh?
♪
It's Pixie!
And Big Blue's with her.
(laughing)
♪
(wind blowing)
Master Moo, I have good news!
The Final Gate is done!
Hm?
♪
Do it.
Yes, Master.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪