♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(stomping)
Ouch!
When they do
jungles around here,
they don't mess around.
Well, Hare, why don't we just
take a raft down the river?
Oh, nice.
So, you have some sort of
better plan, do you, Tiger?
You always come up with
such great ideas, don't you?
Back off!
You wish!
Hey, save your
energy for walking,
not fighting, you guys.
Ooh.
Yeah, you two, come on!
I'll work harder.
(grunting)
♪
Way to go, Golem.
Makes jungle travel fun.
Ah!
♪
(shouting)
Suezo!
Little help here.
(grunting)
♪
Suezo?
Why is it always me?
Anyone got any
idea where we are?
♪
The stone, what's it say?
This way.
Aw.
Let's get going, Hare.
(grunting)
Huh?
♪
‐Gross.
‐Ew.
♪
‐Oh!
‐Scaled Jells!
Creatures who oppose
Moo must be stopped!
At last, I have found you!
♪
Captain, what's wrong?
I'm so pleased that
I finally found them.
Soft mind, soft body, uh, sir!
Regroup, Captain!
(bubbling)
Gali has ordered that
we get rid of them!
Yeah!
♪
(grunting)
What a team!
Awesome!
We wiped them out in no time!
Yeah, so much
for Scaled Jells!
Ah!
Chi!
Whoa!
♪
Those Scaled Jells are immoral.
Huh?
Uh, no, immortal.
Ah!
Get them!
(shouting)
♪
Let's regroup into
the sheet attack!
(shouting)
Oh, boy, now what?
I'm getting dizzy.
(shouting)
I guess that wraps it up.
Lightning impact!
Ah!
(grunting)
♪
It's Pixie!
And Big Blue!
Wow, did you come to save us?
Ha, don't flatter yourselves.
(grunting)
Now you've done it!
Scaled Jell merger!
(shouting)
Jell!
♪
What is that?
(shouting)
Lightning!
(grunting)
(shouting)
♪
Genki!
Ah!
♪
(shouting)
(grunting)
‐Genki!
‐Pixie!
How are we gonna
get down there?
I don't know, but we better.
Ah, Captain, what are
we supposed to do now?
What do you think?
Ah, find Pixie
and the short kid
before their friends do!
Jell!
Monsters.
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Gali, one of
Moo's Big Bad Four ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Big Blue, a monster
with power and more ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Pixie's a mystery,
whose side is she on ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ She's one of Moo's four,
but for how long ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Flips and tornadoes,
without 'em, within ♪
♪ Four hundred monsters,
someone will win ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(shouting)
♪
(groaning)
Hmm, huh?
Pixie, are you all right?
Genki?
You're hurt.
Just twisted it.
Nothing serious.
Huh?
Oh, no, come on,
let's get out of here.
Don't touch me.
I can move myself‐‐ah!
Pixie, your wings
are damaged too.
I told you not to touch me!
Ah!
Hey, chill out.
I'm just trying to help!
(grunting)
♪
Can't believe it.
This is the second
time you saved me.
First, at Moo's
castle, and now here.
Eh, don't worry about it.
I was just passing by.
Thank you, Pixie.
Yeah, well, there's a rumor
around that Moo started
a huge excavation at Kyrus
in the northlands.
What's at Kyrus?
I don't know, so that's
why I'm on my way there,
see for myself.
Well, it could be the
ancient body stuff
he's been talking about.
Probably is.
Ah, well, I don't care
what kind of body Moo has!
Don't underestimate
Moo's strength.
He's not an ordinary monster.
I know that, Pixie.
Huh?
But I‐‐I really believe
that if we work together,
we can defeat him.
We can do it.
I know we can, I know it.
What is that supposed
to mean, that attitude?
♪
(growling)
Ah, that makes me so angry!
I'm going to sleep.
Hmm.
(snoring)
♪
Jell!
Jell, find them!
They fell over a cliff
for crying out loud!
They can't have gone
far, so find 'em!
♪
(sighing)
So, what have you found?
Have you got 'em, huh?
Report, report!
Nothing here, Captain.
Nothing here either, sir.
This will not impress
Master Gali, understand?
You must search
more aggressive‐‐
(warbling)
Have you been hit, sir?
No, it just crossed my mind
that they might
have gotten away.
Soft mind, soft body,
Captain, sir!
Atten‐hut!
♪
Good recovery, Captain.
Well done, sir!
Thank you, let's
try the cliff!
The cliff, they
fell off the cliff!
Let's go!
Phew, close call.
♪
Come on, Pixie, let's go.
We've got to get
back to the others.
The Scaled Jells will find us
if we stay here much longer.
Okay, coast is clear.
Come on.
Don't touch me, Genki.
Man.
You go ahead, I can
manage by myself.
What's your problem?
I don't need
sympathy from humans.
It's friendship,
not sympathy!
You really need to go to
attitude camp, you know.
(shouting)
♪
Genki!
Hmm?
Genki, where are you?
Ah!
Golem!
I'm ready!
♪
(shouting)
Hey!
Whoa, whoa!
♪
This isn't funny.
Suezo?
Did you see Genki?
No, couldn't see anything,
just jungle everywhere.
Oh, no, please tell me the
Scaled Jells don't have him.
Don't even think that, Hare.
Master Pixie is with him.
Chi, chi!
They're okay, we just
have to find them, right?
Right!
♪
(grunting)
It's okay, Pixie,
I'm all right.
(laughs)
♪
Ah!
I'm sorry, are you
all right, Pixie?
(grunting)
Oh, no, Pixie!
Huh?
(grunting)
♪
Pixie, grab on!
Grab my hand!
(grunting)
Hurry up!
(gasping)
Here!
♪
(grunting)
Oh, man, quicksand.
That was totally awesome.
Imagine that, we
survived quicksand.
Ha, you okay?
Thank you.
♪
(laughing)
Is it all right?
Hmm?
Your leg?
You should go on
ahead, Genki.
I'm just gonna slow you down.
If I thought that,
I would've been out of here
a long time ago, so
don't get any ideas.
Anyway, Pixie,
it'll be much easier
if we just stay together.
Don't worry, we'll find them.
Hmm?
‐Ah, smoke!
‐Huh?
Awesome, it's a signal!
Yeah!
No, stop it!
‐We're in a hurry!
‐Genki!
I won't allow it.
I mean it!
Genki, stop!
Stop it!
That's it, over there!
Holly, Suezo?
Guys!
Where are‐‐huh?
(laughing)
Clever little boy, you
walked right into my trap.
Huh?
(laughing)
What's so funny?
There's the Pixie
of the Big Bad Four
carried by a puny human kid!
(growling)
Let's get rid of
the both of them!
(shouting)
♪
(grunting)
Genki!
(shouting)
(grunting)
Just who do you think
you're messing with?
(shouting)
Gali will be so pleased!
(zapping)
Captain!
Huh?
Pixie!
Pixie, thanks.
Traitor to Master Moo?
Saved by a human?
Have you no pride
at all, Pixie?
(growling)
But because I'm such
a nice guy, Pixie,
I'm going to give you one
final chance to save yourself.
You are going to have
to destroy that boy
with your own two hands.
You're all talk, Captain.
Don't move.
Is that your answer?
Then you leave me
with no alternative.
Scaled Jells, jell!
Ha, ultra‐parabola beam!
♪
I take orders from no one.
I only fight for
what I believe in.
Parabola beam fire!
♪
My name is...
Pixie!
(whirring)
♪
What's going on
with that light?
That light is Master Pixie's.
Take that!
(grunting)
(yelling)
♪
(crackling)
(groaning)
Huh?
♪
Pixie!
Ah!
I got ya!
(heavy breathing)
Don't worry, Genki,
I'll be okay.
Well, you saved me
once again, Pixie.
That makes us
friends forever.
(sighing)
Genki.
Help us to defeat Moo, hmm?
‐Someday.
‐Really?
Okay.
It's a promise.
♪
It's a promise made forever.
Can't be broken,
no, not never.
We agree.
Okay!
(laughs)
‐Master Pixie!
‐Genki!
Are you all right?
Sure are!
We're fine, Pixie saved me.
Wonderful, chi!
Are you okay?
She's hurt her leg.
She what?
It's nothing serious.
I just used up all my energy.
Let's go home.
You need the rest.
Ah, come on, you
two, get serious!
‐Hey!
‐Hmm?
It's pretty clear whose
side you're on, so join us.
Hmm.
Pixie!
Hmm?
Don't forget, it's a promise.
(laughing)
Hmm.
♪
Genki, what's wrong
with your finger?
Uh...
Got an owie?
Uh, I, uh...
(laughing)
You got a secret.
Come on, spill the beans.
Golem like secrets.
Come on, confess!
Just between you and me, huh?
Okay!
Well, my friends...
Ha, maybe later.
Aw!
Let's go!
Genki, wait a minute!
(laughing)
♪
Foolish, foolish creatures.
(laughing)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪