♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
♪
And there you have it!
We'll search for
the Phoenix that way!
‐Go!
‐Let's move!
Hey, not so fast!
Follow the leader!
(grunting)
♪
(crash)
Genki, Mocchi,
are you alright?
Sure, except for
this welt on my head.
(beeping siren)
Five whole seconds since we
left and look at you guys!
What's that stone over there?
Huh?
♪
Hm.
Uh‐huh, yes, yes, mhm!
Enough with the suspense,
just tell us what it says!
I think I'm going to
need some more time.
It seems to be another language.
Well, thank you,
Captain Obvious!
Now, translate it!
Give me a break, I'm
thinking as fast as I can.
We've got better
things to do, people.
Hang on, it might
contain some clues
that will help us
to find the Phoenix.
Hmmmph.
Take this!
(thud)
Genki?
(whimpering)
Smart move, chief, what
was that suppose to prove?
(whimpering)
I thought maybe something
would happen if I hit it.
♪
(gears turning)
(in unison)
Huh?
Look, there's something
behind the stone.
Some kind of secret entrance.
Wow, Genki, you did it, 'chi!
(chuckling)
Ow, that hurts.
♪
This place is creepy,
I hope it's not the Baddies'
secret hideout or something.
Probably not,
I don't smell them.
I don't know about you guys,
but I'm getting the willies!
Something's hiding back
there, I can just feel it!
Mocchi, treasure, 'chi!
Uh‐huh.
If it was my sixth sense
would have picked up on it,
by now, for sure.
Then I was right, it
is the Baddies hideout.
Or maybe the Phoenix is in here.
That would be great if
you were right, Mocchi.
You said it, sister.
Go?
Mocchi, 'chi!
♪
Wonder what a shrine's
doing in a place like this?
I don't know, but
something's definitely wrong
with this picture.
Well, I'm gonna go check it out.
♪
Huh?
What?
What, what, did you
find some treasure?
‐What is it?
‐Well, let's see!
♪
Mystery discs!
(fire burst)
Genki, what's going on?
I don't know, but we'll
get to the bottom of it!
What could they be
looking at over there?
It's the Phoenix,
I'm almost positive!
Yeah, all the blood, sweat, and
tears we've put into this search
and now it's finally paid off!
(crying)
♪
‐There!
‐We're all ready, 'chi!
Let's do it and hope
this is the Phoenix.
Something's happening!
So far, so good!
♪
Unlock!
(boinging sound)
Huh, what is it?
♪
‐It's a Bossy.
‐How adorable!
Adorable, 'chi!
(chattering)
Oh, man, talk about
getting ripped off!
I was all psyched
to get the Phoenix,
and then we get some dumb ape!
(growling)
Bossy, stop!
(grunting)
(growling)
That's what I was catching
a whiff of back there, apes.
Are you Baddies?
No, look, they
don't have crests.
Who are you,
you must be thieves!
(growling)
Wait, you shouldn't
be afraid of us.
That's right, 'chi!
We're on a journey, and
we came here by accident.
(chatters)
Our leader!
Honorable One, I see that
you have been resurrected.
(in unison)
Huh?
Men, behold our
great leader, Bossy!
♪
Great Honorable Bossy, bless us
with longevity and prosperity.
(in unison)
Bless us.
Huh?
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk! ♪
♪ The Phoenix sores
like Master Moo ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Everybody wants them,
how 'bout you ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Moo is a giant,
baddest of bad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Nagas fight for him,
to resist would be mad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ 400 monsters,
all shapes and sizes ♪
♪ You can't predict them,
they're full of surprises ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
I see, so that's what you
were doing down in the shrine.
I'll hope you'll forgive
me for accusing you
of being thieves.
No probs, oh, and sorry
for sneaking up on you.
We just let ourselves in
because we had no idea
‐that it belonged to anyone.
‐'chi, 'chi!
(in unison)
Huh?
Many carvings, 'chi!
What are they for?
That's Bossy in the past.
Each lifetime he
was a great leader.
I don't think I'm following.
Our leader is eternal.
Eternal?
That's right, after our
honorable Bossy passes
onto the next world,
he is resurrected
through a
transmigration ceremony.
I think he means they
resurrect the same leader
with a mystery disc.
So, that means‐‐
All the red mystery discs
we saw are Bossy.
(deep sighing)
Just our luck.
The honorable Bossy is
able to predict the weather,
heal the sick, locate food,
and he blesses our clan of apes
with longevity and prosperity.
He's vital to the
existence of our village.
What makes you think it
isn't just a healthy dose
of common sense?
Bossy!
What's the matter?
Bossy, he's in trouble!
(chattering)
♪
Kalaragi mango?
The food supply of the jungle at
this time of year is very low,
our only hope then
is to rely on Bossy.
Incoming!
(laughing)
♪
Bossy, it's just about
time for night‐night.
(chatters)
(fire crackling)
♪
Okay.
There we go.
One bottle of milk.
(chattering)
Guess he doesn't
know about time outs.
He should be on an infomercial
with that kind of energy.
♪
'chi.
This warm milk should
put him to sleep.
Hey, Bossy, got
something for you.
(laughing)
Drink up, and you'll
grow big and strong.
With him around,
our journey must wait.
It would be nice if
he started warming up
to you guys pretty soon.
Please do forgive us, we must
be delaying your journey.
No need to apologize.
It was meant to be.
♪
What's wrong, Tiger?
Heads up, Holly!
(grunts)
Holly!
Whoa!
(monkey noises)
Who are they?
It's the Rock Apes!
(whimpering)
♪
Bossy, no!
Speed it up, team,
they're getting away!
We're going as fast as we can!
Come back!
Holly!
♪
Bossy!
(grunting)
Huh?
(yelling)
♪
(monkey noises)
(moaning)
Man, they sure pulled
a number on us.
I'd say they've been
planning this one.
You said they were
called Rock Apes,
isn't that right?
Yeah, they invaded us,
they stole our water
and food a few times recently.
Golem confused,
why they take Holly?
They didn't want her,
it was Bossy they wanted.
Hm, Bossy has special powers
and they want to keep him
for themselves.
Our clan could never
survive without Bossy.
We must hurry and return him!
We find him!
Come on, gang, let's get moving!
We're going to find him!
Yeah!
♪
(groaning)
Boss, Rock Apes!
♪
We did it, we
brought back Bossy!
♪
(grunting)
(shouting)
♪
What do you plan to do with us?
Tell us that at least.
Hmmph.
♪
(monkey noises)
Bossy, no!
♪
(sinister laughing)
(laughing)
(cheering)
♪
Are you sure you know
what you're doing, Tiger?
Just trust me.
♪
(sniffing)
This way!
♪
(laughing)
(cheering)
What a fine young lad you are.
♪
Our Journey will be much
easier with you along.
We'll be able to find food
and safe places to live.
So that's why they
kidnapped Bossy.
Holly!
♪
(growling)
Genki, you found us!
Hey, are you alright?
Yeah!
Bossy is our great
and honorable leader,
You can't take him from us!
Yeah, if you want him back,
you'll have to fight for him.
(growling)
♪
Ready, attack!
Go get them, apes!
♪
There you go, now,
let's go join them!
‐Hang on!
‐What?
This fighting isn't right!
We have to stop it, right now!
Holly, no!
Stop this!
Stop it!
This fighting is meaningless!
Meaningless, you say!
This is a holy battle to
retrieve our great leader!
Exactly, this battle will
determine whether or not
our clan is to survive!
Don't you get it, you
both have the same problem.
You all need Bossy!
Hey, where'd Bossy go?
Hey, he's vanished!
(shouting)
(in unison)
Huh?
♪
‐Find him!
‐Now!
♪
Bossy!
Get back here, you rascal!
Come out, wherever you are!
Where are you?
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
‐Bossy!
‐We're here!
Bossy!
(together)
(grunting)
Where could he have gotten to?
I don't know, but his
timing could be better.
Bossy!
(chattering)
(all together)
Huh?
♪
Bossy!
Found him!
Hey, you apes, we found Bossy!
(cheering)
♪
I don't believe it!
I didn't know Kalaragi
mangos grew out here.
The leader knows all.
So now we won't have
to worry about food.
(chattering)
Bossy!
Be careful!
♪
Uh‐oh, that's dangerous.
(grunting)
♪
Ah!
(exclaiming)
♪
Genki, Bossy!
We're all hanging on,
just pull us up!
(chatters)
♪
(sighing)
Bossy, you were a
naughty little monkey,
you had everybody worried sick!
You've got to try to be
more careful from now on.
(cooing)
♪
Huh?
Are those for us?
I think he's telling
you to be friends.
♪
You just helped
each other, remember?
♪
Mmm.
So you were attacked?
Yes, Naga's army
attacked our village
and destroyed everything.
And so that's how you ended
up living in the forest?
That's right.
I only wish you'd told us
sooner, then perhaps we could
have been able to help you out.
Thank you, but if Naga's
army had come after us again
you would have been
caught in the middle.
We could not do that to you.
But you were going to run away
and take Bossy with you.
You couldn't have escaped,
Naga would have chased you
to the end of the world.
Sorry about everything.
We will leave
your jungle at once.
Wait.
♪
I think there's room in this
jungle for all of us apes.
We don't have to
worry about Baddies.
We both got Bossy here
to show us the way.
You're too kind.
♪
I accept your offer.
(together)
Hmm.
'chi!
(laughing)
♪
Look at her, she's
like a mom to them.
I'll say, they don't
how lucky they are.
Oh, you guys say something?
‐Not this guy.
‐Me either.
Hmm.
Hey!
Hey, that tickles!
Oh, Bossy!
We should find the Phoenix and
bring it back to life real soon.
Mhm.
So, others won't
have to go through
what the Rock Apes just did.
Mhm, good point.
♪
(wind blowing)
(metal clanking)
♪
How long I've waited
for this day to arrive
and now at last
the time has come.
My original body will finally
be united with my soul
and then the entire world will
be draped in a veil of darkness!
(sinister laughing)
♪
Got to do something before
Moo's body is excavated.
Before it's too late!
♪
(laughing)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪