♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
I summon you to awaken!
Rise, my ever‐changing,
crafty, and powerful warrior,
Metal Jell!
♪
Metal Jell,
this time we'll do in
that wretched group.
♪
That metal body gives
me goosebumps all over.
Metal Jell!
Just to make things
more interesting,
I'll awaken these
ones as well!
You sure?
(laughing maniacally)
♪
The stone has spoken.
All right, it's a brand new day,
so let's go find
that Phoenix!
Mocchi!
♪
It's hot.
Mocchi.
I'm starting to melt here.
Knock it off,
it's the same for everyone.
Oh, man.
Tiger's right,
we're all hot.
Knock it off, funny bunny.
Get off me.
Throw me a bone, Golem.
Hey, there's
something up ahead.
♪
Wonder what it is.
Ancient ruins, I think.
Let's go check it out.
Mocchi!
♪
Hmm, looks like this
is an Iron Bird.
Wonder if anyone's inside.
(screaming)
Huh?
(loud cawing)
♪
Somebody please help!
Help!
Ohh, I might as well give up
'cause no one's around
to hear me anyway.
I don't wanna be
trapped here forever.
I haven't even
had a boyfriend yet.
Huh?
♪
Uh, did you catch much of that?
Just the boyfriend part.
Yeah, well, how
about helping me out?
Sure you don't wanna
tell us any more secrets?
No, thank you.
I wouldn't have
said it if I knew
you were standing right there.
♪
Will you get me outta here?!
Go!
There.
You all right?
Yeah.
I don't think I'm
hurt or anything.
Thank you for
getting me out.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
Thank you, caw!
What's that,
a talking bird, 'chi?
This is my bird, Joy.
My name's Colt.
Hi, Colt.
I'm Genki, you may
have heard of me.
‐Mocchi!
‐Suezo!
‐I'm Hare!
‐Tiger.
Golem.
I'm Holly,
nice to meet you.
Hiya, Holly.
Wow, you're pretty.
But not as pretty as me.
(all groaning)
(caws)
♪
So, what are you people
doing way out here anyway?
You tell us first.
I'm traveling around
researching ancient ruins
and artifacts.
Research, research!
You'd think this area would
be crawling with Baddies.
Can't let that stop me.
I found a lot of
clues in the area
that'll help me to solve
the ancient mysteries.
Hmm.
Take that slate over there.
Huh?
♪
See all those squiggles?
It's a story written
in the ancient language
and it tells all
about the details
of the Last War.
Huh?
Go.
(screams)
That's an important artifact!
Yeah!
Oh, sorry.
Ahh.
Huh?
Sharpen your claws
somewhere else!
Huh?
At least I'm not
gonna ruin the ruins.
♪
No!
I hadn't even touched
that building yet!
Hm.
Something to say?
I'm sorry.
Apology accepted.
So, you never finished telling
me what you're doing here.
We're trying to find the Phoenix
so we can revive it
and stop Moo's evil plans.
The Phoenix?
Wasn't that
the legendary monster
that was created
in ancient times
to try to defeat
Moo during the war?
You seem to know
a lot about it.
Sure, 'cause I'm
trying to stop Moo too.
Stop Moo, rah!
So tell me, how do you
plan to find the Phoenix?
With this.
When I concentrate
on my Magic Stone,
it shows me the
direction to the Phoenix.
Yeah?
Let me see.
Holly wears it around
her neck like a pendant.
Pendant?
That's the name of
an ancient civilization.
Are you serious?
Yeah!
As a matter of fact,
these are Pendant ruins
that we're standing
on right here.
Huh?
♪
The Pendant civilization.
Come on, Mocchi!
♪
What is it, Genki?
Hang on a sec.
♪
Oh no.
It's the Baddies.
This is the crest
of the Baddies.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Baku's a pet
who does a brave deed ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ That kind of monster
is one that we need ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Beware the Knight Mocchis,
look sweet but they're not ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ You see them coming,
don't you get caught ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Metal Jell is a jell
with a 'tude ♪
♪ Don't wanna meet him
when he's in a mood ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
The crest for the Baddies
and the ancient Pendant
civilization are the same.
That's because Moo
was created right here
in Pendant.
(all gasping)
Pendant created Moo!
♪
The ancient
Pendant civilization
was the first to create
monsters through genetics.
They also developed
the technique
to seal monsters
in mystery disks.
♪
Then, things took
a turn for the worse.
The Last War broke out
and Pendant began to
send monsters to battle.
♪
Pendant built
an underground city
for its experiments in making
the perfect, vicious warrior.
♪
And in the end,
they created Moo.
♪
Moo brought out the evil
in the other monsters
and could turn them
into Baddies.
♪
Moo attacked everyone,
allies and enemies alike,
and almost every citizen
of Pendant was vanquished
by the very monsters
they had created.
Fortunately, the Pendant
scientists managed to escape
and with the help of
scientists from other countries,
they managed to
complete the Phoenix
and Final Gate.
♪
What happened to the Phoenix?
What do you mean?
Moo's soul and body
were separated
and after many years, he's
been reunited with his body.
But how about the Phoenix?
The Phoenix's body and soul
were also separated long ago.
In that case,
is the Magic Stone
leading us to the
Phoenix body or its soul?
Yeah, yeah,
that's a good question.
Mocchi!
Let me see.
Yeah?
I don't have a clue
where it's leading you.
(all groan)
(Colt giggles)
Colt, there's something
else I don't understand.
Huh?
Well, the people
in Holly's village
called the Magic Stone
the Pendant Stone.
You're right.
Even more mysterious
is that dagger of yours.
‐Huh?
♪
Some documents
I found in the ruins
had diagrams of a dagger
just like that one of yours.
Like Holly's?
It's probably a Pendant
artifact like the Magic Stone.
(all gasp)
That means Holly's villagers
must have been
descendants of Pendant.
‐Really?
‐No, couldn't be!
'chi!
And if that's true,
your Magic Stone's special.
Huh?
♪
Look out!
Lightning Attack!
♪
It's a Baddie!
Take heed, infidels,
I am the most powerful warrior
in the Jell army
and I go by the name
of Metal Jell.
♪
Dragon Punch!
Tongue Slap!
♪
Now I've got you
where I want you.
♪
‐I know how we can get this guy.
‐How?
Tiger, you hit him
with your Cold Air Bomb
and Blizzard, okay?
‐Got ya.
‐Huh?
♪
Did it!
Now, Golem, you punch him out!
Go!
♪
Wow!
Wow, wow!
Nice, he looked tough
but he was kind of a pushover.
Hm?
Someone's got our number.
(chanting "Mocchi")
♪
They're Baddies
but they're Mocchis!
'chi!
How could that be?
Get a load of all that
armor they're wearing.
They're Knight Mocchis.
Knight Mocchis?
That's right, foot soldiers
created during the Last War
in ancient times.
How harmless could
those puffballs be?
'chi!
(laughs uncomfortably)
‐No offense.
‐A Baddie is a Baddie.
Sure, but those things
look too much like Mocchi.
I don't know if I could
bear to fight them.
♪
(lasers shooting on "'chi!")
(laughing deviously)
Look, he's come back.
'chi.
Get them!
♪
Golem!
I'm all right.
Run, run!
Follow me, you guys.
‐Quick!
‐Run, run!
They're escaping!
Fire away!
(all yell "'chi")
♪
Where are we going?
I know a building
with a sturdy door.
I've never actually
gone inside
but I'm sure the Baddies
won't be able to get in.
This way, this way!
♪
Can you open it?
Golem will open.
♪
(grunting)
Don't give up, Golem!
(chanting "Mocchi")
Fire away!
♪
Golem, hurry!
(all yelling "'chi")
Hurry, everyone!
Get inside!
Right!
♪
(all yelling "'chi")
Go, keep firing!
♪
Let's go in further.
Good plan.
♪
Kinda chilly in here,
if you ask my opinion.
Yeah, and creepy.
Golem not like it.
'chi.
Come on.
Don't be going yellow on us.
Get off me right now!
Aw, be nice, Tiger.
I'm merely trying to help you
build up your muscle endurance.
Huh?
♪
What is this?
It looks like a factory.
♪
'chi!
Hey, the machines are blinkin'.
The Magic Stone.
♪
Look out!
(exclaiming)
♪
Are these machines
trying to get Holly?
No, I think it's the stone.
♪
Why are they after the stone?
It's something to do
with its energy.
They used a special
energy in ancient times
when they were
creating, locking up,
and fusing all
of their monsters.
‐Energy?
‐You mean my Magic Stone
has that special energy?
Possibly.
Huh?
‐Holly!
♪
Outta my way!
(whimpering)
Holly, we'll get ya down.
Hold on, Holly!
What do you want with her?
Stop, 'chi!
♪
Whoa.
Genki, do something!
We've gotta stop it.
Now!
It almost seems like
it's sucking the energy
out of the Magic Stone.
♪
They're Spirit Capsules!
So that's where
the power's coming from!
♪
Look, the whole place
is powering up.
♪
(gasping)
(yelling)
Go.
‐Holly, are you okay?
‐Yeah.
Holly, I'm positive
that Pendant stone
has the special energy needed
to create and lock up monsters.
Really?
♪
Yeah, 'cause as far as I know,
this is a monster
manufacturing plant.
‐This place...
‐... is a monster...
... factory?
What's a factory, 'chi?
Look, mystery disks.
♪
'chi!
Are you suggesting
that I was born
in this factory
full of test tubes?
Born in test tube,
born in test tube!
Quiet, bird!
Was Mocchi born here?
Mocchi.
(groans)
I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to upset you.
♪
I've got you this time.
'chi!
Huh, what is this place?
It's a monster
manufacturing factory.
(laughs)
Did you really think
I'd fall for that story?
Huh?
Hmm.
♪
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Don't just stand there,
destroy them!
♪
That's an order,
so move it!
'chi!
♪
You're in trouble!
This way!
♪
This time you're
not going to escape!
♪
(chanting "Mocchi")
The machines fired up
so this might work too.
♪
It started, get on!
Get them!
♪
Hang on tight!
Those poor Knight Mocchis,
I don't think they made it out.
They'll be lost disks by now.
'chi...
That's the end of
the Pendant civilization.
No, you're forgetting Moo.
And the Phoenix
and the stone.
And the Final Gate.
‐The battle has just started.
‐Yeah!
And it's our job
to make things right.
♪
Are you sure you'll be
okay on your own, Colt?
Yup.
I'll keep doing my research
but somewhere safer than here.
And if I come
across any Baddies,
I'll just escape
in my Iron Bird.
Baddies, Baddies, Baddies!
Hey, watch where you're peckin'!
I'm not a Baddie!
And don't forget
I've got my bodyguard.
You take care of yourselves.
Sure, you too, Colt.
Get my‐‐
I really hope it won't
take you too long
to find the Phoenix.
Thanks; Take care, Colt.
Bye, bye, 'chi!
I'll see ya!
Better get going.
Bye!
Bye, bye, 'chi!
Well, there she goes.
I'm gonna miss Colt.
Me too, but hopefully
we'll meet again
and she can tell us all about
the ancient civilizations.
Well, gang, it's about
time that we got going.
(cheering)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪