♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the Mystery Disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled Mystery Disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
I summon you to awaken.
Rise, unyielding and
invincible warrior.
Captain Astro!
♪
(loud stomping)
I'm impressed, Durahan.
He's beautiful.
At your service,
General Durahan.
Captain Astro,
our enemy has entered
the Madella Valley.
Sir?
Precisely.
That Madella Valley.
(growling)
Off with you!
Unleash your rage
and rid yourself
of that long‐standing grudge.
♪
(panting)
Go!
Ah, they're right behind us!
(panting)
(yelping)
We've gotta keep moving, Suezo.
I can't go on.
They're gonna catch us anyway,
so I'd like to get
a little rest in the meantime.
Oh, what are you saying,
you can't give up.
Chi!
Come on, Suezo, we just have
to make it out of this valley.
I assure you
my heart's in it
but my body just
ain't listenin'.
Go!
Where'd that army
come from anyway?
They've been coming after us now
for three days and three nights.
And it doesn't look like
they're the least bit tired.
Come on, they're getting
too close for comfort.
♪
(slurping)
Ah, good.
Huh?
(stomping approaching)
Let's go.
(panting)
♪
Halt.
Split up.
Yes, sir.
♪
(gasping)
We've come to a dead end.
Genki, let's go this way.
'Kay.
Huh?
(stomping)
Let's move it.
(gasping)
They're coming
from that side, too.
‐Ah!
‐And there, Chi.
They got us surrounded.
(stomping)
Halt.
Don't just stand there, tin man.
Hurry up and attack
if you're gonna.
(yelping)
I didn't mean that literally.
You won't soon forget the
taste of Astro vengeance.
Astro vengeance?
What are you talking about?
(grunting)
(cracking)
(screaming)
♪
That was a little
too close for comfort.
You aren't hurt or
anything, are you, gang?
Chi.
Don't worry about me or the
fact that I don't have hands.
I'll just pick myself up.
So where are the Baddies?
Still up there.
Well, at least
we're down here now.
We'd better get going.
Let's not waste any time.
Chi!
A cave.
That'd make a great hiding spot.
Still can't believe how
persistent that army was.
And it gave me the creeps
how quiet they were.
Army scared Mocchi.
They probably think
we're still lying
at the bottom of the cliff.
(gasping)
Oh, man.
It's huge.
What is it?
That's the biggest
thing I ever saw.
It's smashed up, Chi.
Maybe it's an ancient relic.
It still looks new,
but let's go see.
Good idea.
I get first dibs
on anything good!
Oh, no, you don't.
(grumbling)
(exclaiming)
Sure is quiet.
Shh.
♪
Someone help me, Chi!
Mocchi!
A space suit.
So in other words, that means...
(giggling)
What's the deal with him?
The pressure finally
gettin' to him?
Gang, it's a spaceship.
We found ourselves a spaceship!
Should we be excited?
Isn't that what the ancient
people used to fly in?
Mm‐hmm.
And they used these suits
to go out of the ship
and float around in space.
We found a spaceship!
(laughing)
♪ We found a spaceship,
we found a spaceship ♪
♪ A real live spaceship ♪
And apparently
that's a good thing.
Here it is.
And this, my friends,
is the cockpit.
(laughing)
Wonder if it works.
(whirring)
It works!
You know, I think you're right
about it being a spaceship,
and everything
seems to be running.
Chi.
Chi, Chi, Chi.
(exclaiming)
Man, that was fast.
We're in outer space already.
Golem can't see many stars.
The shiny one in the
middle must be a planet.
I'm almost sure of it.
It's so beautiful.
(laughing)
♪
(humming)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it and claim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Captain Black Dino,
one of Moo's best ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Leads the Black Dinos
on every conquest ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Little Spot Dino,
harmless enough ♪
♪ To unlock a Kuro,
you gotta be tough ♪
♪ Captain Kuro will
stomp and brawl ♪
♪ These monsters rule,
unlock them all ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(gasping)
What's the matter, Genki?
(whimpering)
(gasping)
Lost disks!
I don't understand
what Lost Disks
would be doing here.
Look, there's a bunch
over here as well.
Yeah.
I am not gettin' good vibes
about the people of this ship.
Let's keep on exploring.
We may be able to
find some answers.
Follow me.
♪
I don't believe it.
(gasping)
♪
This must have been
the confinement cell.
And by the looks of it,
the person in confinement
must have broken out.
Holly's right.
Look at that chain.
Handcuffs.
♪
It's just like the one that
that Baddie had on his wrist.
That's impossible.
So, we meet again.
(gasping)
How'd he find us in here?
I see you found the prison
where my people were
locked up for so long.
I don't think I'm following.
This spaceship looks like
it's thousands of years old.
That's right, we've lived
through thousands of years
of imprisonment in order
to get revenge on humans,
and you'll be the first to go!
(zapping)
(grunting)
No, Tiger!
Come on, you guys,
let's get him!
Chi!
♪
After thousands of years,
at last I can take
my revenge on humans.
Could you at least tell us
why you have such
a grudge against us?
I'd be more than glad to share
what your ancestors
did to my people.
The ancient ones used up
all the resources
on their own planet
and were forced to
go to outer space
in search for new resources.
That's where my people came in.
The humans made us
toil night and day
searching for resources.
(grunting)
(electricity zapping)
♪
We were strong,
but our human overseers
pushed us too far.
(grunting)
♪
We tried to reason with them,
but the humans were relentless.
(grumbling)
Unable to withstand
the terrible hardships,
morale was low,
and we lost many of our people.
But the humans
didn't stop there.
They experimented to find ways
to make us endure even
harsher working conditions.
(groaning)
Those who were unable to
keep up with the labor quotas
were sent to be disposed of.
(distant groaning)
(grumbling)
♪
Listen carefully,
and you might be able
to hear the screams
of agony and rage even today.
♪
In the end,
something happened
that even the humans
couldn't have predicted.
An accident that happened
on the way back to our planet.
The explosion took care
of the humans for us,
but we hadn't
gained our freedom.
The ship's controls
were damaged,
and we floated through space
for thousands of years.
But the Astros found
a way to survive.
We used cryogenics and froze
ourselves to conserve energy.
As fate would have it,
one day our ship veered
too close to this planet
and began to enter
its atmosphere.
(rumbling)
Our ship crash‐landed
into a mountainside.
♪
(crashing)
We couldn't have known
we were being watched.
Master Moo found us
and released us
from the prison
humans had placed us in
so many years before.
Revenge.
You must seek revenge
for your fellow Astros.
Declare war on the humans.
♪
Not all humans are bad people.
Take us, for example.
We live with these monsters,
and we get along just fine.
At least give us a chance, huh?
I know you'll change your mind
once you get to know us.
Never!
I will never be able
to trust humans again.
There are good humans.
I wouldn't lie.
I've heard enough!
Run for it!
You won't escape me!
♪
(panting)
Head for that hole!
♪
(yelling)
(grunting)
Hey, are you all right, Genki?
Yeah, Holly.
I think I'll make it.
Oh, sure, you had a landing pad.
Where are we?
What kind of room is this?
I don't know.
Huh?
(gasping)
Listen carefully
and you might be able
to hear the screams
of agony and rage even today.
(whimpering)
It's hard to believe
that something this
terrible happened.
The Astros were worked
like slaves by the humans
and were scrapped as soon
as they got worn down.
That's horrible.
(sobbing)
♪
Don't cry, Genki.
It's true that those people who
enslaved the Astros were bad,
but you're living proof
that not all humans are evil.
I'm sure even Captain Astro
will come to see that.
(sniffling)
Yeah.
Mm‐hm.
But first, we've got
to find a way out.
There's a task for ya.
Huh?
The walls.
They're getting closer!
(trembling)
(grunting)
Do something quick
or we'll be squished!
(groaning)
Got any other ideas?
(grunting)
(Astro laughing)
Captain Astro!
I'll give you a taste of
your own medicine, humans.
Then you'll know how
my people suffered.
This isn't working!
Farewell, humans.
♪
Huh?
‐The walls have been stopped.
I don't understand,
what happened?
(creaking)
(groaning)
Come on, we gotta get
them out of there.
Go!
♪
You won't get away.
Oh.
♪
Let's go and save
Tiger and the others.
Gotcha.
(loud stomp)
Captain Astro.
Stand back, people!
(yelping)
Suezo!
Hang on a second.
You don't have any beefs
with me, Captain Astro.
Oh yeah?
You've got no reason
to fight with me.
Sure I do!
Hey, I understand that you
feel bad about your friends,
but you can't keep
living with a grudge.
That is such
a pathetic way to live.
You understand?
What do you know about losing
all your friends the way I did?
Nothing!
Don't do it, Astro.
(grunting)
♪
(splashing)
Genki, no!
♪
(yelling)
I got ya!
(groaning)
♪
Are you all right, Genki?
Where's Astro?
I don't think he made it.
Wait, Genki!
♪
Astro!
Genki, he's down there!
‐Suezo.
‐Don't say another word!
(yelling)
♪
Huh?
(groaning)
We've got ya, Astro.
Don't worry.
Why are you helping me?
I can't hold on much longer.
‐Let go of me.
‐No way.
‐We'll both fall.
‐I won't let go.
Hang on, Genki!
(groaning)
I'm losing my grip on him.
Don't let go of him now, Suezo.
Release me!
I'm never letting go!
(screaming)
Genki!
‐Genki!
(screaming)
At least the boy
can be saved.
♪
You're safe, Genki.
What happened to Astro?
♪
Astro, where are you?
(panting)
♪
Astro!
‐Astro!
Astro, where are you?
Astro!
Huh?
You're against the Astro army.
Fire.
Wait a second,
you don't understand.
♪
(grunting)
Astro, you're safe!
Yes, now tell me,
why did you put
your life in danger
in order to save me?
♪
'Cause deep down,
you seemed like
a good monster to me.
I just wanted to get
to know you better.
A human wanted
to get to know me?
Huh.
If only I'd met a kind
human like you sooner.
(electricity zapping)
(groaning)
Astro!
♪
I finally found
peace in my heart.
Now it can rest in peace.
Don't say that, Astro.
Come on, get up.
I have one last favor to ask.
Tell my people here
that the fight is over.
Tell them to forget
about getting revenge.
They should enjoy
their freedom
and live with peace
in their hearts.
Don't say that.
It's not over yet, Astro.
Please, stop talking
like your life is over.
Stay with us.
We're just getting
to know each other.
Please stay, Astro.
Astro, hold on!
♪
(whimpering)
Astro!
(echoing)
♪
Chi.
(sobbing)
♪
Huh?
(growling)
No, Tiger.
♪
(whirring)
Where are they going, Chi?
I think they're going to
enjoy their newfound freedom.
I think you're right
about that, Holly.
They're going to find
themselves a new way of life.
I hope they succeed.
They will,
if they work together.
Good luck, tin men!
♪
Well, we'd better be
on our way, Genki.
Yeah.
♪
Hey, that reminds me.
Aren't you forgetting
something, Genki?
That's right, this is
the part where you jump up!
Come on, say it for us now.
Huh?
Chi.
Mocchi.
All right,
you talked me into it.
Come on, gang, let's get movin'!
Yeah!
(cheering)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪