♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
♪
(sighs)
(laughter)
♪
Oh.
(laughs)
Hmm.
♪
(laughs)
Oh‐‐ah!
Oh, I have an announcement!
It looks like the
fuel for the flame
has run out!
Oh!
Don't worry.
We've almost made
it to the other side.
We're gonna hit the rocks!
♪
I don't feel so good!
Going down!
Oh, boy, how are we
gonna get out of this?
Can the hot air, please.
Hot air is exactly
what we do need!
Any ideas?
Anyone?
(sniffs)
Well, this is it, then.
I'm glad to have known
you all, and I've...
Suezo, what's the
deal with Golem?
He's the heaviest.
He's gonna have to jump off,
nobly sacrificing himself
to save the rest
of us, of course.
Uh‐uh.
(yelling)
♪
Out of the way!
(cheering)
♪
Mission accomplished!
Genki, exactly how
do we land this thing?
Uh‐oh, that's the
little detail I forgot.
Hmm?
Ahhh!
Let's try and circle!
♪
(yelling)
Gotta jump!
We're way too high!
Now!
♪
Jump!
(yelling)
♪
Huh?
(explosion)
Phew, that was close!
'chi!
Oh, boy.
Is everyone okay?
I'm just great!
But, the Iron Bird is history.
So much for easy traveling.
Don't be so blue.
Even if we can't fly,
our legs are all right.
We'll be able to walk to
the ends of the earth!
'chi!
Don't you two
ever get bummed out?
Nah.
Even if I did, I'd just
cover it up with a laugh.
(laughing)
♪
(sighs)
(clanging)
♪
This is most annoying, Big Blue.
Neither the evil Hares,
nor Captain Clay
was able to stop them.
I know.
I'm sorry, Pixie.
It's not good.
The troublemakers have
crossed Heaven's Canyon,
and now, I have been informed
that they are
approaching our sector.
My apologies.
You don't understand.
If we don't stop these
troublemakers now,
we'll be hearing from
Master Moo himself.
Yes, we'll concentrate all
our efforts on finding them.
Moo will be pleased.
♪
The mystery disk lies
in that direction.
Okay, I'm ready to roll!
Let's go find
that mystery disk.
Yeah!!
♪
I am so sick of rocks,
rocks, and more rocks!
Relax, Suezo, we have to come
to a village sooner or later.
♪
We're first to the top!
Ahh!
Gotta keep quiet.
♪
This doesn't look good.
What's happening?
Huh?
They're the Clays,
they're Moo's men!
'chi.
And they've got
humans as slaves.
Mining mystery disks.
(groaning)
♪
Right to a Clay!
(whipping sound)
No!
No laziness permitted.
All right, now I'm mad!
Wait, Genki!
Let's have Hare
make a plan first.
Now, let me see.
Judging from the
number of Clays,
we should wait until‐‐
I'm not waiting!
'chi!
♪
He never stops.
Hey, you!
Huh?
♪
Turbo!
(yelling)
(groans)
♪
You've been warned.
Who are you people?
Slaves.
(Clays laugh)
Just a momentary setback.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it,
reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Is it a Jell,
the slippery fool ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Or Captain Jell,
these monsters rule ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Worm from below,
explodes with a force ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Clays and their
Captain have no remorse ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Jump, smash, and roar,
get off the floor ♪
♪ These monsters bite ♪
♪ Unlock 'em today ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
♪
Pixie has been expecting you,
and your friends.
Pixie?
Who's this Pixie?
Mistress Pixie to you, son!
She's one of Moo's
Big Bad Four,
and someone that you
should be afraid of!
It's none of their
business, do you hear me?
♪
Prisoners, you'll do
exactly as I say!
♪
Just because you outnumber us
doesn't mean you've won.
Oh yeah?
And how could you win now?
With the Cold Bullet!
♪
(yells)
(yelling)
♪
Ahhh!
Well, I...guess
we showed them
a thing or two, huh, Mocchi?
'chi...
♪
(yells)
(yelling)
♪
Cherry Blossom Blizzard, 'chi!
Wow, Mocchi, a new attack!
Mocchi!
(yells)
♪
Withdraw!
(yelling)
♪
Guess we showed them!
Ha!
Everyone, everything
is all right now.
♪
That was not a very
good thing you did.
They're Baddies,
what are you talking about?
If we work here quietly
and don't cause any trouble,
we get no trouble in return.
By resisting the Clays, you
just signed up for big trouble.
We don't want to
be dragged into it.
How brave.
Mocchi!
Well, isn't that just
like a human for ya.
You gotta leave here
before they come back.
Don't you want to escape?
Ha, you don't understand.
No one escapes from here.
♪
But we will take
care of the Baddies.
Good luck.
Get going!
That's right, go home!
Yeah!
‐Get outta here.
‐Go home!
We don't need your kind here.
(growls)
Tiger, stop it, now.
Everybody, listen.
♪
Let's believe in these people.
Huh?
Even if we continue working
here without making trouble,
Pixie will never free us.
But, Mickey...
You got it.
Do you really want to be slaves
for the rest of your lives?
♪
Mickey, if we make a mistake,
it could go very badly for us.
Listen to yourself
and just think about
what you're saying!
We won't get another
chance like this.
Right, let's go for it.
Yeah, man, freedom!
Right on!
That's what we need.
Like I said, we're
willing to help you out.
We'll stay here and
deal with the Baddies
and that will give you
some time to get away.
‐Yeah!
‐How can we ever repay you?
Hurry up and go.
You're an eyesore.
Let's go now, everyone!
♪
Come on!
Will you explain just one thing?
Sure, what is it?
Just between you and me,
how bad can this
Pixie monster be?
I mean, with a
name like "Pixie."
Pretty bad.
Just ask the people
in North Town.
What's happening there?
She's got a stranglehold
on the whole town.
All the humans and monsters
are under her control.
Word is, Moo is looking
for something really big.
And Pixie works for Moo?
I wonder what big thing
Moo is looking for.
♪
To have a chance,
we gotta go now.
Good luck, and take
care of yourselves.
You too, my friends.
♪
Captain Clay, explain to me
why you came
running back here.
Kume, I thought
that reporting to you
was first priority,
Master Pixie.
Explain to me why
I would want you here
when you could be
capturing them there?
Kume, a small lapse
in judgment.
I'll gather the troops
and return immediately, Master.
Never mind.
Huh?
Disappear.
♪
Please, give me another chance.
I‐‐I promise, I‐‐I...
(whimpering)
Oh, no!
♪
Kume!
(laughs)
♪
Now, Big Blue, prepare.
I can handle this
mission for you myself.
Yes, but I'll go too,
just to pass the time.
There's‐‐there's
one more thing, Master.
Hmm?
It's about the
slaves who've escaped.
Have they been caught?
Just one so far, but...
♪
You run, I'll try
to buy us some time.
(yelling)
♪
This should prove to be
interesting entertainment.
(laughs)
♪
I don't see anything yet.
They're there.
The Clays are probably
watching us right now.
♪
The unknown here is Pixie.
Wow, she sounds like
a regular cutie pie!
Mm‐hmm.
Uh...
♪
Expect the worst,
and never, never
underestimate your
enemies, my friends.
That's good, solid advice.
Hare, my advice to you
is watch and learn, buddy.
Watch and learn.
Strong Tiger, 'chi!
That's right.
Don't underestimate.
Baddies have all
kinds of tricks.
Here's the plan.
All we have to do is
hold the Baddies' attention
until the humans
have time to escape.
If we get into trouble,
we'll retreat.
I never retreat.
Hmm?
Ahh, they're here!
♪
That's Pixie!
She looks harmless enough,
but she's one of
Moo's top Baddies.
They're the ones everyone
calls the Big Bad Four.
Pixie...
♪
That Pixie doesn't
look so bad to me.
She looks lonesome.
Hmm?
That big blue fella is
awfully big, isn't he?
Yeah.
Taking that guy on
will be my pleasure.
♪
Show yourselves, fools!
Come out now!
We have a friend of yours.
(gasping)
Cooperate, and you'll
make it easy for him.
Oh, no, what are we
supposed to do now?
'chi!
Do as he says.
Holly, look, we can't go
out there and face them.
We're easily outnumbered
by about 100 to 1!
But Hare, it's our fault
they've got Mickey,
so we can't just
leave him, can we?
Nope.
And those are just
the kind of odds
that make it a challenge.
What's the problem?
No problem!
Ha, that's our enemy?
♪
A couple of kids
and some scruffy monsters?
Hardly worth our trouble.
What, what did you say?
What's your name, kid?
I'm afraid you just made
your first mistake, big fella!
Lesson one: never
underestimate your enemy, pal.
And that's all the free advice
you're going to get from me!
Genki's my name,
and we're number one!
You can quote me on that!
Well, well, Genki,
it's nice to meet you.
But didn't your mother
ever teach you
that little boys shouldn't brag?
What did you say?
(growling)
Surrender!
Genki, that's not how to win.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
All right, we'll come down,
but you have to promise
to let Mickey go.
I have never
surrendered to anybody.
Tiger!
This isn't your call, Tiger.
The plan is that we give in now,
and then come up
with a plan later, okay?
(growls)
What are you doing?
Humans will be slaves.
Master Moo will turn
the monsters into Baddies.
(chuckles)
Great planning,
Hare, great planning.
You made a promise.
You said you'd release that man.
So, what about it, Pixie?
I'm so terrible with promises,
I just never ever keep them.
(laughs)
A promise is a promise!
'chi!
♪
(gasp)
Huh?
♪
Doesn't a promise
mean anything anymore?
Nobody touches Pixie!
(yells)
♪
What a foolish boy you are.
(exclaiming)
I think such bravery
should be rewarded,
don't you, Blue?
Huh?
Let him go!
♪
I just hate to repeat myself.
That's lesson one.
I won't lose!
Mocchi!
(growls)
Don't move!
♪
You hear me?
'chi!
‐Double Pounder, Mocchi!
‐'chi!
♪
And now the
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
Try this!
Cherry Blossom Blizzard, 'chi!
Flame Wall!
♪
(yelling)
You still haven't won, Pixie!
Oh yes, I have.
Lightning!
(lightning zaps)
(yelling)
♪
‐Genki!
‐Mocchi!
♪
I win, you lose.
Oh my goodness me.
I think they've gone and
they didn't say goodbye.
How rude.
♪
Genki, Mocchi?
(groaning)
♪
(yells)
There's no way
I'm going to lose.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪