♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(television static)
Huh?
It can't be!
♪
I don't believe it.
Nooo!
♪
(screaming)
(whimpering)
♪
(rain pattering)
(yelling)
♪
I have to get back!
Mocchi, Suezo, Holly?
(panting)
Where are you?
♪
(shouting)
What's happening?
(grunting)
♪
Mocchi!
'chi?
♪
Ahh, Mocchi!
Oh!
Look at your beautiful face!
♪
It's really you,
it's really you!
It was all just a bad dream!
♪
(laughing)
‐What a great, great day!
‐'chi?
‐Yahoo!
‐'chi!
Hey everybody, my
heart's a‐poundin'!
Holly, Tiger!
Hare, Suezo!
Genki, it's awfully early.
(yawning)
Anybody home?
Suezo, you're sleeping
the whole day away.
♪
(groaning)
Golem, you're a
dangerous yawner.
My heart's a‐poundin',
poundin', poundin',
poundin', poundin', poundin'.
Some of us were trying
to sleep, you know.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Wakey wakey!
Suezo?
Suezo.
Suezo!
Suezoooo!
I'm awake!
♪
(chewing noisily)
Doo‐dee‐doo‐dee‐doo‐doo.
(growling)
Wow, that was quite a dream.
What a strange kid you are.
All upset because you
thought you'd gone back
to where you came from.
Well, sure, I miss my parents,
and I do wanna see my friends.
It's just, I‐‐
‐Mmm, good.
‐Ahhh!
(laughing)
Look what I'd be missing.
♪
‐Between you and this rain‐‐
‐Look at it this way,
it's a chance for us to spend
some quality time together.
Right, Golem?
♪
Rain soak into rock.
Not nice.
No point in going on
till the rain lets up.
‐Hmmm.
‐That sounds good to me.
‐Holly?
‐Yes?
We can all sit around the
fire, and tell each other
stories about ourselves.
Do you wanna?
Like, where are you from,
and who are your folks?
♪
Holly?
Genki, you go and
wash yourself up.
‐But I already did.
‐Then go and do it again!
‐What did I do?
‐Just do it!
Tell me!
Genki, smarten up!
You know, even for a human
being, you're pretty thick.
Now please, change the subject.
Huh?
‐Don't you get it?
‐Get what?
Genki doesn't get it,
so Mocchi don't get it.
‐Hmm.
‐It's all right, Suezo.
Holly.
I knew that I'd have to talk
about it one of these days.
Thanks for protecting me,
but if you can't talk about
your sadness with your friends,
then you can't talk
about it with anybody.
It was raining that day too.
♪
(rain pouring)
(whimpering)
♪
My father left on a
day just like this.
♪
Daddy!
Daddy.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters Rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Mocchi is pink,
but Mocchi is tough ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Zuum Troops and their
captain play kinda rough ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Suezo looks far,
soars through the skies ♪
♪ Lookin' for Rockies,
they aren't bad guys ♪
♪ Horn the pirate
says that he's pure
but he's a monster,
can you be sure? ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it,
unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
We lived in a small
village where people
and monsters work together.
Digging wells and
cultivating fields,
mining for coal.
Sometimes we'd use
the magic stone to find
a mystery disk to
increase our number.
And always, we lived in peace.
♪
The new head of
our village is Abel!
(cheering)
It's an honor, sir, I thank you.
Mmmm.
Because my father
lost the election,
he had to leave, forever.
I humbly thank you all.
We're all counting on you, Abel!
♪
Only the head of the village
can possess the magic stone,
and the ability to
control the special powers
that are locked deep within.
♪
Daddy, where did you go?
Oh my, someone's at
my meditation spot.
(gasping)
It's Holly, my word.
The pebbles, they‐‐
she has the power.
Holly!
Come here, child.
‐This power, the pebbles.
‐Grandfather!
‐How long?
‐Forever.
When I come here,
the pebbles glow,
and they make me feel better.
Grandfather, is it
wrong of me to do that?
No, Holly, it's a
special gift you have,
but it must remain our secret.
‐Understand?
‐Mhm.
♪
I missed my parents, but the
village elder was kind to me
and raised me as
if I were his own.
I had no shortage of playmates.
I loved the monsters
and they loved me.
♪
Life for everyone was wonderful,
and I thought it would
always be that way.
Everyone did.
Then one day,
five years later...
That, my dear,
is a mystery disk.
I did it, I found a
mystery disk on my own!
Wow!
♪
Unlock!
(whooshing)
♪
Hiya!
Look, it's a Suezo!
‐Nice to meet you.
‐Likewise!
Although, I gotta say, you're
a pretty funny‐lookin' bunch.
What did you say?
‐Well, you see, I‐‐
‐Ah, please give me strength.
Listen, you little eyeball,
nobody likes a smart aleck,
especially me!
(laughing)
♪
Oh, well, now I
understand you, Suezo.
‐You were born this way.
‐Yup, that's it!
What's the rest of
the story, Holly?
Well, it was two
years after Suezo came.
♪
It was raining that night too.
(thunder rumbling)
♪
(lightning crackling)
(growling)
♪
(evil laughter)
Holly, wake up.
♪
‐What's wrong, Grandfather?
‐Moo's army has come.
Moo?
Moo is the ultimate evil
who turns good monsters
into bad ones.
But I thought it was just
a scary story for kids!
Unfortunately, Moo exists,
and I'm very afraid
that our little village
cannot hold out against him.
What?
♪
Now, quickly, hide in here
until I tell you it's safe.
Holly, there's little time!
(shouting and gasping)
(distant yelling)
‐I wanna fight them too!
‐Yeah, me too!
‐Holly, you can't.
‐But I wanna stay with you.
‐You must stay safe.
‐Your gift must be protected.
‐It is our legacy.
‐Suezo, you must protect Holly.
I will, you betcha!
Here, child, take this.
‐What for?
‐It belongs to you.
‐It's mine?
‐Mhm.
You will know what to
do when the time comes.
♪
Naga, we only want to
live and work in peace!
And we want the magic stone!
Naga, you know that stone's
under our guardianship.
It has mystical powers.
It will show us mystery disks
so we can build Moo's army!
No, you mustn't!
One day, Moo will
take over your world!
Give us the stone
and you can join us!
Never.
Then you can deal
with the wrath of Moo.
For Moo!
(growling)
♪
(screeching)
(crashing)
♪
(evil laughter)
Is it safe?
I think so.
No!
(gasping)
Grandfather, Grandfather!
What happened?
Holly, Naga came,
and the others are...
lost disks now.
No, it can't be.
It can't be!
Moo's forces were too strong.
Our good friends
are gone forever.
Forgive me, for I was the one
who sent your father into exile.
His power over the
magic stone was so great
that it frightened me.
I thought such
power would one day
bring disaster to our village.
‐Grandfather.
‐Holly,
if he had been here to
fight against Moo's forces,
things would've been different.
‐Do you have the bag I gave you?
‐Right here, Grandfather.
Open it.
‐Huh?
♪
‐The stone!
You have your
father's powers, Holly.
You must take the magic stone
and find the mystery disk
that contains the
ancient Phoenix.
What's a Phoenix?
Only the Phoenix has the power
to revive the lost monsters.
But Grandfather, I don't know
what I'm supposed to do.
If the legend is true,
the Phoenix will revive
the lost monsters, and transform
the bad monsters into good ones.
It's the only hope we have
of defeating the evil Moo.
♪
I'm counting on you.
We're all counting on you.
♪
(birds chirping)
(gasping)
♪
The Phoenix!
The magic stone has always
led me in the right direction,
from the very first.
We must go.
Great, I'm with you!
And so Suezo and I set off,
going wherever the magic
stone told us to go.
(rain pattering)
Ohhh.
So that's why you're
on the journey, huh?
Hey, did you ever meet
up with your dad again?
Mm‐mm.
Genki.
And I vowed I'd never cry again.
‐Holly.
‐'chi.
♪
(indistinct remarks)
Genki, at times like this,
you have to lighten the mood.
‐Hare is right!
‐For once.
Hey!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the amazing Genki!
‐Huh?
‐Genki!
Ta‐da, and now I'm going
to sing you a song.
♪ It's raining, it's
pouring, Suezo is snoring ♪
♪ He fell in a puddle
and got in a muddle
but at least he
won't be boring ♪
Yeah, all right, this is fun,
come on you guys, join in!
It's so cool, yeah, all right!
He's gaga.
One more time,
everybody, jump and sing!
♪ While the rain comes
down and hits the ground
with a splashy sound ♪
Yeah, all right, yeah!
♪ Everybody jumps
and dances around ♪
Mocchi!
♪ The drops go bloop,
the flowers droop ♪
♪ The sun comes out, we all go
doodly‐oodly, scroodly‐noodly ♪
♪ Doodly‐poodly, puddly‐wuddly ♪
♪ Duddly‐fuddly, woozy‐woozy ♪
♪ Woodle‐woozy,
doozy‐doozy‐doo ♪
♪ Doo‐doo‐doo‐doo‐doo‐doo ♪
Gaga.
Golem sing too.
‐Huh?
♪
'chi!
Tiger, Suezo, Hare!
Come on, it's fun!
‐It's just silly!
‐Shall we?
Why not?
Career's have been made on less.
Gaga too.
♪ Gabba‐gabba, gabba‐gabba,
gabba‐gabba, gabba ♪
gabba‐gabba, gab ♪
♪ Gabba‐gabba hey,
gabba‐gabba ho ♪
♪ Gabba‐gabba, gabba‐gabba,
gabba‐gabba, gab ♪
Genki.
(singing gibberish)
♪
‐Genki?
‐It's so silly.
‐Holly.
‐What?
Hey!
(laughing)
♪
From now on, the rain
will make me happy.
♪
'chi!
Huh?
Holly!
But it's raining,
for goodness sake!
Don't they know enough
to come in out of the‐‐
(shouting)
(groaning)
Okay, ready to sing.
Too late, no more singing.
(chuckling manically)
(laughing)
♪
Oh, thank you everyone.
Aw shucks, Holly,
you're our pal.
Huh, look.
♪
Rain gone.
Sunshine 'chi!
It's gonna be a wonderful day!
I can tell these things.
Hey, let's move out, people!
Gabba‐gabba, gabba‐gabba hey!
(cheering)
‐Wait, my turn!
‐It's too late!
(laughing)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪