♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the Mystery Disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled Mystery Disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(lightning crashing)
♪
Ah, my beloved
collection of warriors!
Ooh, what a shame.
Your collection
is getting smaller.
No great loss.
They were defeated.
Well, I have a great idea
for getting rid of them,
and you won't even have to dip
into your precious collection.
You do?
(laughing)
Ah, Lilim.
Ever so cunning and devious.
You know that's what
I love about you.
Now, you must share
your plan with me.
(lightning crashing)
♪
(groaning)
I'm soaked!
I'll get you something
to wipe yourself off.
Pass.
Anything of yours is
bound to be filthy.
The important thing is
to keep an eye on that.
Right.
♪
All right!
Hey, look, gang,
the sun's comin' out.
Looks like it's gonna
be a beautiful day!
We'd better get
looking for some food.
We're out of everything.
Chi.
Where's Tiger?
Tiger, Tiger!
What's wrong?
Time to find food!
Mm‐hm.
Didn't you hear us?
We'd been calling you.
Oh, sorry.
(gasping)
Ignore me.
♪
Go?
You wanna play the web
game to see who goes?
All right, and the three people
who end up with Xes
will have to go
and search for food.
Golem go first.
Start here.
(humming)
And it's an X.
(screaming)
'Kay, I'm next!
(slurping)
Now, start here.
(humming)
And it's another X.
(screaming)
Now, let's just see
where Tiger will start.
I'll take this line then.
(humming)
And we have an X!
Ha‐ha, that gives us
our three volunteers!
Show us the whole thing!
Something's fishy here!
(Hare whimpering)
(all gasping)
‐Hare!
Drop it.
(all gasping)
Being cooped up with all
that rain made me stiff,
so I'll go.
(all gasping)
It's nice out.
I could use the exercise.
(gasping)
Wait up, Tiger,
I'll go with you.
Chi!
Let's catch up with him.
(laughing)
Climb on, Mocchi.
♪
Back with some food!
What's with Tiger?
I can't believe
he volunteered.
Actually, he's pretty kind
once you get to know him.
Ha, I'm not falling for that.
Got one!
(laughing)
♪
(grunting)
I'll get 'em.
♪
Hey, good work.
I don't know what you guys
would do if I weren't around.
That day's not gonna come,
so there's no problem.
♪
‐Listen.
‐Yeah?
Kid, I got something
I gotta tell ya.
‐What's up?
‐You've got to develop
your own survival skills,
not rely on others.
‐Meaning?
‐One of these days,
you might find yourself
all on your own.
Then you'll only have
yourself to rely on.
♪
Tiger?
They're late.
Hey, I'm sure
they'll be back soon.
Suezo, do you see anything yet?
(groaning)
♪
Huh?
Enemy!
♪
(zapping)
(screaming)
♪
Tail Attack!
What are you attackin' us for?
I don't see
a Baddie crest on you,
so what have you got against us?
My name is Jagd Hound,
and my orders are
to destroy you.
(screaming)
♪
(grunting)
Chi!
♪
(zapping)
Chironimo!
Tiger, cover me!
♪
(shouting)
Get him!
♪
Oh, no, he's gettin' away!
No, he's not.
Wait, Tiger.
It's too dangerous to go alone.
We know he's not a Baddie,
so I'm gonna find out why
he wanted to attack us.
♪
Wait, Tiger!
(panting)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Don't pet Jagd Hound
'cause he will attack ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Unless he decides
to do a backtrack ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Half‐horse and half‐man,
Chariot will fight ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Any old creature
he finds in his sight ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ If you were End‐Bringer,
would you call it a day? ♪
♪ I wouldn't bet on it ♪
♪ Forget it, no way ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Huh?
Lilim!
Jagd Hound has returned.
Took him long enough.
♪
So, what happened?
Did you finish them?
Halt!
Nothing to worry about.
Hands off that baby.
(chuckling)
You'll get him back.
When you're done,
that is to say.
It's impossible to
destroy them all at once.
That's a lame excuse
for someone's who done in
more than one Baddie.
It will take a while on my own.
Are you suggesting I
lend you some soldiers?
Unbelievable.
I'll consider it,
but first bring me back one
of them to prove yourself.
Then I'll send these evil
Hares to help you out.
(grumbling)
(growling)
What a dirty trick.
(whimpering)
Huh?
♪
Follow after Jagd Hound!
Let's split up!
Call if you find him.
♪
(zapping)
You won't escape.
Surrender.
You allowed that kid
to get kidnapped,
and now you're
forced to attack us.
You're pathetic.
Silence!
Why does that baby
mean so much to you
that you'd come after us?
‐Hmph!
‐Can't you at least tell me why?
Might as well.
It's not like you'll
be doing much gossiping
when I'm done with you.
A human took me in
when I was a puppy
and raised me in a village.
They took good care of me.
♪
But one day,
the Baddies came and
attacked the village.
♪
I did what I could,
but the village was in ruins.
Take care of my son.
♪
I vowed to protect
that baby with my life.
It was the only way
I could repay the villagers
for all their kindness.
I planned to take the
child to a safe village.
♪
The Baddies kept on attacking,
but somehow we got around them.
Up until they got
their dirty hands
on the baby, you mean.
That's right,
they kidnapped him
and ordered me
to destroy you.
Sounds like something they'd do.
Don't take it personally.
(lightning crashing)
♪
So there you are.
Huh?
Hurry up and get it over with.
Lilim's waitin' for ya.
Huh, are you really
gonna take orders
from a little bunny like that?
I've heard all I want
to hear from you.
(zapping)
♪
Lilim, Jagd Hound has returned.
Hmm.
♪
I've been waiting.
Where's Tiger?
♪
(Lilim laughing)
Can't find him anywhere.
Anywhere.
Us either.
And we searched
everywhere we could think of.
Golem worried about Tiger.
Jagd Hound is strong.
How can you say that?
Tiger's way stronger,
and he'd never lose a battle!
Here's a change, seeing
you stand up for him.
I'm not standing up for him.
Does Tiger know he's got a fan?
(screaming)
Let's just change the subject
since we can't do
anything anyway!
I'm with you, bunny buddy.
It's late, and it doesn't look
like the rain's gonna stop.
We'll search again
tomorrow, okay?
Yeah!
Sure.
♪
(birds chirping)
(grunting)
♪
This is the forest where we
looked for Tiger yesterday.
Chi.
I wonder if Tiger's here.
It sure is creepy.
Go.
♪
So, they came for him.
Are you ready to finish
off what you started?
Hmph.
There's no sense in our
waiting here anymore.
Right.
(shouting)
(clearing throat)
I don't really think we'll
be needing this baby anymore.
Right.
Yoo‐hoo, Tiger!
Where are you?
Tiger!
Tiger, Chi!
Tiger, where are you?
Not here.
(gasping)
(shouting)
(grunting)
‐Jagd Hound!
Your friend Tiger
is not coming back.
‐What?
‐Go.
Why should we believe you?
'Cause it's the truth.
(chuckling)
Baddies!
♪
Here you go.
This is what's left
of your friend.
(gasping)
No!
♪
That's Tiger's Mystery Disk.
(gasping)
♪
Tiger.
Chi.
♪
I don't believe it.
Ohh.
♪
Who am I supposed to fight
with now that Tiger's gone?
♪
(whimpering)
Then you'll only have
yourself to rely on.
♪
Chi.
You're the one who
did this to Tiger.
What do you want
to do about it?
(screaming)
♪
Enough.
Back off.
Just let them tire
themselves out,
and then you can move in
and finish them off.
(screaming)
♪
Stop!
Huh?
Stand back.
Let me get him.
For Tiger.
(laughing)
Very amusing, but do you
really think you can get me?
Chi?
♪
(grunting)
Oh, hurry up and finish him off.
I haven't got all day, you know.
(chuckling)
I'm having a lot more
fun that I thought.
♪
(shouting)
No!
Let me at him!
Genki, look out!
(gasping)
♪
(screaming)
(zapping)
♪
(explosion)
What?
Huh?
Tiger.
It's you!
♪
‐Tiger!
You're really alive.
Chi!
Tiger!
♪
Sorry I'm late.
Tiger.
No!
How could this have happened?
Jagd Hound, you've got the kid.
You tricked me!
Villain!
Then where did the
Mystery Disk come from?
Are you sure you
want to find out?
(lightning crashing)
Only one evil Hare followed us.
(shouting)
♪
I've got an idea.
So you've been patting
yourself on the back
when actually this Mystery Disk
is one of your subordinates.
♪
Get every last one of them!
I'll take care
of the baby, okay?
You go and fight 'em.
♪
(thwacking)
Holly, stay here with him.
Right.
(zapping)
(shouting)
(growling)
♪
Huh?
‐Lilim!
(groaning)
I'm... leaving!
(shouting)
Not so fast!
Don't go.
♪
You can't just leave the baby.
What kind of fathers are you?
(chuckling)
♪
I'm really sorry
I had to trick you.
It's okay, no harm done.
I wish I could go with you.
Getting this boy to a safe
place is more important.
Stay as far away from
the Baddies as you can.
Guess you're on your own now.
I'm not asking for your help.
(chuckling)
I'd better go.
‐Bye!
Later!
♪
It's time we got goin'
ourselves, don't ya think?
‐Chi!
‐Sure thing now Tiger's back.
Huh, where'd he go?
Tiger?
What are you doing, Chi?
Will you get off?
(grunting)
Look, I've lost weight.
That's cause I went
on a diet last night.
You were looking in
the pond yesterday, too.
Yeah, and when I did,
I could not believe
how round and chunky
I was lookin'.
And that's why you volunteered
to go find us our food?
Well, running is the best way
to get in shape after all.
And you let Mocchi ride you?
'Cause carrying a heavy load
burns up more calories.
Chi.
That's better, now I
look good and fierce.
(all groaning)
♪
‐Tiger!
You had us worried
sick all that time
just so you could go on a diet?!
This'll be sweet.
What's that?
(growling)
Oh, no, you don't!
(laughing)
We'll get ya, Tiger.
Wait for me, Tiger, Chi!
You'll pay for this,
you monster!
(chuckling)
(laughing)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪