♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Ah, my exquisite
collection of warriors,
I summon you to awaken!
♪
Rise, my coldhearted,
unrivaled warrior,
Chariot!
♪
At your service,
General Durahan.
(giggles)
What a hunk.
Chariot, summon up your anger
and strike the enemy
with your Iron Lance!
Your heart of darkness
will destroy them for good!
(laughing maniacally)
♪
Magic Stone, which direction
will lead us to the Phoenix?
♪
Over that way.
That way it is.
♪
Oh, brother, nothing but hills
as far as the eye can see.
'chi?
Know what they say:
one eye's better than two.
Go!
Whoa!
♪
I spy with my big eye...
Hey guys, I found a forest!
Huh?
♪
Suezo!
We're under fire!
There they are!
♪
Uh‐oh, look at 'em all.
The crest, they're Baddies!
♪
Whoa!
Ah!
♪
Go!
Let's get outta here fast!
You said it!
Let's get outta here!
♪
Over there!
‐The forest!
‐They'll never find us in there!
♪
What's the meaning of this?
Master Chariot.
Who ordered you to stop?
Forgive us.
It's just that...
(panting)
I don't get it,
why aren't they following us?
Who's complaining?
Let's just put some distance
between us and those fireballs.
(yells)
♪
Genki!
‐You okay?
‐'chi?
Yeah, I think.
Huh?
A bridge, come on, follow me.
♪
'chi, 'chi.
Go?
‐Huh?
‐What's that, 'chi?
♪
Okay, now I've seen everything.
Oh, I know, it must be Baku.
Baku, 'chi?
Uh‐huh.
Huh, now that you mention it,
it does look like him.
Yeah, the goofy face part
sure fits the bill.
Ha‐ha, I don't know, I think
that the furball's kinda cute.
What, this thing?
It's cute?
(laughing)
Oh man, you gotta do something
about that taste of yours.
Anyways, we better skedaddle
before those Baddies get here.
‐Come on.
‐Hm?
♪
(exclaims)
Baku!
What's the idea!?
(grunting)
♪
Are you trying to block our way?
Take this!
‐Suezo!
‐'chi!
♪
Oh man, this monster really
likes his sleep, doesn't he?
Maybe it's just
trying to look dumb
but it's a trick to stop us
from crossing the bridge.
Of all the nerve!
Golem, do something.
(grunts)
No, don't, Golem.
Maybe I could talk
some sense into him.
At least let me
give it a try.
Go.
Um, hey, Baku,
how about letting
a bunch of innocent
travelers across the bridge?
Hm?
♪
Huh?
'chi!
♪
Get off, Genki, 'chi!
Get off!
‐(Genki laughing)
‐Huh?
That tickles!
What's the deal here?
Slaps me and tickles you.
It must have something to do
with your personalities.
You're right, Genki's got
a certain strength about him.
Me, on the other hand,
I am just an eyeball.
Nice try, Hare!
Yo, Baku, why don't you lick me?
‐Mm, I taste like chicken.
‐Huh?
(yells)
Why, you!
♪
I feel so dirty.
Suezo!
Huh?
Cut it out.
Baku really seems to like him.
Come on, Baku, these guys
are all my friends.
Can't you just
let us go across?
♪
What do ya say?
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Ape and Rock Ape
fight dirty and mean ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ When they go at each other,
it's quite a scene ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Astros seek vengeance
from outer space ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ They'll take it out
on the whole human race ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Some monsters are good,
some monsters are bad ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all,
you're gonna be glad ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(whimpering)
'chi!
Thank you!
See ya later.
Bye!
‐Bye, 'chi!
‐Talk to you later!
♪
Hey, aren't you
forgetting something?!
♪
‐What's he doing?
‐Huh?
♪
Just ignore him.
Maybe he'll turn back.
♪
That didn't work,
he's still following us.
Come on.
He won't follow.
What's the deal?
♪
‐Run!
‐'chi!
♪
What do we do?
I really don't know, 'chi!
Listen, Baku!
Huh, where'd he go?
He disappeared.
♪
Cut it out, stop!
He really does have
a thing for you.
Hey guys, what do you say
we take him with us?
He would just get in our way.
I'll look after him.
But we get into
a lot of fights, Genki.
Wouldn't you feel bad
if he got hurt or something?
Yeah, Hare's right,
you gotta be firm with Baku
and tell him to
stop following us.
♪
Sorry, Baku,
you can't come.
It's too dangerous,
so don't follow us, all right?
See ya, bud.
♪
Hey, I told you
not to follow me!
♪
Captain, the truth is,
there's a creature of some kind
living in the forest.
It's got many of
our comrades already!
I don't think it
would be wise to go in.
Ah!
After them, there's
nothing to fear!
♪
Don't tell me you're still
thinking about that Baku.
Well, you have to
feel sorry for him.
He really liked Genki.
We've got better
things to think about,
like finding the Phoenix.
Mm‐hm.
♪
We'll get them when
they're least expecting it.
‐Let's do it.
‐Right!
♪
(yelling)
‐Where'd they come from?
‐'chi!
They must have been
following us!
I can't believe I didn't sense
the Baddies were after us.
‐Okay!
‐Let's get outta here!
♪
'chi.
Look, they've turned
into lost disks too!
Yeah, but who's doing this?
♪
(exclaims)
They got us
completely surrounded!
♪
(chuckles)
(growls)
♪
So, the rumors that
you were strong
have some truth to them.
We weren't the ones
who did this.
Destroy them!
♪
Lightning Attack!
Genki!
♪
No, there's too many of 'em!
Huh?
What is this place?
♪
Huh?
Huh?!
♪
Baku!
So you were the one
who turned the Baddies
into lost disks.
♪
Aw, cut it out,
you're soaking me.
♪
Aw, Baku, thanks for
saving us from the monsters.
♪
Baku!
Baku, Baku!
♪
So, you were the one
wiping out my troops.
♪
Huh?
(laughs maniacally)
♪
So you survived
the fall from the cliff.
This time I'll finish you off
just like I did
with your master.
Master?
Get him!
♪
Oh, Baku!
(snarls)
Baku!
♪
Get off me!
I've had enough of you.
No!
♪
This time I finish you off.
Baku!
♪
Hey boy, are you all right?
Are you, boy?
Baku.
♪
Where are you going, boy?
What's in there?
Hey, Baku?
♪
Huh?
That boy.
♪
Poor Baku, the Baddies
killed your family.
♪
Baku!
‐Genki!
‐'chi!
♪
Baku, hang on, boy, please!
Baku!
♪
(giggling)
Baku!
♪
Come on, boy!
(Baku barking)
♪
That tickles!
Baku!
Huh?
♪
(crying)
The villagers
probably made a living
digging up mystery disks.
And that's why
they were attacked,
just like my village was.
♪
Even though the whole
village was destroyed
and his master was gone,
Baku stayed behind
to protect the forest.
He protected us too.
Go.
Genki?
♪
We mustn't forget
that Baku gave his life
so he could protect ours.
We have to find
the Phoenix for his sake.
♪
Yeah, let's go
find that Phoenix!
‐'chi!
‐Yeah!
♪
Goodbye, Baku.
Come on!
Genki, wait for me!
'chi!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪