♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(shouting)
(fire crackling)
♪
Go at once, scat, scat!
(growling)
(clanging)
♪
(thudding)
Destroying this
village was too easy.
As usual, it
offered no challenge.
Where can I find them?
Humans and monsters of merit.
Prey worth hunting.
Master Gray Wolf!
(heavy breathing)
Master Gali of
the Big Bad Four.
‐It's terrible.
‐Gali?
The anti‐Moo rebels.
They're the ones responsible.
They're in the Forest of
the Black Worms as we speak.
Excellent.
At last, a prey of merit.
Let the hunt begin.
Black Worms, hear this,
destroy the fools
who defy Master Moo!
Moo!
(howling)
♪
(grunting)
What's up, Tiger?
Uh, it's nothing.
‐Huh?
‐Chi?
What is this feeling?
♪
Holly, you're sure we're
going the right way?
Yes.
Let's find the phoenix,
not waste time.
Right, Golem, then we can turn
all the Baddies into Goodies.
This sure is a creepy forest.
I don't like it.
Aw, Hare.
Are we a little frightened?
No way, Genki, not a bit.
(shouting)
Good psych.
Not funny, Suezo!
Ooh, now I'm so scared.
Now just cut it out!
Ha, rumors of my fear have
been greatly exaggerated.
I believe you.
We're the team
that beat Gali.
What is there possibly
to be afraid of?
Nothing, chi!
Well, statistically
speaking, of course,
we seem to be due
for another attack.
Have you got a plan?
Let's review the facts.
Pixie and Gali were both
members of the Big Bad Four.
All right, let's
get on with it.
Now we defeated Gali
and Pixie is on our side.
‐Hmm.
‐Your point?
Of the original Big
Bad Four, two are left.
That is my point.
Oh, Hare.
Hey, wait, guys,
there's more!
Huh?
‐Hold it.
‐Forget about Hare.
‐It's not Hare.
‐Huh?
‐Company.
‐Heads up.
‐Huh?
(shouting)
♪
‐Like I said.
‐Oh, great, more Baddies.
(laughing)
They call us the
"Forest Annihilators."
We're the Black Worms.
‐So?
‐Thorn attack!
♪
(grunting)
Ah!
‐Oh!
‐Chi!
Let's circle up.
Oh, poison darts!
Ready?
(whimpering)
Attack!
(shouting)
♪
Regroup now!
Not so fast!
Tiger!
♪
‐Ah!
‐Tiger, wait!
We've already made our point.
Ha, don't feel
sorry for them.
They wouldn't feel
sorry for you.
If you act like them,
you become them.
(growling)
(sighing)
♪
So, what are we
gonna do with him?
Ahem, strategically,
it would be a good plan
to interrogate him.
What are you
talking about, Hare?
Chi.
Here's your first question.
Who are the two monsters
left in the Big Bad Four?
I'm sorry, I'm terrible
with the details.
All right, Hare,
let me at him!
Calm down, Suezo!
♪
Please, can't you just say
who told you to attack us?
Ha, whoever is
leading these nobodies
can't be anybody
of any importance.
Big talk, you're
the nobodies, you.
Don't push me!
Tiger!
I work for one of
the Big Bad Four.
Our leader is none
other than Gray Wolf.
Huh?
Not Gray Wolf!
Your brother, Tiger?
Moo did make him a
Baddie, didn't he?
It can't be!
It's impossible!
Tiger.
I have to go and find
this out for myself.
I'll see you later.
And if it's true, what
will you do then, Tiger?
Tiger?
This has nothing to do
with any one of you.
♪
Tiger.
Hmm.
(gasping)
Look out!
‐Holly!
‐You little worm!
‐Smoke!
‐Huh?
(coughing)
(laughs)
What?
Monsters.
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Mocchi is pink,
but Mocchi is tough ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Zuum troops and their
captain play kind of rough ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Suezo looks far,
soars through the skies ♪
♪ Looking for Rockies,
they aren't bad guys ♪
♪ Horn the pirate
says that he's pure ♪
♪ But he's a monster,
can you be sure ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
I'm glad Tiger's okay.
Oh, no, she's burning up!
The poison in the dart.
Black Worm
poisoning is serious.
First, a high fever,
then delirium.
‐Poor Holly.
‐No!
Is this another theory, Hare?
I'm telling ya, Hare, I'm not
buying this dart nonsense.
Hey, don't shoot
the messenger, I'm‐‐
Answer me now!
What can I do to save Holly?
Tiger, apparently natsume
berries are the antidote.
Natsume berries?
Yes, but I have no idea
where they'd be growing
around this area.
Tiger!
I promise I'll be back
with the berries for Holly.
We need you here!
If it wasn't for me,
Holly would never have
been hit by that dart.
Tiger!
Mocchi, you guys,
take care of Holly.
‐Tiger!
‐Genki!
♪
(panting)
Hey, wait, Tiger!
(heavy breathing)
Must be strong, Holly.
Holly.
Ah!
Genki, Tiger, we're
all counting on you!
Please, hurry back!
Please, please!
♪
(grunting)
So, Tiger, how come
you're so sure
where these berries are?
I don't really know, Genki,
but I trust my senses.
(grunting)
♪
You rest, I'm going on ahead.
No way!
I'm Mr. Energy, remember?
They don't call me
champ for nothing.
Yeah, right, kid.
Hey, why can't
you ever be nice?
What does that mean?
Look, we're a team, Tiger.
You don't always
have to go it alone.
(grunting)
♪
Don't look now, but
we've got company.
Let's get busy.
‐Hold on, Tiger.
‐Huh?
‐I'll do this.
‐Really?
I'll handle these guys.
You go find the berries.
♪
Go get 'em, Tiger.
Okay.
Rip it up!
(shouting)
♪
(grunting)
(coughing)
♪
Yes, I can smell them now.
I'm getting close.
♪
(sniffing)
Ah.
That must be them.
♪
(grunting)
(laughing)
Fancy meeting you here.
(groaning)
Out of my way, Worm, I've
no time to waste with you.
Afraid not, son,
I have my orders.
What?
And you know how it is, Tiger.
Orders are orders!
Ha, you should've quit
while you were ahead.
You don't know who
you're up against.
Arrogance is a
terrible curse.
Back off!
Oh, did I hit you
with my poison dart?
Aw, so sorry!
(shouting)
♪
And it gets even worse.
Right about now
my troops should be
attacking your friend.
No!
♪
(rustling)
(shouting)
(cracking)
They've gotta be
very close by.
Let's find them!
♪
They're gone.
Phew, well that got them
out of our hair for a while
You call that a plan?
Hey, it worked, didn't it?
With Holly so weak
and Golem so huge,
our options are limited.
(laughing)
The poison seems
to be taking hold.
You see, we never
let our prey escape.
Gray Wolf insists.
It's a kind of
ironclad rule with him.
(groaning)
♪
And, remember, never let your
prey escape, little brother.
Always finish it off.
That is the rule of the hunt.
Gray Wolf.
Rest well.
My brother, my enemy.
(growling)
(shouting)
♪
Torpedo!
(zapping)
(exploding)
♪
(panting)
(wind howling)
Gray.
Gray Wolf.
♪
My brother.
(shouting)
(growling)
♪
Huh?
(grunting)
Well, it seems those
natsume berries are working.
But just how long
was I sleeping?
Holly!
♪
Gray Wolf, my little brother,
I will be the one
to defeat you!
Did you find them?
They're nowhere to be found.
They're here somewhere.
♪
(panting)
Huh?
♪
Genki.
Genki!
(groaning)
Huh, Tiger.
What took you so long?
Did you find those berries?
Yes.
Good, come on,
let's go, Tiger.
We gotta get back to H‐‐ah!
(clearing throat)
Get on.
Thanks.
♪
I just don't get it.
Their footprints stop here.
They've gotta be here.
Look again!
(coughing)
‐Over there!
‐Oh, boy.
‐This is not good.
‐Come out of there!
We have no choice.
‐We have to fight.
‐Ready, chi.
That's it, get them!
♪
Hiya!
What the‐‐
♪
‐Genki!
‐Tiger!
Go!
How's Holly doing?
We got the berries.
Chi!
Never mind that, you're back.
And we're glad.
Ah, they've defeated
our noble captain.
Get 'em!
(shouting)
Ha, let's dance.
I've had about
all I can take
from the likes
of you insects.
Hey, Golem, you stay
and protect Holly.
Okay, Genki.
Are you strong enough, Genki?
Is there something
wrong with your ears?
I keep telling you,
I'm the champ, Tiger.
But if I get in a fix,
you gotta be there.
Well, champ, you're
nothing but trouble to me.
(growling)
Chi.
(groaning)
Right, all for one
and one for all!
Yeah!
Attack!
♪
(pounding)
Cherry blossom!
♪
Blizzard!
Ah!
Attack!
Torpedo!
♪
Huh, let's get out of here!
Phew.
♪
Now just the smell, make
sure she gets a good whiff.
(sniffing)
Oh.
Hmm.
Holly?
(sighing)
Yeah!
(laughing)
(slamming)
Shh.
♪
What are you
thinking about, Tiger?
♪
Gray Wolf is my brother,
but also my enemy.
He's one of the Big Bad Four.
He'll send stronger troops.
But we're a team.
I can never forget
how important that is.
When we put our strengths
together like that,
we can overcome
almost anything.
Genki's right, Tiger.
Holly, you doing okay?
Yup.
I'm feeling much better now.
I think we should continue
our search for the Phoenix
'cause then we can
turn Gray Wolf
back into one of the Goodies.
Holly...
Let's do it then.
Let's go find the phoenix,
and when my brother shows up,
I will deal with him then.
Yeah, that's the spirit!
And when Gray Wolf shows up,
we'll deal with him
together as a team.
Yeah!
(howling)
♪
Master Gray Wolf, is
there anything the matter?
♪
No, it's nothing.
Probably just the wind.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪