♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(straining)
They're gaining on us!
We're done for!
Hare, what's the plan?
Let's head for that
building over there.
♪
Get them!
Mocchi!
(sizzling)
♪
Tiger!
Help!
(evil chuckle)
‐Genki!
‐Mocchi!
(Tiger growls)
Tiger, you've been hit.
Salamander!
Huh?
♪
Ha!
Coward!
Centaur!
A true warrior would never
take such an unfair advantage
over his opponents.
Says you!
That's right, says a proud
and powerful warrior...
Centaur.
And the warrior of the wind...
Celius.
And the warrior
of strength, Dragoon.
♪
You're the Centaur?
And you are Captain Salamander,
under the command of Gray Wolf.
Under Gray Wolf's special order,
this is our
territory, Salamander.
(mutters)
Leave now or face
the consequences.
What?
And leave you all the
credit for capturing them?
Back off!
If they want the credit,
they can have it.
Don't you two know anything?
The Centaur can fight
as well as Gray Wolf himself.
(gasping)
These three are like
the big bad four.
That's just great.
Salamander troops, move out!
♪
We meet at last.
You are the ones who
challenged Master Moo?
Yeah, what's it to you, Centaur?
Hmph.
Genki!
Chi!
♪
‐Clarity.
‐Huh?
Come.
Uh...
♪
Our best three fighters?
Correct.
Three matches,
each one of us paired
with one of you.
In this coliseum,
we are not ragged ruffians
but warriors of honor.
If you win, you go free.
Count me in.
Tiger's been hurt.
He can't fight
with these wounds.
(Tiger pants)
‐I can fight.
‐I can fight him.
Have you forgotten that
I'm the monster champ?
You sure?
Mm‐hm.
♪
I'm Genki, and I'll fight you.
Step aside, boy.
Humans are no match for
mighty warriors like us.
Don't worry about me,
I'm the monster champ.
(chuckling)
Very well.
I, Centaur, will accept
your challenge, Genki.
(laughs)
This'll be fun.
Hmph.
And the two other opponents?
Mocchi!
♪
I'll fight.
Golem, go!
That leaves the number
three position open, and...
you're it.
I can't!
I've got a pain,
appendicitis or gallbladder.
But, Hare, you're
always telling us
what a great fighter you are.
Suezo, now that you've got
that new teleporting technique,
you're the monster to beat.
‐Oh no, you are.
‐I insist, Suezo.
‐No, I do.
‐You go.
I'll fight.
Huh?
Holly?
Chi?
I don't like to fight,
but I will if I have to.
Fine.
You guys, what about
the magic stone?
Holly can't fight.
Yeah, but I'm
the lookout, right?
Well, what would you
do without my brain?
You two are something else!
(exclaiming)
(splash)
(gasping)
In keeping with our traditions,
now you both will fight.
(whimpering)
That is the
Fountain of Warriors.
Once you have bathed
in its waters,
you must enter into battle.
It is sacred law.
You're kidding.
Taxi!
♪
(gong sounds)
(trumpet blares)
♪
(whimpering)
‐Way to go, Hare!
‐Beat 'em, Chi!
Pursue victory with honor.
Begin!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it and claim
it, you can tame it ♪
♪ Find a Seed Sister,
charming but frightening ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Or the Usaba,
quicker than lightning ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ There's evil Hare
and his captain ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ They'd love to fight
like Pirate Dragons ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Mighty they battle,
mighty they fall ♪
♪ These monsters rule,
unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
I offer you the
advantage of first move.
Gee, thanks.
(screams)
(gasping)
(skidding)
(clatter)
Have mercy, please!
I'm a nothing, a mere
speck on your hoof.
A flea in your ear,
mighty Celius.
Spare me, spare me,
spare me, spare me!
Please!
Way to go, Hare.
The same cheap trick
that he used against me.
(whimpers)
(growls)
(Hare screams)
♪
The victor.
Celius!
(exclaiming)
♪
(whimpering)
(blade whirring)
Warriors...
begin!
(gong sounds)
(shouting)
♪
(clanging)
Race ya!
Huh?
♪
As long as I can keep running,
I can't be called the loser!
This isn't going good.
Well, he hasn't lost yet.
♪
Listen, up, Dragoon,
you're gonna be sorry.
Slobbering kiss!
♪
Victory to Suezo.
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay!
No way.
That's a new one.
♪
Show him how it's done!
You can do it, Genki!
Hope you were watching, Genki!
It's up to you now, kid.
(gong sounds)
(shouting)
♪
Hi‐ya!
(clanging)
♪
Very impressive.
Back at ya.
It's been a while since
I've met a worthy opponent.
♪
(shouting)
(gasping)
This isn't good.
♪
Alley‐oop!
Gotcha!
♪
And now...
spin attack!
Look out, Centaur!
Huh?
Incoming!
(explosions)
♪
Celius, no‐‐Dragoon!
(gasps)
(thundering crash)
Look out!
Genki!
♪
(exclaims)
(exclaiming)
(groaning)
I don't get it.
You‐‐Centaur‐‐you risked
your life to save me, why?
♪
The noble battle is
a sacred event, Genki.
Ah.
The worthy opponent
must be honored
and valued with
the same regard
one has for a friend.
I don't get it, Centaur.
I don't understand how
an honorable warrior
becomes a bad guy.
♪
I was defeated,
defeated by Gray Wolf.
Huh?
♪
(crowd chatter)
(gasping)
(blast)
(screaming)
♪
We put up a desperate
battle, but...
we were no match for
their cunning tactics.
♪
The defeated must
always obey the victors.
That's how we became followers
of our enemy, Gray Wolf.
He acknowledged our strength
and gave us reign
over this territory.
‐Unforgivable!
‐Hm?
Gray Wolf taking advantage
of wounded warriors.
Where's the honor in that?
The reality is that
a defeat is a defeat,
no matter what
the circumstances.
But‐‐
That is the warrior's rule.
It is our custom.
(groaning)
Huh?
Centaur, we have to get
you to the Fountain.
I've been hurt worse.
‐You should see to your friends.
‐Huh?
♪
I'm sorry.
(explosion)
(exclaims)
Huh?
(evil cackle)
♪
You back again, Salamander?
I've had it up to here
with this honor stuff.
We've got ya this time, kid.
You're not gonna cause
Moo any more trouble.
You're finished.
You.
You defy the rules
of the warrior.
Whatever it takes to win.
That's the only rule
we've got, Centaur.
♪
Leave them to me.
Huh?
‐Centaur.
‐Genki.
Go now, save your friends.
Uh...
Go.
Right.
♪
(sounds of struggle)
I'll blame your
defeat on the kid.
Gray Wolf will never know.
♪
(blasts)
It seems, Captain Salamander,
you don't learn.
You will never defeat me.
♪
(grunting)
Holly, is everyone all right?
Yep, we're fine, Genki.
Great.
'K.
♪
Huh?
Hey, you two are okay.
Hm.
‐Ready?
‐Yeah.
♪
Huh?
I was beginning to wonder
when you two would get here.
We had a few
weighty problems.
But showed those
Salamander troops
a thing or two
about warriors.
(blades clang)
♪
(whimpering)
(rumbling)
Oh!
Genki!
‐Thank you.
‐Mocchi!
Awesome!
♪
Heads up, guys!
Lightning!
Huh?
What now?
♪
Let's get 'em!
Chi!
♪
I am Centaur!
You can be sure we'll
meet again, Centaur!
Retreat!
(celebrating)
(laughter)
♪
Uh...
Goodbye.
♪
We pointed our
swords at allies.
We will receive retribution.
♪
You mean, the Salamander
troops will be back again?
Mm‐hm.
But they don't fight fair.
I'll stay here
and fight with you.
Chi!
(Tiger growls)
You must move on now.
We can take care of them.
But we can help you.
Go.
Huh?
You are a true warrior.
You possess a soul and
eyes that are clear.
You have a quest you
must fulfill, Genki,
so you must go now.
We'll meet again, won't we?
That is not ours to say.
Let us go.
♪
Centaur!
We're not done yet!
I challenge you
to a rematch!
♪
(sniffling)
Are you okay?
♪
Yeah!
Let's find the Phoenix.
Down with Moo, goodies rule!
Okay!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪