♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
It points straight ahead!
Uh, judging from the present
position of the sun,
the magic stone seems to point
to a place called Rema.
So let's go find
that mystery disk
and release the Phoenix!
(giggling)
♪
(sighing)
Oh, what I'd do
for a drink of water.
It's way too hot,
it's way too muggy,
and these bugs are
driving me buggy!
Uh, Suezo, we know already.
Everyone's hot, Suezo.
Guh.
I'm hungry, I'm thirsty,
and I want this to be over!
Chi, chi, chi, chi, chi!
Problem!
Stop it, you two, come on!
Oh, boy, whew.
Aaarrgghh!
(splat)
(laughing)
What a klutz.
Suezo, I tripped over that‐‐
(yelling)
Go?
It looks like a robotic arm.
I've seen this before
in the monster game.
It belongs to a Henger.
Give me a slurp.
♪
Mmm, the feel of
it over my tongue,
there's no mistake.
Give me a break.
It seems it is a robotic arm.
Yeah, cool!
And if we find
the rest of him,
we'll have
ourselves a Henger.
Come on gang,
whoo hoo ha ha!
Mocchi,
But, you guys?
That's our Genki.
Chi!
A leg!
Leg, chi.
(giggling)
♪
Yeah, Mocchi!
Here's another part.
But we need the rest.
Fine, Golem, toss me up
and we'll have a look.
♪
Huh?
What's up, Tiger?
I think something's over there.
Where?
This way.
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait!
Hey, wait up!
‐Hey!
‐Why do you have to do this?
♪
Huh?
Awesome!
♪
Wow!
Wha‐‐what's that?
It looks like
a big ugly city.
Looks like a
pretty good pit stop.
Thirsty!
Hang on!
Ugh, not again.
♪
(echoing)
Hey, is anybody here?
Hello?
♪
This looks like the city
Monol told us about.
Hey, can you spare
a drink of water?
♪
Hello?
No good, nothing.
Wow, this is‐‐
no doubt about it‐‐
Yep.
Well what, Genki?
Just a vending machine, Suezo.
Vending?
So what is that?
You mean you don't know?
And I suppose you do?
Of course.
You simply insert a gold and
the person who's inside there
gives you something.
That's not it.
You put money in
and the machine
automatically
gives you a drink.
♪
You don't seem feverish.
Of course I'm not feverish!
Wait a sec,
you guys don't know
what vending
machines are, do you?
If someone would
give me a gold,
I'd be happy to demonstrate.
I'll do it.
So you're sure there's something
to drink in there, hey, Genki?
Uh‐huh.
Tiger, we're all
hot and thirsty.
Out of the way.
I think he's serious.
Aahh!
♪
Thirsty, thirsty,
thirsty, thirsty!
Apple juice, guava juice,
orange juice, pineapp‐‐
(siren wailing)
♪
Chi?
(growling)
♪
They all look identical!
Arrgh, that's because
they're Hengers, Mocchi.
Are they baddies?
♪
Don't look like baddies.
Aargh!
City dispenser pod
number 0635 is damaged.
Presumed cause,
electrical overload.
(laughing)
It's just a little problem.
Tiger, apologize
to the nice robot.
Hmm.
Please present
citizenship card.
Citizenship card?
Undesirable aliens without cards
must be escorted from the city.
But why, we aren't
undesirable aliens,
we're just
hungry and thirsty.
Citizenship card, please?
It's no use, Holly.
Want to fight?
Now, now.
Huh?
Here goes nothing.
Okay, let's go.
♪
Stop!
Undesirables, deport!
♪
Why is it we always seem to
be running away from someone?
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Find a Seed Sister,
charming but frightening ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Or the Usaba,
quicker than lightning ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ There's Evil Hare
and his captain ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ They love to fight
like Pirate Dragons ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Mighty they battle,
mighty they fall ♪
♪ These monsters rule,
unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
No, my stuff!
The magic stone!
The fruit juice!
(firing)
Maybe I can do without it.
But I...
Holly.
♪
I guess they just wanted
us out of their city.
Mocchi.
But I've got to get
the magic stone back.
No problem.
When it comes to speed,
I'm the champ!
Rip it up!
♪
Aggh, aggh!
(firing)
(yelling)
(crying)
Excellent retrieval, champ.
Knock it off!
I'll find the stone.
♪
(growling)
Undesirable alien, deport.
Lighten up, robots.
(firing)
♪
You get it?
It was nowhere in sight.
We cannot leave
without the magic stone.
Let's look.
(grunting)
♪
Hey, Suezo,
do you see anything?
Keep your shirt on!
♪
They're changing the broken
vending machine for a new one.
Are they soldiers
or maintenance workers?
‐Ugh!
‐Huh?
They got our stuff!
♪
The magic stone, too!
(sigh)
Stop, thieves!
(yelling)
They put our
stuff in a box!
Great, what do we do now?
Let's just have
it out with them.
That's your response
to everything.
(growling)
You two, don't fight.
‐That's right.
‐Huh?
Huh?
Um, over here.
♪
Holly, did you hear a voice?
But it's a garbage dump.
‐Over here.
‐Huh?
Hello, how are you all?
I'm so glad you stopped by.
Ah!
This is awfully kind of you.
♪
Now if you would just
connect the green wires.
Like this?
Oh, oh!
♪
(laughing)
Oh, oh, oh,
this is wonderful!
Oh, oh, I can move again!
Looks like you plugged
something in backwards.
Oh, he doesn't look
like a bad fella.
What is with this weird place?
I don't get it.
Oh, oh, the builder
of this city
ordered us to protect it.
Who's the builder?
Yeah, who is he?
Ancient people.
Do you mean to tell me
that you've been
protecting this city
since ancient times?
Yes.
Mocchi!
The people of this
city perished long ago,
but Hengers will run forever
on solar batteries.
Huh?
But about a year ago...
♪
My command board
short‐circuited.
I found that unlike
the other Hengers,
I was able to move
according to my own judgment.
I decided to go
outside the city walls
to see what
the world was like.
And that's how I discovered
that the Ancients' war was over.
♪
When I returned to the city,
I tried to tell the others
about what I had learned.
However...
(firing)
(yelling)
Oh no!
♪
(yelling)
So I guess that's why we found
you in pieces, huh, Henger?
Yes.
And for sure you can help
us get into the city, right?
Of course.
Then all we got to do now
is find our stuff.
Find our stuff, chi.
(flame flickering)
This will take us to
the center of the city
without anyone noticing.
Okay, let's move out.
♪
Chi.
Mmm, Golem is stuck.
Golem, you just
wait here, okay?
Mmm‐mmm.
I hate being alone.
We don't have time for this.
We'll be right back, Golem.
Mocchi.
Come this way.
♪
Go!
(rocks exploding)
Wait for me!
(shushing)
Please, hurry, hide in here.
♪
What's up?
They don't seem to know
that we're here, Holly.
(screeching)
Henger, what is that?
♪
Oh, that's Techno Dragon,
the maintenance boss.
♪
(roaring)
So, we have an intruder.
Yes, Cover 6405 is destroyed.
Undesirable‐‐get rid of
the intruder, right now.
Affirmative.
♪
All right, you heard him.
Roger that.
♪
It's okay,
they're gone for now.
Chi!
Mocchi thirsty, chi!
Mocchi!
Hey, Mocchi,
that stuff's ancient.
No, freshness and
taste is guaranteed.
Well, what is this stuff?
Ah!
It is a food
and drink machine
that the ancient
people invented.
It will provide you with any
refreshment that you order.
♪
It is good.
Deluxe platter okay?
As long as I can
eat and drink it,
I'm a happy Hare.
Let's chow down!
(slurping)
So, what do you think?
Simply divine.
Golem wants a big boulder.
Go!
(chewing)
This is good!
Mmm, I was so thirsty.
Not bad, not bad at all.
Your belongings will be
in the underground base.
And this elevator
will take us there?
Yes, I've been here
many times before.
♪
You know what, Golem?
Since it's a bit tight,
maybe you should wait here.
I hate being alone.
♪
Shh.
This way, everyone.
♪
City third block under control.
The area has been repaired.
The undesirable aliens
have not been found.
(growl)
♪
There it is!
Our stuff is right
down this hallway.
Well we can just
wait until they go.
Don't you worry about
that, I've got a plan.
Just you wait right here.
Be careful.
♪
So what's he gonna do?
It beats me.
♪
(laughter)
What do you think
you are doing?
These items are
disruptive to the city.
They must be removed.
Under whose orders?
Stop him!
Argh!
♪
(yelling)
Run for it!
♪
So this was your
brilliant plan, Henger?
♪
We did it!
I outsmarted them.
Outsmarted, my eye!
Chi!
(siren wailing)
♪
(growling)
(roaring)
How about if we...run!
♪
(roaring)
(yelling)
♪
(firing)
Listen, the ancient war
was over a long time ago!
There's no need for you
to fight any longer.
Aggh!
♪
Hurry, get out of the city!
Oh, you go ahead.
♪
Henger!
Don't worry, I'll catch up.
♪
(metal clattering)
Henger!
Oh, oh, my,
I seem to have
scattered into
pieces once again.
Henger.
Henger okay!
♪
How about it,
why don't you come with us?
I'm honored to be
asked to join you.
But I'll stay here until
the others understand.
Okay, good luck, Henger.
Thank you for everything.
Try and keep it
together, Henger.
Bye‐bye, Henger,
bye‐bye, chi.
We will meet again someday.
Goodbye!
It was nice to meet you all.
It's weird to
think those Hengers
keep protecting that place,
a city where nobody lives
and nobody goes.
Just because they don't know
how to stop themselves.
Hmmm, but Henger seems like just
the guy to get through to them.
Yeah, I guess.
For sure.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪