♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(wind howling)
♪
(evil laughter)
Here's my original body.
At last the time has come
for my soul and body
to be reunited!
♪
(explosion)
I don't understand.
I've finally come face to
face with my original body.
So why am I unable
to merge with it?
‐Master Moo!
‐Don't bother me!
But I've captured
a suspicious‐looking
character, sir.
Hmm?
♪
I came to tell you
something important.
♪
Awesome!
(laughing)
♪
Hey, Genki, Mocchi, be careful!
Aw, no problem, Holly,
just watch and see!
This is the perfect
place to do some blading.
(laughing)
Yeah!
♪
Ahhh!
‐I told you to be careful.
‐Figures.
Well, when you're that reckless,
you gotta expect
a shortened lifespan.
I didn't even get
a chance to say goodbye.
‐Oh, we're alive!
‐'chi!
I never doubted it for a second!
♪
Look, everyone, what's that?
Hmm?
It looks like a coliseum.
Let's go check it out.
‐Come on!
‐Yeah!
♪
Whoa, check out the
size of this place!
‐Yeah!
‐It's enormous!
‐Whoa.
‐Unreal!
'chi!
Hello?
♪
Anyone here?
Doesn't look like it!
♪
Whoa, eyeballs like me!
This is quite the
place, huh, Hare?
It's like the ruins
of an ancient city!
♪
(gasping)
What's this?
What kind of beast is that?
How come all those
things are dangling down?
Hey, it almost
looks like a castle!
Many monsters here.
Not good.
Mountain, Chi!
(laughing)
Ahh.
Hey, guys, it's
an amusement park!
‐An amusement park?
‐Yeah!
A long time ago, people
probably came here to have fun.
You know, like going on
rides and stuff like that?
This is where people came
in the old days to hang out.
Like over here's
a flying chair ride.
It feels like you're flying,
and it's really fun, you guys.
Let's try, 'chi!
I'm in!
♪
(grumbling)
Genki, I'm not getting
any windburn here!
'chi!
It's no good if the
thing isn't moving.
This thing's ancient, so
there probably isn't any power.
There's man power!
Hey, give us a
little whirl, Golem!
'chi!
Golem spin you.
Ha‐ha!
Yes, he did it!
Flying Mocchi!
♪
(screaming)
Golem, were you trying
to put us into space?
Uhhh.
Too bad, but if we
could fix this thing
and get customers
to come and ride it,
we could rake in a lot
of moolah, you know.
It always comes back to money.
Sure does, know why?
'Cause most of us mortals
have to earn our money.
Of course a crook like you
can steal his way through life.
‐Thin ice, pal!
‐Back at ya!
That swing thing hooked me!
There's gotta be
something else I can ride.
‐Over there!
‐That looks good!
♪
My way looks way more fun.
Golem thinks that
way looks good.
Listen, you won't regret it
if you come with me, Holly.
This way, Mocchi!
Uh, but what about that one?
Don't you think it's strange
with all those big coffee cups?
They're actually teacups.
You sit inside them
and you spin around.
And that is supposed to be fun?
Sure is, Holly!
Come on, I'll show ya!
(laughing)
It's play time.
‐Let's go.
‐See ya!
'chi, 'chi, 'chi!
Suezo, 'chi, what for me!
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Gali, one of
Moo's Big Bad Four ♪
Unlock 'em all!
♪ Big Blue, a monster
with power and more ♪
Unlock 'em all!
♪ Pixie's a mystery,
who's side is she on? ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ She's one of Moo's
four, but for how long? ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Flips and tornadoes,
without 'em, within ♪
♪ 400 monsters,
someone will win ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(screaming)
Calm down, Mocchi,
it's just a mirror.
'chi?
♪
You're right, 'chi!
Mocchi, come here,
this is a blast!
♪
(laughing)
Suezo funny!
You too!
(giggling)
Okay, enough of this place!
♪
Suezo, you're a beautiful sight.
Hey, Mocchi, come here!
You should give this a try!
Hmm?
Hey, where'd the
little fellow go?
♪
Mm, Golem try.
(clanging)
Huh?
♪
(grunting)
(squeaking)
♪
Ahhh!
(laughing)
That was kind of cute
seeing those fluffy things
gettin' the better of ya!
Mocchi!
‐What's the matter?
‐Yeah, what's up, Suezo?
(groaning)
I'll get it.
♪
(laughing)
What a mess!
Genki, are you all right?
Yeah.
Ah, the people who lived
here hundreds of years ago
must've had a lot
of fun here, too.
People in our village
were happy, too,
until Moo's army came.
♪
(thunder and growling)
Holly?
‐Hey!
‐Ahh!
How come you're making her cry?
Butt out, Suezo, I
didn't make her cry!
Genki, Mocchi's missing.
We've looked everywhere,
we can't find him.
Mocchi not here.
What are you talking about?
Mocchi's disappeared!
(together)
What‐‐you mean
he's not with you?
Suezo lost track of him, so we
split up and started looking.
We were hoping he was here.
‐Mocchi!
‐Where are you?
Mocchi, can you hear me?
No luck.
Can't find him anywhere.
‐He's just not here.
‐Help me, 'chi!
Huh?
‐Hear that?
‐Look, there he is!
Ohh!
Mocchi!
(whimpering)
♪
The Baddies have got him.
You, give our friend back!
(growling)
♪
(laughing)
How come he's got Mocchi?
We gotta do something quick.
(speaking gibberish)
I think he's telling
us don't interfere
or he'll drop Mocchi.
Only a real coward would
do something like that.
We must stop him.
(laughing)
♪
Huh?
Sue‐‐
♪
(speaking gibberish)
What has gotten into you?
Shh, I'm buying some time.
(speaking gibberish)
I'm coming, Mocchi.
Suezo is on his way.
(speaking gibberish)
(more shouting gibberish)
(joining gibberish)
Look, Golem, there's Suezo!
(gibberish continues)
(yelling gibberish)
♪
I am gonna be such a...
... hero.
‐Ahh!
‐Suezo!
(growling)
Look, over there!
Incoming!
♪
Oh, well, so much for Plan A,
but, like I always say,
there's always tomorrow, right?
♪
They've got us surrounded!
(yelling gibberish)
♪
Mocchi!
‐'chi!
‐Pixie!
Can't complain about
that kind of timing, huh?
♪
Let's go!
Genki.
♪
Come and get me!
(grunting)
♪
(creaking)
(screaming)
(grumbling)
(panting)
♪
(laughing)
Alley‐oop!
♪
Ahh!
(grunting)
Not bad, huh?
Now let's go back
and find the others.
♪
What was that?
(screaming)
♪
Look, there's the exit!
Surrender!
♪
Lightning!
(explosions)
♪
(together)
Chicken!
♪
Mocchi, you're safe now!
Pixie good, 'chi!
♪
Thanks.
Whoa.
♪
Yo gang, all the
rides are working,
and we've got the whole
place to ourselves!
Think of the fun we can have!
Yeah, and think of all
the money we're gonna save!
(gasping)
♪
Wow!
Wow.
‐Ahh.
‐Ahhh.
♪
There's so much to do,
I don't know where to start!
No kidding!
♪
Huh‐‐what happened?
Hey, who turned out the lights?
Aww.
Huh?
♪
'chi.
I knew it was too
good to be true.
Golem sad.
This must've been such a blast,
but now it's just
a bunch of ruins.
Maybe one day it'll be restored
and the people will return.
It'll happen, as soon
as we find the Phoenix.
Except that we're
running out of time.
Huh?
Moo has excavated his body.
‐Are you serious?
‐I am.
That's what I came
here to tell you guys.
You're leaving?
Big Blue is
researching the Phoenix,
so I'm going right
now to meet him.
We share the same
feelings as you.
Let's crush Moo's evil plans,
and one day the world
will be peaceful once again.
♪
Yeah!
Okay, let's move out, gang!
♪
(wind howling)
In other words, the ancient
wars wiped out everything,
and they were
completely meaningless.
They were extremely foolish.
(evil laughter)
Take him away!
No, please wait!
Please, listen to
what I have to say!
Stop!
So that light was
the final gate.
If the light
caused a separation,
then surely it can
cause things to merge.
Come to think of it, I remember
hearing something about some
ancient ruins in
the Torles Mountains
just like the ones in the story!
I suppose it could be true.
Take the floating castle
and bring the ruins to me.
Right away, Master!
(wind howling)
♪
(laughing)
The day I look forward to will
have to wait a little longer
for the return of
the floating castle.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪