♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(panting)
♪
He's so strong!
Have you decided to surrender?
♪
Ahh!
Run, my frightened little fools.
(evil laughter)
♪
I know exactly why
you're trying to escape‐‐
because the Phoenix
is hidden nearby!
I'll find you, Phoenix...
♪
...down there.
I knew it.
♪
Wait!
Come back and fight!
(laughing)
We're just gonna
have to go after him.
(together)
Yeah!
‐Hey, wait for me!
‐No, it's too dangerous!
Please!
No, you stay back!
♪
Please, let me go with you!
(growling)
♪
Do you honestly
think you can stop me?
Come on, let's go for it!
Yeah!
♪
(yelling)
Did it work?
(laughing)
♪
(grunting)
Let me out!
(together)
Genki!
Let me out of here!
‐Genki!
‐'chi!
(roaring)
(grunting)
Don't worry, you'll each
have your turn with me.
Lightning!
(groaning)
Whoa‐‐ahh!
Genki!
It's you!
Are you all right?
Yeah, 'cause I had a
feeling that you would come.
And I'm not alone.
Huh?
Who are they?
I've brought the
dragons along to help,
and some others
you might remember.
Hey, it's Big Blue and Vulcan!
It's the dragon army!
Attack Moo, troops!
♪
Hmm?
Need a lift?
♪
Thanks for coming
to save us, Vulcan!
Just keeping my promise.
Genki, you haven't forgotten
your old friends Horn,
Allan, Eddie, and Jim, have you?
Not a chance!
(explosions and yelling)
♪
Get after them, men!
And it's not just them, either.
Jim is leading
an army of rebels,
including the
Tainted Kat Brothers,
the Color Pandoras, and a
lot of your other old friends.
My friends.
They couldn't come with us,
but they're here in spirit.
Genki, we've gotta fight
for their sake as well.
‐We can't let Moo win!
‐Right!
Golem never give up!
Mocchi fight hard!
Still overestimating
your own strength, I see.
‐Go!
‐Yeah!
♪
Ahhh!
Attack!
♪
Let's go!
(evil laughter)
Now!
♪
Retreat!
Did we finish him off?
♪
Maybe he wasn't as
strong as I thought.
Let's wait and see.
I don't know.
Look, he's not moving.
(yelling)
♪
You fools thought
you had crushed me,
when in fact I was merely
using you to test my new body.
Now I know for certain this
new body of mine is invincible!
Come on, let's do it again!
Yeah!
♪
Come on, let's get
out of here now!
I'm with you!
♪
You won't get away from me!
Say goodbye.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Shaped like an urn,
Bajarl calls 'em in ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Including a town,
can't tell where it's been ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ General Kato
is good and wise ♪
Unlock 'em all!
♪ He knows how it works,
the summit surprise ♪
Unlock 'em all!
♪ Monol is flat,
but Monol is deep ♪
♪ His biggest problem,
he falls asleep ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(yelling)
(growling)
♪
‐Pixie!
‐Look out, Pixie!
♪
(evil laughter)
Pixie, no!
♪
I could crush your
friend with one hand.
Help.
I'll save you, Pixie!
(grunting)
Are you okay?
(groaning)
Now how do you intend
to save your friend?
Help, get me out of here!
Yes, I can feel your hatred‐‐
the hatred my soul hungers for!
(growling)
No, Big Blue, the
more you hate him,
the stronger his
evil soul will become!
Interesting advice
coming from you, Tiger.
Huh?
I understand you
defeated your own brother!
How did it feel fighting
your own flesh and blood?
(growling)
♪
That's the way.
Let your hatred
consume your heart.
Then you'll become
one of my Baddies.
♪
Hey, that's enough!
Let Pixie go!
Even you have evil
in your heart.
Stop resisting it!
Let it fill you!
Stop!
‐Huh?
‐Holly!
♪
Stop this, Father.
Holly!
(chuckling)
Father, please stop
if you haven't been
completely possessed by Moo!
I'm glad you came.
You watched your father as
his soul was consumed by evil,
and you saw him
destroy your village
and all the destruction
that followed.
You must be filled with
more hatred than anyone.
Surrender to your hatred,
and drag your friends
along with you!
Are you gone forever, Father?
The weak father you
long for is gone.
I consumed him
with my very soul!
Father?
I wish you could have been
there to see how pathetic
and pitiful he looked
at the very end.
But who are you, then?
I am what your father became‐‐
the most terrifying
monster in the universe
fueled by hatred and evil.
Holly!
You mean nothing to me now.
You are merely an instrument
I can use to create hatred!
(evil laughter)
(shivering)
Yes, Holly, let the
hatred wash over you.
You are the key to releasing
the most powerful
hatred there is!
Take a good look.
Her life is nearing its end.
Pixie!
Stop it!
I'll finish her off
as well as your friends
fighting in other lands.
You monster!
(growling)
♪
Stop it, 'chi!
Yes, that's it!
I can feel your hatred!
♪
Hate me, and
feed my evil soul
with your burning anger!
Stop it!
Stop!
(laughing)
♪
(groaning)
Pixie!
♪
(panting)
Yeah!
♪
(roaring)
Who are you?
Moo's acting strangely!
(yelling)
♪
Release me.
Is this the true
evil of my soul?
♪
(roaring)
(crying)
♪
‐I don't know what's going on.
‐'chi!
Maybe it's just like
the ancient battle!
You mean where an evil
soul takes over everything?
There'd be no enemies or allies.
There would only be destruction!
♪
He's going back to Mount Kyrus.
Pixie!
(panting)
‐Pixie.
‐Let's take her
to Jill's village‐‐quickly!
♪
What happened?
Jill!
I thought you'd gone!
I told the others to leave.
She looks bad!
Bring her to my house!
♪
(laughing)
Master, our Baddies
army has wonderful news!
Victory!
(growling)
♪
What's going on?
Master Moo!
Something's wrong with him.
Prepare to fire!
Fire!
(lasers firing)
♪
Fall back!
(roaring)
♪
(laughing)
What's that?
It sounded like Moo again!
(panting)
All right, we're taking
off for Mount Kyrus.
Keep us posted!
If the final gate is there,
we might be able to
resurrect the Phoenix!
You sure you'll be all right?
My troops are pirate dragons,
so we'll make out okay.
Move out!
♪
I'm afraid Pixie might
become a lost disk.
Poor Pixie.
Is there a shrine nearby here?
Well, yes, there is!
Then take us there.
Don't tell me‐‐Pixie!
Think twice about
this, Big Blue!
Don't do it, 'chi!
They're right!
No, Big Blue.
What is it?
Big Blue wants to fuse with
Pixie in order to save her!
Are you serious?
But if he does that, Big
Blue might cease to exist!
'chi!
That'd be the same as
becoming a lost disk!
Fusing no good!
I won't be a lost disk.
I'll continue to
exist inside of Pixie,
and that's good enough for
me if it means Pixie can live.
"Good enough?"
'chi.
♪
(whimpering)
Don't do it.
‐I am ready.
‐You're sure now?
Because in all probability,
you're going to cease to exist!
‐Are you sure about this?
‐Mmm.
♪
'chi.
We're gonna miss you!
You mean a lot to us.
You're a great friend!
Golem will miss you!
No, Big Blue!
(crying)
♪
Huh?
I'm crying!
I thought I'd
forgotten how to cry.
(panting)
♪
It's time.
I'll never forget any of you.
(whimpering)
(together)
Unlock!
♪
Thank you, my dear friends.
(gasping)
♪
Granity.
It's you.
What's this?
Something's happened
and changed my body,
but that can't happen
unless someone fuses‐‐
(gasping)
Where's Big Blue?
Where did Big Blue go?
I think you know what happened.
Big Blue fused with you in
order to save your life, Pixie.
He what?
How could he
throw away his life?
You've got it all wrong.
Big Blue lives inside Granity!
He said that was good
enough if it would save you.
And also he thanked us.
♪
Oh, Big Blue.
Where's the Baddies' crest?
Two life forms
have fused together.
You've become a new life form.
Fused to become a new life form.
The Phoenix's soul may have
been reborn into a monster,
but the monster
doesn't realize it.
♪
If that's possible,
if the body the Phoenix's
soul possesses is fused,
then wouldn't the
Phoenix be reborn?
You'd better get
away from here, Jill.
We'll wait with the Phoenix
until Vulcan returns.
Is it possible?
Could it be?
♪
(roaring)
(evil laughter)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪