♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the
game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place ♪
♪ To save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it
to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place ♪
♪ To save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
♪
(footsteps)
Master Durahan,
Moo will be mad
unless you find
someone much stronger.
Huh?
There's absolutely
nothing to worry about.
My collection of
warriors is enormous!
Soon, the goddess of victory
will smile down on me,
and I shall
destroy those fools
once and for all!
I summon you to awaken.
Rise, elusive and
reckless warrior,
Renocraft!
♪
(laughing)
I could sure use
something to eat.
I'm starving, 'chi.
It's been over
a whole day now
since we've had
anything to chow on.
I'm not sure how much longer
I can keep up like this, gang.
Golem see food.
Ahh.
Huh?
Feeling guilty, are we?
Some nerve eating
right in front of us.
Hmm?
Do it for your
friends, Golem.
♪
Are you picking up a scent?
Yeah, it's an apple.
An apple?
Where, tell me, tell me!
Where, where is it?
Where is it?
Ah!
It's mine, finders keepers!
Oh, get off of me!
Ahh!
(spitting)
(grunting)
Over there!
(panting)
(grunting)
‐Wait up!
‐Wait!
Save some for me!
♪
Hmm?
Ah!
What an apple, 'chi.
But there's only one.
(panting)
Uh, let's see,
one divided by seven
doesn't make much of
a meal now, does it?
I'll take care
of that dilemma.
♪
Not so fast.
We're sharing that apple.
Yeah.
I'm all for this
idea of us sharing,
and as you all know, I'm
the one with the most smarts.
That entitles me to
the biggest piece.
No way.
Mocchi get apple, 'chi.
Huh?
Mocchi!
(grunting)
♪
Ah.
(shouting)
Mocchi!
The apple.
That apple is gonna be mine!
(grunting)
Ah!
♪
Got it, 'chi.
No!
That was the only
one there was!
I thought we
were gonna share.
Big mistake!
Yeah, whatever.
And we're supposed
to be friends?
Mocchi, we've gone all this
way together, haven't we?
And now this.
But Mocchi was
gonna share apple!
Well, I don't think so!
That was deliberate!
(gasping)
There you have it.
Just goes to show that you
really don't know someone
until the going gets tough.
You people are pathetic,
arguing over one lousy fruit.
Bow down before him,
ladies and gentlemen.
The amazing Tiger speaks.
‐Knock it off!
‐No!
♪
(sobbing)
Hey, you owe Mocchi
an apology, Genki.
Hey, he's the one who ate it.
Yeah, but Mocchi
didn't mean to.
It was an accident.
Listen, that does
not change the fact
that he ate the apple.
Hmm!
Mocchi, there's nothing
to feel bad about.
‐Huh!
‐Come on.
♪
(grunting)
Go!
♪
Dumb apple tree.
(gasping)
Of all the rotten luck,
coming across a desert
when our stomachs are empty.
We'd probably be
smart to take the path
that winds along
the mountains.
Hey, the mountain
might be tough,
but at least it's
better than the sand.
Absolutely.
Mocchi's going this way, 'chi.
What's his problem?
I guess we better split up
till Mocchi cools
off a little bit.
Wait up, Mocchi!
They're gonna need
me to protect 'em,
so the rest of you
go the other way
and we'll meet up later.
Let's blow then!
Who knows, maybe we'll even
find some grub up there.
Yeah, you're probably right.
♪
Hmm!
Ah.
♪
Golem go this way too.
(pounding)
♪
(grunting)
Whoa!
Golem should have
gone other way!
(whooshing)
♪
What is that?
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Niton's a snail,
fast talkin' and bold ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ He'd give up his mother
just for some gold ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ This one comes back
each time as an ape ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Sweet Baby Bossy
just can't escape ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Stone Dragon's spewin'
cracklin' fire ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all, 'cause
they're all for hire ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Ah, this road is getting
steeper and steeper.
I thought you said we
were gonna find food.
I knew we should've
gone the other way.
Well, well.
This doesn't look too
promising, does it?
Huh?
Check out this rope.
Looks suspiciously
like it's been cut.
And on purpose.
'chi!
♪
(gasping)
(grunting)
Oh, no!
Something's chasing
the other guys!
Chasing them?
(grunting)
(screaming)
Mocchi!
♪
(shouting)
Torpedo Attack!
(zapping)
It's gone.
(grunting)
♪
Oh!
Whoa!
Ahh!
♪
Ah!
(panting)
♪
Ah!
Dragon Kick!
Yah!
Holly, Mocchi!
Genki, Suezo!
Are you okay?
Well, I'm all right.
And you, Mocchi?
Huh?
Mocchi!
(groaning)
♪
It's coming!
It just won't give up!
Tail Attack!
(whooshing)
Somebody get me down!
I'm gonna barf!
Tornado Attack!
I'm gonna hurl.
(whooshing)
Ooh.
♪
Ah!
A Baddie!
(zapping)
Now he's done it.
Yah!
Dragon Punch!
Torpedo Attack!
(zapping)
(shouting)
(growling)
Here it comes!
No use, Genki.
There isn't anything we
can do to stop that thing.
Run for it!
(grunting)
(shouting)
Go!
Here!
Over here!
Run for those rocks!
(panting)
♪
(shouting)
Go!
Ahh!
Mocchi!
(zapping)
♪
(panting)
Mocchi, grab on!
♪
What the‐‐
(screaming)
♪
Mocchi.
(shouting)
(sighing)
♪
Let's escape while we can.
I'll go first.
No, it's too dangerous!
What do you mean?
He's still waiting down
there under the sand.
The second we jump off from
the rocks he'll attack us.
I think Hare's right.
I guess the safest thing
to do is stay here.
Huh?
How am I supposed to relax
when all I'm doing is
thinking about eating?
That's right.
With all this excitement,
I forgot that we
still haven't eaten.
♪
(growling)
Oh.
(thudding)
You'd think Mocchi
would at least come down
off his high horse
after all this time.
Well, considering
how mad you were,
you can't really blame him.
Hey, you were as mad as me!
Think you're mistaken.
The only people here
who got mad at Mocchi
were you and Hare.
Oh, no you don't!
Don't you go
getting me involved.
Hare, this is your fault!
Stop that!
Genki, you know for a fact
that Mocchi didn't eat
that apple on purpose.
So what?
So, why don't you
just apologize?
Then we can all
kiss and make up
and just get out of here.
Doesn't that make more sense
than sitting here fuming?
Genki!
Hmm!
♪
(sighing)
I'm famished.
Oh, I don't know, gang.
I'm getting pretty hungry
sitting here for
no good reason.
Hare, can't you come up
with some kind of plan?
About time you asked.
Let's see, everybody
except Mocchi is over here
on these two big rocks
and Mocchi's over there.
Hmm.
♪
Way over there.
(wind howling)
Here's the wind.
It's strong 'cause
we're in a valley.
(screaming)
Mocchi, hang in there!
♪
Mocchi!
Made it, but it's
only a matter of time
before he falls,
then he's a goner.
Hare, quick.
We need a plan.
You have come to
the right rabbit.
I call it the
decoy of the desert.
How's that gonna work?
My plan's based on the
fact that the enemy
doesn't come out of the sand
because that's the way
he protects himself
from being attacked
by us, and so...
The plan is to use a decoy
in order to lure
him out of there.
Bingo, you got it.
Except who is gonna
act as the decoy?
Golem will be decoy.
No way, you need
to be light‐footed.
Hare, you'd make
a great decoy,
and since it is your plan...
Out of the question.
You can't afford to lose
my brains, you know.
I'll volunteer.
Good, but you
have to remember
how fast he is on
the sand, okay?
He'll catch up to
you in no time.
Golem will go.
No chance!
I said I'm going.
Golem go.
A carriage.
Hey, I know!
I'm going!
‐No way!
‐Go!
You're an even worse choice.
Then why don't you go?
Oh, I‐‐I think
I'm coming down
with some sort of
a desert storm flu.
(screaming)
♪
Ah!
Mocchi!
I'll save you, Mocchi!
(shouting)
(gasping)
♪
Mocchi, don't let
go, all right?
Hmm!
Mocchi!
Huh?
Ah!
♪
(shouting)
(gasping)
Hey, over here,
sandbag, this way!
Mocchi, you gotta run for it!
♪
(panting)
Ah!
Blossom Blizzard!
(shouting)
♪
Got ya!
(screaming)
♪
Genki!
Get him to go to that rock!
♪
That's right!
Is everything ready?
You bet!
(growling)
‐Air time, Mocchi!
‐'chi!
♪
(shouting)
Let's do it!
Dragon Kick!
Torpedo Attack!
Tornado Attack!
Tail Attack!
(zapping)
♪
(grunting)
(cheering)
Yeah!
Genki, Mocchi!
♪
Well, guys, it looks
like we finally made it
out of the desert.
Eh, I'd start jumping
up and down for joy
if it weren't for
this hunger problem.
♪
What is it, Tiger?
Fruit.
I can smell it.
Where is it?
That way!
(grunting)
(panting)
♪
(gasping)
Go get it.
Go.
(grunting)
♪
Here it comes.
(grunting)
♪
Hmm.
‐Hmm.
‐'chi?
Sorry.
I said sorry.
'chi!
Ah!
Is that for me?
(giggles)
Hmm.
Down the hatchet!
Ah.
(growling)
Oops, hi, guys.
Please don't think
that we're not glad
that you guys have
made up and all.
But how's about sharing with
the rest of your friends?
♪
It's raining food!
Ah.
(munching)
♪
(laughs)
(laughing)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪