♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(mystical humming)
We've gotta get across that?
If it's not a desert,
it's a mountain.
Just leave this one to me;
I'll teleport us!
Here we go.
♪
Teleport!
He's gone!
♪
(laughs)
I did it!
It's a success; I teleported
across the wilderness!
Suezo, you haven't
moved an inch.
Huh, what?
But, but!
Let's go.
Ha, so much for teleporting.
But that's not true!
You see, I moved three inches!
From there to here
is three inches.
Yup, uh‐huh.
(laughs)
Hey!
♪
Hey, you guys wait up!
Oh, come on!
I can do it, I can do it!
(grunts)
♪
You say they're heading for
the Kamarakoo Mountains, Ebony.
Well, according to our
latest intelligence report,
unfortunately, yes,
Master Gray Wolf.
But, don't worry,
we won't let them cross.
Oh, Captain, Master Moo's
enemies must be stopped.
Yes.
♪
All right, gang,
let's get going.
I can't move another inch.
I may never walk again.
Huh?
♪
Water!
Water, where?
Let's go!
Follow me!
Right behind you, buddy!
I thought they said
they couldn't move.
(laughter)
♪
Tiger, what's the matter?
It's nothing, Genki;
tricks of the mind.
Okay, Mocchi, the last one
to the top of the mountain
is a rotten egg.
Mocchi!
Genki!
We'll see ya at the top, Holly!
At the top!
Oh!
(laughter)
♪
(slurping)
That tastes great!
♪
Yahoo!
Mocchi, Mocchi!
(laughter)
Mock.
♪
(panting)
(yelping)
I'll check it out.
♪
Genki, Mocchi,
I'll be right there.
♪
(chuckling)
You've gotta be pretty
agile to dodge that.
You're one of Gray Wolf's
baddies, aren't you?
Ebony's the name, my friend!
(growling)
♪
You're trying to separate
me from my friends!
A little slow on
the uptake, aren't we?
♪
(grunting)
(zapping)
Torpedo!
Tornado!
(wind howling)
♪
(chuckles)
Are you having
a nice flight, fella?
♪
Is that the best move
you've got for me, Ebony?
(grunts)
(evil laughter)
♪
Well, guess there's
a bit more going on
in here than you figured.
(grunts)
♪
'chi?
Run for it, Mocchi!
(grunts)
♪
(yelping)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, you claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Captain Black Dino,
one of Moo's best ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Lead the Black Dinos
on every conquest ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Little Spot Dino,
harmless enough
to unlock a Kuro ♪
♪ You've gotta be tough,
Captain Kuro
will stomp and roll ♪
♪ These monsters rule,
unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
'chi!
♪
Glad that's over.
Go‐‐go away!
♪
'chi, oh, it's the baddies!
They chased me down here!
Oh, no!
(panting)
♪
You have no business
bursting in here like that.
What if they find you?
Get outta here
before you cause me
some real trouble!
But, they've got
my friends, 'chi.
That's got nothing
to do with me!
I've gotta help, Mocchi!
If the baddies see you,
they'll find me!
Go that way!
♪
'chi?
But which way do I go?
This way.
♪
My name's Mocchi,
what's yours?
Please, tell me?
It's Ducken.
Do you live all alone?
Do you, 'chi?
That is none of your business!
♪
Did you make all
these tunnels by yourself?
Neat!
Where do the all go,
Ducken, huh?
Oh, stop it.
♪
That's the trail
over the mountain.
Where's the baddies' camp?
You don't wanna know.
Please, tell me?
Hey, if you hang around,
they're gonna find me, too!
♪
So, hurry up and go.
That way.
Thank you, Ducken!
♪
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Make no mistake, we'll find
your missing colleague soon.
So, say bye‐bye!
I doubt it!
(grunts)
Why don't you just give up?
This is where your journey ends.
Mock, Mock, Mock,
Mock, Mock, Mock.
♪
Now, pick up those roots
and find that little guy
and don't come back
until you do!
Oh, great.
No, how am I supposed
to look for food?
(gasps)
Mocchi, Mocchi, Mocchi.
Huh?
♪
Mock!
Mock.
♪
I think I fooled them!
Make a detailed search
of every blade of grass!
♪
Wow, that guy sure
is dragging his feet.
Yeah, he has
certain similarities
to another monster I know.
Why are you looking at me?
(grunting)
♪
'chi, 'chi, 'chi, 'chi.
What?
(nervous tittering)
Huh?
♪
Wow, look over there!
Over where?
On top of the mountain!
Look, there it is again!
There what is?
I don't see anything.
'chi, 'chi, 'chi, 'chi.
♪
Huh?
We've got 'em.
Mocchi, run!
♪
Come on, Mocchi!
'chi!
Hey, look, it's Mocchi!
Oh, yeah, what was
your first clue?
(laughs)
Did you think a trick
like that was gonna fool me?
Mock.
Mock!
'chi, 'chi, 'chi, 'chi, 'chi!
(grunts)
'chi, 'chi, 'chi,
'chi, 'chi, 'chi!
Huh?
After him!
♪
I've gotta chance it.
I'm starving.
'chi!
(yelps)
♪
(yelping)
You are nothing but trouble!
You are gonna lead them
right to my tunnels, Mocchi,
and then what am I
supposed to do?
Your tunnels?
That's it, 'chi!
Ducken, if I could use
the tunnels, I could lead
the baddies away
from their base!
I told you to get out
of here and leave me alone!
But I gotta save my friends.
Friends, schmends.
Don't you haven
any friends, Ducken?
No, I do not!
And who needs 'em anyway?
My friends just ran
away and left me!
But friends don't do
things like that.
Apparently, you're
right about that.
I guess I'm the only one
who thought we were friends.
'chi.
Yup, there used to be
lots of wild monsters
on this mountain.
♪
But one day, Ebony came along.
Everyone fought
to protect the mountain.
(laughter)
I was too scared to fight.
They were chased
off the mountain
and wouldn't take me with them.
So, I stayed.
All I do is look
for food and hide.
(gasps, panting)
♪
Do you get it?
Cowards don't have
any friends, Mocchi!
That's not true, Ducken.
Friends are friends,
even if you're a coward.
Friendship is from the heart.
Huh?
Please, Ducken, let me
use your tunnel!
Even if they catch me,
I won't tell them where you are.
Please, Ducken?
Hmm?
♪
Do what you want.
Ooh, thank you, 'chi!
Hey!
♪
How hard can it be to find
a little bouncing ball?
Mocchi.
I'd sure like to play fetch
with one of those twigs.
♪
'chi.
Mock!
Mocchi, Mocchi.
(growling)
♪
More, 'chi.
I'm gonna lead more Mocks
into the forest, 'chi.
(grunts)
♪
I can't find
the hidden door, 'chi.
(growling)
♪
Huh, where has he gone?
Huh?
♪
Ha, so that's it!
Find all the secret tunnels
and destroy them right away.
I'm done for!
(growling)
(yelping)
♪
Huh?
(rumbling)
(yelping)
♪
'chi?
(yelping)
Huh?
♪
'chi!
What is it?
♪
How's the defense at the base?
This isn't good.
♪
Mocchi.
Ha, Mocchi!
(grunting)
♪
Tornado!
Genki!
'chi!
Ha, that was a nice try,
you little pinky!
Upsy‐daisy.
Who's your partner?
Hands off!
Mocchi!
Why don't you pick
on someone your own size?
(grunts)
Thank you, Ducken!
Friendship is from the heart!
'chi!
Mocchi!
(growls)
♪
Mocchi, Mocchi!
Ducken, it's too dangerous.
But we are friends,
Mocchi, and from the heart.
Ducken.
Bah, so sorry, kids,
but your time is up!
Ready?
Boomerang!
Hey, that's not funny.
Mocks, get after him!
Huh?
(whirling)
♪
Counterattack!
Golem is glad Holly is safe.
♪
Okay, let's show 'em!
(zapping)
Okay, you Mocks, attack!
(gunfire)
(grunting)
♪
Retreat, let's retreat!
(yelping)
♪
Yay, that was great!
(groans)
Hey, are you all right?
My knees have turned to mush.
Huh?
(nervous laughter)
(laughter)
♪
Are you really gonna stay here?
Mm‐hmm.
Ducken, you will be lonesome.
Uh‐uh.
Even if you're not here,
knowing I have friends
like you somewhere will help
blow the loneliness away.
And now, the Mocks are gone,
maybe the wild monsters
will come back?
I know more about
friendship now.
Ducken, you'll
be just fine, 'chi!
Yeah, thank you, Mocchi!
(chuckles)
Right, we've got
a Phoenix to find!
It's time to hit the road!
Yeah!
Mocchi!
I'll see you again!
See you again!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪