♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Mocchi cold.
Yeah, but we've
gotta keep going.
I'm only gonna
plod along for it,
tired and cold,
not to mention hungry.
We're all tired,
but this is the way
the magic stone told us to come.
Holly's right.
We've gotta keep
heading straight north.
♪
Isn't that the
mountain we saw before?
‐'chi!
‐Yeah, we saw it
from the floating castle!
So that must mean‐‐
Right, that is Mount Kyrus.
Moo is on that mountain.
Man, we really have
travelled a long way.
And we've done a lot,
including getting rid
of General Durahan.
Now we just have
to get rid of Moo.
Yeah, sure, but he's
got the magic stone now.
What if his body's perfected?
Cheer up, Holly.
Even if he has, I'll
still go right on in there
‐and save your dad.
‐Mocchi!
Thanks, that means
a lot to me, Genki.
That is why we must
go find the Phoenix.
‐Absolutely.
‐And no ifs, ands, or buts!
Yeah!
So what are we standing
here gabbing for?
Let's get to it!
‐Yeah!
‐Let's do it!
♪
(heavy breathing)
Easy does it.
♪
Everything's all set
to go, Master Moo.
Shall we commence now?
Yes, commence!
Right away!
Energy accumulation has begun!
♪
(crackling)
Look!
‐He's healing!
‐We've got big trouble!
Something's gone
wrong with the stone!
♪
What's happening to it?
I don't know, but
it's gonna disappear!
♪
(growling)
(whimpering)
♪
Success.
My soul is filled
with even more
hatred than before!
♪
(gasping)
Mocchi!
Are you sure you
can walk in this?
Mocchi doesn't like snow, 'chi!
Let's hurry up and
find some place to stay!
Sounds good to me, Hare.
Well, the cold isn't
giving me a problem.
Yeah?
Only lower forms of animals
can't feel the cold.
‐Take that back!
‐Try and make me!
Look, a village!
Man, it's a pretty
decent size, too!
But who'd be living
in a place like this
way out in the boonies?
Are they Baddies?
Who are you and
what do you want?
(gasping)
♪
Well, he doesn't
have the Baddies crest.
He doesn't look
like a Baddie, either.
Everyone calls me Jill.
I act kinda as the head
of the village down below.
Genki's the name
and action's my game.
(laughing)
Yes, indeed, I can
see that, young man!
But what brings you way out
in this neck of the woods?
Even the Baddies tend to
stay away from this village.
Well then you must
know the evil Moo.
You see, we wanna destroy him,
so we're searching
for the Phoenix!
Who?
So you need the Phoenix?
Well then you've
heard about the Phoenix,
so maybe you can
even help us find it!
(laughing)
You're wasting your time.
The Phoenix doesn't exist!
It's nothing more
than an ancient legend.
You're wrong, Jill.
We believe in the Phoenix.
And we're positive that
it really does exist.
Mocchi!
Everyone thought
Moo was a legend,
but he turned out to be real.
Yes, well, you folks
certainly sound convinced.
But it's late out, so come
stay the night at my house,
and you can tell
me all about it.
Well, I guess it's better
than sleeping outside.
Come on, let's
take him up on it!
Hmm.
♪
(slurping)
Thanks for dinner,
and also for letting
us stay the night!
Hey, it's nothing,
don't mention it!
We've gotta help each
other out in times of need.
By the way, I'm Holly!
Genki's the name‐‐
Oh, yeah, I already
told you that.
Mocchi!
‐You can call me Hare.
‐I'm Tiger.
Suezo here.
I am Golem.
Oh, you're a nice group,
and I'm glad to have you here,
so make yourselves
at home, all right?
Thanks for dinner!
‐Thank you!
‐I'm stuffed.
‐Mocchi hungry.
‐You just ate!
Now let's get back to this
Phoenix business, shall we?
♪
'chi.
You mentioned that the
villagers had an old legend
about the Phoenix.
Yes!
It happened a long,
long time ago.
Our ancestors worshipped
a large, noble bird
called the Cinderbird.
They considered it
their guardian spirit
and lived a peaceful
and tranquil life with it
in the village.
Until one fateful
day when a demon
named Skull‐Capped arrived.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Find a Seed Sister,
charming but frightening ♪
Unlock 'em all!
♪ Or the Usabas,
quicker than lightning ♪
Unlock 'em all!
♪ There's Evil Hare
and his captain ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ They love to fight
like Pirate Dragons ♪
Unlock your disk!
♪ Mighty they battle,
mighty they fall ♪
♪ These monsters rule,
unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Skull‐Capped was
enormous and strong,
and we were no match for him.
But the Cinderbird
fought to protect us.
(groaning)
♪
Cinderbird was very powerful,
and he quickly
defeated Skull‐Capped.
Then Cinderbird asked:
Why did you attack this village?
Because I was famished!
I'll starve unless I
get something to eat soon!
Mmm.
Then the Cinderbird did
something extraordinary.
It flew into the flames
of the burning village.
♪
I offer you my body
so that you may eat.
But why?
You're so much stronger than me,
why are you
surrendering yourself?
‐We are brothers in this world.
‐Brothers?
And as brothers, we must help
each other in times of need.
The flames that surround me,
the falling snow, the rain,
the clouds, the
mountain, the sun,
the flowers, the
trees, the insects,
humans, and monsters,
we're all interconnected
in the never‐ending
circle of life.
(crying)
♪
The Cinderbird's profound
and generous words
moved Skull‐Capped's heart,
and he relinquished
his evil ways.
Farewell.
♪
The Cinderbird rose from
the ashes as a Phoenix,
but was never to be seen again.
♪
And ever since that time,
the Phoenix has been a
legend in our little village.
♪
That's such a sad story.
‐Yeah.
‐Mhm.
Yeah, very melancholy!
Hard to believe
that the Cinderbird
would do something like that.
Mhm, no wonder the
Phoenix has a reputation
‐for being so heroic.
‐'chi.
Especially considering
the Cinderbird won the fight.
Incredible!
I can't imagine doing that.
Fighting breeds hate,
so the more you fight,
the more you hate the
world and everyone in it.
Fighting bad.
Everyone loses.
I'm starting to agree, Golem.
What do you think would happen
if that hadn't
been Skull‐Capped,
but Moo who was
fighting the Cinderbird?
My guess is that Moo
would stop being evil
just like Skull‐Capped did.
Not a chance, Genki!
That guy doesn't even know
the meaning of a fair fight.
You've got a point,
and we can't try it out
'cause we haven't got
the Phoenix, do we?
Well I say that we go
and get the Phoenix
and then give your plan a try!
Except...
...if we we able to find
the Phoenix and resurrect it,
and then Moo eventually
gave up his evil ways,
then it'd seem like
the right thing to do.
But what if Moo was destroyed?
Then wouldn't his evil
soul keep coming back
again and again and again?
♪
We can never know the answers
to questions like that.
I think we should just put
our trust in the Phoenix.
♪
(laughing)
Come with me, everyone.
I want to show you something.
♪
Whoa.
Many Jills holding up torches!
So I see you're taking them
to the sacred place then.
Yes, that I am.
I'm placing my bets on
these brave young folks here.
You're placing your bets on us?
♪
Hey, could you at least
tell us where we're going?
Just wait and see.
♪
Is this what you
wanted to show us?
'chi?
I don't see anything
except for a lot of ice!
Hurry up and cut to the chase!
♪
It's right here,
in front of you.
‐Huh?
‐Golem not see anything.
'chi!
So where is this thing?
Well, I sure don't see it.
I think this is
some kind of a trick.
Hmm?
The sun's coming up.
And it's shining
on this wall of ice.
♪
(gasping)
There it is.
♪
Holly!
It's really the Phoenix!
It's gotta be!
‐So we finally found it!
‐'chi!
It's the Phoenix.
Our search is over!
We've found it, the Phoenix!
Yes, after all
we've been through,
and now it's staring
us in the face!
Golem like Phoenix!
I can hardly believe it!
We found the Phoenix!
(laughing)
Oh, Tiger, our search
is finally over!
You're right, Holly!
Now nothing'll stop us!
Golem happy!
Phoenix is ours!
Now we get Moo!
(cheering)
We found the Phoenix!
We found it quite by accident.
A big chunk of ice broke off
recently, and when it did,
the Phoenix was staring
us right in the face.
We knew that if Moo
found out about it,
he would use every dirty trick
up his sleeve to destroy it,
which is why we've been
watching you so close.
And now we're positive
your intentions are good.
I looked into your eyes
and saw how honest
and determined you are.
You'll be the heroes who
will resurrect the Phoenix
and make the world the
peaceful place it once was.
And that's why I brought
you here today to the Phoenix.
Jill.
♪
(roaring)
Are you feeling any
better, Master Moo?
Out of my way.
I hate to bring up
the obvious, Master,
but wouldn't it be
better to rest a while?
♪
At last, my day to conquer
the world has arrived!
(evil laughter)
Okay, we found the Phoenix,
but how are we
gonna resurrect it?
That's a good question.
We've gotta find
its soul somehow.
'chi, find the soul!
But where do we start looking,
and how will we know
it when we find it?
I'm afraid even we
can't help you there.
Well, this is
quite a predicament.
How are we gonna find its soul
when we can't even see it?
Golem can't find something
that Golem can't see.
We can't even be
sure it's still here.
You're supposed to
be encouraging us!
(laughing)
Oh, don't mind me.
I was just trying to
work out my thoughts!
Now let's get back to Moo.
Didn't you say this all
started a long time ago
when someone was possessed
by Moo's evil spirit?
Exactly!
Oh, I get it!
When you say that the Phoenix's
soul might not be around here,
you mean it might have already
gone and possessed someone.
That's possible, or it could
be locked in a mystery disk,
or perhaps a reborn monster!
Well, if the body's right here,
don't you think the
soul might be nearby?
Are you picking up
any special feelings?
Mm‐mm.
Why don't you try concentrating
like you used to
with the magic stone?
Good idea.
You try, Holly!
♪
Mhm.
Holly.
It's you, Father.
Ohh.
Is something wrong, Master Moo?
I'm going to take care
of the meddling group
that's been searching
for the Phoenix!
(gasping)
I have a debt to repay.
No, wait, Master, come back!
What did you find out, Holly?
He's coming.
Who are you talking about?
You mean the Phoenix's soul?
My father is‐‐I mean, Moo is!
The sun has come out now, Holly.
Good point, Golem.
Last we knew, his body
couldn't stand to be
in any kind of light.
But maybe now his
transformation is complete!
That's possible,
if he used the energy
from the magic stone, of course.
We're in trouble, 'chi!
I think you guys are right.
We better get outta here fast.
If Moo spots the Phoenix here,
he'll destroy if for sure.
You're right‐‐then
it'll all be over.
We gotta make sure
he doesn't find it!
Otherwise, all of our hard work
will have gotten us
a big fat nothing.
You and the others go
back to the village, okay?
We're gonna take off
outta here as well.
Where will you take off to?
We're gonna act as decoys
and try and lead Moo
away from the Phoenix.
‐That's too dangerous!
‐Hey, there's no time to argue!
(panting)
♪
(growling)
Come on, gang!
We've gotta lead
him away from here!
♪
Moo!
It's been a long time, Holly.
The sun's out!
I knew it, he's completed
the transformation!
It's time, Father.
You and your friends
are no match for me,
but I will not allow you
to resurrect the Phoenix.
Although, realistically,
the chances of you
even finding the Phoenix
are extremely slim.
We've already found the
Phoenix, 'chi, so there!
(nervous laughter)
That crazy Mocchi.
That frostbite
really got to his head.
"Already found it," he says.
(laughing)
You found it?
Don't be ridiculous!
Don't you think we would've
resurrected it already
if we'd found it?
Lies!
You have found the Phoenix!
Where are you hiding it?
What are you scared of?
You're the strongest
monster around,
and yet you're obviously so
scared of some little bird
that we can practically
hear you shaking!
‐What?
‐I have to say I agree.
You're putting on a big act,
but you're obviously
scared out of your wits.
‐Mocchi!
‐You big coward!
Golem stronger!
‐Oh, you're all talk.
‐You wouldn't even
stand a chance
against us, you fiend!
You're not nearly as
strong as you think you are!
(chuckling)
You people are so pathetic,
it's almost funny.
‐What's that?
‐Now's our chance.
‐Is everyone ready?
‐You bet.
Which way do we go?
There's a forest on the left,
so we'll try and
head there first.
Come on, everybody, let's
blow this popsicle stand.
♪
(evil laughter)
(coughing)
You're not hurt or
anything, are you, Holly?
I'm okay.
Gol?
♪
He's one strong monster.
Now who's trembling with fear?
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪