♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
(howling wind)
(zapping)
♪
(pained grunting)
Are you serious?
You mean Moo might have
already merged with a monster?
Maybe, but only if
this Final Gate thing
can actually make
merging possible.
Wait a sec, Monol
talked about the Final Gate.
In the ancient war,
the Final Gate was used
to separate Moo's
soul from his body.
So, he's used
the gate before, right?
Then he might have turned
himself back into monster Moo.
(grunts)
Father.
That'd be trouble.
'chi!
Listen, there's only one thing
we can do to stop Moo now!
We must revive the Phoenix.
And quickly.
But we'll fight Moo
if it comes to that.
No way, pal.
What?
(gasps)
Over there!
(zapping)
Look, they're Zuums!
♪
(zapping)
They vanished.
Those Zuums are Naga's henchmen.
What, Naga!
You mean they're Baddies?
The Big Bad Four.
They're probably patrolling
'cause Naga's castle
is just east of this place,
not too far away from here.
Well, then, they probably
know we're here already.
Oh, 'chi!
Golem think we shouldn't fight.
I agree, Golem; we should
probably find another way.
No, we're staying!
It's huntin' season!
(growling)
Teleport!
Suezo!
It actually worked
this time around.
Wonder what's eating Suezo?
Now I get it,
Naga was the one
who attacked your village.
Yeah, that's right.
Time to pay him back.
♪
There it is.
I wasn't counting
on that many of 'em.
Oh, boy, now how
am I supposed to get in?
'chi!
(yelping)
Gotcha.
Shh!
Thanks for the heart attack!
That's some attitude;
we came to help you!
'chi!
I think you're forgetting,
Suezo, that finding the phoenix
is our main objective.
Naga's always gonna chase us.
A surprise attack
is the only way.
Sounds good!
Holly, this could
get pretty ugly.
Maybe it'd be better
if you went off
and hid somewhere.
Mm‐mm.
I can't run away from Naga
with so many reasons
to fight him.
Let me go along with you, Suezo.
Holly!
(sobs)
We're a team, Holly,
we'll fight him together.
♪
Thank you very much
for coming to this meeting!
Tomorrow is the final battle!
Under Master Naga's command,
we'll stage an all‐out attack
on those humans!
Zuums rule!
Long live the Zuums!
So, they're planning
to attack us.
'chi!
They have troops scattered
around the area where we saw
those three Zuums
and they'll bring in
the main troops
as soon as they discover
where we are.
So, that's what Naga and
the Zuums are planning for us!
Bet they'd be pretty shocked
to find out we're right by
their castle.
Yeah, it'll be
a surprise attack!
We'll sneak in
and catch them off‐guard.
We will attack them.
Right.
Pixie, she's back already!
(whooshing)
♪
How'd it go?
Good, I think I know their plan.
Yay!
♪
Okay, guys,
is everybody ready to go?
(all grunt approvingly)
Good, then let's go over
the plan one more time,
First of all,
Golem and Big Blue,
you'll go over the castle wall
and guard the gate here
to make sure the Zuums
outside don't get in.
You okay with that?
Meanwhile, the rest of us
will get into the castle
and head straight
for Naga's chambers.
(all grunt approvingly)
Pixie said Naga's chambers
are at the top of the castle,
so we should expect
to meet many bodyguards
on the way up there.
(all grunt approvingly)
Our plan is very
straightforward,
but speed is the key.
First, we get Naga,
then we'll take control
of the castle and fight
the Zuums until they give up
and surrender.
What about if the Zuums
don't surrender?
That's Plan B...
where we run!
(all groan)
Huh, how come I'm not surprised?
Golem like plan.
Yeah.
Plan is good!
Then let's move out.
(all grunt approvingly)
♪
Huh?
(grunting)
♪
Look, Pixie's signal!
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters Rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Pick up a square,
stand it on end ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ You got Color Pandora,
watch it defend ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Lilim is cute,
but this one's no fun ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ She wants all the marbles
for her honey bun ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ General Durahan
demands it all,
he sees the world
at his beck and call ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Hmm?
(approaching footsteps)
♪
Where do you think you're going?
Delivery for Master Naga.
Show me what you're delivering.
I can't, this is
overnight service.
Hold it!
Hey, you look like that traitor
on the master's wanted list!
Are you trying
to pick a fight?
Silence!
Show me the goods.
(grunting)
Run!
♪
Don't let them get away!
Hurry, they're after us!
♪
(screaming)
There, now they won't get in.
♪
Thanks, we're counting
on you, big guys!
Go!
Me too!
(panting)
♪
It's this way.
(growling)
You go ahead; I'll take 'em.
I admire your courage,
but there's too many of 'em
for one monster to handle.
I'll stay and help ya!
Go!
Be careful!
Come on.
Move it, people!
Halt!
Not one of you
is getting by me!
Attack!
Torpedo Attack!
(zapping)
♪
Huh?
How did you get in here?
Genki, go after Naga.
♪
‐Let's go!
‐Right!
'chi!
I'm with you!
You're not getting
past me, I'm afraid!
You're the traitor, Pixie.
I'll take that as a
compliment coming from
a bunch of hammerheads
like you guys.
Lightning!
Shotgun!
♪
You're gonna be sorry
you ever messed with us!
♪
(chuckles)
Well, well, you've arrived.
That's right, pal!
♪
(chuckles)
Now!
(grunting)
Again!
♪
The gate will break.
You ready?
Get them!
♪
You're not moving.
If you wanna get past,
you'll have to go
through us first.
Get them!
♪
One Dragon Punch!
Not giving up yet, are ya?
Not this bunny.
♪
(zapping)
Lightning!
(grunts)
Get her while she's down!
Thunder!
(zapping)
♪
Monsters like you
can't bring me down.
Get her!
♪
Tail Attack!
Mocchi, come on!
'chi!
No, don't!
Huh?
Let me get him;
he got my sister
and the rest of
the villagers as well.
So let me at him!
Suezo.
(grunting)
♪
No!
I'm not through with him yet.
(grunting)
♪
Suezo!
Holly, don't give up;
I'll get that Naga yet.
Oh, yeah?
Then what are you waiting for?
Teleport!
♪
Suezo!
Suezo.
Double Pounder!
♪
Eye Beam!
Genki.
Come on, let's get him
with the Mocchi Cannon.
Mocchi Cannon!
♪
You can do it, Mocchi.
(grunting)
♪
It didn't even affect him.
You're weak.
♪
We've gotta escape.
Run, Holly.
♪
(grunting)
We've taken care of the others.
And I'm done here.
Where's the rest of the gang?
Huh?
♪
‐Master!
‐Huh?
Holly!
♪
Hmm?
We once attacked your village
for that piece of stone
you're wearing as a pendant.
Did Moo actually
order you to attack us?
Hmm?
The people in our village
were put through so much.
Did Moo order the attack?
Of course he did.
Master Moo wanted
us to make you
and the other villagers suffer.
♪
Father, have you sold your
soul and become truly evil?
Have you, Father?
My friends.
My good friends,
please help me.
Lend me your strength.
(grunting)
Even now, I can remember
how much we all enjoyed
plundering your little village.
But you escaped!
This time,
you won't be so lucky!
(grunting)
One more shot!
Mocchi Cannon!
♪
(yelps)
Huh?
♪
Here!
Take my hand!
♪
What are you doing,
saving a guy like that?
Here.
Holly.
'chi.
'chi!
♪
Grab on.
'chi!
I don't get it!
What's gotten into you!?
If we don't save the enemy,
we'll be as bad as Moo.
Huh?
‐Grab onto us!
‐'chi!
Hurry!
♪
Oh, the things I have
to go through for you guys!
Hurry and grab on.
♪
So, that's why
you're all so strong.
Well, it's too late for me.
Huh?
I've walked down the path of
evil for much too long now.
♪
(gasping)
No, master!
♪
There's still one thing
that we have left to do, gang.
(sighs)
♪
The battle's over,
pull out of here!
It'd be a waste
of time to fight now!
(groaning)
Yes, Genki's right.
It's over, retreat.
(growling)
We've defeated all
the other followers!
You're the only ones left.
If you still wanna fight,
I'll gladly take you on!
'chi!
Call it quits, Captain Zuum.
Fighting now would
be pointless.
We're leaving, but next time,
you're going to pay!
Retreat!
♪
(sighing)
That does it.
Huh?
That does it!
Just spit it out!
We've just defeated
the last of the Big Bad Four!
(chuckles)
'chi!
(laughter)
Holly!
(sobbing)
Yeah.
♪
(wind howling)
(grunting)
♪
It's not safe; stop it!
We can't!
(panicked grunting)
(zapping)
♪
No, he disappeared
inside the monster!
He vanished!
Master!
♪
(roaring)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪