♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Holly, are you sure
that the mystery disk
is around here?
Well, my magic stone
seems to think so.
Come on, where are you?
(grunting)
♪
(groans)
Hey, watch where
you're going, Suezo.
Why don't you watch
where you're going, Genki!
I've got some dirt‐‐
(Mocchi yawns)
(growling)
I'm hungry.
♪
Here, eat this, Mocchi.
Chi!
Thank you, Chi!
Ah.
♪
Hmm.
Maybe all the mystery
disks are gone.
But then why did my magic
stone react like that?
(owl coos)
♪
Could Golem have...
No, he wouldn't do that.
♪
(munching)
So, Golem, what made you
decide to come with us?
When I invited you,
you said you couldn't.
Eyes.
(laughs)
Oh, I see!
♪
Huh?
Golem, you're staring.
You have...
clear eyes, Genki.
Uh...huh?
Oh, I get it,
he's a kid
and I'm just an eyeball!
(Mocchi cries)
What‐‐what happened?
It wasn't me!
‐Huh?
(cracking)
♪
A mystery disk!
Oh, Mocchi, you found
a mystery disk!
You're the greatest, yeah!
(chuckles)
Yeah!
What's going on?
♪
Mocchi?
Oh, excuse me if I...
(yawns)
...sleeping.
Me too.
(snoring)
Hey, it's not naptime!
Come‐‐
(Genki yawns)
Well, maybe just
a little one.
(snoring)
♪
(laughing)
No resistance at all.
We're not only purple,
we're clever.
Can you believe
the Black Dinos and Jells
actually had trouble
with these clowns?
(laughing)
Ah, and there's
the mystery disk.
Something for Moo.
(snoring)
(struggling)
Huh?
Ow!
(shouting)
♪
(gasps)
But they've woken up!
Lighten up, it's
not my fault.
You're working
for Moo, aren't you?
What?!
Sort of.
We find mystery disks
for Moo and he really
appreciates it.
Well, not this time, he won't.
Oh, goody, this is
my favorite part.
Guess why they call
us the Seed Sisters.
(shooting)
Ah, seeds!
Golem?
You can escape.
Golem.
Follow me!
I'm there!
Mocchi?
♪
(Genki grunting)
Got it!
(Seed Sisters laugh)
♪
‐Ready!
‐Okay!
♪
Incoming!
(shouting)
Genki, Suezo...
in the zone!
Genki!
Come on, let's...
Thanks, Golem.
♪
Fine, just walk away.
Hey!
‐Come back here you!
‐Sisters!
‐Huh?
‐(shouting)
I think I'm coming
down with...
♪
That scrawny little
kid did this to you.
We'll get him.
(growls)
Don't worry, sister,
we'll get you back somehow.
Revenge will be ours!
♪
The disk is placed.
Mocchi's ready, too.
Okay, come on Phoenix,
we're ready!
♪
(Suezo whimpers)
Unlock!
(whip smack)
‐Huh?
♪
(whip smack)
Hey, what's the big idea?
Give that back!
That mystery disk is ours.
(chuckles)
Stop!
My name's Genki!
Do you hear me, Genki!
Guess what?
He doesn't really care!
Oh, yeah, Genki's in the zone.
♪
Yeah!
You're busted.
♪
(whip smack)
Hah, oh no, the little
thief has a big scary whip.
Ah!
(rumbling)
Huh, what's that?
(whip smack)
♪
Ah!
(Genki screams)
Oh, no!
A worm!
♪
Not a worm!
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Phoenix soars
like Master Moo ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Everybody wants 'em,
how about you? ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Moo is a giant,
baddest of bad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Nagas fight form,
to resist would be mad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ 400 monsters
all shapes and sizes ♪
♪ You can't predict them,
they're full of surprises ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
You may be big,
but not quick.
What are you doing?
(whipping)
♪
(Genki grunting)
Useless monster.
♪
Hey, kid, I'm your
problem, not him.
Use the poison!
Whoa!
Genki!
Look out!
(Worm screeches)
Get him!
Wha!
Ah!
Golem, over here!
Genki!
‐Chi!
‐Put me down!
♪
(evil chuckle)
Come here you worthless Worm.
♪
(evil chuckle)
Oh, come on,
Holly, that hurts!
You're doing
that on purpose.
Yup‐‐oh, it's not that bad.
♪
Some tough guy you
turned out to be.
Suezo...
Never mind, let's figure
out how to get our disk back.
Chi, Chi.
That kid didn't look like
one of Moo's thugs to me.
It doesn't matter.
Huh?
Who cares who he is.
What do you mean?
Didn't you see!
That kid!
What kind of person
would beat on a monster?
It's not right.
♪
Genki!
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna find that kid,
and I'm gonna get
that mystery disk back.
He's pretty tough.
Yeah, well, I'm not
scared of him.
A maniac like that
shouldn't be allowed
around monsters.
♪
(spits)
Hopeless Worm!
I thought I told you
to pick only the ripe ones!
♪
Hey, you, stop it!
Who says so?
Says me, that's who!
Who do you think you are
treating monsters like that?
Chi!
(laughs maniacally)
Pathetic.
Watch it, kid.
Don't push me.
I could crush you
just like a worm.
Try it!
They're just monsters, kid.
You use them and then throw
them out when you're done.
You're wrong!
(Seed sisters giggling)
What a surprise!
Sister, look who's
back again!
We meet again.
Just who are you?
They're only weeds.
You're the Seed Sisters,
and you work for Moo.
Oh, you've heard of us.
How delightful.
There are three of us,
but our other sister
is temporarily indisposed.
Yeah, no thanks
to Junior here.
‐Yeah!
‐Awesome.
Allan's the name,
and I'm gonna join Moo.
Huh?
Oh, by the way,
I don't intend
to come empty‐handed.
That's why I'm
bringing you this.
That's so delightful.
A gem.
Get real!
Moo's a big cheeser.
You don't wanna join him!
Cheesy Chi!
Be quiet.
♪
Oh, I love this!
(maniacal laughing)
So, Genki...
Mr. Super Energetic
just runs off and leave us!
Are you sure?
Molly, believe me,
if I can't see him,
nobody can.
It's the worm boy.
Oh, no!
Please, help me.
The Worm is after me.
After you?
You brought him here?!
I guess I was just
too rough with him.
I made him angry.
Don't believe him.
He's setting a trap.
I promise, that disk of yours.
In good faith, here.
Hmm.
One moment, please.
♪
Yup, that's a mystery
disk all right.
How can you tell?
Years of experience
and practice.
(rumbling)
♪
‐What's that?
‐Gas!
♪
Let us go!
My dear, that was excellent.
(laughs)
You tricked us!
So sorry.
Come to Papa,
mystery disk.
(laughing)
♪
Revenge is so sweet.
You know, Allan?
You're making
a big‐time mistake.
You think?
Thanks, kid.
(snapping)
Hey, what's the idea?
Allan, darling,
can you spell O‐V‐E‐R?
What do you mean?
As in we're taking
the stone to Moo
and your role in
this is over.
You two tricked me.
Get them!
Now, Worm, you have to decide.
Allegiance to
the friends of Moo
or to the cruel
person who beats you.
♪
Moo is definitely
a nasty person,
but he won't mistreat you
like this one seems to do.
No doubt Moo would value
a fine upstanding monster
like yourself who obviously
has so much potential.
Come on, don't just lie there.
Do something!
You belong to me!
♪
Help me!
There's a nice (indistinct).
Good boy.
I'd like to welcome you
to Moo's happy little family.
See what I mean, Allan?
This is how the Moos operate.
All right, Worm, showtime.
(screeches)
♪
(groaning)
Just a little payback
for our dear sister.
‐Oh, no!
‐Come on.
You're my monster, remember?
Get 'em.
(shooting)
Watch out!
(shouting)
(Seed Sisters laugh)
(Genki struggling)
Free!
Allan!
My Worm...
They've escaped.
You missed them on purpose!
Bad boy!
♪
Holly, grab the mystery disk!
No problem.
Wake up, Golem!
Oh, Worm.
Allan, help us.
Huh?
This is your chance
to make it right.
♪
‐Contact.
‐Contact
Let's do it.
Worm!
Begin the transformation.
♪
Worm, I'm sorry.
No, don't!
Please stop!
♪
(Seed Sisters laughing)
How moving.
I'm in the zone!
Huh?
(Suezo whimpers)
Stop laughing!
Gah!
Argh!
♪
Ahh!
Unlock!
(whirring)
♪
(birds chirping)
It's unlocked.
He's yours if you promise
to be real good to him.
Hmm?
He's pretty small now,
but don't worry, he'll grow.
Cute, huh?
A worm, for me?
You sure?
Uh‐huh.
♪
You think worm boy's
gonna do better this time?
You saw his face, didn't you?
Yeah, he's definitely
gonna be all right.
♪
It'll be different this time.
We'll battle against Moo...
using the strength
that comes from within.
♪
That was kind of fun, I guess.
But now it's time
to find the Phoenix.
Yes, find the Phoenix.
And release all the lost
monsters from their disks.
All right!
Chi!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪