♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
Okay, gang, let's rip it up!
Great day, I'm ready!
Let's go and get that Moo!
Hm.
I get tired just watching him.
Mocchi is hungry!
(collective sigh)
The truth is, ta‐dum...
this is all we have left.
Hmmph!
Makes sense to me seeing
as all we ever do is spend.
Steal it.
(in unison)
Huh?
If I need something,
I just take it.
Come on!
If you really want to be
a member of this team,
you've got to learn
not to steal!
Understand?
Well, who said I wanted
to be a member?
What, why, you‐‐you‐‐grrr!
(growling)
Come on, Genki!
Maybe you and Tiger will be
nicer after you've had lunch.
(squealing)
(giggle)
♪
Wow, this sure is a busy place.
Look at that!
A coliseum!
♪
Hey, there's prize money!
Goodie, this must
be my lucky day!
Win some prize money!
♪
(twinkling harp)
Huh?
Oh!
Wow!
(cheering)
♪
Lots of watchers, 'chi.
There's so many people
I'll bet the prize money
must be pretty good, huh?
So then, who's
going for the gold?
Don't look at me, I don't
have enough moving parts.
I mean, if I got hurt, then
who'd be looking out for ya?
(collective sigh)
Oh, come on now, it was a joke!
Ah, all of a sudden my stomach
hurts something awful.
Mocchi, you'll have to enter.
I'll enter for us.
‐'chi.
‐Really?
So you are a member of our team.
If being on the team
is how I get moving, I am,
and this team's best
hope to win is me.
Way to go, Tiger,
better him than me!
(chuckles weakly)
Gah, come on, lighten up
people, it was a joke!
You could show
some appreciation.
And starting now,
the battle for the prize
money will begin!
(cheering)
♪
And now for our first
contestant, it's Red Eye!
Yeah!
And making his coliseum‐‐
this must be a mistake!
It's no mistake.
♪
(whimpering)
There's no mistake!
It's the one and only
Tiger of the Wind!
♪
(whimpering)
That monster is a renegade!
And a thief!
Huh, lots of loyal fans, I see!
You should see them
when they're mad.
Get ready, get set!
Now watch and learn!
Yeah, do it, Tiger!
♪
‐Tiger!
‐Yay, Tiger, 'chi, 'chi!
Go, oh, the battle has begun!
Red Eye is showing
some fancy footwork,
but, whoa, I don't believe it,
Tiger hasn't budged an inch!
Tail Attack!
Someone check if
he's still breathing!
♪
Tail Attack, give him
your Tail Attack!
Don't rush me!
(whimpering)
Oh, come on!
(growling)
♪
I win.
And the winner is
Tiger of the Wind.
(bell rings)
Tiger has defeated Red Eye!
‐That was cool!
‐Yeah.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
♪
(grunting)
Yeah!
(wind blowing)
(roaring)
(explosion)
♪
Awesome, wow.
Whoa, man, where are you going?
Don't you think
you ought to stay
and study the next guy's moves?
I have no need to do that.
♪
It's time for the final event!
And over here we have the
monster who has defeated
each of his challengers,
it's Tiger of the Wind!
(jeering)
And the final challenger
for the prize money, Hare!
I love you people!
Ha‐ha, muah!
(grunts)
Ha‐ha, so you're
the famous Tiger,
please be gentle with me.
My name is Hare!
‐(growling)
‐Yikes!
♪
Watch out for this one, Tiger.
I'm ready for him.
Let's get this show on the road!
Come on now, we
haven't got all day!
(growling)
Oh, I'm scared!
(maniacally laughing)
Ready...
begin!
Oh, and Hare feints
to the right!
♪
Come on, Tiger,
show 'em who's boss!
So, you wanna box?
Put 'em up!
Tiger, the Hare
is just baiting you!
Yeah!
And we've got a contest!
(thud)
♪
(growling)
Ah!
So, I guess you lose, my friend.
(growling)
(whimpering)
Ha‐ha, okay, you win!
(thud)
I'm not impressed.
What was I thinking of,
you're twice the monster
I could ever be.
Huh?
I just wanted to do my
best here, and I guess,
I got carried away by the crowd.
Mmm.
Please, please,
please, please, please,
don't hurt me!
(crying)
Hm.
I don't wanna hurt you,
I just want the money.
♪
(tittering)
Huh, Tiger, behind you!
Yeah!
(thud)
Cheater!
I win, I win, I win,
I win, I win, I win...
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters Rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it,
reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Monol's a monster,
a story to tell ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Joker is wild,
he weaves a spell ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Up come the Zillas,
crash in a throng ♪
♪ Unlock your disc ♪
♪ And then top it off
with Zilla Kong ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Monol, Joker,
and Zillas too,
400 in all,
see what they do ♪♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Accepting for our
second prize winner,
Tiger of the Wind, is Genki!
(cheering)
♪
Here you go!
Thanks a lot, yeah!
Hey, Tiger?
Hm?
How you feeling, are you okay?
The grand winner and
undisputed champion, Hare!
(laughing)
Yeah!
Too bad your monster
couldn't cut it, kid.
That's it!
Come back!
Sounds like‐‐
(yelling)
Tiger!
No, mellow out,
second prize is good!
(grunting)
♪
Calm yourself, Tiger.
(chuckling)
♪
Poor little baby, why don't
you run home to Mommy?
(laughing)
Tiger, whoa!
(glittering notes)
♪
Wow!
Tiger of the Wind strong.
Sure is, he fought really hard.
He's strong!
That's enough!
You seem to be forgetting,
that I came in second place.
And we got a bunch of money.
All you care about is your‐‐
Come on, don't
wreck it, you two.
We got what we came for which
was some money so we could eat.
Let's eat!
Yeah, you're right, so how
much money did we get?
Oh, about 2,000, give or take.
Do‐doo‐doo‐‐
Suezo!
I didn't do anything!
Oh, yeah, then what's this?
Gee, Holly, I
really have no idea.
Honest, I‐‐
Come on, Holly, it was
just a little joke.
Very funny, Suezo.
Suezo?
What is it?
Mocchi hungry!
Me too, so how about
getting us some grub?
Okay, let's go.
Yeah!
♪
Because he can't fight
like that everyday.
♪
There, doesn't
this look delicious?
I want to go to a restaurant!
We have to be thrifty, Suezo,
the more we stretch our money
the less you have to fight.
Goodie, goodie, goodie.
'chi.
I'm not hungry.
Vegetables, shmegetables.
Well, okay, fine then,
I guess we'll all just
go without dinner.
(screaming in unison)
Hi, guys.
Hey, how's it goin'?
I was looking for y'all.
(growling)
Oh, calm down, I'm not
here to start any trouble.
I just wanted to talk.
Talk to my fist, Hare!
Hey, come on, that
was then, this is now.
It's glowing, why here?
I was wondering if maybe I could
take you all out to dinner?
Who would want to
have dinner with‐‐dinner?
I'd thought you'd never ask.
What's the catch?
Please, Tiger,
I know that you're not
very happy about losing,
so I thought I'd try and
make it up to you somehow.
And I‐‐I guess I kind
of cheated in our match
and my conscience seems to
have gotten the better of me.
Forgive me!
I promise you that I will
never, never, never do it again.
Oh, and did I happen to
mention that I am an orphan?
That's one of the most heartfelt
apologies I've ever heard.
I don't believe a word of it!
Come on, Tiger, let's
accept his invitation.
If Holly says it's
okay, it's okay, okay?
And we'll spare no expense.
Think it's okay?
Yeah, it'll be fine.
I've just got a feeling.
The Magic Stone's glowing must
have something to do with Hare.
♪
We'll take the deluxe
suite, my good man.
Of course, right away, sir.
‐Hare, what are you doing?
‐What?
There's no way we can
afford a place like this.
Don't worry about it, this
little party is on me, see?
(laughing)
‐Wow!
‐Oh!
♪
Wow, this place is pretty fancy.
'chi!
Bring us the whole menu, please.
‐Yes, sir.
‐Oh, and tell the chef
not to skimp on
the pâté, my good man.
Yum!
(chuckling)
You really don't
trust Hare, do you?
Just keep an eye on him, Holly.
♪
It's been a while since
we've eaten a good meal.
Mmmm.
Holly, my dear,
is everything, okay?
‐Just peachy.
‐Shall we dance?
♪
Get down.
Yeah!
♪
(sighing)
Genki, Genki, come on, wake up!
Holly, what is it?
It looks like Hare has run off!
He probably went for a walk.
Sure, he walked off
with our prize money.
Whoa, what?!
(coins clanking)
(whistling)
Well done, Hare, as always.
Like taking candy from a baby.
Well, onwards and upwards, or
downwards, hey, I'm flexible.
♪
Alright, coast is clear.
Gee whiz, I can't believe
that good for nothing weasel
scammed us like that.
Well, if you'd listened to me.
Well, Tiger, if you
knew he was a bad guy,
you should have warned us.
I should have what?
You heard!
No fighting!
In case you've forgotten, guys,
we've got some real problems.
Like what's going on
with the Magic Stone.
Genki, is it clear?
Well, I don't see anyone.
We're out of here.
Ah!
Ha... hi, there.
Well, looks like the big
spenders are checking out.
♪
This is terrible, just terrible!
(crying)
Don't worry, Suezo,
that Hare is going to pay
for what he's done to us.
Making us look
like common criminals.
'chi!
Come on!
Bye, Cinderella!
So, how do we find him?
That's easy, I can smell
that rabbit a mile away.
‐Cool!
‐Yes, I've got it!
And so we'll just find
our little rabbit friend,
get our prize money back
and be on our way!
‐Ha ha!
‐Hey!
Hey, where'd he go?
♪
Hm?
The prize money!
(loud crash)
(groaning)
♪
Why, that Hare!
(laughing)
♪
Well, well, well, another
day, another opportunity.
(cackling)
Bet those guys are going nuts
trying to find their money.
Too bad.
Gold, gold, gold, suckers!
(growling)
Ah!
♪
(whimpering)
Serves you right!
You didn't really think I
was going to let you get away
with this, did you, champ?
Oh, Tiger, so how are ya,
sorry I had to leave so soon,
something just came up.
Just drop the act, furball.
(laughing)
Oh, very funny, drop
the act, I'm dropping soon.
Listen you, I'm hanging here
by a thread, pull me up now!
Yah, help me!
Please, Mommy!
You humiliated me back there
in front of thousands of people,
so perhaps you could explain
why I should help you at all.
No problem, but I don't think
too well when I'm stressed!
(screaming)
Great!
♪
Grab hold!
Okay!
(crashing)
♪
Tiger!
Are you okay?
Mmm.
(chuckling)
Here's the cash.
Yes, well, thank you, my friend.
Sorry for the trouble.
♪
So, let me get this straight.
Now, you're going
to revive the Phoenix
and turn all the
Baddies into goodies?
All the Baddies and
that includes Moo.
Alright, I'm coming
with you guys!
It's a dangerous
journey, you know.
I don't care, I'm not scared,
I have to follow my destiny.
I wanna fight!
(snickering)
And what's your scam this time?
I've got no scam!
I'm Genki and you're
welcome to come with us,
but I sure hope you learned
your lesson back there.
And my name's Holly.
And I'm Suezo.
Mocchi, Mocchi!
Golem.
And of course,
Tiger of the Wind, ha!
And you know about me!
Obviously, my
strong point is this.
Stick with me and you'll
never have to think again.
And trouble will be endless.
The problem with
monsters like him
is they lack
a generosity of spirit, ha.
Says who, Hare?
Says me, Tiger!
(growling)
The pot calling
the kettle black.
How sweet.
‐That's it, let's get him!
(growling)
That's why the
Magic Stone was glowing.
We were supposed to find Hare.
Yeah!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪