♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
♪
Relay this message immediately!
This Genki and his team are
an annoyance to Master Moo.
Now go!
Right away, sir!
♪
Master Moo?
What?
The Weeds have been dispatched.
Then why aren't we underway?
Master Moo, with
your permission,
the gigantic thundercloud
is closing in.
You think a thundercloud
will stop me?
Head straight north,
Captain Weed.
Yes sir!
♪
(cackling)
At last, at last!
(energy blasting)
I will find my real body and
feel like my old self again.
(cackling)
♪
Mmm.
Is it ready?
Hungry?
Remember when Moo talked about
the real power
of the Magic Stone?
Yeah, he used it to
locate his ancient body
and I bet he's headed to
those mountains right now.
And if Moo can use
it that way,
why can't we ask it where the
Phoenix's ancient body lies,
right, Genki?
Yeah, that sounds
like a plan to me.
Oh, well I don't know if
my power is strong enough
to do something like that.
Your power won't work
if you don't believe.
Anyway, Holly, you'll never
know if you don't give it a try
and see what happens.
Hungry!
Yeah, and the seven of us
are getting so good
at working together
as a team,
Moo won't stand a chance.
(moaning)
It's ready!
(laughing)
Hey!
(slobbering)
Hey, watch it!
Oh!
We have... a ways..to go.
♪
Why, those troublemakers!
Yes, Gali.
How dare they even think they
can rebel against Master Moo?
And Master Gali, they
got Pixie to join them.
So it seems they have
some miraculous power!
Hmm.
What is it, Weed, magic?
Master Moo doesn't know.
I'll get Pixie to tell me.
And the rebels?
Ha.
I'll use the Zuums.
♪
Magic Stone, tell me where
the Phoenix lies asleep.
♪
Hmm.
May the power of my father's
talisman help me.
Huh?
♪
(energy humming)
‐You did it!
‐Did it, chi!
That there's my little Holly,
she's all grown up now.
Well, I don't know
for sure if it worked.
Come on, we won't know
unless we try, right?
I buy that.
Yeah, but what if
it's not there?
We just laugh in
the face of danger.
(laughing)
That dagger, so what's the
story on that anyway, Holly?
Dangerous little trinket
ya got there, young lady.
Uh, it's just something
I found at the floating castle
that reminded me of my father.
Huh?
Hehe, yeah!
Okay, let's grab some air!
Make some tracks!
Holly, you coming?
(sighing)
Huh?
Uh, yeah.
♪
(humming)
Hold me back, it's
the sound of waves!
Awesome, so we're heading
to the ocean, that's great!
Ah, the smell of the sea,
nothing like it!
Right on, the ocean, yay!
Chi?
Mocchi, you don't know
what an ocean is, do you?
You know, the ocean!
It's very large
and big and vast.
Mmm, now I see!
Like mountain?
Ha, come on,
let's go, ha, yeah!
(laughing and shouting)
♪
What?
This is it, the ocean.
Chi!
See, pretty nifty, huh?
Suezo, we've never seen
the ocean before either.
I know.
Ah, hey, Golem?
(gulping)
What's happening, Golem?
Oh, nothing, no problem!
Whatever.
♪
Told ya it was big.
Mmhmm.
I can't help but think
that if I had a gold
for every drop of water
that's out there,
I'd be one rich monster!
Is that all you
think about, Hare?
Well, Tiger my boy, it
goes something like this:
If you stop eating so much,
I'll stop thinking about
how to pay for it!
Is that so, Hare?
Yeah it is!
No fighting, chi!
Holly, the Magic Stone.
Where do we go?
(energy humming)
♪
The Magic Stone is pointing
right across the ocean.
Ideas, anyone?
Well, how 'bout a boat?
Yeah, if there's a harbor
somewhere around here.
Umm..
'kay, I'll do it!
You just remember to catch me
this time, Golem, 'kay?
Uh, but Suezo,
of course I will!
Don't worry.
Ready for liftoff, then.
(yelling)
♪
Hey!
The harbor!
Golem!
♪
Nice catch, Golem.
Suezo, I'm so sorry.
No, no problem, there are
lots of Suezo monsters around
if you know where to look.
He said he was sorry.
I'm fine.
Okay, as long as you're sure.
Hey, wait up!
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Mocchi is pink,
but Mocchi is tough ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Zuum troops and their
captain play kinda rough ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Suezo looks far,
soars through the skies ♪
♪ Looking for Rockies,
they aren't bad guys ♪
♪ Horn the pirate
says that he's pure ♪
♪ But he's a monster
can you be sure? ♪
♪ Unlock it, unlock it,
unlock your disk! ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Busy place.
It's a ghost town.
Looks like the Baddies
have been here.
Bingo!
(surprised shouting)
Hi!
(whistling)
Zuum!
Ah!
(laughing)
We present greetings to you
from Master Gali, rebels!
(shouting)
Master Moo and Master Gali
don't take kindly to rebels
cluttering up their kingdom.
It's not nice to point!
Come on, we can
take these clowns.
Chi!
You don't scare us!
Yeah!
Huh?
(shouting)
Halt.
♪
Ha ha ha, ahoy mateys!
Horn, the righteous
pirate is here!
My ship has come in!
Let's heat things up a little!
Aye!
♪
(groaning)
Head for the hills!
Run away!
Ya yellow bellied Zuumers!
Incoming!
I got it!
♪
Ahh!
Lousy landlubbers!
Load up the special,
ya bilge rats!
Fire!
Heads up!
I...got it!
♪
(shouting)
Ashore, me hearties!
My treat, men!
♪
I'll keelhaul whichever one of
you brig rats told me this place
had the best chocolate
milkshakes on the seven seas.
I'm sorry, Horn, I was‐‐
Sorry, is it?
Well, 'sorry' doesn't get
me a chocolate milkshake,
does it, Rocky, my boy?
Hey!
What's the big idea?
Watch it, landlubber, no
milkshake makes Horn cranky.
What?
You want a fight?
♪
Captain Horn, they don't
really look like Baddies to me.
Huh, then who are
ya straphangers?
No, you tell us, first!
Looks like you wasn't
listening, was ya, my boy?
Just like I says,
I'm Horn the Rig‐‐
Huh?
♪ I'm Horn the
Righteous Pirate ♪
♪ I'm pure as the
sea which I‐‐ ♪♪
Get a grip on yourself, Horn!
And who's gonna make me, matey?
I am.
Let's dance.
Fine then, let's tango.
Now Suezo,
just a minute, Horn!
Now let me get
this straight,
you're planning
to defeat Moo?
Yeah, and we need a boat
so we can find the Phoenix.
It's not really that
complicated a concept, Horn,
it shouldn't be too far
beyond your understanding.
We need you to take us
across on your boat.
And since you and
I are both businessmen,
we know everything
has a price, so how much?
Hehe, I find I'm not
partial to money.
How 'bout a game
of cards, then?
Say what?
Game of cards?
Huh?
If I lose, you get your
passage across, and if I win,
Miss Holly sails away with me.
Forget the lousy cards,
let's just fight.
That's no deal, Horn,
it's an insult.
Just exactly what kinda
monsters are ya anyway?
The good kind, ya soggy Suezo!
I say let's go for it.
‐Huh?
‐Holly!
You would risk everything
on a game of cards?
We don't have a lot of choice.
Fine, cards it is, me hearties.
So who's your best?
♪
Five card stud!
No, old maid!
Huh?
And I, Hare, will
shuffle the cards.
Thank you.
(humming)
Very good, chi!
As I've told you, me and me
Rockies are righteous pirates
and we don't take
kindly to cheaters.
This is what we do to cheaters!
Could someone give
me a... hand here?
♪
Just do your best.
No pressure, just win, Suezo.
Hmmm.
(mumbling)
Ha!
♪
Daww!
(laughing)
♪
(gasping)
Not good, chi.
'kay.
(laughing)
♪
(gasping)
Chi.
Would you be quiet?
Now now, there's no need to
take it out on the youngsters,
now is there?
(grumbling)
♪
Hmm.
I think this, no, this.
Ha!
(growling)
Ha ha ha ha!
(giggling)
♪
Huh?
How does he keep doing that?
♪
I get it!
Pick.
Well obviously, it's this one.
Yadda, yadda, yadda,
yadda, yadda.
Ha.
♪
(gasping)
(whimpering)
I choose...
♪
What's the big idea?
Hey!
Come on!
How'd you do that, chi?
(laughing)
Nice try but you
can't kid a kidder.
Righteous pirate, my eye!
♪
Aha!
Cheater, I would have
won, you cheater!
Cheater, cheater,
cheater, cheater, cheat‐‐
Are you saying I cheat?
Got that right, Horn!
(growling)
(crashing)
♪
This way!
The pirate that
runs away, Horn?
I'm no match for them
on land, me heartie!
Please, Horn, take us on board!
Well, I‐‐I might have
had a small advantage.
Chi!
Alright, you won.
♪
Huh?
Lift the anchor!
Hoist the sails, you brig rats!
(metal clanking)
(grunting)
♪
Huh, where's Golem?
Look!
♪
Come on, Golem, get onboard!
I'll stop them, you go ahead!
Golem, no way!
We're not going without you!
Go, bye!
♪
Quickly, Golem, quickly!
See you later!
All this, just because you're
afraid of a little water, Golem?
Huh?
Ha ha ha, he's
afraid of the water!
It's nothing to laugh at, Hare!
Aww.
Naw, come on,
get over it, Golem!
Uhhh...
Let's get cracking!
We're a team, Golem!
Quickly, chi!
When you're scared,
laugh it off, remember?
Ha ha ha!
Huh?
Attack!
Wait!
Golem!
♪
I'm coming!
Wait!
Golem!
♪
(grunting)
(sighing)
You're part of the team, Golem.
Part of the team, chi!
Yeah.
Aww.
I'm really glad you could
make it aboard, matey.
How could you leave us?
Come on!
Thanks!
Ha, shiver me timbers, mateys!
Let's set sail!
Yay!
Now, listen up, ya landlubbers,
I'll give the orders here!
Let's sail!
(laughing)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪