♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Hey, come on, let's go
and find a mystery disk, okay?
Yeah!
‐Mocchi!
‐Yeah!
Cool it, hot shot.
Where are we supposed to look?
You don't even know.
(exclaiming)
♪
You sure know how
to bring a guy down.
Face it, Genki,
some of us have it
and some of us don't.
You'd probably have us
march off the cliff, Hare.
Watch it, Tiger!
You guys are so silly.
‐Hmm?
‐Instead of arguing about it,
we can just call on
the Magic Stone.
♪
It points west.
Go west, young man, yeah!
Uh‐oh.
Problem, Suezo?
I see something.
♪
Eye strain.
Nevermind.
It is not!
♪
Suezo, what is it?
Don't you guys see it?
Look up there, the huge
dark star in the sky.
♪
Really?
Yeah‐‐no‐‐look, it's a‐‐
wait a sec...
♪
It's the Baddies!
(all gasp, exclaim)
So he's come.
Someone gonna fill me in?
It's Moo's floating castle.
You sure?
You could just knock me
over with a feather.
Yeah, it was pretty much
just a matter of time
before Moo came looking for us.
You mean Moo's in that thing?
♪
Moo big trouble!
Mocchi!
♪
Huh?
Why is the Magic Stone glowing?
♪
I'm ready!
Let's not back down!
This is my purpose:
facing Moo.
Look over there!
Perfect spot for
a planning meeting.
I'm good, any port in a storm.
Suezo!
♪
Must be Moo's idea
of a greeting.
Well, don't just
stand there, guys!
Come on, fight!
Oh, please, Genki, get real.
That's Moo who's sitting
up there, you know?
Huh?
Well, I, uh‐‐I laugh
in the face of danger!
(laughs)
Genki, you're losing it.
Oh no, he's here!
♪
Is that...
No way!
♪
Agh, it's Moo!
(whimpers)
So you've come to fight?
Well, you'll be sorry!
(Moo laughs deviously)
I don't like being laughed at!
I want the stone.
(gasps)
You will have to
get by me first.
‐Understand?
‐Remember me, Moo?
You know,
I still carry the scar
from the last time we met.
Hmm.
These guys are
pretty annoyed, Moo,
I'll do my best but it's gonna
be hard to hold them back.
You destroyed the village
we used to live in, Moo!
Holly and I don't
like you very much.
'chi!
You've gotta stop
using mystery disks
to create Baddies!
Yeah, like, what seems
to be your problem, bud?
You know that violence
and destruction
is a real dead end.
You are so foolish.
Hey, don't push me.
Don't try to reason
with him, Genki.
(growls)
Hmm?
Do I know you?
(yells)
♪
Tiger!
Stay back!
Ah, yes, Tiger
of the Wind, wasn't it?
You led a band of
unsuccessful thieves.
Where's my brother?
Brother?
Yeah, Gray Wolf, you took him.
Steady, this is
my grudge, Genki.
(Moo laughs)
Oh, Gray Wolf.
I've turned him into a Baddie.
You're next.
Oh, no you don't!
♪
Genki, 'chi!
Hm?
♪
'chi, 'chi, 'chi, 'chi,
'chi, 'chi, 'chi, 'chi!
Ahh, 'chi!
(groaning)
♪
We can't fight him one by one.
We're gonna have to
charge him together.
You're right, Hare,
united we stand!
I'll stay and guard Holly.
♪
Okay, all attack formation!
Yeah!
(laughs)
Hey, can it, laughing boy!
Oh, but you give me
so much to laugh about.
Your move.
Down with the Baddies!
Yeah!
♪
Yeah, ha‐ha!
Feet first!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take a risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Gali, one of Moo's
Big Bad Four ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Big Blue a monster
with power and more ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Pixie's a mystery,
whose side is she on ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ She's one of Moo's Four
but for how long ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Flip some tornadoes
without and within ♪
♪ Four hundred monsters,
someone will win ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Behind you!
Blizzard!
♪
No more Mr. Nice Guy!
(yelling)
Machine Gun Punch!
Take that and that and that
and that and that and that‐‐
Monsters rule!
Mocchi!
♪
‐Oh, boy.
‐Kid's tough.
So, my dear.
(gasps)
♪
(whimpering)
Don't come any closer.
♪
(Suezo yelling)
Holly, is it?
Stay back!
Now, now.
♪
Holly!
My leg is stuck!
Go, Mocchi.
'chi.
♪
Stop!
'chi!
(Mocchi growling)
Hmm.
♪
Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
What?
Mocchi!
'chi!
'chi, 'chi, 'chi!
'chi...
♪
Oh, Mocchi.
Was that it?
The best you had?
You weren't even close.
Bye.
(minions laughing)
Bye!
Consider yourselves lucky.
Oh, and say
goodbye to Holly.
♪
‐'chi?
‐Huh, Mocchi?
Welcome back.
What's going on?
The good news is we lost.
Holly is gone, Genki.
‐What?
‐'chi.
We haven't exactly
come up with a plan.
And where's Moo?
Well, we're not exactly
sure about that.
What we do know is that
he's in his floating castle
and that's up in
the sky somewhere.
It's not much of a plan, is it?
♪
Holly!
Hang on.
Oh.
We aren't going to let
Moo beat us, are we?
Oh...
Hare, what's wrong?
Well, Genki, it's
just that I don't see
any way of us
getting Holly back.
How can you say that?!
Mocchi, yeah!
It's just that,
in my opinion,
100 times out of 100
if we were to fight Moo
we would lose
the fight for sure.
But hey, that's
just my opinion.
Then I guess we'll
fight him 100 times
and if that doesn't work, 200.
Then 300, whatever it
takes to get Holly back.
Enough.
‐Tiger?
‐'chi?
I hate to say it but we
should probably cut our losses.
What?
But, Tiger,
you're not a quitter.
You're always
the one I count on.
Forget it.
How can we possibly hope
to attack a castle in the sky?
There's a way, we just
haven't thought of it yet.
Am I right?
(grumbles)
♪
I'm not giving up!
No matter how hard it is.
I'm going to rescue Holly.
And if you're not
with me then too bad!
Mocchi!
You're right!
I'm with you, Genki,
and I'll use every dirty trick
in the book to save Holly!
And I, I will fight.
‐Tiger?
‐'chi?
♪
Hmm.
You know, you never
cease to amaze me, Genki.
Vulcan could help.
‐Huh?
‐Are you serious?
Vulcan?
The leader of that
pirate dragon crew?
Yup, he's an old friend
and he doesn't like Moo.
Cool!
♪
We'll never win if we
don't try, am I right?
‐That's right!
‐'chi!
♪
‐Enough already.
Vulcan's hideout!
That rock formation!
(gasping)
♪
Cool!
Let's go!
♪
Moo, you say?
That's right.
Tiger, are you asking me to put
my fellow dragons in jeopardy?
Hey, hey, hey, take it easy.
All we need is a ride
to the floating castle,
that's all, no more.
No one is talking to you!
Hare is right, Vulcan.
All we need is the use of
your wings for a little while.
Hmm, you ask a lot.
I know, but you have suffered
at the hands of Moo yourself.
Maybe together
we can defeat him.
It's an opportunity, Vulcan,
for us to do something
good with our lives.
Get out of here.
♪
Well?
Let's go.
♪
Oh.
What?
♪
Is there something else?
Who do you think you are?
♪
You have clear eyes.
Hi there, my name is Genki.
Well, thank you
for dropping by.
‐Hm?
‐We need your help.
Genki, it is my responsibility
to protect my troops.
You won't have any troops
if you don't stand up
and fight Moo.
Do I look like the type
who would be asking a
ten year old kid for advice?
Vulcan, we can win against Moo
if we all work together.
♪
The kid is right!
He has given you good advice.
Yeah, we'll make
a foolproof plan!
Hm.
Come on.
My friend Holly
is in grave danger.
Please!
Hmm.
♪
(Vulcan chuckles)
Who'd have thought
a human being
could stir my heart?
Huh?
(chuckles)
Well now, what do you say
we take these vagabonds
for a ride?
Yeah.
♪
Thank you.
I'm glad I'm not
fighting against you.
♪
(cheering)
Thank you.
Don't mean to interrupt
the warm and fuzzies
but how we gonna
find this castle?
Just relax, these
things that you see
growing out of our backs happen
to be called "wings," pal.
We fly these skies
all the time.
‐Right on!
‐'chi!
Let's go grab some air.
Hm.
♪
What?
Who‐‐
Daddy?
Can't be, no.
♪
Yes?
So, you're awake.
Where am I?
Why, in my floating
castle, of course.
How dare you kidnap me, Moo!
♪
Are you looking for this?
(gasps)
But that's mine!
(shrieks)
You stole that!
You've been using
this Magic Stone
to look for mystery disks.
We can't have that.
Do you know about
the Magic Stone?
I know a lot more
than you do, young lady.
That's impossible!
Only the people in my
village know its secrets.
Oh.
(Moo chuckles)
‐You disappoint me.
‐Huh?
So you haven't
figured it out yet?
You have the power
to use the Magic Stone,
you should be able to see me.
Take a good look...
♪
...at the face under this mask.
It...can't be.
♪
Father.
Now do you see?
It's a trick,
I know it's not real.
Join us, Holly.
We can be a family again.
You'd like that.
No.
Moo, please.
My father, let him go.
Think what I'm
offering you, Holly.
We can rule the world,
father and daughter.
Can rule the world.
No!
(Moo laughing maniacally)
♪
All right, Monsters rule!
‐You bet.
‐Yeah, rule!
'chi!
Yeah!
Rule.
Ready, kid?
You bet.
♪
Yea‐hoo!
Whoa!
♪
Hm.
(chuckles)
♪
Hang on, Holly, we're coming.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪