♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(panting)
It's cold, Chi!
This rain is totally brutal.
Try no arms to
protect your eye,
this stuff stings!
♪
Hey, why don't we go take cover
under that tree over there?
♪
(Genki chuckles)
This tree is awesome.
We can just wait it out here
till the storm is over.
I've never been so wet
in my entire life.
I'm freezing.
This rain doesn't look
like it'll ever let up.
Chi!
You can say that again, Suezo.
I forget what
the sun looks like.
(shaking)
Hey!
♪
(growls)
Not funny, bunny,
that was deliberate!
Tiger, are you trying to tell me
the soaking I got
from you wasn't?
That was an accident.
Give me a break,
Tiger, you meant it.
‐Don't push me.
‐Make my day, pup.
(lightning sizzles)
(tree cracks, thuds)
♪
Everybody knows you shouldn't
ever stand under a tall tree
in a lightning storm!
(gasping)
(thunder cracking)
Hey, look.
Come on, we can go find
shelter in the forest.
♪
Lightning never strikes twice.
It's way safer out here
than it'll ever be
under those trees.
(crash)
♪
Wait for me, wait for me,
wait, wait, wait, wait for me!
♪
There they are.
Master Moo's enemies
won't escape this time.
♪
Wait, look at this!
Huh?
♪
It's perfect.
Now, that's one shelter
lightning will never
be able to damage.
♪
Man, this sure is
an old building.
This place isn't just
old, it's ancient.
Long as we're safe
from the lightning.
Huh?
Just when things
were looking up.
Would you look at this?
Wow, now, that's odd.
It just looks like an
old pile of scrap metal
to me, Suezo.
♪
Chi!
Huh?
Hm.
What is this?
A robot arm.
Oh, wow.
This is robot scrap yard.
♪
What's that?
Oh, cool.
Wow!
Do you think it still works?
Let's try it.
(tapping on keys)
♪
‐That's awesome!
‐I'll say.
Chi!
Our recently completed
state‐of‐the‐art plant
is able to manufacture
300 robots a month‐‐
specifically,
the technologically
advanced Melcarba.
♪
What's a Melcarba?
I don't know.
I'll bet it's
this pile of scrap.
Probably the robot's name.
This was a robot
manufacturing plant.
♪
(gasping)
Sorry, but this part
of the tour is over now.
Huh?
Jaggernauts!
♪
Master Gray Wolf is
extremely unhappy with you.
♪
Oh, brother!
Incoming!
(blasts)
♪
This is not safe,
this is scary!
♪
No way!
Goodies rule.
And I am Genki,
the monster champ.
(grunting)
♪
(shouting)
(yelling)
♪
(sinister chuckling)
Fire attack!
(Genki shouts)
Whatever made you
think you could defeat
the great Master Moo?
Big mistake, boy.
♪
(yelling)
Genki!
♪
Suezo!
Those dirty rats.
They ain't seen nothin' yet.
‐Do yourselves a favor.
‐Huh?
Give up before it gets messy.
♪
(exclaiming)
It's all over.
♪
(rumbling)
What is that thing?
It's the Melcarba!
♪
He's attacking the Jaggernauts.
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it and claim
it, you can tame it ♪
♪ The Phoenix soars
like Master Moo ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Everybody wants
'em, how 'bout you? ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Moo is a giant,
baddest of bad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ The Nagas might form,
to resist would be mad ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ 400 monsters, all
shapes and sizes ♪
♪ You can't predict 'em,
they're full of surprises ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(thudding footsteps)
Captain, what is that?
♪
Jaggernauts, attack!
They got him.
(whirring)
♪
(gasping)
I don't like the looks of this!
(thudding footsteps)
♪
(whirring)
This doesn't bode
well for our side!
Chi!
He's going to attack us!
Stand back, people.
(zapping)
The lightning.
He's repelled it somehow.
♪
Golem!
Twister attack!
♪
Golem!
I've never seen anything
as strong as this.
It really is an ultimate weapon.
Melcarba, stop!
We're not the enemy.
(shouting)
Hey, we're the good guys here.
This robot could use
some serious rewiring.
It can't tell friend from foe.
Okay.
Genki, forget about it.
It's already defeated
Tiger and Golem.
Let's get outta here!
♪
(panting)
Oh, I can't run another step.
Mocchi's tired!
Golem, let's have
a little look.
Go.
You've got it, Tiger.
Hey!
Huh?
(Suezo screaming)
How can I see when
I can't open my eye?
Aye‐yi‐yi‐yi‐yi!
♪
It's Melcarba!
He's still coming!
♪
He's beaming in on us.
‐We're just like sitting ducks.
‐Back to the forest.
It's all right, just
use and abuse me.
Come on.
Golem, hurry!
♪
(gasping, panting)
He keeps coming and coming.
That's the trouble with robots.
They never know when
to call it a day.
So what's the plan here?
Yeah, Hare, what's the plan?
Come on, hurry up.
I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
Well, I suggest you think fast,
'cause we're no match
for something that big.
That's it, we're gonna
need something way bigger.
Something bigger?
You've got a plan
to defeat Melcarba?
Yep!
What is it, Chi?
Hmph, probably just
another cheap trick.
Gee, Tiger, why don't
you remind me again
about what just happened when
you fired your super‐duper
lightning attack, okay?
Don't push me!
Back off.
Would you knock it off,
you two, just for once?
Yeah, we're all just a teeny
bit preoccupied right now!
Suezo, come on,
buddy, don't worry.
I think this is one of
my best plans ever.
(thudding footsteps)
♪
Okay, there he is.
Hey, Melcarba, over here!
So I heard your
mother was a Y2K bug.
(taunting, laughing)
♪
Good robot.
Now just lay off that
long‐distance attack
for a little while.
♪
Come on, this way!
Catch me if you can!
Come on, slowpoke!
♪
Genki, be careful!
It's all up to you, Golem.
♪
Olly olly oxen free!
Come on, come on,
get the lead out.
I'm in here, Melcarba!
♪
Nice of you to show up.
Ha!
Took you long enough.
Golem, take over.
(grunting)
♪
He's still coming.
I will stop him.
♪
Yeah!
We got Melcarba, awesome!
Chi!
Way to go, guys.
I am a genius.
Okay, okay, okay.
We did it, we did it,
we really, really did it.
we really, really‐‐
(rumbling)
It can't be.
It's not possible.
♪
What is your problem?
(explosion)
♪
Lightning attack!
Dragon kick, ha!
I'm on fire!
Twister attack!
♪
Here comes the tail attack!
He's not listening!
This is just hopeless.
Chi!
♪
Blizzard!
(explosions)
♪
Hare, remind me to
explain the essentials
of good planning to you
when this is over.
♪
Take Hare first,
it's his fault.
Are we gonna let
a malfunctioning robot
destroy us?
♪
Hey!
(Genki grunting)
Help me, Golem.
Go.
(oscillating beeps)
♪
Huh‐‐oh no!
Chi!
Hey, Melcarba!
♪
Alley‐oop!
He's coming!
♪
(lightning sizzles)
(huge thud)
♪
Well, that looks final.
It took a major
bolt of lightning
to short‐circuit that one.
Not even Melcarba could
defy the laws of nature.
Man, that is one
decommissioned robot.
Melcarba, our high performance,
high‐tech robot, is guaranteed
to be the ultimate weapon.
Place your orders now for‐‐
That's a negative.
The ultimate weapon
of the ancient people
was just destroyed.
And just in the nick
of time, I might add.
You can say that again.
(sighs)
It's such a waste.
Just think of all the good
that that technology
could have done.
All the possibilities, gone.
♪
(birds chirping)
Look, the sun is out!
♪
Genki.
‐Hey!
‐Hm?
Oh yeah, okay.
♪
Interesting.
I never thought Tiger
would get this far.
I guess it's all up to me now.
All right, my brother.
(Gray Wolf howls)
♪
Tiger, what's wrong?
Just the wind.
The wind?
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪