♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
(gasping)
‐Ahh!
‐What do we do?
♪
You, take me to
Master Moo at once.
♪
Master Moo.
What's happened to you?
I'm appalled to see you
in such terrible condition.
This is but temporary,
rest assured.
How are things on
the Eastern Continent?
(laughing)
Taking over a
continent like that
has hardly been a challenge.
Conquering another
would be easy.
‐Is that so?
‐My main military unit
will soon have complete
control of the continent.
When they do, they
are to rush here
to your aid, Master Moo.
I've heard you have another
select unit under your command.
It's their help I need.
Hm?
The group searching
for the Phoenix
completely destroyed
the Big Bad Four.
Impossible, they couldn't have!
It came as quite a surprise.
That is why I need
to enlist your help.
♪
Durahan?
That group must be destroyed!
Then I can count on your help?
Yes, Master Moo, rest assured
that I will return
with good news.
♪
Yippee!
(giggling)
♪
‐Uh‐oh.
‐Master Durahan.
♪
I'm so glad you're back.
So, what do you think of
my new nail polish color?
Stunning, you are
lovely as always, Lilim.
♪
‐Man your stations.
‐Yes, sir.
Right away!
Yes, sir.
♪
Start the engines.
Yes, sir.
♪
Commence battleship launch.
(engine roaring)
♪
So what did Moo wanna
talk to you about, Master?
He needs to enlist the help
of evil General Durahan.
So Moo's losing his touch.
Hey, let's get rid of Moo.
We'll get 'em now
while he's down.
Interesting proposal, Lilim,
but I have to save my strength
for the day when we gain
complete control over
the Eastern Continent.
But then again...
yes, we will fight Moo!
The timing is perfect.
♪
We'll fight Moo and his army.
My elite troops
will conquer them,
and then there will be no one
more powerful than me.
♪
Behold, Lilim...
my elite warrior,
my ultimate weapon.
♪
Let the battle fires burn!
Now, to destroy
those who defeated
the Big Bad Four!
♪
Hear my voice and
awaken, brave warrior.
End‐Bringer!
♪
Oh, Master, he's magnificent.
End‐Bringer has arisen.
♪
(evil laughter)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, claim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ High on the mountain,
look for a thrill ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ A monster that ice‐bites,
that would be Jill ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Gangster is tricky
like most monsters are ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Especially the Weeds,
too tricky by far ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Some are too kind,
some are not nice ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all,
it's good advice ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
There you have it, gang.
‐It's pointing that way.
‐All righty.
Let's get on our way and
find ourself the Phoenix.
(in unison)
Yeah!
Last one there's
a rotten baddie!
(shouting)
‐Suezo!
‐Did you hurt yourself?
(groaning)
♪
I really showed that tree
who was boss, didn't I?
Well, it serves you right for
rushing off ahead like that.
What do you mean
serves me right?
I can't help it if I
got a little excited!
I wanna find the Phoenix as
much as the next guy, ya know!
You tell 'em, Suezo.
It's only a matter of
time before we find it.
'chi!
Then we destroy Moo.
Mhm, and we'll
have to do it soon
before his powers are
completely developed.
Sure, sure, but keep in mind,
we really don't
have anything to fear.
'Cause don't forget,
we've already won
against the Big Bad Four.
You sure got that right, Bunny!
So seeing as we've got
nothing to be afraid of,
I think we should take our time
in our search for the Phoenix.
‐Quiet!
‐Tiger!
Watch where you're
aiming that thing!
‐I sense the enemy.
‐The enemy?
‐I don't see anyone.
‐You gotta be kidding, Tiger.
Yeah, what're you talking about?
We've gotten rid of
all of our enemies.
‐It's coming!
‐What is it?
(rumbling)
Lightning attack!
(explosion)
♪
Come out, show yourself!
‐It's a baddie, 'chi!
‐Who are you?
I am one of evil
General Durahan's
most loyal and brave warriors.
They call me
End‐Bringer.
You might be loyal, but
let's see if you're brave.
So who's this evil General
Durahan guy supposed to be?
♪
What is that?
Baddies!
(evil laughter)
‐What happened?
‐Attacking us is impossible.
'Cause the thing is,
we're just 3D images.
‐What's a 3D image?
‐Mocchi don't know.
I'm not sure either,
but I can tell you
they're not real.
It is an honor to
meet you, strong one.
I am the evil General Durahan,
the highest officer
in the baddies army.
I reign over the
Eastern Continent.
How could he rule over
the whole continent?
Have the baddies got
that much control already?
Silence!
Our first meeting
will also be our last.
My gallant warrior, End‐Bringer,
shall see to that.
Drill rocket.
(rocket whooshing)
♪
Golem!
Defense metal reduced
to 65 percent.
Courage level 52 percent.
Rocket punch.
♪
Laser cutter.
‐No, Tiger!
Attack metal 72 does
not pose fatal risk.
‐He's stronger than you think.
‐I don't know, guys.
I don't think we stand
a chance against him.
Let's just see what happens
when we join forces.
Let's go show him who's boss.
Stay back, Holly.
‐This could get ugly.
‐'Kay, Suezo.
♪
‐Gol'.
‐Ahhh!
‐You need a tongue slappin'.
Blossom blizzard!
♪
‐Oh no, guys!
‐Double cutter.
♪
Drill rocket.
Eye shots.
♪
Double drill rocket.
(trees crashing)
Golem.
♪
Are you okay?
Genki, are you all right?
♪
Only you remain.
Farewell, strong one.
♪
Laser blade!
(shouting)
♪
Come on.
Here, Genki.
You can't give up
on us now, Genki.
The only reason we got this far
was 'cause of your strength.
You're what kept
all of us going.
Wake up, and help us
find the Phoenix, Genki.
♪
Genki!
‐Yeah?
‐Genki.
♪
I know you're in there.
(explosions)
♪
You cannot escape
the End‐Bringer.
How am I gonna get
Genki to safety?
♪
Target sighted.
Napalm cannon.
♪
Scanning data, target confirmed.
Gigadon hammer.
♪
Up here, tin can!
Double cutter.
♪
The battle ends here.
Where am I?
♪
The pendant.
Where did she go?
♪
Either way, you've reached
the end of the line.
Genki, promise you'll
find the Phoenix
no matter what happens to me.
♪
Holly, I'm comin' for ya.
Trust me, Holly, be brave.
Don't give up, Holly!
Believe in yourself!
Use the power inside!
Never give up, Holly!
♪
I'm comin' for ya!
'chi?
♪
Hey, this ain't no time to
be lying around like this.
Get up, everybody,
get a move on!
(grunting)
End‐Bringer, here we come!
Teleport!
♪
Locking on.
My dagger!
♪
Didn't think we'd
abandon ya, did ya?
'chi.
‐Hm.
Hey, Holly, you
forgot something.
Thanks, you guys,
I knew you'd come.
Does not compute.
Courage level has risen,
88, 90, 92, 93,
97, 95, 91.
Impossible, does not compute.
Why did their courage
levels rise so much?
You'll never beat us!
We're gonna find the Phoenix,
and nothing's gonna stop us!
♪
This doesn't make sense.
I'm far stronger than you.
I should be able
to overpower you.
♪
Lightning attack!
Now's my chance.
(yelling)
♪
Blizzard blossom!
(groaning)
Alley‐oop!
♪
Why, doesn't make sense.
Why, why?
(screaming)
(explosion)
♪
Guess that's the end of him.
Talk about a misnomer.
‐Watch who you're pinchin', bud.
‐All right!
That End‐Bringer
was something else,
but we turned him
into scrap metal!
Back off a foot
or two, would ya?
Aw, come on, give me
a hug, ya big furball!
(shouting over each other)
Hey, what's the
matter with you two?
Are you guys hurt or something?
‐Absolutely starving.
‐'chi.
♪
(laughing)
(engine whirring)
♪
What?
End‐Bringer!
♪
No.
End‐Bringer, I will not
let your defeat be in vain.
Your story will be legendary,
passed down for
generations to come.
♪
Alley‐oop!
Blossom blizzard!
(shouting)
♪
‐Never beat us.
‐Impressive teamwork.
And their courage is undaunted.
That's how they
were able to defeat
the four big baddies.
♪
This is only the beginning.
I will not let this stop me.
I will defeat you yet!
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪