♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
(wind howls)
♪
(moaning)
Hurry up and increase
the energy level
of the Final Gate,
on the double!
Yes, sir.
‐Let's commence.
‐Right away.
(whirring)
Commencing energy increase.
♪
(groaning)
Final Gate energy output is
currently measuring level 8.
Increase output to level 7.
Yes, sir.
(louder moaning)
♪
Master, stop the engines.
Right.
♪
(loud groaning)
He seems a little
better now, at least.
But we can't continue charging
him with all this energy,
‐or else‐‐
‐I know!
His cells will be destroyed.
(low moaning)
‐Excuse me.
‐What?
Sir, we've discovered
an analysis program
in the interior system
of the Final Gate.
Transfer it here at once.
Right.
♪
The system's final program.
If we get this program
up and running,
Moo's body will be perfected.
What's that hologram?
Turn it back.
Yes, sir.
What could it be?
The Magic Stone?
‐Master Moo!
‐So that's it.
I need the Magic Stone
in order to perfect
the union of my body and soul.
You go tell Durahan
that Master Moo needs that
Magic Stone on the double.
‐Got it?
‐Got it.
♪
(maniacal laughter)
(engine roaring)
I refuse.
I know nothing of this
Magic Stone nonsense.
But I refuse to send
my precious warriors
merely to find a piece of rock.
But sir, listen.
Master Moo needs that stone.
Silence!
I won't stoop to the
level of a petty thief.
But sir, surely you
wouldn't disobey
the Master's orders.
Are you challenging
the evil General Durahan?
(whimpers)
Now, now, boys.
No need to get all worked up.
I'm sure we can work things
out, don't you think?
♪
I summon you to awaken.
Rise, my sharp‐shooting warrior.
Gangster!
(crashing collapse)
(chuckling)
♪
You summoned, General Durahan?
Rise, Gangsters!
♪
At your service,
General Durahan.
♪
These Gangsters will
take care of those pests
once and for all.
(maniacal chuckling)
They look absolutely evil.
Witness my firepower!
(staccato thrumming)
(mechanized laughter)
As for that stone?
You can steal it yourself.
No problem.
I'll get it if these
guys are backing me up.
♪
(sinister laughter)
So, which way do
we go from here?
Go that way, 'chi!
♪
Well, judging by the
position of the sun,
it looks like the Magic
Stone's taking us north.
'chi!
Yes, then north
it is, right, gang?
‐Hang on.
‐Huh?
(all gasp)
(radiant sparkling)
What's goin' on?
I don't know.
Why is it glowin' like that?
I've never seen it
do that before.
Chi!
I wonder what it means.
Maybe it means we're
really close to the Phoenix.
(all gasp)
Holly could be right.
Well, in that case,
what are we waiting‐‐
Beat you there!
(giggling)
My eyeball‐‐wait, wait!
(laughter)
Oh, brother.
♪
(gunfire)
(screaming)
♪
Forward, march.
Move out!
What's the holdup?
♪
Suezo's down!
Gotcha.
(sizzling)
(explosion)
Hold your fire.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Is it a Jell,
the slippery fool ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Or Captain Jell,
these monsters rule ♪
♪ Worm from below
explodes with a force ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Clays and their
captain have no remorse ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Jump, smash, and roar,
get off the floor ♪
♪ These monsters bite ♪
♪ Unlock 'em today ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
(all gasp)
♪
(laughing)
There were so many of 'em,
they had me freaked out
for a little while,
but you know,
wiping him out was
like a walk in the park.
I woulda had you
running for cover
if you'd just
given me a chance.
You know, you're lucky
I didn't have to use
my Tae Bo on you,
you big recycling heap.
(Suezo laughs)
♪
Huh?
(exclaims)
♪
Ready, aim...
fire!
How'd they do that?
They must be able to
reassemble themselves.
Mocchi doesn't
understand it, 'chi!
It means they can never
really be destroyed.
♪
(panting)
The Magic Stone!
(Holly gasps)
Oh!
♪
(straining)
Aim...
♪
(yelling)
Why you after stone?
Hmph.
‐Why?
‐Golem!
We need it...
to perfect Master
Moo's new body!
Master Moo?
♪
They're reconstructing!
Go!
♪
Fire!
(bullets hitting bark)
♪
(tree thuds)
(gasping)
♪
They got us surrounded.
'chi?
♪
Ready...
Full steam ahead!
Teleport!
Fire!
♪
Teleport, teleport!
(yelling)
(gasping)
Teleport!
♪
You still haven't found them.
Well, I don't care
how long it takes.
Get searching and don't stop
until you've found them!
Yes, sir!
Hm, where could
they have gotten to?
♪
I think we're safe
for a while, 'chi.
Maybe, but the sooner we
get outta here, the better.
Now, Golem, I know
that you don't like
getting wet and all that,
but we can't stay here
and nurse your phobias
forever, you know.
It's just a river and
a couple of fishies.
Golem hate water.
Suezo's teleporting bad.
Yeah, well I'd like to
see you give it a try.
Will you two knock it off?
We've got an emergency here.
It's the Magic Stone
they're after.
Hm.
What do they want it for?
Moo wants Magic Stone
to perfect his new body.
(Mocchi gasps)
That's why he needs it.
I won't let him take it.
There's no way.
They'll never get
the Magic Stone
with us guarding it,
isn't that right, guys?
Yeah, 'chi!
I agree.
Mmm.
Even so, it's pretty
hard to imagine
how we're gonna get
ourselves outta this one.
Mm‐hm.
The enemy's got us
completely surrounded.
I thought teleporting
was supposed to get us
out of trouble.
It's easy to get confused
in the heat of things.
(Suezo nervously laughs)
Spinny!
See, at least
someone understands.
Who you calling Spinny?
Isn't there some way
we can get out of here?
There is.
Not only do we have a plan,
but we have one
that's unique, smart,
and dripping with class.
Quit flattering yourself
and just tell us the plan.
'chi!
Hm.
(giggles)
♪
Haven't you found
them yet, you fools?
Maybe I'm being hard on 'em,
since robots can't smell.
If I'da known this
was gonna happen,
I'da brought along
some Caballos.
What‐‐over there,
it's them, fire!
Run!
After them!
♪
(gunfire)
We can't keep running forever.
Think of something,
quickly, 'chi!
Quickly, quickly,
quickly, quickly...
(all clamor)
In the ditch!
♪
This way!
Go!
♪
Yeah, Golem!
(gunfire)
♪
No!
What are you stoppin' for?
(Suezo exclaims)
(rocks tumbling)
♪
(screaming)
(giggling)
You can't escape.
Maybe surrendering is
the only choice left.
Time for the white flag, huh?
Okay, we give up.
So you've finally
come to your senses.
Now, hand over the stone.
Heh.
You talking to me?
Ooh... who are you?
Hm.
You're not the one
with the stone!
♪
I'm not picking up
the enemy at all, Holly,
so just hang on tight.
♪
This is an outrage!
You tricked me!
Fire!
(grunting)
♪
Bye‐bye.
Dragon Punch!
Tornado Attack!
♪
Huh?
Think Genki and them
are all right?
We have to go on
believing they are.
Hm.
Lightning!
(exclaiming)
Holly!
♪
Huh, I knew that Weed
didn't have what it took.
I can't believe he fell
for a stupid trick like this.
‐The Magic Stone!
‐That's right.
The Magic Stone.
Give it back,
that's my stone!
(giggling)
Mm, thanks.
‐No...
‐Follow her!
You get back here!
Give back my Magic Stone!
♪
Keep on firing!
Golem!
'chi!
No!
Stop!
Hold your fire.
Huh?
What's going on?
Who's there?
(giggling)
Lilim!
The Magic Stone!
How'd you get it?
It was so simple.
I can't believe you were
tricked by such a foolish plan,
little Weed.
Hm, well, at least we've
got the stone, I guess.
So, what to do.
Give it to you?
Or keep it?
Don't be cruel,
hand it over.
(all exclaim)
Mm, just imagine.
Moo's life is hanging
in the balance
because he needs
this Magic Stone.
Traitors!
No.
You tricked me
right from the start.
Right.
You see, General Durahan
wanted to get the stone
for himself.
That evil traitor!
The Baddies are fighting.
No kidding.
Who woulda thought
that the Baddies could
end up fighting each other?
(Lilim chuckles)
I'll make sure to tell Moo
that you went out honorably.
Gimme back that stone!
(snaps fingers)
♪
That's way too cruel.
Don't you even have
any feelings at all
for the guys who
are on your side?
(chuckling)
Right.
On my side, he says.
Huh?
Oh!
♪
(snaps fingers)
(explosion)
What?
Got 'em... with my face drill.
♪
Now, look out!
Master Moo!
♪
What's the matter
with these things?
Are they stuck or what?
They look like
great big toys, 'chi!
The one that was destroyed
must have had
control over the rest.
Gah!
Yah!
♪
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
I'm leaving.
Wait!
Hands off, you horrible pest!
♪
(yelling)
Genki!
Thanks again.
Come back!
♪
The stone was stolen.
And it happened when
I was guarding her.
It's my fault for
coming up with the plan
in the first place.
Now what are we
supposed to do?
'chi!
Keep going.
We'll keep going north, the
way the stone was pointing.
That's right.
We've gotta find the Phoenix
before Moo perfects his body.
Hm.
♪
So, this is how
strong Moo will be
once he's perfected.
Incredible.
Unfortunately for him,
I'll make sure that
day never arrives!
Look!
What's this?
A message from the east.
Yeah?
Great news.
Our troops have
finally taken control
of the eastern continent.
Well.
That is great news.
♪
The time has arrived.
I will defeat Moo
and reign as leader
of the Baddies.
(evil laughter)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪