♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
I'm thirsty, chi.
We all are, Mocchi, shh.
(whirring)
♪
Hmm.
Okay, let's see.
Looks to me like Silk
City is the next town.
Something doesn't
feel quite right.
‐Hmm?
‐The magic stone seems
to point in a different
direction every day,
it's never the same.
For once, I agree, Tiger.
Nah, it's nothing
to worry about.
You sure, Genki?
Yup, we can't always
travel in a straight line,
so it just shows us
the right road to take.
We take the right road.
And on every single road
it's told us to take
we've come across trouble.
Hare, wait.
You know, I think
Genki's on to something.
Hmm?
Yeah, what does
"right road" mean anyway?
Think of all the
experiences we're having.
Experiences?
That's right, we're
much stronger and wiser
because of all the things
that have happened to us.
Yada, yada, yada, yada.
Listen, let's be
up front about this.
Some of us are
stronger and wiser,
and some of us aren't.
Like who?
Come on, Mocchi, you haven't
come up with a new technique
since that flower
shower thing.
(gasping)
♪
Suezo, your teleport
was a one‐time wonder.
I could do it again.
I'll teleport myself
before I hit the mountain.
‐What?
‐Suezo, don't.
Maybe these guys
will think twice
about putting
down my technique.
I'm Suezo, the one and only
master genius teleporter!
Beam me up, Golem!
Up against that mountain
as hard as you can.
Give it all you've got!
Teleport!
♪
That may have looked to you
like I crashed
into a mountain,
but it was only an
optical illusion!
♪
Hey, wait up, you guys!
I can do it!
Hmm, so this is Silk City.
So much for finding
a drink of water.
Ah!
Did the Baddies
destroy this city?
This seems like a
very lonely place.
Hey there, Mocchi,
what's going on?
Mocchi isn't wiser.
Come on, that's just Suezo.
Don't pay any
attention to him.
Chi.
Huh?
♪
(shouting)
Some tornado.
I'm still spinning, chi.
Look where we are.
♪
I'm so thirsty.
Huh?
(splashing)
Whoa.
♪
Water.
Move.
Allow me.
Not bad.
Don't mind if I do.
Wait, Suezo.
Don't hold back
on our account.
What nerve.
Chi.
Ah, how refreshing.
You were saying?
Ah, water.
Just out waiting for us.
Holly, aren't you thirsty?
Mm, mmhmm.
Holly, come on, relax.
Enjoy.
Somebody must be
living here, Suezo.
But just look around.
I mean, the place
is deserted.
I guess.
(slurping)
(door opening)
(laughing)
Huh?
Welcome to my castle.
A Baddie, chi!
Hmm, fairly perceptive
little Goodie.
I am Gali, one of
Moo's Big Bad Four.
So Moo's behind this.
We're ready to
fight you anytime.
Hmm, what's the rush?
(laughing)
The big bad Gali
must have heard
of our reputation, you think?
Yes, I commend you on
your past successes.
Please honor me by
sharing some food.
Sounds like a trick.
I'm not hungry.
Oh, don't you trust me?
Why should we?
I live here alone.
There are seven of you.
Clearly, I have
the disadvantage.
We aren't looking
for a fight.
I think he's
telling the truth.
His troops aren't
hiding anywhere.
I feel no other presence.
Oh, yeah, right,
you just want
to talk things
over, is that it?
Over a meal befitting
such brave war heroes.
Come inside.
Let's go then.
‐Chi.
‐Hmm.
♪
Monsters.
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk,
take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Gray Wolf and Tiger,
brothers but foes ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Golem doesn't think
fighting solves woes ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Join up with Hare
who likes a good box ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ He's the team planner,
smart like a fox ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Some of them friendly,
some of them not ♪
♪ Four hundred monsters,
which ones have you got ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
Oh.
Please, help yourselves.
I'll volunteer to
be the food taster.
(munching)
♪
‐Whoa!
‐Suezo!
Is it poisoned?
It's delicious!
(grunting)
(sighing)
Everything seems
to be all right.
Of course it is.
When it comes to poisoning,
water is so much easier.
The fountain!
Not to worry.
Phew.
If the water was bad,
we'd know it by now.
Hare, don't butt in.
Get in line.
Watching Suezo eat
makes me hungry.
♪
Hmm.
Wow, this is awesome!
(munching)
♪
Chi!
How was it?
♪
They've somehow camouflaged
themselves into the walls.
So big bad Gali
is a liar too.
All is fair in love and war,
and I don't believe in love.
Huh?
(shouting)
♪
(shattering)
Hmm, think of the sand as
delicate, soothing jewels
that will gently blanket
you for a nice, long sleep.
Golem, hurry!
Come and throw me at Gali!
♪
Huh?
(shouting)
♪
Welcome to Gali's
special sandbox.
The more we struggle, the
faster we get sucked in!
Then how do we get out?
By focusing our energy.
Okay.
Introducing the Gali finale.
(shouting)
♪
(laughing)
It sucks the energy
right out of you.
♪
(thudding)
(clanging)
♪
Come on, get up, chi!
Sure, right away.
Good thing we landed in sand.
That's for sure.
Ah, look how far
down we fell.
We can't climb out of here.
Yes, we can, we
just have to try.
Okay, let's try.
What is wrong with you?
Gali's finale drained
all the energy out of us.
Somehow you
missed it, Mocchi.
So that's what
happened to us.
That's why we're all so weak.
Hope you enjoyed
your refreshments.
I'm afraid we don't
do room service.
Next time I see you,
you'll be lost disks.
♪
Chi?
Oh, no, what's that
in the shadow?
I guess a few monsters
dropped in before we did.
Lost disks, we're doomed.
Genki, come on, move it!
Yeah, Mocchi,
let's go grab some air.
Genki, what can we do?
Yeah, well,
you can count on me.
I'm Mr. Energy.
Chi!
Tiger, you gotta wake up!
That Gali finale thing
hasn't got a hope
of working on me.
Then again, I could be wrong.
Chi!
Hare, we need a plan!
Mm, it's hard to plan
when you've got no‐‐
(snoring and screaming)
I'm too little.
♪
What can I do, chi?
That seems to be
the only way out.
Golem, Golem, toss
me up there, chi!
Go, nice Mocchi.
Golem, no, I want you
to toss me up there now!
Go.
‐Can't.
‐Huh?
My strength is gone.
Never mind,
I'll do it myself!
♪
I see you've escaped
the sand cave.
My Gali finale
missed you, did it?
(laughing)
Hmm, bye‐bye, chi!
How far do you
think you'll get?
♪
Rope, I got to find
some rope, chi.
♪
(shouting)
(slamming)
Chi, chi!
Ah!
♪
Chi!
Ahh!
Chi, chi, chi,
chi, chi, chi!
♪
(laughing)
You won't escape.
Gali punch!
Chi!
(shouting)
Oh, I'm not done yet.
Chi, chi!
Rope, rope, rope, rope.
♪
(screaming)
Gali strike!
Chi!
I'm not giving up!
♪
Huh?
Chi, chi, chi!
What's going on?
Not sure.
I keep thinking I'm hearing
Mocchi's voice calling out.
Not giving up!
I know that Mocchi's really
trying hard somewhere.
I wish that I...
♪
What are you doing, Genki?
I'm gonna pile this sand
on this mound higher,
then we can get out through
the hole at the top.
Statistically,
it's very risky.
Do you have any idea
how long it'll take us?
Doesn't matter.
If we don't give in,
we can do it.
Yes, if we don't give in.
We can do it, guys.
Yeah.
You're right, Genki.
I'll help.
(grunting)
♪
(shouting)
Mocchi, rope,
Mocchi, rope!
Rope, chi, rope, chi,
rope, chi, rope, chi,
rope, chi, rope, chi!
Ahh!
Oh, dear, while
you were away,
the hole just started
getting smaller.
I think you're too late.
No, cherry blossom!
♪
Wall of fire!
(whirring)
♪
‐Mocchi, Mocchi, Mocchi!
‐Spin cutter!
♪
Ahh!
(grunting)
Huh?
♪
Mocchi!
Hmm, it's over, give up.
Never, chi!
I'll never give up no
matter what happens.
I'm just gonna keep trying.
Yeah, that's the spirit.
We're not giving up.
(groaning)
We've gotta fight this
and get back our energy,
our strength, and our fight.
Hmm, now to finish you off.
(grunting)
Energy!
♪
What's this?
‐Mocchi!
‐Genki!
Let's show this guy.
Show me what, hmm?
‐Just you watch.
‐It's payback time, Gali.
Now we're gonna fight!
Hmm, haven't you
learned anything?
I'm Gali of the Big Bad Four.
You're no match for me.
Get them!
All for one!
Ah!
Think first!
Tongue slam!
Gali finale.
♪
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah!
Gali strike!
(shouting)
Suezo!
Gali press.
Golem!
Double pounder!
Stiletto!
Why you!
Gali strike!
‐Genki!
‐Chi.
Hey, Gali!
Guess what?
We're a team here.
‐We don't give up.
‐Way to go, Genki.
We're a team!
My, I'm so touched.
What rubbish!
Here's what I say,
"Gali strike!"
(grunting)
♪
(clanging)
How dare you, you‐‐you human!
Gali hurricane!
♪
Destroy everything!
(shouting)
Destroy!
Hang on, everyone!
♪
Mocchi charge!
Mocchi!
What?
♪
(yelling)
(heavy breathing)
(screeching)
♪
We're gonna call that
the "Mocchi Cannon."
Huh?
(cracking)
Everybody run!
♪
(rumbling)
That's the end of
Gali's castle.
Now we've defeated two
of the Big Bad Four.
And all because Genki and
Mocchi wouldn't give up.
Nah, all the thanks
should go to Mocchi
and his new Mocchi
Cannon technique.
He really saved the day.
Uh, Genki?
Mocchi is so hungry.
Mocchi, you can have
whatever you want.
Yeah, you were
totally awesome.
Mocchi, Mocchi, Mocchi!
(laughing)
♪
(wind howling)
What, they defeated
the great Gali?
Yes, this is terrible.
It must be reported
to Gray Wolf at once.
Yes, sir!
(whimpering)
♪
I can feel it.
I can feel it!
My ancient body lies nearby.
Soon I will be complete.
Monsters.
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪