♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the Mystery Disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled Mystery Disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
(lightning crashing)
So I hear they gave
you a hard time.
Well, they were a lot
tougher than they looked.
It's hard to believe
they beat Gray Wolf.
I agree,
but they would not have
beaten you, Master Naga.
Are you suggesting
that I am stronger
than even Gray Wolf
used to be, Cabalos?
(chuckling)
(laughing)
Flattery will get
you everywhere.
I like you.
You're too kind, Master Naga.
For a long time,
I've wanted to serve under you,
not Gray Wolf.
So, will you accept me?
I have no use for you.
♪
(screaming)
(lightning crashing)
Get Stone Dragon!
Yes, Master, right away.
(loud stomping)
♪
You summoned, Master Naga.
Stone Dragon, the fools
who dared to defy Master Moo
have entered our territory.
Allow me to take care of them.
(lightning crashing)
♪
Well, what's the word?
It's pointing to this forest.
Great, it just had to
be someplace creepy.
Hey, we're supposed to be
looking for the Phoenix.
You're not gonna let a few
trees scare you, right?
Let's move.
Go.
All right!
Look out, Phoenix,
'cause we're comin' to get ya!
Chi!
(Chi singing "Chi")
This forest sure is
quiet, isn't it, guys?
Yeah, it is kinda creepy.
Maybe Suezo had a point.
Ooh, check out
the tough guy here.
Now who's scared?
What'd you say?
I said it was creepy,
I never said anything
about being scared!
(gasping)
(arguing continues)
(tree creaking)
Huh?
(screaming)
♪
Genki, it's a trap!
The Baddies!
Huh?
(screaming)
♪
I'm stuck!
I'm coming!
(grunting)
Don't touch that stuff!
You'll never get it off!
♪
Look out!
(whistling)
(screaming)
Maybe next time you
guys will believe me
when I try to give
you a warning!
(screaming)
(groaning)
(spitting)
Just stay where you are.
Don't move.
(screaming)
Guess I shouldn't expect
an eyeball to listen.
Thanks for the warning.
Get out of this forest at once!
Leave now or you'll be sorry!
Who are you?
I don't see anybody.
Huh?
There he is, come on!
♪
I'll get you!
You're messing
with the wrong guys!
(screaming)
Huh?
A cabin.
Wait, look, a tripwire.
♪
(screaming)
Run for it, hurry!
(panting)
♪
(shouting)
'Kay, now we got ya.
Don't be so sure.
Put up your dukes!
You got it!
Wait, Genki!
(shouting)
♪
(whimpering)
(screaming)
(groaning)
You can't fool me that easily.
(chuckling)
Let's just see about that.
♪
(screaming)
(chuckling)
I have to admit, you're
pretty smart for a Baddie.
Huh, what do you mean?
Hey, you don't have a crest.
No, and neither do you.
So you're not one
of the Baddies then?
No way, I'm a Color Pandora!
Huh?
(soaring overhead)
♪
(mumbling)
The Stone Dragon's coming.
Ah, no!
(soaring)
This time it really is
one of the Baddies.
Huh?
(grunting)
How are you makin' out?
I'm having a great time,
but what was that sound
that I just heard?
They said it was one
of the real Baddies.
Baddies?
(groaning)
Atta boy, nice and slow now.
(grunting)
(soaring overhead)
Huh?
What's that sound?
♪
(screaming)
(growling)
♪
So you're the ones?
Master Moo's very upset.
(growling and zapping)
(laughing)
(groaning)
♪
That's a strong dragon.
‐Hey!
‐Hmm?
‐Genki!
‐Chi!
This way!
(panting)
(loud stomping)
♪
I get it.
These trees are gonna
slow down Lizard Lips
while we escape.
♪
(trembling)
Dad?
I thought I told you
to stay in the house!
(whimpering)
(screaming)
♪
Huh?
(loudly stomping)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it and claim it ♪
♪ You can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Isn't a Jell a slippery fool ♪
♪ Or Captain Jell,
these monsters rule ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Worm from below
explodes with a force ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Clays and their captain
have no remorse ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Jump, smash, and roar,
get off the floor ♪
♪ These monsters play,
unlock 'em today ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
Look out!
(roaring)
Hey!
Come and get me!
♪
Attack!
(smashing)
Got him!
(groaning)
♪
(gasping)
Mocchi.
What is this?
I'm stuck!
Sure are!
(grunting)
♪
We got him!
Is it over?
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐Uh‐huh.
(creaking)
(gasping)
♪
(crashing)
Dad!
Are you okay, Dad?
♪
No need to worry.
Your dad's not hurt that bad.
Chi.
Huh?
Food!
♪
Hey, can I have some?
No way, Chi!
It's not even mine,
it's Color Pandora's!
(hissing)
Chi?
Why's it smoking?
It's gotta be a trap!
(screaming)
Ah, fire in the hole, guys.
Toss it, Mocchi!
(screaming)
♪
(panting)
That one must be a dud, I guess.
(sighing)
Chi.
You woke up.
Yes, and thanks for your help.
You sure know how to
yank a guy's chain.
(grunting)
(screaming)
Somebody get me outta here.
Come on, you guys.
Man, this place is
loaded with booby traps.
The best way to fight
against the Baddies
is to use booby traps.
You don't waste energy that way.
Huh, traps are for cowards.
Cowards?
Why don't you just fight them?
You should just
say no to a fight.
Besides, if your
opponent is strong,
you'll get squashed.
Sounds kinda lame.
Chi!
Huh?
(grunting)
(stretching)
(chuckling)
Is that boy the only
child here, Color Pandora?
That's right.
Every time we try
to bring 'em back,
the Baddies come
and steal them again.
The Baddies steal your children?
That's despicable!
But what do you mean,
when you bring them back?
♪
Huh?
(gasping)
It's a monster gate.
♪
Whoa, check out all
the Mystery Disks.
So are all of them
Color Pandora Mystery Disks?
Yes, they are.
What's stopping you
from unlocking them?
The Baddies are.
A long time ago,
this was a peaceful
and happy forest.
We knew this forest inside out
and could lay all
kinds of booby traps,
so the Baddies
came after us.
They stole our children
and tried raising them
to be fighters.
(whimpering)
Sounds like the Baddies.
The villagers here have
always been peace‐loving
and opposed to any
kind of fighting.
They didn't respond to
the Baddies' training,
and we haven't seen a single one
of our precious children since.
Crying won't solve anything!
Huh?
♪
(grunting)
Ah‐ha, quite the
trap you've got.
I've always wanted to learn
how to make one of these.
Mind if I stay and watch you
in action, Color Pandora?
So you lure the
enemy to the swamp,
drop the net,
and hope they can't swim.
That's right, and this one has
the Stone Dragon's name on it.
You really think this
swamp is deep enough
to get rid of Stone Dragon?
He's a pretty big guy.
(screaming)
What'd you go and do that for?
(sinking)
(gulping)
It's a bottomless pit.
Are you nuts or somethin'?
How am I supposed
to get outta here?
Come on, please help me!
(sighing)
I'm sure the Stone Dragon
will attack tomorrow,
which means I gotta
finish it tonight.
I'm not so sure this
plan of yours will work.
Why wouldn't it?
'Cause you're using
your head too much.
You're just saying that
'cause you're jealous
that I'm so much
smarter than you.
‐Say what?
‐It's pretty obvious,
so don't bother
trying to deny it.
You're way off!
Listen, brainy,
you can do all the
calculating you want,
but things never turn
out the way you think!
If you're the one
doing the calculating,
they probably won't,
but I'm a brain and I
don't make mistakes.
I can't believe how
stubborn you are!
Then let's make a bet.
If I finish off the Stone Dragon
tomorrow with this trap,
then you'll work for me and
make my traps from now on.
You're on,
but if you lose,
then you work for me,
and believe me, I'm gonna get
my money's worth outta this.
Think you can handle it?
Yeah, 'cause I
won't be the loser.
(growling)
♪
I can't see any dragon, Chi.
Think he's really gonna come?
You bet he will.
Hey, guys, where's Holly?
She's hiding in the cave
with all the villagers.
Let's finish off this dragon.
Good idea, but he is strong.
He's got a point.
This ain't no fly in our soup.
Don't worry, it's under control!
You guys just lure him
over to the swamp.
I'll take care of
the rest on my own.
You mean you're gonna
use us as your bait.
Mocchi, Chi!
(soaring)
Here he comes!
♪
Lightning!
Come on, run.
♪
Do you think you can escape me?
(whistling)
(groaning)
(sneezing)
Over here, Stone Dragon.
(sniffing)
(shouting)
♪
Right this way.
That's it, keep comin'.
♪
(shouting)
Attack!
(screaming)
♪
(grunting)
(roaring)
♪
Look, guys, it's working.
I knew that trap
would work all along.
I guess you lost your
bet to the brain, huh?
(grumbling)
♪
(whimpering)
No, he's out!
(roaring)
(whimpering)
♪
Did you fools think
you could finish me off
with a trap as lame as that one?
Oh, I've got to be dreaming.
No chance, this is
as real as it gets.
Now's the time we gotta fight.
All right!
We've come a long way,
and we're not gonna
let this guy beat us!
Chi!
Blossom Blizzard, Chi!
♪
(wind howling)
Chi!
Tornado Attack!
(Golem screaming)
♪
(groaning)
(screaming)
♪
(groaning)
So, who's next then?
You're lookin' right at him,
but you'll have to catch me.
Hey, Color Pandora,
you got any traps on ya?
Nope.
That last trap didn't work,
so now we're done for.
What?!
I don't think so!
I'm a‐comin', lizard!
(slapping)
♪
You're my next victim.
(thud)
(grumbling)
♪
Come on, guys,
let's do this right.
Yeah!
♪
(whimpering)
(screaming)
♪
(roaring)
We're just getting started!
Who needs traps?
(shouting)
They won't give up.
♪
Even if they're losing.
(grunting)
Here comes my
Pinwheel Fireworks attack!
♪
(slamming)
(gasping)
(groaning)
♪
Who was that masked man?
(screaming)
He's come back for more!
♪
(slamming)
(screaming)
♪
(dizzy whimper)
Huh?
(bubbling)
♪
You got him!
You really rocked, Color.
Great, Mocchi, Chi.
Are you saying I did that?
Come on, you can fess up to it.
You got that Stone Dragon
all on your own,
and you didn't even use a trap.
Huh?
Hey, I didn't mean to hurt you.
Come on, Color, snap out of it.
Come on, little critter.
♪
There.
You all ready to bring
them back to life?
Mmm.
(whirring)
♪
I lost the bet, Hare.
So I'll be your servant.
(laughing)
Just forget about
that stupid bet.
You're gonna have
your hands full
just helping to raise these kids
and protecting that forest.
(babies cooing)
You sure about that?
(laughing)
Yeah, I'm sure,
'cause knowing I was
right about that trap
is good enough for me.
You had to bring that up.
Well, I was right after all!
No, you weren't!
Ha, what did you say?
Stop, Mocchi, Chi!
♪
(laughing)
Mocchi, Chi?
(all laughing)
♪
I'm going to Kyrus.
And I'll continue
looking for the Phoenix.
♪
You be careful.
Don't take any risks.
I won't.
You watch out
for danger as well.
Hmm.
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪