♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ I played the game
like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Pendant shows
the mystery disk ♪
♪ We'll take it to the shrine ♪
♪ We'll redeem that
fabled mystery disk ♪
♪ And release
the Phoenix inside ♪
♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ I was transported
to a faraway land ♪
♪ Into a world
where monsters rule ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Played the game like an ace ♪
♪ Now we're in this place
to save the monsters
from the evil Moo ♪
‐♪ Monsters rule ♪
‐♪ Monster Rancher ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
(howling wind)
♪
(roaring)
(laughter)
Our army of Baddies
will conquer the world!
(laughter)
♪
We've got trouble!
(yelps)
Master's merged
with the monster!
What's all the commotion about?
Sorry, but we've just received
word that those pesky humans
defeated Naga!
(maniacal laughter)
♪
(rumbling)
Master, considering
the humans just attacked Naga,
they must be close
to the castle,
so finding them
should be simple.
I'll sense her
when she gets close,
she is my daughter after all.
♪
Magic Stone, show me the way.
So, it is this direction?
Yes.
We've climbed high up.
And we've got another
mountain to cross!
I could use some earmuffs.
Oh, right, no ears.
Mocchi cold.
Feels like snow's coming.
Golem doesn't like snow.
Are you quite sure the Phoenix
is lying dormant up ahead?
Yeah, that's what
the Magic Stone tells us.
I've never seen
anything as mysterious
as that Magic Stone of yours.
I can understand that
it points out mystery disks,
but it can even locate
Moo's new superbody
and the place where
the Phoenix lies dormant.
Maybe it has some sort
of connection with
an ancient civilization?
Yes, you're probably
right, Holly.
It seems to me that the Phoenix,
Moo, and the Magic Stone
are connected.
Yeah, sure, Hare,
that's a fascinating theory,
so find someone who cares
and tell them about it
on the way.
You always interrupt me
when I'm trying to explain
one of my theories.
Hey, Suezo, wanna hear
something interesting?
♪
Cold, must find shelter.
We better find someplace
to camp out for the night.
Camp out, are you serious?
We'll be icicles by morning!
'chi!
See something, Mocchi?
Hey look, there's
a village below.
Why don't we ask one of them
to let us stay
at their house overnight?
You mean we gotta
walk down there?
It's better than staying here!
Yeah, come on, gang!
Hello?
Sorry to bother you.
I know it's late,
but we need a place
to stay for the night.
Would you be so kind enough
to put us up just one night?
Hello?
This is the third
house we've tried!
What's the matter
with these people?
You'd think they'd have
a little compassion.
Ha, you're overrating humans.
(growling)
Maybe this'll get you
to open the door.
That's enough, Genki!
But it's cold out here!
Cold!
Are you okay, Mocchi?
I guess our only choice now
is to set up camp after all.
I vote that we find
a camp far away
from these stingy people.
Yeah, who needs
their help anyway?
Please, can't we
let them in, Dad?
No way.
Mom, why not?
Just for one night?
Because your father
said no, that's why.
But Mom, they'll freeze
if they stay outside.
I already told you no.
Now, time to get to bed.
No!
Come on, Eve, don't start
giving your folks a hard time.
But‐‐
Today is Ogre Day, that's
why they won't let 'em in.
Ogre Day?
That's right, come here
and I'll tell you all about it.
Okay, Grandpa.
Come on.
There.
Did you know that today
is the shortest day
of the year, Eve?
It's known as Ogre Day
here in the village.
How come?
That's because the ogre
comes on this day and steals
all our young children.
So, on Ogre Day,
legend has it
you must never go outside
or even open
the door for anyone.
Oh.
And while we're here
locked up inside the house,
we're also supposed to pray
that Colona will come
and take the bad
ogre away for us.
Who is Colona?
Colona is the sun god
who protects us from the ogre.
Protects us from the ogre?
Mm‐hmm.
Colona the sun god
is very powerful, dear.
Although he's strong,
he's gentle
and has a warm and kind heart.
That's the story.
Do you think I
could meet Colona?
Eve.
Why can't you understand
that no means no?
But he only comes
out once a year.
You don't mind if
the ogre gets you?
He will if you go outside.
Colona will save me even if
that ogre does catch me.
She's impossible.
Eve, time for bed.
No, I wanna go see Colona.
Children who don't listen
to their parents get taken away
by the ogre.
Grandpa.
Listen to your mother.
♪
(blows)
I'd do almost
anything to see Colona.
♪
(gasps)
Colona, is that you?
Hang on, I'm coming!
♪
Huh?
(gasps)
♪
What is that?
It's so bright,
I wonder if it's Colona.
♪
I can't believe it;
he's come here to meet me!
(panting)
♪
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪ Get a disk, take the risk ♪
♪ Spin it fast,
through the past ♪
♪ Unlock it, reclaim it,
you can tame it ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Shaped like an urn,
Bajarl calls them in ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ Including a town,
can't tell where it's been ♪
♪ Unlock your disk ♪
♪ General Kato
is good and wise ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ He knows how it works,
for some, a surprise ♪
♪ Unlock 'em all ♪
♪ Monol is flat,
but Monol is deep ♪
♪ His biggest problem,
he falls asleep ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪
(grunting)
♪
How come we're
pushing around snow
when we should be
setting up camp?
Sorry.
Back at home,
we call this an igloo.
An igloo?
Sure, Genki, I can see
how this'd keep you warm.
It works, I tell ya.
We're gonna be nice and toasty.
♪
Genki's right,
it's warm, 'chi!
Hmm?
Well, let's all go in
and give it a try.
Yeah, that sounds
like a good idea.
♪
What's wrong?
I'm not sure, but look!
Hey, that's weird.
You think there's
something nearby?
Or it could be
someone approaching us.
(gasps)
♪
Footprints of those people
who knocked on our door!
This one's pretty big, though.
I wonder if it
belongs to Colona?
I'll follow it and find out.
♪
(roaring)
(roars)
♪
What was that?
I was positive
something just flew by.
♪
Huh?
(yelps)
♪
No.
(roars)
(screams)
Who screamed?
Who's out there?
I don't know, come on.
Wait up!
(nervous tittering)
♪
(roars)
(screams)
(chuckles deviously)
♪
(panting)
Look, it's Moo!
Yes, and he's
merged with his body.
Moo's monster, it's come back!
♪
It's just like Monol told us.
He's enormous.
Go!
Holly.
Huh?
Seeing this little girl
reminded me of when you
were young, crying
for your mother.
♪
What do you mean,
when Holly was young?
How do you know about Holly?
What's going on?
So, you haven't told them yet?
Holly?
I guess I should
have told you sooner.
Moo told me that
he's my real father.
Huh?!
Father?
So, you're his daughter?
That can't be true.
This dagger used
to be my father's,
and it was very precious to him.
Moo gave it to me
in the floating castle.
(explosion)
(panting)
So, that's what was going on.
I was so desperate
to believe that Moo
had stolen it from my father,
but he didn't.
I was wrong.
Our destinies
are intertwined, Holly.
How come you didn't
tell us sooner?
Sorry, I was having such
a hard time believing it,
but I sensed that inside
that he was my father.
I was horrified,
but I knew it was true.
♪
Eve?
Eve!
Oh, no.
What's the matter?
I can't find Eve!
(gasps)
(panting)
♪
Her coat's gone!
And the door's unlocked.
She couldn't have
gone out by herself.
Wake Grandfather,
I'll go get the village chief.
If you really
are Holly's father,
then why did you attack her
and the rest of the village?
Yeah, she's your own
daughter, and the villagers
were your friends,
weren't they?
Perhaps you've forgotten
that I feed off of grudges,
the bigger the grudge,
the more evil I become
and the more evil I become,
the bigger the grudges I need
to devour.
Then that's why
he wants to eat someone.
So he can devour
all of their grudges.
You picked the wrong place
to come this time, Moo Monster!
You've become wiser
and more brave
since we last met.
You're bad!
(growls)
That's right, you're pure evil!
♪
We've gotta get him.
Yeah, you do what
you have to do, Genki.
He stopped being my father
the day he was taken over
by that evil soul.
To me, this thing
is just the evil Monster Moo.
It seems you've made up
your minds about me
and this little child.
(gasping)
Somebody catch her!
♪
Be careful, Pixie!
You have a grudge
against humans,
yet you help them.
Monsters don't need
to terrorize humans.
There's no reason we can't live
together in peace with them.
(laughter)
You fool!
Monsters must rule;
there's no other way!
What good could possibly come
from Baddies ruling the world?
Hearts will turn to stone
and wars will pervade,
the entire world
will be as it should.
(growling)
Hurry and escape while you can!
Right.
(maniacal laughter)
♪
Take care of the girl.
Run for cover, Holly.
Right.
(grunting)
♪
(zapping)
To make things fair,
I'll fight you without flying.
♪
Big Bang!
(roars)
Wall of Fire!
♪
Let's get him, Mocchi!
'chi!
Mocchi Cannon!
♪
You're still
underestimating my power!
♪
Run for your life, Holly!
(zapping)
♪
Golem!
Suezo, let's teleport!
Gotcha!
Dragon Punch!
(evil laughter)
♪
Where are you?
Eve!
Eve, are you out there?
Evie!
Where are you?
Can you hear us, Eve?
♪
Unbelievable.
It's the ogre!
No!
Save her!
Oh, no!
(growls)
I'm coming, Eve!
Don't!
Let me go; he's got my daughter!
Let go of me!
Do you really think there's
anything you can do to stop me?
Hmm?
I think not!
No, Moo!
♪
We have what it takes,
let's get him, gang.
♪
You don't stand
a chance against me!
Now!
(zapping)
Mocchi Cannon!
Torpedo Attack!
♪
Big Bang!
(zapping)
♪
(gasping)
Like I said,
you don't stand a chance.
♪
(growling)
Did I merge too soon?
♪
I'll be back!
My guess is his body
wasn't used to the sunlight
and he started to burn up in it.
Something happened
when he merged with his body.
It doesn't matter.
We did it!
Go!
(laughter)
Eve, are you
all right, sweetheart?
Eve, baby, are you
all right, sweetie?
Oh, she's all right;
she's just exhausted.
♪
What can we ever
do to repay you?
Food, for starters!
Yeah!
Your offer's very generous.
Thank you, but we wouldn't
wanna do anything
that would cause you
any more trouble.
Say what?
Shall we?
Uh‐huh, let's go.
See ya!
Bye‐bye, 'chi!
Take good care, be safe!
Bye!
Keep out of danger!
♪
Daddy.
You're awake.
What happened?
How come the ogre
didn't eat me?
The sun god, Colona,
took care of that nasty ogre
and brought you to safety.
Huh, those people?
♪
You mean they're
all gods named Colona?
I suppose.
Thank you, Colona sun gods!
♪
Bye, thank you!
Come back again!
Bye‐bye!
(laughter)
♪ Monsters ♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪
♪
♪ Monsters rule ♪♪