Of course.
I remember now.
It was Frieren.
The mage who made great contributions
to humanity's analysis of Solltrag.
And sent more demons to the
grave than anyone else in history.
Frieren the Slayer.
One of the geniuses I despise.
It's important that you
rest for the time being.
I appreciate it.
Whoa there!
You doing okay?
I will survive, but only
because of you two.
I'm grateful.
I'll pardon your companion
for her actions as well.
She was right to take
a stand when she did.
Which means nothing's
stopping Frieren from coming back.
The peace envoy's
as good as dead.
Also, please know that Mistress
Frieren didn't kill your guard.
I am aware.
The demons are to
blame for that, too.
More importantly, you said
this woman's name is Frieren?
Yes.
which almost certainly makes her the
elven mage who adventured with the hero.
I've committed a grave
discourtesy against her.
My family owes a debt to
that great band of heroes.
During my grandfather's rule,
this town was attacked by demons.
Frieren and her comrades drove
them off and saved our people.
That same enemy has returned.
Aura, one of the Seven
Sages of Destruction.
It's been a while, Aura.
Eighty years.
The decades fly by,
don't they, Frieren?
No doubt you planned
to attack the town ahead.
But I'd appreciate it if
you turned back now.
That won't do.
Why not?
Because I carry an advantage
that assures my success.
Oh?
You have more
puppets than before.
Your magic must be unbelievably powerful if
you're able to control this many at once.
I'm sure no human could even
begin to dream of wielding such might.
But this dark magic is
enough to make me vomit.
It's disgusting.
Vomit? you wound me.
It took a lot of work to
gather such an army.
I recognize some
of those crests.
Right then, it seems my best
option is to kill you once and for all.
The scales of obedience.
They're why we haven't been
able to defeat Aura over the years.
Her magic allows her to control a person's
will, forces them to obey her every command.
The Seven Sages of Destruction wield
power beyond human comprehension.
We believe Aura places her soul and the soul of her
target on the scales, then weighs them against each other.
Whoever has greater mana
gains control of the other.
turning them into a
puppet for all eternity.
Until their body withers
away and only armor remains.
The risk involved
makes the spell powerful.
And when it's cast by someone as
mighty as Aura, it cannot be overcome.
There must be a means
of countering the spell.
Aura's strength seems unbeatable, but the
scales themselves are fair and partial judges.
If a soul with greater mana than Aura's were
to be placed upon them, she could be defeated.
Still, according to what we know, that has yet to happen once in
the last 500 years, ever since she became a Sage of Destruction.
You mean... there's no way
for us to stand against her?
Once upon a time, there was.
Those with fierce determination were
able to temporarily resist Aura's spell.
The warriors who had wills forged
of iron, the greatest among us.
But even then it was temporary.
Which made them
her primary targets.
They stood in her way,
threatened her victory.
And so...
When she finally broke them, Aura the guillotine made
certain they would no longer pose a threat to her.
It's a tragic tale.
Well, haven't I impressed
you with my immortal soldiers?
My, this is a surprise.
You dispelled the magic
I used to control them.
No one's ever done that before.
Such a formidable act must consume a monumental
amount of mana, though, leaving you exhausted.
Why would you use such
a roundabout method?
The last time you faced me, you
were casting flashy spells left and right.
Himmel scolded
me after that battle.
You're holding back for him.
I don't see why his words
should matter to you.
Why wouldn't they?
Because Himmel is
rotting in the ground.
Thank you for saying that.
You've reminded me that demons are just
monsters, so I can kill you without mercy.
All right.
I've regained
most of my mobility.
Father, this place
is safe, right?
Yes.
There's a defensive barrier around the church,
though it's not as powerful as the towns, I'm afraid.
Got it.
Graf, you wait here.
Not so fast.
What do you plan to do, brat?
We may have escaped the demons, but
they're still out there plotting somewhere.
Mr. Stark, be reasonable.
We only injured that demon before
because we took him by surprise.
Even with that advantage,
we couldn't finish him off.
If we had kept fighting those two, we
would have been the ones who were killed.
Someone's gotta step
up and try to stop them.
But... You're right.
Let me do this with you.
No.
You need to head
to the guard station.
Start evacuating the townsfolk.
You'll go out there alone?
Yeah.
No sweat!
I'll swallow my pride
and beg Frieren to return!
She's obviously the only person
around who can defeat Lügner!
Not what I was expecting,
but more realistic.
Here.
The guards will listen to you
if you show them this crest.
Very well.
I'm heading out of town.
What is it?
Your arm.
It's all covered in blood.
You're not worried they'll
question you at the gate?
I'll be fine.
Comes with being a warrior.
Plus, it's not that much.
I've never seen a warrior walk
through town with two bloody hands.
You look like a murderer.
You're one to talk.
You've got just as
much on you as I do.
Wait, whose blood is this?
Couldn't be mine.
Hey!
What is the matter with you?
Mr. Stark, there's
mana in this blood.
Fern!
An axe?!
Unbelievable, I've got to
be dreaming or something.
Because that looks like
my master’s technique.
I meant to hit your vitals, but
you’re faster than I expected.
It truly wasn’t my intention
to make you suffer.
Why do you look so shocked?
Did you think your attack could killed
me? That I was mortally wounded?
No.
You're surprised you didn't
sense us as we approached.
You aren't unique in your
ability to conceal your presence.
It's a simple matter of
controlling one's mana.
Any demon can do the
same, should they wish.
To be fair, it's hardly a noble way to
approach a battle between two mages.
But these things happen.
You like to hear yourself talk.
Didn't you come here to kill me?
True, but seeing as you're still alive,
I might as well ask a few questions.
Unless, of course,
you're in a hurry to die.
Go on.
How strong is that boy?
He's Eisen the
Warrior's best student.
I see.
How unfortunate.
The poor thing will
die a torturous death.
Linie likes to take her time.
One last thing.
Where is Frieren hiding?
She fled town after escaping.
She had to, because you
killed the Dungeon Guard.
Graf Granat blamed
me for that as well.
Is it really such a
serious offense?
The penalty's death.
Still, a woman like Frieren wouldn't
flee because of such a danger.
It's obvious she holds a
grudge against demons.
One so spiteful she taught her
student a spell designed solely to kill us.
No, she would not run away.
She left for another reason.
For Lady Aura.
Do not take another step.
I suspect you know
exactly where she's headed.
Explain.
You're wasting your time.
You were lying when you said
your intent wasn't for me to suffer.
That attack was
never meant to kill me.
It was revenge for
catching you off guard.
You are a proud and arrogant demon, so sure of your strength
that you see Mistress Frieren as the only threat in your way.
Underestimating me has
put you in a dire predicament.
From this distance, I can blast
a hole clean through your heart.
Try it.
Your head will fly before
you get the chance.
Mistress Frieren, am I
of any real use to you?
Why would you ask such a thing?
I'm not as skilled
with magic as you are.
That's more than apparent.
I've lived many, many
more years than you have.
You can't hope
to catch up to me.
I see.
Of course, that only applies to your
technique and your mana reserves.
I often let you handle monsters.
You prove yourself
in those battles.
Yes, you force me
to fight them often.
Apologies.
Battles end sooner
whenever you fight by my side.
You fire off spells
much faster than I do.
Human.
I've dedicated the majority of
my life to the pursuit of magic.
As have I.
How is she
responding so quickly?
If I hadn't acted reflexively,
that would have pierced my heart.
You blocked my attack, which must
mean your heart is your weak point.
This girl...
Interesting.
You weren't lying about
dedicating your life to magic.
That's good.
I won't need to hold
back in this fight.
Varterie!
It sounds like
they've gotten started.
That makes me
a little bit jealous.
Our fight is all but over.
Perhaps I'll observe
their battle from afar.
Lord Lügner gets
cross when I interfere.
You're up?
We're not finished yet!
Aren't you tough.
Perhaps this will be amusing.
My mana, technique, and
control are all far superior to hers.
She can't compare
to me in any way.
The very thought
of it is ridiculous.
However, she is fast.
I'm being overwhelmed by
the sheer number of her attacks.
Damn you, Frieren.
How did you train this
girl to put up such a fight?
It's no matter.
She'll exhaust her mana soon.
On second thought, I'm
not sure I can wait her out.
If I can just create an opening...
Linie, quit playing around!
Hurry up and kill that boy!
The human wants
to deny me my fun.
He's refusing to do
anything but defend himself.
I don't understand
the way you're fighting.
Your technique
is like my master's.
I'm exceptional at reading
the mana in other people.
My specialty is memorizing the way it flows inside of a person
as they move, which allows me to imitate them, just like this.
I recognized your technique the
moment you attacked us at the mansion.
Because I memorized it years ago,
as I watched a great warrior fight.
What an odd coincidence.
Fate is a funny thing.
You mean...
I'm going to take your life using
Eisen the Warrior's movements.
If I am dreaming,
then this is a nightmare.
I can't win against her.
There, he's finally fallen.
I should go back.
I don't want to
upset Lord Lügner.
Is that it?
Is this how it ends?
Stand up, Stark.
Find the strength.
No matter how battered
you get, you cannot fall.
Why do we keep
sparring like this?
No matter how hard I try,
I'm not going to beat you.
Of course not.
I'm far stronger than you are.
Then what's the point?
Look at you.
You're back on
your feet, aren't you?
You haven't lost yet.
That makes no sense.
Listen, Stark.
I'll teach you the secret to
defeating powerful opponents.
It's simple.
All you have to do is keep getting
back up and hitting your enemy.
Understand?
The winner is the warrior
who's still on their feet at the end.
You talked like it
was so easy, Master.
You and your crazy logic.
You should have trained your
brain as much as your body.
A smarter person would
have stayed in the dirt.
I've already defeated you.
Yet here I am, still standing.
You know, now that I think about it, my
master's blows were heavier than yours.
You're just the poor
imitation of a great warrior.
Imitation or not, I'll
still be the death of you.
Erfassen.
Vertarie!
Wideswing, with no
regard for defense.
Idiot.
When I saw how you fought, I was
prepared for us both to kill each other.
But your attacks don't have
any weight behind them.
Lightning Strike!
Linie!
Shit.
Solltrag.
Magic designed to kill demons.