I see now.
Your training is what
made this fissure.
But if you don't intend to fight the
dragon, why do you continue to train?
When I first got to this village,
its people were living in fear.
Hard not to with
a dragon nearby.
Now they're all smiles.
They're convinced that as long as I'm around,
their home remains safe from another brutal attack.
Even though I haven't
done a damn thing.
The only reason the Dragon hasn't destroyed
this place is because it hasn't felt like it.
What if it does feel like it?
Will you fight it if
there's no other choice?
I'm not keen on dying,
but that's a minor thing.
I have a title to uphold,
and people to protect.
I'm Stark, the hero of this
village, and it's my job to defend it.
Easy to say that now, but
knowing myself, I'll run away.
This scar on my forehead, I
didn't get it taking on a monster.
It's from a fight I
had with my master.
It was the first
time he ever hit me.
He must have been disappointed.
Had to have been.
Throughout our whole relationship,
he never praised me a single time.
What now?
We just met, but...
I don't think you'll run.
You don't know me at all.
You're right about that.
But I have been in
a similar situation.
Alright, let's hear it.
The first time that I fought a monster, I had
trained more than enough, but I was frozen by fear.
I couldn't muster the
courage to fight back.
All I could do was run.
It kept on chasing me.
And for some reason,
Mistress Frieren wouldn't help.
My master was like that too.
When it finally had me cornered, I
steeled my resolve, and instinct took over.
All that I needed to
do was ground myself.
Your training isn't
going to fail you.
Mine didn't fail me.
You're a coward hiding beneath a veneer of
bravery, but your resolve to protect the village?
That, at least,
I believe is real.
My resolve...
How did it go?
I don't know for sure.
But if I had to guess...
I think it'll turn out alright.
He ran then.
That's a shame.
I had high hopes for the lad.
We're left with no choice.
Prepare yourself
for dragon size tag.
Huh?
Frieren.
You only need 30 seconds, right?
You took your time.
I want you to
promise me one thing.
If I die fighting this dragon,
you have to finish it off for me.
All right, I promise.
But why would you sacrifice
so much for the townsfolk?
What?
Just... that's kind
of an odd question.
I've lived here for
three whole years now.
Not long.
Yes, long.
Okay, let's get to business.
Your hands are shaking.
I'm scared.
What do you expect?
Something funny to you?
You're exactly like Eisen.
I am?
This is a powerful foe.
But your hands,
they're out of control.
You afraid?
Yes.
Didn't take much
to get that out of you.
Being afraid isn't a bad thing.
Without fear, I wouldn't
have made it this far.
Even the way they
tremble's the same.
I get it now.
My master, he was afraid too.
All I have to do is
steel my resolve.
He's entered the dragon's range.
Why isn't it attacking him?
It knows better.
I thought so.
No wonder it left
the village alone.
Dragons are smart creatures.
They're not foolish enough to pick
a fight against a powerful opponent.
Eisen didn't hit Stark for being weak
or because he was disappointed in him.
It's much simpler than that.
The two of us parted in anger.
You hit him?
My body moved on its own.
I feel terrible.
I'm forever sorry
for what I did.
I was afraid.
I was afraid of
the boy, Frieren.
I couldn't believe his power.
My apprentice will
become a great warrior.
Now!
Let him have it!
Hey!
Shoot it already!
I did exactly what
you told me to!
You expect me to kill it myself?
You can't be serious, old hag!
You're just like my master!
It's already dead.
Huh?
Old hag, huh?
He'll live to regret that.
I killed it… on my own?
I didn't need any help.
I beat the dragon.
Good work.
You were exceptional.
That was quite the show.
Well done.
Now this hoard
of treasure is mine!
At last!
We can't take it all with us.
Three items only.
Does this not feel silly to you?
You're really interested
in this old junk?
This junk is treasure.
My master always told me that you
made the hero's adventure a ridiculous one.
Oh?
In a good way.
I guess your silliness
made things fun.
Incredible!
You actually made shaved ice!
I told you this
spell was worth it.
I would take on armies to
experience such fluffiness!
Rightly so.
This is ridiculous.
We're wasting our time.
We have time to spare.
Our journey has only
just begun, after all.
The Hero of the South was
said to be our strongest weapon.
The Seven Sages of
Destruction slaughtered him.
The four of us may well
not make it back alive.
So what then?
Want your last journey
to be painful and hard?
That's no fun.
If you ask me about it, I would take
the more lighthearted journey any day.
One I can laugh
about at the end.
Just the warmth of a finger and
it melts almost instantaneously.
Please keep your fingers
away from our food.
Ridiculous.
Oh, and what do we
do about the syrup?
I don't have a spell
to produce that.
Really?
Even more ridiculous.
Well, can you see through them?
Yes, but...
I can't say I find
this spell interesting.
I'm so sorry my body
isn't interesting to you.
Hm?
What?
So small.
No part of me's small!
Well, Stark, where will
your journey lead you next?
I suppose you could make
your way back to Eisen now.
Didn't my master tell
you to take me with you?
Besides...
I'd like to have a ridiculous
adventure or two of my own.
There is monster activity
in the Northern Lands.
At this time, no one can
pass through the checkpoint.
Well, at what time can we?
It has to open someday.
Does it?
It hasn't since I was
very first posted here.
After all, no people out
means no monsters in.
Pardon me.
The Castellan would
like to see you, sir.
Be right there.
Listen close, adventurers.
You would be wise not to
cause any trouble in this town.
That wasn't a very warm welcome.
He's a good guard, wants to keep his people
safe, and is appropriately harsh on outsiders.
As every proper town guard
ought to be, in my opinion.
Speaking of safety, this city seems to have it in
spades, which is a positive of being stuck here.
This is the perfect time to
slow down and study our craft.
Once we drop off our things,
the magic shops are all mine.
Come now.
The checkpoint is locked tight.
We have no other choice.
Run along, you're free to roam.
I'll secure us a
room at the inn.
Wanna get something to eat?
Loud and clear.
Scary.
Rumor is they shut
down the sea routes, too.
The Northern Lands Army says they'll take care of the problem,
but I give it two years until the checkpoint opens up again.
Business is at a standstill.
I haven't had this in forever.
The Jumbo Berry Special.
I was just a kid
when I came here last.
I actually had to split it with my
master because I couldn't finish it alone.
But, uh, I feel like
this thing has shrunk.
I would know.
It's the same size as ever.
You've simply grown up.
I suppose age does
change our perception.
Everything seemed
huge when I was a kid.
I used to think my
master's back was so broad.
But even that
started to look small.
Eisen is getting
up there in years.
I hope you're being
a dutiful student.
Duty is what brought me here.
You sure the portion's the same?
The passage of time is cruel.
You've got no
reason to glare at me.
I bought this with my own money.
Pardon me.
One milk, please.
Sure thing.
So... what?
You're clearly mad.
Mr. Stark.
Fine, I guess you can have half.
This isn't about dessert.
What if I told you we're going
to be waiting for a long time?
Two years even.
Huh?
No thanks.
So you and I feel the
same way about it then.
Sure.
What's our deal?
That's a relief.
You're relatively
normal at least.
I'm lost.
Did I do something
to offend you?
So you want to find a
way through the checkpoint.
Sure.
I'll see what I can do.
Thanks, you won't regret it.
What if you just flew us
up and over the city wall?
The wall's only one
part of the problem.
There's a powerful barrier all around the border
that extends to the maximum flying height.
That makes sense.
Explains how they keep
the winged monsters out.
Let's ask around.
Our first stop should
be the Merchant's Guild.
They must be trading somewhere.
The trade has been
completely shut down.
If guarded caravans aren't allowed through, things
in the Northern Lands must be quite serious.
I'm afraid we may need to
give up until things settle down.
Not yet.
We should ask around the Black
Market and Thieves' Guild first.
Wouldn't that be a bit
dangerous even for us?
Lucky for you, I look tough
enough not to be questioned.
Plus, I bluff like a pro.
You do have a thievish face.
I heard that.
What a waste.
It's no big surprise.
The town's stuck
on the defensive.
If they don't open back
up, we're stuck too.
You know, we could always
pay the guard station a quick visit.
You good?
Yes.
I'm just a little surprised
by your cooperation is all.
You said that you didn't want to
wait, so I'm doing all of us a favor.
You're even more
desperate to leave than I am.
Well, I don't
have a lot of time.
That was awfully vague.
This view.
Nice, isn't it?
You can really
see the north side.
When I was little, my
master brought me up here.
We departed for the northern
lands from this very city.
Tell me all about it, Master.
You want to know?
See that trail over yonder?
He hardly ever spoke about himself, but he happily
relayed every detail of the hero's adventure.
He's been around for a long time, and for whatever
reason, those ten years mattered more than all the rest.
I'll bet the same
is true for Frieren.
I wonder...
He's old now, and can't
travel like that anymore.
He sent the two of you to find
me so that I could fill his spot.
Now it's my turn.
I'll go on this adventure and return
with stories just like the ones he told me.
If they happen to be ridiculous,
then that's all the better.
It's the least I can do
to repay my debt to him.
If I take too long to get
back, my master will pass on.
I see.
Then we can't allow
ourselves to get tied up here.
Nope.
But I bet he's still
got plenty of years left.
Mistress Frieren?
Is there a reason you're
creeping around the city?
Shh.
Quiet yourself.
They're following me.
Don't stop.
She must be lurking
around here somewhere.
Oh, great.
How'd you rile him up?
I've no clue.
I was happily perusing a
magic shop when suddenly...
I'm so terribly sorry.
Please, Miss Frieren,
forgive my insolence.
Okay.
I have some concerns about
where this seems to be going.
I understand the Captain of
the Guard was quite rude to you.
As the Castellan of
this city, I apologize.
Oh, it's no issue.
He did his guardly
duties well, if you ask me.
In any case, I'm not
in an enormous hurry.
Am I right to assume that you
do plan to travel north again?
According to our information, the Northern Lands are in
constant battle with the remnants of the Demon King's forces.
You must be concerned
about their situation.
My goodness, a hero
as kind as she is mighty.
The people of the North will
be thrilled to hear of your arrival.
And as for our checkpoint,
pass through as you wish.
I can't believe that's
really all it took.
Shouldn't we have told them who you
were from the moment they turned us away?
I didn't think there was
any point in alerting them.
And I wanted to take my time.
What a commotion.
This kind of thing
just isn't for me.
Who could feel
comfortable like this?
I'm happy I get to
see a proper send-off.
This must have been how it was
when my master left for the North.
That's right.
If only I'd had a little
more time for my research.
You need to move on.
You know we risked life and
limb trying to get out of there, right?
Indeed.