Let's split up and replenish
our traveling supplies.
You'll be shopping too?
You've assigned all the necessities to me.
There's food, water,
other daily essentials.
I'm a bit confused as to
what that leaves for you to buy.
Herbs and things of the like.
Great.
That's the face she makes when
she's hiding something from me.
I've known Mistress
Frieren for a long time.
Nothing good happens
when she makes that face.
She's plotting to buy
something we don't need.
Look what I got.
What are you going to use that for?
A corrosive potion that
only dissolves clothing.
Return it!
Here, a history tome.
There's value in traditional study.
Well, maybe that last one
wasn't entirely unnecessary.
Best of luck.
I'll meet you at the inn later.
We can't afford to waste
what meager funds we have.
I'd better keep a close eye on her.
An accessory shop?
You should stop going
to sleep with wet hair.
Really.
I never thought she would
be interested in fashion.
She seems so conflicted.
Huh?
What's that face?
In all these years, I've never seen
Mistress Frieren look so troubled before.
Hmph.
She certainly took her time.
I suppose one accessory doesn't hurt.
It's better than heavy
bones or strange potions.
I should probably get
back to my own shopping.
Is there anywhere I can get
a good dessert in this town?
No way, now she's taking it too far.
Try the tavern.
It's over in the basement of that building.
You should ask there.
I will, thanks.
It's been months since I've
even seen a granule of sugar!
Hmm...
This must be the place.
Does anyone know where I can
get a good dessert around here?
Something tells me this
isn't a pastry-loving crowd.
A dessert joint?
Do you realize who you're talking to?
Oh no.
You've stumbled upon the biggest
sweet teeth in town, lucky lady!
We'll find you a sugar fix near or far.
I was not expecting that.
I would have thought you
lot too rugged for sweets.
A bit of sugar fills us with the
energy we need to adventure on.
So they're adventurers, then.
Still, I'd say rugged is an understatement.
Terrifying.
She must be on her way to the restaurant.
Huh?
That's strange.
She's heading in the direction of our inn.
Did she give up on dessert?
I'm not even close to done shopping.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
No matter.
Put down your things.
I was thinking, it's been too
long since we've had a treat.
What an incredible view.
A superb recommendation.
I feel awful.
It was wrong of me to ever doubt you.
What do you mean?
Choose whatever you would like.
You're absolutely sure we can afford this?
I've been saving up in secret.
So she is capable of saving.
What will you order, Mistress Frieren?
Let's see... Today I feel like...
You feel like Merkur Pudding, right?
Tonight you feel like
Merkur pudding, don't you?
How did you know?
You travel with someone for
years and you pick up on things.
I can just tell with you.
I can't tell what any of you are thinking.
Then we should put in more effort
so you can get to know us better.
My favorite food, for
starters, is a ruff omelette.
Mine is grapes.
The sour, the better.
And mine is... Those, correct?
You make that clear, you corrupt priest.
That is nothing to blush about.
I find it disturbing that your vice
is a primary player in our tale.
I'm sorry, Fern.
What do you have to be sorry for?
I realized I don't know
the first thing about you.
So I... didn't know what
sort of present you would like.
This is for me?
I completely forgot it was my birthday.
It's a hair ornament, right?
It's absolutely perfect.
Thank you.
I love it.
I did well?
Very well.
And because you're hopelessly dense when it
comes to these things, allow me to be clear.
I am overjoyed that you're
trying to get to know me.
That is a gift in itself.
Simply trying means that much?
Maybe we should find you a spell
for understanding people's feelings.
Hey Fern, are you ready to be off?
Sure.
Tell me the truth, Mistress.
Does our journey have a
notable purpose this time?
Not especially.
Hopefully we'll be able to find
some decent spells, though.
That and, whenever possible, I'd like to retrace
the adventures I had with Himmel and the others.
Before all signs of it fade.
I see.
Remembering those adventures,
it's very important to you, isn't it?
I don't know.
That's what I want to find out.
It seems you've finally
grown taller than me.
Well, I am sixteen.
I could be your big sister.
Is that right?
Our diets are largely the
same, so that can't be the culprit.
How strange.
Your defensive training
is coming along nicely.
Now, let's put your work to the test.
I aimed for the gaps in your magic.
If this were a real fight, you'd be dead.
Right.
How will you handle it this time?
That is plenty for today.
Defensive magic is powerful,
but it rapidly depletes your mana.
Maintain defense over a large area,
and you'll exhaust your supply in seconds.
Meaning that the best option is to cast it in
select locations at the precise moment of impact.
Exactly.
We've been practicing
nothing but defense for ages.
Yes, to improve your odds of survival.
I guess that makes sense.
Being able to cast one defensive spell can
protect you from most every offensive spell.
It's eerie how powerful they are.
So, you haven't read the tome
on magical history I gave you.
Magic is just as much about
theory as it is about practice.
Fine.
You leave me no choice but to
read it to you at bedtime every night.
I'll read it myself.
I'm not a child anymore.
Why is this village so special?
It's just another place
to find spells, right?
No, unfortunately not.
It's all up to the weather now.
That it is.
Could one of you gentlemen help us?
It's an elf.
That hair...
Do you happen to be the
mage they call Frieren?
How did you know that?
You're here to see the
place where Qual was sealed.
I'll show you the way.
Qual?
The Elder Sage of Corruption, Qual.
He's a horrific demon, responsible for the
many atrocities that befell this region.
About 80 years ago, Himmel the
hero and his party sealed him away.
That seal doesn't have much time left, so
I'm here to defeat him before he's an issue.
Where does your information come from?
I don't recall telling anyone about this.
Until about 30 years ago, Himmel always went
out of his way to pay our town an annual visit.
He told me it was to check
on the condition of the seal.
He was always rather soft at his core.
You were a frequent subject
of conversation between us two.
We agreed you were quite
heartless for not checking on him.
She's a touch cold.
Yes, and then some.
Sorry about that.
But still, she's not so heartless that
she'd leave your village to its fate.
When the seal is on the
verge of collapse, she'll appear.
And it would seem he was right.
Indeed.
This is it?
I was right to assume that it's unstable.
I shall dispel the seal
tomorrow, then take care of Qual.
You were the one who thought to seal
him away in the first place, weren't you?
Why didn't you and the others
defeat him when you had the chance?
The story isn't as enthralling
as you might guess.
I couldn't beat him.
All the Demon King's forces were formidable,
but Qual was an exceptional mage.
He developed Zoltrak, the first
piercing spell in the history of magic.
It can pierce not only defensive spells,
but the most durable magic-resistant armors.
It directly targets and destroys the body.
It is said that in this region, 40% of their adventurers
and 70% of their mages were killed by Zoltrak.
A spell with that much
power shouldn't exist.
Agreed.
As would most.
It was too strong.
And it was that strength that
caused it to backfire on him.
What do you mean, backfire?
It's painfully clear that you
haven't read your history tome.
You sure you don't need
nightly bedtime stories?
I'll start reading now.
Don't.
It's fine.
It's more important that
you get a good night's sleep.
You'll see for yourself tomorrow.
I'm dispelling the seal.
You mustn't let your guard down.
What the...
Long time no see, Frieren.
How many years has it been now?
Eighty.
No time at all, then.
For us, perhaps not.
What's become of the Demon King?
We killed him.
I see.
Then...
I shall avenge his death.
Fern, cast a defensive spell.
Zoltrak!
Oh, what have we here?
You blocked Zoltrak.
That defensive spell of
yours must be powerful indeed.
Mistress Frieren, can you
please tell me what's going on?
That was ordinary offensive magic.
You just saw his life's work.
Allow me to introduce you to Zoltrak,
the great killing magic of legend.
Qual, your spell was simply too powerful.
After you were sealed away, mages across the land studied and
analyzed Zoltrak until they had a complete understanding of it.
In just a few years, your work was incorporated into humankind's magic system,
and new defensive spells with power like none before were developed in response.
The magic resistance offered by equipment
has improved significantly as well.
These advancements have made
Zoltrak a death sentence no longer.
Your great weapon is now
ordinary offensive magic.
It's rather remarkable how much humanity
can achieve in the span of 80 years.
Qual, if you don't resist, I'll
grant you a painless death.
It's interesting, but I
see what you've done.
Your defense attunes itself to my
magic, and then disperses its power.
You have a complex spell indeed.
It must consume a great deal of mana!
He figured out the
weakness of defensive magic.
Fern, you know what to do, don't you?
Yes.
I remember from our practices.
Then I'm going to ask
that you protect me as well.
Ha ha ha ha!
Oh, the elf can fly.
How fun.
Zoltark.
Frieren, that spell is mine.
Because of you, our quiet village
can live in peace once more.
I've seen that hat.
This old thing?
Around these parts, the sun
beats down on us all year long.
Every farmer has one.
I've seen this one, this exact straw hat.
You.
You're the little delinquent
who flipped up my skirt.
Have you got a death wish, you brat?!
I've been wanting to do that for
ages, but unlike you, I have self-control!
You better not kill him.
Gross.
So you're still alive, then.
Thanks to your visit, I'll
be able to live even longer.
I'm glad I trusted Himmel's
words and waited for you to come.
You saved them.
They all seemed so thankful.
Thankful, yes, but not to me.
His prophecy came to pass.
Himmel was who they believed in.
I don't understand exactly.
But it seems to me that the person
Himmel believed in all this time was you.
What is it, Mistress?
Nothing.