It's a grimoire written by
Flamme, the legendary mage?
No, books supposedly attributed
to Flamme are never real.
Every tome uncovered so
far has been a fabrication.
This is probably the best imitation
I've come across over the years, though.
It's not a terrible reward to
receive for defeating monsters.
If you say so.
I don't see the appeal.
What a shame.
When you find nothing but forgeries, you start to doubt
whether the genuine article ever existed in the first place.
The Great Flamme,
founder of humanity's magic.
To be fair, it's
like a fairy tale.
Is that what people believe?
I suppose enough years have passed
that she's become something of a myth.
I might be the only one left alive who
knew her, who remembers her face.
Good morning.
It's a miracle!
She woke up early!
Okay, and you're
shocked by that?
Astounded.
This is deserving of a reward.
What is happening?
My most humble thanks.
When I saw this landslide, I feared I
would never find a way through the pass.
Hey, uh, is this
actually necessary?
Are you unhappy?
He's offered a fine reward.
No, that's not the issue.
This would go faster if you just
used your magic to move his cart.
But what of future travelers?
They'd be stuck here.
That's what Fern said.
We wouldn't want to be
selfish now, would we?
That's rich coming from you.
I insist you have a drink.
Oh, thanks.
That'd be great.
It's strange.
I thought landslides
happened on a bigger scale.
The Northern Lands have been fighting demons in this area, and
their clashes have had a far-reaching impact on local terrain.
This was likely caused
by such a skirmish.
So now we're tending
to the scars of battle.
Mr. Stark, would you
mind helping me over here?
I could use your
assistance for a moment.
Mr. Stark?
Hey, could you maybe
drop the Mr. part?
Stark is fine.
It weirds me out.
I'm pretty sure we're
close to the same age.
Very well.
If you'd prefer it.
Stark, you're wasting
everyone's time.
Help me.
Dude!
I just meant that if we're gonna go on this
journey together, you can drop the formalities.
We can talk to
each other casually.
And it wouldn't hurt you to
be a little friendlier, you know.
I'm a warrior with
a sensitive soul.
What a pain in the rear.
What'd you call me?!
I assume you're
making good progress?
You heard her.
Let's hurry, Mr. Stark.
Fine.
Ah, you have my
undying gratitude.
If you'd like, I can show you
the fastest route into town.
I have the honor of
escorting an elf, eh?
I've lived for many decades, but this is
my first time meeting one of your kind.
I suppose we are a rarity.
Now that I'm thinking about it, you're
the only one I've ever seen in person, too.
There aren't very many of us.
In fact, I've only ever met a handful
of other elves in all my travels.
We may live a long time, but
we've scattered to the winds.
Of course, it doesn't help that we don't have
romantic urges or reproductive instincts.
We're experiencing
a quiet extinction.
Over 400 years have gone by
since I've laid eyes on another elf.
We may be close to disappearing.
This is a lovely
view of the town.
It's a busy day at the gate.
Those look like merchant wagons.
The Liberation
Festival is tonight.
It was on this very day, many moons ago, that Himmel and his
party of heroes defeated the demons who plagued this land.
That must have been quite
the experience for them.
The Liberation Festival
commemorates their triumph.
Every year, the statues of Mr. Himmel and his companions in the Central
Plaza are decorated, and the town throws a grand celebration around them.
Humans love to make a fuss.
They'll use any
excuse to hold a festival.
More than 80 years have passed since the demons
were finally defeated on that auspicious day.
That's plenty of time for even something so
important to begin fading from the minds of men.
But we can't have that.
And so we celebrate in remembrance
of those who fought on our behalf.
Excellent work.
The fifth time's a charm.
This sculptor worked
faster than previous ones.
You are constantly getting statues
put up in your honor, Himmel.
Well, how else can I assure
that people will remember us?
Our lives are fleeting
compared to yours.
We won't be around for long.
Take a look at this face!
Future generations must
see how handsome I was!
Whatever, I'm
heading back to the inn.
Though... there is
a greater reason.
When we three are gone, maybe our
statues will keep you from feeling lonely.
Come again?
You'll know we existed.
That we aren't just fairy tales,
but people who stood beside you.
Every year, we gather in celebration of the spectacular
deeds accomplished by this brave band of heroes.
Now that we're here, I must say that you bear a striking
resemblance to Miss Frieren, that mighty mage of yore.
Will they still be doing this
a hundred years from now?
Oh yes, for as long
as this town stands.
A thousand years?
That's more
difficult to foresee.
Well, shall we be off?
We have a long road ahead of us.
Speaking of which, you haven't told
me what our final destination is yet.
Where are we going?
To heaven.
That sounds fun.
There are a lot of guards here.
Do you suppose
something happened?
Maybe we should decide who'll
be in charge of the shopping.
We're in town, Mistress Frieren.
Demons approach.
Well, Graf Granat, did
you hire an elf to kill us?
I can't take credit.
Though it's true I despise you and
pray for your death, Lord Lugner.
I wouldn't be so bold as to openly
attack a peace envoy in the center of town.
I'm no fool.
It's a peace envoy?
They're probably adventurers who
don't understand what's going on here.
Certainly, if that's your story.
But in these cold, calculating
eyes, I see bloodlust.
I know how the town folk feel.
They tremble at the sight
of me, loathe my existence.
But despite that, they
still view me as a person.
Not you.
Whenever you look at my face, you see
only a wild beast that should be put down.
And is that not what you are?
Demons are simply monsters
who have learned human speech.
You only communicate with lies.
Throw her in the
mansion's dungeon.
My lord!
Hey, wait!
This is so boring.
We have bad news.
They say you'll be down
here for two or three years.
A shorter term than I expected.
Could you bring me
a few grimoires later?
I know you don't experience time as
humans do, but this is going a bit too far.
It's not as though I actively
chose to be locked away.
So, what did he mean when he
called those demons Peace Envoys?
I tried to get some
information while shopping.
Aura the guillotine.
You have heard of her, right?
The Seven Sages of Destruction.
And Aura was one of them.
She was a servant
of the Demon King.
We killed most of her followers, but
she slipped away and disappeared.
Has she re-emerged?
Afraid so.
I'm told that she came
back to power 28 years ago.
Since then, her forces have
been locked in battle with this town.
There have been many casualties.
But the demons have grown
exhausted by the endless fighting.
They've come here
to propose a truce.
Which is why they were
let inside as envoys.
How unwise.
There's no use trying to
negotiate with their kind.
Surely some good can come of it.
Why not speak to them?
Wouldn't the best option be to stop fighting
and start talking their problems out?
No.
Nothing will be
resolved that way.
Demons are beasts
who seek to devour.
Have you ever wondered why those monsters
chose to speak the same language as humans?
Please, Hero.
You must slay this devil.
It's only a child.
No!
Don't be fooled
by its appearance!
It ate her!
My daughter is dead!
Swing your sword!
It hurts.
Make it stop.
Please, Mommy.
Step away.
I'll handle this.
Kill her, and we'd be
no better than them.
My friends, surely this scared little girl
can eat what we do in order to survive.
Why don't we give her the
opportunity to atone for her mistakes?
No, Chief, you can't!
Are you crazy?!
It took our daughter!
I'll never hold her again!
Here, let me tend
to your wounds.
You're in luck.
I've been looking for somebody
to help out around the farm.
Himmel, you're going to regret
not killing this girl, this demon.
She's here.
Why don't you
speak to her and see?
We'll be in this village
for some time anyway.
We might as well try.
Fine.
Why did you murder
the village chief?
We should have
killed it at once!
These monsters
cannot live among us!
There it is again.
Every day since I came here,
I've felt your desire to kill me.
But I just wanted
to live in harmony.
I figured out a way
to make things right.
Here, take this child as a
replacement for your offspring.
The one I ate.
That girl is the daughter
of the village chief.
Yes, but he isn't alive anymore.
Despite my good intentions, it seems as though
I've unfortunately made another mistake.
You've given me no choice.
I'm taking this child hostage.
You won't stop me again?
No.
Mommy, please.
Why call out to a mother?
Demons are monsters, and like all
monsters, they don't raise their young.
Once born, you are abandoned.
You walk this world alone.
That makes you
ruthless, solitary creatures.
Lone wolves with no
concept of what family means.
Explain.
Why would you call out to a
mother you've never known?
It's simple.
That word stops humans.
It keeps them from murdering us.
Isn't that magical?
Demons use words
to trick humans.
You can't trust
a thing they say.
They're monsters
who learn to speak.
That's how the legendary
mage Flamme defined them.
It's in their blood.
They're descended from liars.
Monsters who found they could
lure in humans by crying, help me.
Don't forget about
the grimoires.
Granat is late.
What insolence.
It's a human diplomatic tactic.
Frankly, I'm more curious
about the rogue mage.
I've seen her face before.
Wild beasts who only
communicate with lies.
It's not an inaccurate
description.
She can see us for what we are.
No one else in this town
understands our true nature.
Or perhaps she's just logical.
She knows there's but one
reason to learn our prey's language.
They talk to us so that
they may deceive us.
Every word is a baited trap.
This town won't be
standing for much longer.
I should use the confusion
as a cover to escape.
Where are we?
This is my son's room.
He was a good boy.
He'd often boast that he'd take control of the
family soon, offering me a chance to finally relax.
He fought bravely alongside His
Majesty, who then gifted him this sword.
And where might your son be now?
He died in battle against your
leader, Aura, ten years ago.
This sword is all
that was left of him.
You monster!
I invited you here to avenge my
boy, the child you took from me.
I will slaughter
you in his name.
Your peace means nothing to me!
Allow me to compliment the
tidiness of your son's room.
I wager you've kept it just
as it was ten years ago.
What does it matter to you?
I've kept my father's room the same since he was
lost to us two, from when you struck him down.
We can put an end to
all of this, don't you see?
Or we can go on spilling each other's blood,
causing more grief, ruining more lives.
We can speak to one
another, can we not?
So please, let's
find another way.
Show them to the guest room.
I shall consider this.
Lord Lügner, what is a father?
Who can say?
Graf Granat resents us, but he is also an empathetic
man, and that's a flaw we can wield against him.
I aim to win his trust, and if I do, I'll ask him to lower
the town's defensive barrier as a show of good faith.
Then Lady Aura's forces will raze
this meddlesome town and feast.
I can't help but notice
it's just you and me, Linie.
Where has Draht run off to?
He said he was
eliminating an obstacle.
How irresponsible.
What will I do with
that reckless youth?
Lord Draht!
This area is
forbidden to guests.
Why are you here?
Please, return to-
Sorry, I'm told
visiting hours are over.
I'm an executioner named Draht.
I serve Aura, the guillotine.
Don't fight.
I have come here to kill you.
I see.
Not pretending you
want peace anymore?
We've just begun.
According to Lord Lügner, this girl is
the only obstacle standing in our way.
If I dispose of her now, and we get Graf
Granat to trust us, this town will crumble.
I should warn you
that I am fairly strong.
Stronger than me?
Stronger even than
Aura the guillotine.