It... hurts.
Of course it hurts.
It's only been two days since the surgery.
Two days?
That’s right.
Why can't I move?
Like I know. Ask the doctor.
Hey, are you feeling any better?
Medoki?
I'm glad. Just like we planned.
We were able to prevent a collapse.
We didn't plan anything. We're just dealing with it.
If that was the case, you would have
done more than just give him a shot.
I'm not a doctor.
Um, what happened to me?
How did I end up here like this?
Tomori.
Is Tomori all right?
She's fine.
She's also here in this hospital.
Yeah, thanks to Kumagami.
I see.
I'm glad. And how is he doing?
Huh? It can't be.
Yes.
It wouldn't have happened if you weren't
so damn busy trying to save your own ass.
You have no room to complain.
You were the one who said we should bet everything
on his ability to time‐leap, did you forget that?
Kumagami is...
Those guys must have decided that they didn't
need your time leap to get what they wanted.
Collapse was the biggest threat to them
so they tried to use hostages as shields.
Both sides miscalculated.
It's all my fault.
You shouldn't blame yourself.
Hey.
Are we gonna have to deal with this stuff all the time?
Not from those two, at least.
We erased their memories using Maedomari's ability.
But there's no telling when you might be targeted next.
All in all, I'm just glad you woke up.
We’ve been taking turns watching you.
Hey, uh, it's time now.
Right.
Hold on. I have one more question.
What is it?
Why isn't my brother here?
Really? Are you that stupid?!
You need to calm down.
What does he mean?
Let go!
He means that, for your big brother,
Kumagami was his best friend in the world.
Yes, come in.
Hey, Big Brother.
Oh, Ayumi.
It's been a while.
Are you sure it's OK to talk?
Yeah. As long as I stay still.
They said you'll never see from your right eye again.
Apparently, it was such a big
accident, I shouldn’t be alive.
I'd rather lose one eye than my life.
But...
With proper rehabilitation,
they said I could live a life
that's almost the same as before.
It would be nice if that's the case.
How are things at the facility?
Everyone is super nice to me so it's been really great.
But Big Brother Shun has looked
heartbroken since the accident happened.
I'm worried about him.
Big brother.
Losing Ayumi was the most
painful thing that's happened to me.
For Shunsuke, Kumagami was someone just as special.
And if I had died because of the collapse,
what would Ayumi have gone through?
Yes, come in.
Hey there, it's been a while.
Takajo, it really does feel like it's been a while.
You look like you're in a lot
more pain than I had imagined.
Yeah. What a sight, huh?
And I come bearing gifts.
I think this will make you perk right up.
What is all this?
A lunch box with insulation!
And the contents are...
The smell. I know it.
That's right!
The cafeteria's beef tongue curry!
Whoa! I never thought I'd have it in this place.
I can even help you eat it.
Please do.
Say ahh!
So good! This reminds me of the days back in school.
Yes, this is truly the taste of our adolescence.
Another bite, please! Ahh!
There's still plenty left,
so just eat until you get bored of it.
By the way, how is Tomori doing?
Her injuries are a lot less severe than yours,
so they'll probably
let her out soon.
That's good to hear.
You've had a lot of hardships lately.
No kidding.
We're looking forward to you guys
coming back to the council once you’ve healed up.
Granted, I love holding down the fort with Yusarin,
but it's just not the same.
Yes? Come in.
I came to visit!
Hey, Kurobane. What’s up?
Not much. I made this for you if you're interested.
Ah, would that be cream stew, by any chance?
That's amazing, you got it!
Yusarin's handmade cream stew!
This recipe is cherished in the Kurobane household
as a tasty source of strength.
It even works wonders on illnesses and injuries.
I see.
So that's the reason she brought me cream stew that day.
Thanks a lot.
Yep. Now then, open wide.
Well? What do you think?
Mmm. Great. I feel a bit more energetic already.
Ahh? I'm so glad.
Takajo can never know this happened.
Misa, you there?
Calling on the dead now?
Yeah. Where do people go when they die?
Who knows? I never left this place.
I'm like a candle that Yusa is holding onto.
When her ability fades away,
my flame gets snuffed out with it,
just like a candle in the wind.
I see. In that case,
shouldn't you use all the time
you have to visit your loved ones?
Huh? What's all this about?
I almost died the other day and it made me think.
You could be gone at any point in time, you know.
You should visit your friends while you still can.
I hear ya.
I know I got one more chance,
but that doesn't make it any easier.
You know, I used to eat that a lot.
It used to be our mom's best dish.
But Yusa copied her and made it all the freakin' time.
Just like our family.
Unlike Yusa, I made our parents miserable,
though you could say dying was
the worst way to be a bad daughter.
Then you should go see them
again, before the ability is gone.
Yeah. Well, I'll take that suggestion into consideration.
W-was I asleep again?!
No, you're all right.
If you don't mind me asking, Yusa,
what do your parents do for a living?
Oh, yes, they make soba noodles
deep in the mountains of Nagano and serve them.
I see. Then I suggest you go visit them sometime soon.
No, you don't have any time left, go now!
S‐Sure. I'll talk it out with my manager right away.
This is really gonna take some getting used to.
Fairly close to Last Supper, "Fair Supper" for short.
This is a show where celebrities...
She made regular appearances on a show like this?
... wouldn't be their last supper
but is a supper fairly close to it.
On today's show, I'll be introducing you
to the Fair Supper from me, Yusarin!
It's just over this hill.
Actually, this is a soba restaurant that Yusarin...
She used her work to go see her parents, huh?
Nice Yusa.
... and she seems very happy about it.
This is the handmade soba and
wild greens tempura set‐meal.
First, I'll have some of the tasty soba.
I'll take the dipping sauce and dunk it.
So good!
Next up, I'll have some mugwort tempura.
This is really tasty too!
With such a lack of vocabulary,
I'm surprised they chose you
to be the host of a food show.
Honestly, there's nothing special about the taste.
It's so plain, in fact, you
could get the same from a store.
Misa! What the heck are you doing?
But the love of my parents
is the secret ingredient that makes this so exquisite.
That's why I love this dish.
Nothing can ever replace it.
Thanks for the awesome meal.
You reminded me of Misa just now.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
She was a delinquent with a bad mouth and attitude,
but she was good deep down.
That was a great way to repay them.
Uh, yes? Come in.
Good morning, brother!
Oh, hey, good morning.
Ta‐da!
Happy birthday to the best brother ever!
Today is your 16th birthday!
Congrats on another trip around the sun!
No kidding, it is?
I would never forget such an important day.
So I made sure to pull out all the stops.
Uh... what's wrong? Don’t you want to eat it?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah! Then open wide for the airplane.
I can eat it by myself.
That's silly. You're recovering, so take it easy.
It's sweet but it's good.
Here.
It's the same flavor.
Maybe it's that ingredient Misa was talking about.
So, do you like it?
It's great.
I'm so happy!
Now next.
Tasty.
Next, next!
Guess my vocab's limited, too.
I probably shouldn't criticize Yusa.
Grats on getting all better.
I'm coming along, anyway.
There's a favor I'd like to ask of you.
Hey, bro.
I heard you'd been up here all along.
Could you please say something?
This hospital's all right.
You won't have to deal with the police here.
More than that. I...
He's just like how I was back then.
The terrorists are acting up overseas.
Japan will become involved shortly.
And Kumagami is no longer here either.
I wonder, what will happen to all of us?
It's been a while.
Uh‐huh. Uh, Tomori!
Oh, gee, it's nice to see you, too.
W‐Well, I was just surprised.
The hospital discharged me a little while ago.
So I thought I'd come and have a chat with you.
Have you heard anything from your big brother yet?
He said Japan will soon be involved
in the activates of overseas terrorists.
Interesting.
My brother's had all the life knocked out of him.
He's so different.
Dangerous people may keep coming after me in the future.
I don't want to lose anyone
or make them miserable ever again.
If there's something I could do
with my powers, I'd like to do it,
but I don't know how.
Tomori, what am I supposed to do?
There's only one thing I can think of.
All right, what is it? Please, tell me.
Your big brother's research facility.
The scientists there have already completed the
anti‐ability vaccine in preparation for Charlotte.
Yeah?
So then, everything ends if you can
plunder all of the abilities that exist,
as well as any new ones that might
happen to sprout up in the meantime.
Of course there are risks.
What will happen to you after gaining
thousands upon thousands of abilities?
What will happen?
You might turn into a monster that can
potentially annihilate the human race.
Even then, will you be able to hold on to your sanity?
It definitely won't be easy.
But it's something only you can do.
That is the only method I can think of
that can save all of the ability wielders.
To be honest, I wasn't planning
on having this talk with you.
But... you came back here from
the future in order to save Ayumi.
Then you came to rescue me and Kumagami too.
At first, I thought you were just a filthy cheater,
but I can believe in the person you've become.
That's a drastic change of opinion.
Well, this is way too reckless
for it to be one of my tactics.
Forget I mentioned it.
Now, you should probably be getting some rest.
Later.
Hold on.
I'll try it.
No way, it's reckless.
I'm serious. Besides, I kind of owe you one.
And if you think it's the only way, that's all I need.
Your motive is a bit weak.
But what happened to us could very well happen again.
This time I'll be the one that saves you.
I promise.
Why is that?
Because I love you.
Huh? What are you talking about? You mean like romance?
Yeah, romance.
You say that with such a straight face.
I don't think there was ever a
time that you thought favorably of me.
I've said this before,
that in a different world I threw myself into despair,
and you were there the whole time watching over me.
This is just a wild guess,
but wasn't that my way of taking
responsibility for Ayumi's death?
Yes, but you still saved me.
So, how do you stumble from
that into a full‐blown romance?
It doesn't make any sense at all.
Right, like you need reasoning to fall in love.
You're the one who's using it as a reason, you big moron!
See? Our compatibility is absolutely the worst.
But I still love you.
You’re so strange, you know that?
Say whatever you like.
OK, fine, I'll say it. I'll be waiting, here.
Huh? For what?
For when you've saved the ability wielders
and finally come back to me.
Once you've pulled that off,
the two of us can become lovers.
Aren't you overestimating my abilities?
Think of it as incentive.
If you really manage to do this, I've no
doubt you will be irresistibly dear to me,
after such a big feat.
That sounds like a challenge.
So, has that increased your motivation?
Yeah, bigtime.
Then promise me.
Swear you'll come back.
We will meet again. I know it.
Yeah.
I'll make sure to come back.
If you lie, you'll cut off the tip of your finger.
Pinkie promise!
That's a scary promise.
So that you'll keep your motivation up.
Sure.
Good. Then start with me.
You're going to plunder every single ability, remember?
I see. This is what the mission entails.
Hadn't thought of that.
Yep, go ahead.
I'm sorry.
There's really no need to apologize.
I'll finally be a regular human again.
Thank you very much.
Big brother, I have a plan.
I'm going to go plunder the abilities of
every wielder in the world and save them.
That's impossible. Don’t bother.
Out of all the ability wielders,
I'm the strongest, aren't I?
I don't want Kumagami's sacrifice to have been a waste!
You're not the only one who feels that way!
Damn it. Damn it!
He saved me so many ways just by being at my side.
But I didn’t even get to say thanks to him in the end.
That's why I'm going.
So that no one who's important
to me will ever suffer again.
Don't you feel that way, too,
especially after losing Kumagami?
Are you serious about this?
Sure am. I've already taken Tomori's ability.
Taken...?
The wheels are already in motion.
and I'm not turning back.
That's some determination.
But how are you going to search for ability wielders?
Someone close to the syndicate's leader
must have an ability similar to what Kumagami had.
They couldn't gather that many ability
wielders in such a short time otherwise.
Yu, fly overseas. Leave Japan to the rest of us.
We lost Kumagami.
But we're still a powerful syndicate in our own right.
We'll hold them down until their abilities are gone.
If we can't do that much,
we couldn't possibly look him in the eye again.
Yu, you just turned 16, isn't that right?
Yeah.
You don't have much time left.
You'll have to do all this in record time.
Right.
Otosaka.
Oh, hey, guys.
I heard the whole story from Tomori.
We want you to take our powers too.
If it helps you even just a little bit, it'll be worth it.
Take Yusa's too.
Misa, you know what that means for you?
Yeah, I'm cool with it.
This is as good a spot as any for me to fade.
Come on, dude. Don’t make this harder than it has to be.
That's right, Otosaka. Go ahead.
All right then. If you're absolutely sure about this.
Yeah.
See ya.
Right.
What the...?
Sorry, did I doze off again?
Yusa, your big sister entrusted
me with this letter to you.
"Yusa, I've had a blast lately.
It was fun hanging out with
those guys from the student council.
I felt that I wanted to be with you forever.
But the one thing that was hardest for me, Yusa,
was that I was always right there with you,
yet we never really saw each other.
I love you more than anything.
And now I'll be a good dead person and fade out.
Goodbye for now.
From Misa."
My big sister was always together
with all of you, wasn't she?
Yeah. We had a lot of fun together.
Indeed.
In that case, I'm glad.
Otosaka, don't keep us waiting too long, OK?
Yeah.
After all, we're high‐school
buddies who suffered together.
We're friends for life. We'll be waiting here for you.
So get back to us as soon as you can.
Right.
Yep.
About frickin' time. Take this, I insist.
It isn't much, but it's all I can do for now.
What is it?
While you're there, it should help
you get by, if only a little bit.
You made this in one night?
I know what your standardized test scores are like.
Yeah. After all, I'm just a filthy cheater, aren't I?
Fine. In return, I want you to hold onto this for me.
Sure, I understand.
It'll be here when you get back.
I'm uneasy. It's all so uncertain.
But I have to do this,
because I am the only one that can.
Well, it's time to go.
Right, have a safe trip, 'K?