Hey, Yu, Ayumi. It's been a while.
What is it?
Um... Who are you again?
He's our big brother.
I had to erase the memories you had of me.
I didn't want to, but it was necessary.
Necessary? I don't understand.
Well, there was a lot going on.
Seems like it, big bro.
Uh... huh?
Yu, it seems that you're finally fully
aware of the true ability that you wield.
That's why I had you come here together.
I would have ended up here whether you brought us or not.
Convenient.
What do you mean by that?
It's a long story.
So you used my time leap.
Well, that was a job well done.
What's gonna happen now?
Can you maybe come home and live with us?
More like the reverse.
You can plunder any ability that you want.
You were the strongest of all ability wielders.
You even have the power of time leap.
That makes you a liability.
What are you trying to say?
There are syndicates around
that would try to use your powers.
I can't let you live in the open anymore.
You'll have to remain here until your powers fade.
For real?
Yeah.
You may already know, but we created this
research facility as a safehouse for ability wielders.
In other words, this is the best place that you could be.
Come with me.
Hmm? Look who it is. So nice of you to drop by.
Grandpa here is head of the research team.
Dr. Tsutsumiuchi.
I know.
He's the one that saved me back then.
And this?
A research facility that is creating a vaccine
to prevent future outbreaks of special abilities.
Vaccine? You mean we're all sick?
Yes. The special abilities are a disease.
So before particles are spread all over Earth again,
we need to vaccinate every person in the world.
Particles?
Have you ever heard of a long‐orbit
comet by the name of Charlotte?
Oh, yes! I know about it, sir.
Oh, you must really like the stars a lot, young lady.
That's right. Stargazing is my favorite hobby.
Charlotte's long orbit brings it by Earth every 75 years.
And when it does, an unknown particle
is showered onto our planet's surface.
Those who inhale the particles generate special powers
during the times when they are most sensitive.
The particles make their way into the cerebral nerves,
then dig up and awaken a sector
that is supposed to stay dormant.
And that is the reason we have powers?
For instance, 400 years ago,
we had an extremely close encounter
and many particles came down.
In Europe, some of those that inhaled the
particles became witches with special powers.
The people who feared the abilities conducted a witch hunt
and tens of thousands of ability
wielders were mercilessly slaughtered.
Roughly 12 years ago, that comet
barely grazed our atmosphere again.
Soon, one after another, young
people began to wield special abilities.
Yu, he's talking about us, you know.
We're developing a vaccine so that
this doesn't happen again in the future.
Its production has already begun in Japan.
Sounds like there's nothing to worry about, then.
No. Japan may be safe, but that doesn't mean
it's the same everywhere else in the world.
Witch hunts are still happening all over.
It never ends.
But that has nothing to do with us.
You can't just dismiss what's going on, Yu.
The ability wielders overseas have banded up.
There's always the possibility that they'll
become terrorists and interfere in world affairs.
Use the vaccine!
We can curb the number of infected that way,
but it doesn't do anything for the
people who already developed abilities.
Then just make a wonder drug to counter it or something.
Disappointing.
It would seem your sharp intellect
doesn't exactly run in the family, Otosaka.
Unfortunately, it takes a very
long time to create a new drug.
We don't know what's gonna happen to us from here on out.
But I promise to protect you both the best I can.
All right then, but at the very least,
I'd like Ayumi to regain her memories about you.
Impossible.
Why is that?
I got all mine back, didn't I?
We don't know why you were the
only one that regained memories.
Was there a large factor somewhere
that caused it or was it just coincidence?
In either case, it's impossible for now.
Damn it, that's just so sad for Ayumi.
Starting today, we can make all new memories as siblings.
Hi, Ayumi.
I'm your oldest brother, Shunsuke.
It's very nice to meet you.
OK. Can I call you "Shun" for short, Big Brother?
Yeah.
Jeez, that was quick!
You won't be able to see your school friends for a while,
but these guys will be your new friends.
They're also ability wielders.
Ayumi Otosaka. It's super nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you too.
You're so sweet.
Shichino, why don't you walk through a wall for starters?
Sure thing. Try not to wet yourself.
Wow! That's incredible.
The recreation room here is pretty substantial.
I think you'll find plenty of fun things to do.
What about music? Can I listen to How‐Low‐Hello if I want?
Sure can.
All right!
I'll be teaching you academics.
OK.
You're adorable.
Thank you very much.
I feel like everyone is keeping their distance from me.
Huh? Is everyone gone already?
They call this one the Bunei Invasion
and the second one the Koan Invasion.
Those are funny names.
In the literature...
Got a sister complex?
No, not really.
You look so fussy.
Big Brother took Ayu away from you.
Wow, Big Brother...
Not true. I'm just bored.
Then you wouldn't mind hanging out with me.
I want you to play for me, OK?
Play?
All right, I got a good hand.
Reach!
Ron.
Double‐value tiles and little three dragons.
All told, I have 36,000 points.
Crazy.
I've never seen someone bomb out in round one.
You really suck at this game.
Are you sure you're Shunsake's little brother?
Damn it, let me play one more!
No. I just found another one.
As usual, it's rather sudden.
Well, my power doesn't let me choose when to find them.
It's always quite random.
Believe me, I wish I could use my ability proactively.
It would make things so much simpler.
So, what did you find exactly?
An ability wielder. What else?
So he didn't have to be drenched in water!
You're going to the student council?
That's right.
Mind if I tag along this time?
Are you really that stupid?
Out of everyone here, you're in the most danger by far.
You can't just leave.
Oh, right, I forgot about that.
I wonder how Tomori's doing.
Wait, why am I thinking about her?
Please head over to Hoshinoumi Academy.
What's wrong? Is something the matter?
No, I'm fine.
Hey, we were supposed to take that turn.
Furuki.
I'm sorry, Kumagami.
I have to take you to a different location.
I don't have a choice.
My family...
They've taken my family hostage.
You didn't say you had a family.
If you guys had found out, I would
have had to leave the syndicate.
That is the rule, yes.
I prided myself on helping you.
It was my greatest honor and purpose in life.
Please forgive me.
Sheesh. Guess it's gonna be one of those days.
Over here. Follow me.
Sure.
Hey, I brought him!
Here goes.
Welcome, mighty one.
You certainly took your time getting here.
Some foreigners. Oh, brother.
He's here, OK. Give me back my family.
Not yet. There is one more thing we need you to do.
We'll contact you later. Now leave.
That's not what you promised!
If he ever again wants to see them alive, he'll do it.
You want to see them again, don't you?
This can't be.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Furuki, you can just think about your family.
Sorry!
It's your turn. Make sure he lives.
Where... am I?
My head feels woozy.
Looks like they injected a truth serum.
You're obviously after information.
We'd like to know about every other
psychic that you're hiding from us.
Hah. Do your worst.
I won't have any left soon.
I'll make sure you pay for my dentures.
I told them anything and everything, didn't I?
I'm sorry, Shunsuke.
Hello?
You are the one who gathered all
the psychics in this country, correct?
He's a foreigner.
So, what if I am?
Kumagami told me who the
strongest psychic in this country was.
He was very helpful.
Kumagami did?
They must have interrogated him.
Is he still alive?
Yes, for the moment.
But he's missing all of his nails and teeth.
What the hell!
What do you want from me?
We want Yu Otosaka.
That won't happen!
We have kidnapped a psychic by the name of Nao Tomori.
We would like him in return for both Tomori and Kumagami.
Where at?
Furuki will take you there.
Furuki?
I would like Yu Otosaka to come by himself.
I have heard all about you from Furuki and Kumagami.
We've been planning this
operation for quite some time now.
If the plans diverge, we will assume you
went to the past to try and change things
and we will kill Furuki's family.
They went that far.
Make a call. Furuki's cell.
Otosaka.
Are you all right?
Did they hurt you, too?
They threatened me. I'm sorry.
Just as I thought.
How long have they been threatening you?
Since before we started building the academy.
That makes it pretty tough.
If I talked, they said they would kill my family.
I thought about suicide,
but I couldn't leave my family behind.
So that's... that's why all this happened.
It's an error in my judgment.
There's no need for you to torment yourself.
I'll make sure your family's safe.
I'm really sorry.
So they've made it out to Japan as well?
How did they get their hands on Kumagami?
They've been threatening Furuki.
It was my mistake. I knew he had a family from the start,
but I let him join anyway.
We're dealing with some evil people.
Then why don't we have your little brother time‐leap to
before Furuki started getting threatened by these jerks?
Because it began before the academy was even built.
If he goes back to that point, it could mess things up.
Meaning there's a possibility
our syndicate may not even exist.
They have us backed into a corner.
Then how about we just have your
little brother rescue Kumagami?
If we do that, Furuki's family will be sacrificed.
They're watching us closely. They'll know if we try it.
How about using an ability wielder
other than your little brother?
They specifically said Yu needs to go alone.
If we screw this up, everyone
they've captured will be killed.
There's nothing we can do then.
If your brother goes in alone like
they said, it might be our best shot.
What?
If we're dealing with other
ability wielders, we can plunder them.
Even if he screws up, he can just use time
leap to redo everything from this point in time.
That way there won't be any irregularities,
so they won't be able to tell that he time‐leaped.
We'll bet everything on him.
So unbecoming. What a sight.
Tomori's captured?
They took out a ton of security guards.
They’re obviously professionals from overseas,
and I'm sure that they're armed.
You want me to take them on by myself?
You'll be fine. I know it.
First, you'll need to plunder all their
abilities and make them drop all their weapons.
Can you do that?
Sure thing, if they don't shoot me first.
The enemy wants you alive. They won't do
anything that might kill you, understand?
Still, if you get caught,
or if they put Nao and Kumagami in harm's way,
use your time leap quickly and
come back to this point in time.
We'll try something else.
And try not to get worked up.
Your collapse power will trigger,
and then your own life will be in danger.
Yu, understand?
What's with all this?
Yu?
What is this? There's no way in
hell I can do something like that!
I'm not some one‐man army, all right?
I'm just a guy who cheated his way
through school and got caught in the act!
I'm selfish and cowardly and only think of myself!
All I ever wanted was to be popular
and glide through life without problems!
That's all I am.
What can I...?
Calm down!
Just focus on my heartbeat. Concentrate, Yu.
Are you calm now?
I'm sorry, I was rushing things.
If you think you're in trouble,
just time‐leap back to this point.
That's all you need to remember.
We still have some time. Think it over for a bit.
I gotta say, you seem like you'd
be popular from just your good looks.
Did you really need to play the
genius by cheating as much as possible?
We didn't start off that great.
Some investigation, of course.
My dream is to film a video for their band.
That's why I've decided to stick
with you until this is through
and you're back to normal.
It was the same thing with Ayumi.
You can't have something once you've lost it.
I will rescue Tomori.
I'm ready.
So you're OK with it?
We'll go as far as we can with you,
so you won't be alone.
If something happens, we'll rescue you.
OK.
I'm guessing you're Furuki.
Yeah.
Get in.
I brought him!
Looks like it's just these two out in the open.
But they're adults, not ability wielders.
Then, as I promised, I will let your family go free.
Here, catch!
That's the key to the condo.
The location is written on the tag.
I'm sorry.
This was the only thing I could do!
Let's do this.
They're not armed?
Are you satisfied now?
Where is Tomori?
Right below us.
Both of them are in the basement.
Let them go now and I won't hurt you!
I gotta time‐leap.
It's pointless.
Even your impressive powers won't let you
travel to the past with only one healthy eye.
Use collapse if you like, but your
friends in the basement won't survive it.
Damn it!
Damn it, that wasn't necessary!
Hurry!
Not good. He's using collapse.
Why isn't he using time leap?
I have no idea. What do we do?
No way.
Why the hell are you just standing there?
We have to save them!
Y‐Yeah.
How does it look?
Pretty hopeless.
But we still have to search for them.
Nao!
Kumagami! Yu!
Shunsuke, over here!
Are those the main culprits?
Medoki, please.
Right.
I found your brother!
He blocked it with telekinesis.
He's still alive.
However, they ruined one eye.
So that's why he couldn't time‐leap.
Please, take him somewhere safe for me.
Right.
I swear, if he ends up being OK but
the other two die because of all this,
I'm gonna be seriously pissed off.
Kumagami, Nao... where are you?
Found them! They're both here!
Over here!
Kumagami! Kumagami! You there?
Come on, answer me. Hey!
Kumagami.
Is that you, Shunsuke?
I... tried my best.
Kumagami! Don't you die!
I won't allow it. Do you hear me?
You've gotta stay by my side forever!
I'm afraid that might be too tall of an order now.
Shut up! Don't talk like that.
You can't go off on your own.
You can't leave me here!
Shunsuke...
I guess the name "Pooh" was just a lie after all.
Kumagami! Kumagami!
Kumagami!