Good morning.
Good morning, sleepy head!
Here, I made some French toast for you.
It's red!
Since you won't be needing lunches for school anymore,
I decided to put more effort into your breakfast.
Put more effort, huh?
Looks like that's nothing more than adding pizza sauce.
Time to eat!
The sugar from the pizza sauce mixed
with the sugar in the French toast!
What's wrong? Does it taste weird?
Oh, no, it's fine.
Seems like I'm not feeling too well.
Aww, did you catch a cold?
Maybe you should stay home from school today.
It's not that bad. I'm sorry that I'm making you worry.
Are you sure you're gonna be all right?
I'm totally fine!
Thank you for the meal.
You really do look pale.
You should be taking the day off today.
No, no, there's nothing wrong, I promise.
I need to find a place to bury that pizza sauce.
I got some amazing news.
Yusa Nishimori is transferring into our school!
You mean the Yusarin?
No way.
This isn't a big art school or anything.
If she's the real thing, I'll be so happy.
As expected, everyone is getting pumped.
There's going to be a riot when she actually shows up.
Just thinking about it's really got me on edge.
Quiet.
You there, sit down.
Seriously?
Over here.
Now, this transfer student will
be your classmate starting today.
Introduce yourself.
I'm Yusa Kurobane, known as Yusarin.
Quiet! I said be quiet!
You there, sit down. And you there, stop dancing!
Even in a place like this, she calls herself Yusarin?
So her real name is Kurobane?
How could you not even know that much?
I may not be able to attend every day
because work can keep me pretty busy,
but when I'm here, I look forward to
enjoying high school life with all of you.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
Yusarin! Yusarin!
Sit down and shut up!
Oh, brother.
Kurobane, you sit there. That's your seat now.
It's nice to see you again.
Same. I'm sure I'll trouble you a
lot, but I'll try to be a good neighbor.
It's very nice to see you, too.
What's with her? She's so rude.
So not friendly.
Why did you transfer here?
Oh, I preordered your new single.
Me too. It's such a great song.
I always watch Movement Morning!
Me too, me too.
Will you please be my friend? What's your email?
You bastard, what do you think
you're doing? Don't try to cut us out.
I'm not doing any such thing.
Now, now, both of you, be nice to each other.
Ahh! Is she gonna do what I think she is?
Huh? Do what?
I cast a spell on you, I cast a spell on you.
Now we can all make up and be friends too!
There it is!
Yusarin's Magic Spell, series
number 13, the spell for making up!
There, now don't you two feel better?
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
All good, I was wrong.
What is that so‐called Magic Spell series?
Yusa was once a regular cast member of the hit morning
information show Movement Morning!, or "Move‐Mo."
After the day's fortunes, she'd send out various spells,
particularly towards the viewers
who had bad luck that day.
And just how many episodes of this are there?
There are 64.
But two of them actually overlap, so there are really...
Big turnoff.
Hello. Will he be appearing before us again?
Yes.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, hey, watch it!
Kurobane, I'd like you to come
with us to the student council room.
Hey, Student Council President, that's not cool.
Let's get going.
Right.
Yusa, that Magic Spell you did earlier, series number 13,
the spell for making up, it was fantastic!
Wow! I can't believe you know so much about it.
Yes! I checked out the show religiously
for the entire time you were a part of it.
Wow! Thank you very much.
You're such a fan boy. Get over it, already.
I have a question.
What are we going to do in here, exactly?
A comrade will arrive soon.
However, we should probably
get you mentally prepared for him.
His unusual appearance might shock you.
Now, don't be afraid.
He's one of us. He will never do harm to you.
The ability is telekinesis.
Um, can someone tell me what just happened?
Someone with a special ability is in this general area,
and the power he has is telekinesis.
That guy found you in exactly the same manner.
What? That's amazing!
I'm going to do my best. All right!
You know, you can get possessed
by spirits and have pyrokinesis.
You're even more amazing.
Looks like another school.
I think it's Kannai Academy.
Yeah, bingo!
Uh, what is?
This is the sports paper from last week.
I've had my eye on this guy for a while.
Wow! He pitched three perfect games in a row.
"With sharp knuckleballs, no doubt this super
high school level pitcher will join the pro league."
The next day, I went and watched them practice.
Everyone should look at this.
Here we go.
Strike!
That's one heck of a curveball.
He's like major league caliber.
It gets even better.
Watch some footage where we get a
closeup of the pitcher's throwing hand.
There. Take a look.
See something strange?
Like what?
He's gripping it like a fastball, one that goes straight.
Knuckleballs are supposed to move irregularly
by stopping the ball rotation as much as possible.
The basic knuckleball is thrown by putting your
index and middle fingers against the ball like this.
How you grip a fastball makes it spin and it doesn't
allow it to wobble around like a knuckleball does.
You sure know a lot.
I get it now.
He's using telekinesis to move the ball
around after he's thrown it, isn't he?
Yes.
Wow! That's amazing, right?
Does she get any of this?
It will be bad if we can't get ahold
of him before the national championship.
Let's head there right now.
Well, what about class?
It's all right. No matter how we act, as
long as we're a part of the student council,
there can be no demerits towards
our grades or our school reports.
Is that so?
We're from the Hoshinoumi Academy Student Council.
We're practicing right now. What is it you guys want?
I'm sorry.
Yusa Nishimori?!
Could you just ignore her for the moment
and listen to what I have to say, please?
What is it?
I'm not beating around the bush here.
Do you use telekinesis to control
your knuckleballs after you throw them?
Telekinesis? As in supernatural abilities?
Are you insane? Of course I don't.
Are you from some occult research
club instead of the student council?
All right, wise guy, listen closely.
That power of yours is like a disease
that's only around during your adolescence.
Even if you were aiming to be a pro,
by the time you reach it, it will be long gone.
Not only that, but if someone notices you have powers,
you'll be captured.
Then you can kiss baseball goodbye for good.
So from here on, don't use that
special ability of yours, understand?
And who would capture me, exactly?
Scientists who are experimenting on
people with abilities just like you.
You expect me to believe something that crazy?
All right, fine.
Do me a big favor and don't look away.
What?
So, do you believe me now?
You really are a sore loser, aren't you?
I say that we roast this chump.
Hey!
What?
Oh, uh, my bad.
This isn't the time to be showing off.
Ohh! Yusarin's spit. No, this is Misa's saliva.
I don't know how I should react.
Turnoff!
Back to business.
So, how are we gonna resolve this?
I know. How about a game of baseball?
It'll be our baseball team versus your baseball team.
And if we win, you have to do whatever we say.
All right, then.
And if we win, I don't see you ever again.
Deal.
But still, you'll never become
a professional baseball player.
I don't understand what drives you to play. What is it?
I want to go to the national championship, that's all.
Understood.
Next Sunday at 3 p. m. at our
school courtyard. How about it?
I don't have any problems with that.
What's wrong, Arifumi?
So someone that can hit that
knuckleball exists on our baseball team?
We'll be using our abilities, so it will be just fine.
And what kind of powers does the team have?
They don't.
They have several people with potential
but no one's developed a special ability yet.
Then how do we pull this off?
We'll be there to support them.
You mean we're all a part of this?
We won't win otherwise.
Besides, if it's on our school
courtyard, it won't turn into a riot.
That was the appropriate move.
I'm getting fired up now.
Don't you burn anything.
Bow.
Have a good game.
Our opposing team has girls in it, huh?
No way they can hit your pitches.
What's the point of this game, anyway?
It's all about the future, Takato.
I see, all right. Let's do this then.
If you lose, I'm smacking all your asses, with this bat.
Win!
Yeah!
Smacking asses with a bat?
What is she, an old woman?
Play ball!
Yes.
They must have the worst batters on the
planetif they can't even hit one of our balls.
Is that so?
I'm doing you a favor being out there.
What kind of talk is that?
It's the truth.
Screw you, I'm outta here!
That won't do. Please keep pitching.
Then think before you open your big mouth!
Kurobane, please go ahead.
OK.
I cast a spell for thee, I cast it, don't you see?
Now that you are nice and calm, please smile for me!
It's from Magic Spells series
number 9, the spell for calming down!
Yep. Now everything's gonna be A‐OK.
Knock it off!
Strike! Batter out.
That knuckleball's insane. No way we're ever gonna hit it.
Just go ahead and smack me, I don't care.
You know, it's pretty amazing the
catcher manages to catch pitches like that.
Guess that means that he's super high school level, too.
There's no way we can win this.
We just need one run.
If the two of us can score one run,
we can win, as long as we protect that lead.
Here goes!
Not good. So they went after Yusa after all.
Misa, on the other hand, has athletic reflexes.
Damn, why is Yusa so weak?
I see.
She can make the right decision,
but she can't physically keep up.
Strike! Batter out.
Out!
Ball four!
Not looking good.
Out!
Safe!
This is a total crisis.
We should use abilities as well.
Specifically...?
You need to take over the opponents' batters.
What I want you to do is make the last two of
them listless so they barely swing their bats.
Throw outside of the strike zone.
Just be careful to not throw a wild pitch.
Yeah, got it.
All right now, I'm counting on you.
Play ball!
Never thought I'd use my powers for something like this.
Strike!
Huh? What the...?
What's the matter?
Strike two!
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, totally fine.
It's two outs with the next guy.
Arifumi, if you want to be that thorough
in winning this thing, we have to go all out!
Catcher!
Safe!
Takato.
Wait, what the hell happened?
I didn't think that far ahead.
Did he steal home base?
Damn, damn, damn!
Guess we ain't winnin' this one.
Strike! Batter out!
Just make sure that you hit the ball when you bunt.
Then use your ability to run past
first base, and don't forget to touch it.
Are you sure that they'll see me make it there?
I'll record the evidence with a super‐high‐speed camera.
Understood.
Strike!
Strike two!
If I screw up the next one, I'm out.
Here it comes, four‐eyes.
Yes!
He touched first base, it's plain as day.
Come on now, it's safe. Call safe!
Safe!
What the heck happened?
That was great. We won't let it go to waste.
I need a pinch runner!
Yusa's weak, but I'll use my
own game sense to hit the ball.
All right!
That's the way. It was awesome!
It's your turn to bat now, so what are you going to do?
A sacrifice bunt, and once it succeeds,
one base hit will get us a walk‐off.
Huh? I can't hit like that with my ability.
How about you go face things head on once in a while?
Show me the fiend that cheats on tests.
Please hit it!
First base!
They're just a bunch of amateurs!
Out!
I have to face this crap head on?
Lead! Lead!
Strike!
Strike two!
Damn!
Foul ball!
I finally hit it.
Foul!
His timing is inching closer.
I'll move it a bit more on this one.
Crap! It's all over.
It's not over. Move it. He fumbled!
Safe!
We can do this. I have the game sense!
Takato, home!
Safe! That's the game!
Did you see that? I ruled!
That was amazing, Yusarin!
So did we win?
Yes, by the skin of our teeth.
We won. That's awesome.
All right!
Wait, why am I getting so happy about something like this?
We were victorious.
Please never use that ability again, ever.
I'm just an ordinary pitcher.
But Takato, the catcher, is different.
He's a catcher that really
deserves to be in the spotlight.
The two of us have played together for a long time.
He knew that the baseball team at our school was weak.
But still he chose to pair up with me.
I just wanted to take him to nationals,
even if it meant using this power.
The nationals, that big stage
where even pros would notice him.
So instead of personal gain, you were
using your ability for your friendship.
That's right.
We won the game today because
we cheated with our abilities.
But you've been cheating while pitching for quite a while.
But there are people who will notice him out there,
even if you don't cheat,
and it doesn't matter if it's in
college or in the business leagues.
You can keep watch over him as his best friend.
Someday he'll shine out there and you'll
point to him and say, "That is my closest friend."
I'm sure of it. It'll be all right.
I know.
As a small experiment, can you try taking over his body?
Uh‐huh. What for?
Like I said, it's an experiment.
You don't say that to your test subject.
He's the test subject, so don't worry.
Whatever.
Whoa! What the...?
Thank you for indulging me.
No, it wasn't anything much. Did you figure something out?
I'm not sure for now.
Just going to see how things go for a while.
I beg you, just this once, can I
have dinner without pizza sauce?
I'm back!
A secret recipe of the Otosaka house.
A cream stew full of broccoli!
It's red!
But cream stew is supposed to be white, isn't it?
That is what makes it a secret family recipe.
Just as I thought.
What do I believe in, you ask?
I have to believe in myself, of course.
The power to believe...
Oh! It's a new commercial from Yusarin.
And it's How‐Low‐Hello's new song.
That reminds me, did Yusarin really
transfer to your school, Big Brother?
Yeah.
That is just... so incredibly amazing!