Doctor!
How are you feeling?
Ayumi. My little sister!
I'm terribly sorry. She didn't make it.
I'm Detective Someda.
I'm terribly sorry for your loss.
I'd like to work with you so we can
figure out what really happened at the school.
I heard that you were at the scene...
Are you all right?
I'm sure this has been rough for you.
But for her sake, you have to keep moving
forward with your life, you understand?
There are many things in this world that time solves.
But it won't solve everything.
Did I do...
even one thing for her?
Was I able... to repay her?
No. I didn't repay her at all.
Nothing.
I never thought she could be gone this quickly.
It just didn't seem possible.
Even if I wanted to repay, I couldn't.
I'll never get another chance.
Was there anything left?
The love letters just keep pouring in.
In your dreams, maybe. Be honest.
The last piece of fan mail you
got was from your mother, wasn't it?
Actually, she sent hate mail.
Accepting enrollment at Shinkou Seminars now.
Let's move on.
The flavor of instant noodles...
Uh, yuzu pepper!
What's?
Correct!
The entire question was this:
We were in studios,
what is the best ingredient that can be added
to enhance this incredible flavor to be its best?
Otosaka!
Otosaka, if you haven't eaten yet,
would you like to have dinner with us?
I brought some. It's my special homemade cream stew.
Come on, you can't turn down something like that.
I don't want any.
Well, what should we do?
Let's look again.
Darn it, I think he went back already.
It was going to be mine!
Now Yusarin's cream stew is ruined!
You creeper!
Look, I'll have Yusa make you as much as you want.
All you have to do is break the door with your ability.
I can break fortified glass,
sure, but this door is too thick.
Due to security reasons, it's made
a lot sturdier than normal condos.
You're so damn useless.
Even if I burn the door, nothing will come of it.
I don't know what to do in this situation.
I get what he must be feeling now.
Hell, I know it a lot better than most people.
What?
OK, so what happened here, exactly?
It seems that he needs a bit more time to heal.
I see. Then let's come back again later.
Excuse me.
Sorry to barge in without permission.
It's me, Shirayanagi.
Is he all right?
Yes. He seems OK to me.
All right, I'll leave him to you, then.
Who is it?
You saved me from a truck when we were classmates once.
So?
I heard that you haven't been to school ever since...
About your little sister, I'm terribly sorry.
I'm in no position to say this, but...
is there anything I can do?
No.
Anything is fine.
Please, Otosaka, I just want
to help you, if you'll let me.
Help me?
What makes you think that I need any help?
I'm totally fine.
There's no way that's true.
I mean, you've been eating nothing but instant noodles.
I like them, so it's OK.
Well, then... how about those pancakes we had together?
We could get them again.
Pancakes?
When did we eat that?
The day you saved me.
Instant noodles or pancakes.
Aren't they about the same nutrition‐wise?
Yeah, I suppose you're right.
But we could still go outside.
Right.
I'm glad.
Can you get me more instant noodles while you're out?
You’re running an errand for me, aren’t you?
Instant noodles. I don't care what kind.
No, no. Otosaka, you're coming with me.
I don't feel like it.
I'll pay you back later, OK?
I won't go unless you do.
You won't go unless I go, huh?
Shirayanagi, was it?
Are you my legal guardian now?
No, I don't mean it like that at all.
But I am concerned for you right now.
So you won't do it?
No, I won't!
Look, Otosaka, it's important that you get outside a bit.
If you stay cooped up, you'll only drive yourself insane.
Like mentally ill?
Yes.
There's no chance of that at all.
I told you, I'm totally fine.
If you were, you wouldn't be living like this.
It just proves that you're depressed.
Who do you think you are?!
I never asked you to come here!
If you're not going to run errands for me, you can leave.
OK, I'll go.
I shouldn't have come here. I'm sorry.
I better stock up again.
I guess they're here to capture me by force.
Shirayanagi may have been acting because she was asked to,
which means it's time to make my exit.
I'll be out for a while.
If I have this much,
I'm sure I can live for a while without going back home.
I need to go somewhere far away so
that soggy freak show can't locate me.
This might be far enough for now.
I'm sick of noodles, so I guess I'll have some pizza.
What do you know? I gave them the slip.
Excuse me.
Your pizza and a salad.
Salad? Must be a free item. I'll pass.
So damn boring.
How many days has it been?
Nothing has gone on for this long.
I'm sure they won't find me.
I guess.
I'll go out for just a little bit.
Can I have that?
Sure thing.
It's good.
It's been a while since I had something sweet.
Watch your left. Your left!
I got it!
Kick ass!
Never seen a game like that.
Now, this is fun!
Die! Die!
I'll kill every single one of you who gets in my way!
Die! I want you to die!
Eat my lead and like it!
Take this! Boo‐yah!
You've been playing for hours.
Get outta the way!
The hell. What'd you say? Trying to pick a fight?
What's up?
This punk hit me with trash and told me to move.
Who do you think you are, kid?
Just a normal, law‐abiding citizen.
A law‐abiding citizen that assaults people with trash?
Yeah, it looked good on you.
Don’t mock us!
Take him outside.
Just remember, you asked for this.
Ready for some pain, hot‐shot?
You think you can beat me? Bring it.
I'll make sure you can't play games for a while.
You bastard! What do you think you're doing?
What the hell, I thought I punched this guy!
What's wrong?
You guys have a falling out? Kiss and make up.
What is this? What the hell is going on?
I still have one more left.
No, stop, stop!
Now you know how strong I am.
Next time you go against me, I won't hesitate to kill you.
Got it?
Yo. How's it going?
You're the punk that beat Gondo's gang all by himself?
Maybe. It's not like I stopped
to ask their names, you know.
Well, I'm Hosoyamada. Remember that.
I give it five seconds before I forget all about you.
You've got some balls, kid.
You should really learn some respect.
Give him his first lesson, boys.
What the hell are you doing?
It wasn't me!
You don't need this eye, right?
If I take it, you can call yourself something
cool like "One‐Eyed‐Hoso‐whatever."
You don't seem excited.
What's wrong, don't like the name?
Better choose!
Fine! I give! Mercy!
The Hosoyamada lost?
Impossible.
Nobody can win against me.
Real fights are tons more fun than a stupid game.
What is this thing?
Something important to you?
So that's how it is.
Hey wait... When did... when did you...?
The whole time.
The whole time?
It can't be.
If you keep following this path,
you'll lose your humanity and never get it back again.
That's why I stopped you.
Did somebody send you?
No. I'm on a leave of absence for now.
This is personal.
How so?
I feel responsible for this as well.
When you get down to it,
I might have made a bad call concerning Ayumi.
Maybe I should have quarantined her immediately.
At least then she would have been safe.
That's why I've decided to stick
with you until this is through
and you're back to normal.
This is none of your business! You owe me for that stuff!
Do you want to be done with your life?
Do you want to stop being human?
Then...
what am I supposed to do?
A fresh change of clothes would be a nice start.
But let's get some food for now.
A good meal is the foundation
of a healthy mood and lifestyle.
There's nothing wrong with what I've been eating.
Right, a diet of pizza and sweat
soy sauce mochi is so healthy.
It'll calm you down, at least.
What are you saying I should eat?
You just leave it to me.
I'll get it for you right away.
Hey, it's me.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I didn't say for you to set something up for me!
Just take one bite.
After that, I swear we will have
nothing to do with each other again.
Just one bite, huh?
Then you'll leave me alone forever?
Yes, I promise.
Fine.
Good, then let's go.
That promise is absolute?
Right.
Takajo?
Yes. His family home.
Is this an ambush or something?
Nobody is here so you can relax.
Watch some TV or something.
What are you making me eat?
That's a surprise for you to see when it's finished.
I didn't know she was allergic.
Are you stupid?
It was a poison mushroom, idiot!
It grew naturally, out of the
ground. It couldn't be poison.
Here, it's done!
Here you go.
It's the same taste.
Glad I did it justice.
How?
Your mother left behind a big notebook full of recipes.
I took the liberty of borrowing it.
The page with the omelet rice was the
only one with a big, flowery circle on it.
I have a feeling it was your
favorite food when you were a kid.
After your mother was no longer around,
I think Ayumi saw that and tried to
recreate the taste to make you happy.
So that was...
the last omelet rice.
Damn it.
It's sweet and it tastes so horrible.
Why am I eating it?
It's not healthy for you to scarf it down like that.
Just eat slowly and savor it.
OK.
Here. Have some tea.
And take this, too.
Hey, Tomori.
Yes?
What the hell am I supposed to do with myself now?
Well, you could always return to
the student council and help us out.
But that's not possible.
We promised we would never have
anything to do with each other.
Huh? What the heck are you talking about?
You said that's what would happen after I ate this.
Yeah, if you ate one bite, but you
scarfed it down like a hungry stray.
"Oh, wow, he must really wanna stay with me!"
That's what I kept thinking, at least.
Of course you did.
All right.
Student council it is.
I'm glad to hear it.