So what is it you do on your days off?
How about some tea later today?
And it's really cute.
Yusarin, you should go too!
Sure, that sounds good to me.
Aww, come on, how long are they gonna keep this up?
Can you blame them? Yusarin is a pop idol.
This was bound to happen soon.
Huh? What's going on?
I think I might know, but it's
probably better if you don't.
First, for Rika!
Next, for Yuriko!
Group beating? Not cool.
Though I guess it's expected when she
does stuff like that without thinking.
So, uh, are you all right?
You were watching the whole time.
You tell me.
Oh. Our comrade is going to appear.
Oh, my gosh, what happened to you?
I just got beaten by a mob.
Are you all right? Shouldn't you go to a hospital?
I'm used to it, I'll be fine.
So, who are we going to pummel?
I'm not going. Too much of a hassle.
You're so boring.
The ability is... floating on air.
All right, we got this! Check it out!
A flying humanoid is found in Japan as well?
Are they saying that this black shadow is that person?
For the moment, it's only a
scoop in a small occult magazine.
But if we leave this alone, it will turn into a huge deal.
Let's go.
Where to?
Here, in the middle of the mountains.
This is just a hunch, but I think that's
where our target is practicing how to fly.
If we stake out that location,
they're bound to appear at some point.
Just how long of a stakeout are you thinking?
No clue. Until they show up.
Don't make Yusarin say something like that!
We could be in for a long haul,
so we should probably stock up at the supermarket first.
Seriously?
Um, can you go back to being sweet Yusa, please?
I don't like your tone, four‐eyes.
Give me one good reason why I should take orders from you!
'Cause you always end up like this.
Some team we've got. Just my luck.
All right, you guys, let's get going.
So is there a reason you're getting so much corn?
Because you can't have a barbecue without roasted corn.
Barbecue?
If you do that, they'll know that we're all out there.
True, but who's to say this person
won't decide to approach us on their own?
Huh? Yeah, like that'll happen.
What else?
Steak meat, spare ribs, sausages.
OK, so now you're thinking only about meat.
Yeah, because meat is good.
Watch and learn.
Oh, shishito?
The spice gives a nice accent to flavors.
Fine, we'll get them, but they
better not touch my meat, OK?
Those two have been getting along
rather well lately, haven't they?
Hey, do you think they could be dating?
It hasn't been long since they first
met, so I don't think it's gone that far.
But they are a couple that's pleasant to watch.
Yeah. I think they're well‐suited for each other.
All alone with Yusarin! I'm so glad I'm alive!
All right, boys, you two get to
carry the tent and the barbecue grill.
Kurobane and I will carry all the food to the campsite.
Tent? You mean we're spending the night?
I told you, we're going to stay on
stakeout until our target shows up.
Excuse me. I didn't bring a change of clothes, so, um...
You won't die if you wear the same thing.
Now let's go.
All right, we're here.
We should set up the tents before dark.
Right.
Careful. It's dangerous over there.
What is this?
The remnants of a well.
Why didn't you say anything about it earlier?
Well, if you fell, that would have been funny in a way.
Don't make jokes about life‐or‐death situations.
Why don't we set it up further that way?
Good call.
Don't worry. I'll plug up the big hole
just as soon as we're done setting up.
Sorry, there's a student council camp,
so I don't think I'll make it home tonight.
You can't come home? It's awfully sudden.
That's right. That's why I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine, I'm fine. No worries.
Later.
Roger that.
This could be useful.
Don't use me as a lighter. I am not a camping kit.
What are you thinking?
This makes us stand out way too much.
Roasted corn is so delicious!
OK, come on, everyone, eat up.
I guess she can have this.
What just...?
Here, have some roasted corn, Yusa!
Thank you so much!
Oh, my! Tasty!
I know, right?
When it comes to roasted corn, I'm your girl.
We'll have meat soon!
Mmm. Eat vegetables, too.
Spare ribs are so good!
The wieners are super juicy when you crunch into them!
Don't have just meat.
Sandwich some vegetables in the middle when you eat.
Oh! This meat is so delicious.
This sauce is the best!
And in the end, I'm the only one eating any vegetables.
So you only eat meat, too, just like my big sister.
Oh, is that so?
Yes, she was a very finicky eater.
She was? Hey, I'd be interested to know
what kind of person your big sister was to you.
Well, let's see.
Big sister and I have basically
polar opposite personalities.
She was such a tomboy that no boy in
the neighborhood could win against her.
But to me, she was a very kind big sister.
And I loved her exactly the way she was.
No matter what, I always tagged along behind her.
Oh! Sorry, I'm talking too much.
When it comes to my sister, I get so carried away.
No. I kind of understand how you feel, actually.
There are way too many enemies.
I think I'm in really big trouble.
Don't you worry, leave everything to the mighty Taka...
I don't need your stupid help!
That was my moment to shine!
You guys are completely
forgetting the reason why we're here.
Hold on... where?
Is there something wrong?
Well, um... no, nothing.
So, uh, what is that music?
You listen to it day in and day out.
This? It's a band called Zhiend.
Never heard of them.
My brother loved them.
Are you sure you're OK?
Yeah.
Mind if I listen to that for a bit?
Why...
I think I've felt this before.
How is it?
It's kind of strange.
I feel like I'm standing all alone in a vast, open space.
Ha‐ha! You understand it, don't you?
You are so on point.
The music Zhiend creates is incredibly
vast and downlight lonely‐feeling.
I believe it's because the vocalist,
who also composes the songs, is completely blind.
Her words paint scenery extending as far as you can go.
For now, I'm only recording this poor, misguided cheater,
but my dream is to film a Zhiend music video.
She's never had this expression before.
Of course, filming a documentary would be OK, too.
Yeah. Don’t film poor old me.
Just go ahead and film them if you want.
Don’t worry, I'm never gonna film you again, I promise.
Keep it. I'm giving it to you.
No way. I'd feel bad about it.
I have quite a bit saved up thanks to a few of our jobs.
I can just buy a new one, so don't worry about it.
I see.
Then I'll take it.
Good.
Two will keep watch at a time.
We'll take shifts all the way until morning.
The boys will sleep four hours,
then switch places with us.
Hey, Otosaka. It's our turn now.
Hey, time to switch.
Oh, it's that time already?
This again. Who was that person?
Whoa! A trout! I caught a rainbow trout!
Damn it. I'll catch one bigger than
that. Trout, trout, come to me now!
I'm not going to lose either.
All right, got one!
Oh, wow, rainbow trout is tasty.
Yusarin, this one is cooked perfectly.
I'm not Yusarin!
But I guess I'll let her enjoy it.
Oh. Are you sure you don't want to eat it, Takajo?
I'm sure. It's all yours.
Whoa, so delicious!
Things like this are nice every so often.
Yes!
Is it me, or does she just want to play?
So, um, are we spending the night again?
Yes. Is there a problem with that?
I was thinking I'd like to take a bath today.
That's fine. I have one all ready.
Come on, I'll show you.
How nice.
Here's a towel and some soap.
You've got some nerve.
You set this up and just assumed I would jump right in.
I'll keep an eye out in case
the boys decide to try peeping. OK?
You said there was a bath all ready?
It's only for girls.
You boys can clean yourselves down at the river.
I can't bathe in the water that Yusarin has bathed in?!
Turnoff!
You don't look that ripped when you have clothes on.
Because of my ability, I had to train my body.
Regardless of how much armor
I would wear under my uniform,
I had to build a body that wouldn’t
get too injured when I teleported.
You did all that just so you
could properly use your ability?
Yes. But I doubt that I'll be the only one who does that.
What do you mean by that?
In the future, you may face a challenge that's beyond
your expectations and that forces you to make a change.
You never know.
Yeah. Because taking someone over
for only five seconds is so useful.
It's because you haven't...
Just forget I said anything.
What? Come on, now. You got me curious.
With an attractive face like that, you
might have some issues dealing with the ladies.
Of course, just saying that gets under my skin.
You're telling me.
I was just dumped by an intelligent
and beautiful girl thanks to this ability.
A wise choice.
I think we should focus on love and romance
only after we are freed of these abilities.
How old do we need to be for them to be gone?
It should happen by the time we graduate high school.
Two more years. That's a long time.
Yes. For us, it is a very long time.
You know what? This is way too cold.
Ah, this feels good.
We'll sleep using the same rotation as yesterday.
Tomorrow is Monday, right?
Are we gonna go to school from here?
Haven't you been listening?
We're staking out until they show up.
This is ridiculous.
It feels like we're all trying
to live out here or something.
That's exactly what I'm after.
Besides, it's not like ditching class
will affect our school reports at all.
Even so, I'd like to go home at some point.
I have a younger sister.
Yes, I already know that.
Then I'll promise to be back in the morning.
Just let me go home.
I can't. If I allow that for you,
everyone else will say the same thing.
Besides, I think it'll be all right.
What will?
I'm sure everything will be squared away by tomorrow.
Man, I'm really sick of corn.
Excuse me.
What do you guys think you're doing all the way out here?
Someone really showed up. Is this the guy?
Well, we all met after running away from our homes.
We hit it off pretty well so we
decided to set up camp together.
Another obvious lie.
I take it, since you're camping,
that you intend to stay here.
Yes. We’re planning to stay here forever.
It's not like people will find us here.
Really? Well, I found you.
And I'm sure your parents are worried as well.
If you're thinking of calling the police,
you should know that they'll arrest you, too.
What for?
Simple. It's private property.
And then there's this. That’s you, isn't it?
What is that, a magazine?
A scoop article on you practicing flight.
You're joking.
It's too easy to get caught if
you practiced in public mountains.
But this place is private and conveniently
close to the boundary of Tokyo.
Normally, you'd be fine, but we
camped out and showed no sign of leaving.
You got restless and decided to try and scare us off.
Once we were gone, you could
practice flying again in peace.
If you really believe that, you must be insane.
I'll call the police for you.
You're not very sane either if
you're coming out here all by yourself.
I came to pick some chestnuts.
There aren't any chestnuts this time of year.
And you can't deny that you were out
here because I already captured you on film.
How very sad for you.
You little brat! Give it to me now!
Yes!
You used the well to trap him?
Of course. If you fall into a hole that you
don't know the bottom of, you use your ability.
I put some hay at the bottom, just in case I was wrong.
But thanks to you, I have some
amazing footage for a scoop.
She set a trap out here and didn't even tell us about it?
She is just like the devil.
Give me the camera!
Otosaka, take over his body!
Then I'll defeat him using my teleport ability.
No way. That hurts every time I do it.
Damn it!
Thanks a lot.
He's escaping.
And so fast.
I have no choice.
I'm so high up!
I have to control it for now.
Stop... stop... stop!
Stop!
You took such a reckless risk there.
I should have just taken him over
immediately instead of complaining.
What is this?
What just happened?
Well, a bruise or a broken bone for one.
You're pretty lucky.
My camcorder is fine, too.
It's a good thing you survived.
What the hell? Who are you guys?
We all have special abilities like you.
But these abilities are kind of like diseases
that only show up during adolescence.
They'll disappear,
but if someone finds out about you,
you'll turn into a guinea pig for scientists.
You don't want that, do you?
And what would happen if your ability
disappeared while you were flying?
You would fall to your death.
Is this something to risk your life over?
Misa, if you would, please.
Of course.
I see.
I thought that this power to fly
was something granted just to me.
But I guess there are others, too.
What a bummer.
I wanted to fry freely someday.
I even had a dream of becoming "Sky‐high Saito,"
the biggest star in Hollywood.
What a corny name?!
I understand the feeling,
but for the sake of your life and future,
please don't use your ability anymore.
I got it.
Thank you so much.
That ended peacefully.
Phew! That took so long.
Yeah. That's totally how I feel.
I'm back.
I didn't think the student
council was something this busy.
I can't help it.
I know you're very competent,
but are you being pulled all over the place?
It's really nothing that extravagant.
Well then, in honor of my big
brother and all of his hard work,
I have prepared a feast!
Chanpon noodles with lots of vegetables!
It's not red. This is... doable!
It's time to dig in.
It's time to eat.
At last!
So, how is it?
Delicious! So delicious it makes me cry!
Actually, I wanted to use the
pizza sauce as a secret ingredient,
but I only have a tiny bit left.
If you can make food that's
this delicious without pizza sauce,
can't you leave it out of all the other food, too?
The Otosaka pizza sauce secret recipe
needs to be handed down to the last generation.
But when I was about to go to the supermarket,
the security guard stopped me.
I couldn't buy the ingredients for it.
Nice security!
This is the first thing that's made
me feel happy about moving here.
But this is delicious all on its own,
so you really don't need any secret ingredients.
If you say so. That saves me a lot.
Yes. I succeeded in getting rid of
that pizza sauce once and for all!
You really aren't feeling well, are you?
No, no. I'm totally fine now.
By the way, I had so many stories that I wanted
you to hear while you were gone, Big Brother.
Yeah? What stories?
For starters, I was suddenly asked out by
one of the boys in my class the other day.
What? And what did you do?
Oh, you know.
Oh, don't give me that.
I politely declined the offer.
Oh, man, that could have been a pivotal
moment that would have changed your entire life.
Aww. What do you mean, Big Brother?
Do you want me to have a boyfriend or something?
It depends on the guy.
It's gonna have to be someone better than my big brother.
Someone like that is a rarity.
You're right.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You might have a cold or something.
A fever. How is your appetite?
It's OK. I can finish eating all of this, no problem.
37.8°. You totally have a cold.
After your body is warmed up from your bath,
you need to crawl right into your bed.
Right. Roger that.
I'm sorry.
Can you fall asleep like this?
I'll be all right. Don't you worry.
OK. Sleep tight, Ayumi.
Good night.
Good night. Sweet dreams.
Well, if she stays put, she should be all right.