So do your time leap and change this world for us.
Just make sure to time it right...
Take my power of permeation.
Been a while, little bro.
I'm leaving the rest up to you, Big Brother.
Hey, might as well stay in bed.
We already did your job and made food.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Jeez, we have rules for a reason.
You better make breakfast tomorrow, all right?
Let's dig in!
Hey, Ayumi, how old are you again, now?
I'm eight, of course.
That means we get captured around three years from now.
After I made the time leap,
I started by becoming friends with Kumagami and his group.
That way we could fight together,
like we had promised, in the future.
Kumagami was the one that found me.
That's an amazing ability you've got.
Jeez, about time you showed up.
Huh? What are you talking about?
We were best friends.
We swore that we would change the world together.
And I'm here to make sure that we do!
Stay back, don't come any closer!
What in the world are you?
Come on, you know what my ability is.
Put two and two together and take a guess.
Can it be that we met in the future?
Yeah, you got it!
Hey, we may know each other in the future,
but for now we're strangers.
Don't get all chummy on me.
Jeez, you're such a drag here, Pooh.
Pooh?
I call you Pooh after that red‐shirted bear.
No way. I'd never let someone
call me a nickname that stupid.
At that point, Kumagami had already
made a small group of ability wielders.
I followed him to their safehouse
and met with the fledgling
group as I had originally planned.
This is the one who can time‐leap. Shunsuke Otosaka.
It's been a while.
At least that's the way it's been for me, not you.
Apparently he knows us.
He recently came here from the future.
You really expect us to believe that crap?
You're Shichino.
The wielder of permeation, the
ability to pass through matter.
Unfortunately, passing through even one wall
makes you feel like you just ran a marathon.
What?
Next Medoki.
You possess powers of hypnotism.
You can make someone fall asleep,
but you also fall asleep afterwards.
Then Maedomari.
Yes.
Able to erase a memory from
someone with pinpoint accuracy.
However, for it to work, you have to touch the target.
And it takes you a long time to find that memory.
How's that?
Amazing. You're spot on.
That doesn't prove anything.
Kumagami could have told you all that.
But that would mean Kumagami is someone
we can't trust. Are you cool with that?
So, since you came from the future,
you obviously want something from us.
Yeah. Let me explain.
And so I told them about the tragic future
everyone with special powers faced,
about myself and about them,
and then about the plan that I
had made with Kumagami in the future.
There was only one path for us to take.
We need to find everyone and protect ourselves.
And so we started creating a
syndicate of ability wielders,
but in the end, it was just a gathering of children.
No matter how many times we started
over, we weren't able to protect ourselves.
What's worse, there were members that went out of control
and assaulted the lab facility to save their friends.
Damn it!
We don't have enough power to protect ourselves.
This wasn't something children
could take on in the first place.
What should we do?
We can get help from some adults.
Adults? There's no way we can trust them, and you know it.
They don't have any abilities.
How can they possibly understand what we're going through?
Some of them used to have abilities.
In fact, I know a few of them.
Don't you all think it's at least worth a shot?
Well, if you say so.
Let's try it out.
So, what will we do, exactly, Shunsuke?
Well, let me think about it for a bit.
Pooh.
Big Brother Shun, we'd like to
wish you a happy 15th birthday!
I need to time‐leap soon or I'll get caught.
Get ready for the Mega Jumbo Fortune Lottery!
Our number‐one prize is...
600 million!
Six‐hundred?
If we had that kind of money,
we could easily sway some adults.
But why stop there?
If I use my ability...
This is it. This is the only way left.
We need funding.
I'll leap back to the past and gather all sorts of
gambling information like horse‐racing and lotto.
Nice.
And after that?
We'll gather even more wielders and create
a syndicate the scientists can never touch.
So we have to follow this guy's orders again?
Come on, just give him a chance.
Well, see ya yesterday.
I just wish I didn't have to explain all this again.
The morning that I made the time leap,
I noticed something wrong when I looked in the mirror.
This ability takes a bit of vision
away from me each time I use it.
Since then, we added all sorts of comrades
and created a plan for us to gather a large sum of money.
It took many tries and many time leaps.
My vision gradually started to fail.
My ability takes in the light off of every object,
every person, everything I see,
and uses it to take me into the past.
If I went blind, I wouldn't be able
to use it again. But I knew the risk.
The research facility was one step ahead of us again.
How many times has this happened?
It's getting more frequent.
At this point, we're fighting over ability wielders.
Shunsuke, we need a place to
keep them safe, not to hide them.
Yeah. Give me a little time to think up a plan... Pooh.
How many times have I experienced this?
An environment where I can protect them.
Is there such a thing?
By the way, entrance exams are coming up for you.
Have you picked a high school yet?
Hey, now, there's an idea.
You! You are a freaking genius, you know that?
Great, now will you let me breathe?
I'm going to leap one more time, Pooh.
Why?
I created a syndicate and gained funding.
And yet I haven't been able to protect everyone.
But you can't. You know what'll happen.
Of course I do.
One more time leap and my eyesight is as good as gone,
but I have to take this chance.
You'll only get one shot, so what
are you planning to do, exactly?
Create a school.
Why a school?
I've said it many times.
Our abilities disappear once we're past adolescence.
If we build a school for them,
we can protect ability wielders
until they reach adulthood.
That way, I can protect the
potential ones like you and Ayumi.
I see, but this will truly be your last gamble.
And it will cost you your eyesight.
I know, but I'll live with it.
Of course you will. You haven't changed one bit.
Please make sure to find me
after I've gone completely blind.
Leave that to me.
I made my very last time leap.
I haven't seen light since.
From that point on, I walked
down the ultimate path in darkness.
But not alone.
For the final touch, we decided to buy
out a certain educational institution.
It was a pretty tiresome job.
But the joy everyone felt once
it was over made it all worth it.
Now, something can be made of this, right?
Yeah. You really came through on this, thank you.
But this is just the beginning.
I know that.
On that note, Pooh, I have two favors to ask of you.
Go ahead.
First order of business.
I want you to erase my existence
from you and Ayumi's memories.
Why?
If that doesn't happen, there's no way I'll
be able to move around freely from here on out.
I can no longer live in the open. Forever.
I must keep living behind the scenes.
Oh, I see.
Second.
I want you to create similar syndicates all over Japan
and build more schools that
can harbor those with abilities.
Hadn't thought of that.
Even if we can't reach them from here,
it's still our duty to protect them.
But if I do that, my face will be known all over
and it will become dangerous for me.
Well, if that's the case, how about you
hide your face with that long hair of yours?
Good idea. A little water on top would make it perfect.
Did you really just drench yourself?
Sure did.
I'm back.
Where have you been? I've been worried sick about you!
You could have tried to give us a call.
I'm sorry. I brought a friend.
Is it cool if she comes in for a bit?
This place is a mess! Hold on!
Medoki, go do it.
Where should I start?
Ayumi?
Oh, yes?
Ayumi? Who is it?
Thank you.
Maedomari.
Yes.
There, it's over.
I owe you one.
Your future should be fine from here on.
Live your lives peacefully.
I'll always love you, no matter what.
All right, shall we?
Yes, sir. ‐Sure.
And so I left,
completely vanishing from Yu and Ayumi's lives.
And that's the end.
So you created this school we've all become
a part of by time‐leaping repeatedly. Wow!
I'm sorry we didn't make it in
time to help your big brother, Nao.
No. He's well on his way to
recovery right now. It's all right.
You erased my memories of you using an ability?
Yep, that's how it all went down.
You even lost your eyesight.
I tried to leap again, but it just wasn't happening.
There is something I still have left undone.
I believe that Kumagami mentioned it to you.
A promise the two of us need to fulfill.
Ayumi. He said that we could save her.
But you can't see.
You have to make my time leap your own.
Use that ability of yours and presto.
Plunder, right? I've dreamt about it.
Taking abilities is your true power.
And it's our only chance to save Ayumi.
I never knew that.
Takajo and I knew the whole time.
Kumagami saw through your ability.
It's kind of his thing, you know.
His ability is the plunder of other abilities.
Crazy! I can't believe that kind of power is even real.
It's way too powerful.
We need to investigate how he
does it before we go in guns blazing.
Good idea.
We'll have to keep our guard up at all times.
As a result of our investigation,
we realized that you had misunderstood
the true nature of your ability.
It's not that you are merely possessing them.
The method by which you plunder
abilities is by possessing wielders.
As proof of that, everyone you've
possessed up till now has lost their powers.
You're saying that we could have
avoided a lot of crap from the get‐go.
I could have possessed the target outright?
Then everything would have been fine?
Even for ability wielders, that kind
of treatment violates human ethics.
We figured it would be better for everyone concerned
if you understood why you
shouldn’t use your ability carelessly.
Also, we were afraid that you
would have become a dangerous threat
if you kept gaining more power through plundering.
It was fortunate you didn't realize this until now.
Very impressive. I knew I liked you.
Then I can...
My ability itself should not have been lost, Yu.
Plunder that so you can leap into the past
and save our sister.
All right, you should jump to the
day that Ayumi develops her ability.
Once you get there, plunder collapse from her ASAP.
That should make it safe for her.
Afterwards, find me in the past
and fill me in on everything that's going on.
You got all that?
Ayumi, I'll save you.
All right.
Good.
Then I'm counting on you.
I'm leaving the rest to you, bro.
Don't worry, I won't mess this up.
Now go!
Ayumi!
What is today's date?
Yes, right where I need to be.
The ability is collapse.
Here we go.
Any idea what that is?
No. My guess is they can destroy anything they target.
Where's this guy?
This is our condo complex.
Can I have a minute?
What is it?
It's probably my little sister.
What’s your basis for that?
She’s absent from school with a cold.
To be at home at this time of day
means it has to be my little sister.
You're unusually sharp. It's uncharacteristic.
Well, none of us are scientists, but still...
I say we visit her.
That way we can see if she's actually
turned into the wielder of a special ability.
Wait, won't it seem a little
strange if we all show up at once?
Tomori, it should just be you and me.
That makes sense.
You're right. You're right indeed. Let's do that.
Come on, it's time to go home!
Ayucchi, get better soon, 'K?
I'm sorry for being so rowdy just then, sir!
So it was her.
Anyway, I'll get out of your hair.
Get well soon, kiddo.
Thanks for coming. I hope to see you again soon.
I'm gonna go see her off. Back in a bit.
Whoo‐hoo‐hoo!
No.
Please ask her what the nightmare was about.
It might be a clue to figuring
out what the collapse ability is.
Hey, Tomori,
if I told you that I had time‐leaped here from the future,
what would you think?
I would believe you.
If it was for Ayumi's sake,
you'd do something just like that.
I have no doubt.
Good. Awesome. That saves a lot of trouble.
In two days, Ayumi will die
when collapse goes out of control.
I used a time leap so I could come back here
and prevent that from even happening.
So that's how it is.
I'm worried about you doing this on your own,
so the student council will help you.
That's great, thanks.
You know...
Yes?
I think I may have completely misunderstood you.
After I lost Ayumi,
I became reckless and nearly went to pieces.
I fell down a dark pit,
but then you came and pulled me out.
Since you're talking about the future,
I don't recall any of this,
but if you say that's how it happened, I guess it's true.
I saw all sorts of horrible things,
but you always knew what to do.
Sure.
Thank you.
Well... you're welcome.
I guess it's time for bed again, isn't it?
No, not just yet.
Let me cast a magic spell that can cure your cold.
Sure.
How do you feel?
Pretty good. Thanks, big brother.
Ayumi's ability is no longer with her.
One more thing to do.
See ya. I'll come pick you up to go home.
You're still recovering so don't overdo it.
Right. I'll do my very best, sir.
This is the hard part. I'll need to be careful.
Good morning.
I can't believe you got ahold of those things.
And what are you supposed to be?
They decided that no matter what I did,
I wouldn't look like a middle‐school student.
So I'm disguised as a teacher.
Are you sure you shouldn't have a disguise?
Hell yeah. I want her to know it
was Ayumi's big brother that showed up.
Good idea. That totally changes how formidable you look.
Hmm. Everyone, I'm counting on you.
Right. We'll make sure to save your sister's life.
After that, we party! Yeah!
Yeah!
By the way, there isn't a magic
spell for saving someone's life.
I'm sorry.
Now, over here.
We'll go in from the back entrance.
Hey, are you a student of this school?
Uh, I'm a teacher here. Is there some kind of problem?
I don't recognize you at all.
Let's go to the faculty office.
Well, sure, I'll go. After all, I am a teacher.
I've already freakin' lost one!
At least I still have Tomori and Yusa.
Whoa. Hey, you're Yusarin, aren't you?
No, I'm totally not.
I knew it. You are her!
Everyone, Yusarin, the famous
idol, just transferred to our school!
She's prettier than on TV.
I ain't nothing like Yusarin!
So you're saying you aren't like how you act on TV?
Ah, for the love of crap.
Would a pop idol do something like this?
What should I do with this saliva?
So creepy!
Hey, this other new girl is pretty cute, too.
Maybe she's an idol like Yusarin.
They could be filming a secret show right now.
I thought Yusarin was in high school.
You damn traitor!
Don't leave me here by myself!
They were caught instantly.
What was the point of wearing disguises?
One hour left.
It's all because you showed up.
Oikawa! It's like he's completely forgotten about me.
He just looks at you all the time!
It's all your fault.
It's all your fault!
No, that's not true!
That's why I'll make you feel pain for a change!
Who are you?
Big Brother Yu?
I'm gonna have to scare you a bit.
What's happening?
The next time you try to harm my little sister,
you won't get off this easily.
Get lost before I get mad!
I was so scared!
I'm so glad you're safe.
Let's go home for today. Sound good to you?
Uh‐huh. Yeah.
I saved her. I was able to save her.
We actually did it.
I don't care if people say I have a sister complex.
I never want to lose Ayumi again.
You're already here, Kumagami? That was fast.
Hold on. You already know about me?
That's right, Pooh.
That makes it easy.
Come with me, you and your little sister.
Sure thing. Take us to him.
To our big brother.