What is up with me? Why can't I just pick one?!
All right, I'll be going now, Ayumi.
Oh, hey, good morning.
Oh, right. Good morning.
Let's get going.
Over here.
We could get crepes, if you like.
Why are we going so early? The gig is tonight.
I wanna buy some of the band merch.
You can't do that after it's over?
Sure, but most of the popular stuff will be gone by then.
Guess that's how it goes.
I pegged you as a pretty hardcore fan girl.
I can't believe you didn't wanna meet Sala yesterday.
I don't have any desire to buy
t‐shirts, hoodies, or stuff like that.
I want... their functional and
tricked‐out smartphone case.
It's got an internal battery and a
high‐quality linear PCM recorder.
OK, I get it. It sounds awesome.
But you don't want one.
If I did, we'd have a matching pair. You cool with that?
Oh, you're right.
Please make sure to not buy one.
Well, that was blunt. I don't know how to take it.
The line is huge.
Then we shouldn't waste time.
The line's over here!
Come on, let's go get in line.
But I'm not buying anything.
But you're still here with me.
I don't want to stand there with
no one to talk to. That's boring.
When we first met, I was sure she hated me.
But now... inviting me to gigs,
hanging out together.
I hope they don't sell out.
Why are we getting all friendly?
What's the matter?
Nothing. I was impressed by the line.
Well, yeah, they're loved the world over.
This venue is way too small for a band of their caliber.
She really is an amazing person.
I got my case!
Look, isn't it epic? Check out the cool logo on the back.
Zhiend is such a figurative art.
Uh... yeah, that's for sure. It's awesome.
I know, right?
In the end, you are a fan girl.
It's so cool!
It's starting.
Lying before me.
Scene painted in green.
I was never found.
And I played hide and seek.
There remains a little scar.
On your face still facing down
to the ground.
You hold yourself.
And crouch like you've been wounded.
I adored the days When we just
want more things with no means.
Oh I adored when you were always just there for me
by my side.
What's this strange feeling I'm getting?
Next up, we have a special world première,
a song written just for you, Japan!
"Trigger"!
Come now heading to the oblivion.
To the darkness sink me.
Future is lonely as it seems to be.
And I am reaching from there.
I know this song... but this is my first time hearing it!
My mind is clear now
I feel like I can do anything.
When I want to do it, yeah.
I feel I'm notorious.
Do you know what you can handle?
Do you know me?
Spinning round and around going back and forth.
Will be here as an angel that's fallen deep.
See, there's the dark side waiting for me.
Never end forever.
Out on the rim no need to breathe...
What's the matter, Big Brother? You scared me!
I'm sorry.
I guess Zhiend's new song really got to me.
They're a pretty amazing band.
Their songs are just so powerful.
They stick, no matter what happens.
What about you?
How‐Low‐Hello was How‐Low‐Hello. Awesome as always.
It is time for dinner in D Block.
Oh, perfect timing. I'm starving!
It's this old man again.
Why is he here all the time?
Nothing beats classical.
There is no stagnation, like a mathematical formula.
That girl, is she your sister?
Yeah.
I see. I pity you, kid.
So there's a researcher that feels that way towards us?
Why are you here every day?
To get away for a bit.
As a researcher, my hypotheses
are often seen as extraordinary.
I come to lose myself in thought.
I see.
Are you familiar with the Ptolemaic theory, young man?
Well, I've heard of it, at least.
It's an extraordinary view by today's standards,
but back then it was the normal view.
But reality was different.
What do you think happened to the
first person with a different view?
Dunno.
He was treated as a nonconformist
and was shunned by every one of his peers.
Just like I am now.
I see.
All right, we're gonna have curry today!
Yeah. Chockfull of chemicals that boost abilities again.
It'll taste like crappy medicine.
Yeah, maybe, but I still think its tastiness will
make people happy and forget about all that stuff.
I wish Big Brother Shun was here, too.
It would be great to eat with him.
His unusual ability made him stand out way too much.
He just couldn't.
What was his ability again?
Traveling through time, or time leap.
That is so amazing!
They decided his power was way too
strong so they're keeping him imprisoned.
Poor Big Brother Shun.
Yeah, you're right.
So we shouldn't talk about this ever again, understand?
Thank you for the food!
Tastes like medicine as usual.
They think that my ability is merely
taking over someone's body for five seconds,
but there's more to it.
If they'd caught on to what my true ability is,
I'm sure they'd have taken my freedom away from me,
just like my big brother.
But if I keep getting tested like this,
they're bound to find out eventually.
Been a while. Stay still and quiet.
Kumagami, did something happen?
I've finally tracked down someone with telepathy.
What? Are you for real?
Yeah.
They can send and receive.
Amazing.
But they've already been caught, right?
Exactly.
First, you need to take over the
guy with the pompadour to your right.
I found him. His ability is pulverize,
but his power is limited.
Got it.
Good one.
Was that part of the trick?
Next is the location of the one with telepathy. Take this.
Just make sure to time it right.
You're the only hope we have now, understand?
If you fail, they will dispose of you,
and then they'll come for us.
Yeah. I know that.
Oh, man, is Kumagami really wasting
his time with that idiot right now?
Oh, you jealous, Shichino?
You know that's not it.
We've been waiting for this moment for a long time.
A situation like this is about the only thing
that will make his little brother serious.
No, man, he's just overly attached to his little sister.
He cares for his siblings. All we can do now is trust him.
I just wonder what our odds are of
actually winning this little gamble.
If it ain't 100%, I want no part of it.
There can't be any mistakes.
Does that mean you're actually gonna
use your power to contribute to us somehow?
We've done our part and managed to find
someone with telepathy for the team, you know.
Like I've told you, I'm just waiting
for the perfect moment, OK?
So, it's never gonna happen then?
You piss me off.
Less chitchat, more eating.
Damn it. I hope this world changes.
I can't take it.
It's time now. Pack up.
Well, so much for smelling the air outside.
Excuse me.
Hey, you. Did you accept something from someone?
Not a thing.
Then you're fine.
I don't get it.
Why do they treat him differently?
He do something bad?
He's not as powerful as big brother,
but he has an ability that is pretty amazing.
All the plans for saving our brother are in place.
The only question now is when to go through with it.
That ends today's program.
All test subjects other than those called
over must return to their rooms immediately.
Cool. Guess we'll go back.
Oh, I nearly forgot. They called me over!
They what? Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
Go back, kid.
Wait!
This is absurd. My sister doesn't have abilities.
Why is she being called over?
Big Brother Yu!
Ayumi! An earthquake?
We have shut D Block down.
Please remain where you are until you receive...
What the hell's going on?
I repeat. We have shut...
I have a really bad feeling about this.
Come on, let me outta here! Hey!
Damn it!
It's you. What just happened?
Do you know where Ayumi is?
Your sister's dormant power was
prematurely forced into the open.
Her ability was collapse.
They shut D Block down because half of
it caved in when her ability was set free.
Is she OK?
She's fine.
But due to the unstable nature of her power,
they have her restrained at the moment.
Just like my big brother.
No. After they dissect her, they’ll get rid of her body.
You don't have time to stand here!
You can save her if you use the
true ability you've been hiding.
Plunder: The most powerful of abilities.
How do you know?
You don't have time for me to explain.
He's right. Just go.
All right.
And now they will dispose of me as well.
I'm going up against someone with telepathy.
Gotta be mindless, mindless, mindless!
Who is it?
That was in my head?
It's gotta be him, the telepath.
What do you want with me?
I gotta see his face.
What about my face?
It's fine. I'm done here already.
What do you mean?
Hey, stop!
Excuse me, sir.
So, uh, I don't need to erase this guy's memory, do I?
I hope that's the case...
What's going on?
Let me out! Let me out!
Shutting down B Block!
I repeat: There is an emergency situation in D Block.
All employees arrange yourselves according...
Damn it! What's going on out there?
I don't care who it is, just tell me!
That voice. I can figure out the direction, too.
Big Brother, can you hear me? It's Yu!
Yu? You've taken that kind of power now?
If they find out, you're done for.
I didn't have a choice. They're about to dissect Ayumi!
Ayumi! What's she have?
An ability strong enough to destroy this place.
Her too, huh?
I'll save you, Big Brother,
so do your time leap and change this world for us.
How the hell are you gonna pull that off?
Damn, I just need light in my eyes.
What?
What's wrong?
Shichino.
Damn it.
Why do I have to do this for
a sister‐complex guy like you?
What the hell...
No time to explain!
Take my power of permeation.
You sure?
I'm telling you, we don't have any time left.
I understand.
Don't make me regret this, OK?
I'm sorry, but I know my brother will change this world!
What the crap. What's going on here?
I'm so tired!
What's happening?
I got Shichino's ability too.
I'll be right there. Hold on!
Finally!
Wish I could stay, Yu.
But I really don't have any time to waste.
I know. I'm leaving the rest up to you, Big Brother.
Yeah. For the future.
No, for every one of us.
I'm gonna change the world!
Kill him!
What is it with you and screaming?
Where are we?
A hospital. You collapsed during Zhiend's gig.
Do you remember that?
That's right.
Ayumi's gone.
Did you have a bad dream or something?
Dream?
Was what I saw really a dream?
No.
In the past, Ayumi had said that she felt
like we had one more member in our family.
It's best if you don't get up yet.
I think I might have a big brother.
In fact, I'm almost sure of it.
What?
Oh. So you remember now.
Who are you?
I find people with special abilities.
Does this help at all?
Water boy!
You're pretty handsome when you're dry.
You were there, too, in my dream.
But this is the first time you've seen me like this.
Kumagami, you know all about my brother, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
Please, tell me everything!
Calm down. That's what I came here to do.
Come with me quietly,
and I swear all the questions you have will be answered.
After that, you'll rescue that sister of yours.
What did you say?
You're going to save your sister's life, simple as that,
Yu Otosaka.
But how can I save someone who's already dead?!
Remember your brother?
If you do, then you already
know what Shunsuke's ability is.
Understood.
Just to clarify here, you mean the Shunsuke?
That's right.
Wait, you're kidding me. You're his little brother?
But you look nothing alike.
Does that really matter?
So, uh, can I go see him as well?
It's been a hot minute.
How do you know him?
He's the one that guided my path,
after my big brother became the way he is.
I met the one person I could truly trust,
and that's how I'm here now.
So she was talking about Shunsuke.
That's fine. Follow me.
Thank you very much.
We have to walk from here.
This is so cool!
Money is no object here.
What is this?
It's kind of an ability research center.
Didn't that start this mess in the first place?
Not so.
Stop yapping and follow me.
Incredible! Can I record this?
No, of course not.
Nuts!
Overkill much?
This is the last safe place we have.
So close. He's so close to me.
Been a while, little bro.
I brought him.
Yeah, thank you.
That's him?
For real?
He still hasn't remembered?
It seems like he still hasn't regained
all the memories that Maedomari erased.
I see.
Erased memories? What do you mean?
That voice must be Nao. It's been a while, hasn't it?
Yes. I still walk down the path you set for me.
It really changed my life.
You've been helping out quite a bit.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you very much.
What the...?
How about you, little bro?
You just gonna stand there and gawk?
This is our melodramatic reunion.
At least give me a hug.
No, thanks.
Still confused.
Lots of questions.
Well, that's a bit lonely.
Though I'm probably reaping what I've sown.
Guess I should tell the whole story.
Right, Pooh?
Yeah.
Pooh?!
Relax.
The story of my time leap's going
to take quite some time to tell.
I'm in for the long haul.
Just what is he going to tell us?