(static crackling)
(reverberating thudding)
- [Phil] All right,
let's get underway
with the hyperdrive checklist.
- [Mission Control] I
have the checklist ready.
- [Phil] Okay.
- [Mission Control] Uh, lights?
- [Phil] Are okay.
- [Mission Control]
Breaker check.
- [Phil] Breaker one is
okay, breaker two okay,
and breaker number three okay.
- [Mission Control]
Ion drive engine check.
- [Phil] All righty, uh,
engines one and two okay.
(thrusters whooshing)
- [Mission Control]
Clearance from mothership.
- [Phil] Mothership, mothership,
please confirm
permission to depart.
- [Mission Control] Roger,
permission from mothership
for clearance
okayed at this time.
Proceed to standby.
(screen crackling)
- [Phil] The signal
flare check is completed.
- [Mission Control] Roger.
- [Sevarest] Let's go, Phil.
- Okay.
- [Mission Control] This is an
order from John's mothership.
Something is approaching
rapidly from the north.
Please check out.
- [Phil] Roger.
Sevarest, is some kind of test
taking place near location 7402?
Object 942 miles
away at 10 o'clock.
- Roger.
- [Phil] It seems to be
changing moment by moment.
- Where is it now?
Oh, wait, I see it.
Uh, something's wrong.
(alarm blaring)
It's, uh,
it's coming right toward us.
- [Phil] Let's get outta here!
(object whooshing)
(explosion booming)
- [Mission Control]
637, what's wrong?
(Sevarest gagging)
Having trouble calling, uh,
come in, 637, what's
wrong up there?
(explosion booming)
637, what's wrong up there?
(energetic electronic music)
- [Mission Director] This
is Space Station L-3,
Constellation Control.
Search Ship Constellation
will lift off
in 20 minutes and counting.
All final systems
checks completed.
19:45 and counting.
All personnel, please
leave the launcher.
All personnel, leave the
launcher immediately.
(bay doors rumbling)
Ship moving to ignition status.
Five minutes and counting.
10 seconds and counting.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero.
Ignition.
(engines whooshing)
(waves crashing)
(birds squawking)
- [Radio Host] Today on this
16th anniversary, we remember
the extraterrestrial object
which landed on Graviton City,
killing its population
of six million
and reducing it to
rubble in an instant.
The impact burned
out all vegetation
over a radius of 60 kilometers
and the pillar of smoke
could be seen 200
kilometers away.
A new Graviton City has grown
in the crater left by the impact
and remaining wreckage
of the meteor itself
is incorporated
into what has become
our Military Command Center,
which dominates the downtown
skyline of our great city.
It is also appropriate that
the rebuilt Graviton City,
a showcase of modern
technological achievement,
has been chosen as the center
to celebrate the launch
of the Constellation probe
(A-ko groaning)
from Space Station
L-3, a space project
specifically designed to
identify any threats similar
to the one that
struck 16 years ago
and to defuse it before
it can cause a repetition
of the devastation that
engulfed Graviton City then.
And now to more everyday things.
It's a beautiful day
here in Graviton City,
so all you kids on your
first day back at school
will have to give up the idea
of going for that
swim in the lake
and get down to some
serious work instead.
And the kids transferring
to new schools today,
let's hope you're happy,
make lots of new friends,
and get on well with
your new teachers.
Okay, the time's just
coming up to 8:15!
(alarm ringing)
- Ah, I'm late for school!
First day and late!
Oh!
(A-ko grunting)
(A-ko slurping)
(objects thudding)
(doorbell ringing)
- A-ko, hey, hurry
up, you're late!
(window rattling)
Hey, hurry up, A-ko!
You know what time it is?
- Hi, yeah, I know!
I'm coming now, I'll
be right with ya!
Sorry I'm late!
- I swear you'd sleep
right through it
if another meteor
landed in town!
(both laughing)
(upbeat electronic music)
A-ko, will they put us together
in the same class, do you think?
- I expect they will because
they know we're friends.
- Yeah, well, they'd better
or I'll yell the place down!
- What?
- I only came to Graviton
High because you did!
(school bell chiming)
- Oh, God, the
time, hang on tight!
(C-ko yelping)
I still don't think
we'll make it in time
and that won't make a
very good impression!
There it is!
We'll take a shortcut, C-ko!
- If you say so!
(C-ko yelping)
(table crashing)
- Huh?
(air whooshing)
(C-ko shuddering)
- Ah!
- Enjoy your meal!
(air whooshing)
(pensive music)
(stranger breathing out)
- What a terrible dump.
(air whooshing)
(air whistling)
Huh?
- [A-Ko] Excuse me!
Excuse me!
(wall crashing)
(stranger groaning)
(air whooshing)
(school bell chiming)
- [Miss Ayumi] Okay,
girls, a nice big welcome
for two new students
joining us this semester.
Like to introduce yourselves?
- Well, my name is A-ko and
I'm really happy to be here!
- Hi, everyone, it'll be great,
and when I say great I mean
great, making new friends here!
- That's very nice,
only what's your name?
- I'm called C-ko, don't
you think that's cute?
Do you think it suits me?
I do, it kinda expresses
my personality.
And I must say,
you're pretty as well!
The prettiest schoolteacher
- Oh jeez!
- [C-ko] I've met! (giggling)
- [A-Ko] C-ko, shut up!
- [Miss Ayumi] Thank you.
(C-ko giggling)
- [A-Ko] C-ko, shut up,
you're embarrassing me!
- [C-Ko] I don't care, let
it all hang out, I say!
I'm gonna love this
school, I know it!
It's so much fun! (giggling)
- [Miss Ayumi] There
there, dear, I think
that's quite enough.
- Oh, what a mouth I've got!
- C-ko!
- Now, where will you sit?
- [B-Ko] Excuse me, Miss.
- I'm getting a bit
impatient, what do you want?
- If they sit near me,
I might show them the ropes
the first couple of days.
- That's a good idea.
So, C-ko, you sit
on B-ko's right side
while A-ko takes the
place next to the window.
- Uh-uh, uh-uh, I wanna
sit by the window!
- Stop complaining, will ya?
Miss, let her sit
where she wants.
- Well, if you think
that'll settle her down.
I don't care as
long as you don't.
- Hurray, I get to
sit near the window!
And as long as
everybody's happy,
then that's all that counts!
(students whispering)
(students giggling)
Great!
- Thanks for offering to help.
So ignore me.
- [Miss Ayumi] Quiet,
everyone, and let's begin.
- [Students] Shh!
- C-ko, face the front and
pay attention, would you?
- [C-Ko] I'm bored!
- Well, if I can
persuade you to listen,
you might be less bored.
- Ah!
I'm sorry, teacher, I
promise I'll concentrate.
This place looks great.
(students laughing)
- [Girl] Over here, over here!
- Bring it forth towards me!
A bit further, line
it up with this one.
(machine clanking)
(rockets whooshing)
- Wow!
- Hey, can I fly as well?
I'd like to try a rocket too!
Ooh!
(blow thudding)
(C-ko groaning)
You hit me!
- And I'll probably do it again
if you don't pay a
bit of attention!
(C-ko whimpering)
(C-ko wailing)
Stop, stop it!
Stop crying, C-ko, please!
Oh, there's a good girl,
I didn't hurt you, did I?
Oh God, what have I done?
You won't report this to
the head teacher, will you?
(school bell chiming)
- [C-Ko] Surprise!
- That for me?
- Mm, just something I ran up
out of my Cordon Bleu
lunch book, try it!
- Mm, well, uh, remember
the last lunch you made?
- Oh, that was a long time ago.
Come on, mouthwatering, hm?
- Uh, gee, thanks.
- Doesn't it look delicious?
(playful music)
(A-ko groaning)
(A-ko gagging)
That's pretty
terrific, ain't it?
What about that?
(A-ko groaning)
Oh!
Hey, you've gone all
blue in the face, A-ko!
What's the matter with her,
don't she appreciate
home cooking?
All anyone'll eat these
days is junk food.
(C-ko yelping)
Help, help, fire, fire!
(C-ko groaning)
(C-ko screaming)
I'm gonna blow up!
What did I put in it?
I don't wanna die!
I've poisoned us both!
(C-ko screaming)
I didn't mean it, I
swear it was an accident!
(Mari chuckling)
Oh, everything's going black!
(B-ko chuckling)
My life's flashing
before my eyes!
Tell them I died with my
cook's hat and apron on!
(C-ko yelping)
(B-ko chuckling)
(school bell chiming)
- Oh, there's the bell!
Time for afternoon class!
- When the poet says,
\"O, to substantialize
\"this suppositious
ontological quiddity,\"
he is expressing something
which I think you'll agree
is central to most
people's lives.
At the same time,
what does it tell us
about his absurdist
views of human existence?
A good question!
Then his obsession with
ecumenical transcendentalism
is revealing.
From here, it is but short--
- Great!
- Imaginative leap--
- Laid back after that
Cordon Bleu lunch of yours!
No surprise we're out there
with placards around our necks
described as a pair of
hostile, disruptive students
with no regard for the school.
That's some reputation!
Next time, you keep your
lunchbox to yourself.
(C-ko wailing)
- I thought we were good friends
so I wanted to give you
something! (wailing)
- For Pete's sake,
stop blubbing,
we'll get sent
home if you don't!
- Shut up, will you?
I've had just about
enough for one day,
in fact, I've had enough
to last me a lifetime!
I won't put up with this
kind of thing in my class!
(C-ko wailing)
C-ko, stop crying!
How old are you anyway?
A-ko, do something,
make her stop!
- Is the substance really
a phallic illusion?
- Oh, what an
interesting question!
We might get the answer
if you read a few lines.
- Right.
\"O, to substantialize this--\"
- So, let's put all this
behind us and do some work now.
- But if A-ko had
been a bit more--
- So it was all your fault!
Why are you making C-ko cry?
No more crying now,
wipe those tears away.
- You'll stay behind
when school's over
and clean the classroom up.
(A-ko groaning)
Oh?
B-ko, why have you
stopped reading?
- It's a short poem.
You don't keep us
busy, do you, Miss?
- What?
But you won't go complaining
to the headmaster, eh?
Oh, come on, girls, let's
see how hard we can work
for the rest of today's lesson!
(school bell chiming)
Ah, what a shame,
time to go home.
- Having really--
- So the lock
gets stuck on my bicycle.
- A-ko, look, I'm terribly
sorry you're being punished,
I know it's my fault, I'll
never let it happen anymore.
- Forget it, I've had
school detentions before.
You go home, this
could take a while.
- No way do I go alone,
I'll wait for you!
- There's lots to do, it
could take me quite a time.
- Still, I'll wait
for you outside, A-ko!
- Okay, if you like.
I'll get this done
as quick as I can,
then I'll pick you up
at the school gate.
- [C-Ko] Right, see you there!
- Yeah.
- I think we're going out.
- Shh!
- Wait 'til tomorrow!
- Oh, that.
- Oh, I'd love to, yeah!
- Come on!
- You think so?
(A-ko grunting)
(desk thudding)
- Let's go.
- Bye, see you tomorrow!
- See you tomorrow!
- Don't forget take this!
- Okay!
- [Student] Do you wanna
walk this way with me?
- Okay, cool, great!
- Are you gonna
pick me up in the morning?
- Yeah, do you want my number?
- No, my mom doesn't--
- Oh, that's too bad!
- See you tomorrow!
- C-ko!
- [C-ko] Hm?
- A-ko's still
working and she says
would you go see her
behind the gym block?
- Huh, really?
- And pink!
- What's she doing there?
- You're right!
I thought she had to
clean the classroom?
- [Asa] I don't know, maybe
she's emptying the trash there.
- Yeah, right, I'll
go and help her out!
That's the least I can do!
- Sound off!
- Three, four!
- Change count!
(Asa chuckling)
- [Runners] One,
two, three, four!
One two!
- Three four!
* La la la la
* La la la la la la
(knuckles cracking)
- [A-Ko] Whee!
(water splashing)
Whee!
* La la la la la la
- Asa, I don't
see A-ko anywhere!
- Just go a little
further along.
(C-ko yelping)
(ominous dramatic music)
(knuckles cracking)
- Hm?
(Mari chuckling)
Hi, hi, big boy!
- What?
I ain't no boy just
because I shave every day!
You gotta be initiated,
which you might find painful.
- Scissors, yeah!
Scissors, scissors cut paper!
- Huh?
(C-ko giggling)
- [C-Ko] Go again!
One, two, three!
(Mari growling)
Paper!
Paper wraps rock!
- Huh, what?
(C-ko giggling)
Huh?
- I won again! (giggling)
You aren't very good!
Let's do it again,
one, two, three!
(Mari yelling)
Aww, don't be a sore loser!
(birds chirping)
- [B-ko Voiceover] I got to
have that girl for myself
and I know how to get her.
First, I get A-ko
out of the way,
then I tell Mari
to frighten her.
(blows tapping)
I come to her rescue.
She'll fall in my lap
and A-ko's history!
- Ha!
(B-ko chuckling)
(Mari growling)
- Come on, what'll we play now?
(Asa gasping)
- Mari, calm down, wait
for B-ko to get here!
(gasping) Remember?
- Hi-yah!
Ee-yah!
(C-ko screaming)
- Mari, can't you
do anything right?
(C-ko screaming)
- C-ko!
(energetic electronic music)
(Asa screaming)
Hey!
(A-ko grunting)
(Mari growling)
(B-ko panting)
- It isn't too late as long
as A-ko isn't there yet.
(tires screeching)
(A-ko grunting)
(air whooshing)
- And now say your prayers!
(C-ko shuddering)
- What?
(Mari shrieking)
Oh?
(Mari grunting)
Oh, A-ko!
- C-ko, are you okay?
- [C-Ko] Okay, A-ko!
(Mari grunting)
- What a bully!
- Crossed Fist of the
late Akuki School.
(Mari growling)
(Mari yelling)
(shirt crashing)
(magical chiming)
(wall crashing)
(Mari screaming)
- Hey, you're terrific!
(A-ko laughing)
We showed 'em, didn't we?
- A minute more and
you'd have been hurt.
- [C-Ko] Mm-mm!
- [A-Ko] Had enough
excitement for one day?
- [C-Ko] Yeah, let's go home.
- Where are they?
Perhaps they took her away.
I'll find her.
(B-ko gasping)
(air whistling)
(stranger laughing)
(calm rhythmic music)
(water splashing)
* Looking in your eyes
* How I hope that you will
- [B-Ko Voiceover] C-ko.
God, she's beautiful!
My heart's been racing ever
since I laid eyes on her.
She's got such a great laugh,
and even when she
cries she's cute!
Her eyes, the way she moves!
C-ko, you've gotta be my friend!
(air whooshing)
So I've got to get A-ko out
of the way, that's for sure.
But how?
Even Mari was no match for her.
Then I'll take her on myself!
I'll beat her, even if I have
to reveal my true powers.
* To be next to you
* Shine your light on me
* Nothing else will do
* Deep inside my heart
* I believe that
you and I could be *
* Friends forever more
* Through eternity
- I could swear I've met
A-ko, I remember her.
I'll have what I want,
no matter what it costs!
(scope whirring)
(stranger sighing)
- Why assign me to this beat?
Hm.
(scope whirring)
(stranger chomping)
(air whooshing)
(air whistling)
(stranger yelping)
(stranger crashing)
- [A-Ko] Sorry!
- [C-Ko] Wouldn't it
make things simpler
if you got 10 minutes earlier?
(energetic music)
(tires screeching)
(B-ko moaning)
- Huh?
C-ko!
(air whooshing)
Huh?
- I thought I told you to
clean the room, not destroy it!
Look at it!
Desks smashed to
pieces, chairs in bits!
It looks as though a
typhoon has hit it!
Or some creature with the
strength of a superhuman!
(B-ko yelping)
You're going to repair
each and every piece
of furniture in the
place, no get on with it!
(hammer clanking)
(A-ko yelping)
- (yawning) Hungry!
- [C-ko] A-ko, A-ko!
- C-ko?
Is that you, C-ko?
- [C-Ko] Lunch time!
(A-ko yelping)
Hee!
(A-ko crashing)
Oh, you're sick?
- [A-ko] No, not yet at least.
- Well then, if you feel ill,
I suppose you shouldn't eat.
(sniffling) Not if you're sick.
Even so, it's a shame, my food
going to waste (sniffling).
Hey, I'll tell you what,
I got a terrific idea!
School's out for the
day so let's go downtown
and find a little adventure!
- Yeah.
- Okay?
- Yeah, anything!
- Great, that's great!
- Anything at all!
- That will soon set you
on your feet again!
- Only no lunch!
- [C-ko] Great, terrific!
We could take a look
at the Command Center
and even end up
going to a movie!
- [B-ko] Follow them.
(playful upbeat music)
* Your imagination is
all you really need *
* When you start believing
* Love is just a kiss away
* Life is what you make it
* There's no guarantee
* It's you who has the power
- Be sure to have
a nice day now!
* And love is just
a dance away *
* When you start believing
* You can do anything
* Let the magic fill you
* Take you above
the highest star *
* Dance away
* Your sorrow
- Wow!
Oh, gee!
(footsteps tapping)
- Shit!
(can clanking)
I ain't doin' his
dirty work no more!
Uh...
(metallic whooshing)
No!
(footsteps clanking)
It's, it's
the Colonel!
(man yelping)
(A-ko yelping)
Keep away!
(man screaming)
(A-ko screaming)
(C-ko screaming)
* When the world around you
- Ah, great film, wasn't it?
- Mm!
I'm glad that you're better,
I got real worried
at lunch time.
- Do you mean to say
you were really worried?
That's a surprise!
You normally only get time to
worry about yourself, C-ko.
- That wasn't a nice thing
to say to a friend like me.
- Even though it's true?
- [Announcer] We interrupt
our scheduled program
for a newsflash.
Constellation Control has
just issued a statement--
- Okay, I forgive you,
- That all signal to the--
- Let's go!
- Science Academy's unmanned
deep space probe ceased
abruptly a few minutes ago.
Constellation, which departed
from Space Station L-3
last week, was in the
neighborhood of Iapetus
and was due to pass by Jupiter
before leaving the solar system.
A spokesman for Constellation
Control attributes
the communication loss to
a transmission failure.
(A-ko and C-ko laughing)
- A-ko, next time
we've got time off
I wanna go up the Seaside
Building and take a look
at the planets and stars
in their planetarium.
- Yes, all right, if you like.
* You might make
all your dreams *
- A-ko, do you mind if I
tell you how much I love you?
- I love you too, even
if you drive me insane.
Oh, my toe!
(A-ko groaning)
(cable creaking)
* Dancing into the light
(A-ko groaning)
(C-ko laughing)
(cable snapping)
(air whooshing)
(A-ko gasping)
- C-ko!
(beam crashing)
(C-ko yelping)
- Wow, that's amazing!
- Will you get a look at that?
- God, she must be strong!
- Are you hurt?
- Hey, that cable wasn't
supposed to break,
I wonder what happened!
Gee, what's keeping it up?
Can't be what I
think I'm seeing.
(crowd applauding)
- Wow!
- It's Superman!
- [Man] That's ain't
a man, she's a girl!
- Maybe, but this is some girl!
- Some kinda stunt girl!
- Hey, I'm not!
- [Woman] Well, it
sure is a mean stunt!
- [Boy] Can I have
your autograph?
- [Woman] What time's
the next performance?
I missed it this time around!
- [Girl] She's terrific!
- She's amazing!
- Did you see that?
- My arm, it's killing me!
(air rumbling)
- [Captain] Do you have a
status report on the collision?
- [First Officer] An
unidentified metal object
obstructed our passage
through hyperspace.
- [Captain] Damage report?
- [First Officer] A
small crack is visible
in the outer skin of section 21.
- [Captain] Initiate repairs.
(console beeping)
- [First Officer] Captain,
a signal from planet Earth.
- [Captain] One of our
operatives, put it through.
- [D] This is Operative
DC138621-S113, code name D.
- [Captain] Go ahead.
- Captain, I, ah, Captain,
I believe our long search
through the universe is over
and I have found the person
we're looking for at last.
- Oh, really?
You found her?
- [D] I believe so.
- [Captain] You're not certain?
- I cannot confirm with
complete 100% certainty,
but I estimate a
probability of 80%
at this moment in Earth time.
- Hm, report again
when it's 100%
- Right!
(console beeping)
(footsteps tapping)
- [Captain Voiceover] So
we've found her at last.
(dog barking)
(curtain rustling)
(film reel clicking)
(gentle music)
(door creaking)
- Huh?
- [Computer] The
background information disk
you requested is beside you.
- Thank you.
(machine whirring)
Huh?
Of course, that was it!
(B-ko laughing)
That was where our paths
first crossed each other.
(alarm ringing)
(A-ko grunting)
(muffled alarm ringing)
(doorbell ringing)
(A-ko yelping)
(objects clattering)
- [C-ko] Huh?
(footsteps thundering)
- [A-ko] Hi, C-ko!
(A-ko yelling)
(A-ko panting)
(air whooshing)
(D groaning)
- Let's see here.
The certainty
factor's gone up, 85%
(air whooshing)
(D screaming)
- Did we smash into someone?
- No, straight through him!
(energetic music)
(air whooshing)
(air whistling)
(A-ko gasping)
- I've been waiting
for you, A-ko.
- Well, that was
friendly of you, B-ko.
- You and me have got
some outstanding business
from a long time ago.
- What business are you
talking about, B-ko?
We two only just met!
- We didn't just
meet, you and I began
at the same kindergarten,
and C-ko was there too.
- [C-Ko] Huh?
- We all started at
the same kindergarten?
- I can't believe I didn't
recognize you at once.
You haven't changed
at all, you're still
the same self-righteous
little bitch you were then.
(air whooshing)
I remember the day
everything changed,
the day the wolf
escaped from the zoo
and almost killed C-ko.
(gentle chiming music)
You saved her, and
from that moment
C-ko was never the same again.
She'd been my friend,
but not anymore!
After that, you two
were always together
and you seemed to have so much
fun, it made me really mad.
Even when you had fights it
didn't stop you being friends,
and you still are!
A-ko, you haven't forgotten
the girl who swore
she'd get even with you for
taking C-ko away from her?
- What? Afraid so!
And I've got a
pretty good memory.
- [B-ko] Who challenged you?
- Sorry, but I don't remember.
Anymore clues?
- [B-ko] A fight to the finish?
(A-ko groaning)
- [A-ko] Yeah!
- A-ko?
- Yeah, now it's all come back!
- [C-ko] Oh, who was it, A-ko?
- Her piggy eyes, basin
haircut, and dumpy legs,
and she had that nasty superior
expression I used to detest!
- [C-ko] Oh!
- [A-ko] She thought
she could do anything
because her daddy was rich,
and she used to pick
on you all the time!
She used to put spiders
and frogs down your back.
- [C-ko] Yes, I remember!
But you saved me
from her every day!
- And then at last she said
she was going to fight me,
a fight to the finish she said,
but that was the very
day we moved house,
and so it never happened.
Her name was, wasn't
it something like,
I think it was,
Blinko, Burko, or--
- I made such a big
impression on you
you don't even remember my name.
Hmph!
- You!
- I was that girl
and my name's B-ko!
- B-ko, is it you?
It is you!
Yuck!
- I challenged you
to a fight, A-ko,
and you ran away like the
little coward you were!
I challenge you again, winner
take all and C-ko is all!
(dramatic clanging)
- (giggling) Oh, come
on, you're crazy!
She can't really mean she
wants to fight me again now!
- And anyway, I'm
not up for grabs!
- Well, I guess
it's time for class,
so I'll pass your
offer up, thanks.
- Wait a minute, you
don't rush me off!
I get what I want and
what I want is a fight!
- [A-ko] Cut it out, B-ko,
that was 10 years ago!
And you can't fight for C-ko
as though she's some
sort of a prize.
- Yes I can, yes
I can, yes I can!
We'll call it our
own Super Bowl.
(B-ko grunting)
(tense electronic music)
One last thing, just
to make the fight fair
I want you to meet someone.
(power suit whirring)
(giggling) My ally.
This is a power suit
I invented and built
as I know how strong
you were as a kid
and I'm sure you've
added a whole new battery
of fighting skills
in the meantime.
- [Ena] B-ko, are you really
sure this is a good idea?
- Shut up, Ena!
- [Ena] Sorry.
- Is this what you
call a fair fight?
- I don't!
- [Ena] It may not be fair,
but that's the way it is.
So why don't you give
in now so that I don't
have you on my conscience
for the rest of my life!
Please?
- Ena, kill.
(footsteps booming)
(B-ko chuckling)
(blow crashing)
(Ena screaming)
- Gosh, A-ko, the
power suit seems
to have lost some of its power!
(school bell chiming)
- Oh, gee, there's
the bell, hurry!
- [C-ko] We're going
to be late again!
- [A-ko] What'll
we tell Miss Ayumi?
- She beat me again!
I can't take it, I can't!
(welder crackling)
- [B-ko Voiceover] I must
have C-ko as my friend.
Tomorrow, tomorrow'll
be the day.
(B-ko chuckling)
And as for you, A-ko,
tomorrow's your last day!
(B-ko laughing)
(A-ko breathing heavily)
(A-ko sneezing)
(A-ko screaming)
(air whooshing)
- Gotta get that identification
percentage factor up.
I'll get it to 100%
for sure today.
(bodies crashing)
(D screaming)
(energetic music)
(D crashing)
- [A-Ko] Sorry!
- Hey, wasn't he the same man
we almost killed yesterday?
- Well, he seems
to have survived!
Ah!
B-ko!
- Well well, so A-ko,
you didn't have the
sense to stay home.
- [A-Ko] I don't
give in to bullies!
I came to school to study!
- Oh, aren't we a
goody two-shoes!
Anyway, as you did come,
you deserve a nice welcome.
All right, let's have
her surprise now!
(grim dramatic music)
(machine whirring)
- Oh, a customized convertible!
Boy, isn't it great?
- [A-ko] Oh!
- (chuckling) Wait 'til I
demonstrate what it can do.
(machine whirring)
(electricity crackling)
(console whirring)
(robot stomping)
- [C-ko] Wow, it's cool!
- Thank you, C-ko,
it did take me
most of last night to build it.
The MAX-5000.
Standard features include:
the MAX Arm Crush,
these drills made
of nigninium alloy
go through five-meter thick
steel plates in 2.4 seconds;
the MAX Bomber Saw,
razor-sharp extending shredders
designed to reduce evidence
to absolute deniability;
the MAX Beam, this reaches
1,000 degrees centigrade
and vaporizes any
physical body instantly;
the Multiple MAX Facility,
a helix of holograms
which throws the enemy
into total confusion
as to what is real
and what is illusion.
All these MAX factors add up
to an irresistible weapon,
the Blue God of Death!
Let's forget the optional
extras, even without them
I think the MAX-5000
will cope with you!
- A-ko, it's pretty late,
perhaps I'd better go ahead.
I'll see you in class!
(birds chirping)
- And now, Uma, all systems go!
What's the matter, Uma?
Give her the benefit
of the whole works!
- [Uma] Yeah, but I
seem to have a problem.
- (groaning) What's
the matter with you?
Just do as you're told!
- There seems to be
a basic design flaw,
the start lever's
slightly out of reach.
I'm doing my best!
(Uma screaming)
(electricity crackling)
(kick crashing)
(air whooshing)
(MAX-5000 crashing)
(B-ko yelping)
- [A-ko] Hold on, C-ko,
I'll come with you!
- Oh, well I guess it's
back to the drawing board.
(school bell chiming)
(air whistling)
(curtains rustling)
You've humiliated me
once too often, A-ko!
Revenge is sweet, sweet, sweet
and you, A-ko, are
going to die, die, die!
(pencil snapping)
(B-ko laughing)
(birds chirping)
- Hey, whee, whee!
(C-ko yelping)
- You're in a pretty good
mood this morning, A-ko!
What's made you so happy?
- I feel good because
I got up earlier today!
We'll be in plenty of
time, and with luck
we won't have to fight with B-ko
because she won't
expect us so early!
- Whee!
(A-ko giggling)
- Woo!
Come on, go, run!
Whoa!
Whee!
(road crashing)
(birds chirping)
(pensive music)
(D chuckling)
- I made myself very vulnerable
in the middle of the roadway,
but here I've got
some protection.
Besides which, there's
my warning device.
(device beeping)
Uh-oh, here they come.
Huh?
(door crashing)
(D screaming)
- [A-ko] Sorry!
- Morning!
- Good morning!
- I'm glad to see you're
on time this morning, A-ko.
- Excuse me, I'm in
a hurry, Miss Ayumi.
- She might do well in
the school 100 meters!
- Slow down, A-ko, we've got
plenty of time, haven't we?
- I don't want another argument
with B-ko if I can help it.
- Wow!
- It's really amazing!
- [Student] What's she
gonna do when she sees that?
- [Student] I don't know!
- This is scary!
- I know!
- [Student] Stay here,
don't go, don't go away.
- Look!
Here come A-ko now!
- [Student] Oh, the poor girl!
- Oh boy!
- Oh, I hope A-ko gets the
better of B-ko at last!
- [A-Ko] Huh?
(students cheering)
- [Student] Oh, it's
the most incredible
thing I've ever seen!
- What're they waiting here for?
- [B-ko] A-ko, look around you.
(grim dramatic music)
- You've been busy, huh?
- Oh my!
Even you couldn't beat them!
- I want you to meet
my Abashiyama Five,
though you may not
appreciate their friendship.
- Hey, I'm getting real
fed up with all this,
especially as I got outta bed
10 minutes earlier than usual
so I wouldn't be
late for school!
I don't wanna be late again
because of these wind-up toys!
Anyway, I'm too old
to play with them.
- A-ko, I'm gonna pay you back
for all the things
you've ever done to me!
Ruining my friendship with C-ko,
humiliating me again
by disposing of my
robot inventions!
(grunting) The time
for revenge has come!
You won't dispose
of these beauties,
they'll dispose of you!
- C-ko, what's she
flipped her lid about?
- Hey, ask B-ko, I've no idea!
(scooter engine rumbling)
- As you've got to
school early for once,
why not go straight in so
we can start work, okay?
(scooter engine revving)
You can always finish your
girl talk at lunchtime, B-ko.
- Right, yes, Miss.
- Do you hear?
So, come on, stop
gossiping now, girls!
- Okay.
- Are we done?
- I wanna stay and watch!
- What do you think we'd see
if we had to sit in class?
- It's not fair!
- I know!
- I guess if we don't
go she'll keep us in.
- Yeah, I guess,
better go in now.
- I'd like to see
B-ko get hers, though.
- Oh, C-ko's not so great.
- Oh yeah,
that's rich!
- Have you seen
her blonde curly hair?
(school bell chiming)
- [Blue-Haired Girl] Hey,
wait for me, you guys!
- Now we can get
down to business
without interference or
interruptions from any of them.
(dramatic whooshing)
- I managed to get
up in time today
and left home with
plenty to make it here
with a bit to spare, which will
probably never happen again,
but now I'm late anyway because
of you, and I feel real mad!
(B-ko yelping)
(A-ko screaming)
(blows crashing)
(robot crashing)
(energetic music)
(air whooshing)
(explosion booming)
Real mad!
(electricity zapping)
(blow crashing)
(robot whirring)
(robot crashing)
(A-ko grunting)
(air whooshing)
Strike one!
(explosion booming)
(B-ko shuddering)
- Wow!
She's got it!
- B-ko!
It's thanks to you
I'm late again,
don't you think
you've done enough?
- No, I haven't started!
I'm gonna get you,
you selfish creep!
- When will you learn you can
build all the robots you like
and it won't make
you feel any better,
all it does is make
us late for school!
- Is that the only
thing you care about?
Being a good girl,
charming the teachers?
Well, naturally it's
never occurred to you
that there are some
children who just
aren't born with the same charm!
But you don't care, you've
always been the heroine
while I always
had to be the girl
that everybody said was spoiled!
Okay, if they say
I'm the bad girl,
then that's what I'm gonna be!
- Look, can't we
talk about this?
- It's too late!
(jacket whooshing)
(B-ko yelling)
(grim dramatic music)
Now, now I'm dressed for action.
This suit gives me the power
to match you in unarmed combat!
(students laughing)
- What does she look like?
- Oh!
- And number one--
- I quite like her boots!
- Oh, come on!
- So stupid!
- Ain't it cold enough?
- Oh, gee!
(both laughing)
- [B-ko] Laugh all you like!
En garde!
- I'd better go on
into class, A-ko.
- Sure, and do something
for me, would ya?
Answer for me at roll call.
- Sure, bye now!
- I'm ready!
(energetic electronic music)
Okay, B-ko, this is gonna
be our last meeting!
- [B-ko] You took the
words outta my mouth!
(air whistling sharply)
(B-ko yelling)
(A-ko yelling)
(console beeping)
(technicians chattering)
- Second two.
- Five.
- What do you see, Bill?
- Sorry, sir, it's disappeared.
- [Technician]
Roger, I have you.
Release.
Continuing.
- Are you saying that
Constellation's destruction
was the result of
certain hostile actions?
- Yes, the Central
Astro Agency think
that's the likeliest scenario,
though they can't be sure yet.
- Any idea who did it?
- There's no way that a
bomb could've gotten planted
on the craft as it stood ready
on the launchpad of
the satellite station,
that's absolutely ruled out.
- Which means it was them!
- Possibly, Colonel,
however, I suggest
you don't jump to
conclusions right now.
But we could consider this:
in 16 short years we have
progressed at a phenomenal rate
in stellar defense
and it could just be
an unknown galactic
power doesn't like it!
(jets whooshing)
(D chomping)
(pensive rhythmic music)
- That feels a lot better.
(phone beeping)
- [First Officer] Earth calling!
- [Captain] Put it through.
- [First Officer] Right!
- Operative CD138621
et cetera, code name D.
- [Captain] Yeah, yeah,
yeah, get on with it.
You're in worse physical
shape each time you call.
- It's a pretty
rough assignment,
these earthlings play
serious hardball.
- Hmm.
Do you have a definite ID report
or is this call a social one?
- [D] It's a breakthrough!
There's been danger, but
I've solved the case!
- [First Officer]
Data coming in!
- [Captain] Put
it on the monitor.
- [First Officer]
Right, Captain.
- [D] The technical
quality of these pictures
may not be up to
my usual standard,
but they were obtained in
extremely difficult conditions.
The speed of the
subjects approach
on each individual
sighting finally burned out
the auto-control
and necessitated
a switch to manual recording.
- [Captain] Hey, that's
a second-generation
Nagota class ship.
Brilliant results, D!
- Thanks, I set the shutter
at A for long distance
and aperture was 14
millimeters in strong light.
- No doubt about it,
that's the princess!
I'll get the Pilot
Star for this!
I'm heading for Earth sector
now, proceed to phase two!
- Right, Captain, count of
me to get things organized!
(console beeping)
- [Captain] This calls
for a little celebration.
For 16 long years we've
searched the universe
and at last we can return home!
Damn, you can never find
a drink when you want one!
I don't ask for a lot, just
a little drink now and then!
(air rumbling)
(alarm wailing)
(technicians chattering)
- [Shireikan] What do we got?
- An object which
we can't identify
has penetrated our
absolute defense sphere
and the course it's
now on will bring it
into collision with this
station in 40 seconds.
- What?
- [Tactical Officer]
Unidentified object carrying
intelligent life for an
estimated fighting power
above level 300.
- Sound action
stations, condition red!
- [Tactical Officer] Roger!
Action stations,
action stations,
all strike units
scramble immediately,
scramble immediately.
(dramatic electronic music)
(machines whirring)
(machines rumbling)
- [Strike One] Strike
units ready for take off!
- Roger, Strike One.
Sir?
- Strike units take off.
- Aye aye, sir!
Command Center to Strike
One, launch all units.
(engines whooshing)
(ships whooshing)
- [Strike One] Strike
One to all units,
take up attack formation E.
All units, take up
attack formation E.
- [Tactical Officer]
Target maintaining speed
and has now penetrated
Sector Yellow Two.
No change in target's course,
which is calculated to
take it into Earth orbit.
All strike units
intercept and disable.
- [Strike One] Roger.
(missiles whooshing)
(explosions booming)
- What's happening?
- [First Officer] Unprovoked
surprise attack, Captain!
- [Weapons Officer] Engage
synclonic deflectors!
- [First Officer]
The enemy is from the
third planet, Captain!
- That's where our lost
princess is being held.
How appalling to have to endure
their unrefined appetites,
but chin up, princess,
we'll rescue you,
but first I could use
a couple of drinks.
If we take any more Earth
missiles, strike back at them.
Let the puny Earthlings
oppose our power
and I'll show no mercy!
(explosions booming)
(missiles whooshing)
(lasers whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(missiles whooshing)
(explosions booming)
(lasers whooshing)
(explosion booming)
- [Strike One] Jeez, look at
it, look at the size of it!
(lasers whooshing)
(missiles whooshing)
(explosions booming)
(explosion booming)
(lasers whooshing)
(console beeping)
- [First Officer]
Captain, we've targeted
the enemy's space station.
- We don't have
time to negotiate
in a civilized way, destroy it!
(energy warbling)
(blast whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(alarm blaring)
(technicians screaming)
(both yelping)
(energy warbling)
(blast whooshing)
(technicians screaming)
(explosion booming)
(A-ko grunting)
(B-ko grunting)
(B-ko exclaiming)
- [B-Ko] While I'm
wearing this suit,
my reflexes are twice
as fast as yours!
Get ready, A-ko, it's
curtains for you!
(B-ko yelling)
(A-ko grunting)
(blow thudding)
(A-ko groaning)
(blows thudding)
(A-ko grunting)
(glass shattering)
(energetic music)
(A-ko yelling)
(B-ko screaming)
(glass shattering)
(students screaming)
- [Teacher] Don't you
take the time to knock?
- What the?
- Go!
(B-ko yelling)
(both grunting)
(A-ko grunting)
(B-ko screaming)
(B-ko crashing)
(A-ko yelling)
- Huh?
(blow crashing)
(B-ko laughing)
(A-ko grunting)
(B-ko chuckling)
One Forichi, ha!
(A-ko crashing)
(A-ko grunting)
Traditionally followed
by the Karoke Whirl!
(A-ko screaming)
(air whooshing)
(students screaming)
(A-ko crashing)
- [A-ko] Ah!
(missiles whooshing)
(explosion booming)
- Hm, Akagiyama missiles!
(air whooshing)
(air whistling)
(A-ko yelling)
(B-ko grunting)
Hey, that's
tickling, cut it out!
Overhead Throw!
(A-ko yelping)
(A-ko crashing)
(A-ko grunting)
So, had enough yet
or would you enjoy
a little bit more of the same?
Okay, have it your way,
this'll hurt you more
than it hurts me!
(B-ko yelling)
(A-ko yelling)
(both grunting)
(blows thudding)
(A-ko screaming)
And now
my Black Jacovini Lash!
(A-ko grunting)
(lash whooshing)
(A-ko yelping)
Down, girl!
(A-ko grunting)
Down, I said!
(A-ko screaming)
And again!
(A-ko grunting)
(blows thudding)
(B-ko grunting)
(air whooshing)
(A-ko grunting)
(A-ko yelling)
(B-ko yelping)
(A-ko crashing)
Fire!
(missiles whooshing)
(explosions booming)
- [A-ko Voiceover] I've gotta
get her away from the school
before it gets smashed up!
- [B-Ko] (laughing) Surely
you're not running away, A-ko?
- [Miss Ayumi] And so
the story concludes
with the purple-backed
black piping shrike
talking to the little red
idol in the temple at--
- [C-Ko Voiceover] Oh,
where's A-ko got to?
I covered for her at roll call,
but if she doesn't
get here soon--
- C-ko!
- What?
I don't know where she is!
- You weren't paying
attention again,
which I'm beginning to
realize is quite normal,
and as for A-ko and B-ko,
they're gossiping
outside I imagine!
(C-ko moaning)
(A-ko screaming)
(loud crashing)
- [C-ko] A-ko!
- C-ko, stop, you silly girl!
C-ko, come back!
(C-ko panting)
What's happened to
old-fashioned discipline?
If you ask me, it's
parents who are to blame!
(students groaning)
(Miss Ayumi yelping)
Girls, what's happened to you?
Why are you wearing bandages?
Come back here at once
(girls screaming)
and tell me what's going--
(Mari crashing)
(Mari yelling)
(Miss Ayumi yelping)
- A-ko, A-ko!
Hey!
Are you still fighting?
What's happened to you?
(helicopter whirring)
- Hi, C-ko!
- [C-ko] Huh?
- If you're looking
for A-ko, climb up here
and you can get yourself
a bird's-eye view!
- [C-ko] Well, I...
(Mari grunting)
- [Mari] Well?
- [Asa] Are you
coming or aren't you?
- [C-ko] Mm!
(helicopter whirring)
(explosions booming)
- Hey, smoke!
I'll bet that's the two of them
still fighting it
out with each other!
(explosion booming)
- [B-ko] Hey!
(A-ko yelping)
(A-ko crashing)
(B-ko yelling)
(B-ko grunting)
(B-ko yelping)
Akagiyama missiles!
- [A-ko] Oh no, not again!
(explosions booming)
(A-ko grunting)
(explosion booming)
(A-ko yelping)
(B-ko growling)
- [Technician] Position
of delta two, tango six.
- The alien craft still on
the same course
towards Earth, sir.
- Six minutes 'til
our interceptor units
are in firing range.
- They've come at last.
(jets rumbling)
- Alpha One to Command HQ,
still no visual contact,
but I've got 'em on radar.
Alpha One to all units:
10 degrees port 80,000
and let's get a look at 'em, go!
(jets whooshing)
There!
(mothership rumbling)
(grim electronic music)
- Look at the sky!
- Wow!
- Look at that!
- It's huge!
- How big you think it is, eh?
- I'd estimate it's
gotta be four miles long
from bow through to stern.
(jets whooshing)
- [Alpha One] Alpha One
to HQ, visual sighted!
Going into attack formation.
(jets whooshing)
(energy whooshing)
(spidership whooshing)
- [Bill] Defense force
engaging now, sir.
(jets and spiderships whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(missiles whooshing)
(energy whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(jets and spiderships whooshing)
(missiles whooshing)
(explosions booming)
(jets whooshing)
(civilians screaming)
(missiles whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(spidership crashing)
(spidership stomping)
(tank guns blasting)
(explosions booming)
(spidership stomping)
(energy whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(A-ko grunting)
- Damn it, B-ko, you're
pretty persistent, aren't you?
(spidership whooshing)
(A-ko grunting)
(explosions booming)
Now, have you had enough?
(ground rumbling)
(A-ko yelping)
(tank crashing)
- Why haven't you
been evacuated?
We told everyone
to get out of town.
That's the way to
safety, now get out!
- A-ko, you can run
but you can't hide!
(solider screaming)
(A-ko yelping)
Muscle Attack!
(tank crashing)
More Akagiyamas!
(missiles whooshing)
(explosions booming)
(helicopter whirring)
- No sign of her anywhere!
- Those two oughta be down
in the city somewhere,
judging by the chaos.
- [Ena] There sure
is something strange
going on down on the streets.
- [Asa] Yeah, I can see
tanks and stuff everywhere,
but there ain't a whole
lotta people around.
- Hey, I think I
see them over there,
a couple of blocks down!
- [C-ko] Where, where are they?
- [Asa] Mari, pedal a
bit harder, can you?
(Mari panting)
(tank guns blasting)
- [B-ko] Stiletto Leap!
(tanks crashing)
(explosion booming)
- [A-ko] A-ko Tank Gun, fire!
- [B-ko] Spider Nit!
- [A-ko] Spider Nit Crash!
(explosion booming)
(B-ko panting)
(A-ko panting)
- [C-ko] A-ko!
- [A-ko] Huh?
- B-ko!
- A-ko!
Hey, A-ko--
- Can you hear me?
- Have you two settled
your argument yet or not?
- Hey, C-ko, what are you up to?
Come down!
- I just thought you must be
exhausted after your fighting
so I brought you something!
Lunch!
I made it myself, naturally,
especially for you!
(A-ko groaning)
- Anything but that!
(ominous music)
(ship whooshing)
Hey, look out!
(Asa yelping)
- Oh?
(ship thudding)
Ah, your lunch, A-ko,
it'll be ruined!
(ship whooshing)
- C-ko!
(A-ko grunting)
(grand dramatic music)
(ship whooshing)
- [B-ko] A-ko, we
haven't finished yet!
- What's wrong with you?
You saw what happened up there!
We can finish your
stupid fight later,
right now we have more
important things to do.
- [B-ko] Well, if
you put it like that.
- We gotta rescue C-ko first
and then I'll deal with you.
(fire crackling)
- Well, just once,
I'll be the hero.
Wait for me!
(ship whooshing)
- [C-ko] Take me back,
let me outta here
you lousy kidnapper!
- Don't be upset, you
won't come to harm!
(C-ko wailing)
Stop crying, Your Highness,
we'll get you home
in two light-years.
(C-ko wailing)
(D yelping)
- I don't like this,
you're kidnappers!
Take this old crate back
down to the ground right now!
I'm gonna get shot, strangled--
- Really, I'm not
that sort of person!
All right, then,
here's the ship.
- I'm too young to die!
(C-ko wailing)
(air rumbling)
(ship whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(explosions thundering)
(B-ko whooshing)
(energetic music)
- [B-ko] I want to make it
clear this truce only lasts
'til we get C-ko back,
is that understood?
(jets and ships whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(A-ko and B-ko yelping)
(A-ko screaming)
- A-ko!
I wanted the pleasure of
finishing you off myself.
Oh well, can't have everything!
(A-ko screaming)
(jets whooshing)
(pilot screaming)
- A little to the
side, I can't see!
(A-ko yelping)
(missiles whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(pilot yelping)
(A-ko grunting)
- Hold tight, I'll get you down!
(explosion booming)
(pilot yelping)
(A-ko grunting)
- Jeez!
(missiles whooshing)
(B-ko whooshing)
(B-ko yelling)
(explosions booming)
(B-ko gasping)
- Boy, that is big!
Well, someone appreciates
that size does matter.
(mothership whirring)
(lasers zapping)
(B-ko yelping)
(peaceful music)
- Your Highness?
Why aren't you pleased
that we searched
16 years to find
you, Your Highness?
Talk to us.
- [First Officer] Captain?
- Why do you interrupt me?
- [First Officer] Sorry,
Captain, but you're wanted
on the bridge immediately!
- [Captain] On my way.
(air rumbling)
(A-ko grunting)
(A-ko panting)
(footsteps thundering)
(A-ko sighing)
(lasers zapping)
(A-ko screaming)
(A-ko grunting)
- Drop Kick!
(soldiers yelping)
(A-ko panting)
Death ray machine!
(A-ko yelping)
(lasers zapping)
(A-ko screaming)
(explosion booming)
(A-ko panting)
(lasers zapping)
(A-ko yelping)
(lasers thundering)
(A-ko grunting)
- [Captain] What is it, Spy-D?
I was with the princess!
- Forgive me, Captain, we
have rats on board the ship.
- [Captain] Rats?
Not rats!
- [D] Yes, Captain, these
rats are Earthling friends
of Her Highness who
found their way aboard.
- [Captain] Exterminate them!
- Count on me, Captain.
With all the experience I had
on Earth, this'll be easy.
(B-ko whooshing)
(lasers whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(B-ko yelping)
- What's that down there?
(peaceful music)
Why are her beautiful eyes
staring into space like that?
(glass thudding)
(shots thundering)
(glass shattering)
C-ko?
My God, she's dead!
No, hypnotized!
No, drugged!
That's all right, then,
she'll come out of it.
(C-ko moaning)
Huh?
- Oh dear, B-ko, I think
I've been in shock!
- [B-ko] Oh, C-ko, did they use
some terrible alien drug on you?
- No, I tired myself
out whining and crying.
- Ah.
(C-ko giggling)
You poor thing, but now
let's get out of here.
- Mm, is A-ko here?
- She's somewhere
around, I guess,
but she couldn't rescue
you, it took me to do it.
(C-ko wailing)
- I want A-ko!
- Don't cry, C-ko, come on!
- [B-ko Voiceover] How
are we gonna escape?
I'd never make it the way I
came, poor C-ko'd be terrified.
Maybe I can steal a plane?
(door crashing)
(A-ko grunting)
- Mm?
(blows thudding)
(A-ko grunting)
(door thudding)
(A-ko yelping)
(door crashing)
(A-ko groaning)
Mm?
Yuck, I'm gonna be sick!
This must be the ship's laundry!
Wait a minute, they all
seem to be women things.
(door chiming)
(air whooshing)
(A-ko groaning)
(A-ko panting)
(A-ko yelping)
(elevator whirring)
Some elevator!
(electronic warbling)
Huh?
(A-ko gasping)
(sword whooshing)
(A-ko screaming)
- [D] Ah, you avoided
that with some skill!
- Ha, that was dirty,
coming from behind!
(pensive electronic music)
- This is as far as you go,
and the only way you
go a step further
is across D's dead body.
(D yelling)
(D grunting)
(A-ko grunting)
You really are a rat
scurrying around like that!
Well, this is how
I deal with rats!
(D grunting)
- Some rats are
hard to deal with!
My cheek!
(D laughing)
It's cut!
(A-ko growling)
How dare you!
(A-ko yelling)
(D grunting)
(D groaning)
I'm not as easy to beat
as you seem to think.
(D groaning)
(D yelling)
- I haven't got enough
breath left, B-ko!
Unless we rest, I
might start whining,
I've got enough
breath left for that!
- Look, it's her!
(B-ko grunting)
(C-ko yelping)
(blows thudding)
- [B-ko] Okay, we've
gotta find a way out!
These tunnels are endless.
(A-ko yelling)
(swords clanging)
(D growling)
(both grunting)
(swords clashing)
(both groaning)
(A-ko yelling)
(A-ko yelping)
(D grunting)
(A-ko yelling)
(D growling)
(swords clanging)
(sword shattering)
(shield shattering)
(A-ko panting)
(shield clattering)
- [D] Oh.
(D growling)
(D grunting)
(A-ko yelling)
(door crashing)
(D yelping)
- Holy mother!
- You've got my friend!
Tell your men to bring
her up here quick smart!
- [Captain] What men?
And did you say your friend?
That child is the fourth
princess of the fifth queen
of the Lepton Kingdom
of Alpha Cygni!
- I do believe
that you're drunk!
Listen, I've had enough
bull from you guys.
- Obviously there's
no point in trying
to negotiate with you
in a civilized way.
(Captain screaming)
- What's wrong?
- [Captain] On the console,
quickly, gotta have a drink!
- Huh?
(growling) Look, I'm
starting to feel real mad!
(Captain groaning)
- If I don't get a
drink soon, I'll go mad!
- [B-ko] Oh hell, this
doesn't look like the way out!
- No, hey, A-ko!
- C-ko, are you all right?
- (yelping) Your Highness!
- He's drunk, how repulsive!
- A-ko!
(C-ko yelping)
- As for you, A-ko,
now I've rescued C-ko,
I consider our truce at an end
and it's business as usual.
(missiles whooshing)
(Captain yelping)
(explosions booming)
- That's dangerous!
(intense music)
- [A-ko] Let her go, B-ko!
- Ah, A-ko, I'm so
pleased to see you!
(D growling)
- I'll kill her!
(gun firing)
- Stop firing, you fool,
or you'll hit Her Highness!
(console booming)
(all screaming)
- Cut it out, stop I say,
you'll hurt somebody!
And you, stay away
from those controls!
(Captain screaming)
D, calm down and
control yourself!
Look, I'm sure we can
talk this through!
D, anger's no use!
(Captain sobbing)
(D growling)
- [B-Ko] Okay, buster!
(missiles whooshing)
(explosions booming)
(Captain and D screaming)
- All right!
(minigun blasts thundering)
- [Soldier] Not us!
(explosion booming)
- Oh!
Oh boy, my head!
Ah, take that, you dirty rat!
(Captain laughing)
(minigun blasts thundering)
(energy whooshing)
Ah, ah, gotta get a drink!
(explosion booming)
(explosions booming)
(alarm blaring)
- Wowee, we're out of control!
(energetic dramatic music)
(explosions booming)
(explosion booming)
- Nobody leaves here
unless the booze
has been taken safely
off the ship first!
(mothership rumbling)
(technicians screaming)
- Let us out!
- Everybody run!
- Let me out!
- Let us outta here!
(mothership rumbling)
(soldiers screaming)
(explosions booming)
(mothership crashing)
(explosion booming)
(explosions booming)
- \"Not only weeps the crow,
but also weeps the popinjay.\"
(loud crashing)
(students screaming)
(Miss Ayumi panting)
(Miss Ayumi yelping)
(A-ko laughing)
- Sorry we're late again!
- Hi, Miss!
We've got back!
What happened was that these
women from outer space,
who look like men, said
I was their princess
and they kidnapped me
and they were going
to take me back to their planet!
But before they could get away,
A-ko got onto the
ship to rescue me!
And the Captain was drunk,
which wasn't very nice,
and that's probably
why the ship crashed!
And I cried a bit, which
drove everyone nuts!
But luckily, they weren't...
(gentle electronic music)
(alarm ringing)
(A-ko groaning)
- Just another five minutes!
(A-ko thudding)
(A-ko yelping)
(A-ko yawning)
(A-ko groaning)
(A-ko chomping)
I'm ready for a change!
(doorbell ringing)
- [C-ko] A-ko, time to go!
(footsteps thundering)
- Bye!
Hiya, C-ko!
- Ready to go?
- [A-ko] Naturally!
(C-ko giggling)
- Whee!
Mm!
(upbeat electronic music)
(debris clattering)
- [Captain] Habit to support.
- [D] Help, homeless alien.
- [Captain] Expensive
habit to support.
- [D] Help, homeless alien.
- [Captain] Expensive
habit to support.
* There's a vision
in your heart *
* Only you can achieve
* You can climb the
highest mountains *
* If you only believe
* If you try to do your best
* Nothing stands in your way
* So don't put off
until tomorrow *
* What you should do today
* I remember I saw you shine
like a diamond in the sky *
* I knew that you had a dream
* A dream that would never die
* Follow your dream
* You've got to follow it
* No, don't you ever
forget your dream *
* And you will never regret it
* The world's waiting
in front of you *
* Follow your dream
* You've got to follow it
* No, don't you ever
forget your dream *
* And you will never regret it
* You'll find all of
your dreams come true *
* There's a light
that's shining bright *
* It's the light in your eyes
* You can swim the
deepest ocean *
* Or fly high in the sky
* Now's the time
to shoot the moon *
* Or to reach for the stars
* You can be anything
you want to *
* If you know who you are
* I remember I saw you shine
like a diamond in the sky *
* I knew that you had a dream
* A dream that would never die
* Follow your dream
* You've got to follow it
* No, don't you ever
forget your dream *
* And you will never regret it
* The world's waiting
in front of you *
* Follow your dream
* You've got to follow it
* No, don't you ever
forget your dream *
* And you will never regret it
* You'll find all of
your dreams come true *
* When you look into a mirror
* Tell me what you see
* Is the light that's
always shining *
* Shining in your heart
* When you wake up
in the morning *
* Tell me how you feel
* Is it just a dream
* Or is it really real
* Really real
* Tell me is it really real
* Follow your dream
* You've got to follow it
* No, don't you ever
forget your dream *
* And you will never regret it
* You'll find all of
your dreams come true *
* Follow your dream
* You've got to follow it
* No, don't you ever
forget your dream *
* And you will never regret it
* The world's waiting
in front of you *
* Follow your dream
* You've got to follow it
* No, don't you ever
forget your dream *
* And you will never regret it
* You'll find all of
your dreams come true *
* When you look into a mirror
* Tell me what you see
* Is the light that's
always shining *
* Shining in your heart
* When you wake up
in the morning *
* Tell me how you feel