And now, the crown jewel of today's auction.
A masterpiece that brings pride to all of humanity.
Thought to be lost forever...
Vincent Van Gogh's beautiful, "Sunflowers"!
No way, the lost "Sunflowers"?!
I thought it was destroyed in the last great war?
Quiet down, please!
We have a specialist on hand that can explain.
It's believed that Van Gogh created seven
"Sunflowers" paintings when he was in Arles.
The second painting in the classic
series is what's being presented here today.
It was believed to have been destroyed in
1945 during an air raid in Ashiya, Japan.
But a painting with the same
composition was found in Arles last year.
Master appraisers have examined the piece,
and have undoubtedly verified that this is
indeed an original work of Vincent Van Gogh.
All right! How about we breathe some
life into these once lost "Sunflowers"!
Presenting Vincent Van Gogh's
masterpiece, the second "Sunflowers"!
The bidding will begin at 10 million dollars!
Seriously? 10 million?
And it's going up 100,000 each bid.
If I had that kind of money, I'd
rather spend it on a trip to space.
20 mil by phone... And a 20.5 mil online!
50 million!
Huh?
It's that famous buyer...
One hundred million.
Huh?!
Did I stutter? I said 100 million!
One hundred million!
Do I hear 110 million? 110 million, anyone?
Damn it. Who is that bald old man in the back there?
What do you want to do now? - And now 120!
Ugh, looks like we'll have to go to 200.
All right...
200 million!
Huh?
Suzuki is here!
Yes! Two hundred million!
Um, if I heard correctly, #705
has just bid 200 million dollars.
So he's the infamous...
Mr. Suzuki!
Uuh, we're a little behind with our online bidding...
Um, hey Uncle, they all think we're crazy.
I prefer not to waste my precious time.
His time is precious, hehe.
Huh?
Forget about those online bids!
Hmph.
Three hundred.
Huh?! Ugh...
Three hundred million dollars!
That's hammer price! Hammer price!
Sold for 300 million!
Van Gogh's lost painting, "Sunflowers" has been sold,
Conan! It's about to start!
All right.
Hurry, hurry!
So whatcha got there?
What is it? Some kind of robot or something?
Turn it on already, Doc!
Hold down, the most important past isn't here yet!
So tell us, where has this painting been
all these years? Why has it suddenly surfaced?
Scholars everywhere were under the impression that it
had been destroyed in an air raid during World War II.
Destroyed?
So this is not the original painting, then?
No, it's the original. Despite rumors to the contrary.
- Ah.
Stating that a painting thought to be a lost work of
Van Gogh's was discovered in Arles, France, last year.
Oh! Come to think of it, there was talk that it
was found in the attic of an old cottage, right?
Right, and it turned out to be the second Sunflowers.
I see.
Now let's start!
Ah...
Wow, so cool!
So cool!
This is the biggest one I could get!
Push these buttons here, and...
Bet it makes grilled eel!
I don't think that's possible.
But how likely is it that this one's a fake?
The specialists are very careful in that regard,
and did a thorough appraisal
of the piece before the auction.
As a result, it was found that the canvas was the same
one that Van Gogh had used for other paintings in Arles.
Better than grilled eel? Like grilled eel over rice!
Why would you think that?
Woah! It's coming out!
Huh?
What's wrong?
It hasn't changed at all.
What is this, another failure?
Just wait, you'll see.
Huh?
Oh.
Woah!
Kamen Yaiba!
Wow!
Cool!
It's Kamen Yaiba!
Wow!
Cool! How did you do that?!
What are you doing, Doc? Don't
you have other stuff to make?
... may have been a forgery?
Well, considering all the facts, that's a possibility.
Moreover, some speculate that there were actually
8 painting, not 7 in Van Gogh's Sunflower series.
The "Sunflowers" sold at auction today,
and the "Sunflowers" that was in Ashiya,
may be two separate paintings with the exact
same image, both of them painted by Van Gogh himself.
Would the original creator really
make a copy of their own work?
Yes. Out of the 7 "Sunflowers" paintings that
we've been able to verify, 3 of them are copies.
And each was indeed painted, by Van Gogh.
Nothing against Van Gogh,
but shouldn't you show a little more
interest in the Doctor's work also?
His art deserves recognition too.
Looks like he has enough of that already.
Ah, it seems the press conference is about to start.
We now bring you a live broadcast of
the press conference happening in New York.
Ehem. First, a few words from the winner of our auction.
Jirokichi Suzuki, the proud new
owner of the second "Sunflowers"!
Mm.
I'm glad to say that my plan to purchase the painting
with the highest possible bid was a resounding success.
Huh?
You mean you planned to pay 300
million dollars for the painting?
That's correct.
Hmph.
It was all so I can hold a
"Sunflowers" exhibition back in Japan.
A "Sunflowers" exhibition?
We, the Suzuki Financial Group, are pleased to
announce the "Sunflowers Long for Japan" Exhibit,
at our Lake Rock Art Museum.
The "Sunflowers" scattered all
around the world will finally
be gathered into a single vase. We hope to see you there!
Ms. Suzuki! With this purchase, how
many "Sunflowers" paintings will you have?
So then, winning this auction was
all part of this planned exhibit?
Yeah! The perfect opportunity so we
could announce our exhibition to the world.
Including the "Sunflowers" from today, we
plan to gather and display the entire collection.
Huh?! All seven of them?
Well that possible, even for a Japanese conglomerate!
Don't you fret. The project is already well underway.
We're happy to announce, we've made contact
with "Sunflowers" owners all over the world.
They know all about our desire to
exhibit the entire "Sunflowers" series.
Thanks to getting the second
"Sunflowers" in today's auction,
museums and private collectors have
agreed to give us their complete cooperation!
That's not all! We've hired seven elite specialists,
they'll tend to the paintings, supervise
their transport, and provide security.
Wow, seven specialists, huh?
Hmph. You could say they're my seven samurai.
And I've brought them to join us!
So, this group is what you'd call your seven samurai?
Exactly. They're the cream of the crop.
All of them are experts in their respective fields,
and have trained in Van Gogh's
native homes of Holland and France.
Starting from the left, we have Ms. Natsumi
Miyadai, overseeing art history and appraisals.
Glad to be here.
Another art scholar, Mr. Koji Azuma, will be in
charge of restoration and preservation of the paintings.
Next is Ms. Keiko Anderson, who'll be in
charge of exhibition planning and operations.
Mr. Taizo Ishimine, will be handling
transportation of the paintings.
Call me Ishimine.
Next we have Ms. Kumiko Kishi. She'll be
overseeing the staging of the "Sunflowers."
I promise to make the exhibition a big success.
And last but not least, we have lieutenant Charlie,
on loan from the NYPD as our head of security.
I'll do my best to protect the "Sunflowers."
Let's see, didn't you mention you hired seven
samurai? But you've only introduced us to six of them.
That's because the seventh member's in Japan,
where he'll be providing additional security.
And his name's Mister...
Kogoro Mori!
Huh?! You mean the last one is Pops of all people?
It's probably because he knows he gets
the "Kid Catcher" as part of the deal.
Huh?
Best of luck Mr. Samurai.
Oh! Wow, check it out!
Sonoko's on TV! How cool!
Wow! I wanna watch!
Let's all watch!
Would you still exhibit the other Sunflowers, even if you
aren't able to gather all seven paintings in one place?
No. It's either all of them, or none at all!
You can't be serious?!
Don't you worry.
I've long dreamed of holding a "Sunflowers" exhibit.
And when I have a dream, I always make sure it comes true!
Huh...
Don't tell me that's...!
A Kid Card!
Move back, he's got a gun!
Call security!
Drop your gun!
Didn't you hear me? I said, drop your gun!
Hmph.
No way!
I can't tell what's going on!
Something must have happened!
Huh?!
Look, it's Kid!
Hahaha!
Kid!
Woah!
Ah!
Freeze! Freeze or I'll sho...!
Gah! Woah..!
Woah! Urk!
Hup!
What the?!
Freeze! Give yourself up!
You're surrounded! Don't move, there's no where to run!
Kid!
Hmph.
Drop your weapon! Right now!
Good. Now stay we you are and raise
both hands where I can seem them.
Hey! Do you hear me?! I said raise
both hands where I can see them!
Kid!
Good, slowly. Just like that.
Charlie! Stop shooting!!
Damn you, Kid the Phantom Thief!
He got away.
It was a chaotic scene but not
casualties have been reported.
Oh no! It's over already?
So what just happened? Did Kid steal the "Sunflowers"?
It's weird cause Kid never goes after
paintings. He's only targeted jewels before!
I only caught a glimpse, but was that really Kid?
What?!
Having some trouble?
- Huh?!
What?! What the heck are you doing here?
I came as soon as I heard that
Kid was after the "Sunflowers".
If you would like, I can be of some help.
I'm Shinichi Kudo, a high school detective.
I went to an amusement park with my childhood friend, Ran.
And while we were there, we witnessed
some men in black making a dangerous deal.
Because I was so absorbed in watching them,
I didn't notice the man who came at me from behind.
He forced me to drink a poison that
knocked me out... and when I woke up...
I discovered that my body had shrunk!
If those guys ever found out that Shinichi
Kudo was still alive, they'd come back.
So on Dr. Agasa's advice, I
kept my real identity a secret.
When Ran asked me who I was, I quickly
made up the name, "Conan Edogawa."
I knew if I wanted info on the men in black,
the smart thing would be to stay at her house
with her, and her dad who ran a detective agency.
By the way, there are a few others
besides Doc that know my true identity.
Ai Haibara, her real name is Shiho Miyano.
She used to be a member of the Black Organization,
but she wanted out so she tried to kill herself...
Taking the exact same poison I was
given. And it shrank her body too.
And we can't forget...
Kid the Phantom Thief and his assistant.
Things haven't been settled between us yet.
But as a detective, someday I'll catch you!
My body may have shrunk but my IQ hasn't!
I will leave no case unsolved!
There is always only one truth!
This plane will soon be landing in Haneda Airport.
Please make sure all baggage is in
the overhead bins or under your seats.
If you have to use the restroom, do
so now before landing procedures begin.
Here's the dummy we were able to retrieve.
Uh... Well you're a happy guy.
Uncle's always falling for those kinds of
tricks, he's just glad he's not the only one.
Huh?!
By the way, are you sure about this?
You won't even let a cabin attendant
in here unless there's an emergency,
but you're letting that kid come and go as he pleases?
Well, that's because he's a
detective that represents Japan.
There's no need to worry about him at all.
But how do you know he's not Kid in disguise?
They do have the same features.
Um.
You've got too much time on your hands.
This oughta help. Watch carefully.
Huh?!
What did I tell ya?
What the heck you old fart?!
Charlie thinks you look suspicious!
What's that American even doing
on this plane in the first place?
You were supposed to escort "Sunflowers" to the airport.
So why don't you tell me what you're still doing here?
I may have been contracted as
security exclusively in America,
but now we're certain Phantom Thief is going
after the painting, I couldn't leave this unfinished.
Aah, I knew you'd be a perfect samurai.
Do what you must to protect "Sunflowers." - Hm.
You can count on me, sir.
Now all we need is the Kid Catcher on
our team and we'll really be in business!
Are you alright, Natsumi?
Yeah, I'm just a bit airsick.
You can try to walk it off? That's what I'm doing.
Come on. It's not good to keep still for so long.
I appreciate it.
Where are you headed?
The restroom.
Hmm...
Come on, Kid's probably on the
look out for when they arrive.
We told him not to make the plane so darn flashy...
We also suggested to him that he keep a low profile.
But apparently it's for marketing, not just transport.
Aren't you supposed to keep him
under control, Inspector Nakamori?
Do you honestly think that old man
would listen to a single word I say?
I guess you have a point there...
So this is the plane they're coming back on?
Is that painting of those sunflowers on it too?
Why does this brat have to
tag along, each and every time?!
We didn't have a choice! Mr. Jirokichi
said he wanted Conan to come along, too.
Hmm.
Huh?
Conan is known as the Kid Catcher after all!
Kid Catcher, huh? What a bunch of nonsense.
You're lucky to be here, kid. So don't cause any trouble.
Right!
Ran! Don't let this brat out of your sight.
Well that's what I always intend to do...
Oh... huh?
Who's this? Just a sec.
Uh...
Oh, hey there Sonoko!
Yeah! Hey, Ran! I just couldn't wait to tell you.
So we're almost there, and I have some good news.
I'm really not supposed to say anything
because he wants to surprise you, but...
Yeah, uh-huh?
What?! Shinichi's with you?
Huh?!
J-Just because Shinichi's there doesn't mean... well...
Hey, Sonoko! Is Shinichi there with you?
Well, he was sitting right here a minute ago.
Hmm... Hmph.
What the?!
Ah!
Ugh!
Sonoko?! Sonoko, are you okay?!
Hey! Ran, what's going on?
There was a lot of screaming, and then
there was some kind of horrible noise!
What the...
Nakamori, come quick! Something's happened on the plane!
Are you sure?
We haven't heard anything on our side.
Don't tell me Kid did that?
Ugh... The right wing's aileron
and slats, they aren't responding!
Forget it, shut down engine
four! That should put out the fire.
Right!
Is that a...?!
This is the control tower, Flight 2501.
We're clearing runway A for you. Can you make it?
This is flight 2501.
We'll try, but better clear all of
the aircraft in the surrounding area!
Copy.
Inform all aircrafts! Check
fuel levels and clear the area!
Huh?
We have to hurry, there's no time!
Right!
Attention all aircrafts! This is an emergency...
Even if they do manage to circle back,
At that altitude they'll overshoot the runway.
They've got to pull this off.
Attention all passengers. We
are having some engine trouble.
So we're preparation for an emergency landing.
Please check to see that your seat belts are
securely fastened and all loose items are stored safely.
Ugh... Hah!
Aah!
Fifteen thousand feet!
Ten thousand feet!
Okay...
Ugh!
Ah! Woah!
Ah! Ugh!
Kid's out there!
What the?! Kid?! Where is he!
Where's Kid?! Where's that thief!
Where is he?!
Kid's up there?!
So he is there!
Hello? Hello?!
Inspector Nakamori! - Huh?
There seems to be a problem with the plane!
They're going to be making an
emergency landing using runway A!
Emergency landing?!
I can't see from here!
Kid's behind this?!
Conan?
Hey Sonoko, answer me!
Sonoko!
Uncle Jirokichi!
Please Adviser! It's too dangerous!
If Kid's here, I need to make sure "Sunflowers" is safe.
Huh?
We will now be making an emergency landing.
As you may know, the explosion has
impaired our control of the craft.
As a result, this will be a very difficult landing.
We're doing all that we can to
ensure that we land the plane safely.
All right, here we go!
Okay, next! Hurry! - Gate #8! Get going!
This is not a drill!
The aircraft just isn't stabilizing!
We can't give up, just keep trying!
Right!
Help us!
Ah...
Out of my way!
There it is.
Here it comes!
It's wavering!
They're coming in too high!
Oh no, this isn't good.
Damn it! You're gonna listen to me!
Reverse thrust!
You sure that's not gonna make us lose control?!
I don't care! We have to stop this plane!
Got it!
Reverse thrust!
What on earth?!
Everyone at the international
terminal, evacuate immediately...
Oh, no! They're gonna crash!
Please stop! Come on, come! Stop!!
No! Please, stop!
Ugh...
That was close!
Shinichi, Sonoko!
This is air control. Flight 2501, can you read me?
Flight 2501, please respond.
This is Flight 2501, I apologize.
I ignored your instructions and
changed runways on my own discretion.
Yes sir, but is everything all right?
Yeah, we're good, but barely.
Everyone's safe. Please begin
rescue procedures immediately.
Roger.
Hey, brat! You okay?
Mhm...
Look at that! Talk abut a close call, huh?
Yeah. That was too close for comfort...
This could've been a disaster.
Yeah... Would Kid really do something like this?
What's that?
Wow!
It's Kid!
Hmph!
No you don't!
Hey! Now where are you going?!
Kid's flying away with the "Sunflowers"!
What?!
Wait, really?
Shinichi! Sonoko!
Huh?
Sonoko! Where are you guys? Are you both okay?!
Calm down, Ran. I'm fine. We're fine!
By the way, did Shinichi call
you? Have you heard from him yet?
Huh? Shinichi? No, not yet.
Why? Is he okay? I thought you were with him!
Actually, I don't see him anywhere.
Hey, kid! That place is off limits!
Damn brat, where'd he go?!
Stop right there! Hey!
Ah, at a time like this?
The person you have dialed is unavailable...
Please no, Shinichi...
Please, answer!!
Sorry, Ran. I'm chasing Kid right now!
I'll call you back later!
I'm so glad... Shinichi.
Where is he?
Ah... Huh?
You won't get away!
Take that!
Hmph.
No..!
Ugh... But he wasn't holding the
"Sunflowers" when he jumped from the building...
Judging from the time I lost sight of him...
I'm sure it's hidden somewhere in that building...
I knew it!
Hm...
This airport doesn't really have art
supplies. So I hope these will work for you?
It's fine. We're just making
sure there aren't any scratches.
So, are you ready to begin?
Ready.
Hopefully it's just dirty from smoke...
One scratch on that painting, and
this exhibition would totally fall apart.
Inspector! Look at this!
You were right! The security
camera on the roof did catch Kid.
Looks like he was right above us
about an hour and 15 minutes ago.
And it looks like he was still holding
onto the "Sunflowers" at that point.
Agreed. But why in the world did
Kid abandon the "Sunflowers" outside?
Cause the second "Sunflowers" was larger than he expect.
It created too much wind resistance
while he was flying on his hang glider.
Maybe he planned to come back after everything
calmed down, but then the little guy saw him.
Huh? I wasn't the one who found it. It was Shinichi.
He said he saw where Kid hid it
while he was chasing after him.
All right, then.
So, where's that high school detective now?
Urk... He's never around at the same time as Kid.
It's as if he's Kid the Phantom Thief.
Sorry, but I don't think that's possible, sir.
Hey she's right. She got a call from
Shinichi about an hour and 15 minus ago.
That's the same timing as the security footage.
Great. It's like I went to
the states without leaving home.
Forget all that trivial stuff.
The real question here is why did
the kid stick around the airport?
Maybe he wanted to see what happened to
the plane he was responsible for blowing up?
Murderers often return to the scene of
the crime, looking like innocent bystanders.
Seriously?
How can you say that?
You can't just go around
treating Kid like he's a murderer!
You need to wake up!
He almost killed you too, you know?
I don't want to believe Kid's capable
of causing a plane crash like that.
Of putting innocent folks at risk, you know?
Although the painting's been dirtied a bit by the
smog, we're confident there's no need for restoration.
Ah, that's great! We really
dodged a bullet with that one, huh?
You've all done amazing work!
And we're just getting started!
Thank goodness it was found before
anything else could happen to it.
You're right. If the painting had been
left out there on the roof of the building,
the heat of the sun and the UV rays
would have caused irreparable damage.
Huh? Job well done, boy!
Just what I'd expect of the Kid Catcher!
But I keep telling you it wasn't me who found it...
Built using Suzuki's great financial
power, I give you the Iron Tanuki Kai!
There's no safer place we could keep it!
Excuse me, but hasn't Kid already
proven he can break into this safe?
Don't you worry. This one's the improved version!
Right, Lupin?
All right. Confirm that everyone's out of the safe!
Right.
Hmph. We're clear. There's not a single soul inside.
Hm.
Iron Tanuki Kai... Let's go!
According to reports from the
Metropolitan Police Department and the MLITT.
Traces of an explosive were found on the
outer wall of the plane's cargo bay door.
Police are searching for a missing
employee who was in charge of the cargo area.
It looks like the owners of the other
"Sunflowers" are getting cold feet.
Dad? Isn't there a meeting
you're supposed to be at right now?
Well yeah, but there's a big horse race today.
Seriously? Slacking off because of a horse race?
... to do if you get fired?
There's no way they'd fire such a fine detective!
Here. I found these in the mail.
Hm? What's this?
Letters, huh? Hey, what if these are fan letters!
Canon?
Sonoko invited me to tag along at
their meeting do you want to come with?
Do you wan to come with?
As much as I'd like to go, I can't...
I promised the gang I'd go to
the art museum with them today.
Oh that's nice! That does sound like fun.
Um... By the way...
Huh?
I was wondering, have you heard anything from Shinichi?
Uh-uh. Nothing at all.
He could have at least tole he was going to go to America.
I haven't heard from him since
he went chasing after Kid...
Ran...
Conan!
Are you ready yet? Time to go!
Come on, Conan! Let's go!
Okay, I'm coming!
Hurry, hurry!
Hey Doc! Conan's on his way!
Hey Ai! Looks like he's ready to go!
Guess I'll see you later.
All right, have fun. Tell them I said hi!
Hm.
Ran!
Erk! What?
Contact the police right away!
Huh?
It was in one of the envelopes that was in the mail.
Mm!
"Tonight, I come for the left 'La Berceuse'
the first copy will belong to me soon enough."
Blast you Kid..! I can't believe you haven't given up yet!
the owners of the other "Sunflowers" have expressed their
reluctance to loan their paintings to the exhibition.
Therefore, in order to recover
the trust that we have lost,
I'm installing an Anti-Kid security system at Lake Rock.
Based on Natsumi's suggest,
we placed camouflaged security cameras
amongst the sunflowers throughout the museum.
Please don't hesitate to speak up
if you have any other good ideas.
Of course, money is no object.
Yes. It's our duty to make this
sure this exhibition is a success.
We'll gather our best ideas
and present them to you shortly.
Hm. Very good.
Charlie, I will have your cooperation as well?
but he's nothing more than a murderer who
will stop at nothing to achieve his goal.
Huh?
Actually, he's a terrorist!
You don't know the first things about Kid!
You have no proof that he's even
remotely responsible for what happened!
Then help me figure this one out.
Who would sabotage the plane?
And what would be their motivation to do so?
Huh?
Uh... Adviser, sir. Something urgent has come up.
What is it?
Inspector Nakamori has called, and if
you don't mind insists on speaking with you.
Fine. Put him through.
Yes, sir.
All right Nakamori, what's going on?
Hm...
The Iron Tanuki's impossible to break
into, but I'll have it investigated at once.
We'll have to save this meeting for later.
What happened, sir?
What's going on?
Do you think Kid's behind this?
Hmm. It seems Detective Mori just received
one of his cards, along with a message.
Tsk. So what exactly did the message say?
It says, "Tonight, I come for the left of
'La Berceuse' the first copy will soon be mine."
It can't be...
It's possible he means the left painting in the triptych.
If it's a first copy then...
The rest of you sit tight for a few minutes.
Wait! Adviser!
Kid's message is not talking about the
"Sunflowers" that we have in the safe down stairs.
The left of "La Berceuse".
The first copy. He's referring to Van
Gogh's fifth "Sunflowers" not the second.
Huh?
And as you're aware, Van Gogh's fifth
"Sunflowers" isn't kept in some far off country.
It's right here in one of our museums.
The Sompo Japan Nipponkoa Art Museum, huh?
Art museum?
We're gonna get to see paintings!
It's gonna be fun!
Thank you for supporting us with your patronage.
It's my first time in a museum.
Really? Me too!
Ah! So high!
What a view, huh?
Look! You can see Bell Tree Tower from here!
Wow! That's cool!
Didn't you guys come to see the "Sunflowers"? - Huh?
Oh yeah! That's right!
Okay, you guys! Let's go see the "Sunflowers"!
Hey, stop! There's no running in here!
Ah, jeez. Do they actually have
any interest in the "Sunflowers"?
You know, they're not the ones
who were really interested in it.
Isn't that right?
That's right! We've got to
see it before everyone else gets
a chance at the "Sunflowers Long for Japan" exhibition.
Sounds like a plan...
But still, I didn't expect that
you'd be tagging along with us.
Weren't you supposed to bet that meeting?
Well six of the samurai are already going to be attend.
It's more important to figure out what Kid's plan is.
Huh?
It's just that he's never shown interest in
anything but jewels before. Something's different.
So you decided to come see the target,
Van Gogh's "Sunflowers," for yourself, huh?
That's right.
I wanna learn more about what it is he's after...
I'm hoping to be able to figure out
his motive, and anticipate his next move.
Huh? Are we done already?
But which one's the "Sunflowers"?
Look, there it is!
Which one's the "Sunflowers".
It's this one right? The one in the middle?
Woah..!
So pretty!
It's incredible...
Hey, what's so great about this painting anyway?
You guys... Keep your voices
down, or they're gonna kick you out.
Okay...
Sorry if they were bothering you.
Not at all.
Ooh! So this right here is Van
Gogh's fifth "Sunflowers" isn't it?
Hey, Doctor! Come on!
Wow it looks truly wonderful!
Huh. Oh, I do apologize!
Oh, it's all right.
All right! We saw the "Sunflowers"!
So that's it then?
Awesome, let's go buy some souvenirs!
Yeah!
Come on, Doc! Let's go!
All right.
For crying out loud. Why did they even come here?
Excuse me, young Miss.
Hm?
It's not only the "Sunflowers"
you're interested in, is it?
Huh?
Ah... Mmh.
I'm sorry for bringing it up.
It's just you reminded me of myself when I was your age.
Oh...
Do you visit the museum often, ma'am?
Yes, every day.
Huh...
You must really love Van Gogh's "Sunflowers" huh?
Ah, I do.
But it's a different one I love...
Ah...
This way!
Well, looks okay to me?
Pops! What's going on?
Aah!
What on earth are you doing here?!
What about you?
Good timing, boy! You should join us.
How about it?
It's not Kid, is it?
Mhm. His next target's right here.
Adviser Suzuki, would you mind
not discussing that right here?
Yes, of course.
You can see for yourselves that
nothing is out of the ordinary.
Now, our presence here may be
a disturbance to our patrons.
We should continue this discussion in the reception room.
Sounds good to me, let's start making our way back.
Haibara! I'm gonna stay here with Pops and
the others. You head back with everybody else.
Also!
I've got you. The other kids won't know a thing.
Great. Thanks a lot.
I see he trusts you, doesn't he?
Hm... Our relationship isn't
exactly what you think it , ma'am.
No!
Your gaze is the same as mine was some 70 years ago.
It's just like what the sunflower
says to the sun, in it's own way.
"You are the only one I see."
But if all you do is look and take no
action, then that's something you'll regret.
As I now do.
You realize how much someone
means to you only after they're gone.
Just like that "Sunflowers."
Hey Ai! It's time to go!
Huh?
Where'd Conan go?
He had to go.
Huh?!
Something urgent must have comet up.
Not again?
I bet he's just in the restroom!
- Thanks for the advice. - Ah.
I'll try not to have a single regret.
It's too bad you didn't have more
time with the painting, huh, Doctor?
Oh, it's okay! This whetted my
appetite for the "Sunflowers" exhibition!
Oh, Kiyosuke...
What makes you think this
letter that Kid the Phantom Thief
sent you was referring to the "Sunflowers" at this museum?
The title "La Berceuse" translates
to "Woman who rocks the cradle."
It really has nothing to do with "Sunflowers."
The only things that are important is when he's
referring to "the left of" and "his first copy."
"The left" probably refers to that part of the triptych.
Did you just say it's a triptych?
Yeah. When three paintings come together to form one work.
Thanks. We're well aware of that.
Uuh....
But how exactly does that idea
connect, "La Berceuse" to "Sunflowers"?
Well, that... Uh, what was it again?
Get your act together! You're
supposed to be a samurai, remember?
Why don't we have Koji Azuma explain? He's the one
that deciphered the note for us in the first place.
He did figure it all out! Think you can handle it?
Yes, sir!
As Detective Mori was saying, if we assume
the triptych interpretation is correct then,
we can imagine "La Berceuse" at the center of one.
Now which paintings would be on either side?
Well, "Sunflowers."
Right. In a letter Van Gogh
sent to his younger brother Theo,
he even included an illustration,
of the triptych as a whole.
So there can be no doubt as to what Kid meant.
And if we set up the paintings like in the illustration,
the third and seventh are on the right,
and the fourth, fifth, or sixth are on the left.
Out of the paintings on the left, the first copy of
"Sunflowers" that Van Gogh painted is the fifth one.
The one which is currently on display in this museum.
Now I get it. Then Kid may have set his sights
on the "Sunflowers" in this museum after all.
All right then, what are our
options? What can we do about it?
Kid's letter revealed that he'll be breaking in tonight!
We've got to get the "Sunflowers"
somewhere safe immediately!
Right this minute? Preposterous!
Not to worry.
We'll explain the situation to our
patrons and close the museum early.
Thank you so much for your cooperation.
All right, let's go. Slowly, slowly. Good.
I feel rather useless just standing here. Can't we help?
Good question.
Ishimine's Cheetah Transport really is fast.
They did all this in only half an hour.
And we've got an hour before sunset.
Looks like we'll be done just in time.
All right!
There you go. Slowly. Just like that.
Are you sure there isn't any
way we can help you with this?
Uh... Let's see.
You can help bring that lid over there?
That way we can quickly wrap this up.
You got it. Hey Natsumi, help me with the lid.
Okay.
Uh... May I give you a hand?
Wait. We can handle it.
Mr. Ishimine wouldn't want anyone
who's not on the team handling it.
Good point. We do appreciate the thought.
Ah, of course.
Ready? We'll lift on three.
It's ready to go.
Good work.
We've brought the lid over.
Thanks for the help. We'll take care of it from here.
Don't you think it's about time
we made sure the safe is secure?
I like that idea.
Director! Can I have a moment of your time?
Kid left a clue saying he'll show up tonight,
so I'm sure he'll take a shot at that safe.
Ah! Sorry!
No problem. Let's keep go.
Yes sir.
Huh? Wait!
I see something under the lid!
Shut up, brat!
We're running behind as it is,
can't you just behave yourself?
But it looks like there's a Kid Card in there!
Huh?
Hold on, lift that lid up.
Yes, sir!
Huh?
Uh... Huh?
It is a card! Could this be...
Let me see that, Natsumi.
Here.
No doubt about it. It's Kid's Card all right.
"I took the 'Sunflowers' off
your hands. Kid the Phantom Thief."
He says that he took it...
But the "Sunflowers" has been here the whole time.
Is that all?
Is anything else written on the card?
Hm.
Wait, what do you mean?
Don't tell me the "Sunflowers"
we have here is already a...
Do you mean it's a fake?!
Hmph.
I can't believe Kid would lie
about when he was going to appear.
Yeah. The Kid I know would never do anything like that.
They're right, something's definitely wrong here.
He's nothing but a thief.
He'll stop at nothing to get what ever he wants.
Even if that means murdering those that get in his way.
- Huh?
So what's the verdict?
If this is a fake, it's an extremely well made forgery.
It's difficult to accurately appraise it without my gear.
Ah... Yes, I see.
Would it be possible for me to take
the painting with me for a little while?
I would be able to do a more thorough
appraisal back at my company's studio.
Yes, of course.
Since it's possible he switched the real one with a fake,
I shouldn't have any trouble
getting approval from my boss.
No need to go through all that trouble, Director.
What on earth is the meaning of this?
You can't push us around like that!
Hm? What the... Kid the Phantom Thief!
No way! This appraisal, it was Kid's trap!
Believe me, this "Sunflowers" is the
real deal. You can bet your life on it.
Why you! You trickster, you deceived all of us!
Aah! No!
Huh?
Mr. Azuma! Ms. Miyadai!
Stop standing around, he's got the "Sunflowers"!
Somebody catch him!
What?
He took it?!
Come back here, Kid!
This is Nakamori! Kid snatched the "Sunflowers" and fled!
He'll likely show up on the roof! Be on guard! Roger!
Kid spotted! He's on the very top of the roof!
Hmph.
We can't let him get away!
Ugh... If only I had my gun.
Kid the Phantom Thief has
launched multiple flying objects!
We've lost sight of him!
Are you kidding?! Find him!
Hey, get a load of that!
That one!
Argh... He's getting away!
Where is he? - Huh?
I'm afraid it's too late.
Kid... Is he even human?
He stole it tonight, just like he said he would...
This is the card Kid left in my pocket,
when he revealed himself and stole the painting.
"I'll sell you the "Sunflowers" back
for the low, low price of ten billion yen."
"Let's meet in room 1412 of the
Touto Plaza Hotel in two hours."
"Have the cash ready in all old
bills. Lay the bills on top of the bed."
"If you can't do this, then
no deal. Kid the Phantom Thief."
Ten billion yen in two hours!
So Kid was after money this
whole time, not the paintings...
But I just don't understand why he's changed this much?
There must be a reason.
Unless, it's not really him?
There's no way the museum can prepare
ten billion yen in the space of two hours!
There's only one person in Japan who could come up with
a ridiculous sum like that in such a short amount of time.
Hmm, all right. I guess I could put the money up.
You would do that?!
On one condition.
As soon as your "Sunflowers" is recovered,
I get to put it on display in my exhibit.
Of course.
As long as we could really get it back,
I'm sure my boss would agree to those terms.
Would you be willing to use your position here to convince
the owners of the other five paintings to join us?
Yes, of course. I'll do what ever I can!
Oh, that's great!
All right, we've got a deal.
Let's head to the hotel. On the double.
Right.
As soon as you're ready director, meet us over there.
I will!
Will you be going ahead with the police, Charlie?
Actually I have something important to get.
Something important?
Yeah. It'll be just the thing to help me take down Kid.
All right. Just make sure you
return in time for the exchange.
You can rest assured. I'll definitely be back in time.
Well um, if possible, I may need one more favor from you.
Hm, another? Out with it.
I know someone who would love to be
invited to your Sunflowers exhibition.
Who would that be?
An elderly lady who's been coming to this museum just
about every day since we put "Sunflowers" on display.
Oh, that lady was here today too, wasn't she?
Yes, that's correct.
It must mean a lot to her. She
doesn't look at any other paintings.
She just gazes at "Sunflowers" for
hours with a sad look in her eyes.
It's done.
I won't forget this!
It's me. I'm gonna be needing it, after all.
Are you sure?
Even having one in your possession
in this country makes you a criminal.
I know.
But I can't let a terrorist
that blew up an airplane get away.
Hmph. Fine, I'll have one ready soon.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Bring it to the parking lot behind
the Touto Plaza Hotel in an hour.
You got it.
This is the entrance lobby. All clear!
Emergency stairs. Nothing suspicious to report.
There's no way we'll have everything ready at this rate!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
How's the security working, Inspector?
We have police officers covering every exit.
That doesn't do us any good if he's already in the hotel.
Even if he is, we'll make sure to catch him this time!
The only way out for him is in handcuffs!
Hurry! There's no time!
Bring it in already!
Put it here, quickly!
So um... Can we even negotiate under these circumstances?
We're just following Kid's
instructions. We have no choice.
Now don't talk to me unless it's absolutely necessary.
If he realizes we're here, the whole deal is kaput.
Right....
OK keep going.
Hurry... Quick, hurry! We don't have time!
I don't get it. Is it really necessary
to put all the money on display like that?
What else could we do? Those were Kid's instructions.
W-Woah!
Quiet down! This is serious!
Uh, Haha...
You want to see the monitor, little guy?
Uh, yeah.
Hold on.
Hm.
There you go.
Thanks Mister! That was nice of you!
You need to help us with this...
Huh?
I couldn't help noticing that you're a
pretty sharp and insightful young man.
It's obvious they don't call
you the Kid Catcher for nothing.
Uh... I just got lucky.
I'm still an elementary school student, you know?
That doesn't really matter to me.
Let me know if you find something, okay?
Okay.
Thieves usually demand that their money be
deposited directly into an overseas bank account.
The fact that he demanded it
in cash must mean something...
Wh-What? - Huh?
The media's here?! How the heck did that happen?
We're supposed to be the only
ones who know about this deal!
I know, but newspapers and TV
stations just keep pouring in!
The press are everywhere. It's gonna
get out of control here in the parking lot!
They're already reporting live in front of the hotel!
We're at the Touto Plaza Hotel.
According to Kid the Phantom Thief,
a deal between him and Mr. Suzuki
will be taking place here tonight.
Kid, he's using the media to turn this
into a circus! It's going to be chaos!
Inspector.
Huh?
If Kid's the one who alerted the media, there's no reason
for him to call off the deal just because they showed up.
Time's running out, we have to hurry!
Forget about putting the money on the bed!
There's no choice... Our times up.
You can just leave the suitcases open!
Everyone, out of there now!
Hey, don't worry. We'll be right across the hall.
Please, just stay right where you are!
Woah! Ah!
Hurry!
Ugh... Why's this room got to be so hot?
Can I at least open a window?
Please hang in there.
We don't know if Kid's going to come in through the door.
Oh boy...
We pulled out from all areas!
Ok, good work!
All teams, stand by where you
are until further instruction.
Knowing Kid, he's got something up his sleeve.
I've got to figure out what he
has planned, before the deal starts.
Huh?!
Hold on, something's change.
It's not the same as it was before.
No way! I have to hurry!
Huh?
Damn!
He took the master key!
Hup!
Damn it! I don't have time for this!
Get down here!
Kid Catcher! - Huh?
Hey! What's going on?
Just get in!
Okay, now explain.
The water level in the Director's
plastic bottle suddenly went up.
The atmospheric pressure must be rising in there.
Why would he cause something like that?
I don't know.
But if we don't get the atmospheric pressure
back to normal fast. Score one for the Kid.
Hey, hey, hey! What are they doing there?!
Are they trying to blow the whole operation?!
There's only 20 seconds until Kid will be there!
Damn it!
The air pressure's pushing the door shut from inside!
Those two are gonna ruin everything!
It's too late, there's less than ten seconds left.
We'll just have to keep going.
Damn.
Five seconds left...
Four, three, two, one, zero!
Woah! Aah! What's happening?!
What's that?
Is that Kid? Did Kid appear?
I'm opening it now..!
Right!
Aah!
Hm...
Hm?
Aah! Ugh...
Ah...
There's Kid!
Hmph.
Huh?!
Kid the Phantom Thief, damn you!
It's Kid!
The deal between Kid and the Suzuki Group really happened!
He escaped!
Are you all right, sir?
Uh... Yeah...
Did Kid even bring back the "Sunflowers"?
I don't know.
Huh?! Hey Charlie, over there!
Look at that painting!
How could you?! You morons screwed everything Argh...
Charlie! Where is he? What happened to Kid?
Well, he got away.
Then... The "Sunflowers"?
Don't worry. The "Sunflowers" is safe.
Ooh!
Ah!
It's the "Sunflowers"!
You got it back!
Yeah, but at what cost...
Who cares about that? We got it!
Let's announce this to the press conference!
Adviser Suzuki!
Please tell us again about your victorious
showdown against Kid the Phantom Thief!
You have nothing to fear from Kid!
The owners of the other "Sunflowers"
don't have to worry either!
I don't know... It's all too good to be true.
Everyone's talking about how
"Sunflowers" the international masterpiece,
has twice been saved by Kid the Phantom Thief's grasp.
Mr. Jirokichi Suzuki's pet project,
Hey, look at that.
I'd really love to see that with you.
Oh, you mean the sunflowers thing, right?
The rest of the paintings in
Van Gogh's "Sunflowers" Seriously,
are being gathered here in Japan, for the exhibit.
Our special guests today are the people behind
the the aforementioned Sunflowers exhibition.
Here with us, the Suzuki Group's senior adviser,
Jirokichi Suzuki, and his niece, Sonoko Suzuki.
Let's see what they have to
say about the upcoming exhibition.
The exhibition will be held at our Lake Rock Art Museum.
I don't believe I've heard of that one.
That's because it's a brand new art museum
constructed specially for this exhibition.
Oh, that sounds intriguing!
We've reviewed the entire design from top to bottom,
making sure each masterpiece is displayed properly.
With the most robust, impenetrable
security system imaginable.
Aah.
Let's take a look at a preview of the museum.
Ms. Suzuki, would you please describe what we're seeing?
The Lake Rock Art Museum has been established at the
site of a sprawling limestone cave owned by our company.
The eight story structure has exhibits on every floor.
Each of the seven "Sunflowers" will
be displayed on a different floor.
So our guests can take their
time viewing them, one by one.
And then, as our guests make their way to
the lowest floor, which is deep underground,
A special elevator will have
moved each of the "Sunflowers",
from their original location,
to be displayed in an eighth room.
While waiting for the elevator that
will take them to the roof top exit,
guests will be treated to a view of
all seven "Sunflowers" finally together.
I get it!
At first, the paintings are
set up to be viewed separately.
That way the guests can marvel at the intricacies of
each individual painting. Was that what you had in mind?
Of course! But also, it's perfectly secure.
If the various sensors notice even the slightest change,
the paintings are immediately
sealed in fire and waterproof cases.
So there's no danger of them
being harmed by flames or flooding.
And even if someone did try to steal a painting,
the security system would activate, closing off all exits.
So let's say Kid the Phantom Thief
disguised himself to blend in with the crowd,
he'd never be able to get away.
Our safety measures are flawless as well.
The security system will never shut
down the elevator that goes to the exit,
and will always provide lighting for safety.
I understand, it can produce its own power?
That is right!
And we have some footage of that
as well. How about we take a look?
Water's sucked from the lake that's in front of
the museum into the tanks on the top most floor.
This allows us to generate hydraulic
power by using the difference in elevation.
That way we can direct our guests to the roof top exit.
While the "Sunflowers" take a special
route that delivers them to a storehouse.
Which will provide emergency escape access.
Wow, you have thought of everything!
You've made quite the impregnable
fortress for the "Sunflowers"!
That's right!
At the same time, people can see our great treasures,
the seven "Sunflowers" in this fantastic environment!
At the "Sunflowers Long for Japan" Exhibit!
The "Sunflowers Long for Japan" Exhibition will be open
to the public for one month, with only 100 guests per day.
So when will you be opening the
raffle for tickets to the event?
Right this very moment!
Seriously?
Just head on over to our website
and you can register right now!
There'll be a lot of competition for
tickets cause the raffle is open world wide.
Okay! Don't let this opportunity pass you up!
Aw, I didn't get it!
I thought for sure we'd win
by using Doc's internet, but...
What the heck? None of us got a ticket!
Doc, what happens when you win?
Anything cool? We just keep losing...
First it'll take a photo for facial recognition purposes,
then it will display your registration
ID, and give you a unique PIN.
Then you'll enter that info into the application screen,
and get your tickets a few days later.
Doctor, how do you know that?
Wait! You mean...
That's right. I'm a lucky winner! Hehehehahaha!
That's a really creepy laugh.
Huh?!
You actually got one?! Please
let me have it, I really wanna go!
Me, too!
Me, three!
That ticket's mine alone!
How immature of you, Doctor. - Oh?
Yeah Doc, immature!
Childish even!
Yeah, childish!
Well, I don't know...
Let's use a quiz to decide who gets it!
Huh?!
It's multiple choice, so you get only
one chance to answer as a group. Okay?
Yeah!
I'm in!
This is gonna be fun!
Then it's a showdown!
So, what does a sun-loving sunflower, in a
field of sunflowers, hate more than anything?
Is it one? Spiders.
Or two, is it snakes?
Or, three? Scorpions!
So it's spiders, snakes, or scorpions, huh?
Yeah. So then the answer is...
Shh!
You two don't get to answer!
I've got it!
I know, I know!
Me, too!
The answer is number three, scorpions!
Huh?
That's wrong, Genta!
Huh? But scorpions are poisonous.
Spiders and snakes can be poisonous too!
Are you serious?!
The correct answer...
Would be number one, spiders!
Spider in Japanese is "kumo".
Ugh, "kumo" also means cloud in Japanese!
The sunflower loves the sun, so it hates anything
that would block it like clouds! That's why it's spiders!
What the heck? So poison doesn't matter at all.
And so, I'm not giving my ticket
to anyone. You all failed the quiz!
And so we all want to see the Sunflowers exhibition.
Is there any way..?
We really wanna see it!
Pretty please?
We'll do anything!
Hmm...
All right then.
Huh?
Oh yeah!
Are you serious?!
However...
I will need you to help me out, more than ever before!
It's on you Mr. Kid Catcher.
Adviser Suzuki.
Hm?
We really need to get back to that meeting.
Um... Yes, that's right.
Okay everybody, I'll give you all a ride back home.
Okay!
Don't forget to save a couple extra
tickets for Ran and Shinichi, uncle.
Right. Ishimine.
Please go on ahead without me.
Yes, sir. Let me know when you've chosen
the time and the route for each vehicle.
Wait, then how are you going to get them to the museum?
Even if Lake Rock's security is perfect,
transporting them is the most dangerous part.
You don't have to worry. We've got a
lot of dummy transport vehicles prepared.
And I'm the only one who knows which vehicles have them.
Ah, great. Then it's definitely in good hands.
But if you're gonna use that thing, remember this...
No matter how just you think you
might be, no life should be cut short.
That's very true.
But lofty ideals like that will
eventually come back to bite you in the end.
The same way that Kid the Phantom Thief has.
Conan, what are you doing? We're leaving!
Everyone else is already in the car!
Coming!
Hm...
Blegh!
She sure doesn't like me, huh?
E-Excuse me.
We've just received a package
with a letter addressed to you, sir.
Ah, thank you.
Let's see, now why was it sent here, not the company?
Will you keep it down, Lupin!
Always wanting attention!
Huh?! H-How can it be?
From Kid?!
Please show me.
There's no mistake, it is a Kid card. But what's that?
Well it's wrapped like a present, but...
What is it, Lupin?
Sir! Stay behind me.
Get away from there Lupin, now!
What the...
This stench and ignition speed... Phosphine?
It's extremely volatile! Everyone, get out of here!
You all right, Charlie?!
Yeah, it's safe now.
Get Inspector Nakamori on the phone, now!
Yes, sir!
Not a good idea sir. This was
designed to do more than just kill you.
Huh? Contacting the police could delay the exhibit.
Worst-case scenario, it could even be canceled.
He is right. Charlie brings up a really good point.
Understood.
This goes for all of you. Not a
word of this to anybody, got it?
Yes sir, understood.
Ooh, good job using your nose, Lupin.
Charlie, we should seal this room. Just in case.
Yeah.
Hmm...
Kid the Phantom Thief. You've revealed your true colors.
You won't get any mercy from me.
All right! All right!
Just how many dummy trucks did Suzuki hire, exactly?
About what happened earlier. Your thoughts?
My thoughts?
What's his motive?
If for any reason they decide to cancel the exhibition...
The second and fifth "Sunflowers" will
be released from Lake Rock Art Museum.
Giving Kid another chance to steal them.
If that's true, then he could just
take them when the exhibit's over.
Why would Kid the Phantom Thief be in such a hurry?
Hmm...
Welcome everyone, to the grand opening of our "Japan
Longs for Sunflowers" Exhibition. Thank you for coming!
Let me introduce the man behind the exhibition!
Let's all welcome, Mr. Jirokichi Suzuki!
Well, we're here because we're captivated by "Sunflowers!
Are you excited?
Excellent! Then the "Japan Longs for Sunflowers" is open!
We will now begin to admit our guests.
Please wait your place in line, with tickets ready.
Excuse me. I'm Ran Mori.
Okay, I'll just need to see your tickets.
There are six of us.
Looks like you're all good to go.
Please enter this way.
We get to go in it first!
Awesome!
Hurry up, Ran! Come on, let's go!
You're all here together,right?
Yup!
Please insert all your tickets right here into the gate.
Sure!
... your ticket ready as you move forward!
Everything going smoothly with the admissions?
Yes, sir.
And the display and security systems
are also in perfect working order.
Mm. I want everyone besides Goto to return to their posts.
Right!
Uh, wait! Can he operate all this by himself?
Stop worrying! Everything here is automated.
Besides, very few people know where this
room is. Let alone, have any access to it.
Well, I guess that's true.
Gah!
Now what's wrong?
N-Nothing...
You don't know how to calm down, do you?
That teen detective's ate exhibit, too?
Goto, do you notice anyone acting suspiciously?
Just a minute ago, the initial group took the
elevator, to the first "Sunflowers" exhibit room.
But one of them went straight
for the second "Sunflowers" exhibit.
I'll bring up the image.
It's weird that they went straight to the second painting.
Let's zoom in a bit on that one.
Goto?
Huh..? Right!
What the... Is she crying?
I guess she really wanted to see the second "Sunflowers."
Don't worry sir. She won't be causing any trouble.
Let's focus on fig Kid.
Right, right. Of course, let's go back.
Yes, sir.
They're beautiful!
Uuh, but I don't think these are real, Ayumi?
If they were real flowers, they'd wilt.
Well I don't care if they're fake, but they
could at least make them smell better than this.
It's that kinda weird.
These were Natsumi's idea, but she never
mentioned she'd be giving them a scent?
But never mind that! I wanna go see the second
"Sunflowers"! We should go check that out next.
Great idea!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Huh?
Security cameras?
They've got them all over the place!
Conan? Come on, we need to go!
Coming!
Look, there it is!
No way!
Awesome!
I can't believe we're finally seeing it!
Huh..?
Ran!
Huh?
I just saw Shinichi!
No way!
Shinichi..!
Sonoko, is he here?
Sorry. I lost sight of him.
You sure he was really here?
Now that you mention it...
I'm not sure. It must have been someone else.
I hope so, but...
Considering the high security at this place...
It'd be impossible to enter in disguise
because of all the bag checks and x-rays.
Meaning the only way Kid could enter...
Would be by impersonating me, since
our features happen to be similar.
Hmph.
Huh?
Hm... What is this?
A Kid card!
So he is impersonating me!
Are you okay?
Huh?
I couldn't find him anywhere.
Sorry. I guess it was somebody else, huh?
Hey, Ran! Sonoko!
Lower your voice, Conan!
I need to see security!
Huh?
Look, a Kid card! He's already here in Lake Rock!
Kid the Phantom Thief!
What does all this even mean?
If we assume it's about the "Sunflowers"...
Van Gogh painted 15 sunflowers
in a couple of those paintings.
The fourth, the fifth, and the sixth
paintings all have 15 sunflowers in them?
So is there a painting with just 14?
There's none that I can think of.
No!
See, there's a theory that for Van Gogh
the numbers 14 and 15 have the same meaning.
In a letter to his brother Theo, Van Gogh wrote that
one if his paintings with 15 flowers actually had 14.
So if that's the number of sunflowers, what's
the meaning behind all those numbers after it?
Just doesn't make sense.
Scholars are confident that there was
more to his paintings than met the eye.
Including the 14 sunflowers.
Which are said to represent,
Theo, Gauguin, and the 12 apostles.
Yeah! I bet that's exactly it!
How do you figure that?
Let's take another look at Kid's card.
Eleven people plus 1 person equals Christ's 12 apostles.
Plus two more, they're often
thought to be Theo and Gauguin.
That makes 14 people all together.
And when he said there were actually 15 sunflowers,
the idea is that Van Gogh was
including himself as the extra person.
That interpretation's a possibility,
but how exactly does this theory
of yours tie into the equation?
Why did Kid have to make it so
complicated? This is gonna take us all night!
I have no idea, but how do we even
know that Kid intended it to be a clue?
Hmm...
Clue or not.
What's the point of this Kid card anyway?
Let's worry about catching him first
so we can ask about it face-to-face!
With your help, we can lock
Kid up. Right here in Lake Rock!
Ah... Ok!
Goto? Let's evacuate all guests and employees at once.
Right.
But sir! You're closing the exhibit
when it's been open for less than an hour?
If you do this, you'll have a riot on your hands.
Don't you worry.
Hm?
Anything can happen during a grand opening.
That's why we only invited company
connections and Sonoko's friends.
Adviser.
Huh?
We'll take charge of security, just as you planned.
Mm. I'm counting on all of you, you're my Seven Samurai.
I see. Looks like you were
ready for an emergency after all.
All right. Let's follow through with the plan and stay
in contact with each other in case we leave our posts.
Understood.
All right everyone, there's an issue with the display.
Please proceed to the elevators, we
do apologize for any inconvenience.
I bet Kid's here somewhere.
Then this is a job for the Detective Boys!
No, it isn't.
Huh?
This time, Kid's dangerous.
Don't you dare leave my side, got it?
Fine!
All right then, how's the guest evacuation coming along?
Smoothly, sir.
It's just taking longer than
we expected due to the x-rays.
Then eliminate the X-ray inspection.
Allow each guest to exit after returning their bags.
You're willing to let Kid escape that easily? Seriously?!
Oh, calm down.
He isn't the kind of thief who'd
escape when the prize was in front of him.
You know that as well as I do.
Well, I guess he wouldn't leave the building so quickly.
Exactly. So we'll seal up all the
escape routes. That way he can't get away.
The only way he could've gotten
in here is if he wasn't in disguise,
and that means he wouldn't have his usual bag of tricks.
We have Kid the Phantom Thief right where we want him!
Hm.
Besides that, I've got my 12 trustworthy associates
watching out for him throughout the building.
Twelve trustworthy people.
I see. He didn't write the "12 apostles"
as "12 people," but as "11 people plus 1."
And that must mean...
Mr. Jirokichi!
Hm?
- You have 12 trustworthy people,
that's the same number as Christ's
apostles referenced on Kid's card, right?
I couldn't stop wondering why Kid
didn't just write "12 people" instead.
Maybe there was one person who was left out?
Oh... What about, uh... Judas!
And Judas was a traitor!
So Kid's trying to tell us something! He must be trying
to show us that there's a traitor hidden in our ranks!
Wait, you're saying someone other
than Kid is targeting the "Sunflowers?
Adviser Suzuki, would you mind if I took
another look at the profiles of your Seven Samurai?
What if he's trying to plant seeds of doubt, to
disrupt our security and turn us against each other?
Well we don't have to led on
that we're investigating them.
Hmm. In that case, there'd be
no harm in looking into them.
Go on.
Got it.
All guests and employees have been evacuated, sir.
All right. Make sure all the exits are sealed.
Yes, sir. Sealing the exits.
Please keep moving forward! Please keep moving!
Lake Rock Art Museum is being
evacuated en masse as we speak.
The question is, what went wrong?
Neither visitors, nor staff, seem to have any info.
The only places left with lax video
surveillance are the server room and power plant.
But only a select few know that those are our weak spots.
I'm gonna test it out.
Hey, this is Charlie. I checked
out all the security blind spots.
There's no sign of Kid anywhere in the building.
Roger.
The buildings been fully evacuated,
please return to your posts.
Hmph.
It's almost time...
Hm?
Ah!
Kid! Stop!
Huh?!
What the?!
A blackout?!
It's okay! Activate the auxiliary generator!
Right!
We need to see the "Sunflowers"
I'm on it!
Monitors are online!
They're all here! The paintings are secure.
We need this monitor on too.
Megure's sending me more information!
Right!
The light!
Goto! What in the world is going on out there?!
There's trouble in the electrical control room!
Whatever's happened has caused the lights,
elevators, and security cameras to malfunction.
I'll put extra security on the second and fifth paintings.
Kid's still here. He must be
hiding somewhere in the building!
Not necessarily. It may not be Kid, after all.
Wait, what makes you think that?
While I was going back over the Seven
Samurai's files, I found something odd.
What?
What was odd?
We know that Van Gogh painted the
seven "Sunflowers" in Arles, France.
The suspect has a twin brother
who died there six months ago.
The local police said he died
of a gunshot wound in the chest.
and ruled it as suicide, since he had
traces of gunpowder smoke on his right hand.
So what was the name of the victim?
Koichi Azuma.
Azuma? Really?
Yes. Koji Azuma, our restoration specialist's brother.
It wasn't suicide. I killed Koichi.
Wait, isn't that him on one of the monitors?
With the second painting!
Azuma! Why? He was your brother.
Yes, that's true. But Koichi betrayed
me after we found the Ashiya "Sunflowers."
We had been searching for sot long.
He found the Ashiya "Sunflowers"?
What are you talking about?
That "Sunflowers" was destroyed during an air raid.
That's not what actually happened. - Huh?
True, there was indeed an air raid.
The city was an inferno, burning with hellfire.
My grandfather worked as a carpenter for the
businessman who bought Ashiya's "Sunflowers".
To burglar-proof the painting,
Grandfather fastened it firmly to the wall.
When the air raid came, he rushed
into his burning house to save it.
Aah!
Ugh.
Azuma!
My lady!
Azuma! What are you...
Stay back!
No..!
My lady! Take care of the "Sunflowers"!
No! Azuma!
Watch out!
We need to get out of here, my lady!
No!
Azuma..!
Even if we lose this damn war...
I'll never let them have our "Sunflowers"!
Azuma...
Azuma!
My lady, we have to go!
Japan, our home land... Will one day
have a place to display our own masterpieces.
So people all over the world...
could see these "Sunflowers"...
We grew up hearing that story from our father.
After he died, we continued
searching for the Ashiya "Sunflowers."
Our only clue was from the servant. To
whom my grandfather entrusted the painting.
So a servant had it?
He kept is safe from the GHQ.
To conceal it, he made the painting look like a
counterfeit, which helped him smuggle it into Europe.
S-So you're saying the "Sunflowers"
I bought at the auction...
Is the Ashiya "Sunflowers"?!
Then it wasn't destroyed!
That's right. My brother and I
finally discovered it's hiding place.
The Ashiya "Sunflowers", secretly tucked
away in the attic of an old home in Arles.
Except, finding the "Sunflowers" after
having searched for so many years...
Had a dramatic effect on my brother.
He said the "Sunflowers" should
be left in Van Gogh's beloved Arles.
He even started suggesting, that
we should just destroy it there.
I simply couldn't forgive my brother for
betraying our father and grandfather's wish.
The argument became a struggle.
He wanted to shoot the painting.
The gun we kept for protection went off...
K-Koichi...
Stay back... -
Koichi!
You need to get out of here!
But I..!
Just go!
Ugh...
So that's why, when I learned of this Japanese
Sunflowers exhibit, I offered to join as a curator.
Because of that choice, I've witnessed
the Ashiya "Sunflowers" returned to Japan.
Grandfather's dying wish came true.
After this exhibition was over,
I was going to turn myself in.
This is a little early, but...
It all makes sense.
Megure from the Metro PD is on his way here now.
You're turning yourself in?
Yes!
Of course!
But I'm not the one you're after. I
had nothing to do with all of this.
All right, then who did?!
Wait, the sunflowers are on fire!
What are you playing at?!
They're literally on fire!
The fire's here too!
We need to put it out!
Hey! What's going on here?!
What happened to the "Sunflowers" heat sensors?
The temperature's shooting up!
There may actually be a fire, sir!
Can't we extinguish it?!
No. The fire suppression system is down!
There's nothing else to do! We need to evacuate everyone!
Get us access to the roof immediately!
Yes, sir.
All right, let's go! Everybody follow me!
Come on, Conan!
Right!
Come on you need to hurry! The flames are already here!
I'm trying... Got it!
Huh?
All right kid, let's go. Hurry!
This way, over here!
Just keep running! Go, go, go!
Come on, hurry!
Is everyone all right?
Yeah, looks like we all made it.
You okay, Conan?
Yeah, I'm fine. But what about the "Sunflowers".
Safe. The emergency procedures should be working.
But "Sunflowers" numbers two ant five...
Don't worry they'll be all right.
But I know what I saw back there...
They were both still on display!
If we don't do something fast,
"Sunflowers" two and five will turn to ash!
What's the emergency?
Never mind. Just land.
Yes. sir.
According to Inspector Nakamori,
they'll bring Azuma out the rear entrance.
Hey, we're over here!
Ah!
Hurry!
Azuma's in Lieutenant
Charlie's custody!
What in the world is happening here?!
Sorry, but there's been a fire! We're
going to need an air evac out of here!
Got it!
We'll have to take the lead!
Yeah!
Huh? Conan..?
Don't tell me...
Come on!
This isn't good... If I don't
hurry, I'll burn with this painting!
Kid!
Huh?!
You?! What are you doing!
Let's just focus on the paintings!
Is the fifth "Sunflowers" also stuck?
No, I was able to get that one free
pretty easily. But I can't pry this one loose!
If we can't get this one moving
fast, the paints gonna melt!
Make some room!
Aah! Don't you idiot! This is a "Sunflowers"!
It's one of man kind's treasures!
Ugh!
Did we get it?!
Ow, hey! You aimed straight for my head!
This is no time to argue!
It didn't work. Now what?
Just how strong did the old man make this thing?
Conan?!
Urk!
Huh?
Shinichi!
It's true, you were here, after all!
Guys, what are you doing?! -
We have to get out of here right away!
Ran!
We're gonna need your help!
Uh... My help?
We can't get the "Sunflowers" to budge.
We need to destroy the wall to get it out of there!
But that's impossible!
Ran, you can do it.
Mm, I'll try. Stand back, Shinichi!
You too!
Please!
Ran!
Haah!
Yes!
I did it!
Good!
Now let's get go-... Hm?
Huh? Ah!
Ran!
Wait a second!
What are we gonna do Shinichi?!
It's okay. Just stand back.
Mm...
Hey Jii, can you hear me?
Stay calm! Do not panic!
Yes, understood.
Ran.
Ah..!
Hold on tight. And don't you dare let go!
Don't tell me..!
Woah!
Huh? What now?
The water tanks have broken open! Looks
like they're leaking all over the cliff!
With all that water, do you think the fires been put out?
Hey!
Have you guys seen Conan?
Wait, he's not with you guys?
I thought he'd be here!
Wait! Ran's missing too!
Figures! Like I'm not busy enough.
Now where did they run off to?
This whole time I thought they were right behind us.
Now she's not answering.
They might've already made it safely out of the
building! Should I go see if I could find them?
Yes, please.
We should help her look for them!
Yeah!
Kudo. Don't tell me you...
You all right, Detective?
Worry about Ran!
Ran! Wake up!
She just swallowed a bunch of water.
But she's gonna be okay in a second.
Hey, look!
Seems like the water pressure is dying down!
Then there's probably no more water left in the tanks!
We have to check the "Sunflowers"!
You knew what the culprit was planning all along?
Yeah. I knew all those sunflowers would act as a fuse.
And I figured the tube road could become an aqueduct.
So the person who suggested planting all
those sunflowers in the tube road is our culprit.
You got it. Sounds like you finally figured it out.
Now come on. Let's get out of here.
Okay, but how are we gonna do that?
We'll take the tube road to the top
floor, there should be an exit around there.
Then we can take an elevator shaft to the roof.
What was your original plan tot get out?
Hm?
You know, escape?
Hmph.
Come on, you wouldn't be here unless you had a way out.
I had an exit route through the cave. I new I
could fly to it and get out of here pretty easily.
Except I wouldn't be able to
reach it while carrying you and Ran.
Kid.
Hold on, if you knew the culprit's
plan, why didn't you stop it?
Well I only knew what they were planning, because
I managed to hack into their computer and steal it.
But I couldn't tell if they were working alone.
I was gonna try to fix the power,
but then Charlie found me and
started chasing me all over the place.
So I figured I'd give a certain
someone a heads up using a clue.
I just though you'd be able to solve it quicker than that.
Well, excuse me!
Hah. Wait here a second. I'll get my gear.
I'm gonna make sure it's feasible to
escape from the elevator shaft up ahead.
Meanwhile, you go on ahead and catch the one behind this.
All right.
Cause it'd be a pain if I fell for another cheap trick!
Hm!
Yeah.
Good luck, I'm counting on you to stop them!
Shinichi...
Ah.
Just hold on, Ran.
Huh... This isn't good.
It took too long for the fire to be put out,
and now the air pressure in the cave is too low.
We need to get out of here before this place collapses...
Please stand back, the gate is now opening.
Good! The "Sunflowers" are safe.
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Wait a minute! There are only six here!
Are you sure?!
It's true! We're missing one!
What is the meaning of this?!
Huh?! Where'd the second "Sunflowers" go?!
The Ashiya "Sunflowers" isn't here!
Oh, no!
Why? Why only the Ashiya Sunflowers ?
Don't worry!
Huh?!
That voice!
Shinichi Kudo?
Yeah. I put the Ashiya "Sunflowers" into
its protective case just a little while ago.
Who do you think you are?!
Mind your own damn business!
Calm down a minute, and listen to me.
I've been protecting the "Sunflowers" after all.
There's a traitor amongst you. I'd be
more worried about the Judas in your ranks.
Huh?! So one of them really is a traitor.
That's right, but you can rest easy.
I know who the Judas is.
Huh?
Yeah, but Azuma's already been arrested.
Koji Azuma isn't the traitor I'm talking about.
Makes sense. If you think about
it, the last thing that Azuma
wanted was for the Ashiya
"Sunflowers" to come to any harm.
Besides, when the sunflowers started
to burn, he was on camera talking to you.
That may be true, but...
I can't believe anyone here would be a traitor.
Yeah. We've done everything we
can to protect the "Sunflowers."
That's right, and Kid's the one who
suggested there even was a traitor.
It'd be down right crazy to believe
a thief's word. Especially right now.
Exactly!
We should just be relieved that all
the "Sunflowers" made it out safely.
Really, now? Is that how you feel?
Even though you were the one that lit the fuse?
What are you saying?
You were the one trying to destroy the Ashiya
"Sunflowers" and the fifth "Sunflowers" in that fire.
Destroying those two "Sunflowers" masterpieces
has been your goal from the very beginning.
That's just utter nonsense!
Why would I want to do something like that?!
All right then.
Let's go over the details, shall we?
After Kid the Phantom Thief
caused a ruckus at the auction,
they beefed up security. This prevented you
from getting your hands on the "Sunflowers."
Huh?
You gave up on destroying it in America,
but when you found it'd be flown to Japan,
you bribed one of the workers and planted
a bomb on the door near the cargo bay.
But Kid interfered there, too.
So you decided to change your target
from the second, to the fifth "Sunflowers."
Ugh.
Kid, figured that out pretty quickly,
So he sent a clue to Detective
Mori, resulting in heightened security.
Kid had foiled your plans twice in a
row. So to finally get the jump on him,
you stuck a fake Kid card in the
fifth "Sunflowers" transport box.
Your goal was to get it back to your studio.
Are you saying Kid played the villain
in order to protect the "Sunflowers"?
It's a lie! All these connections
are just your imagination!
I believe her! Natsumi loves Van
Gogh's "Sunflowers" more than anyone!
So there's no way she'd want to harm them!
Yeah. Besides, why would she
only want to destroy those two?
Good point, I still haven't figured out
why only those two paintings were her target.
This detective show is a farce!
Well, we'll be getting the truth
from Natsumi herself soon enough.
Allow me.
Natsumi, I heard you were the one who suggesting
decorating Lake Rock's tube
road with all those sunflowers.
Is that true?
Well, yes.
You used your position as an appraiser to get turpentine,
which is often used to restore paintings.
pouring it into the sunflower
gardens from the top floor down,
turned the whole place into a giant fuse.
The real traitor took advantage of this
situation. I had nothing to do with it!
How dare you try to pin this on me,
and with only circumstantial evidence!
Really now. I was hoping you'd confess, to be honest.
But if you need more proof,
then I'll show it to you later.
The files on your computer contain your
plan to destroy those two "Sunflowers".
I guess there's no point in continuing this charade.
So that's the real reason you're here, huh?
You only joined us because you wanted to
destroy the fifth and the Ashiya "Sunflowers."
That's right!
You see, Kid the Phantom Thief
just kept getting in the way,
so things didn't go exactly as I'd planned.
When Kid's interference proved to be too
much, you started a fire here at Lake Rock.
You wanted those two "Sunflowers" to turn to ash.
Yes. But it wasn't my intention to cause this much damage.
My plan was to create a blackout to use
as cover and dispose of the two Sunflowers.
Then it would have been all over.
But Kid and then a staff member got in my way.
I'll put extra security on the second and fifth paintings.
How did you tamper with the sunflowers?
Our security system would notice that something is wrong!
Hah, easy!
Huh?
It merely took covering them with Phosphine.
Wait! Phosphine.
It's a chemical that can spontaneously
combust at room temperature.
So you're the one who sent that gift and tried to kill me?
I see! If the sponsor died, the
opening would have to be delayed,
and the entire exhibition itself may even be canceled!
Why Natsumi?
Between this fire and the explosion on the plane...
One wrong move and you could've been killed!
Not to mention all of the innocent people.
That's just...
That's how much I love Van Gogh's "Sunflower!
I would rather die than let
those two counterfeits be displayed
next to masterpieces like Van Gogh's real "Sunflowers"!
Neither your actions, nor your motives truly add up.
There's a dissertation from the Art
Institute of Chicago that proves it...
The fifth "Sunflowers" is the genuine article.
Van Gogh and Gauguin split the
same canvas to make their paintings.
That's more than enough proof.
An appraiser like you should
know that much at the very least.
B-but I...
And that whole thing you said
about dying for true masterpieces?
Before you forced the plane down with your explosive,
and set this fire, you had already prepared
an escape route that would get you to safety.
Th-That was...
If you were really willing to die for your plan,
why didn't you stay behind to
guarantee Kid didn't put out the fire?
In the end, you're just a criminal,
who can't think of anyone but yourself.
You're no curator.
You had me fooled, Natsumi.
Time to take you in.
A woman obsessed with Van Gogh's paintings,
she had more faith in her own beliefs than
the truth of an appraisal, and turned to crime.
Sounds like you've got everything wrapped things up.
I do. Did you find a way out?
Yeah, but I'm the only one that can reach it.
So now what?
Should we call for help?
Not a good idea.
If someone tried to rescue us,
it could just make things worse.
Oh no!
Are you okay?
Yeah, but we need to get out of here!
I'm surprised we haven't already been crushed.
All it would take is a small hole in the
ceiling, to change the air pressure, an we'd be dead!
Hey, Kid!
Can you fly with just Ran?
No, you've got to be kidding!
Can you do it or not?!
Well? Tell me!
Hmph.
I could do it with Ran.
However, I'm not sure I can
keep airborne in a place with low
atmospheric pressure while
dodging all those falling rocks...
Ugh!
Ran!
Kid!
Ah! Ugh!
Save Ran!
Damn it! Stop trying to be cool.
Woah!
Ugh!
There's still a way out of here.
With this child's body...
Damn, at this rate we're gonna fall!
Where's the way out?
There it is!
Go!
This pint sized body should
fit into "Sunflowers" elevator.
Ran!
The Ashiya "Sunflowers"!
Oh no! The water tower...
We have to find those two, fast.
That looks dangerous!
Huh?, look!
No... They're not still in there, are they?
Woah that was close. I can't
believe we made it out of there.
Ugh... Shinichi?
You came to save me...
Well of course. You'll be safe with me.
Thank you...
Where are you going, Haibara?
Kid and Ran are in the air!
Huh?
Is she for real?!
Let's follow her!
Yeah!
Hey, Sonoko!
Huh?
Ai said Ran and Kid are flying.
Wait Ran and Kid are flying?
What the?
Damn it. That way's blocked, too?
Looks like I'm out of exit.
At this rate, the Ashiya "Sunflowers" and I are...
Are you serious?
Please tell me you were able to escape... Detective?
Ran!
Ran! Where are you?!
Ran! Ran, are you all right?
Ugh...
Oh, is that you Dad..?
Ran!
Are you hurt? Are you okay?!
Mmhm. Shinichi came and saved me...
Huh?!
Nuh-uh! Kid was the one that saved you.
On his glider! You were like whoosh!
You don't remember that?
Urk! Wait, you mean it was Kid?
But I thought for sure it was Shinichi...
So what happened to the brat? Where is he?
Huh?! Conan isn't here?
No. Kid was only carrying you, no one else.
Oh, no!
Then Conan's still...
No way!
Conan...
Damn!
Tsk. So much for escaping, I'm gonna
drown in less than a minute down here!
If I shoot the ball out, it
might be able to move this thing,
but it won't keep me from being submerged.
That's it! Submerged!
With this much water is pouring in, it
must mean I'm below the lake's war level!
So if I can use my fireworks ball to
change the direction it's collapsing,
the atmospheric pressure will fall out of balance...
It's a long shot but...
It might thrust me into the lake!
All right! Time to go!
Five, four, three...
two, one, zero!
Conan!
What are you doing, Conan!
Please find a way out!
Damn it, what the hell's he doing?
Conan!
Don't worry, he'll be okay...
Knowing Conan, I'm sure he...
Please, Conan. Make it out...
You can do it!
Almost... Just a little more...
There's something on the water!
The "Sunflowers"!
Ah, it made it after all! -
But wait a second, Conan was in
the case with that "Sunflowers"!
Huh?
So Conan must be somewhere nearby!
Everyone help me find Conan!
Conan!
Where are you?!
Where could you be?! Conan!
Conan!
Mm... Ran...
Huh?! Look guys!
Yeah! From under the painting!
Huh?
Where?
Huh?!
I'm coming for ya kid! Hup!
Oh Conan...
Hey, are you gonna be okay?
Good going, little guy!
I expect no less from my Kid Catcher!
Haha!
You all right, brat?
Yeah.
You protected the "Sunflowers"! Good work!
Taking all the sweet moments for himself.
Hm?
There's still something I don't get.
Why don't you help me understand it?
Huh?
How'd you know the real identity of the criminal?
She left a voice message trying to hire me.
She said she wanted me to steal
the second and fifth "Sunflowers".
I see.
You have a talent for disguises, so I'm
sure you knew right away by voice alone
who had tried to contact you.
But why did you feel compelled
to interfere with her planes?
What were you gonna get out of it?
I wanted a certain someone to see the Ashiya "Sunflowers."
What are you talking about?
That day, amid the furious flames of an air raid.
a carpenter entrusted that "Sunflowers"
to the woman who secretly loved him,
then died before her eyes. She's the one.
But how could you know about
something that happened so long ago?
Hmph. I heard the story from an
old man who witnessed the whole thing.
He lived with them. Back then he
was one of their most trusted servants.
The student who saved his ft love from
that sea of fire asked me for a favor.
To show her the Ashiya "Sunflowers."
Huh..? Hm.
I see. Then that solves everything.
Are you sure? You won't arrest me?
I'm letting you go. Just this once.
Hmph. You don't have it in you
to take me in, do you officer?
In honor of your friend and that doomed love,
and because he trusted you to give him a hand...
Well, let's just say I'll turn a blind eye.
It looks like I may have misjudged you, Charlie.
The feeling's mutual.
Hmph.
It's not here! Or here! Or here?!
Where is it? Where'd it go?
If I still can't find it after looking this
hard, then someone must have stolen the darn thing!
But who?! Who the heck stole my ticket?
So, you're not gonna tell him
the exhibition's been canceled?
He'd find out if he watched the news.
Huh?
What the heck? That's not very nice.
If I look at you too much, I
have a feeling I'll regret it.
Huh? What?!
Just some advice someone once gave me.
Who stole my ticket?! I want it back!
Where is it?! My ticket!