Whoa! Look, Clain!
There's a teddy bear...!
And some snacks...
Both of which will
come in very handy...
Since the two of us
are about to be killed.
Well, actually you're
a just a dopple... So...
I'm the only one who
has a life to forfeit.
Ow...
You gonna try and
get out of that net,
or are you two
pretending to be tuna?
What's that mean?
Move it, seafood!
--Whoa!
And where do you
think you're going...?!
Hey...! Damn it! Wait up!
Wow...! Look at this stuff!
They're using actual
antique monitors!
All the pretty yellow blooms!
This is not a field
trip, pipsqueak!
In case you haven't noticed,
you're prisoners...
No way! You've got
to be kidding me!
Jeez.
Can it... or we'll can it
for you... Sayyy hello!
Your sniper's using a
bona fide optical sight!
I have found paradise!
You're an itchy trigger
finger from the real deal!
Oh hello!
Enri!
You're back!
Yup...! You finish
all your homework?
Mm hmm!
Welcome back.
I take it that's
the trouble-maker
Sunda's been up in arms about?
Right... Sorry.
We've got more company!
It's so nice to meet you!
Let's shake hands, kay?
Dear, dear... Does this mean a
dopple came along for the ride?
Sure did.
My, what a darling outfit...
What splendid fashion
sense she has.
Oh, that's precious!
Let me get a closer look...
Aren't you just a darling?
Thank you... Enri!
I don't get it... Why
couldn't they see Nessa
before you pointed her out?
--Well, see...
--Keep your distance, everyone!
Bad customs spread like plague.
Bad customs?
Right! Meet-and-greet's
over, people...!
And big brother wants
a word with you two!
Hey, hey! Welcome!
Good to see you both...
Please excuse the mess...
Here.
Let's you and me have a
little pow-wow, tiger...
Just one reckless
romantic to another, huh?
Wait, you...?
So now what?
That person doesn't like Nessa.
--Huh?
--Because if he did,
he'd be able to touch Nessa
like the rest of his friends!
Seriously?
Nessa chooses to
stay with Enri...
Excuse me?!
Come on, let's hunt treasure!
Show Nessa where you
found the teddy bear!
That wasn't treasure!
We just used that stupid
thing to bait you!
Race ya!
Like hell you will!
They're all crazy.
Alright, kiddo...
So we're back to that, are we?
You ever heard of
The Lost Millennium?
What?
The thousand years
before Fractale...
The era when we
all lost our way...
When the human race sold its
independence up the river...
All for some naive
idea of luxury.
Oh, great. A lecture.
Well, there are some of us
who decided to adopt
that dark era's name and take
up arms, to oppose Fractale.
Sure, we Granites are just
a drop in the bucket,
but a sizeable faction
all the same...
Not something to sneeze at,
if you know your stuff.
Oh man. Lost Millennium.
I'm being held hostage by a
ragtag group of terrorists.
Drink your coffee
'fore it gets cold.
Yeah, 'kay...
It's not every day you get
treated to something
made the old fashioned way.
This village produces
by hand every single thing
it consumes... We don't
rely on dopples...
We teach our children
using--wait for it--books,
so their heads are filled
with actual knowledge
instead of just empty
terabytes of data.
And each of us who
calls this place home
has had their Fractale
Terminal removed
to make room for more
important things.
C'mon. You're pulling my leg.
Not at all... What choice does
a person have if he intends
to live as he was
meant to... As a human!
Whoa! You have a dishtowel?
With just a little
bit of patience,
the problem will rectify itself.
You're just going to air dry?
My point is that Fractale is
on the brink of collapse...
The fact balloons keep
falling out of the sky
is proof enough of that.
The powers-that-be
can rail to the contrary
all they like,
it doesn't matter!
The Temple will
preach about Freedom
as long as it has
the breath to lie...!
The Lost Millennium sees
through their masquerade!
I'm sorry, I really have no idea
what you're talking about,
but could you just tell me what
you guys want with Phryne?
You mean the temptress you
got all lovey-dovey with?
Uh... She... I...!
She's the key to
the world, my friend...
A priestess of the Temple
with a very harsh fate.
Okay, still not following you.
Look, kiddo, all you need to
know right now is this...
The girl stole a dopple
from the higher ups.
You're not telling me she
made off with Nessa...?
She risked life and limb
to smuggle her out...
Which translates as
pretty damn important!
So it's just as I thought...
Your run-of-the-mill dopple
wouldn't warrant that effort
unless it contained
sensitive information...!
Information capable of bringing
the Temple down to its knees!
You're gonna use
Nessa as a pawn...
I'd consider my situation
before I got too uppity...
After all... You are gonna
be here for a while.
You walk so fast, Enri...!
Nessa doesn't see the point
for us to be in such
a big, fat rush.
Gah! Then stop following me!
Oh wow! Is this where
you guys live?!
No. It's just our mother ship.
Nessa bets where there's a ship
there's all kinds of treasure!
Go back to your stupid
friend already.
You're driving me up
a wall...! Geez...
Ugh! Man! Since
when does a dopple
have to be so damn chummy?
Hello!
Stupid...
Condition check complete...
Your condition today,
according--
Someone's had more sugar
than she should have!
Oh! You wanted privacy
to use the bathroom...
Just remember to wipe your
bottom when you're done, okay?
Hey! It's dark in here...
Fine mess I've gotten myself
into. Really fantastic.
No!
Nurse, this man
needs a sedative...
Right.
Not that it's any
of my business...
but is this place some
kind of hospital?
Sort of. We have
inpatient facilities,
but there aren't really
enough beds to go around...
We can't do much here
beyond simple first aid.
I've never seen so many
people in need of care
gathered under one
roof like this.
Well, if these folks had the
luxury of Fractale access,
they'd be welcome to a hospital
of their choice, more or less.
But this village is
a different story.
Why remove their terminals
if this is the price?!
It may not be pleasant,
but that's the price of
fighting the good fight.
The sooner you understand
that no amenity
is worth giving up
your freedom...
The closer you'll be
to a real person.
But this...
No point arguing if you
don't understand the issue.
My damn knees are giving
me trouble again.
I'm so sorry... The wait
today is a fairly long one.
There you are, Clain!
Nessa can tell you what
color underwear...
Ahhhhhh!
A real person.
What makes you think
I want to know?
Her underwear
doesn't interest me.
Gah! Just blurt it out,
why don't you...?!
Like I wanted you to be
interested anyway!
What's wrong with him?
Alrighty...! Let's Drink!!...!
No, wait'fore that... Everybody,
visors...! Chop chop.
That is one impressive dopple.
Right...! Time for a toast...!
Here's to our esteemed hostages!
Darling!
We're definitely blessed.
You're so quiet...
Are you sad?
These people just confuse me...
That's all, I guess.
They've built their entire
lives around a crazy idea...
And they look like good people,
but I don't feel like
I can trust them...
Here you go.
And this is... what?
Smellie grass and bean soup.
Go on! Gulp it down!
It's not out of a tube,
but oh well...
This is weird!
It's such a complicated flavor.
Get out of here...!
First it's all sweet...
then it's salty...
Ugh! Come on, just
tell us if you like it!
Yeah, no... It's amazing.
Excellent... Thanks!
Help yourself to more.
What's the matter?
Beans not agree with
your tummy, sweetheart?
Think about it, Granny...
She doesn't have a tummy,
so she can't even eat it.
Oh... Quite right, dear...
I'm so sorry.
This is gonna be your bedroom
for the next few days.
Just do us a favor and
don't make too much noise.
I told you before...!
Why the heck is there
only one bed...?
Do these people really
think a guy my age
wants to mess around with
a kid like Nessa? Gross.
What's your problem?
Nessa wants you to tell her what
the bean soup thing was like.
Well, it was very tasty...
It was sweet and salty
kind of at the same time.
I need more details than that!
Mmm... I guess the
beans were pretty soft,
but beyond that, I can't think
how best to describe it.
There might've been a hint of
bitterness in there somewhere...
Nessa doesn't understand!
You should express the taste
through the power of dance!
Uh, how's that
gonna help at all?
Nessa can't understand
words about food
because she doesn't eat food.
Oh. I'm sorry...
So the only way
for her to get it
is to sort of make it go
with something else.
Okay fine, then.
Maybe it was a little something
like this...? I dunno...
Bean soup tastes like
sneaking around in the dark?
No, wait! It was
more like this...!
Kind of starts up here like
this, and then, whoa Nelly...!
Bean soup tastes like
being overjoyed...?
Tell Nessa what the
pancakes were like!
I think they were more
down here like this.
Hooray! Pancakes are like
slinking around in the mud!
The lovebirds are
getting lively...
You ask me, the lovebirds are
gettin' downright weird.
What's the matter, Clain,
did you have a bad dream?
Are you getting ready
for some kind of party?
You could say that.
We just got word they're holding
a Star Festival tonight.
What?
Temple must be getting
anxious to bump up the date.
You mean one of those ceremonies
where the Temple priestesses
gather everyone together
to pray and stuff?
Butcher! Get the
lead out, man...!
In case no one's told you,
the site's three whole sectors
to the west, 'less you
know a faster route?
Sorry, sir!
Exactly what are you cooking up?
Heh... What do you think,
kid...? The Granite clan
is going to gate crash
themselves a Star Festival.
Huh?!
Best suit up, tiger.
Hold on!
Nessa can't wait...!
A Star Festival...!
The Lost Millennium isn't a
travel agency, gingersnap!
You park your butt here!
No!
No way...! Their ship is
a goldmine of antiques!
This is the coolest thing ever!
Alright! Reality check, people;
we're about to put our
heads in the lion's mouth
and some of us may not
be coming back...!
Is that understood!
Yes sir!
Ugh, give me a break...
You make it sound like
we're going to war.
You have no idea what
you're in for, do you?
Well hey, they say
ignorance is bliss...
The Fractale Terminals
are good for one thing...
letting idiots stay blissful.
Heh... And with all
the womanizing you do,
it's a wonder you
can think at all!
If you don't stop
taking shots at me,
I'm gonna plant
my foot in your--
Get this strait, big guy:
Clain is as sweet as they come!
What the...?! I thought we
left her back at the village!
Uh-huh. I had a feeling
we'd run into this.
She's pure data,
an abstract concept...
meaning Little Miss Sunshine
can go where she pleases.
Nessa isn't only data.
That's how she got
in the bathroom...
Bathroom?
You stop eavesdropping!
Comin' in for a landing.
What is a Star Festival,
you think?
Eh...? That question is
for our youngest recruit.
Give me a break,
everyone knows that.
At the new moon,
a bunch of stars--
well, balloons, actually--
cluster in the sky,
and Temple priestesses
pray to them.
It's how people "guarantee
divine protection"
for themselves for
the upcoming phase.
Refuse to participate
and all kinds of stuff
starts going haywire on you...
Even folks who aren't
really all that religious
take part just to keep
their dopples up to date.
I'd give that answer a D.
Ever wonder why people
toe the line even though
the festival can't satisfy
secular needs anymore?
Captain, if we get any
closer we might as well
send the priestess
a gift basket.
Good, good.
Bring 'er down, then.
Wowie! There's so
many people here!
'Kay, if I just pick my moment,
maybe I can get somebody
to rescue me from
these head-cases...
Put these on before the festival
or the so-called stars
will get you, too.
Wait. What do you
mean they'll "get me"?
Alright. It's show time.
What's about to happen?
Look up to the stars...
Give them your prayers...
Be at peace...
Bask in abundance...
You will be received
into heaven's breast...
There you shall know love...
Look up to the stars...
Give them your prayers...
Be at peace...
Bask in abundance...
You will be received...
What's going on? What's
wrong with everyone?
The stars... See how
they're pulsing?
Yeah...
This isn't some quaint
religious rite...
It's the Temple's pretext
for updating the nano-stream.
What does that mean?
It's brainwashing.
Brainwashing?!
Leave people to their own
thoughts and sooner or later
they start questioning
the powers that be...
If you're in a
position of power,
the last thing you want folks
to ask is whether or not
the way things are is the
way they have to be...
People start wondering why
they rely on dopples so much;
why families don't live
under one roof anymore...
But hey... hook everyone
up to a nano-stream
and a simple update erases
all that pesky "thinking"...
People go right on accepting
life as they've always known it
because they've been sapped
of all incentive to doubt.
But... people...
Open up your damn eyes
and take a look around...!
Do they look like
people to you?!
Fractale's made them husks
of what they could've been!
Move out!
Just stay out of the way.
You filthy, lying hags!
Die already!
No!
What?!
It's another me!
Hey!!
What the hell are you doing?!
Vile, treacherous turncoats who
defile our sacred ceremony...
You shall be judged...
By the heavens.
Nessa!
Wait! Come back here!
Butcher!!
Damn you all!!
Oh my god...
This isn't happening!
Look up to the stars...
Give them your prayers...
Be at peace...
Bask in abundance...
Look up to the stars...
Give them your prayers...
Be at peace...
Bask in abundance.
You will be received
into heaven's breast...
Is that Phryne?
Pray for the departed...
Usher them to the stars'
greatest reward...
Let those left behind
shelter in earthly plenty.
Welcome back, my sister...
The stars are glad.
Down by the salley gardens
my love and I did meet
She passed the salley gardens
with little snow-white feet
She bid me take love easy,
as the leaves grow on the tree
But I, being young and foolish,
with her did not agree
But I was young and foolish,
and now I am full of tears