So, I suppose we ought to expect
you home late again today?
Sweetie, big boys
don't prop their chins
on their hands like that.
"Flea market" doesn't
sound very reputable.
Sure it's someplace
you ought to be?
Trust me, it's fine.
The boy gets his
curiosity from your side.
Those itchy feet of
yours give him ideas.
Oh, I got the wanderlust out
of my system a while back.
Retired. Settled down in
Luimnigh five years ago now.
Really? I live in Vale!
We're practically neighbors!
'kay. See ya.
Oh, have fun.
Just make sure you're home
in time for dinner, alright?
Remember: it's important
for us to be together
as a family at mealtimes.
I'll be home in time.
Whoa-ho...!
Neat way of putting it,
but kind of weird.
"Wishing"? Prayers are what
they're usually called.
Which makes sense, 'cause
what's there to wish for?
I mean, how crazy would
that be to actually
have to ask the Day Star
for something...?
I'd feel so stupid...
Hello!
"Illuminate all we
forgot." Whatever.
More people here than
I thought there'd be.
Mm hmm.
Whoa! This place
is a gold mine...!
You see anything
compatible with my stuff?
Ah yes, here we go...
Just the right size.
Oh, man. I've already burned
through my donay for the month.
You need a handout?
Nah, just window shopping.
So? Let papa have
a look! What gen is it?
Hey, don't get all shadow on me.
Kid, forget the antiques-
try this stuff out.
Try what out?
Don't tell me you're
in the dark?
That's a data drug!
Yeah, and word is it'll
make your mind explode.
You should give it whirl!
I'll pass if it's
all the same to you.
Freeze!
Everybody stay right
where you are.
Fantastic. Ninety-five percent
of the suspects were dopples.
Pay dirt. Step on it!
Ah! There it is...
Fractale is a trillion-machine
cyber network designed at the
absolute cutting edge of
22nd century technology...
Well, not as nifty
as an old-school
scratch track download,
I guess, but still.
...their data can be downloaded
at regular intervals
by the Sky High Hovering Server.
A basic income is then allotted
to all participants
in perpetuity.
This system creates a world
where everyone's financial means
are met regardless of
their ability to work.
Consequently, a world
free of poverty and war.
Indeed, it's no overstatement
to call Fractale
the godlike manifestation of
humanity's oldest dream.
So this thing was patched
about the time Fractale
first came into existence.
Not a bad accidental find.
The world this old
info-track is talking about
has been present-tense
for a while now.
And it's right. Life is
pretty sweet. Mostly.
People get by well when
they don't have to bother
interacting with each
other in the flesh.
Sometimes it's
boring, sure, but...
it's not like the alterative
wasn't given a shot...
Time for the five
o'clock prayer...
Based on your current location,
the direction of the temple is
approximately ten degrees to the
right of where you are facing.
And now, let us pray together.
I guess if this is the most
we've got to put up with,
things could be worse.
Remain calm and
refrain from blinking.
The heck is that?
Am I seeing things?
It's a girl!
She's in trouble!
This looks serious...
I know it sounds crazy... But...
Well... for a second there...
Just for a second...
It wouldn't have surprised
me to see her fly.
Guess they're giving
up the search. Good.
There she is.
Now what?
Off to a great start.
Hey, um... Are you like...
okay, or what?
Well... At least
she's breathing...
If she really is
a "she," that is.
Uh, oh!
Er, I, uh...
You really shouldn't try to move
till we, uh, know how badly...
Oh... Suppose I should say hi.
Um... Nice... night?
Uh... You know, you're right.
The day star's already headed
down, so I guess it is night.
I guess so.
I'll just go and find something
to patch you up with
before it gets any worse...
I... uh...
Welcome home, son.
Find anything exciting
at the flea market?
Got a bit more than I
bargained for, actually.
What is it, Jackie?
Not to shrug you guys
off or anything, but...
I was sorta hoping you could
give me the night to myself?
I just need some time
alone, you know...
What's gotten into
you all of sudden?
Well, I suppose we could if
it's alright with your father.
Uh, as long as you
don't stay up too late.
Good night, then.
Okay, the coast is clear.
You can come in.
You're very kind. Thanks.
You really think
you're okay enough
not to have to go to
the hospital or anything?
I forgot! There was one
thing I wanted to-- Clain!
And who is this young lady?
No one, just, uh...
My name is Phryne.
Don't start a conversation!
Oh dear, the poor thing's hurt!
No, no! It's fine.
Believe me. It's--
Look. I'll explain later, okay?!
Hold on just a minute--
Well, they seem very pleasant.
Do those dopples belong
to your parents?
That's right...
And the little yapper
who broke our cover was Jackie.
You didn't have to do that
just for me, you know...
Make your family
disappear, I mean.
That's kind of a dramatic
way of putting it,
I mean c'mon,
they're just dopples...
Sure, if you say so.
Oh yeah, let's get you fixed up.
Let's see. First aid kit...
It's not much, but it ought
to take care of the scratches.
I should be able to tend
to my wounds on my own
if you don't mind giving
me a little bit of privacy.
Not to impose, of course.
Sure, not a problem at all,
I'll just bury my head upstairs
while you do your thing...
You won't even know
I'm here. So, uh, yeah.
What a weird girl.
Weird, but...
Well I guess she's
kind of nice, actually.
Um... Sorry to trouble you...
I believe I may need
your help after all.
Fine! No problem!
What'd ya need?
You will have to
look at me first.
You really don't mind?
I can't explain otherwise.
I tried to reach here...
But, I'm too stiff...
So, if you'd be so kind...
You sure you...
don't need a hospital?
This is wonderful...
I'm absolutely charmed.
These objects wear an
aura of history and care
I find quite delightful.
It's really magnificent.
Did I hear you right when you
said your name was Phryne?
Uh huh.
So, not that it's any of
my business or anything,
but who are you exactly?
I mean, why are
people chasing you?
I'd rather not say.
Like I told you, it's none
of my business anyway.
I'm going to say
this one more time:
are you sure you don't
need a hospital?
I'm so tired.
Huh?
Pardon me, but...
That's right.
Look at daddy, Clain.
You startled me...
Did you sleep okay?
What's this?
It's just a video file of
when I was a little baby.
Those are my parents. I mean,
you know, the real ones.
I owe you an apology
for implying
your family wasn't
important to you.
Clearly I misjudged
your feelings
if you're sentimental
over something like this.
I don't know if I'd call
myself sentimental...
Video data in this format is
crazy hard to come by these days
and I have kind of a thing for
collecting old stuff, so I--
But my parents are cool...
It's different.
Your smile held a
different aura then...
Your face no longer
accommodates such joy.
Aw c'mon, I smile plenty,
my face is just more grown.
You misunderstand me!
I demand that you smile as
you do in this video...!
Like... like this, perhaps...
Is this what you mean?
You have a silly face.
Thanks, I guess... Have
you looked in a mirror?
Now I'm satisfied
that baby was you.
♪ I look up to the sky and offer
my wish to the Day Star-- ♪
Hey!
I offer a wish on your behalf...
One that I hope...
Oh wait, I need to
know your name first.
It's Clain.
Lovely...
♪ I look up to the sky and offer
my wish to the Day Star... ♪
♪ Asking that Clain's
old smile... ♪
♪ be boundless as
the wreathing blue. ♪
My amulet...! Of course!
Here.
What is that?
This amulet has always been
the source of my smile,
so keep it close
and from now on
maybe it can be the
source of yours too.
Good evening. We're from
a local medical agency.
We've come to take the
injured woman into custody.
You don't mean like
the hospital, do you?
'Cause I haven't actually
called anyone about it...
Well, that's because
Fractale alerted us
to the woman's condition,
which according to the database
is bad enough to
need an ambulance.
You really expect me to believe
that's an ambulance?
Are you calling me a liar...?!
You see that little
red blinky thing?!
How much more legit
you want us to look?!
Hey! Don't be a smartass!
If we tell you it's
an ambulance,
it's a freaking ambulance,
okay punk?!
Bad news, Phryne. I think
those guys know you're here.
So that was them, then?
The good news is I think
you still might be okay.
They don't exactly strike
me as brains, this bunch.
There's something
I have to tell you.
Here they come again.
You sit tight, I'll handle them.
I'm traveling with my sick
brothers and we really need
a place to stay for the night
if you'd be so kind.
Uh...
Well, I'll give 'em one thing:
they're pretty persistent.
Clain, I really should...
Ugh. Oh, come on!
Hello. We're from Security
and we're looking
for a suspicious female
whose data can't be tracked.
Okay, apart from the hat
you borrowed from your buddy,
you look exactly the same.
Well excuse us for not
rolling in enough donay
to buy a more convincing
costume, Mr. Detective!
Your finances aren't really
the issue here, so...
I only wanna hear one
thing out of you...!
Where have you got her
squirreled away?!
I don't know what you're--
What gives you lug
heads the right...?!
Upstairs!
Look, you can't just barge
into someone's home!
Ahhh!!
You pervert!
We caught you in
the middle of doing
something you
shouldn't have!
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Don't try to play innocent!
Ignore the act, ma'am!
This little creep is making
all stupid so you'll have to
fill in the blanks yourself
and end up saying something
super embarrassing
and un-ladylike!
Ew, gross...! Sanitize!
Yes ma'am!
You better not be making a mess!
Are you checking the bathroom?
You wouldn't believe the things
he's got lying around in here!
Get out of my stuff!
What's the big idea making
us think she's here?!
Hmph. Let's go before
we waste any more time.
Yeah. Big bro'll
be waiting for us.
Wait... Hold on a sec.
Having trouble with
the clutch again?
Not exactly...
Whoa. Okay...
There you are.
Do you think they'll mind
that I borrowed this?
That is really cool.
It's just a little farther.
This is the one place where
radio waves don't reach...
No one'll be able to
find you up here.
It's the ruins of an old
chapel I found a while back.
Not sure how old
they are, though.
I kind of consider them my
secret hideout, or whatever.
You have a very fascinating
perspective on things.
Yeah?
I've often heard that the people
living in this era romanticize
the idea of personal freedom
until it defines them...
They won't be tied down...
Not for anything.
What do you mean "people
living in this era?"
If you don't want to say...
I guess it's only natural you'd
be curious about who I am...
I mean, that is a priestess
outfit you've got on, right?
On second thought, never mind.
You aren't curious?
Hey, when you want me to...
I'll be all ears.
Nights get pretty
chilly up here.
This ought to generate enough
warmth to keep us from freezing.
You say so.
The moon is so bright.
Yeah?
From where I used to live,
I'd gaze up at it every night.
Of all the lights in the sky,
hers was the only one that
made me feel at peace...
No matter what I was
going through at the time,
I'd only ever feel her
gazing down on me with love.
I know he'll look after you.
Huh...?
Phryne? Where'd you go?
That's gratitude for you.
Just like that, she might as
well have never been here.
Well, it's the same with
everybody--why not her?
I mean, really...
I don't even know why
I'm so ticked about it.
Wait a minute!
♪ I look up to the sky... ♪
♪ And offer my wish
to the day star... ♪
♪ Bidding farewell
to the night... ♪
♪ that hides from us
what we once were... ♪
The amulet's got some sort
of data embedded on it...
Old data...
The heck is this thing?
Ta-da!
Down by the salley gardens
my love and I did meet
She passed the salley gardens
with little snow-white feet
She bid me take love easy,
as the leaves grow on the tree
But I, being young and foolish,
with her did not agree
But I was young and foolish,
and now I am full of tears