Alright, then.
I think the coast is clear.
I've heard tell of God's fury
at a people brazen enough
to try and build an edifice
to equal his glory.
I'm inclined to believe
that we share that hubris,
and that it has finally brought
upon us the wrath of heaven.
You speak blasphemy!
Damn the L.M.
Fools! I alone have
walked in the light
where my forebears
stumbled in darkness...!
I alone have refined the key
to Fractale's salvation...!
Yet a band of ruffians thinks
nothing of spitting in my face--
Oh, my dear... yes...
I have you.
152589... I knew
it would be you.
If sapping the life and
love of countless girls
is the measure of our success...
Then well have we reaped
the reward of our cruelty...
How fragile this world is--
Is that bitterness I hear?
Do you think yourself a
displaced God... No. 141923?
You know full well that I do
not consider myself a god.
She and she alone
can answer that need.
I wonder what's to become
of you in all this...
It breaks my heart to think
what your next move must be.
We are but identical links
in an endless chain.
Fractale decrees that
we shall not be whole
in and of ourselves;
but strong only in pieces...
One, only together.
It is through submission
to this pitiless scheme
that happiness for
all is ensured...
I know this in my heart of
hearts... As Archpriestess,
I accept what becomes of me:
what must be done.
This world teeters perilously
on the brink of annihilation...
Mutiny prunes the tree
from which we feast;
would see it rotted...
its fruit left to wither
in the unforgiving dust...
Our way of life will
end... cut to tinder
by the axe-wielding children
of the Lost Millennium.
Though their blades
be dull and few,
the sheer persistence
of their blows
has taken a disastrous
toll upon this Temple.
And our mercy has
reached its limit...
It is not only us, but the world
which demands their death.
You guys are from
that ship docked
on the outskirts of the
town, aren't you?
Boss, wait!
Grant their souls
everlasting peace...
Let them rejoin Fractale
as symbols of penance.
Her fever shows no
sign of breaking.
What about you, Phryne?
How're you feeling right now?
I'm alright.
Look you say that,
but I know better...
What you need is rest...
Especially after what you've--
I don't disagree... But I'll
need your help to fall asleep.
Last thing I want to
do is dream... So...
You want me to stay with you?
Nessa wants to hold hands
with Clain and Phryne!
Welcome back, Ness.
And it's not a mistake?!
I wish. But, no: it's an
all-out imperial ordinance
from the Archpriestess;
first of its kind in 300 years!
...Sunda, we were just
in town and the Arch--
What's Ryme saying? He leaving
us to deal with this alone?
Her temperature's starting
to level off, I think.
That feels nice... Nessa likes
how cold Phryne's hands are.
Poor circulation has its use.
You know, I could swear you were
sisters, seeing you like this.
Oh. Yeah, right.
Silly me; I guess you
two are kinda sisters...
Or, you know, whatever
the name for it is...
I'll shut up now...
So, uh... Would you like to
know about Nessa and me?
It'd be nice to have some idea
about what's going on...
I really shouldn't have left you
in the dark as long as I have.
It's not easy to explain,
but basically Nessa
is like the ephemeral
spirit of a God...
A long time ago, in a whole
other life, before Fractale,
her soul was the first
to inhabit this body.
What does that mean?
Nessa is the original mind...
I am just one of many bodies
prepared for her to inhabit.
The Temple believes that
when Nessa--the soul--
merges with me--the body--
the "key" to Fractale's
salvation will manifest itself.
The system's been
breaking down for ages;
and the "key" remains
the only hope
of staving off what would
otherwise be inevitable:
the triumph of
entropy over order.
'Kay, but what does it mean
for the two of you to merge?
That's sort of ambiguous...
I don't really know.
But when we do merge,
my guess is... Well...
It will be the end
of what we are now.
What does that mean,
"the way you are now?"
Are you saying if you do this
merging thing, you'll die?
Clain, I...
What is it?!
Nessa saw herself...
Nessa disappeared completely...
But... She doesn't want to die!
Nessa wants to be Nessa!
Disappearing is forever!
Then there's only darkness and
loneliness and no more friends!
Hey! That's not going to happen!
Don't let Nessa disappear!
Say she gets to go
on being Nessa!
You have to promise, Clain!
It's going to be okay.
I promise.
Not a damn thing is
going to change...
You're going to go right on
being what you are...
Your smile won't fade. Your
laughter's not going to stop.
Nessa is going to be Nessa;
Phryne is going to be Phryne.
And that's how it'll
always be... From now on.
I have no problem
feeling you right now...
You can still feel me like
you always have, right?
Nessa feels you.
I'm not gonna lie;
the whole thing's still
a big mystery to me,
but you know what?
I for one am not gonna look
a gift-horse in the mouth.
Boss!
What is it?
What's going on?
The townspeople have gathered
outside the ship with torches!
I'm sorry, but we need
your people to leave.
Does the damn Temple
intimidate you that badly?
They'd cut off our donay supply
if they found out we were
harboring you lot...
Nothing to be done against
a threat like that...
What would you do in our shoes?
This just proves how badly you
need to break free of 'em...!
They've been controlling
every aspect of your lives
since the day that
you were born...!
How much longer are
you willing to suffer
before you refuse to be
a puppet anymore?!
You'd have us die?
That's not what we're saying!
We just want you to act
like genuine human beings
for once in your life!
You're murderers.
You destroyed one of
their medical facilities
without a thought.
Is that true?!
That's not how...
It's true.
Butchers!
You sons of bitches don't give
a damn who you have to kill
to bring the system
down, do you?!
You'll be the end of us all!
Get out of our town!
Peddle your bullshit
somewhere else!
You're going to
endanger our children!
At the end of the day they're
only human, you know?
At least they own their fear...
That's always the first step
toward genuine courage.
I don't understand.
Why is the Temple suddenly
changing its tune
about you guys?
'Cause they're in dire straits.
They need us to hand you over.
They're upping the ante.
They know we'd never
turn you guys in
'cause the last thing we want
is for Fractale to be saved...
The Temple wants to
"reboot" the system
while they still can and
they know we'd be damned
before we see that
happen. Make sense?
Yes it does...
Too much sense.
Look, don't overthink
things, kiddo...
What's going on isn't your
fault, it's just that--
What?!
What is it?
They've made their move...
The village has been hit...
The Temple set it on fire!
Porphyry, Diorite,
Greywacke, and Granite,
all burned to the
ground tonight...
Four villages destroyed by
the Temple because of us!
I'm told no one in
Greywacke survived.
They took the brunt
of it and none of us
was there to protect them.
You see?! That's why
I was so deadset
against being the
aggressor in all this!
Duly noted, but it's meaningless
to assign blame at this point.
We must defend our families!
I agree. We'll separate
and protect our homes.
I'm sorry our first quorum
meeting in fifty years
has to end on this note.
If there are no objections,
I move we adjourn.
Objection.
How can none of you see
that the Temple's resorting
to these measures because
the position we're in
puts them between a
rock and hard place...?
There is no more opportune
moment to strike than now.
Dias, please...
I agree with him!
I say we go at them!
We can't just knuckle
under to tactics like this!
Well, I daresay destroying
the lab has given someone
a great deal of clout in
a short amount of time...
Suppose we consent to
your rallying cry, Dias;
what exactly do we have
to strike at them with?
Sunda just so happens to have
the key to rebooting Fractale
as a guest onboard the Danan.
Isn't that right?
Is this true?!
Are you holding
out on us, Granite?
And what of it if I am?
You do understand...?
The Temple has essentially let
its raison d'etre slip right
through it's greasy fingers.
Without the key, they're a husk
of what they once were...
Their position is as
weak as its ever been...
Making this the perfect moment
for our clans to swoop in
and realize Lost Millennium's
thousand-year-old ambition!
Boss! The quorum
meeting is done!
So what did they decide?
To attack... The
clans have agreed
to consolidate their military
power and storm the Temple
before any further actions
against us can be taken.
Yeah!
Yes! Muster up all
the ammunition we have!
It's gonna be a showdown!
Can I talk to you?
What is it?
Okay, so correct me
here if I'm wrong,
but the L.M.'s trying to
change things, right?
It is.
Change them how?
You asking me what kind
of world we'll have
when it's all over with...?
Tell me, kid, what kind
would you like?
I don't know...
I definitely think
that what the Temple's
been doing is wrong.
I think it's time for me
to get in this fight...
I can't just keep standing
around on the side lines.
How much good you think
you'd be in a fight?
Gee, thanks!
If you want to be
treated like a soldier,
then I'll give you orders...
Stay here in the village
and promise me that you'll
protect Phryne and Nessa
with everything you've got.
They have to stay
here at any rate...
We can't risk the Temple
getting them back
or shooting them down
with the rest of us, can we?
And besides... I
appreciate the sentiment,
but this is Lost Millennium's
fight, not yours...
Trust me... You're a good kid...
Hell, I'd even go so far
as to call you friend...
Everyone on board would...
But you're not one of us.
Still... There
actually is one thing
that only you could do
to help the effort...
Yeah?
Everybody move just a
little closer in, 'kay?
I wanna make sure I get
all of you in the shot.
Nessa, you ready...?
Lookin' good!
Don't take it yet!
There he is!
Way to be on time, doofus!
Hey... I had to get this.
That's very sweet of you...
But late-comers have to move
to the back of the line!
What'd I tell you,
Butcher, old pal?
She's a ball-buster...
Same as always.
Damn right I am.
Alright, that's everyone...
Let's snap this puppy.
Everybody stay like you are.
I don't want Daddy to be killed!
Be sure to leave the picture
with Granny Elder
and the others, okay?
Wait, you're going
along for the fight?
Like Sunda's got a chance
in hell of stopping me.
Yeah. No kidding, right?
By the way, I kinda wanted...
to tell you something...
Oh, yeah?
Well, uh... You see...
Look, if you gotta use
the bathroom or something,
you can tell me later--
Do you always
have to be a perv?!
What the hell'd I do
to deserve that?!
You shut up!
You've got till we get
back from the front lines
to clean up your act
or so help me, Clain,
I will make you rue the
day you hit puberty...
Clean up my act?
You're the one hitting people!
Enri's angry!
How can they laugh and carry on
like that before a battle?
Aren't they terrified?
Well, naturally
they're terrified...
All the more reason to cut up.
I think I'm too afraid of death
for that... aren't you?
Hey now... There're
things out there
a lot more frightening
than death;
like not being able to
protect your loved ones.
True.
That's why Clain's gonna look
after you while we're gone:
we want you both to feel safe.
I do feel safe...
I know Clain will do
everything he can to
protect me from harm...
And I'm grateful
to him for that.
Alright! Now...!
All hands on deck!
Keep running the
engines at half power.
I want us at a snail's pace.
Done and done!
It's time to bring
this fight to them!
It's so pretty!
It certainly is.
You know, there are all sorts
of people in this world...
Those who swear by Fractale;
those who hate it.
Some who'd do anything
to see it continue on;
some who'd do anything
to see it falter;
and people like me who
can't make up their minds.
But when it comes down to it,
the world doesn't care
about Fractale. It just keeps
moving forward on its own.
Clain...
If the Day Star could grant
your wish... What would it be?
Oh that's an easy one;
to be by the side
of the people I love
forever... Not bad, huh?
And it's totally gonna happen!
Because Clain gets to stay
by Nessa and Phryne's side
for his whole entire life...!
Fooorever!
And everyone'll live happily
ever after, won't they?
You bet they will.
Absolutely.
"Dear Clain... I wish
I could tell you
why I left that
first night, but...
I guess the truth is,
however hard I look at it,
I really don't understand
why myself..."
"I stood by my decision then,
though... and I still do."
"You have to understand
that Nessa was me
when I was beautiful and free.
I haven't been that person in
a long time, but with you...
she stands a chance.
So I'm leaving...
If anyone can begin to
convince Archpriestess Moeran
or my father,
it would surely be me.
Because I am half of the key."
"I'm sorry for leaving
without saying anything...
But since this all started
because I left the temple...
I believe I have to
go back and end it...
It was you, Clain, who made
me feel that I could...
that I wanted to...
You, Nessa, and everyone else.
I am grateful to you all.
Thank you. With love, Phryne."
Didn't we just talk about the
three of us staying together?!
How could she go off and do
a thing like this
without talking to us?!
You know what?
It doesn't matter!
I am done trying to get my
head around that woman...!
After all we've been
through together,
she's just as self-centered
and arrogant
as she was the
first time we met!
So, then... What are
you going to do?
Oh, you wanna know what
I'm gonna do about this?
Not a damn thing!
To hell with her!
You promised!
A thousand needles...!
Remember...!
Nessa's decided she
really likes Phryne...
Sure, she was mean
and scary at first...
But it turns out Phryne is
pretty nice after all...
More than nice, in fact...
And Nessa knows that Clain
really likes her, too!
Well... look, it's not that...
Come on. Clain likes being
happy just as much as anyone...
So! Admit you like her...
Nessa knows you do.
I like Phryne! Is that what
you wanna hear?! You happy?!
Damnit, she really
owes me for this one...
Phryne, you're an idiot!!
We're ready.
All ships, prepare to
engage immediately...
The second the enemy's in range,
open fire. I repeat: open fire.
Missiles in launch
position, now!
Fire!
Just you wait, Phryne...
You're not getting away from me
this time. I promise you that.
Okay, listen:
I'm not gonna lie,
if the Temple gets
a hold of you, the world is in
a lot of trouble... Still sure
you wanna come along?
We're staying together, Clain...
Forever... You promised Nessa.
That settles it. Let's go
save Phryne from herself!
Aye-aye, capt'n!
Down by the salley gardens
my love and I did meet
She passed the salley gardens
with little snow-white feet
She bid me take love easy,
as the leaves grow on the tree
But I, being young and foolish,
with her did not agree
But I was young and foolish,
and now I am full of tears