Phryne, you...?
Nessa, go to Clain. Now.
But...
Just do it!
Am I coming in loud and
clear for you now, boy?
By way of thanking you
for taking such good care
of our girl, permit
me to let you in
on the secret of this world.
An object lesson, if you like.
You're a creep.
Get your hands off her!
It's only fair to mention,
your friendship will be
sorely tested by the
chestnut of wisdom I offer.
Phryne is a copy of the girl
on whose biological script
the inner workings of
Fractale are based.
To preserve the script,
scientists at the project's helm
split the girl's personality
into abstract neural data
and biological information.
In essence: a body, and a soul.
Together these formed the key to
Fractale's continued existence.
700 years later, however,
when the time came
to rejoin them, a fault in
the basic code prevented
the key from fitting, as it
were, into the keyhole.
Since the original Phryne
was ten years of age,
a "vessel" thought to be
appropriate was cloned
from preserved tissue
samples in hopes
of merging the
neural data with it.
Much to their chagrin,
this approach foundered.
Each attempt became
an exercise in futility.
The godhead of Fractale simply
would not be stirred to wake.
Countless duplicates were tried
and discarded in the process.
Years later, having toiled
for generations,
the best minds
then turned to me...
By my nature I am a
compassionate soul...
During the course of my work
I became fond of the clones
and took several under wing
out of a sense of obligation...
One was this brazen
young thing...
A beloved daughter on whose
supple, milk-white shoulders
the responsibilities
of a god shall nest
like a majestic peregrine...
Isn't that right, my dear?
Her loveliness far
from distracted me
in my work, however.
Quite the contrary:
I uncovered the vital
secret my predecessors
in their frenzied
haste neglected.
I was staggered, but
understood instantly.
My forbears were misled:
god, as it were,
was not a ten-year-old girl
at all... but sixteen...!
The exact age of our
darling Phryne here!
The maiden on whose
biorhythms Fractale hinged
had created a childlike
second persona,
an imaginary friend
through whom she might
deflect the burden of painful
childhood memories!
We've got to get
them out of here.
Watch your ass!
I need both of you to
backtrack and find
a route around these
sons-a-bitches.
We're gonna find our comrades.
Before Dias does. Got it?
--Yes sir!
Why the hell haven't you
found the sanctuary yet?
What happened to the
reinforcements I asked for...?
What do you mean they're
"not responding"?
I refuse to accept that!
You find those cowards!
You see, this Phryne
had much the same,
shall we say, "experience"
as the original.
This is why her biorhythms fit
so perfectly into the mold.
Wait, what kind of experience?
It's complex, but...
love was the essential feature.
Love?
I don't get it. Phryne,
what does he mean by that?
I mean that despite your
efforts she belongs to me.
Just as the world she so
reluctantly preserves,
will eventually belong to
the two of us alone.
Yes... I empathize with
your pain at having
to give the girl up. After all,
she is the finest specimen
brought to maturity under
my care. Just look at her!
Burn with envy,
would-be interloper!
You will forever be a
millennium too early to win
both the maid and the world;
though there is comfort
in knowing she cared enough
to spare you the knowledge...
That said, I believe it's time
you showed your affection
by sparing her
the sight of you!
Fare thee well, my
misguided romantic!
What's gotten into you, my dear?
You know it hurts your
father's heart to see
such a refined young
blossom resort
to lowly, attention-grabbing
tactics like this...
From where do you
learn this behavior?
Certainly not from me...
Nooo!
Don't leave Daddy. He's hurt...
Phryne, wait...!
Clain, Phryne needs us now!
Nessa's following her!
Get it off...! Get it off!
Get it off, get it off,
get it off, get it off!!
Nessa, wha...
what are you doing?
When Nessa felt cold, this is
how Phryne made her warm...
It was a very nice thing
Phryne did for Nessa,
so she's happy to
return the favor.
Believe me, the last
thing I deserve
is to be treated with
anything like kindness, or...
Why do you say that?
I'm a defiled creature,
Nessa... There's...
There's no denying it...
It's who I am--
Nessa thinks you're pretty...
When you cry your tears
sparkle like jewels.
Nessa... What's happening?
I remember this song.
We should go.
Go where?
As long as we can be together...
I really couldn't
care less where.
Clain can come, too?
Say what you will...
Our love is not of
the common ilk.
For all your boyish infatuation,
the world whose rebirth
she represents shall
belong only to she and I.
Stop saying that crap...
She is the finest
specimen of my art--
the very pinnacle
of my genius...
It's only natural you'd
want to possess her.
Stop it... Stop it!!
What are you doing?
More to the point,
where is Phryne holed up?
We have to find her before
Alabaster gets to her!
--What?
--Oh, do the math...
Hey, why the hell is
Nessa not with you?!
Please tell me you didn't
just let her wander off!
Suck it up, doll face!
You don't get all wobbly-kneed
when people are
depending on you...!
I mean do you love
them or not, pervert?!
I do...
Oh my god... I've never told
Phryne the way I feel about her.
You what?
Come on!
The defensive detail
onboard the Tristan
has been completely annihilated!
We're not going to be able
to hold out much longer.
Without reinforcements,
we're dead!
I wish I could disagree,
but I've just received word
that the three clans
meant to back us up
have broken from the line.
Are you kidding?!
Betrayal is par
for the course...
All's fair in love and war,
my brothers.
My hand has been forced.
I'll enact strategy E
as we discussed...
You two catch a ride
out of here with Sunda.
Not a chance!
We're not leaving
our leader's side!
Thank you both.
Things are gettin'
rougher out there...
Enri!
There you are!
Clain... Hate to be
the bearer of bad news,
but for some reason Alabaster's
taken it on themselves
to blow the Temple
to Kingdom Come.
What?!
I want you both to get
back to the Danan
and steer it as far away
from here as you can.
You're not gonna stay behind...?
I've got some loose
ends to tie up...
Clain, what about you?
Yeah, me too...
I'm giving command of
the Danan to you, Enri.
No, you're the captain!
I refuse!
Now, now...
I haven't misjudged
my little baby sister's
ability to man up, have I?
Please... I can't...
C'mon, sis, I'll be home
before you know it...
Takamy, you promise me
you've got Enri's back.
Yes, sir!
Alright, Clain! Let's move!
Dias, you asshole.
Least let us get there
before you blow us up.
Hold on...
What is that music?
Sounds like it's coming
from over that way.
What's all this?
Phryne! Nessa! It's me!
Stand down, all of you...
We are in the midst
of a holy ceremony; I will
not allow violence here.
Phryne, get away from them!
She has come here of
her own volition, boy.
She has embraced her calling.
Yeah, sure she has.
Without talking to me
about it first? No, c'mon!
You can't.
Come forward. You're
welcome to join our prayer.
The millennial rite is calling
the beloved maidens
to heaven's summit, and it
would be a shame for us
not to share it... I beg
of you, let us both widen
our narrow ideologies
and bestow a blessing
upon the world as fellow
spirits in peace.
Nicely done...
I assume it's alright
if I join in as well?
Dias...
I can't even begin to tell you
how gratifying it will be
to take part in something larger
than my "narrow ideology."
Stand clear, Archpriestess!
He's dangerous!
It's an honor to
meet you, your grace.
Stand up, please...
Your words and manner
tell me you are a
kindred spirit, sir...
Permit me to say that in another
life I believe the two of us
might have been the
closest of companions.
Permit me to say your words
move me as an ocean.
I assume that you've already
placed a device in our midst?
Yes. Two of my greatest
friends since childhood
gave their lives to
see that it was done.
I mourn their loss.
Thank you.
Archpriestess!
What the hell?
Does loneliness plague you?
Sometimes. But in
the final loneliness,
the two of us can be the
closest of companions.
I yield my life freely without
a qualm in my heart...
However... Let it be known
that I do not yield the world.
Now's our chance!
Son of a...
Jump the gap!
Don't think about it, just go!
--Are you alright?
--Clain!
Dammit!
You're hit!
Don't worry about it,
just get in the elevator!
Stop looking at me and move!
How do I get it to go up?
The button there on your side.
And this'll take you to
"heaven's summit"
or whatever the hell it is?
Right.
Make sure they get
up there safe, 'kay?
You're not coming?!
I really wish I had more time
to explain it to you, kid...
Honestly, I don't have the first
clue how the world ought to be.
But I have zero regrets
for the path I chose;
hell, in the end we've
all gotta pick sides
without knowing what's
right for everyone...
And now... it's time
for you to make a choice.
No matter what decision
you make, Clain,
we're in this together.
You're gonna have to
get through me first!
Just get in here!
With any luck, I'll see
you on the other side!
That was close.
Don't get comfortable; we're
not out of the woods yet...!
Come on... girl!
We're just gonna leave Sunda
and others back there?!
Full speed ahead.
Boss...!
Captain's orders, Takamy.
Hello, Phryne.
Hope you're not cold...
No.
I'm glad it's warm enough
for you in here, then.
Nessa likes Phryne's
warmth the best.
Are you gonna go
through with it?
Yes.
Why?
Nessa's on the verge of
completely dissipating.
I have to do something.
But... I mean,
you said so yourself:
once the two of you merge,
there's no way of knowing
if either one of
you will survive.
There is that...
Come on...!
It's practically suicide!
And if that's the way this
unfolds, then at least
I'll have walked into it
without any illusions...
Oblivion isn't such a terrifying
idea if you think about it;
it's where we come from,
it's where we end up...
So you've made up
your mind, then.
Without considering how I feel.
What do you mean, Clain?
How do you feel?
I don't have the first clue how
the world ought to be either...
Between The Lost Millennium
and the Temple,
both sides have their
pros and cons.
If someone asked
me to choose
one over the other
right now I couldn't...
But I know this much...
If I lose you and Nessa,
I might as well be dead.
That's how much it'll hurt.
I really wish you could hear
yourself talk right now;
someone like me
isn't worth a fraction
of the worry you've put
yourself through--
Shut up.
I love you, okay...?
Yes, you're volatile.
You smack me around.
The crap that comes out of your
mouth sometimes is insane.
The way you do whatever
you want can be selfish.
But... I wouldn't
change you if I could...
I would, however,
risk life and limb
to blast my way in here
to tell you that.
Please, don't do
this to me, Clain.
Whatever's gonna
happen up there,
I want the two of us in it
together as much as possible...
No. The three of us.
Clain, Nessa and Phryne
will be together.
Forever and ever...
No matter what happens.
Whatever you want, it can wait.
Get back to your post.
No slacking off till we've
reached neutral airspace.
I can see your face
reflected in the glass.
It's... just that
I don't know...
There there, girl: let it out...
Can I tell you something
I think might help...?
Despite what you might believe,
The Lost Millennium didn't arise
out of the intention to destroy
Fractale and the Temple.
It was meant to preserve the
memory of life before Fractale,
so that future
generations would know
there were once
alternatives.
In the end, that's the
essence of freedom.
It's beautiful...
Careful...
Try not to disturb anything;
remember, this is a sanctuary.
So then, what exactly are
we supposed to be doing?
I'm not sure.
Nessa's memory
is meant to lead us
from this point.
Nessa sees you...
Who do you see, Nessa?
That's you, Phryne!
That's God.
Hope I'm in the
shot... 'Kay, so...
I finished getting ready and I'm
about to head into work...
A couple of weeks
ago some people
with this thing called
Fractale or whatever told me
they were looking for a
girl to help 'em out...
I can't remember exactly how,
but it has to do with data...
I'm sorta nervous, actually...
But I've gotta buckle down
and go through with it if I
don't want Dad to get upset...
And the last thing any of us
want is for Dad to get upset.
But I'll be okay...
They're letting me bring
Nessa along for the ride!
"Everything's gonna be fine"...
I don't know what I'd
do without my Nessa;
I'm so glad they're letting you
be part of all this stuff...
"Nessa's not about to
let you face it alone."
Ha! That's what makes
you the best friend
a girl could ask for, right?
How cheerful she
is despite it all.
This is my favorite song! Hey...
What is Nessa going to wish for
from the Day Star this time...?
"Nessa wants to stuff
her face with cake!"
Ooo, that sounds good!
One with lots of
berries on top, yeah?
Ah, Dad's here--
gotta go... Bye-bye!
She's just... an
ordinary... girl...
A lot like me... That's right.
She's different from me, though,
because she can still smile...
She could accept the
world as she found it,
twisted and
malevolent as it was,
and still find something
worth taking joy in.
Just like Nessa.
Are you ready... to go?
Thank you. I can find
joy in the world now,
no matter what
I've been through.
Because of wonderful
people like you...
Because of Nessa...
What I'm doing now
I do because I want
to protect the people
I care about...
If that means I'm selfish,
so be it, Clain. I'm sorry.
I was wrong about that...
Whatever happens...
I'm here for you
both all the way.
Once you've merged,
I'll bring you home.
We'll live together
just like we planned.
I wanna protect what
I care about, too...
If that means letting you
go through with this...
So be it.
Can you stand?
Mm hmm.
Then what do you say to
a game of hide-n'-seek?
Phryne wants to play now?
You bet, only this time,
the whole world will
be our playground.
Nessa likes the sound of that...
Phryne is "it" first, though.
Whatever you want, sweetheart.
Thank you, Clain...
Thank you for you.
Nessa...
♪ I look up to the sky... ♪
♪ And offer my wish
to the day star... ♪
♪ Asking that Clain's
old smile... ♪
♪ Be boundless as the
wreathing blue... ♪
Oddly enough, I didn't cry...
It occurred to me
that anyone else in this
situation would, but...
For some reason...
I just didn't.
Not because I
wasn't sad... I was...
But what Phryne and Nessa wanted
most from me was a smile...
Maybe the best I could
do for them was not cry.
Time for the
Five O'clock Prayer.
Today we celebrate
the first anniversary
of Fractale's
glorious renewal...
Let us bear in the mind the
noble sacrifices of those
who made it possible as we offer
up a prayer for continued peace
and prosperity under Fractale's
benevolent guidance...
My left foot under its
benevolent guidance.
How gullible do those
drones think we are?
Let 'em spout whatever nonsense
helps 'em sleep at night;
least the Temple's out of
commission for now.
Good point.
Not to complain, but do our
nails have to get so grubby?
C'mon man, you're killin' me
here; of course they do.
You teaching these folks to
work the soil or aren't you?
I'm doing my best...!
Enri's taken to leadership
like a duck to water;
Sunda'd be so proud.
Yep.
Ooooh, I found a squirmy!
Look, your rear-end's stickin'
out like a sore thumb...
You gotta bend those knees more.
Get your hands off me, you perv!
What the heck was that for?!
Someone's taken a page
from Clain's book...
Maybe.
Yeah, well...
Don't expect to live up
to that tiger's level
any time soon...
That boy... I wonder
what he's up to.
You want some bread...?
Weirdo dog... Have at it.
You sure get excited over
something you can't taste.
It's been a year... I've started
cooking at home more...
Struck me as nice
chance of pace.
I'm getting better.
Another lovely day you're
sleeping through, girls.
Neither of 'em have stirred
so much as an eyelash
since that day.
Goin' out. Gonna
scrape something up
for us to call dinner.
Back in bit.
Hey, you're awake...
Have you ever seen
a morning so lovely?
Uh... Are you feeling...
The Day Star looks
so pretty! I like it...!
And I like liking things,
don't you?
Yeah, it's pretty
great, isn't it?
Nessa...?
Huh?
Oh, nothing... I was
just wondering
if you were hungry yet.
Am I hungry...?
Well this part in here
hurts a little bit so I
guess I must be...
Wait right there. I'll have
breakfast up in two shakes.
Hooray!
Clain... Thank you.
Thank you...
You've been the best friend
a girl could ask for.
And the truth is I've liked
you since the day we met...
You make me happier
than I've ever been.
You don't have to
get all weepy...
Though it is kind
of adorable...