Welcome back, my sister.
The stars are glad.
I implore each of you to
all look up to the stars
and give them
your prayers...
Be at peace.
Bask in abundance...
Crooked bastards are going right
on with the updating process...
Alright, plan A has
been officially thrown
out the window...
Time for plan B...
Bag ourselves a priestess!
Don't let them
infiltrate the altar!
Nessa, c'mon...!
Snap out of it; we've got to
get out of here right now.
It's Phryne...
Eternal happiness will
reign for the simple effort
of our obeisance to the sky.
Wha... What happened?
What the hell have
they done to us...?!
They're all...
Please...! Someone help us!
This should make
things easier.
Follow my lead, okay?
Don't be scared...
We're gonna have
a word with Phryne.
My Sister...
Come with us.
Phryne!
No!! What are you thinking?!
It's her!
Look alive or you can stay here!
We're gonna call it a day.
I've got the whole
world in my hands...
Somehow I thought it'd be a
little harder to get to.
Move it, dumbass!
What're you waiting for?!
Stop where you are!
Don't let them get away!
Please, Priestess,
can't you see? We're dying!
Unhand me!
Ugh. The Archpriestess must hear
of this outrage immediately!
Switch over to manual
navigation...
We don't want the Temple
sniffing us out.
Roger that.
Stupid... stupid...
fat bastard...
Would it have killed you
to lose some weight...?
We told you that you
gotta be able to run...
Damn you...
Damn you!!!
I've never seen a
dead guy before...
Not up close...
It's like... It's like he's made
of plastic now or something...
Just like that...
These people are murderers...
This is life for them.
Hey, it's me!
Uh... Hello...
How's it going down here?
Right, so...
Let's skip the small talk.
It's okay, we're going to get
you out... Just hold tight.
Take my word for it,
we're not among friends...
Just do me a favor... Take Nessa
back once we're out of here?
Argh! This knot's insane...
You're giving Nessa back?
Don't get me wrong,
it's been fun.
But Phryne is where you
really belong, okay?
Ta-da! Freedom!
Just who do you think you are?!
What made you think you were
entitled to awaken Nessa?
Wait, what...?
You walked out on me without
so much as saying thank you.
I was curious about the amulet
so I did a little research--
You presumed to research it...?!
What a despicably
untrustworthy thing to do!
Hold on...!
That's way out of line!
You can't let a mystery
like that hang in the air
and expect a guy not
to be interested!
Don't you dare hit
Clain ever again!
Don't... Nessa...
People who hit Clain are mean!
Nessa doesn't like mean people
and Nessa likes liking people!
Sorry, it's the legs.
They kinda got a mind
of their own, you know?
You don't say!
Yeah, so I'm gonna have to
break this little party up...
The priestess and I need
a moment to ourselves...
If you'll excuse us,
I'll escort her
somewhere a
bit more private.
I don't need to be escorted.
You all right?
Nessa doesn't dislike
very many things...
But she definitely dislikes her.
Daughter of the Archpriestess--
excuse me: Key to the World...
Why'd you run away
from the Temple?
Oh yeah... and that
flighty little dopple
you decided to take with you
as a parting gift... Is she...?
It's not important...
Only a matter of time
before the whole shebang
collapses anyway.
That's one way of
putting it, yes.
Oh...? So we share
that opinion...?
Well, you know,
with that attitude,
someone with your
knowledge of the Temple
would be a prized
addition to the family.
But we'd want you to take your
time with a leap that big...
And in the meantime...
you can watch the world
crash and burn from
the safety our our ship.
Sound good?
Don't weep. We all return
to ash in the end.
That's the way of things...
Remember the cause
our brother died for.
You should be glad for him.
'Kay... I'll be glad...
I won't cry.
Atta girl. Spoken
like a warrior.
They really have no perspective.
I mean, give me a break...
At the end of the day
he was a terrorist...
He got what was coming to him.
♪ I look up to the sky, ♪
♪ and offer my wish
to the day star... ♪
♪ That there be
acceptance of pain... ♪
Nessa, cut it out!
♪ til it shines like a... ♪
♪ ...to the sky...
and offer... ♪
Whatcha lookin' at?
Granny...?
What is it?
Put on your goggles, dear.
♪ I look up to the sky, ♪
What the hell is she singing?
♪ and offer my wish
to the day star... ♪
Take off your visor!
Oh, sweetheart,
he didn't mean to yell.
♪ We bid the day
star goodnight... ♪
♪ Though darkness will
fall as it slumbers... ♪
♪ Our dreams will reach
out to the sky... ♪
♪ shining from heights
above like the stars. ♪
♪ I look up to the sky... ♪
Another of Fractale's stars has
dislodged from the firmament,
as did its sister
the day before,
and their sisters
before that...
This world is crumbling
before our eyes;
fast approaching the brink.
For that reason,
the Lost Millienium
will no longer be tolerated...
We have forgiven them
their wayward antics
in days past out of pity;
that ends now.
By abducting one of the
world's Beloved Maidens,
they have effectively
surrendered their right
to our indulgence...
That they would take advantage
of Fractale's decadent
state is unpardonable.
There is but one answer for
such an offense... Suppression.
If these errant
children still refuse
to reenter the fold
in the here and now,
then they will embrace Fractale
in the sweet hereafter.
These goggles are too
big for me, Grandma!
Come here, love.
They've already got us on
their Most Wanted list.
Well, they can cast their
nets wide as they want.
We should still be pretty safe
here, as long as we're watching
the lower frequencies bouncing
off the radial outposts.
We come bearing gifts: food and
blankets for the lot of you.
Oho! Thank you!
Go on and wheel 'em in...
Is it true that the whole clan's
gonna clear out of town?
Yeah, it's better for everyone
if we leave before the Temple
tries to get its hooks
into you for helping us.
Right now, they're only
ticked off at the Granites,
and we'd like to
keep it that way.
The last thing any of us want
to do is draw their attention
to the good folks who've given
us a hand when we needed it.
It's inconcievable how
cruel the Temple can be...
Forcing an angel like Sanko
into life on the run.
Well I'm a whole lot stronger
than the temple thinks I am...!
I can even eat fish bones
sometimes like Grampa!
In theory, you all stand a much
better chance of survival
the further away the Granite
clan gets from here.
Well yeah, but what
about your own chances?
We'll be alright...
It's a helluva lot easier
running from ghosts than
flesh-and-blood human beings.
And what are they but
a bunch of ghosts...?
I mean, face it:
that's why the Temple idiots
want us in the first place--
they're jealous
of the lifeblood coursin'
through our veins!
Maybe, but...
Hey, you agree
with me, don'tcha?
That's right,
use those lungs...!
Take a page, everyone: the
future cries out to be fed!
Fed on a steady diet of fresh
air, adventure and true freedom!
Sunda...
We should all be wailing
like babes right now...
Let our voices be heard!
The Lost Millienium
is the future...
And the Granite clan is
proud to be a part of it.
Get a move on, we sail at dawn!
No time for dilly dallying!
Now what?
We get out of here while
we're on solid ground...
We've got a ways to go.
We're running away?
Yup. We're stuck between
a rock and a hard place
the longer we stay here...
The Temple's no good and we
can't trust these freaks...
But what am I going
to do about Phryne?
Stop it! Clain's thinking
about Phryne, isn't he?!
Well, I...
Get that mean person out of
your head right this instant!
Think only about
Nessa from now on!
Nessa! Nessa! Nessa!
--Nessa! Nessa! Nessa!
--Okay, okay! Cut it out!
Nessa! Nessa!
All woman and children
take cover in the rocks!
Everyone else to
defensive positions!
Bear in mind, people,
our first priority
is to steer the Beloved Maiden
clear of the enemy.
Innocent bystanders should be
spared whenever possible,
but don't let them cloud
your judgement...
If these Granites
get in your way...
You have my permission to fire.
However, we do not intend
this to be a massacre.
I want these poor
souls to see us
as avatars of
Fractale's blessing...
Hey-hey! Didn't take
you long to find us, huh?
Oh we've been aware
of this place...
In her munificence though,
the Archpriestess
turned a blind eye to you...
Would that your sense of
gratitude were equal to it.
Yeah. Damn shame, that.
Now...! Show no mercy!
Come... on...!
Nicely done, Enri.
Now go do the east side before
the bastards circle around back!
Granny, what are you doing?
We've got to hurry!
Where'd Nessa run off to?
I can't see her...
She's just a dopple, she's fine.
Okay. This isn't good.
Wow. Look at all the
pretty flashing lights, Clain!
Nessa, c'mon!
Phryne! That must be where
they were keeping her...
She's gonna get herself killed.
Don't even think
about rescuing her!
What?
Nessa forbids you
from resucing Phryne!
Nessa, c'mon! This is
no time to be jealous...
She's gonna get hurt if
we don't help her out.
So?
Look, I'm going to her.
You're not just gonna
stand there...? Seriously?
Suit yourself.
Phryne!
Where is she?
W-Well, uh...
You don't have to cover for her.
I know she hates me.
What? No... I mean...
It might surprise you to know
she was very fond of you
long before you had
the chance to meet.
I thought no one would be able
to access that data
without guidance...
Least of all someone like you...
How could you?
Where are you going?!
I can't let myself be
captured by the temple!
I'm sorry, but I don't
think you and I
are very likely to
see each other again.
Whether you like it or not...
I have a right to
know what's going on!
You totally left me in the dark!
I'm sorry but there's
no way I'll let you
try and pull that crap
on me a second time!
If I left you in the dark
it was for a good reason,
can't you see that?!
Is it so wrong of me
to wanna get to know
you a little better?!
That's why I hacked the
amulet in the first place...
I just wanted to see if--
Oh, thank the stars;
our Beloved Maiden is all right.
I was getting a little worried.
They've got us.
Clain! Do you...?
What did you say...?
I couldn't hear you!
I was asking if I happened
to be somone you like...
Nessa said she likes
liking people, right...?
Well, I'm sorry... I don't
feel the same way she does.
L... Look out!!!
There you are,
you naughty little girl.
Innocent blood was about to
be spilt because of you...
Are you so selfish that
another's life holds no value?
No, of course we know
you're better than that.
Don't we... Darling girl?
Who the heck is this creep?
It's a shame the same
thing can't be said
of your would-be abettor...
Whatever he's convinced you
his motives are,
Phryne, he only wants
what every hormone-riddled
boy his age wants.
Now, you've only
three choices...
And sadly, the world has
just so much time to spare
waiting for you to
reach a decision...
The first option...?
You behave
as one of the World's Beloved
Maidens are meant to behave...
What is he talking about?
Which means you return to
the temple without a fuss.
Two... You could do
so flailing about like a bird...
Or three, you could stay out
here in the wilderness
and waste away to nothing.
Which will it be?
Disconsolate child!
There is no fourth option!
Phryne, wait...!
What are you gonna do?!
Whoa...
Maybe she really can fly.
How much must those
who love you endure
before you'll see reason?!
Damn it all! If you
let them get away,
every one of you can bid your
careers a bitter farewell!
Fly to the corners of
the earth, if you like!
Your foulness leaves a
trail wherever you go!
I will sniff out your inequities
and track you like common game!
Well, well... Come
crawling back, did we...?
I feel for you, kiddo...
Your options out there must've
been pretty bleak to choose us.
I don't want to hear it!
Nessa...? Are you here?
Did Nessa come with you?
A dopple can go
wherever it pleases;
for all we know she's
dancing on the hull...
Or waiting in ambush
for me in the bathroom.
Nessa, I'm sorry I left you
by yourself out there.
Please don't be mad.
It won't happen again.
Great. She's sulking...
She doesn't want to
come out and play?
Well, give it time. I'm sure
she'll turn up before too long.
As long as I'm here...
Don't bet on it.
Clain...
You big doof...
Down by the salley gardens
my love and I did meet
She passed the salley gardens
with little snow-white feet
She bid me take love easy,
as the leaves grow on the tree
But I, being young and foolish,
with her did not agree
But I was young and foolish,
and now I am full of tears