Good news, we're
about to converge
on a huge blind spot in
the system's coverage.
Good. So we've made
a clean break of it?
We're out of the
woods for now,
but don't start popping
corks just yet.
Just a matter of time
till another hot zone.
One day at a time, Gramps...
Proceed as you will.
Looks like we're back to
square one, doesn't it?
I hope at least after all that,
you can appreciate
that our goals aren't
mutually exclusive.
So, uh, where's the
ship headed to...?
Any place marked out
or are we flying blind?
Hah! File that question under
"none of your business."
You should know you're
in great peril here
since you don't
serve a purpose...
You're more like a
growth than a passenger.
Is that a threat?
So where'd that sprightly
little dopple run off to, huh?
Without putting on a visor,
I can't see or hear her.
What makes you
think I would know?
C'mon. The two of you
are attached at the hip.
Look, it's complicated...
Sort of...
No matter... Just keep
the leash nice n' tight
so she doesn't get
herself into trouble.
Lucky for you, if you can
endure being treated
like a fifth wheel for a bit,
we'll cut you loose.
Eventually, that is.
It may be a while
before we can plan a side
trip to drop you off,
so best steel yourself
to being here... Unless...
Wait, I--
This is...
Your very own parachute...
Not a lot of people get to
experience freefall these days.
May seem a bit daunting
on the face of it,
but the most you'll
do is break a leg...
You want me to show
you how to use it?
If you don't have the
balls for that, kiddo,
I suggest you make
yourself useful.
Seriously...? Who cleans
by hand anymore?
It's barbaric...
No, that's not it...
I can think of a better word.
The seat back has not
been sufficiently cleaned.
You've got to be kidding!
Ugh! I just told you those
go up on the shelf, bozo!
I heard you... I just need
a second to rest, okay?
Oh, hey, don't worry:
you can rest all you want
after I throw your lazy butt
off the prow of the ship!
For your information,
I didn't sign up
to be a cabin boy for
a bunch of terrorists.
You know for someone who treats
women like slabs of beef,
you sure do take the moral
high ground an awful lot...
The Lost Millennium is
not about terrorism.
Oh, please.
Spare me the lecture.
Well, go on! No one is forcing
you to stay on board...
'Course we know you're
too afraid to jump.
You think I'm too scared
to use a stupid parachute?
You're miserable and still
on the ship, aren't you?
Maybe I have other reasons.
What's that supposed to mean?
Wait... Don't tell me you're
thinking all pervy again.
Give me a break already...
I wasn't thinking anything
pervy... It's not like that.
Easy does it, son.
Your first time doing
laundry, I take it?
Ah, me, how I envy all
the new experiences
in store for someone your age.
Very satisfying, isn't it?
You sweat all over the
clothes you work in,
then clean 'em again,
hang 'em out to dry,
only to repeat the
whole mess over.
Circle of life, eh?
In fact...
From the looks of 'em,
I'd say your pants could
use a good scouring.
You... think?
Take 'em off and hand 'em over.
Wait... This second?
Uh-huuuh.
But don't we need to
get this laundry done?
Now, now...
There's no need for you
to feel embarrassed.
Please, I'm begging you;
don't... do...
Oh!
What on earth is that?
I... saw this in an old book
and thought it looked cool.
Well, I don't know
about "cool," but...
You are a man.
First the square one,
then the long one...
then we find a little one...
Oh, good job...!
Now make that one next!
Hold on; I'll go
get us some more.
Who are you talking to?
I'm playing with Nessa.
Aw, she's gone...
Nessa...! Will you just
come out already...?
I know you're here somewhere...
Why could Sanko see
her and I couldn't?
Does she hate me now? Fantastic.
C'mon! Don't be like this!
Fortunately, the Obsidian
boys down south
are willing to take us all in,
if we try to keep a low
profile for the time being.
Do you guys always eat together?
Heh. Sure.
Food's always better
when you have some good
conversation with it...
Try to do this whenever we can.
How do you not get
sick of each other?
They keepin' you busy, tiger?
Feels good. Right?
Life returning to those
rarely-used limbs?
Just reminds me how much
I prefer not to be busy.
Naturally... You can
lead a horse to water
but you can't make him think.
A boy raised as this one's
been is never going to learn
the value of a hard day's work.
I don't want to teach
him anything, Gramps,
I just want the kid to earn
his keep while he's with us.
Give me some credit. I'm not
that much of a romantic.
So you've told us for years.
Not yet, son.
We must say grace.
You say grace...?
To the Temple?
That's a good one,
kid, but no way.
Granny's talking about
something nobler
than a Temple prayer;
though if I had my druthers,
there'd be no prayer
of any kind on this ship.
Sunda...
Look, I'm not trying to
start another argument.
I'm just saying this
constant need for prayer
is what got the human race
into such a bind to begin with.
Institutions like the
Temple have been
taking advantage
of it from day one.
Phryne isn't here.
I told her to come.
Don't expect too
much of a priestess.
You gotta remember,
kid, she's had
a lifetime's worth of training
just to prevent her
from becoming a
heathen like us.
If you're here, please come out.
Think only about
Nessa from now on!
Believe me, I'm trying to.
Why is this getting me
so bent out of shape?
Hi there...
Sorry! I really wasn't trying
to spy on you or anything...!
I was told these clothes
were for anyone...
So I came to pick something out.
You had a chance to
meet the busybodies
that do all the washing up here?
Mm mm. Do I look strange?
Uh... No, you...
look great.
I thought as much.
I haven't seen her for a while.
Typical.
You mean she does this kind
of thing all the time?
Well, only when she's jealous.
Wait, what?
Like it or not, she's become
very attached to you.
Well, attached to the idea of
messing with my head, maybe.
I don't know about "jealous."
I mean, surely she's not...
You really think that?
You're rather fond of those
boxers... Aren't you?
You know, I... At first I
guess I just kind of assumed
that Nessa was
your dopple... But...
I hate to ask...
But did you take
the amulet she was in
without, like, permission...?
'Cause that would explain
why everyone's after you...
I mean, not that any of
this is my business!
But if you wanted to
talk about this stuff...
Like, for example,
why that creep
called you a Beloved Maiden...
I'm sorry. I shouldn't
pry so much...
It's just, all these things
are in my head now...
Just answer me one thing, okay?
Do you... dislike Nessa
as much as it seems?
If I do, it's a function
of how I'm meant to act.
What does that even mean?!
Fine. Leave me in
the dark, why don't you...
Does it not seem to be
getting rather hot?
You're just now noticing?
It's been hot.
The hell's going on? The place's
heating up like a stove!
It's a systems malfunction...
Trying to pin it down!
You mean you don't know which
system's on the blink...?
Tell me you can
fix this, Gramps.
I'm workin' on it...
Keep your shirt on;
it's no big deal...
At least it'll keep
us on our toes!
What's with this heat?
Someone forget to clean a vent?
Looks like we're keepin' cool
the old-fashioned way.
I don't like this. The two
of you hanging together
can't be a promising sign...
Is he up to his old tricks?!
Man, you really don't
have an off switch!
Well! No wonder the ship is
starting to feel like an oven!
Don't turn this into a joke;
you'll only encourage him!
Sorry everybody--
These clothes are comin' off.
Nobody wants to see that
coat rack you call a body.
Hey, whoa!
Something wrong?
What's going on with the heat?
Hey! Mind your
own business, kid.
Come on...! Maybe there's
some way I can help.
Get the hell out of here!
We don't have time to
babysit you too, kid!
Check-up commencing...
Please sit at the proper angle
with your genitals exposed.
Mind your own business.
That's an impressive
patchwork...
It's amazing what you can
do with balloon shrapnel.
I may have a newfound respect
for this crew... This might be
the best piece of stitched-
together technology I've seen.
I hate to admit it,
but this thing might be
a little out of my league.
It's got to be a glitch in
the pre-Fractale components...
Don't you think?
Hmm...
I don't believe it!
How many old OS-es
did they hash together
to build this thing?
I mean, some of this stuff
predates Fractale
by generations...
Even if I can hack it,
finding the issue's
going to be a whole other thing.
Funny this is what we're
reduced to, huh...?
User manuals; might as
well study warrantees.
Still, ancient texts do get
the blood up don't they?
Sure.
Not even a 26th century
patch works?
Alright, then...
What the heck?!
Hm? The hell is that beeping
noise? And why's it roving?
Hey, listen!
Get off this channel, ya brat!
Hang on; let him talk.
You're hearing
that noise, right?
I think it's got to be Nessa...
Nessa?
I may just be shooting
in the dark here...
but I saw a similar sine-wave
when I first let her out.
That doesn't fly, kid.
The blip showed up when we
probed one of the older OS-es.
No way a dopple
would be compatible
with a system dating
that far back.
Yeah, I know...
Sounds crazy, but still...
So then what you're
telling me is that Nessa's
wreaking havoc on
our ship, is that right?
Probably.
Just what we need.
A rogue program pitching a fit.
What's going on?!
For some reason the
auto-pilot's decided
to go for a coffee break...
Or it likes storms.
Steer the hell around it!
I'm trying! The controls aren't
responding worth a damn!
Kid, you've got to
call Nessa out!
I would, but... She's kind
of upset with me right now...
Oh, great. She's upset...
What did you do to her now?
Nothing...
Heh. That's what seeing
two girls at once gets ya.
Look, kid whatever she's
mad at you for, trust me;
find a way to make her feel
real special real quick
or this clunker's toast.
You could fry an egg
on my forehead...
Somebody please open a window.
Yeah, and put out a lightning
rod while we're at it?
Look at the bright side;
this is an excellent way
to shed those unwanted
extra pounds.
If this is an endurance
test from the higher ups,
then I am jumping ship.
Don't worry, people!
We know what the problem is...
The trick is finding Nessa
and persuading her to come
out of her hiding place
before things get
worse than they are.
Are you insane...? What's
Nessa got to do with this?
Let's just say the
longer she hides out,
the more the rest of us
are gonna feel the heat.
Good enough for me.
If it'll cool things off,
I'm up for a little hunt.
How do we find a dopple that
doesn't intend to be found?
I'll track her at a console
and fill everybody in...
But if I know Nessa at all,
the best way to coax her out
of wherever she is will be
to make her think we're all
having a lot more fun out here.
Perfect! My boy, I can whip up
something in the kitchen
to lure the stubbornest child!
That'd be great if she
could actually eat food...
Wait a minute. Once, she had me
explain the taste of something
by doing this crazy
dance for her!
I believe we can manage
something like that.
Uh... For your
lentil soup,
perhaps a little
something like this?
Surely it's got a much
livelier flavor than that...!
Look at me!
Take a lesson from
the Master, ladies!
Yeah, of course...
Why wouldn't this work...?
What a way to go...
Taking advantage of the havoc
your little friend
caused, ya pervert?
Oooo! Nessa's never
seen this game before!
What a good way to
keep nice and warm!
Yeah. It'd be
great if it didn't
already feel like
a stove in here...
Hey! There she is!
Sorry, sorry...
You stepped on my hand!
Be careful!
She's in storage now! Wait...
She's moved to the kitchen!
She's moving down shaft C-3...
Nessa! Come out come out
wherever you are...
Please?
My darling little girl...
You can run but you can't hide.
There she is!
Together, just as I thought...
but Nessa is our first priority.
Oh no, she's gone...
How long is she going
to keep us all hunting
for her like this...?
It's been hours.
Please, sweetheart!
This is foolishness!
I'll have you know you're
still our prisoner!
You've got no right to lock
us out of our own hold!
Prisoner...?
Phryne!
Open the stupid door!
It's for your own good...
I know you can hear
me in there, girl!
Phryne!
It's no use! The systems
have all the hatches
on automatic lockdown...
What are you even
doing in there?!
It's all my fault.
Nessa won't come out
because of me... I know it.
No you don't!
C'mon, it's Nessa!
For all we know,
something shiny
caught her attention...
She probably doesn't
even remember
why she's hiding
in the first place.
She's just having fun with us;
that's all this is, believe me.
This is why I didn't want you to
bring her out of the amulet.
Phryne, please...
Seeing her is too painful.
I didn't wish to endure it!
What are you talking about?
As far as the
Temple's concerned,
Nessa is infinitely more
important than I am...
I just... I wanted to take
her away from them
so we could put an end
to this whole thing!
Put and end to what...?
I don't understand you!
For us, putting a stop to
this endless repetition
is the only way that we...
No! Whatever you're
talking about,
there's got to be a better way!
If you just turn your back
on whatever it is,
things can't get better.
Think about it;
Nessa would never let you
talk this way if she
could hear you...
She's having too much
fun to end it all...
We could all learn
a lesson from that.
I mean, hey... That childlike
enthusiasm is kind of infectious
if you just let it work
its magic on you...
Take me for example:
I'd have never thought
this whole mess was
anything but a drag
if I hadn't stopped to see
it through her eyes...
But now I'm actually
having fun...
Nessa's an unfettered
soul. If we'd all just
take a page from her book,
we'd be the same way.
How dare you?
You don't have the first clue
what you're talking about...
Don't presume to tell me what it
feels like to be "unfettered"!
Then tell me what I'm
supposed to say!
Explain the situation!
I just want to help you!
No... I won't let you!
Wait! Phryne! Don't do
this! I'm begging you!
Phryne! Phryne!
Phryne?
Are you looking for
a good hiding place?
Nessa...
Oh, no. Don't be sad...
Nessa doesn't like
to see you cry.
Nessa doesn't understand
why people cry.
It's fine...
I'm just hiding like you.
You like to hide?!
I like to be found.
You've been found...?
Who found you?
You did... Which means
Nessa did good.
Really? So you
want Nessa to find you?
It's okay if Nessa plays
hide-and-seek with you?
I don't see why not
if you'd like to.
Okay, then... Nessa's
found Phryne and she's it!
You have to do better than that.
The rules to this game
are a little different.
You have to take me by the hand.
Like this...?
Nessa captured Phryne!
When Phryne found Nessa--
no, wait: rather,
when Nessa found Phryne,
all the system glitches
disappeared in
the blink of an eye
and the ship returned to
what, for it, was normal.
Better still, Nessa settled in
to life among the Granites
like nothing could
be more natural.
She wasn't the only one who
settled in, though.
Phryne started joining the
rest of us for mealtime;
even started smiling
every now and then.
They no longer yell me
off the flight deck
when I come in to gawk at the
old-fashioned gauges and stuff.
Oh... And I still
wear a fundoshi.
No! Stop it!
Please! Waaahhh!
But they made me a red one.