We're here!
Ah... Good for the ol' dogs
to be on solid ground.
One more league to
the west and we'd be
right back within
range of Fractale...
I'd say this is an ideal spot
for us to do some
routine maintenance.
Yeah... Wouldn't
want the old girl
going all fluey on
us again, would we?
Right, Clain?
No sir!
Well, while the men folk are
tinkering with the ship,
why don't we gals
cook up a nice meal
as a reward for all of
their hard work?
You heard Granny.
Let's cook!
Not to be a nay-sayer,
but c'mon...
The temple's bound to have
extended its reach--Hello?
I don't like this one bit...
Huh?
If we're out of range,
then why is it
we can still see
that dopple girl?
Wow... No offense,
but that is painful to watch...
Here, just let me get the rest.
I can do this!
See, look...! I'm
peeling it so that
the skin will come off
in a single piece.
Of all the dunder-head things
to get particular about...
Good grief.
Hey, no fair!
You can't get wet!
Dang it, Sanko! I can tell
you're playing with Nessa!
Get up here and help us!
Come on, Phryne! Swim! Let's go!
This is not good.
My... That Phryne is
a bold one, isn't she?
You act all prim and proper,
but you sure strip down
at the drop of a hat!
And if I know Clain, by now I
bet his radar is going nuts!
Surprised the perv's
not here already--
Hey!
Guys! Sunda wants you...
Clain's a peeping Tom!
Clain is a pervert!
No! I didn't know
you guys were--
Perv, perv, perv...
Clain is a pervert!
Cut it out!
The water's cold! Ah!
He's got a camera!
He's taking pictures!
Hold on!
Clain!
Wait! I just want to...
A genuine, antique digital
camera that actually works!
That's awesome!
Your kind have to look out for
each other, is that it...?
There anything you pervs won't
let each other get away with?
It's one thing to have it...
But getting it to work?
Are you still thinking
about the camera guy...?
Oh, wow...
Where are they going?
Dunno.
They go wherever the
wind carries them.
We call 'em out of
range refugees.
They look pretty lost.
Yeah... It's sad.
When the balloons
crashed and burned,
the radio frequencies
fell off out this way
and left these people
without access.
You're looking at souls who've
grown so dependent on Fractale
they don't know any
other way to live.
Only choice open
to 'em is to pick up
and seek out another hot zone.
The system failed them.
Left them dry...
They've been more
or less condemned
to live life as a
nomadic tribe...
I get pissed off just
thinking about it.
Oh, man...
Nessa...
Let go! There's not a damn
thing in here for you!
This is mine!
Don't give us that
line, old man...!
We're not stupid; you're
hiding food in there!
Ah! It's...!
We're better off leaving it be;
fights like these break out all
the time between these types...
They're animals,
every last one of 'em.
Oh, no!
Uh-oh!
No!!
Put it down!
Who the hell are you?!
Stop! You'll break something
more valuable than food!
Have you lost your mind...?!
This is not a scuffle you want
to get in the middle of...!
Trust me on this!
Everybody, freeze!
Who are you?
That hurt...?
Ah, but this pain is such a
petty, superficial thing...
Not really the core of your
problem, I would guess.
Hey! Let go of me...
I bet it's nothing compared
to what your heart feels...
Shattering under the
weight of betrayal...
knowing Fractale
abandoned all of you...
Stop it, Dias.
Well, look at that... Sunda...
Feels like I haven't
seen you in forever.
Wish I could say I
felt the same way...
Still up to no good?
You two know each other?
Everyone's attention,
if you please...
We are from the Alabaster clan;
a proud part of the movement
known as Lost Millennium...
Our mission is to aid those
whom Fractale left behind...
poor souls searching
for a signal.
One sector to the east lies
a village reduced to ruins
by Fractale's treachery,
now our outpost.
If you will follow me there,
you'll have food
and a warm bed to sleep in.
Don't be afraid...
We bear you no ill will.
Well, that was kinda weird...
Where's he going?
No loyalty among
perverts, huh...?
You'd think he'd at
least say thank you.
Where you going?!
Where the heck could
he have gotten to?
You're kidding me!
An antenna?!
You followin' me?
It's not what you think...!
Your hobbies are fine with me.
I don't care who you
photograph...?!
I mean, sure,
it's kind of strange
when you try to be all sneaky...
but Phryne does kind of
take her clothes off a lot,
and you couldn't have
known that about her...
Answer me this then, kid...
Why'd you come all this way?
Because... You seem
like a neat guy
to strike up a friendship with.
Look at all this stuff...!
You've got to be kidding!
Whoa...! Vacuum tubes!
I've never seen any up
close like this before...!
This place is like a
friggin' museum!
Got a thing for antiques, do ya?
Yeah!
The hell for...? They're just
garbage from another age...
Flotsam and jetsam.
I guess you're right...
I don't know why.
Dad kept an old projector
in the house...
Maybe that's what started it.
I couldn't really tell you why
my folks had one lying around...
But the damage was done.
Their dopples
consider it junk...
They're always on my
back to throw it out
'cause they think it
clutters the place up.
A twenty-first
century cell phone!
Heh... Those were the days
when people appreciated
things you could
actually hold in your hand...
They really knew what they
were doing back then...
No mere raw data for
those folks, huh?
Don't tell me...
You're with the L.M.
For the record, I'm not
"with" anybody--
certainly not a bunch of
half-baked extremists!
But, uh... Well, I guess
if I'm totally honest...
I suppose they're not
really all that bad.
Somebody's got a lot to learn.
There's a new moon tonight,
boy... You're just in time...
Why don't you come back
here after it gets dark?
I'll show you something
you won't soon forget.
What?! That was all
we had for tonight?!
Of course it was...!
Should have been here on time
if you were so hungry...!
Part of being a valued
member of this group
is following the rules...
So tough titty!
Oh, wait... Those
Alabaster guys
said they were distributing
food, right...?
Surely they still have
enough left over to--
You even think of mooching
off the Alabaster gang--
I'll throw you out of
the Danan myself!
Aren't you guys all part
of the same thing...?
What've you got against them?
Let's just say not all
Lost Millennium factions
see eye to eye...
Not every revolutionary
mind is created equal.
Oh, yeah?! Because if you ask
me, between Dias and Sunda...
It's pretty clear which of them
has a better head on their--
You know it really is
just too bad someone
couldn't be bothered to show
up for dinner on time...
It's a helluva thing having
to keep watch all night
on an empty stomach.
What are you up to?
Uhh... Please don't tell...!
You can't imagine how
badly I need to do this!
What's so important you're
willing to get into trouble?
Well... This is probably
gonna seem a little odd to you,
but I kind of made a promise
to that guy with the camera.
One pervert to another?
No, no! Believe me...!
This guy really isn't like that
at all... at least... I think.
Wow. This man has certainly
piqued your interest...
Well, that settles it then;
I'm going with you.
Look, we... sorta agreed to
make this just between us men...
I'm sorry, but girls
aren't... allowed.
I will have you know, mister,
that I am Phryne
before I'm a girl...
Did this person
expressly tell you
no "Phrynes" were allowed
on your little excursion?
Well, no, but... Ugh! Fine!
Hmm. What's going on down there?
That must be the Alabaster camp.
Patience people!
No cutting in line!
There's more than
enough to go around;
everyone'll get their share.
Vaccinations are now
available, my friends...
And if you're not aware
of the alpha virus
the malnourished
are susceptible to,
all the more reason
to protect yourself.
Are the vaccinations...?
Free? Yes... Donay and
Monay units are little more
than empty numbers to members
of the Lost Millennium.
I don't know how to thank you...
You truly are a godsend!
No one's ever been
this good to us!
It's the least we could do.
It's more than enough!
One of these days,
we're going to repay you for
the kindness you've shown.
Please... Come in.
Yes, sir!
Right. Line up!
Oh, wow... I guess
Lost Millennium
attracts all types
of people, huh?
You gotta admit: handing
out vaccinations
for free is pretty
darn impressive.
All the same... I think I
prefer the Granite clan to them.
Hey, look, don't get me wrong:
I'm not down on Sunda and the
group or anything... I mean...
yes, I do think they've
got some problems,
but deep down they're
a good bunch.
You're still implying
that Alabaster's better.
Look at it objectively...
You saw how well taken care
of those refugees were...
What's your problem?
Can't stand to lose, can you?
No more than you can!
A girl?
You're not mad... are you?
A pleasant evening to you,
sir... I'm coming inside.
You can't just barge
in there... jeez!
Is this your girlfriend?
Ew, no!
Alright, then...
I suppose she can join us.
Hey, thanks a lot...!
Come on, Phryne! Hurry up!
'kay.
Okay, I'll give her the whole
"I'm Phryne before
I'm a girl" thing...
But she could at least
still act like a girl.
Holy cow! It looks even more
incredible up close...!
The way you must've
scrapped this thing together
has a lot in common
with the Danan.
Almost there...
In just a few seconds...
I'll show you something
that blows antiquing
out of the water.
Nights of the new moon...
The temple range-tests a
bunch of the older balloons...
Spikes up the base frequency
just a fraction...
If I tune this baby right,
the antenna array picks it up.
I get it... This is how
this place looked
before the balloon fell and
it lost its connectivity.
You got it, son... That's
what my work here's about...
I'm gonna plug this no man's
land back into the grid.
Right or wrong, Fractale
is how we live now.
People can't
function without it,
and why even try...?
It's better than
wandering around
aimlessly in the darkness...
By god...! Give me
one good reason
a place like this doesn't
deserve a second chance...!
I...
You okay?
Not yet...! The best part's
still 'round the corner,
believe you me...
Come on, girl.
Climb down and go
to the square.
See for yourselves...
trust me... It's amazing.
If you say so.
it's unbelievable!
This is a Fractale town!
Hey! What is it you see?
What the hell...?
I can't see anything!
What is going on?
Where the heck did he fall?
Hold on a minute! Clain!
It's not what it seems!
What happened?
Mr. Dias...
The connection's restored...
What the hell--
we haven't finished
the procedure on
everyone yet...
Mister... What is this...?
What's going on...?! I--
Ah. Are you ill at ease...?
I might've misled you
about the vaccination...
What we actually
did was remove
your Fractale
terminals permanently.
You bald-faced liar!
Where did all that
gratitude go...?
And you swore to
repay our kindness.
Come now...
Redirect that anger...
Use it to help us fight
against Fractale.
I'm out of here!
That so?
Escape is someone
else's dream...
Provided you could
find another hot zone,
you've been stripped
of your terminals for good.
Connection is impossible.
But don't worry... Lost
Millennium will provide for you.
No!
You all right?
Please tell me you're alright!
Has... Has it already
blinked out?
Mister!
Good as the antenna is,
the frequencies it picks
up are transient...
But you saw it...? The square?
Yes, I... I think...
But that's not important now...!
You need a hospital...!
Please, Mister...
The Danan can drop you off
somewhere in range
of Fractale...
You can get proper
medical treatment!
Heh... I don't think so.
But... You could die!
So...? Heh...
There's no one around
anymore to grieve
over a cranky old
hobbyist like me.
Not true... I'd be really
sad to see you go.
Back home I never hang
out with real people...
All I do is interact
with dopples...
Hardly anyone shares
my hobbies...
And those that do--
I don't know their faces!
So, yeah...! I'd grieve.
You're very nice... But...
I couldn't abandon this
old place if I wanted to.
Of course you could!
This house and its clutter
is an extension of me.
My most precious memories are
the junk of bygone eras.
You said so yourself:
this stuff isn't
some digital ether,
it's real; tangible.
A lot of people wouldn't
understand it...
And I wouldn't really
expect 'em to...
But if I'm gonna keep
searching for Fractale,
unless it's from here
there's no point to it for me.
It's alright. I get it.
Tell you what...
This should be yours.
Why are you giving this to me?
He'll be okay.
Oh... Pics?
Stolen ones, I'm afraid.
You stole these...?!
You've got some scary layers
to you, you know that?
Wait, these are the pictures
that pervert took!
And I'm a little surprised at
the subject matter, actually...
This one's quite a bit
older than the others.
Aww! Little baby fingers!
I think I have a pretty good
idea who this baby is.
Oh, yeah? Who?