[RIN] I always wanted
to be like my dad.
[RIN, RIN'S DAD laughing]
[RIN'S DAD] Rin, when on
earth did you get so big?
You're gonna grow up strong.
I'd bet money on it.
[BOTH laugh]
Daddy!
Oh.
Who's this?
My favorite daughter,
Gou! Ready to fly?
[RIN'S DAD] All right.
Hang on tight! Ally-oop!
--[GOU] Bestest biceps!
--[RIN] Super strong!
[GOU]
Read this book to me?
[RIN'S DAD]
"And then, they finally reached
the island of the demons."
Then, the demons came out?
That's right.
There were a lot of em.
Oh, wait. I can
count them for you!
One, two, three...
[RIN'S DAD]
Whoa, what an amazing counter!
[RIN]
Gou and I loved our father.
Look! Those're panties!
[laughs] No, they're swimsuits.
When Daddy was little, he
competed in a lot of swim meets,
and, of course,
he won all the time!
[BOTH gasp]
[RIN]
Welcome home!
[RIN'S DAD]
Aw, thanks.
You won all the time!
Yeah, Mommy told us
how you did swim meets
back when you were a kid
and you always won.
She said you were the strongest!
I wanna swim, just like you!
[RIN'S DAD]
Okay, then.
Yes, that's perfect!
--[BOTH laugh]
--You kids are so good!
[gasps]
No fair! I want one.
Gimme one, too, Daddy!
You can have one
next time, okay?
[RIN] All I wanted was to
eventually be just like him.
[RIN] I thought those days
would continue forever.
[RIN] I wanted them
to continue forever.
But then...
[RIN'S DAD] Don't worry, we're
not going that far out today.
I'll be right back.
[MIYAKO]
Be careful.
Mommy?
[MIYAKO]
Sorry, hon. Did I wake you up?
Look at the clock.
It's not moving.
[MIYAKO] Oh, yeah, it stopped.
Hope it's not broken.
[MIYAKO] We'll be right back
after I drop off her clothes.
I'll be fine, Mom.
Tell Grandma I hope she starts
feeling better really soon.
[MIYAKO]
I'll tell her.
[phone rings]
Mom, you home?
[RIN]
Hello?
[MAN]
Uh, Matsuoka's boy, right?
Now, try to stay calm, son.
No one expected the
weather to get so bad.
Your father's boat
that left the fishing
harbor this morning--
it's been shipwrecked.
We can't get ahold of rescue,
but even if we could,
the waves are too
dangerous to send help.
[RIN] In an instant,
my whole world changed.
[RIN] I was just so,
so sad. My heart hurt.
[RIN]
But--
I wanted to support them.
[RIN]
I had to become stronger.
[SOSUKE]
You were really fast just then.
You wanna race
me now, don't you?
Sure, ready to lose?
[RIN]
At that tournament.
That guy was there.
Haru! Ow.
Why'd you just stop
out of nowhere?
'Cuz the light.
Jeez, maybe you should try
looking in front of you, Asahi.
It's not like I can help that!
'Cause of our meet today,
my vontage is now like
off the charts high!
You sure you didn't mean
your "voltage" is high?
Stupid.
[gasps] Oh, shut up,
and stop acting like...
[IKUYA]
Will you let me go?!
[MAKOTO] Both of you,
please knock it off!
[NAO]
Hurry.
You guys had better
get a move on.
You'll be late to
the practice meet.
Seriously?
You just did your team
best a little while ago.
What're you doing?
[NAO chuckles] At least you're
in sync with relay exchanges.
[IKUYA]
Not by choice.
[ASAHI]
What did you say?!
[MAKOTO] Stop it, for real!
We don't need any injuries!
[MIKOSHIBA] You don't look
all that scary anymore.
[RIN]
Huh?
You're kidding me, right?
I can't be captain!
[MIKOSHIBA]
It's my call.
I'm not qualified.
I mean, leading
the whole team...
[MIKOSHIBA] Quit whinin'.
I thought you wanted this.
Well, I--
Look, this is me sayin'
I believe in you.
[MIKOSHIBA]
Matsuoka.
Yes, sir.
Starting tomorrow morning,
you call the shots.
That means you're
the new captain.
[RIN]
Yes, sir.
I didn't see that one coming.
Rin's far from
the obvious choice
for Mikoshiba's replacement.
Are you crazy?
His body's in top shape!
If that's not a captain's
physique, I don't know what is!
[REI] No one's saying he
doesn't look fantastic.
[RIN]
Dad.
I'm following the
path I believe in.
[RIN]
So...
[SASABE]
Hm.
I guess.
Huh? Oh, hey, there!
You lookin' to join up?
I won't be operational
for another month,
but we're accepting
membership applications.
[SOSUKE]
No, thanks.
[RIN] To make it on
the Samezuka Swim Team,
you need to beat the
benchmark time, no exceptions.
Pay attention to form.
Pick a style you
feel comfortable with
and show us what you got.
[SWIMMERS]
Sir!
[gasps]
[NITORI]
You all right, sir?
You look a bit preoccupied.
[RIN] Ai. You really gotta
stop callin' me sir.
[NITORI]
But--
Just drop it.
[NITORI]
Yes, si-- Uh, okay.
There's a ton of people here.
I didn't know we'd
stirred up so much hype.
[RIN]
Maybe they wanna catch a glimpse
of the "world-class athlete"
Mikoshiba was talking about.
Do you think there's a chance
he's here right now?
I dunno, but keep
standing here you might
lose your place to a First Year.
Oh! Right!
[NAGISA]
How's it goin', Rin?
I'm good. What's up, Nagisa?
[NAGISA laughs] You think you'll
be free after practice today?
Let's see.
I don't have anything
planned. I guess so.
That's perfect.
Do you wanna come do
something fun with us, then?
Somethin' fun, huh?
[REI] Nagisa, wait!
You should invite him properly!
Rin doesn't want us
to be like that with him.
So how come you do?
Give me the phone,
and I can talk to him.
Rin?
Oh, hey, Haru.
[HARUKA] Come to
Iwatobi High around dusk.
You wanna race because we
got the same times again?
[HARUKA]
Show up or don't.
You don't have to be like that.
I'll come when I finish
checkin' the practice regimen.
Yo, it's me! Are you in there?
Let's do this. Whatever it is.
Huh.
Nothin' like chickening out
of your own show down.
[RIN]
Okay.
[gasps]
[RIN yelps]
[NAGISA]
Take him away!
[MAKOTO, REI]
Ki-ki!
[RIN grunts]
What the...? Put me down!
[HARUKA]
Don't be such a baby.
[NAGISA]
Haru, stay on script!
[HARUKA]
I mean, don't fight it.
[RIN] Somebody better
explain this to me!
[GOU]
Guys! What are you doing?
Put him down, now!
[RIN] Gou, is that you?
What's goin' on?
[MAKOTO]
Rin, stop kicking!
[RIN] ...if you don't get
this stupid thing off--
[gasps]
Remember that time in school,
about your dream?
You wanted to swim in a
pool of cherry blossoms.
Our original plan was to
spruce up the pool a little
as an advertisement
aimed at new members.
Miss A got us permission
to open it early.
But no one came, so the
work was all for naught.
[MAKOTO] Seemed like a shame
to let the end result
go to waste, so, we, uh, y'know,
thought you'd appreciate it.
This is amazing.
[giggles]
[REI]
Well, go on. Take a dip.
[RIN]
What?
[NAGISA, MAKOTO, REI]
Enjoy yourself!
I mean, since you're here
and all, you might as well.
Not to be ungrateful,
but it's still sorta chilly
for a swim, don't you think?
Bah, come on! Don't be
a wuss, get in there!
[REI]
It'll be bracing!
--[RIN] Quit it!
--[NAGISA] Don't be afraid!
Couple minutes won't kill ya!
Nobody's afraid!
Look. I just don't feel like it.
[GOU yelps]
[NAGISA]
Argh! It's freezing!
[NAGISA] It's not gonna
let up any time soon.
All that breathtaking beauty,
spoiled by a little rainfall.
Is your glass always half empty?
I mean, I'm just sayin'.
[REI]
I'm being a realist!
[MAKOTO]
I didn't even know that rain
was in the forecast today.
[RIN]
Hey, uh.
You guys... You ever
give any thought
to life after graduation?
We can't all have our
sights set as high as you.
[RIN]
You're kidding, right?
I've wasted so much time,
it's not even funny.
The Nationals this summer are
my last shot at being scouted.
They'll be comin' from all over.
I need to batten down,
focus on bringin' my A-game.
Might have been staged,
but I dunno, it looked
pretty real to me.
[STUDENT 1B]
Hey, thanks. I owe you one.
Yeah, sure.
[TEACHER 1A]
Take your seats, please.
I'd like to introduce
your new classmate.
Just transferred this morning.
Everyone, please join
me in welcoming
one Sosuke Yamazaki.
He comes to us all
the way from Tokyo.
[applause]
Holy crap.
[BOTH laugh]
Been a li'l while, hasn't it?
Yeah. Five years, right?
So, what's the story?
Heck of a time to
transfer to a new school.
You're one to talk.
Least I didn't leave in
the middle of sixth grade.
Dead of winter and you couldn't
even finish out the year.
[RIN]
Here's the deal.
This time next week,
I'll be at Iwatobi.
Their relay team's got
a real solid rep.
It's callin' my name.
No contest. Wasn't
a hard choice.
Anyway. Why Samezuka?
I thought that place
you were at in Tokyo
had a pretty awesome team.
[SOSUKE]
Yeah, well, things change.
You gonna tell me or do we
hafta' play 20 questions?
[SOSUKE]
I graduate this year.
Thought it'd be cool to swim
my last season back at home.
Things are gonna get
crazy after graduation.
[gasps]
Why are you talkin' like that?
Wait, you're not--
You're not quitting swimming?
Yeah, as an amateur.
Uh--
You sneaky little jerk!
--You got scouted, didn't you?
--[SOSUKE] Hey. Stop it!
Seriously. You're
messin' up my uniform.
[SUGIMOTO]
Listen up!
My name's Sosuke Yamazaki.
I transferred here from
Tokitsu High School in Tokyo.
You should all be
aware that Yamazaki's
butterfly stroke has ranked
him nationally in the top ten.
--Treat him with every respect.
--[SWIMMERS gasp]
[SWIMMERS]
Yes, sir.
I'm Mr. Sugimoto.
Matsuoka, I leave
it to you to show
this fine gentleman the ropes.
[RIN]
Yes, sir. Welcome to the team.
It's gonna be great havin' ya.
Thanks.
Lookin' forward to
swimmin' with you again.
[NITORI] So this is
what a nationally ranked
swimmer's build looks like.
[SOSUKE]
Hm?
Oh, sorry sir!
I'm Aiichiro Nitori,
Second Year, and it's, uh,
it's an honor to swim with you!
[gasps]
Nice to meet you, kid.
[laughs] Excuse me for asking,
but is Tokitsu's Swim Team
really all that?
That came out wrong.
I mean, of course
they're amazing!
Duh! Wait a second.
If you know Rin, do you know
Nanase and the others, too?
We haven't seen each other
since the sixth grade.
He hasn't met Haru
and the gang yet.
Well, that's not exactly true.
I've competed with him before.
I learned a lot about my
own limits as a swimmer.
If you're not careful,
he's the type of rival
you can become obsessed with.
Uh--
Freak.
Look at him go!
He can get his torso higher
above the water's surface
than most swimmers--
decreases the resistance
he'd have to deal
with otherwise.
And his shoulder
flexibility isn't somethin'
that happens overnight.
The guy's a beast.
He's worked hard to get there.
So, that must mean Sosuke
is the world-class swimmer
Mikoshiba was telling us about!
That's right, and when
I watch him swim...
...it brings back memories.
[RIN, SOSUKE panting]
[RIN]
It's so hot!
[SOSUKE]
No kidding, right?
Which one of these you want?
[BOTH]
On your mark, get set. Go!
[RIN, SOSUKE]
Rock, paper, scissors!
Best two out of three!
Winner takes all!
[laughs] I'm gonna
get brain freeze.
Ugh. Whatever.
If we'd done butterfly,
I'd 'a had this in the bag.
Oh, yeah?
You wanna see which one
of us has better form?
I'm always up for a race.
You don't scare me.
All right.
Let's make it interesting
and say the loser
has to do whatever
the winner wants.
Hey, sounds like
a solid plan to me.
Cool. We've got a deal, then.
Last one to the pool
is a monkey's uncle!
Hey! Hold on!
You can't just take off
like that! I wasn't ready!
This is so cheating!
[MAKOTO]
"Sprashu Fes"?
Uh, what is that
supposed to say?
Is it like a culture
festival or something?
[SASABE chuckles] Oh,
there'll be lots of fun stuff
goin' on here--you'll see.
And you guys are gonna
get to help out.
[NAGISA]
All right!
Let's come up with something
cool for the main event!
[GOU]
What about a dog-paddle race?
[NAGISA]
Could be fun.
[REI] I'll go you one better:
how about a competition
to see who does
the best butterfly?
We can call it
"Butterfly of Beauty!"
[GOU] A muscle contest
would be pretty cool.
Oh, come on!
Is there nothing you can't
work your obsession into?
[laughs]
You're pretty quiet.
Any ideas floatin'
around in there?
We could do a relay.
[ALL]
Huh?
[MAKOTO]
That's a fantastic idea!
People would lose their minds!
I believe we have
ourselves a winner!
[GOU]
It'll give everyone a taste
of how we'll kill
it at Regionals!
[MAKOTO]
True.
We'd need to find a team
to race against, though.
And why are you callin' it that?
[BOTH]
Pretty please?
[RIN] I'll say this for them--
they're a carefree bunch.
Drives me nuts.
Yeah, you complain,
but we both know
you're gonna do it.
[SOSUKE]
Who you takin' with you?
[RIN]
It's not like an official match.
Finding people will be a pain.
[SOSUKE]
Count me in.
Wait. Seriously?
Sure. Why not?
[SOSUKE]
I'll do freestyle.
That's fine by me.
You sure you don't wanna
go with butterfly, though?
I feel like expanding
my area of expertise.
[RIN]
Come on.
[NITORI]
Bad news, sir--I mean, Rin!
What's up?
[NITORI]
Nakagawa.
He-He got detention
for goofing off in class,
so he can't make it!
Argh. You're kidding me, right?
We can't do a relay with
just the three of us.
I know, it's terrible!
We don't have time
to find anyone else!
The race is in half an hour!
[RIN]
We're screwed.
Who else do we know that
can swim the backstroke?
[SOSUKE]
I'll just go twice.
It's not like this is an
official event or anything.
There's some leeway to fudge
the usual competition rules.
Look, it may not be
the real deal,
but it's still a race.
There's no point in doin' it
if we're not gonna
take it seriously.
[STUDENT 2D]
Yo! Mikoshiba!
[BOTH]
Did that guy say...?
[MOMOTARO] Jeez, hold
your horses! I'm coming.
[STUDENT 2D]
Come on!
[MOMOTARO]
Heh. You see me, don't ya?
[RIN] I'm gonna go out
on a limb and say that's
not a common name.
Only one person I know has it.
[NITORI] Yeah. I was just
thinking the same thing.
[RIN]
Hold on there, champ!
[MOMOTARO]
Huh?
What's your problem?!
Listen, I know this is comin'
from out of the blue,
but your Seijuro's
little bro, right?
[MOMOTARO]
Yeah, so?
Why the heck is that
any business of yours?
[RIN]
Bingo! This is our guy!
[NITORI]
We're saved!
So, uh.
You, swim the
backstroke like him?
Um. Well, yeah.
That's sorta my area.
Matter of fact, back home, I won
tons of competitions and stuff.
Swimming the backstroke made
me kinda like a celebrity!
I had an awesome
nickname and everything.
They called me...
...The Otter.
[RIN]
Okay then.
Uh, I'm starting to think
the world-class athlete
Mikoshiba was talking about
was actually his brother.
Yeah. Guess he wanted to pave
the way for him or whatever.
It's what a big brother does.
[STUDENT 2D]
You comin' or not?
Keep your shirt on!
Later, guys! Time to go
pick up some girls.
No, I told you I'm
not joining, so lay off.
Chicks don't like swimmers.
Look, nobody's asking you
to join the Swim Team.
But if you wanna get
the ladies' attention...
We might be able
to help you there.
[MOMOTARO]
Let me go!
You're full of lies!
You made it sound like
we were going somewhere
I could try my moves on
--tons of cuties--!
--[RIN] Hey! Shut up!
There are kids in here, idiot!
Enough about "your moves"!
Somebody help!
I've been tricked!
--[RIN] Stop squirming.
--Let go!
--I wanna go--
--[GOU] You are so late.
[laughs]
Hey, big brother!
Hey, Gou. 'Sup?
[GOU]
You excited?
Yeah.
Hold on a second.
I think...
I think I might be in love.
[RIN]
Oh, no.
[NITORI]
Just like his brother.
Rin, we really appreciate
you guys being here.
[RIN]
Sure.
[NITORI]
Thanks for asking us to come.
I've been looking forward to it.
Yeah? Cool! It should be fun.
[GOU]
Here, take a few programs.
[NITORI]
Thanks. These look great!
Oh, Sosuke!
Whoa!
Feels like I haven't
seen you in forever.
Right? I can't even
remember the last time.
I guess transferring
to a new school means
you get to treat the old crew
like they fell off
the face of the earth.
Not that Rin bothered to stay
in touch with anyone.
Well, you know.
[GOU]
Yes I do.
Should we know him?
Sosuke's an old friend of Rin's.
They used to be teammates
in the Sano
Elementary Swim Club.
He was actually in a lane
next to ours when we all
swam that relay together
back in the day.
Talk about a blast
from the past.
See you guys in the water?
Of course.
Yep!
Let's go.
Momotaro Mikoshiba!
I love nature!
I collect stag beetles!
My mantra is
"never stop swimming."
I can cook an egg five
different ways--not poached,
that's a pain--and the
first place I wash when I--!
[RIN]
Shut your trap. Move your feet.
[MOMOTARO]
I'm tryin' to have a life!
Something I can help you with
while you're standing there?
Hey. Long time, Nanase.
So I saw what happened in the
relay at Regionals last year.
Didn't know you were there.
Had nothing better to do.
I gotta tell you,
what you and your boys
pulled out there was insane.
Can't believe Rin played along.
Going somewhere
with this, or what?
I'd have never made him
do something so crazy.
What are you trying to say?
If you know what's good for you,
you'll stay out of Rin's way.
[AMAKATA]
All right, ladies and gentlemen!
We come now to the main event:
a 200-meter medley relay!
Let's hear it for Team
Dolphin and Team Shark!
[MOMOTARO]
Hey!
I think the guy yelling is
Mikoshiba's little brother,
they say his
backstroke's incredible.
Huh. Small world.
[NAGISA]
Oh, and apparently Rin's
going with butterfly today.
[REI]
That's certainly a 180!
[NAGISA]
No kidding, right?
That's why Yamazaki's
gonna be doin' freestyle.
[SASABE]
Get set.
--[whistle blows]
--[CROWD] Go!
Nice one! There ya go!
That's how ya start a race!
Wasn't sure he had it in him.
Kid pulled a nearly
perfect backstroke.
[REI] He's got nothing on
Makoto for speed, though.
And here he comes.
You swimming breaststroke
today, Aye-Aye?
Bold choice.
Please. You don't scare me.
Look at us.
That's why all those hours
of training pay off.
I guess so.
[REI] They're about to
get their butts kicked.
[MAKOTO] Nagisa's always
faster in the second round.
That's when we'll close the gap.
Hate to break it
to you, my friend,
but I believe we've got
this one wrapped up.
Heh.
Dive in first if you want to--
doesn't bother me.
Watch your back once
you get goin', though.
If you're not careful,
the water will sink
its teeth into ya.
Wha--?
I suggest you worry
about yourself.
Rei against Rin--
talk about a race!
[MAKOTO] Little by little,
Rin's gaining on 'im.
Man, he's fast!
[NITORI] Rin's catching up!
He's gonna overtake him!
All he needed was
a second, and boom!
Guy's some kinda super hero!
Why do you think your
brother made a big deal
about handing the reins over
to him once he'd graduated?
[SASABE]
It's gonna be close!
Atta boy, Rei!
[REI] There's barely any
gap between them!
He's keeping pace with
Haru. That's incredible!
Yeah! Lookin' good!
Go!
[CROWD cheers]
[RIN]
Heads up.
Good race.
Thanks for comin' to this thing.
Wouldn't've wanted
to do it without ya.
Sure.
I'm sorry!
I guess my heart just
wasn't in the race.
For your first relay,
you actually did pretty good.
Don't beat yourself up.
[MOMOTARO growls]
Next time we'll make 'em pay!
Hey.
[yelps]
Ow.
If by "next time," you mean
you wanna join the team,
we could use a guy with
your backstroke skills.
Just somethin' to think about.
[gasps]
[RIN] So, what do ya say
we go grab some food
on the way home?
[NITORI]
That's sounds amazing.
[MOMOTARO]
Wait. You payin'?
[RIN]
What? Are you kidding? No.
[MOMOTARO]
Come on, pay!
--[RIN] Fine.
--[NITORI, MOMOTARO laugh]
Wow.
No one kills it on butterfly
like Yamazaki, huh, sir?
You think what he's
doin' now is impressive,
wait till he decides
to quit holdin' back.
[SWIMMERS gasp]
Capt'n, you gotta
see this! It's crazy!
When this Momo guy goes all out,
his backstroke speed
is totally off the rails!
Whoa. I think he just
broke the club record!
Where's he been all this time?
Looks like we might've
underestimated--
[MOMOTARO yelps]
[BOTH] You gotta
watch out for the wall!
[UOZUMI]
Are you okay?
[MOMOTARO]
Ow.
[MINAMI] Didn't you see
the five-meter line?
Well, leaves us somewhere
to go, I suppose.
You been holdin' out
on us, you li'l freak!
You feel up for another round?
Ha! You kiddin'?
I could do this all day
and then some!
[UOZUMI]
I'm liking the attitude.
I'd like it more if you
didn't hit the wall.
[NITORI]
Focus, Nitori!
Everyone's upping
their game but you.
Kid's got promise,
but he's not relay ready.
He's still too slow.
I know.
Heart'll only take
the poor guy so far.
He's gotta learn, sink or
swim isn't about raw talent--
it's about hard work.
Without dedication, talent
alone ain't gonna cut it.
You know that stuff's
loaded with sugar.
You have the diet
of a fifth grader.
Eh, what the heck.
Wanna RPS me for it?
You better believe it.
[SOSUKE, RIN]
Rock, paper, scissors!
Ah! Hadn't had one
of these in forever.
[SOSUKE] Makes me think back
to that one time, remember?
[RIN]
Huh?
The loser had to promise to
do whatever the winner said?
[SOSUKE]
No whining, either.
You lose, I choose. Got it?
You hafta' promise--
no take backs.
Yeah, I got it.
Let's do this already.
We go when the second
gets to the top, okay?
Ready--
[RIN] Ah! I so had you
till that stupid turn!
Yeah, right. Whatever.
Ugh. Fine. I lose, you chose.
Just don't make me do
anything embarrassing.
That's all I ask.
Hey, there's no need
to cry about it.
[RIN] I'm not crying,
tell me what you want me to do!
All right, then. Fine.
Ah, sorry. I need time to
think of something good.
Wow, y'know, I'd
completely forgotten
about that whole thing.
Yeah, I never did
quite figure out
what I wanted you to do,
but before I knew it,
you were leaving for Australia.
[RIN] I still owe you
for the butterfly race.
Don't worry about it.
We're cool, I couldn't
think of anything.
You're killin' me.
If it means that much,
I'll make something up
for the next time I see you.
Till then, huh?
Yeah.
[RIN]
I'm still waitin'.
You've had more
than enough time.
I mean, here we are, is there
somethin' you want me to do?
[SOSUKE]
Maybe.
Well, how 'bout lettin' me
sleep on the bottom bunk?
That doesn't count.
We competed for that
the other day and I won. C'mon.
Don't go wastin' my promise
on somethin' stupid.
Fine. Give me the rest
of your soda, then.
Will ya knock it off
and take this seriously?
[laughs]
[SOUSUKE]
Relax.
I need to sit on it for
a little longer, that's all.
[RIN sighs]
[SOSUKE]
Let me ask you something.
How come I never heard
from you in all that time?
What happened over there?
You didn't call.
You stopped writing.
It was like you fell off
the face of the earth.
For all I knew, you had.
I didn't push back then
'cause I didn't wanna
get all up in your
face about it.
But, I mean, now...
I feel like I need to know.
[gasps]
[RIN]
It wasn't anything major.
I hit a wall with the swimming.
Life can be rough when
you're the new kid.
I fell down, couldn't
get on my feet.
Happens.
I thought about saying goodbye
to swimming altogether.
Until... Haru stepped in
and kinda woke me up.
He and his buddies.
You really like those guys, huh?
Well, yeah!
It's 'cause of them I fell
in love with the water again.
They made me see
in a whole new light.
It's like, with them,
I recaptured that spark, y'know?
I don't swim for myself anymore.
Not really.
The people who've inspired me
have become part of my dream.
Hah. There's my Rin.
If the world ever needs
a poolside Socrates,
you could dive right in.
[RIN]
Screw you.
[SOSUKE]
Heh.
I don't understand.
What could possibly be wrong
with you being on the same team?
It's just 'cause Sosuke and me
know each other too well.
He's all about theory.
I'm all about practice.
So, we butted heads a lot.
Usually, whoever was
fastest would call dibs.
Man. We were so
stupid competitive
over the tiniest things.
You guys hate each other now?
No. Not even close.
He's like a brother to me.
Nobody else seems
to understand the way
I think most of the time.
It's just...
I know from experience
relay's not our thing.
[UOZUMI]
What's the deal, Momo?
Extension! Extension! Extension!
Crap. Was the other
day like a fluke?
He just clocked the worst
time on the whole team.
What the heck is
wrong with me today?
He's got talent,
but he's too inconsistent.
Exactly. Fat lot
of good talent is
if you can't deliver
on it at will.
[SOSUKE]
Going for a run?
Yeah. That's right.
Well, can I tag along?
If you want to. Sure.
[RIN, SOSUKE panting]
[RIN] Seriously, don't feel like
you gotta keep up with me.
I have to do this every now
and then or I'll go all squishy.
Keeps my metabolism
at full bore.
[RIN]
Whatever works for ya.
What?
[SOSUKE]
Is that...?
Ah. Well, what do ya know?
Ai keeps at it, he might
just make the cut after all.
[SOSUKE]
Rin.
What's more important to you--
going solo or swimming relay?
Huh? Well, I guess they're
both equally important.
[SOSUKE] Times not on your
side if you wanna compete
at the international level.
You gotta cut the fat.
Every second you
spend on your pals
or the relay thing hammers
a nail in the coffin
of your solo career.
Dreams before friends.
It's how it has to be.
You can have a shot
at the big time
or you can try to play
nice with everybody.
[RIN]
It's not that cut and dry.
The only reason I have a shot
at all is on account of
the people who've
helped me get here.
I'd have given up without them.
My dreams are only real
'cause of my friends.
I mean, I still want
a solo career someday.
But swimming with them
gives me strength
and a purpose.
[gasps]
Yeah, go ahead, call me
naive, but I feel like
if I have to choose
between the two,
what's the point of either?
I want a shot at the
big time and a team.
If I'm willin' to give my all
to make that a reality,
what's it to you?
[SOSUKE]
Because, I...
I want you to think of me
as part of your team.
Wait, what are you sayin'?
I want in. Put me on relay.
But, Sosuke.
Doesn't that go against
your whole philosophy?
[RIN] Take it back!
Take it back right now, jerk!
[REFEREE 4B]
That's enough!
[REFEREE 4A]
What is going on with you two?
[RIN] Badmouth my dad
again, I'll punch you.
[SOSUKE] I didn't mean it
the way it sounded.
I'm sorry.
[RIN] What was up with
your swimming today?
[RIN]
Hey, I'm talkin' to you.
[SOSUKE] I don't think
swimming is a team sport.
I mean, once you're in the
water, you're on your own.
It's not like anyone
can help you be faster.
That's not true and you know it!
When you swim relay,
you swim as a team!
You're a link in a chain!
Look, I think it all
comes down to this.
Our goals are too
different for you and me
to be on the same team.
[RIN gasps]
I don't wanna be on
relay anymore, period.
If I have to worry about
the other guy all the time,
it's gonna kill what
I get out of swimming.
What can I tell ya?
Back then, yeah,
that's what I thought.
I was just a dumb kid.
Thing is, now I'm not so sure.
I need to figure this out.
Maybe relay is how.
Sometimes you don't know
what you're looking for
till you've got it.
'Times you just swim
too far ahead. Come on.
You want me to
spell it out for you?
Look, you made a promise
to do whatever I said--
don't even think
of backing out now!
'Cause...
[RIN gasps]
I can't promise
you'll find yourself.
That's not how it works.
There is no guarantee.
I'm afraid you are
on your own there.
[sighs] Yeah, I know.
[RIN]
But...
...I'll do what I can
to steer a friend
in the right direction.
I hold the Samezuka Team
record for both
freestyle and butterfly.
So, if you think swimming
relay will be some kind of
spiritual awakening,
you'll have to earn it.
If I'm hearing you
right, you're saying
you'll accept me
on the relay team
if I can beat you in a race.
Let's do it, then.
Like old times.
Yeah, well don't
get too cocky, pal.
Things change.
[RIN] We're doin' butterfly.
One hundred meters.
[RIN]
Ready.
[SOSUKE, RIN grunt]
[RIN]
Power. Confidence.
This is how it should be.
This is the real him.
[panting]
Yeah!
[RIN] See, that's what
I'm talkin' about
when I say passion.
The perfect combination
of skill and desire.
Any doubts I had before
are pretty much gone.
Nice goin', Sosuke.
[RIN]
All right. Listen up.
It's time for all of us to
start thinkin' about District.
And just so you know,
I'm makin' some changes
to the way we decide who gets
to be on the relay team.
It used to be based on speed--
if you were consistently fast,
you made the cut.
But that's not how we're
gonna do it this year.
Whether you swim relay
or go solo is your call.
So from now on, you'll
only be picked for relay
if that's your thing.
Your overall speed
is still important,
but just as important
is where your heart is.
Sure, this might
be a stupid idea.
Times are usually
the best way to go.
A few of you probably think
I'm sacrificing our chances
of winning for the sake of
proving some kind of point.
And you're right.
But it's a point that
needs to be made.
We're a team.
And if our mutual passion
isn't what binds us together,
we could get all the way
to Nationals and have
nothing to show for it
but some stupid medals.
More importantly, you deserve
to be led by someone
who sees this team as a family.
So, you wanna swim relay,
you show me you
believe in yourself.
And you also believe
in your team!
[groans] Well, at least
I should be feeling better
by the tournament.
Huh?
That's Sosuke.
--[GOU yelps]
--[RIN] Whoa there, sis.
Watch your step.
Sorry. I'm a klutz.
[RIN]
Are you watching us, Dad?
[RIN] I don't know what
kinda karma this is,
but even Gou, Little Miss
Un-Athletic is involved
in the world of
competitive swimming, now.
It's all because of the
opportunities you created.
I promise you, Dad,
I'm gonna do great this year.
Keep an eye on me, huh?
Thanks. I really appreciate it.
[GOU] 'Kay, Dad, we're out.
See you next time.
Oh, wait, hold up a sec.
This is for you.
Wow. How long have you
been holding onto this?
[RIN] Might make him happy
to see it back at Iwatobi.
Dad was the
sentimental type, right?
Now let's get out there
and bust our butts!
[RIN] What exactly are you
gonna do? Ugh, I swear.
[GOU] Hey, wait! What is
that supposed to mean?
I do stuff!
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 6A]
Ready.
[CROWD]
Go!
That was a good start.
[MINAMI]
Come on, let's see some spirit!
Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Fight! Fight!
[MINAMI]
Come on, guys, fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Fight!
Not gonna lie,
Nitori's putting on
a pretty good show. Look at him!
[UOZUMI] Atta boy! Give the
lead a reason to worry!
[gasps]
[applause]
[panting]
[MINAMI] So much for Nitori
clearing round one, huh?
Can't say I'm surprised.
[MIKOSHIBA] Say what you will,
the kid's stepped up his game.
Team's new coach must've
lit a fire under him.
Right.
Only one who can
take credit is him.
He put in the time
and worked his butt off.
Good for him.
Hey, great job out there today.
Thanks. Next up is gonna be Rin.
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 6A]
Ready.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
Yeah! Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Kill it, Rin. Come on.
Whoa!
They're unbelievable!
[CROWD cheers]
Less than a second apart!
Rin was behind him by .02.
Wow. That's incredible!
[MINAMI]
What a race.
[IWASHIMIZU]
For real.
Seriously, .02 seconds.
What gives?
He clearly had the
drop on me today.
His speed's better.
So much better
there's no tellin'
how much time he's
spent practicing.
The guy's so good now, it's
startin' to get on my nerves.
Meh. Tomorrow's another day.
Last day of the relay,
in fact. You ready?
Heck yeah.
[gasps]
[RIN]
Sosuke.
We need to hurry.
The bus is about to leave.
Gotta get rest before tomorrow.
Yeah, I know.
Is there somethin' on your mind?
Just a blast from the past.
Huh?
I'm kidding.
[GOU]
Yes. Perfect.
Hey, hurry up.
Everybody's waiting for you.
Right.
What, you can't decide?
Not that it's my call,
but after the crap he pulled
out there today, Uozumi
clearly needs to be benched.
Yeah, yeah, I hear ya.
[RIN]
Uozumi.
Sir!
[RIN]
Momo.
Sir!
I know you both have strong
feelings about the relay,
but unfortunately only
one of you can do it.
After looking at the results
from today's races,
we need to make
some tough choices.
Keep our sights on Regionals.
Momo.
You're on.
[gasps]
Tch.
Uh!
[UOZUMI]
Yo.
Uh, yeah?
I'll never forgive you
if you screw this up.
Get out there and kick
some butt for Samezuka.
Awesome! Heck yeah! You got it!
Watch me!
[UOZUMI]
That's more like it!
Ow! Come on!
But, one of these days,
somebody's gonna teach you
a lesson, ya cocky little jerk!
[RIN]
Here's the lineup for the relay:
Momo, Iwashimizu, Sosuke, me.
You guys ready for this?
[SOSUKE, MOMOTARO, IWASHIMIZU]
Sir!
[RIN]
Okay.
That's it for our
post-race "debriefing."
I want you all to go home
and rest up for tomorrow.
Understood?
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yes, sir!
[NITORI sighs]
You're in the way.
[NITORI gasps]
Uh. Sorry about that.
[NITORI laughs]
Ya know.
I can't believe I actually
let an underclassman beat me.
You really wanna be in
the relay that badly, huh?
[NITORI]
It's only natural.
[SOSUKE]
What is?
[NITORI]
Look, I-I just...
From the second I laid eyes
on him, Rin's been my hero.
To tell you the truth,
when I first started swimming,
I couldn't have cared less
about medley relay.
It was just another
race, y'know?
But now, I realize
there's a lot more
to it than that.
This past year, I've had the
opportunity to witness firsthand
how much Rin truly
cares about it.
Swimming with him inspires me.
I wanna make him proud.
What sucks is,
this was my big chance
to make it happen.
And after this summer,
I'll never get another one.
[SOSUKE]
And who exactly decided that?
[gasps]
[SOSUKE] If you wanna
swim with him that badly,
then you figure out a way
to make that dream a reality.
Don't limit yourself, kid.
Thanks!
Here goes.
Huh? He's already asleep?
Momo, it's too
early to be in bed.
All right, let's see.
Okay, look, I thought this
was my moment to shine,
but it turns out it's yours.
So go out there and win
this tournament for me!
[gasps]
[sighs]
[RIN] Ya know, it's been quite
a while since we've done
a real tournament together.
Yeah.
[RIN]
Let's win. Sound like a plan?
[SOSUKE] Of course.
That's why we swim. Right?
Heh! Whaddup, Nitori!
[NITORI]
Oh, hey. You forget something?
[MOMOTARO] No, it's just--
I want you to know
I'm gonna do my
best to win today!
[laughs] Wish me luck!
Uh... Huh?
[ANNOUNCER 7A]
Attention, ladies and gentlemen.
We will now begin the men's
400-meter medley relay race.
[RIN] Until... Haru stepped in
and kind of woke me up.
He and his buddies.
[SOSUKE] Good for you.
I don't owe him squat.
[RIN] No matter who wins
today, no hard feelings.
Deal? Just make sure
you make it to Regionals.
[HARUKA]
Like I need you to remind me.
[laughs] I let you walk away
with the freestyle
race yesterday.
But today'll be
a different story.
[REFEREE 7A]
Ready!
[RIN]
We pulled it off!
[SOSUKE]
Nice one.
[NITORI] You got offers
from multiple scouts?
Rin, that's incredible!
Congrats, this is a big deal!
[RIN]
Thanks.
Of course, after
watching that race,
what else did we expect?
You were absolutely amazing!
[RIN]
If I got a bunch of offers,
that means Haru did, too.
I can't get comfortable.
Gotta stay on top!
Oh, I meant to tell you.
I got an offer from the
school you decided on, too.
[gasps]
[RIN] Of course,
it's not official yet,
but we might be able
to swim on the same team
after graduation.
Cool. That'd be great.
[RIN]
Did I say somethin'?
Look, don't worry about it.
Yeah, right.
You've been acting
weird since yesterday.
You lost momentum
during the race, too.
You in some kind of slump?
[RIN sighs]
Sosuke.
Why don't we talk outside?
[SOSUKE] I told you not
to worry about it, okay?
[sighs] Just tell me.
How was it for you
swimming in the relay race?
You said it yourself.
[SOSUKE]
I need to figure this out.
Maybe relay is how.
Sometimes you don't know
what you're looking for
till you've got it.
'Times you just swim
too far ahead. Come on.
Did you figure out what
you're looking for or not?
I don't know.
Come on!
[SOSUKE]
You heard me.
Will you just back off already?
What did I say to you?
Not everybody gets to be
a part of this, remember?
Only the guys who want it
more than anything else
have the right to be
on the relay team!
"Back off already?" You got
nothin' better than that?
So what? That's it?
Was this a joke to you?
[SOSUKE]
Swimming with you isn't a joke.
That's not what I'm saying!
Then what's wrong? Talk to me!
[SOSUKE]
It's not what you think.
It's 'cause it's not a joke
that I can't fake it!
[RIN gasps]
But I do know there's
at least one thing
I'm sure about.
I love it. And I
don't wanna stop.
[SOSUKE]
But that's not enough.
Then you better
keep on swimming.
Swim until you
figure it all out.
Never give up.
[SOSUKE]
Yeah.
[NITORI yelps]
Oh! Sosuke, it's you!
What are you doing here?
Your form's a mess
'cause you're too tired.
Huh?
Do you mean you
were watching me?
[SOSUKE] You won't get
better just by swimming
as often and as hard as you can.
Your body needs time to heal.
Right. I'm so sorry.
It's just, I'm one of the
slowest people in the club.
If I want to compete,
I have to push myself harder.
[SOSUKE] If you go at it
too hard you won't be able
to keep doing the things
you're good at.
[SOSUKE]
I'll watch you.
[gasps] You will? For real?
Yeah, I'll watch you practice
and give pointers or whatever.
After you take a break.
You wanna swim with Rin, right?
[gasps] Yes!
Every time I drop by, that poor
kid's always practicing alone.
No, your legs are
too far apart again!
Sosuke...
[SOSUKE]
That's better.
Hey. You all right?
Where are you goin'?
Just out.
[RIN]
What about practice?
I... I'm not going
today, so, sorry.
Holy...
This is insane!
[gasps]
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Whoa!
[SAMEZUKA 9A]
He broke Iwashimizu's record!
Oh, right! Way to
kill it, Nitori!
Looks like someone's
coaching bumped our boy's
game up a notch.
Oh, shut up.
[MOMOTARO]
You are now officially my idol!
I'm totally serious!
There's no way you're not going
to Regionals with that time!
Whoa there, champ,
you're gonna jinx me.
Nothing's written in stone yet.
Whatever! You gotta
let me in on your routine!
It's like some kind of
super ultra secret, huh?
Sosuke just gave me a few
pointers on the side,
that's all there was to it.
Aw, no fair!
I want some pointers!
Ugh. Just great.
[MOMOTARO]
C'mon! Please!
[RIN]
Ai.
Don't let today go to your head,
Regionals are still
up in the air.
No gettin' comfortable.
Yes, sir!
Shota Nakagawa?
[NAKAGAWA]
Here!
Kazuki Minami?
[MINAMI]
Here!
[RIN]
Dai Ryono?
[RYONO]
Yo!
[RIN]
You guys are on freestyle relay.
Next up, medley roster.
Backstroke, Momotaro Mikoshiba.
Awesome!
[RIN]
Breaststroke, Aiichirou Nitori.
--Yes, sir! Thank you!
--[SAMEZUKA CLUB] Whoa.
[RIN]
Butterfly, Sosuke Yamazaki.
Yeah.
'Course, yours truly will
cover the individual freestyle.
No partying tonight,
I want all of you to rest.
Dismissed.
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yes, sir!
What'd I say?
You were a shoe-in
for the relay team!
Thanks! Congratulations!
[RIN]
Sosuke.
Tomorrow, no regrets
either way. Right?
[SOSUKE]
No regrets.
[MOMOTARO]
Stag beetle!
[MIKOSHIBA, MOMOTARO grunt]
Ow! What the heck?
Oh, hey, big bro!
Whatcha got there?
Your relay order sheet?
Here. Let's have a li'l look.
Hey! Come on, you're not
'sposed to see that!
You're on the roster! Nice!
Duh, 'course I am.
What else they gonna
do with the guy
who slayed your
backstroke record?
So this is Matsuoka's idea
of an ideal team, huh?
Ideal? What're you
talkin' about?
All right, people! Pony up!
We got a reputation to spread!
Let's show them all how an
ideal relay team does it!
[RIN]
Glad you decided to join us.
Now what are you babbling about?
I ran into my brother!
He told me all about last year!
I know about the tournament!
[ALL gasp]
[MOMOTARO] Sounds like something
out of a cheesy movie, yeah,
but the fact is, when
you guys got together,
miracles happened,
plain and simple!
It's the best story ever!
Seriously, it almost
made me cry!
I want that! I want a
team like you guys had!
Look, I'm flattered,
but you gotta take it easy.
That was last year--we need
to focus on the present.
Let's do some exchanges
in the warm-up pool.
[MOMOTARO]
Yeah! I'm all about it!
Teamwork! C'mon, Nitori!
[NITORI]
Actually, I'm uh...
I'm kinda starting to
get a little nervous.
[SOSUKE]
Easy there. It's just a warm-up.
[MOMOTARO, NITORI laugh]
[RIN]
All right, let's do this!
[NITORI, MOMOTARO]
Yeah!
[SOSUKE grunts]
[RIN]
What was that about?
Sorry. My bad. Got
distracted. Screwed up.
You got "distracted"?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna go take five
and grab a soda.
[ANNOUNCER 9A] Next up,
the men's 100-meter freestyle.
[GOU]
Go, Rin!
No offense, but I'm
rather glad Haru and Rin
are in different
heats for this one.
Who can take that tension?
[NAGISA]
Haru's in the next one.
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 9A]
Ready.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
[SAMEZUKA 9C] And... Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
[NITORI]
Come on! Fight!
[MAKOTO]
That's incredible!
He's already taken the lead!
[REI]
Here comes the turn!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
One down!
[MAKOTO]
Wow. Still way out ahead!
[NAGISA] Look at him! Guy's
so fast, he's like a torpedo!
[REI]
Outstanding!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yeah!
[GOU]
Oh, yeah!
If this were the finals,
that time would win
him the whole thing!
So then, he definitely
made it to finals, yeah?
--[UOZUMI] Yeah, duh.
--[MINAMI] Ha! Of course!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
All right, all right, Samezuka!
All right!
[ANNOUNCER 9A] Next, we have
the men's 100-meter freestyle,
sixth heat.
Nanase's group's next.
I wonder how they're gonna do!
[RIN]
Huh?
Just what is he doing out there?
Haru!
[RIN] What was that?
Are you outta your mind?
[HARUKA]
Like it's any of your business.
[RIN]
What?
Do you realize how many
scouts just saw you tank?
What about your future?
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER 10A] Men's 100 meter.
Butterfly. Group three.
[whistle blowing]
[BOTH]
Go, Rin!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
[REFEREE 10A]
Ready.
[CROWD]
Go!
[MINAMI]
Ready! Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
[BOTH gasp]
[sighs]
[gasps]
I'm not happy about losing,
but you know what?
That was a pretty good
showing for our first relay.
Our take away from this
should be that we can all--
[SOSUKE]
I've had enough.
Relay team's just not for me.
I don't wanna lose
'cause of someone else.
Or even worse, for you guys
to lose because of me.
It's not my thing.
Who do you think you are?
Take it back. Now!
You talked smack
about the relay.
Of course he got mad.
Rin's Dad swam the
relay in school, too.
It's pretty much the most
important thing in his life.
Yeah, I know how
much he loves it.
But you'd think I
told him his father
was a moron or something.
If you don't wanna
swim it for yourself,
you should swim it for him.
It's a nice thought, but no.
[gasps]
[yelps]
We don't do things
for each other.
That's just not how we are.
[KISUMI] Ah. Well, guess that's
what it is to be rivals.
You're right on the money.
[RIN] Their relay team's
got a real solid rep.
It's callin' my name.
[RIN]
Sosuke. What's wrong?
[SOSUKE gasps]
Did something happen?
Nitori was worried about you.
Everything's fine
[RIN] You were weird this
morning when we practiced
in the sub pool, too.
You just up and took off.
Don't worry about it.
It's nothing.
Look man, when you
miss practice like that,
I'm gonna worry. You wanna
tell me where you were?
Ah, come on. You gotta
talk to me here--
I just said it was nothing!
[RIN sighs]
[RIN]
Sosuke.
Incoming.
[SOSUKE grunts]
Your shoulder's in pretty
bad shape, isn't it?
[RIN]
Let me see it.
[SOSUKE]
Piss off!
[gasps]
When did this happen?
This morning. It's really
not as bad as it looks.
Oh, come on!
You and I both know it
didn't happen this morning!
[sighs]
Well I guess I can't slip
anything by you, can I?
The truth is, I injured
it about two years ago.
I pushed myself too
hard in training.
But you were
already being scouted.
Why push it when you knew
what college you were going to?
[SOSUKE]
'Cause I didn't. I lied.
No one scouted me.
You wanna go watch
the next race?
[GIRL 10B]
Yeah!
[SOSUKE sighs]
Can we get outta here?
[NITORI] Hey, Rin!
Are you guys here, or...?
What's goin' on?
Did ya see the
individual medley?
Everyone was super
fired up! Awesome.
Momo, stop!
When's the last time
you saw Rin and Sosuke?
Huh?
[RIN] Tell me why.
Why did you lie to me?
I think I have a right to know.
You and me are like rivals.
We shouldn't be
on the same team.
At least, that's how
I used to see it.
[SOSUKE] When you told me you
were transferring to Iwatobi,
I didn't say a word.
Why would I?
And when I started
middle school,
all I did was focus on swimming.
You were off chasing
your dreams in Australia.
So I figured I would work
toward my own dream.
After a while, your
letters stopped coming.
I kept rooting for you, though.
I knew you'd break through
that wall one way or another.
Once I got into high school,
I got even more obsessed
with my training.
My dream was gonna happen
no matter what the cost.
[SOSUKE] I used to imagine
what it'd be like
when I'd finally made it
to a big International meet.
Every time I pictured it,
you were right there beside me.
Those were crazy times.
I trained hard,
all day, every day.
No one could touch me.
I was the best.
[SOSUKE]
And that's when it happened.
My shoulder starting
giving me issues.
Nothing I couldn't
handle, at first.
So I ignored it
and kept on going.
Eventually, it got worse.
Every day it hurt a little more.
But no matter how bad it got,
I refused to give up.
I had to get stronger.
It's like my dream
was out there,
calling from a
distance, mocking me.
I stayed at it,
but before long,
my shoulder finally gave out.
[SOSUKE] It was the summer
of my freshman year.
You wanna know why I lied?
[SOSUKE] 'Cause when Gou
told me you were back,
I didn't want you
to see me that way.
to know the truth.
I just couldn't handle it,
for you of all people
to see me all broken down.
Rehab. Injury. Rehab.
That was my routine.
Day in, day out.
[SOSUKE] A busted rotator cuff
makes it hard to come in first.
I got sick of being a loser.
Truth is, I was miserable.
And then, one day,
I accepted reality.
No matter what I did,
my dream wasn't gonna happen.
So I turned my back
on swimming for good.
[gasps]
[RIN]
You quit swimming?
But I wanted to see you
compete one last time
before I decided to retire.
So I dropped in on
last year's Regionals.
Wait, you actually
saw that race?
Yeah.
I wanted to watch the best
swimmer I've ever known
accomplish a goal
we used to share.
Thing is, when I
saw you struggling
the way you were... What can
I say? It broke my heart.
I thought you were
the type of guy
who could overcome any obstacle,
burst through any wall.
But something was wrong.
Something must've happened.
I give up!
I quit years ago and
I shoulda stayed quit!
[SOSUKE]
I wanted to call out to you.
But the words wouldn't come.
[SOSUKE] And then, in the
relay you swam with Haruka...
[SOSUKE] You went at it
with such intensity--
it's like you were
a changed man.
Seeing you with
the guys afterwards,
the way you were laughing
and carrying on.
I dunno.
It gave me a little twinge
of hope, I suppose.
The old dream came back to life.
[SOSUKE] You and me were
gonna swim side by side.
Honestly,
I didn't know what
it meant to you.
How important it was
to swim as part of a team.
[SOSUKE] I realize It's over
for me. But, before I go,
I wanna swim the
best damn relay I can!
With you. Today.
[RIN] Idiot! Why didn't
you tell me sooner?
Why did you lie to me? Why?
Because if you would've known,
it would've broken your heart.
You son of a-- You just--
[SOSUKE] Come on.
The race is about to start.
Are you nuts?
You can't swim a relay
in the condition you're in!
[SOSUKE]
Oh, yes I can.
But if you push
yourself too hard,
you really will be done!
I know. That was the
idea from the start.
Forget it! I won't
let you hurt yourself!
I'm doing this whether
you want me to or not,
that's all there is to it.
Make your peace with that.
Yeah right!
[SOSUKE]
I'll make you a promise.
I'll see this race
through to the end.
'Cause that's my dream.
What's left of it anyway.
No!
[NITORI]
Let him swim!
It's the right thing to do!
[MOMOTARO]
Yeah, come on.
[RIN]
You guys? How did you--?
We are a team!
I've wanted to swim with you
ever since I saw you
compete at Regionals.
That's how long I've
waited for this honor.
Please, don't take
that away from me!
Sosuke put a lot of
time in to my training.
Let me show you what I've got!
[MOMOTARO]
That's right! Come on!
How many people get to say
they were part of something
larger than themselves?
Isn't that what
this is all about?
Who cares if it's all
off the table tomorrow?
We can give it all
we've got today!
[NITORI]
We're your dream team!
[MOMOTARO]
Heck yeah we are!
[SOSUKE]
You know they're right.
And you're our captain.
[SOSUKE]
Let's do this while we can.
[ANNOUNCER 10A]
Ladies and gentlemen.
Next up on the docket we have
the men's 100-meter
medley relay finals.
[REI] Look at his shoulder.
I think he's hurt.
Oh, no. Sosuke.
I'm proud I get to swim
the relay with you guys.
Let's go win this thing!
Can't let all this attention
go to waste, can we?
Focus. If we swim
well, we do well.
Exactly, we'll show
everyone just how strong
this team really is.
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 10A]
Ready. Set.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
Momo's so fast!
Right off the platform!
[UOZUMI] He's already
got a lead on Iwatobi!
[IWASHIMIZU]
Wow!
[MINAMI] No. Iwatobi's
starting to close in!
[UOZOMI]
Go, Momo!
[RIN, SOSUKE]
Momo!
[UOZUMI]
It's close!
They tied!
Did you see that exchange?
[MINAMI] That guy just
keeps getting better.
[IWASHIMIZU]
Yeah, but Iwatobi's fast, too!
[REI]
Nagisa!
[RIN]
Come on! Swim!
Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
[UOZUMI]
Oh, no. Sosuke.
[MINAMI]
His shoulder.
Look, they're head-to-head!
--[NAGISA] Rei!
--[NITORI] Go!
What's this all about?
I don't know what
the heck you guys
think you're doin' right now,
but I know what you
should be doing, and that's
cheering your teammates on!
[UOZUMI]
Ready! Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB] Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
[GOU] Oh, no, Sosuke's
catching up to Rei!
[AMAKATA]
He's widening his lead!
[grunts]
[groans]
[BOTH]
Swim, Sosuke!
Sosuke!
[yells]
All right!
Come on!
Rin!
[NITORI]
They're both speeding up!
[SOSUKE]
Don't let us down. Go, Rin!
They entered the turn
at the exact same time!
[panting]
--[NITORI] Let's go! Swim!
--[MOMOTARO] Hurry!
--[SOSUKE] Go!
[RIN yells]
[CROWD cheers]
Second place?
What was our time?
[ALL gasp]
[MINAMI] It's good enough
for Nationals! All right!
[AMAKATA] Wow! We're going
to Nationals, ladies!
[BOTH] Yay! We're going
to Nationals. No way!
Good job, guys.
I'm proud of all of us.
[MOMOTARO yells]
[ALL laugh]
That rocked!
Yeah!
Yeah. It sure did!
[GROUP laughs]
Thanks, you guys.
[ALL]
Huh?
Look at Sosuke bein'
a big cheese ball.
[RIN, NITORI laugh]
[SOSUKE]
Rin.
Well, I think I finally found
what I was looking for.
[gasps]
[RIN]
Took you long enough.
[SOSUKE, RIN laugh]
[SUGIMOTO]
The following swimmers
have advanced to Nationals.
Ryono in freestyle.
Mizutani in breaststroke.
And, of course, Rin Matsuoka.
He advanced in the
100-meter freestyle
and medley relay. You should
be proud of yourselves.
Now let's get ready
for nationals!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yes, sir!
It's pretty exciting stuff.
[SUGIMOTO]
Matsuoka.
After your incredible showing
at the Regional Tournament,
every scout in the country
is paying attention.
You can have your "pick of the
litter," as the saying goes.
You should narrow down
your top choices
as soon as possible.
[RIN]
Right.
[gasps]
Hey. Pretty good practice.
Thank you.
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot--you got
something in the mail today.
[gasps]
[SOSUKE]
Is it good news?
[RIN]
Hey, Sosuke.
[SOSUKE]
Yeah?
Do you know what you're
gonna do after you graduate?
I dunno.
Maybe move back in with
my parents for a while.
Help my dad run his business.
So, you're really
gonna quit swimming.
It's all over.
[SOSUKE]
Yep.
[RIN sighs]
[SOSUKE]
Hey, stop with the moping.
I told ya, my dream's
already come true.
Here it goes.
[SOSUKE]
Hey. Nanase.
Can I talk to you for a second?
[HARUKA]
What do you want?
Tell me.
Why did you stand up in the
middle of the freestyle race?
Whatever I did has
nothing to do with you.
Yeah, but I'm pretty sure
it has something to do with Rin.
Which means it's
my business now.
If you don't keep going,
then Rin might follow suit.
You know, it's not
the first time
you've said something
like that to me.
[SOSUKE]
Even if you don't realize it,
you're important to Rin.
Which is exactly why I'm here.
Because you and Rin
are connected.
Would you just get
to the point already?
Rin needs you, Haruka.
When he competes with
you, he's at his best.
You help him reach
his full potential.
I don't get you.
Why the hell are you
so hung up on Rin?
My career is over.
But he could still compete
on the world level.
I wanna see him do what I can't.
[HARUKA gasps]
[SOSUKE] Most people would kill
to have the ability you have.
And it sucks to
watch you sit there
and do nothing with it.
You have talent! Use it!
[HARUKA gasps]
[SOSUKE] That's all
I wanted to say. Later.
All right, so is
everybody here now?
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yes, sir!
[RIN]
Starting the day after tomorrow,
we'll have a one
week club break.
The next time we meet will be
at the National Tournament.
Those of you who are
competing will get there
two days early to practice
and make any final adjustments.
Until then, let's make sure
we all get plenty of rest.
So do you guys think
you can handle that?
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Sir, yes, sir!
Hey, Rin, let's go.
No time to stare into space.
Yeah. I know.
You guys, wait!
You're totally about to walk
to the train station together
and go home, am I right?
Your houses must
be really close!
Yikes.
What do you want?
Well, it's Pyunsuke,
my pet beetle.
Tell her to take care of him.
[RIN, SOSUKE]
Oh, boy.
[MOMOTARO]
Hey!
How about I release him back
into the mountains instead?
[yelps] Don't even joke
about my sweet little
Pyunsuke like that, you jerk!
I've raised him
since he was a larva!
I harvested sap,
gave him protein jelly,
monitored the
temperature in his cage...
Makoto?
Yeah, what's up?
[MAKOTO]
Hey, Rin. I, um...
Sorry, there's something I
wanted to talk to you about.
[RIN] You sound kinda down.
Did something happen?
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, kind of.
[RIN]
Wow, that explains a lot.
Guy doesn't even sound like him.
[MAKOTO]
I know.
I have a feeling
Haru needs to see
more of the world,
like you have.
Strange as it seems,
I think you're the only one
who can to get through
to him right now.
[MAKOTO] We all really
love Haru, you know?
We want him to find
his own dream,
no matter what it may take.
Yeah, I'm not as into
his dreams as you are.
[MAKOTO laughs]
That's fair.
I suppose I can
figure somethin' out.
Don't worry.
[MAKOTO]
Thanks.
I still owe him for what
he did last year, anyway.
You got any plans
after graduation?
Actually, I do.
I've decided I'm gonna
go to college in Tokyo.
[RIN]
Really?
Finally found somethin'
you wanted, huh? I'm glad.
Yeah, thank you. I am, too.
[RIN] I was kinda worried you'd
be so concerned with Haru
that you wouldn't be able
to make any choices
about what you wanted
to do for yourself.
[MAKOTO laughs]
No, I figured it out.
[RIN]
It is a little sad, though.
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, it is.
[RIN]
Hey, Makoto?
[MAKOTO]
Hm?
One day, it sure
would be nice if we--
Catch ya later!
Bye! Don't forget to
bring me something!
Are you seriously going?
[RIN] Huh? Yeah, it's been
a while since I moved
back from Australia.
This isn't just for Haru.
Couldn't hurt to remind
myself how I felt
when I was there, either.
Ultimately, though,
I want Haru to really
look at his future.
Funny.
Wish you could see the
expression you make
when you talk about him.
[RIN]
Sorry, what?
Nothing.
[RIN sighs]
I guess that's it.
So, tell me, what do you
want me to bring back for ya?
Nothing too sweet.
Way to be specific.
I'm sure whatever
you pick up is fine.
Just don't let it take up
too much luggage space.
[RIN] If you say so.
Not too sweet, huh?
Make sure you're gettin'
the rest you need. Okay?
Yeah, I will. Take care
of yourself down there.
[RIN]
Yeah.
[NITORI]
All right, Momo!
I think we should use this break
to polish up our exchanges
and make 'em super fast!
Heck yeah, that's an
awesome plan!
If we practice hard,
there's no way we won't
have the best exchanges ever!
[SOSUKE]
Hey, you two.
We've got this break before
the tournament for a reason.
You gotta be careful not
to wear yourselves out.
I get that, but it's
our first Nationals,
and the last thing
we wanna do is compete
while we still don't feel
100 percent confident
about our exchanges.
[MOMOTARO] I'd like to finish
in the best position I can
to pass it off to Rin!
[sighs]
Then, make sure you
don't slow down right
before your finish.
Bend your knees to get ready,
and focus on that goal.
Don't take your eyes off it.
Hold on, I need to
write down some notes!
Crap, where'd my pen go?
Thank you so much!
At the joint practice
after the break,
I'll help you guys out myself.
Until then, please make sure
you keep stretching.
[NITORI, MOMOTARO]
We really appreciate it!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Good morning!
[RIN]
Hey.
Hope you had a good trip
there and back, Captain!
It was awesome.
Been any earth-shattering
changes since I left?
No, sir--I mean, Rin!
We've been stay--!
[MOMOTARO]
What'd you get me?
Can I have my souvenir now?
Subtle. Nice.
Why not? Sure.
Knock yourself out.
Awesome! It's a boomerang!
[gasps]
[SOSUKE] Give yourself
more time to recover.
Your center of balance is off.
[MOMOTARO]
Sosuke!
Oh, hey.
Sorry I'm late.
Got here as soon as I could.
So Australia. Good?
Oh, yeah, it's incredible.
[SOSUKE] Man. Kind of a long
way to go to make a point.
Yeah, well. It's worth it.
And I'd do it all again
in a heartbeat.
[NAGISA laughs]
[SOSUKE]
Bet you would.
[sighs]
[RIN]
What's the matter, ladies?
No one got the guts
to take on the captain?
Momo!
[MOMOTARO] Give me a second
to not die, will ya?
[RIN] Today, we third
years say good-bye.
Lot of change on the horizon.
Come April, there'll
be new recruits.
Club as you know
it'll be overhauled.
My hope for each
and every one of you
is that you'll make the cut,
be part of the Regionals team.
The year after that, same thing:
new recruits, new team.
I want you to feel like
you're carrying the torch,
keeping the dream alive
from season to season.
You all need to know
that you're part of
something bigger
than yourselves!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Yes, sir!
Heh. Nice. Surprised
you're not bawling.
[RIN]
Ai!
Uh, sir!
Next year, you call the shots.
[RIN]
I'm making you captain.
Sir.
[MOMOTARO]
Go, Nitori!
[UOZUMI]
Congratulations, Captain!
[SOSUKE]
Rin?
[RIN]
Where you gettin' this idea
that your shoulder
can't be fixed?
[SOSUKE]
What?
Are you seriously
out of the game?
Or are you closing the
door on your dreams
before you even try?
Give it some thought.
When you decide not to
be done, I'll be waiting.
[SOSUKE]
Wow. 'Course you'd say that.
What else did I expect?
Well, it hasn't
fallen on deaf ears.
[MOMOTARO] Hey, Rin!
Let's go get something to eat!
Uh-- Okay.
Sosuke, you're gonna
come with us, too, right?
[laughs]
Uh...
[RIN] Come on, Sosuke.
Don't fight it.
All right.
[GOU]
Take a break, Rin.
You don't have to
practice all the time.
Maybe try coming home
every once in a while.
You know how worried
Mom gets about you.
[RIN laughs]
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I am planning on coming
home this weekend
if you wanna tell her for me.
[GOU]
For real?
Well, since you'll
help out with Mom,
I guess I won't move out.
[RIN]
Here, give me that.
[GOU]
Huh?
[RIN]
Move it. I'm walkin' ya home.
[GOU]
Oh, okay.
[RIN]
Shut up. I can hear you smiling.
[GOU giggles] I can't help
liking that you never change.
[RIN]
And you never make sense.
[NITORI] This will be
the official training
regimen for everyone.
Uozumi and Iwashimizu,
please check all the equipment.
And Momo, I'd like you
to please take care
of the chlorine before practice.
[MOMOTARO, UOZUMI, IWASHIMIZU]
Yes, sir!
[MAKOTO] I realize how hard
you worked this year.
So, from now on, I'd like the
three of you to work together
on the Iwatobi Swim Club.
That sound doable?
--[NAGISA] Yeah!
--[REI] Yes!
[MAKOTO]
Rei.
I'm entrusting this
Swim Club and its future
to you from now on.
Captain.
Yes, sir!
[NAGISA, GOU cheer]
[SOSUKE]
Oh, yeah, I remember, now.
[RIN]
So funny.
Can you believe how
stubborn we were?
Whaddaya mean "we were"?
[RIN laughs]
So, is your plan to head
to Australia right away?
No, I'm thinkin'
I'll go back home
for a couple of weeks
before leaving.
Mom misses me a lot,
and that's not easy
for Gou, you know?
I'll be taking off after that.
Gotcha. I'll be
writing you again.
Oh, you will? Well, I'll
make sure to reply this time.
Really? You'll write back?
[RIN]
Yeah.
[SOSUKE]
Hey, Rin.
Actually, there's something
that's been bothering me
for a little while.
[SOSUKE] During Nationals,
this one swimmer caught my eye.
Yeah, I noticed that
Kinjo from Suda-East
has gotten a lot better
in the 100 and the 200
in just the past six months.
[SOSUKE]
No.
Uh...
It's Ikuya Kirishima.
Hold on, who?
[SOSUKE] This guy. I
completely forgot about him.
He was a breaststroke swimmer
during middle school.
Had a pretty decent
time back then.
But he didn't really appear
in any official races
in high school.
When I saw him swim at
the tournament, though...
The individual medley.
[SOSUKE]
Yeah. His strokes were perfect.
I couldn't find even
a single flaw.
And if that was all,
he would have just
been an amazing swimmer.
No big deal.
I wouldn't have been
so hung up on it.
What surprised me
about him was...
[SOSUKE]
He swam like someone else.
Haruka Nanase.
[SOSUKE] I can't shake this
feeling I have about him.
I think he actually wants
to swim freestyle.
Rin, if you're aiming
for the world after this,
you're not gonna be able to
avoid swimming against him.
[RIN]
Ikuya Kirishima.
[HIYORI] I mean, it was
our last tournament.
You could've at least attended
the awards ceremony, Ikuya.
Plus, you had some old
friends that were there,
and you missed out
on seeing 'em.
Hey, what was the middle
school you went to again?
Iwatobi, wasn't it?
Where are you goin'?
Just gonna call my brother.
Always with the big brother.
Will you stop saying that?
I swear, he's so adorable.
Finally third years.
It's about time, huh?
We're so gonna own this year!
I know, but first we need
to get some club members!
This time, we're gonna show
all the new students
at this school something amazing
that they've never seen before!
[HANAMURA] What on earth
could that even be?
Hey, don't laugh.
I'm serious! Gah!
[NAGISA, NITORI]
Ah--
Hey, Iwatobians,
long time no see!
Yeah, not since the
tournament, right?
Oh, yeah. Congrats, Ai.
We heard you were made
the new team captain!
[NITORI]
Thanks!
And congrats to Ryugazaki
for being your new captain!
Thank you! Looking forward
to the coming year!
Well, you wanna
keep up the tradition
of a healthy rivalry between
Samezuka and Iwatobi?
[REI]
Yeah!
I mean, how could we not?
So here's a friendly warning,
prepare yourselves for
the next joint practice!
Oh, you don't have
to worry about us.
We'll be more than ready
to show your team
how it's supposed to be done!
[MISAKA]
Sir, thanks to you,
we were able to
make it to Regionals.
It was the most amazing thing
I've ever experienced!
[ARATO]
Thank you so much, sir!
Now, don't cry, you guys.
Remember, we still
gotta get ready
for the coming school year!
You need to focus.
Believe in yourselves first,
and I know you'll
get amazing results!
[MISAKA, TAKAMARU, ARATO]
Yes, sir!
[phone vibrates]
Huh? One sec.
It's my sister telling
me not to forget
that we're going back to my
grandma's to visit next week.
[phone vibrates]
Huh?
No way!
It looks like I'll get to see
one of my old friends
while I'm there!
[TAKAMARU]
Cool.
And where exactly does
your grandma live again?
Um, how do you not remember?
She lives in Iwatobi.
[KISUMI]
Oh, nice! Asahi!
That name sure takes me back.
I wonder if he's doing okay.
It'd be nice to get
everyone together again.
[MAKOTO]
Wow. There are so many people.
Unimaginable back at home, huh?
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
Hey, is something
bothering you?
I can't relax.
[MAKOTO laughs]
Yeah, me neither.
I just feel really anxious.
But...
I'm pretty excited, too.
Same here. Should be fun.
[REFEREE 13B]
Take your marks.
Makoto. You're ready, yeah?
[MAKOTO]
Mm-hm.
[HARUKA] By the time
you're 20, you're normal.
I wonder.
When I look back on these days,
will I be happy with who I am?
[HARUKA]
For now, I just want to treasure
each moment as it comes.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
[MAKOTO] Let's see.
The preview for next time is...
[HARUKA]
This is Haruka, moge .
I've been captured by an evil
organization and transformed
into the monster,
Iwamogera, moge .
[RIN]
Not at all accurate.
[REI] In March, when the
third years all graduate,
these four beautiful
stories will bring color
to an early spring.
[NAGISA] Rei and I will
be transformed, too!
[HARUKA] The biceps brachii
muscle versus the soleus muscle.
A duel at Iwatobi coast, moge !
And then, the true identity
of the mysterious
trapezius muscle man
who appears there is...
[RIN]
That's not right! Next time:
[MAKOTO]
"Choice of Fate!"
[NAGISA] "Cooling Down at
a Secluded Hot Springs!"
[REI]
"Butterfly of Promise!"
[HARUKA]
"Eternal Blue of Setting Off!"
[RIN] We're bringing you
these four stories.
[HARUKA, MAKOTO, NAGISA, REI,
RIN] In Free! Take Your Marks !
[RIN] Ah, no, no guys, I got
this. Take Your Marks .