[BOTH gasp]
[MIYAKO]
She's returning each one.
Riko, you don't suppose
this Hanesaki girl is...
[RIKO]
Yeah, the one who beat Nagisa
at last year's junior
nationals in a shutout.
[MIYAKO]
Oh, I knew it!
[TACHIBANA]
A shutout?
[RIKO] She was still in
middle school at the time.
[NAGISA] If placement
doesn't work, how 'bout this?
[NAGISA grunts]
8-3.
What awesome defense.
[NAGISA]
The corners, the body.
No matter where I aim,
my smashes don't get through.
You can do it!
You've got to win this!
Otherwise Hanesaki
won't join the club!
She'd be a great addition!
[TACHIBANA] Yes. Her reflexes,
the flexibility of her wrist,
it's all exceptional.
[NAGISA grunts]
[gasps]
[AYANO]
Mom...
[grunts]
[YU]
Service over! 4-8!
Ayano.
You didn't even go for it.
[AYANO]
I've had enough.
[NAGISA grunts]
[NAGISA]
What does that mean?
We're in the middle of a match!
Are you not feeling well?
I'm the adviser by the way.
Have you decided to join?
No, thank you.
--Huh?
--I told you I didn't want to.
Come on. We're leaving.
[ELENA] If you need one,
I'll be the team manager.
[gasps]
Not gonna lie.
I wish it had been full of
hot guys like tennis club,
but what can you do?
But, Elena, why?
[HAYAMA sighs] Look at what
all your practice is doing.
You've worn out these birdies.
[YU] But you keep yours
in perfect condition,
don't you, Hayama?
What's that supposed to mean?
[YU giggles]
So, how many times has
she done this drill?
This is the fifth, I think.
[RIKO]
Last one!
Great job.
I wasn't the one doing the
drill, and I'm exhausted.
[NAGISA]
No, let's do one more set.
[gasps]
You should probably
take a break.
[NAGISA]
No.
I have to practice more.
Can't afford to relax.
I need to get better.
[TACHIBANA]
Heya, what's up, team?
--[PLAYERS] Hello, coach.
--[ELENA] Hello, perv boy!
Where in the schedule are you?
Done. We're onto
practice matches.
Good.
Then on Court A, let's have
the older Isehara and Hayama.
On court B,
Aragaki and Hanesaki.
Okay, and the rest of you--
[AYANO]
I'll pass for now.
Since I just joined.
[TACHIBANA]
Why did you quit?
Huh?
Why did you give up
playing badminton?
[TACHIBANA]
Like I said before,
you have naturally
flexible wrists,
and you're left-handed,
which is an enormous advantage.
You have real talent!
We'll crush the Inter-Highs,
move to the nationals...
...then the world tournament!
After that... on to
the Olympic--[groans]
I told you, cut it out with
the creepy hand groping!
[AYANO whimpers]
But you're still
playing badminton.
I won't let you quit.
What? How come?
'Cause the perv's right.
You've got major talent.
[AYANO groans] Even if that
was true, I don't want to play.
[TACHIBANA groans]
Izumi.
Yes?
[TACHIBANA] For today,
you and Aragaki can partner up.
This is so stupid.
Let's get started.
[RIKO]
Mm-hmm.
[BOTH grunting]
[HAYAMA gasps]
[SORA]
21-15.
Match won by Isehara.
[HAYAMA grunts]
Hey!
[YU gasps]
[NAGISA]
Don't get distracted!
What? Oh, sorry.
[NAGISA]
Wrong one!
You know what I think?
After she lost in the junior
nationals to Hanesaki,
it really threw
Aragaki off her game.
[NAGISA] All the time I've
put in hasn't been a waste.
After all, I have my smash.
With it, I can win!
[RIKO]
I've got it! I can...
[YU]
21-19. Match won by Aragaki!
[RIKO sighs]
I got so close
to beating you
that time, Nagisa.
This is gonna be tough. Yep.
[YU]
Hey. What's Ayano's deal?
She acts like she
couldn't care less.
[SORA]
Not sure.
But for someone that
apathetic, she's really good.
Must be nice to
have natural talent.
I don't know.
I think you and your
brother are talented.
We're average, really.
Well, catch you later.
See you tomorrow!
[TOMO]
Yu!
[gasps]
Down the hatch!
Look at you, going to town!
I can't help myself!
I'm telling you guys,
after a workout,
nothing restores your
energy like meat!
The club. How's it going?
I mean, is she
still on a rampage?
[MEGU] Come on. Be honest.
Is it miserable?
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
But recently, the slump she's in
seems to be, uh, getting worse.
[MEGU]
Sounds like karma.
[TOMO]
It's what she deserves
for taking out her
anger on the team.
Huh?
But I thought you were hungry.
It's not as if
I worked out today.
Let's go.
[MEGU]
See ya!
[TOMO]
Later, Yu!
See you guys around!
--[thud]
--[AYANO, NAGISA groan]
Well, get back on your feet.
[HAYAMA]
Nagisa, the unstoppable force,
and Ayano, the immovable object.
Those two should be
the perfect complement
to each other, and yet...
They're both so different,
I don't know if they
can work together.
[gasps]
[NAGISA grunts]
Whoa!
Nice save, Ayano!
[NAGISA]
I can match her!
[NAGISA] Here it comes.
I need to get this one.
I can't let her--[groans]
Owie!
--Are you okay?
--What the hell's your problem?
I was gonna smash it,
but you just had
to get in my way!
You're the one who
crashed into me.
[NAGISA]
What was that?
Step in, Izumi.
[AYANO sighs]
[TACHIBANA]
No, Hanesaki stays.
I meant Aragaki.
Why am I out?
You have tunnel vision.
You're too fixated
on your smashes.
Step out and watch.
[RIKO]
Take it!
[ALL gasp]
[TACHIBANA]
You see that, Aragaki?
What did Izumi do different?
She used judgment
while you did not.
Yeah, sounds about
right. Got it.
In other words, I need to
make your favorite look good.
Right, Tachibana?
I mean, it's the least I can do.
You need untalented
players around
in order to make the
gifted ones stand out more.
[CROWD cheers]
[REFEREE 02A]
21-10. Aragaki wins the match.
[GIRL 02A] Wow! You even
won against Takashi!
[GIRL 02B] That jump smash
of yours is so cool!
No one can beat it!
[TAKASHI]
There she goes, the sasquatch.
[BOY 02A]
Don't worry about it, Takashi.
She's basically a guy anyway.
[GIRL 02A]
They're just jealous.
[GIRL 02B] Yeah. Don't let
their trash talk get you down.
[GIRL 02A] But Nagisa doesn't
really play fair, does she?
[GIRL 02B]
She's taller than everyone else.
Of course she's
always gonna win.
[NAGISA] It doesn't matter
how good at badminton I get.
They think the only reason
I win is because I'm tall.
Even though I practice.
More than any of them!
[NAGISA panting]
[door opens]
[AYANO]
I'm heading out.
[RIKO]
Good practice today!
You shouldn't take it so hard.
The only reason my doubles
match with Ayano went so well
was pure luck.
In a one-on-one game,
everyone knows you're
a better player than me.
Yeah? Are you sure?
Then why did you go easy
on me during our match?
Not gonna deny it?
Go on. I'll return the key.
Okay. Thanks a bunch, Riko.
[YU]
See you tomorrow!
I know I shouldn't,
but it's become a
full-on addiction.
[YU gasps]
So good.
After a workout,
you gotta have meat, right?
You know what?
I hope I can learn to do a great
jump smash like you someday.
You're just out of
your groove right now,
but don't worry.
It won't be long.
You're so tall and, like,
way stronger than me.
Once you've got
your rhythm back,
Ayano won't stand a
chance against you!
[GIRL 02A] But Nagisa doesn't
really play fair, does she?
[GIRL 02B]
She's taller than everyone else.
Of course she's
always gonna win.
[YU]
The bottom line is
you're much more talented
than I'll ever be, Nagisa.
[NAGISA]
Shut up! I'm not talented!
Everyone knows I only have
one thing going for me.
I'm tall.
[NAGISA]
Yuka.
Taking your anger out on others?
Not much has changed.
What are you even
complaining about?
Quit whining and
get back to work.
Heh. I don't need any advice,
especially from a quitter.
Wait, Yuka.
[YU]
Not good. This isn't good!
I never told you how much
I envied you, did I?
Look, I'm not talented.
How many times do...
[YUKA]
I don't care about that.
What I envied wasn't
how you played. It was why.
That genuine love you
always had for badminton.
Let's end with
laps and stretches.
[PLAYERS]
Yes, sir.
Aragaki. Get on the court.
You and I are having
a match. First to 21.
Why should I play
someone like you?
[TACHIBANA]
Afraid?
Maybe you don't want to play
someone who can beat you?
So now you're saying you're
a better player than I am?
Honestly, I'm not sure.
How about we find out?
Don't underestimate me
'cause I'm a girl.
[NAGISA]
Further than I thought.
Damn it. This guy's good.
[TACHIBANA]
7-love.
Oh, by the way,
I heard you got shut out
at nationals last autumn.
By a middle schooler?
Shut up! Are you
gonna serve or what?
[NAGISA]
Will it be short or long?
It's long! A smash!
The best return would be
a cross-court drive.
[NAGISA]
It went to the middle,
but I forced him to
return it underhanded.
I can attack from here!
[TACHIBANA]
She didn't hit cross-court.
She's too worried
about striking the net.
It slowed her judgment.
[NAGISA grunts]
[TACHIBANA]
There's another weak angle.
[gasps]
[TACHIBANA] She's too
concerned about control.
She's not following through.
[TACHIBANA] I'm starting to see
where her slump is coming from.
[NAGISA]
He returned it again.
I need to place my shots.
Think about the angles.
It doesn't make sense.
None of my smashes
are getting through!
[NAGISA]
Damn!
[NAGISA] He's intentionally
returning clears.
[NAGISA grunts, pants]
[TACHIBANA]
I'm tall like you. I get it.
You're relying on a jump smash
from a high vantage point,
because you're convinced
it's your greatest weapon.
You've thought that
since you were young.
"She's only good
'cause she's tall."
I bet you heard that
from the other students
all the time, right?
Thing is, they don't realize
it also makes you heavier,
so you need to work
out your legs more,
or you won't make contact.
The reason you win isn't
because you're tall.
It's because you train
harder than everyone else.
[TACHIBANA]
It's okay to hit the net.
It's okay if your
placement isn't spot on.
And that smash of yours,
it's pretty damn hard
to return at all.
You should be proud of that,
because you worked for it.
[TACHIBANA] You love the hell
out of badminton, don't you?
[TACHIBANA]
Come on. Our game's not over.
[NAGISA]
What was I so unsure about?
I've trained more than anyone.
If they don't know that, I do!
[panting]
That's more like it.
Everyone, I'm sorry.
A captain should
never put herself
ahead of the rest of the team.
It was wrong of me.
[RIKO] The Inter-High
prelims are coming up soon.
Nagisa, you know
I love this club.
I want to keep playing badminton
with you as long as I can.
Since this is our last summer,
wouldn't it be awesome
if our team won?
Look at those starry eyes.
We're gonna see this
through! All the way!
[RIKO]
Mm-hmm.
Go on!
Let's go! Kitakomachi, fight!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[PLAYERS clapping]
Ayano.
We're on the same team,
but I am going to beat you.
Yeah. I can quit
whenever I want.
[TOMO]
Yu!
So what's new?
I'm guessing practice
went late today?
Yeah, things got a little crazy.
What about you guys?
Don't think just 'cause
you're in badminton,
you're the only one
with a busy schedule!
We just got out of cram school.
What? No way. Oh!
Uh-huh. You had it in your head
we were a bunch of slackers.
To be honest, I don't have
enough time these days
to pursue much else.
However...
--[YUKA laughs]
--[YU gasps] Huh?
You know, meat's
just the thing you need
after a mental workout.
That's the truth.
Agreed.
Can you hear me?
I want the world to know
how much I love myself!
If I want to win,
it's now or never!