[NAGISA] I started
badminton really early,
back in elementary school.
It was frustrating.
Sometimes even painful.
Despite that, it was always fun.
"I'll become the best in Japan
and play on the world stage."
That's what I thought...
until that day.
No matter how I hit it,
no matter where I sent it,
I couldn't manage to get
a single shot past her.
My opponent... was overpowering.
[AYANO]
Finally home.
[AYANO sighs]
[UCHIKA]
Welcome back, Ayano.
But I guess it's
the other way around,
seeing as how I haven't
been here in a while.
I heard the news.
You're going to the finals
in the Inter-High.
My dear, Uchika...
for long time, you and Ayano
have shared a deep connection,
a mutual passion
for the sport of badminton.
Won't you consider coming home?
[clock chiming]
I wonder how she plays now.
I've been gone a long time.
Things change.
Has she gotten better?
Intense!
Watching them play
is wearing me out.
[BOTH grunting]
[AYANO]
Dang it!
[YU]
Seventeen-fourteen.
So close!
It makes sense he's good.
Coach Tachibana
was an Olympic hopeful.
[RIKO] But Ayano could have
played him anytime this summer.
Why is it suddenly
so important?
[grunting]
Final score, 21-17.
Coach Tachibana wins the game.
I'm exhausted.
Thanks again
for asking me to play, Hanesaki.
-[AYANO] One more time.
-No way, no how.
Go easy on an old man,
all right?
No fair! Just one more, please!
I was only getting warmed up!
[AYANO grumbling]
You. Want to go?
It'll be a dry run
for the finals.
Not like there's anyone else
here worth practicing against.
You want to play me,
don't you, Nagisa?
Wait a minute.
What's the rush?
You'll both get your chance
during the finals!
Don't be so uptight, Riko.
It's only a practice match.
Yeah, I'm not stupid!
But I don't want...
-[TACHIBANA clapping]
-Huh?
I need everyone
to come gather around!
[sighs]
Let's go.
As you all know,
the boys' prelims are tomorrow.
Hayama, Isehara,
it all comes down to this.
Don't hold anything back.
[HAYAMA and GAKU together]
Yes, sir.
Good luck tomorrow.
[laughing]
I got paired
against one of the top four
players from last year.
Luck's not on my side.
You can't predict what's going
to happen during a match.
The only thing you can do
is offer up your best.
Right! I'll be seeing you
in the finals, Gaku!
-We're in the same bracket.
-Huh?
If we do play each other,
it'll be in the semis.
Yeah! I was
aware of that, obviously!
It was a joke, really!
I mean, you do know
not everything has to be
taken so literally!
So, pretty cool, huh?
How we have two girls
from our school
who ended up being finalists!
For sure!
And it means they're both
going to nationals,
which is way exciting!
Yeah, agreed.
When they finally play,
I'm sure it'll be great.
I don't know why the two
of you are pretending.
Let's be real.
Nagisa doesn't stand
a chance against me
after how messed up her knee is.
Well, you can't be sure of that
until you have a chance
to play her.
Nagisa, you don't...
I need to make a stop
at the coach's office.
Go on ahead without me.
[door opening and closing]
Talk about lame!
She's such a buzzkill.
[YU and RIKO groaning]
[knocking on door]
-[NAGISA] Excuse me.
-Hey.
You wanted to see me?
[MIYAKO]
How's your knee treating you?
There's some stiffness and pain,
but it's not affecting me
on the court.
There's no reason
you should push yourself harder.
You made the Inter-High.
So what? You're telling me
I should forfeit?
You can wait to face Hanesaki
on the national stage.
We may never get matched up.
If you continue winning,
eventually, you will.
You're both capable
of reaching that point.
[sighs]
Don't get so fixated
on every match
and think about your future.
[TACHIBANA'S stomach grumbling]
Well, mull it over.
Let me know what you decide.
The only thing
on my mind now is food.
See you tomorrow!
I've told you this before,
but he went really far.
[NAGISA]
Coach was in the running
for the Olympics, right?
His knee was
giving him problems too.
He had a big international
match coming up.
Since he was a shoe-in
for the Olympics,
he decided not to participate.
Then another Japanese player
came out with a surprise victory
during the competition.
The Olympic slot ended up
going to that athlete,
and soon afterwards,
Tachibana retired.
Okay, back up.
Coach was worried
about his knee,
and it ended his career?
Then I--
I'm saying that he knows
what you're going through,
and he's still telling you
to be careful.
At this moment,
I think he can relate
to you better than anyone else.
Try to understand, he only wants
what's best for your future.
[RIKO] What did Coach Tachibana
want to talk about?
[NAGISA]
You can guess.
[RIKO]
Your knee, huh?
Look, I know
it's not my decision,
but if you have to choose,
I don't think
you should play her.
And besides,
I'm worried about Ayano.
She's been acting
stranger and stranger.
I guess
I really don't like the idea
of you two going head-to-head.
But hey, I should learn to start
minding my own business!
It's your choice!
[HAYAMA grunting]
[UCHIKA] I see! Sounds like
she's gotten really good.
Oh, I know that.
Just leave everything to me.
I'll be in touch with you soon.
[UCHIKA]
Godnat, Connie.
Great shot!
Gaku's burning through this
match like it's nothing!
Mm-hmm.
-[GIRL] Isehara, up here!
-[ALL] Huh?
Come find us after the match!
We know you're gonna win!
I don't think those girls
even go to our school.
Apparently, he's also
received some fan mail.
Whoa!
For real?
I mean, he is a handsome guy.
No denying it.
Sure, I guess.
I always paid more attention
to his talent.
Awesome smash!
Keep raking in those points!
[MIYAKO]
Congrats on your win.
See if you can conserve energy
through your second match.
Right.
[GIRL]
I'll be cheering you on!
[SORA]
Some advice.
Goku, don't get cocky
out there, okay?
How can she tell?
Boy's got a poker face.
No clue.
Your first match of the day.
You ready?
[HAYAMA]
Yeah.
[MIYAKO]
Do your best!
[TACHIBANA] What gives?
Where's your usual passion?
I'll be there to watch you
during the early game.
Start out by hitting him hard
and making him lose his focus.
Sure, coach.
After coming this far,
what else can you do
but give it your best?
Remember, he made it
to the final four last year,
but he's a second-year.
Experience is on your side.
[YU]
You don't have to fight so hard!
You don't have to fight
so hard anymore!
[TACHIBANA]
What's the matter, Ebina?
[NAGISA] I don't get it.
Was it something I said?
Hmm?
Huh? Hold on!
It's my not my fault!
[footsteps approaching]
Yu, come sit beside me.
[REFEREE]
On my right, Shun Hosoi.
On my left, Yukiteru Hayama.
Hosoi to serve.
Love-all. Play!
Nice!
Yes!
-All that training paid off!
-He's really moving!
Yeah!
-Luck is on his side!
-Come on, Hayama!
Damn it!
-He's on a roll!
-Three points in a row!
You're doing great, Hayama!
[RIKO]
Since his opponent's flustered,
he should widen his lead
as much as possible.
-[GAKU] He got it!
-[NAGISA] Now!
[HAYAMA]
It's out.
Finally on the board!
What? But didn't it land
out-of-bounds?
Almost. It was on the line.
He scored, which means
now, the real match begins.
-[REFEREE] Out.
-[grumbling]
Sixteen!
We can count. He is so annoying.
Keep calm!
You can still catch up!
His opponent sure
has a lot of skill.
There's a reason
he reached the final four
during his first year.
[ELENA] Do your best, Hayama!
Fight! We believe in you!
[GAKU] Lower your gravity!
And don't watch your shots!
[NAGISA] Now finish strong!
Don't sweat it!
[RIKO]
You're still in this!
[GAKU]
Don't give up!
You'll make it back!
[HAYAMA] Damn! I gotta change
this momentum somehow.
[HAYAMA]
Yes!
[gasping]
-In!
-There we go!
So close! What a shame!
Come on!
Always keep your feet moving!
You're leaving?
[YU]
Bathroom break.
Your opponent's worn down, too.
You've gotta hang in there.
[HAYAMA] I'll try.
He sure is good, though!
Well, I should get to my match.
Don't get distracted, okay?
-Fight hard!
-Sure.
Yeah, I see you up there.
[HAYAMA] Your third match
is coming up next, right?
I know you can make it...
to nationals.
[HAYAMA] Okay, the backhand grip
looks like this.
You got it! Just raise
your index finger higher.
-Like this?
-Perfect!
And for the next lesson,
I'm gonna teach you
how to serve!
The first thing you should know
is there's two kinds,
short and long serves.
[breathing heavily]
[COACH] Isehara!
What were you thinking?
I told you to hit
around-the-head,
not a high backhand!
If you take the easy approach,
you'll never get far!
Sir.
[COACH]
Also, you're changing
the direction
your racket faces too early.
You need to hold it
until the last second,
or you won't beat
stronger opponents.
And your eye-line.
If you always look
in the direction
you want the birdie to go,
you'll give your angle away.
[HAYAMA]
No matter what you tried,
you always managed
to pick it up right away.
I guess I'm kind of a dummy
and could never get the knack.
-You're wearing him down!
-That's in!
[HAYAMA]
I didn't have the talent for it.
The thing is
I have a different one.
A talent for not knowing
when to quit!
[NAGISA]
Want to talk?
Did something happen
with you and Hayama?
I saw him. He was training
in the park at night.
I knew he was putting
in time practicing,
trying to be a better player.
But then, actually seeing him
working so hard at badminton,
for some reason,
it made me feel so frustrated.
It was painful.
[HOSOI]
Oh, yeah!
[panting]
[grumbling]
[REFEREE]
Game. Match won by Hosoi.
Scores are 21-17, 21-13.
Thank you!
Good match!
[crying]
Talk about rough luck.
I'm going to keep playing
in college.
Yeah, I know.
I thought this would be
the end of the road,
but I don't want to quit now.
I'm behind that idea completely.
Yu? Is this usually the way
you take to get home?
[YU]
Nope.
Thanks a bunch.
[laughing]
Feels strange practicing
when it's over.
-Let me talk, all right?
-Why are you shouting at me?
Because, I think
I kinda liked you!
For real?
[YU] But now,
I'm not so sure anymore.
I kinda had a realization.
The reason I wanted
to encourage you
was probably because
you helped me understand
I shouldn't stop playing,
even if I'm actually
no good at badminton.
[grumbling]
Wait!
Okay, I have no talent
for badminton,
and I'm not going to be
the best in the world.
So I thought, "Why shouldn't
I give it up entirely?"
But you taught me
that wasn't the point of game.
Struggling, working hard,
that meant something on its own,
something important.
So what's going on?
Does that mean
I like you or what?
I think it means you really
like playing badminton.
Oh! You know,
I think you're right!
Well, thanks
for clearing that up!
-No problem?
-See you later!
Who knows?
Maybe I'll keep playing.
21-14. Ayano wins.
-Thanks.
-[SORA] No, thank you.
What a work out!
Wanna play?
Oh, yeah. That's right.
Your knee could blow out
at any time.
Although, it's not like
it would make any difference.
[NAGISA]
I'm playing in the finals.
You know she's provoking you.
Don't let her get
inside your head.
[NAGISA] When Ayano beat me
in the All-Japan Juniors,
it's because I gave up.
I stopped chasing her shots.
And that's when I lost.
Not to her, but myself.
It's important I play Ayano,
because I'll be fighting
the person I was back then.
Honestly, I kind of figured
you were gonna say that.
[NAGISA] I won't push myself
past my limit.
Coach me.
I need your instruction
if I'm going to win.
[TACHIBANA]
I'll give you my best.
[MIYAKO]
And you have my support too.
[UCHIKA]
I heard you played Connie.
[UCHIKA] Once this
tournament's over with,
why not leave Japan with me?