[ELENA]
Ayano, listen to me.
I've been watching
you play badminton
since we were little kids,
and your mom
was first training you.
All the times I did,
you want to know
what I was thinking?
I guess.
I felt like I was left out.
[AYANO]
Huh?
[ELENA] Honestly, I've been
feeling like that again lately,
watching all the girls
in the club fawning over you.
But even so...
I think it'd do you
a lot of good
to keep on playing badminton.
Just my opinion.
I love playing badminton!
♪
[YU]
All finished, Sora!
Could I play
with your hair, please?
Nothing major!
And afterwards, I'll put it back
the way I found it!
Come on. Just a little bit?
-[AYANO] Okay.
-[YU] Awesome!
I am the painter,
and you are my canvas.
Wow! Whatever
you wash your hair with
makes it super silky.
[exclaiming] Hey!
What in the world
are you doing back there?
Leave everything to me.
You're in good hands.
Nagisa, here.
I'm not interested.
Plus my hair's too short.
Well, then how about a pin?
Maybe this one?
My masterpiece is done!
You're looking so adorable, Aya!
Huh? Did you call me "Aya"?
That's right!I took your name
and shortened it,
-thus making it cuter!
-Okay.
Whoa! It's crazy
how much different you all look.
Stop staring
and take our picture already!
Sure!
Okay. Three, two, one.
[shutter clicking]
[ELENA] Turned out pretty well,
didn't it?
It feels like
we're part of a team now.
Part of a team.
[coughing]
[CONNIE speaking in Danish]
[KO]
I'm really sorry, Tachibana.
I was sure
someone had already told you.
[TACHIBANA]
Definitely not.
So you're saying
there's another school here
for a training camp
at the exact same time as us.
Afraid so.
And apparently, they really want
to have a practice game
against Kitakomachi High.
[TACHIBANA]
You don't say?
[shouting and cheering]
Go! Make us proud!
[NAGISA]
Fredericia Girls?
Their team always makes it
to the Inter-High tournament.
I believethey're based
in Miyagi.
What do you think a power house
school is doing out here?
[SHIWAHIME]
You want the truth?
One of our players insisted
on playing Kitakomachi.
My name is Shiwahime.
I'm the captain
of the girls' badminton club.
It's nice
to make your acquaintance.
Oh, wow. Super classy.
These are our club regulars.
We're honored.
May the best team win.
[TEAM in unison]
A pleasure to meet you!
[gasping]
Our team looks
a little intimidated.
I'm Kitakomachi's captain,
Nagisa.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, too.
[TEAM in unison uncertainly]
A pleasure to meet you!
Hmm.
[TACHIBANA] Given
the small nature of our club,
this is what
I'm proposing we do.
I'm thinking one singles match
along with two doubles matches.
So for singles, Aragaki.
For doubles teams,
team one,
Ebina and the younger Isehara.
Team two, Izumi and Hanesaki.
They're a strong team,
but the important thing is
to not get psyched out.
-You ready?
-[together] Sir!
[exclaiming]
Let's get out there and win!
We'll be counting on you, Aya!
This should be exciting.
I've never watched
you play a full match before.
I'm just dying to see
how you handle the competition.
As for Hayama and Gaku,
you'll be playing
against the college students.
[HAYAMA]
What?
[HAYAMA] Man, we got
our work cut out for us, huh?
[AYANO]
My team is counting on me.
-Ayano.
-Yes?
Let's do our best out there!
You bet.
I almost forgot.
Who wants to run
to the convenience store
and pick up supplies?
There's one nearby?
I didn't see anything for miles
on our drive over
except for cabbage fields.
Excuse me. I could go.
That is...
if nobody else wanted to.
Wait right there for a second.
I'll get you some money.
-Aya, you're such a big help!
-Oh, it's nothing.
Don't worry.
I'll draw you up a detailed map.
I... don't know where I am.
What should I do?
[CONNIE]
You lost?
[AYANO]
Her accent! Is she a tourist?
Hmm, didn't you hear me?
I asked if you were lost.
[AYANO]
Yeah, a little.
[CONNIE] Join the club.
I got turned around myself.
I was looking
for a convenience store.
[AYANO] Me too!
I'm also headed that way.
Great!
We'll search together then!
You got a map there?
[AYANO] Well, kinda.
It's not official or anything.
Yeah, no kidding.
Looks like it was drawn
by a 10-year-old.
Ah, I recognize that symbol.
[AYANO] Where are you...
I mean, where are we going?
I checked everywhere!
Wherever she is,
it's not inside the building!
She's not picking up
her phone either.
[SHIWAHIME] I know
she's our youngest player,
but sometimes,
she acts half her age.
This is so typical of her.
Chill out. I'm sure
she'll be back any minute now!
She better.
I mean,
the entire team traveled here
so she could play Kitakomachi.
Then she doesn't even show up
for the match?
I know.
I honestly don't have any idea
why she's so obsessed
with this school.
I knew it!
Check it out.
See this shape? It matches
the one on the map, right?
I think so.
Okay, then if we're facing away
from the entrance,
the store would be over
on our left,
which means we head this way.
Oh, thank you.
[CONNIE]
Are you really in high school?
I find that hard to believe.
You look way younger than me.
[AYANO]
Yeah. What about you?
Where are you from?
[CONNIE]
Miyagi.
[AYANO]
Cool. Wait. Miyagi?
[CONNIE laughing]
Well, I'm from Denmark.
I came to Miyagi
as part of an exchange program.
Oh, okay. That makes more sense.
So, out of all the places,
why'd you choose Japan?
A girl lives here,
and nothing would give me
greater pleasure.
than beating her.
[excited chatter]
Can you believe
we're about to play a match
against the Fredericia Girls?
Feels like my heart's going
a million miles an hour.
-[SORA] Yeah.
-But the good news is
we have Nagisa playing
for our side,
and Aya seems like she'll have
no trouble in her game.
I've got a feeling
our school could win.
[YU]
By the way,
did something happen
between you and Aya?
Not at all.
Nothing?
It just seems like you're...
Hey, guys. Sorry,
but do you know if she's made it
back from the store yet?
[YU]
You mean Aya?
Come to think of it,
she's been gone a while.
[AYANO]
What do you mean "beat"?
[CONNIE]
I want to play and defeat her.
That's why I transferred
to Japan
and attended this camp.
It was all so I could fight her.
And I've waited a long time.
Just the thought
of pummeling her
into the ground...
It's so exciting.
What a coincidence!
I'm also attending
a training camp
with my club from school!
[CONNIE] Something about
seeing you from behind feels...
I don't know... familiar.
How so?
Not to sound weird,
but it's kind of soothing.
In fact, it reminds me
of a someone I know.
[CONNIE]
So, what about you?
Why'd you join your club?
[AYANO]
Uh, at first, I didn't want to,
but I've started
feeling different lately.
I like the idea,
being part of a team.
Why's that?
You see, for the longest time,
I was convinced
I'd always be on my own.
But you know what?
Getting involved with a group
might not be such a bad thing!
Huh.
What exactly does your club do?
There's the store!
[cash register dinging]
[SHOPKEEPER]
Thank you. Come again.
That's a lot of weight to carry.
I think
I can manage it all okay.
Besides, I like the idea
of helping out my team.
Helping people out?
That's so weird.
Hey, what group did you join?
[AYANO]
The badminton club.
[CONNIE gasping]
How interesting.
And what school are you from?
[AYANO]
It's called Kitakomachi High.
[CONNIE]
Hold up a minute. Are you...
[SORA]
Hanesaki!
Sora! Hi!
Someone from my club came
to find me.
Can you get back okay?
[CONNIE]
Was there a point
to your little
friendship routine?
Huh?
Pretty cute.
Do you usually get
everything you want that way?
Uh...
[CONNIE]
Later.
Boy, I'm glad to see... Um.
Did the team send you
to find me?
I want to carry a bag!
Hey! Wait up!
[door opening]
Welcome back you two!
You're just in time!
The singles match with Nagisa
is about to get started.
We're the official cheer squad
and we want you to enlist!
Come on, guys,
let's make some noise!
-You too.
-[grumbles]
Team captain, go on
and show them
what you're made of!
[AYANO]
This will be the first match
I've watched with the club
since joining.
All right, time to win
and be a part of this team.
Look who decided to show up.
[SHIWAHIME]
Hey, Connie.
[ALL grunting and exerting]
That's game point!
The match is won
by Shiraishi-Misato,
Fredericia Girls.
[panting]
It was my fault.
I messed up that last return.
I should have covered you.
It's not your fault.
-Great teamwork!
-That slice though!
[YU]
They were really good!
I was hoping we'd be able
to score a few more.
-[PLAYER 1] It was all skill.
-[PLAYER 2] You're too kind!
[ELENA]
Now the score's one to one.
Down to the last doubles match.
It's all up to Ayano and Riko
to break the tie.
[TACHIBANA]
Connie C?
I mean, Ayano can beat someone
from Fredericia, right?
Well, sure. Hanesaki's talent
should get us far.
But something
about this match bothers me.
[TAGAJO]
You were gone forever.
Didn't realize the store
was in the next town.
Wait. Let me guess.
You got lost again, right?
I made it back in time.
So what's the big deal?
We just thought
you were dead, is all.
Hina sure doesn't know
when to quit.
Sometimes I wish she did.
Connie never
takes the bait, anyway.
-[RIKO] You ready for our match?
-Uh-huh.
You can win this! Okay, Ayano?
Heads up. I'm going
to play this match my way.
Even if I had an opinion
on the matter,
not like you'd listen.
You're finally catching on!
[CONNIE humming]
[HAYAMA] I completely get it.
I'm black and blue!
Those college students
are insanely talented!
I gotta say,
you hung on pretty good
in that second game!
Imagine what would have happened
if that hairpin had landed.
No use dwelling on it, though.
Hey, you guys,
you must be thirsty.
My advice, you shouldn't let
one loss bring you down.
It's just
a practice match anyway.
Work hard
for the next time, okay?
You're right.
[HAYAMA] If only there was
a little more wrist snap
in that hairpin. Hmm.
Oh, there you two are!
I just wanted to tell you
the match is about to start!
Just in time.
Thanks a bunch.
You came to find us
and let us know?
You're the best.
[REFEREE] All right,
the third match will now begin.
[PLAYERS]
Let's play!
[CONNIE]
Prepare yourself.
You'll see how meaningless
your team is.
You're in for a real surprise.
Hey, Ayano, what did
that girl say to you?
Not sure.
[CONNIE] Relax.
I'm not going to need you.
Huh?
[CONNIE]
So do me a favor
and don't interfere
with my match.
Interfere? You do know
how doubles
is supposed to work, right?
You got this!
Do your best, Aya!
Come on, Ayano!
Get us that win!
[REFEREE] On my right,
the Fredericia Girls,
Connie, Tagajo.
On my left,
Kitakomachi High School,
Hanesaki, Izumi.
Hanesaki to serve.
Love-all. Play.
[TAGAJO] I know
she told me not to do anything,
but how can I let a perfect shot
like that get away?
[REFEREE]
One-love!
-It was just a lucky shot!
-Defend against those smashes!
Sorry. That was my fault.
[REFEREE]
Uh, service over. One-all.
Huh?
Hey, Connie,
what the hell are you doing?
There's no point to this match
unless I win it by myself.
If you're going
to get in the way,
you can play without my help.
[TAGAJO]
Huh?
[TAGAJO panting]
Ayano, stay focused.
I don't know
what this girl's deal is,
but we can't let it distract us.
You're right.
[WATARI]
Sorry I'm late.
Hopefully,
I didn't miss too much.
Coach Watari, good morning.
A good morning to you as well.
You won't have to worry
about me interfering.
Much appreciated, Coach.
[exerting]
[REFEREE]
Ten- two.
[TAGAJO panting]
[TAGAJO]
It's impossible.
I can't possibly win by myself!
I can. Wanna trade?
Huh?
[REFEREE]
Service over. Three-ten.
I'll handle it from here on out.
So don't get in my way again.
What do you think?
Could you have returned
a shot like that?
That's what I thought.
I didn't even see it.
-Great shot!
-[TACHIBANA] Yes! It's through!
[gasping]
So high!
[exclaiming]
[CONNIE]
How insulting!
You expected that
to get past me?
We're finally face to face.
Pull out all the stops.
What's with this Connie chick?
She acts like this is personal.
Wait.
That girl's Connie Christiansen.
[ELENA]
Huh?
[TACHIBANA]
She's a prodigy from Denmark.
We're talking about the winner
of multiple world titles
before the age of 16.
Hold up, you said Denmark?
So what's she doing here
in Japan?
[TACHIBANA]
Whatever the reason,
she's an internationally
ranked player.
It's not hard to see why.
The length of her limbs,
her physical prowess.
Hanesaki might have
great instincts,
but compared to this...
[REFEREE]
Eleven-ten. Interval!
[panting]
-We can still win, right, Ayano?
-Uh, yeah.
[REFEREE]
Forty more seconds.
[gasping]
Like I told you earlier,
your team is meaningless...
big sister.