[NAGISA] In a battle,
you either win or you lose.
[AYANO] There's only one
way to prove yourself,
and that's by defeating
your opponent.
[AYANO]
But...
[NAGISA] What you see on
the other side of that net...
[AYANO]
Is always...
[ELENA grunts]
[YU whimpers]
[grunting]
[NAGISA]
Come on!
She hit it...
using her right hand?
[KAORUKO gasps]
[MALE REFEREE A]
Nine, love.
How typical. It's anything
goes with her.
[NAGISA]
She noticed my placement
and switched the racket
between hands.
[MALE REFEREE A]
Serve.
[AYANO]
Why?
Yes!
[MALE REFEREE A]
Ten, love.
[AYANO]
What's the reason I'm fighting?
[NAGISA]
Was that intentional?
[SASA]
Another easy return!
Is she trying to lose?
[gasps]
[grunts]
More hesitation.
She's losing ground.
[AYANO] What am I still
playing badminton for?
[NAGISA grunts]
[CROWD cheering]
[MALE REFEREE A]
One, Ten.
She's got a point on the board!
Keep 'em coming, Aya!
Don't let it get to you!
You'll make the next one!
[NAGISA] Snap out of it.
You need to be more confident.
[MIYAKO]
Something's different.
Hanesaki's stance isn't
the same from before.
The zero position.
[MIYAKO gasps]
She used her right hand to
make that earlier play as well.
It wouldn't surprise me if she's
always been ambidextrous.
This whole time?
Why'd she keep it a secret?
I don't think she
intentionally concealed it.
Playing with both hands, you
lose time switching the racket.
Plus, you risk
directional imprecision.
But she decided to do it anyway.
She's giving it all she's got.
[NAGISA] I can visualize it.
The next point is mine!
[YU]
She's being aggressive!
Did you see that? Guess that
means she's in the zone again!
It does, meanwhile you can
tell Aragaki's losing steam.
[TACHIBANA]
The momentum's reversed.
[SASA]
That looks like...
[KAORUKO] She's stealing her
opponent's ability to think
with swift rallies. Sheer power
isn't enough at this point.
Nagisa doesn't have the
strength left to regain control!
[NAGISA pants]
[NAGISA]
I need to regain control!
[HAYAMA] It was a ten-point
difference minutes ago!
[AYANO pants]
[RIKO]
Nagisa!
I need to take a
quick sweat break.
[RIKO]
Here... Try and relax.
What've you been doing
so far has worked out.
[NAGISA grunts]
[MALE REFEREE A]
Please return to the court.
And remember who
you're doing this for.
[gasps]
[NAGISA] I've got to
focus on myself first.
It's another lift!
[SORA]
There we go.
Aya tied the score!
[MALE REFEREE A]
Seventeen, all.
One thing's certain.
Hanaysaki's figured
out her smashes.
What will you do now, Aragaki?
Bring it on!
[AYANO]
Hm.
[gasps]
They should be exhausted!
How can they keep playing?
[AYANO]
Now I see.
[SASA]
She made it! It's over the net!
[AYANO gasps]
[CROWD gasps]
[AYANO]
At this moment,
I know why I'm
playing badminton.
[AYANO]
It's for one reason.
To beat Nagisa!
[NAGISA] Ayano. You're an
incredible player.
[NAGISA] When people
use the word "gifted",
they're talking about
players like you.
[NAGISA]
The thing is...
[SORA]
She did it!
They're neck and neck!
I should call the match.
I'm pretty sure she
has patellar tendinitis.
It also goes by the
name Jumper's Knee.
Inflammation caused
from overuse.
If not properly treated, it can
kill a player's career.
Can we hold off Coach?
Just a little longer.
[TACHIBANA grunts]
[RIKO]
She needs this.
[NAGISA]
I don't want to lose!
How can she keep up that
speed after three games?
She's done more training runs
than anybody on the team.
[HAYAMA]
Hm!
[NAGISA]
Even if it's brutal...
--[NAGISA] Yeah!
--[NAGISA] Even if it's ugly...
[MALE REFEREE A]
Twenty match point, nineteen.
Just one more. C'mon, Nagisa.
[NAGISA] It doesn't matter.
As long as I beat you!
I don't know what
we're supposed to do!
Cheer for Nagisa or Aya?
Both of them!
[gasps]
[NAGISA]
Now I got you!
[RIKO]
Did she do it?
[CROWD gasps]
[NAGISA, AYANO pant]
[MALE REFEREE A]
Twenty, all.
It's deuce.
At this stage, scoring two
points in a row
is gonna be tough
for both of them.
[MALE REFEREE A]
Twenty-one, match point twenty.
A cut smash where she
least expected it.
Hm. Not bad at all.
Ayano only needs to
score one more point now.
[KAORUKO] Ha! Put her out
of her misery already!
That's some
impressive stamina.
Who?
I was talking about
both of them.
[AYANO] You want fun, Nagisa?
Then let's have some fun.
Try and return this!
[YU]
It's over!
[NAGISA gasps]
[AYANO]
Hit this!
[KURA gasps]
[gasps]
It's good!
[AYANO gasps]
[CROWD gasps]
[MALE REFEREE A]
Twenty-one, all.
She was a split second too
late approaching the net!
Ayano's past her limit!
They're both running on empty.
[AYANO pants] It's frustrating.
So frustrating.
I think I'm
actually having fun.
I told you so.
[CROWD cheers]
[RIKO sobs]
[YU] What a crazy match!
You were legendary!
There's no other word for it!
I'm sorry, for everything.
You didn't have to cheer
for me, yet you did.
[SORA, YU whimper]
No sweat. It's just good
to have the old Aya back.
[AYANO]
Mm?
[SORA, YU gasp]
Hey, wait here.
[YU]
Huh? You sure?
[UCHIKA]
You didn't do bad out there.
Actually, you were amaz--
[AYANO]
I hated you.
You left because
I had no talent,
because I wasn't a good enough.
I hated you.
Yesterday, I asked
you a question.
What're you playing
badminton for?
[AYANO] Right now, for me.
It's because I love it too.
[UCHIKA chuckles] You and I
could go overseas together.
Would you like to
come to Denmark?
It'd be you, me and Connie.
The three of us
could play badminton.
I'm staying here,
with my friends and team.
[AYANO]
If I'm taking the next step,
I want this to be
my starting line.
[ALL giggle]
I guess it's fair. This time
I'm the one being left behind.
[AYANO] Don't worry.
We'll play again sometime.
[UCHIKA chuckles]
[AYANO hums]
[ELENA]
Hey, Ayano.
[ELENA] What I said,
before the match.
It was wrong of me. I'm--
[AYANO]
Elena.
Before I go home,
I want to stop somewhere.
[RIKO]
You're sure your knee is okay?
[NAGISA] Yeah. I'm going
to the hospital tomorrow.
Not that I'm complaining,
but don't you have to
babysit your siblings?
[RIKO]
Today's Sunday.
So Mom and Dad are
home looking after them.
You deserve a break.
[RIKO] I can't get the
finals out of my head!
You were so impressive!
What's next? Think you could
be the national champion?
I really don't know. It might
turn out I'm not as talented
at badminton as I hoped.
But even if I'm not,
I'll probably keep
playing it forever.
[NAGISA]
Riko.
I wanted to say...
Thank you. I know,
if you weren't by my side,
I would not have
made it this far.
[NAGISA]
So thanks.
[RIKO chuckles]
If I'm being truthful with you,
I was feeling
kind of frustrated.
[NAGISA gasps]
I realized something.
The place you're at
as an athlete now can't be
reached with hard work alone.
Discovering that was a
little disappointing.
[AYANO]
Octo-octo!
[ELENA giggles]
[AYANO]
Elena... I'm sorry.
[ELENA]
Huh?
You mean about the match?
You worked really hard!
There's no reason to be upset!
[AYANO]
I didn't mean the finals.
I'm not sorry I lost.
[AYANO sobs]
[AYANO]
You were always there.
You never abandoned me.
You were the one who encouraged
me to play badminton again
and gave me a chance
to be a part of a team!
Thank you!
[ELENA sighs]
[YU]
Hey there!
Crazy. We actually beat
Nagisa to practice?
She went to the hospital
with Coach Tachibana.
[YU]
To get her knee looked at?
[RIKO]
Yeah.
[HAYAMA]
We have arrived!
[YU]
Oh, it's you.
[HAYAMA grunts] That's how
you greet an upperclassman?
You're supposed to look
up to those who are
older and wiser than you!
[YU] Speaking of wise,
shouldn't you be studying?
You don't want to be
in the bottom ten.
[HAYAMA grunts] Today was
my last day at this school.
[YU]
Hm?
[HAYAMA] I'm trying for
Meisei University.
[YU gasps] I remember hearing
they're supposed to have
a great badminton team.
Seemed like a good choice.
Since I'm going to
keep playing the sport.
Fat chance they're going
to accept you now,
given your grades and all.
[HAYAMA]
You're supposed to have my back!
Besides, I've still
got six months!
[TACHIBANA]
We're back!
[GAKU]
Hm?
[RIKO gasps]
Nagisa!
[TACHIBANA] Turned out to be
patellar tendinitis after all.
Whatever you said,
it sounds way bad.
It can be sometimes.
The X-rays came back
showing small tears in the
tendon beneath the kneecap.
So what does that mean?
[TACHIBANA]
It means don't worry.
The symptoms were only minor.
For the moment,
it's not a huge concern.
She'll be okay...? I'm so glad!
I kept telling you it wasn't
gonna be some big deal.
[RIKO]
I know, but still.
We're all relieved,
but for right now,
you need to rest as
much as possible.
So I want you to
skip any practices
that might work
your legs too h--
[AYANO]
Wanna play?
[ALL gasp]
[AYANO] What're you
waiting for? Let's go!
[gasps] Did you even hear a
single word the coach said?
She needs rest
before she's ready to--
But how does Nagisa feel?
[NAGISA]
Uh, I feel, um...
You're well enough to
play me, aren't you?
Not exactly.
No, I get it.
Obviously, you're too scared
to accept a rematch.
[ELENA]
Uh...
So much for the real Aya
being the shy, quiet type.
Rule number one in life,
people never change.
[AYANO] Yeah. There's no
point for us to play again
when everyone's knows
I would beat you.
You got yourself a match.
Huh?!
[NAGISA] And lucky for you,
since my knee's a total wreck,
we ought to be on the
same playing level now.
[TACHIBANA]
Woah! Woah! Woah! Slow down!
Let's see if you can
back up your trash talk.
[ELENA]
Is everyday gonna be like this?
You're so mean.
I just want to play Nagisa
as soon as possible!
[NAGISA]
Good morning!
About time you showed up!
I took the first available
bus to get here.
[AYANO] What you see on
the other side of that net...
[NAGISA]
Is always...
[NAGISA, AYANO]
...a reflection of yourself!