[AYANO]
A smash or a cut?
Feel better?
[AYANO]
I'm okay now.
Oh? That's good.
I'm not expecting you
to be bring me a gift,
but those chocolates
you brought back
from your last one were amazing.
[clock chiming]
[AYANO]
You know, I didn't really lose.
I mean, every other time
we played, I won.
I got so sick of it.
I decided not to
push myself as hard.
But I didn't expect her
to get worked up like that.
So, you see,
I didn't really lose.
You're coming back,
aren't you, Mom?
[gasping]
Don't go!
[AYANO]
Please don't leave me.
You've really become
quite a sneaky player,
haven't you, Nagisa?
Then again...
what I think is
you don't want me
to see that smash of yours.
[NAGISA]
Stay calm.
If she riles you,
you'll lose control of the game.
[badminton volleying]
[gasping] She's going
to force her way through?
-It curved.
-Almost like it ran away.
[giggles]
I want to know why
you walked out on Ayano
and left her behind.
You're her best friend.
Always by her side
all these years.
Thank you.
[UCHIKA]
The short version is
I wanted to develop
Ayano's talent.
Have it grow
as much as it could.
[AYANO whining]
Well, that's all for today.
Aw! But that's not fair!
Aw, one more!
[UCHIKA]
If you want longer games,
you'll need to become
a much better player
than you are now.
[AYANO]
But if I play you,
I will get better!
Mom, please! Just one more time!
[UCHIKA]
Guess she took my advice.
[YOUNG AYANO exerting]
[UCHIKA] At that moment,
I could plainly see.
She was only invested
in badminton for my sake.
That's why?
You left her because of that?
[REFEREE]
One, two.
What the heck is going on
over there?
It was all vroom,
then zwoo! How?
You've seen
a cut smash before.
Well, sure!
But when I try to pull them off,
they don't look
anything like hers did!
That's probably because
you play right-handed.
You make it sound
like a bad thing.
[NAGISA]
I need to turn things around.
[KURA]
Her doubt's showing.
Hanesaki's going
to pick up on that.
-[stretching]
-[grunting]
There it goes! The same curve!
[KAORUKO]
Look at this birdie.
The feathers
run counterclockwise.
Meaning, if a southpaw hits
with a cut smash,
it gives the shuttlecock
a wild spin.
Or as it's also known,
a crossfire.
[NAGISA]
I can't let this bother me.
Otherwise, I'll lose
even more initiative.
One more time.
Go on the attack!
She's pushing through!
[AYANO]
It's really stretched out.
-[shuttlecock landing]
-[gasping]
Like, whoa!
Did she just hit it
while jumping backwards?
[KAORUKO] By removing both feet
from the ground,
she was able
to soften the impact
as well as place herself
just far enough away
to make the perfect net shot.
Ayano, you beautiful monster.
That's not the sort of move
you can pull out of thin air.
It must have taken
Hanesaki years of practice
in order to master.
Mop, please.
There's sweat on the court.
[NAGISA]
From this point forward,
I won't be surprised
by anything you throw at me.
Then again, I was never
under the delusion
I could overwhelm you, anyway.
Bring it on!
[AYANO]
I know I'm better than Connie,
better than Nagisa.
But if I lose...
then this was all for nothing!
[UCHIKA]
I may be an awful parent.
Badminton always came first,
even before my duty as a mother.
Because I wanted
to open her eyes
and show her how far skill
can take you in life.
We're talking about a sport.
You make it sound like
some kind of philosophy.
[UCHIKA] There's only
a very small number of people
who can make a living
being a professional athlete.
Even if you achieve that,
one injury can end it
all in an instant.
Dedicating your life to a sport
hardly seems like
a worthwhile endeavor.
But it is.
Feeling your body move
the way you want it to.
Controlling the path
of the shuttlecock
like it's an extension
of yourself.
Giving your all
against a challenger.
I feel it's during
moments like those...
you find purpose.
[SASA]
They're at game point!
You can tell Ayano is
way more determined than usual.
She is. Definitely.
But her opponent's calm
is equally intriguing.
[RIKO]
Nagisa, do your best!
[NAGISA]
Go on the attack! Now!
Yeah! Nice!
[CROWD cheering]
[REFEREE]
Game! First set won by Hanesaki!
Twenty-one, sixteen!
She's outpacing me.
You've gotta be kidding!
That was amazing!
Real quick, how's your knee
feel after game one?
[NAGISA]
It's fine. Don't worry.
Hey, do you want a towel?
[YU] I'm the older one here,
and I'm terrified of her.
[exclaims]
Good work in the first set, Aya!
[AYANO]
Yeah, thanks.
You feel... okay?
[AYANO]
Sure. No complaints.
Other than the fact
Nagisa's been playing deviously.
Doesn't matter.
I won't lose.
I've played better.
She's nothing compared to Mom.
[UCHIKA]
I want to be clear.
I know what I've done
is unforgivable.
Regardless,
I don't have any regrets.
You have to understand.
She's on the verge
of taking the next step.
It's all thanks to you,
the members
from her badminton club,
everyone who stayed
by her side.
If you're ready,
let's head back.
We're probably missing
a great match out here.
[REFEREE]
Second game! Love, all! Play!
[AYANO] Just one more set to go.
Then I win the match.
[NAGISA]
Let's have some fun.
[AYANO]
She's still not smashing it!
Fine! Then I will! Enough!
[gasping]
She's holding on.
Nagisa won't lose
without a fight.
The match has become
real intense.
Yeah.
Hanesaki may be winning for now,
but she's been forced
to play badminton
in a way
she's not accustomed to.
[MIYAKO]
She's on the offense.
Meanwhile, you have Aragaki
putting up a strong defense.
It's like they switched styles
with each other.
What gives?
She didn't smash it?
Yeah!
[YU]
It's getting close.
Aya's losing her cool.
What's wrong with her?
Ayano doesn't understand
what terrifies her opponent.
See, the most frightening way
to face her is in a rally.
She uses an unusually
fast return speed,
stealing your ability
to think.
Let's say you adopt large clears
to counter her reflexes.
She'll answer by using shot
placement to rob you of stamina.
And typically, that works,
but Nagisa's strength
rivals male players'.
[REFEREE]
Fifteen, all.
[KAORUKO] She's been
freely offering up her stamina.
All to protect the one thing
she can't surrender!
And it's working!
She did it! The game's tied!
Go, Nagisa!
[AYANO panting]
There's no way I'll lose.
The idea of being defeated
by her, it's unthinkable!
I can't let that happen!
Because this time,
I'm going to win!
Then I'll abandon Mom!
-She returned it!
-There wasn't enough curve.
Ayano's swings
are becoming weaker!
[AYANO]
Time to retake the lead!
[CROWD cheering]
[REFEREE]
Sixteen, fifteen.
She's in the lead!
There's that jump smash
we've been waiting for.
And it couldn't have come
at a better time!
Not only for the score,
but psychologically too.
Nagisa traded stamina
to protect her key weapon,
her ability to think!
I said we'd have fun, right?
[AYANO]
Another short serve.
[TACHIBANA]
A split second too late.
[AYANO]
Make it big.
Hanesaki possesses
lightning-fast reflexes,
which allows her
to return birdies
while remaining
close to the net,
shots most can't make.
However...
if she keeps refusing
to move any closer,
it won't make a difference.
She's out of gas?
[NAGISA panting]
I know the exact expression
on Ayano's face.
I don't even need a clear view.
Whenever things get tough,
it means you've got
to take a step forward!
Was that a cheer?
[AYANO]
Shut up. I'm going to.
I don't need you telling me.
-No!
-Good.
Got it!
-Yes!
-What? That was in bounds!
[REFEREE]
It was out.
[HAYAMA]
Talk about a comeback!
She's made it to game point.
[GAKU] Refusing to use her smash
in the first set
is paying off now.
Come on!
[panting]
Yeah!
[REFEREE]
Game! Second set won by Aragaki!
Twenty-one, eighteen!
[CROWD cheering]
You totally won!
[NAGSIA] Easy! All I did was
manage to tie the match.
[RIKO]
Yeah, but it's still a big deal!
Right, you need a drink.
[TACHIBANA]
Aragaki.
Let me check.
How's this?
[NAGISA]
It's fine.
-[TACHIBANA] And this?
-[NAGISA] Fine.
[TACHIBANA]
And this?
What'd I just say?
[TACHIBANA]
Promise me one thing.
If you start feeling like
you can't go on at any point,
you don't have to say a word.
Just look over at me.
I'll make the call
and end the game.
Thanks for offering.
Thing is... I might look
your way accidentally
after scoring another point.
[laughs]
I'll be sure
to tell the difference.
Are you okay?
Do me favor. Quit pretending.
I know you're on Nagisa's side.
You all want me to lose.
Like I can't tell what
you're really thinking.
What? No.
Leave me alone. You're annoying.
[BOTH gasping]
[whimpering]
[REFEREE]
One minute!
Game number three!
Love, all! Let's play!
[NAGISA] It's the final stage.
Things are getting exciting.
[AYANO]
I'll be abandoned again.
Don't go!
[AYANO]
I need to be better than good.
Otherwise,
I'm useless to everyone.
I have to win.
If I don't,
nobody will ever need me.
[AYANO giggling] Well,
what do I need boys for?
I'm happy enough just being
in the same class as you.
-Sure took you long enough.
-I said I was sorry.
[ELENA] If you need one,
I'll be the team manager!
[exclaiming]
Not gonna lie,
I wish it had been full
of hot guys like tennis club,
but what can you do?
[whining] But Elena, why?
Go on!
You're looking so adorable, Aya!
Huh? Did you call me "Aya"?
[ELENA] Turned out
pretty well, didn't it?
It feels like
we're part of a team now.
Part of a team.
All right, time to win
and be a part of this team.
[AYANO]
She said she abandoned me
so I would become
a better player.
[giggling]
Isn't that funny?
I feel so dumb,
withdrawing like I did.
Now that I think about it,
I'm glad I didn't stop
playing badminton.
Because back then,
Mom was the one who deserted me.
But this time,
I'm going to abandon her.
-[ELENA] This is all my fault.
-Huh?
I'm the one who brought you
to the badminton club.
You have to understand,
she's on the verge
of taking the next step.
[REFEREE]
Eight, love.
If you would,
please exchange your racket.
I said please exchange your--
Hanesaki's through.
The match is done.
[SORA] Don't throw the game,
you hear me?
[grumbling]
I wanted to go.
Play in the finals same as you.
But you know what?
It didn't work out that way.
Guess what.
Like it or not, you're fighting
for us out there too!
One hundred percent.
Aya, I've been
holding this back,
but I wanted to say...
Just do your best!
I'll never let you get
off the hook if you lose!
Well, you heard them!
Get back in and fight!
Ayano! Don't give up!
[CROWD cheering]
Nice to have a team
cheering you on.
But here, out on
this badminton court,
there's only you and me.
Nobody else can enter it.
This is our world,
and nothing outside matters.
If you're ready, let's play.
[NAGISA]
Come on!
She hit it using her right hand?