[badminton volleying]
[AYANO]
Why am I even doing this?
Where are you going?
Don't leave, Mom.
What am I...
What am I playing badminton for?
[NAGISA]
Why am I even doing this?
What am I playing badminton for?
[CHO] Such healthy appetites!
Like mother, like daughter.
But then you're so active,
and going through
a growth spurt too.
I'm pretty sure my days
of growing are over with.
It doesn't matter
how old you get,
I'll always see you
as my child, Uchika.
[AYANO]
I'm done.
You sure?
But we're having cake
for dessert!
Oh, Uchika, is Ayano even
on speaking terms with you?
[UCHIKA]
Not exactly,
but she does have
a match coming up.
[sighs]
Dinner was wonderful!
[knocking on door]
[UCHIKA]
May I come in?
[UCHIKA] I remember when
you craved my acknowledgment
above anything else.
Always wanting to be by my side.
That's why you played badminton.
But you don't need me anymore.
You can play on your own.
Pretty well, I might add.
[UCHIKA] That's why I'm here,
the reason I came back.
Nagisa seems
pretty on edge.
Well, there are only three days
to go until the finals.
That's true, I guess.
Plus, it's gonna be
quite the re-match.
Speaking of, have you noticed
how Aya's been acting
spaced out recently?
Yeah. In fact I'd say
it's a pretty common occurrence.
Ugh!
What the heck's
she thinking about?
[door opening]
-[HAYAMA] 'Sup?
-Huh?
-[YU] It's Hayama!
-Hey, Yu.
And you brought Gaku!
Don't you need to be studying
for entrance exams?
[gulps] Why are you only looking
at me when you say that?
I should be hitting
the books too,
but thought I'd stop by
in case anyone needed help
or to practice.
Exactly. That's the same
reason we're here.
-Right?
-Huh?
Well, Gaku's smart enough
to be in the top ten,
so he doesn't need
to study that hard.
Where does Hayama
stand academically?
Oh, well...
[grumbles]
Just how low are we talking?
He's, um...
Well, I'm sure he's not
in the bottom ten, right?
What? How could you ask that?
So I guess you're ranked higher
than the bottom 20 students
in your year?
Uh...
We're off topic!
I'm here because of my love
for the game!
Hayama, how about
you and I play?
-[HAYAMA] Huh? Me?
-[giggles]
[BOTH exerting]
Hayama seems more
in the zone.
He's playing way better
than at the prelims.
You're right, but Aya's not
letting anything through.
Her defense is amazing.
Makes sense.
Uchika Shindo trained her,
and she's a ten-time
consecutive national champ.
[BOTH exerting]
[HAYAMA panting]
[SORA]
Twenty-one, five.
-[HAYAMA grumbles]
[AYANO] What's wrong?
You're not going to bail
on our second game.
-[NAGISA] You've done enough.
-Huh?
Leave him alone.
Aw, but he said he came here
to play badminton, didn't he?
[grumbling]
I know you want
to go against me, don't you?
[NAGISA]
And we will at finals, 'kay?
Funny! You sound
way too relaxed about it.
[upbeat music playing]
[YU giggling]
You always manage
to put your shirt
on backwards, Sora.
[giggling]
[RIKO]
Finals are tomorrow.
So both of you, go straight home
and get plenty of rest tonight.
Sure, but it's not like
I need a full night of sleep
to win against Nagisa.
[NAGISA]
See you.
[RIKO]
What the heck?
I told you to go and rest
for your match tomorrow!
[RIKO'S SIBLINGS clamoring]
Riko?
-[RIKO'S SIBLINGS clamoring]
-[laughing]
[RIKO] What did I say
about swarming people?
-Give her room to breathe.
-[laughing]
[RIKO'S BROTHER]
A grasshopper!
[RIKO'S SIBLINGS clamoring]
[RIKO'S SISTER]
What should we name it?
[RIKO'S BROTHER]
Let's take it home!
Well, tomorrow's the big day.
I'm rooting for you.
Good luck.
Yeah.
Listen, Riko...
I wanted...
Never mind. I'm off!
[RIKO'S SISTER] Big Sis,
Mako fell asleep on my back!
Huh?
Let's go back home.
[panting]
[AYANO]
Why am I even doing this?
-[badminton volleying]
-[YOUNG AYANO exerting]
[AYANO] What have I been
playing badminton for?
-[badminton volleying]
-[YOUNG AYANO exerting]
Once it lands, we go home.
[chuckling] You didn't like
that rule very much.
You'd always shout, "One more,"
and start crying.
Takes you back, doesn't it?
[AYANO] What have you been
playing badminton for?
Who me?
I play because...
Well, I love it
[AYANO]
Oh.
[clock ticking]
[NAGISA grumbling]
[REFEREE on video]
On my right, Ayano Hanesaki.
On my left, Kaoruko Serigaya.
Serigaya will serve.
Love, all. Play!
[CROWD cheering on video]
[alarm clock ringing]
[yawning]
It's a bigger crowd
than I expected.
People want to watch
the top players compete.
[YUKA]
Riko!
Hi, Yuka! Glad you made it!
Well, these two wouldn't
stop nagging me
to come cheer on Nagisa.
[sarcastically] Oh, yeah, we
were really twisting your arm!
Get real! The only thing we did
was mention to you the location
and what time
it was getting started!
Uh...
By the way, I heard
she's playing a first year.
A new student who goes
to the same school as us?
-[AYANO] That's me!
-[YUKA] Uh, hello.
I'm gonna beat Nagisa
for the second time.
My name's Ayano.
[YUKA] You sound confident
for a first year.
Hey, where is Nagisa?
-Uh...
[MIYAKO]
I really messed up!
I should've gotten
iced coffee instead.
It's nearly August after all.
Did you ever imagine
the two of them
would be paired up
in the finals?
[TACHIBANA] No. Honestly,
I didn't expect Aragaki
to grow as a player
in such a short amount of time.
Because of you.
Asking you to coach was one
of the best decisions I've made.
I can't take credit.
She did the work...
both on and off the court.
It's only been three months,
but she's become a much
stronger athlete than before.
You mean the way
her playing has improved?
Her technique's definitely
come a long way,
but most of all,
I mean her mental state.
From watching her,
I can tell she's got
what it takes to be a champion.
[MIYAKO]
What about Ayano?
I had a feeling
she'd make it to this point.
And she's certainly
throwing herself
into the game with abandon.
I guess, she really does have
some kind of natural talent
for badminton.
Tachibana, you've always
focused on working hard,
but there's a player
you've ignored
because you thought she didn't
need anything from you.
The way you coached Nagisa,
you put in the time figuring out
what she needed to get better.
But what about Ayano?
She deserves the same treatment.
No one's born knowing
how to play badminton
or good the moment
they pick up a racket.
You shouldn't draw
such a hard line
between effort and talent.
What I'm saying is...
Ayano, well... she's put in
the effort that she needed to,
day after day,
in order to become
the kind of athlete she is now.
In that way,
she's just like Nagisa.
[YU] I'm free.
You want to play, Aya?
No.
[RIKO]
Should we move on to smashes?
No, I'm done for now.
Don't wanna give her too much
to work with.
Both of you, do your best
out there, okay?
Sure.
[YU]
You work hard, too, Aya!
[AYANO]
I don't need any encouragement.
[YU] Um, I didn't mean
to insult you.
It's not like cheering
or wishing someone luck
makes them play better.
Wait. If you think it might
help Nagisa somehow,
then that's
a different story! Go ahead!
In fact,
it'd probably be better
if you all encouraged her
for my sake!
At least, then she might give me
a decent run for my money.
Can we have a word alone?
Huh?
[ELENA] Why did you talk
to them like that?
You realize they
were offering support?
Why can't you be gracious
and accept it?
[AYANO]
Because it's stupid and fake.
Acting like we're
all best buddies.
[ELENA] Are you having fun
playing badminton this way?
I don't get you.
What're you fighting for, Ayano?
Mom's here, finally.
She came back home.
She said she abandoned me
so I would become
a better player.
[laughing]
Isn't that funny?
I feel dumb withdrawing
like I did.
Now that I think about it,
I'm glad I didn't stop
playing badminton.
Because back then,
Mom was the one who deserted me,
but this time,
I'm going to abandon her.
-[ELENA] This is all my fault.
-Huh?
[ELENA] I'm the one
who brought you
to the badminton club.
[ELENA gasping]
[RIKO]
It's time. You ready?
[NAGISA]
I'm going to win.
This year,
I'm going to defeat myself.
[RIKO] Nagisa, you're no longer
the person you were back then.
[exhales deeply]
[NAGISA] You were wearing
the same expression a year ago.
[AYANO]
I have a question.
Why do you play badminton?
[NAGISA]
Because--
Let me guess.
You love it, right?
[AYANO]
You people, I swear.
[ANNOUNCER]
The Kanagawa Prefecture
Girls' Singles Finals
will now commence.
From Kitakomachi High School,
Hanesaki, first year.
Also from Kitakomachi
High School,
Aragaki, third year.
Ayano... let's go have some fun.
Hey, be careful out there.
[REFEREE]
Players to the court.
-Hey, something wrong?
-Nope.
[REFEREE] On my right,
from Kitakomachi High School,
Ayano Hanesaki.
Also from Kitakomachi,
on my left side, Nagisa Aragaki.
Hanesaki to serve.
[NAGISA]
When I played you last year,
it wasn't just that you were
a stronger player than me.
I had a flaw I was blind to,
a weakness in spirit!
[REFEREE]
Love, all. Play!
[NAGISA] First up, she'll make
me pick up some low shots,
reading the trajectory
of my racket.
Ayano's playing
really cautiously
for someone with such a giant
superiority complex.
[KAORUKO]
She'll start with lobs,
sending her opponent back.
That'll cause the rally's
initiative to balance out.
[NAGISA]
It's okay. I'm staying calm.
I see it, the entire court.
I feel it!
[BOTH exerting]
[REFEREE]
One, love.
Pretty quiet start
to the match, huh?
Scoring the first point
is significant.
It gives you a mental edge.
Her uncertainty's growing.
She's the kind of player
who plans out her match
while observing her opponent.
Based on their history,
she was probably hoping
for a game facing
an aggressive Nagisa.
But her opponent realized that
and went against type.
[NAGISA] That first rally
ought to introduce the idea
of diagonal shots
into her head.
I want to get as far as I can
without using smashes.
Once I do, her eyes will adjust
instantly to them,
and the game is
basically over. Meaning...
A smash?
-No.
-A cut?
[NAGISA]
I'll rely on cuts and drops
to constantly
put her off-balance!
More than likely, she wants
to keep Ayano confined
to the rearcourt.
[AYANO grunting]
[NAGISA]
She's on guard.
Waiting for a smash
at point-blank range.
Ayano's more
in control of things,
if she continues
driving her opponent back
while pressing forward.
However, the more they maintain
a back-and-forth
from the midcourt,
the more Nagisa is in control.
From Ayano's viewpoint,
the question is when to force
her opponent away.
[KAORUKO]
A simple arrangement would be
a series of repeated shots
to the rearcourt
in order to focus the other
player's attention there.
Then use a cut disguised
as a smash,
catching her off guard
and scoring the point.
That would be ideal.
She'd get
a perfectly good ace that way.
And by making her opponent
lift up low shots,
Ayano would have
control of the game.
[NAGISA]
But you can't afford
to stick with
simple arrangement, can you?
Because you never know
when I'll throw in a smash.
So your mind has started
making the game complicated,
filling up with more scenarios
than you actually
need to think about!
[AYANO] A smash!
She threw me off.
[NAGISA] And what's producing
all those options
is your uncertainty!
[AYANO]
A smash? Or a cut?
-All right!
-[CROWD cheering]
[REFEREE]
Two, love.
-That was totally unexpected.
-[GAKU] Yeah.
[gasping]
[breathing heavily]
Huh?
[thudding]
It's been a while, hasn't it?
-[UCHIKA] Uh, you are?
-Elena Fujisawa.
I've been friends with Ayano
since kindergarten.
[gasps] Elena!
Of course I remember you!
[ELENA] Um, this may seem weird,
me coming to you now.
I wanted to have a conversation
with you about Ayano.
[NAGISA]
So far, so good.
But those points had
the element of surprise.
The real trouble's coming.
You've really become
quite a sneaky player,
haven't you, Nagisa?
Then again...
what I think is
you don't want me to see
that smash of yours.