[ELENA]
Ayano, you're coming with me!
[AYANO]
Where are we going?
Are you...
Stop complaining
and just come on!
[ELENA and AYANO struggling]
Hey there!
[ELENA]
You're doing this!
The girl from yesterday?
But why? Elena!
Because I really think
you should be playing badminton.
[TACHIBANA] You have
all the natural elements
that practice can't give you.
It's almost like you were born
to play badminton!
Please stop.
I'm not going to change my mind.
[AYANO]
I've had enough.
[NAGISA] What does that mean?
We're in the middle of a match!
[AYANO] That's why Mom walked
out of my life.
Because I lost to Kaoruko.
I thought if I was good enough,
she would come home.
I wanted her back,
so I kept winning!
Uchika Shindo.
You know Ayano's mother?
[CHO] She pursued badminton
like a woman possessed,
as if the world had
nothing else to offer her.
[CONNIE] So, what about you?
Why'd you join your club?
At first, I didn't want to,
but I've started
feeling different lately.
I like being part of a team.
[CONNIE]
Was there a point
to your little
friendship routine?
Pretty cute. Do you usually get
everything you want that way?
Where are you going?
Don't leave, Mom.
[badminton volleying]
[grunting]
Her smash, it's insane.
How could anyone return it?
Well, that's part
of the problem.
[TACHIBANA]
Ever since the interval,
her response to each shot
has gotten slower.
What's going on
with you, Hanesaki?
[breathing heavily]
You don't look so hot.
Are you okay?
[AYANO]
Big Sister?
[REFEREE]
Game!
First game won
by Fredericia Girls.
Twenty-one, twelve.
They won?
But we have two players
against one!
[breathing heavily]
[CONNIE]
Is this all you've got?
Yeah, I thought so.
There's no way
you're really Uchika's daughter.
How does she know about Mom?
Who is this girl?
Ayano, it's the interval.
You can rest.
And voila!
My masterpiece is done!
Was there a point to your little
friendship routine?
Turned out pretty well,
didn't it?
It feels like
we're part of a team now.
-Big Sister.
-You can win this! Okay, Ayano?
There's no way
you're really Uchika's daughter.
[TACHIBANA]
Let's see it.
Good motion. Just add
a little more follow-through.
Then you've got it.
I don't understand
anything anymore.
Remember.
You're not in this alone.
I might not be
the best player here,
but I'm your partner.
During low points,
I'll always be
right by your side,
sharing the burden.
[giggles]
All right, team, change of plan.
Starting next game,
you'll stop defending together.
What a showboat!
Bet she's also gonna play
the next game by herself.
What is going through
that girl's head?
[SHIRAISHI] Poor Hina. I hope
she's not too discouraged.
[sighing]
[footsteps approaching]
Oh!
What the--
Whoever that is, cut it out!
Do me a favor.
Support Connie, all right?
By doing what?
That psycho Dane is obliterating
the other team single-handedly.
[SHIWAHIME]
She is. For now.
[YU]
Hey, look.
Is Riko going to be playing
closer to the net this game?
[HAYAMA] I've never seen
a formation like that before.
Huh?
[CONNIE scoffs]
If that's the way
you want to do this,
I'll play along.
You're still going down, though!
[RIKO] They're all
being returned to Ayano.
Okay, coach,
I'll let her handle it.
[TACHIBANA] That's right, Izumi.
It's for the best.
[RIKO] You want us
to stop defending together?
Won't that leave us open?
Connie favors a hard smash
from a high vantage point.
It's her most dangerous shot
and near impossible to return.
In order to deal with it,
I'm going to be assigning
both of you different sections
of the court.
Izumi will stick to the net
and return birdies
that come in high.
Hanesaki's defense is strong,
so she should cover everything
mid-court and beyond.
Leave shots in the forecourt
to Izumi
and focus on only one thing,
returning smashes
Connie sends over.
[RIKO]
I follow,
but won't that put
more pressure on Ayano?
It won't be easy. You game?
Good.
Each of you,
believe in your partner
and cover
your assigned territory!
-Got it!
-Mmm.
That's it!
Dumb luck is all!
Damn you! Miss already!
[CONNIE gasping]
[gasping]
[ALL gasping]
[YU]
She did it. They scored.
That was intense!
Nice drop shot!
[CROWD chatting excitedly]
Even better than expected.
That's classic Ayano.
Since she was kid,
she's been finding different
ways to return the birdy.
It was her favorite game
to play growing up.
[badminton volleying]
[UCHIKA]
Come on! Over here!
Try hitting this one!
Too far!
[YOUNG AYANO grunting]
Looks like I'm the winner!
[UCHIKA]
Honey, did you hurt yourself?
[YOUNG AYANO]
Nope. I'm fine!
Love what you do,
and you'll end up great at it.
At least, that's what they say.
Not to mention,
her teacher was Uchika Shindo.
That certainly helps out.
Now's your chance, you two!
Push the attack!
[exerting]
[RIKO]
Here it comes.
Ayano's been defending us
the entire game!
I need to land one too!
[grunting]
[REFEREE]
Two, three.
Yes!
Let's keep this momentum going,
right, Ayano?
[exerting]
Who is this Hanesaki girl?
I can't believe
she's only a first year.
Every shot Connie hits
over the net,
she manages to send back.
Must be hard on her.
Connie insisted
on playing alone, remember?
There's no point
feeling sorry for her.
[USHI]
No, I guess not.
[PLAYERS exerting]
[REFEREE]
Eleven, seven! Interval!
[AYANO]
Um, Riko?
It looks like
we found our rhythm.
Let's keep this up.
[AYANO]
Okay!
Still think it's a good idea
to go it alone?
[CONNIE] I said I was doing this
on my own terms.
No one's interfering.
[SHIWAHIME]
For someone calling the shots,
you seem to be struggling.
Connie, let's play like a team.
[grumbling in frustration]
Offense!
[AYANO]
They're cheering for me.
Get that point!
-[AYANO] I can't let them down.
-[REFEREE] Play.
[AYANO] I've got to win
and become part of a team!
[CONNIE]
Don't get cocky
just because you have
a slight lead right now!
Is it just me,
or are her shots faster
than before?
She's starting to get serious.
[CONNIE]
I don't need a team.
[CHILDREN laughing]
[CONNIE]
I'll win all by myself!
[REFEREE]
Fourteen all!
She caught up to them!
All right, girls, don't panic.
Keep your cool.
It'll be fine.
We'll get back in there.
[AYANO]
Yeah.
[CONNIE]
If I can't win this game...
[breathing heavily]
[AYANO]
I have to be part of the team.
I need to win.
[AYANO]
I can't lose.
The score is 20, match point 19!
You can do it!
[AYANO]
I'm going to lose.
Just one more point.
If I miss this, it's over!
We're gonna win this together,
all right, Ayano?
[exerting]
[REFEREE]
Game one, 21-12.
Game two, 21-19.
Match won
by the Fredericia Girls,
Christiansen and Tagajo.
[TAGAJO]
You bet we did!
[TAGAJO] Gotta cramp, huh?
You need a stretch?
[CONNIE grunting painfully]
[TAGAJO]
I can't win.
[HAYAMA] What a bummer!
You almost had them too!
[YU]
You were so close, Aya!
[AYANO]
No. I didn't really lose.
[AYANO] I would've beaten her
if my string hadn't broken.
[RIKO]
Ayano?
[AYANO] I mean, they were trying
to confuse us the whole time.
That one girl playing us
the entire game.
Then the other jumping in
at the last minute.
It was totally unexpected!
It wasn't fair,
so I didn't really lose!
Don't make excuses. They won.
[AYANO crying]
[TACHIBANA]
Hanesaki! Where is she--
[YU]
Aya! Wait!
[TACHIBANA]
Hanesaki, where are you?
I wonder
if they've had more luck.
I'll check.
Same here. We haven't found
any sign of her yet.
[YU]
How you doing, Aya?
Why don't we head back
to the gym?
Everyone's looking for you.
[SORA]
I need to say this.
I hated you, Ayano.
Huh? Why would you say that?
[SORA] You had talent,
so people counted on you,
but you acted
like you couldn't care less.
And when you stopped showing up,
the club went looking for you.
[SORA]
But in that last match,
I couldn't help but think
how cool you were.
From now on, no excuses
for being awesome, okay?
We should head back. You coming?
[CONNIE]
What's that? A pity gift?
Uh-huh, but I was kinda worried.
[CONNIE]
I just want to be left alone.
Didn't you hear what I said?
[crying]
[CONNIE]
That girl today,
the way I treated her,
I think I went too far.
Who do you mean?
[CONNIE]
Hina. [gasping]
And you wanna make it up to me?
I know just the thing!
Help! Somebody call the embassy!
[TAGAJO]
Commence cleaning!
[CONNIE] Gimme my clothes back!
I want out!
I prefer to take my baths alone!
But you said you'd do anything
to make it up to me.
Pretty sure you made that up
in your head!
Let's not sweat
over the details, okay?
Besides, it's time
for your massage!
Should I start here?
[exclaims]
Oh!
There, there. It's only a bath.
You're being such a baby.
I am not! [crying]
[TAGAJO] No fair, captain!
I wanna wash her hair!
[CONNIE]
Hurry up and get this over with!
[SHIWAHIME]
I would if you'd hold still.
You know,
Connie always struck me
as the unapproachable
prodigy type.
Ditto, but she's kinda cute
or whatever.
[SHIWAHIME]
Almost done.
[grumbling]
[CONNIE exclaiming]
[GIRLS giggling]
[YU]
Read 'em and weep, babes!
[GIRLS grumbling]
[laughs] The queen of cards
gets the pot at last!
I think I won.
[YU] Aya! Why?
You're a regular card shark.
[YU]
Betrayed by everyone!
[exclaims] Life is over!
Huh? [chuckling]
Look, Elena,
you want to team up with me?
-Huh?
-Good.
She says she can't wait to play!
Do you have your phone
in camera mode right now?
Let's take a group photo!
Yu! Wait till
I take off my mask!
Okay, say cheese!
-[exclaiming]
-[camera clicking]
-[GIRLS chatting]
-[exclaiming]
[TAGAJO]
What gives?
The minute we take our eyes
off you, you go missing!
[CONNIE]
I can't brush my teeth in peace?
If you'd told us,
we'd have gone with you!
Which is exactly
why I didn't say anything.
[TAGAJO] Brushing as a team
would've inspired you.
[door closing]
Bye, Nagisa.
Kitakomachi has a unique team.
Make it to the Inter-High,
so we can compete
with each other again.
Thanks for saying so,
but that was always the plan.
[SHIWAHIME]
See ya.
Before we go, I need to ask you.
How do you know my mom?
You must be confused.
Uchika's my mother.
[AYANO]
What do you mean?
She saved me.
Before Mama entered my life,
I was alone.
[AYANO] "Mama"?
Why're you calling her that?
[CONNIE] Because
she taught me how to live.
[AYANO]
You're not making sense!
Is that...
I looked pretty cute
with short hair, didn't I?
You're the girl.
Mama's coming to Japan soon.
Surprised?
[CONNIE]
She's my family,
the most important person
in my life.
I bet it's the same for you.
It doesn't matter
if you belong to a team.
If she doesn't acknowledge you,
there's no point
in playing badminton, is there?
[UCHIKA] Okay, that's
enough practice for today!
Please! One more!
And if I miss,
then I promise we'll stop!
No, Ayano,
you said that last time.
Practice is over with for today.
We'll try tomorrow.
That's no fair!
We gotta keep going!
Say it didn't count, please!
If you get good enough one day,
I'll play with you
any time you want.
[YOUNG AYANO]
Don't leave! Wait for me!
I'm going to beat you one-on-one
and prove to Mama
I'm worthy of her love.
We'll meet again soon.
Hey, so, um, did you get to talk
to that Connie girl
about your mom?
[AYANO]
What does it matter?
I don't need a mom.