-Meet Ranma Saotome
of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
And here's Akane of the
Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
-The two have been
engaged to marry
by they're loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
-As for the cause of
poor Ranma's suffering--
-What did you do that for?
-When Ranma is splashed with
cold water, he becomes a she.
-Goodbye Girl-type.
-My very own horn of plenty.
[laughing]
-Give me that [inaudible].
-The more things change, the
more they stay the same, right?
-Right.
-Huh?
-Ow.
I'm going to get that old goat
if it's the last thing I--
-Must you keep interrupting?
-Interrupt?
You think I enjoy when
he beats up on me?
How else am I going to be
a whole man again, huh?
-What's this?
Be a whole man again you say?
-But son, what actual proof do
you have that there's really
a spring of drowned man
right here in Japan?
-He won't know unless he can get
that urn from master Happosai.
Right, Ranma?
-But Kasumi, this isn't
exactly the first time
he's claimed to
have found a cure.
-Let's not forget that
instant Nanniichuan.
-This time it's for real.
I just know it
is, I can feel it.
-But maybe you
should reconsider.
I mean, think how
much more interesting
your honeymoon
would be this way,
at least you'll never be bored.
Right, Akane?
-Huh?
What did you say?
-You don't know what
it's like to be a guy.
-The boy's right.
No woman could
ever understand how
we've suffered for
the sake of our art.
-Here, have some desert.
-Thank you Kasumi.
If the master would
only be so reasonable,
then we could get those
urns, find the spring and--
-Good luck.
You how selfish the master is.
He has no respect for
other people's property.
I'd give up if I were you.
-Boy, I don't care what it
takes, you that urn, hear me?
-You bet.
-Never let me take what's yours.
-I won't.
I'll make you proud pop.
That pot's as good as mine.
-Atta boy.
-If only was that easy.
-Huh, he's practically
giving it to me.
Got it.
-Ranma, you can do it.
Do it if it kills you boy.
-That's easy for you to say.
Get me down.
-To your feet boy.
Get up I said.
What are you, a man or woman?
-I'm a guy!
You hand that pot over.
-He's never been subtle has he?
-Oh my.
I guess I'll have to call
the repair man tomorrow.
-There's got to be a
better way to do this.
Huh?
What the heck are these?
-Well, want to talk to me about?
-I uh, hey, Ryoga,
how's it going man?
We're pals, ain't we?
Pals do stuff for each
other without having to ask
questions, ain't that right?
-I, uh--
-Don't say it, you don't
got to say nothing.
I know just how you
feel, without you
saying a word at all.
We're enemies and all, but
we can still be friends.
Like now.
Yes.
You understand Ryoga,
it's all for the sake
of the spring, alright.
Now go.
-Hey, ho, who's the runt?
That piece of merchandise
on your head belongs to me.
Give it right back!
-All right.
-No fair, you cheated coward.
Let me down.
You put me down this instant
or I'll come down there and--
-So that's the red urn?
-Atta boy.
-Well what do you know.
-Ha, ha, there
was nothing to it.
-Ranma, no fair.
-Hey look, It's Ryoga, hi.
-How dare you force those on me.
-Force?
These?
Huh?
-Nothing, Akane, certainly
not girls underwear.
Ranma!
-Come on man, it's like I said
before, all for the spring.
Right peach hen?
-Don't call me that!
-Sorry man, I got
no time for that.
See ya.
-You come back here!
-Wait for me!
-That's the spirit Akane.
It's times like these
that fiance's need
each other the most.
-Yeah, go for it.
-If only our dear
mother could you now.
-I'm not.
Oh forget it.
-OK, now I'm really mad.
What are you waiting for?
Cut me down!
-Now only one to go.
-I want to know where
the heck on Earth
is that last crummy pot.
-Patience son-in-law, these
old urns are tough to read.
Let's see, if this stands for
that then that would mean this.
-Ranma, giving me
that underwear,
that was a dirty
trick, even for you.
-You still thinking about that?
-I've got It.
This should lead you to the
third time and final urn.
-All right.
-Bring me that third
pot and I'll bet you
we figure out where that spring
of drowned man is located.
-OK.
Hey, no fair, come
back here Ryoga.
-Wait up you guys.
-It says start by going
three thousand steps north
by northeast.
-Ryoga, wait up, you little--
-Which way is north
by northeast anyway?
-It's this way.
-Give me back my map!
-Hey, haven't we been
through this once before?
You leave the
path-finding to me.
Next, 790 steps east.
-Whatever happened to
us being pals Ranma?
-OK, run up the
slope heading north,
and then, it should be the
next building, dead ahead.
There.
What the?
-What are you doing here?
I thought you were
finding the urn?
-What's going on?
-Admit it, you did it
on purpose, didn't you?
-Oh, Ranma, calm down.
-I'm going to get
you, you old ghoul!
-Calm down I said.
-Ronma!
-Ronma, is you OK?
-Cyan urn.
The Magenta urn.
The yellow urn too.
What do you know it
was here all along.
-That one [inaudible]
when building
cat cafe, right
great-grandmother?
-That's right.
I thought I might use
it for making pickles.
-Yeah, OK, whatever
granny, just read the code
and tell me how to turn
back into a guy already.
Now what?
What's wrong now?
Does it say where
the Nanniichuan is?
-Ah, it's written right here.
When you see the
first evening star
sibling stones will not be far.
What you seek flows
from the jars.
-Uh, when you see the
first evening star.
What was that again?
The stupid stones
will not be far.
What you seek floats
from the jars.
-Sibiling?
What's that?
-Who knows.
Maybe they're
brothers or something?
-Ah!
I think I know where they!
-What!
You sure Akane?
-Uh hmm.
-Whoa, get a load of
the gorgeous scenery.
-Yep.
And those rocks you were telling
us about are right over there.
-Is you sure?
-Well, yeah, it's the
name that tipped me off.
They're called the three
boulder brothers or something.
I came here on a
field trip once.
-Three boulder brothers, huh?
Hey what do you say we
go and introduce them
to our three pots?
-Yeah!
-I never thought
I'd see the day.
You really are friends.
I used to think that you
two hated each others guts
but why else he go to all
this trouble just to help you?
-Well, he can't fool you but
Ryoga is not really-- whoa!
-Come on let's go.
What are we waiting for?
We're not getting any younger.
Come on, hurry up.
Come on.
-That was a dirty
trick, even for him.
Come back here you cheater!
-Hey Ranma, you
little punk, what
am I supposed to store
my collection in?
-There's nothing like
good, clean mountain air
is there, Saotome?
-That's right, Tendo.
-Ranma, you find them rocks boy.
The future of the Saotome
school of anything
goes martial arts depends on it.
I'll take care of the old
geezer just you watch.
-Go on Genma.
What's that about
the old geezer?
-Huh?
What?
Ha, ha, the geese must
love this weather.
-An actor are we?
Don't give up your day job.
You fool.
The day you pull one over
on me is the day I retire.
-Got it.
Until we find that spring
no more dirty tricks.
It's for our own
good, all right?
-Well just remember that
I'll be watching you too.
-Unlike you Ranma,
I keep my promises.
Don't think I've forgotten about
those panties you put my head.
-Are you still
thinking about that?
-You be quiet.
-Why you come here Akane?
You no hate Ranma no more?
-Because I'm the only one who
knows where the stones are.
I could ask you
the same question.
-Ranma is finance.
Shampoo want real
man on her honeymoon.
-I am so sorry I asked.
-What a beautiful
day for a hike.
Don't you girls think so?
-Uh oh, it's getting cloudy.
We better hurry.
-Look out!
-That's my son-in-law.
I'll be you don't want
to be a man again, eh?
-Close one.
-Ranma you really
worry for shampoo?
-For the pot, yeah.
-Goodbye!
I know where I'm not wanted.
Forget it!
-Ah true.
Akane is green-eyed monster.
-Huh?
-Wrong!
I am not jealous.
You two can stay here the
rest of your for all I care.
-Hey dope, if it weren't
for the pot I'd be--
-Ranma, is that you really feel?
Maybe broken pot not worth.
-Ah, don't do that, ah.
Oh?
-Somebody did that on purpose.
It's the old freak.
-Hello son.
-Yoo hoo, Ranma.
-Huh?
-Hey pop.
-I've got you,
you little creeps.
If you want to get
through this pass then
give me back my property.
-Oh yeah?
-But, but master
what about a loan?
-Oh please, I just
want to be normal.
Is that so wrong?
-I'm not stupid!
No, he stole something
that belongs to me
and now he's going to pay.
Give me back my property.
-No you can't have it.
Later, maybe.
-You can't take it
without a fight.
-Shampoo ready fight you too.
-So am Time! .
(THUNDER)
-Looks like we'll be
here a while boys,
why don't you take a load off.
-Come on, you want
a piece of me?
-You better be careful.
He don't look like too much,
but he's about as sneaky
as they come.
-So let's beat him up
before he tries anything.
-Get him!
-School Anything Goes Martial
Arts final attack bean
jam blowout.
-Ow, that's got to hurt.
-Hmm, the one he developed
to eat seasonal bean jam
buns by himself.
Only the master would invent
a technique like that.
By using his key to knock
his opponents off their feet
he can enjoy the entire
feast by himself.
-How's about it, hmm?
Are you bums ready to surrender?
Or do you want me
to really get mad?
-Think again freak.
We haven't come this far
only to turn back now.
Are you with me Ryoga?
-Yeah!
Wait I'm not sure you
kids are up to this.
I'll have to take
him on myself .
-Great grandmother?
-Who wants to live
forever anyway?
Besides that old crony
hasn't beaten me yet.
-Whoa, check it out.
-Their battle orders
are going head to head.
-Mmm huh.
It's the beast that came from
China versus the greatest
evil in all of Japan.
Which one of them has
the strongest will?
-Oh, how sweet.
-It's not just me you
want to see in a bra.
It could be anyone.
-Oh, no!
Master!
Look how deep the
ravine is, Saotome.
How can he survive?
-What a terrible tragedy, Tendo.
-Yes!
You did it boy.
You're your father's
son all right.
-I'm proud to have
you as my son-in-law.
-Tendo at long last,
we can look forward
to growing old in peace.
-They ought to be
ashamed of themselves.
-Master, please forgive us.
-You traitors can
stay there all night.
You too Ranma.
Don't think you're
off the hook yet.
-Come on you slow pokes.
-Just a little more and
I'll change back for good.
Normal, I can, I
can be normal again.
-See, we made it.
-Where are the stones?
-I don't know.
There, there they are.
-The three boulder brothers.
-I'm so happy for you Ranma.
-Ranma!
Come on, I help you
with [inaudible].
-Oh, sure, OK.
-Thanks Akane, you
can go home now.
-You have got to be kidding.
-OK granny, now what?
-Don't ask me, you
remember as well as I do.
When you see the first
evening star, what you seek
is in the jar, and
all that nonsense.
Maybe it's still too early
for the first evening star.
-Come on baby.
Twinkle.
Once you come up the
spring will appear
and then I can say goodbye
to me girl side for good.
-Goodbye P-Chan.
Goodbye humiliation.
-Ryoga looks like
he's going to cry.
He must really can
about Ranma after all.
Look.
-Oh, the first star.
(GASP)
-At last, it's the spring.
-Wait, let's let
it fill up first.
-OK.
-Is it ready yet?
-Almost, room from one I'd say.
Ah, over there!
-Huh?
-Ranma.
-Alright!
I'm 100% guy again!
Or, maybe not.
-You broke it!
-I did not.
What's this?
Looks like some kind of sign.
To our valued
customers, thank you
for visiting
Japan's Nanniichuan.
Unfortunately, this local
spring of drowned man franchise
is no longer in service.
However, we look
forward to serving you
at the original Nanniichuan
in mainland China.
Thank you.
The manager.
-Well, that's that.
Come on girls, let's go.
-Ta Da!
Look, I made cookie
all by myself.
You'll try one, won't you Ranma?
What do you mean Kodachi, the
black rose has made some too?
Next time on Ranma
one and a half,
it's a fine line between
pleasure and pain.
See ya there.