[theme music]
-Meet Ranma Saotome
of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
And here's Akane, of
the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
-The two have been engaged to
marry by their loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this!
-Who asked you?
-As for the cause of
poor Ranma's suffering--
[water splashes]
-What did you do that for?
-When Ranma is splashed with
cold water, he becomes a she.
-The Abduction of P-chan.
[music playing]
-Come here and take a break.
-Sure.
Huh?
You think I should
join the skate club?
-Come on Akane, it will be fun!
-And I bet you'll
really be good at it!
-Hmm.
Oh!
I knew I forgot something.
I left P-chan in the rink!
-Who's P-chan?
-It's her little pet pig.
-[pig squealing]
-[sighs] Oh, Charlotte.
Come on Charlotte!
Be good and come
home with Azusa.
-[pig squealing]
-You're so cute!
-P-chan!
P-chan!
Where could he have gone?
[cars honking]
-So what's the deal?
Are you going to
introduce us or what?
-We'd give you our word.
-Ugh, we'll be so
polite, we promise.
We'd never do anything
to hurt that other Ranma.
We'll treat her like she's
our sister, just like a sister
I tell ya.
-Come on!
Cut it out already.
I told you I don't want nothing
to do with that crazy girl.
-Hey, get back here!
-After what you've
done to Akane,
how dare you treat us like this?
-What!
-After I--
-Don't play dumb.
You're engaged to her right?
-Yeah, what do you need
two girls for anyway?
-No fair keeping
her to yourself.
Give her to me!
--What!
Shut up.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
You guys shoud
have learned by now
to stay out of other
people's business, anyway.
And besides she's so uncute!
-Ranma!
-Ahh!
What do you want?
Are you going to hit me again?
- [crying]
-Oh, uh.
Ah, man, now cut
that out, would ya?
Don't cry, Akane.
I always say that
you're un-cute.
-P-chan is gone!
-Just 'cause I say it don't
mean that I-- what the-- P-chan?
-P-chan vanished at
the skating rink.
Somebody kidnapped him.
We've got witnesses
and everything!
-Come on, Ed!
-What did this
kidnapped pig look like?
-You know what he looks like!
-Well I don't suppose
he looked like that.
[pig squealing]
-P-chan!
P-chan.
-Go away!
Who are you?
This is Azusa's
little Charlotte.
[pig squealing]
-No it's not!
Enough jokes.
This is my pet pig.
P-chan.
-But you're wrong.
Don't you think Azusa knows
her own little Charlotte?
[whimpers] Give it back!
Give Azusa back her Charlotte!
Charlotte!
-Is it yours?
-Uh, uh huh.
-What a dream.
-I'll say.
-Please accept my apologies.
-Thank you.
It's all right.
[whimpers]
-You see, she makes
a hobby of collecting
these cute little things.
-Give Azusa back her Charlotte!
Charlotte, Charlotte,Charlotte!
-Even if they don't
belong to her.
-Charlotte,
Charlotte, Charlotte!
-She has this appalling habit
of giving things a silly name
and taking them home with her.
-Isn't that against the law?
-And that's why the one she
calls Charlotte is actually
your own abducted pet.
-Charlotte!
Charlotte!
-Ugh, that's enough already!
You have made your point, OK?
[crying]
-If you won't give
Charlotte back, then
Azusa challenges you!
-You want to fight
me, is that it?
Don't be so tacky!
-Azusa is talking
about figure skating!
-Skating?
-You do know how to
skate, don't you?
If Azusa wins, you give
her back Charlotte!
-Ah, now I remember.
-Huh?
-I just knew I'd send
those two somewhere before.
I'm sure.
It is them.
The legendary Golden Pair
of Kolholtz High School.
-I'm Azusa Shiratori.
-Mikado Sanzenin.
-(OFFSCREEN) Will someone
please order something?
-Akane, I think I'd cancel
the match if I were you.
-The Golden Pair has
an unbroken record
of 950 consecutive
figure skating victories!
-It makes no difference!
-Why don't you surrender
and get it over with, hmm?
-Surrender?
You'll have to kill me first!
--[giggles] Be brave
darling, Charlotte!
Azusa will take
care of everything.
-P-chan, don't you worry.
There's no way I'm going to
let her take you from me.
-(TO HIMSELF) Man, I
hope they both lose.
-Can you find it in
your heart to forgive
my partner's rudeness?
As a token of my apology.
-Huh?
-[all gasp] [music playing]
- (TO HERSELF) Ranma?
-What a refreshing way
to issue a challenge.
Very well.
I will accept.
The match will take place a
week from today at the Koholotz
high school skating rink.
-Oh!
That fish sausage is so cute!
-You can skate, can't you?
-(FRENCH ACCENT)
Francois, Francois!
-Have it your way.
-Ugh!
-Come on let's get out of here.
-(FRENCH ACCENT)
Francois, Francois!
Francois, give it back!
Give it, give it!
[giggles]
-Do you realize
you completely ruin
the effect, you
annoying little brat?
-You can't have it!
-OK mister, you can pay
this bill for 1,545 Yen
for that ramen your friends ate.
-Huh?
-Come again.
-Now don't you go thinking
I'm jealous of you or nothing.
-Why would I think that?
-Suave guys like him give
me the creeps, that's all.
-Well, it's really none
of your business anyway.
-Hey, you!
I stuck my neck out
for you back there!
Is this how-- oh.
-Well what?
-Don't tell you-- I mean, you
don't really like this guy,
do you Akane?
-Ha!
If you'd have thrown that
fish sausage a second later,
I'd have-- I sure would
have made him sorry.
-You are so un-cute.
-Or maybe, I just need a
guy who appreciates me.
Have you ever thought of that?
-You're what?
Over that pig?
-Figure skating as a
couple, did you say?
-You two?
I thought skaters
had to at least like
each other before they
paired up as a couple.
-Akane and Ranma like each
other just fine, right?
-We do?
-Look.
Win or lose, I
could care less what
happens to that
little pig of yours.
-Let me skate with you!
-Oh, hello Ryoga.
Have a seat.
-Akane, let me be your
figure skating partner!
-But Charlotte, how do you
know about that skating match?
-Shut up!
Who you calling Charlotte?
Ah, forget it.
Pairing up with Akane is
my problem, not yours, OK?
-Come on Ranma, I'll
skate you for it!
-Ha!
Well, I bet you didn't know
that ever since I was little,
they've been calling
me the Iceman!
-Ha yourself, Ranma!
Little do you know
that my childhood
nickname was Mr. Frosty!
-[laughter]
-Let's go!
[music]
-(OFFSCREEN) Looks
like Iceman and Mr.
Frosty should learn to crawl
before they try to stand up.
[music playing]
--Whoa,whoa!
Ah!
-What am I going to do with him?
[sighs]
-[laughs] Ah, boy do you look stupid!
Is this your first time skating?
You want me to teach ya?
-[grunts] Ugh.
-Hang on Akane,
I'll be right back.
-Ranma, how dare you do that!
That was no fair.
You come back here!
-Ranma!
Come back here!
-Here we go.
--[sighs] Figure skating is
just too embarrassing as a guy.
Even little kids make fun
of guys when they fall.
-Ranma.
-Huh?
Ugh.
-Ha, you're so predictable.
I knew I'd find
you hiding in here.
Why don't you fight
like a man for once!
Go out there and take
your medicine like me.
You don't see me running away
because Akane's watching.
You don't-- ah!
What are you doing?
Ah!
-Look at it this way, Charlotte.
[pig squealing]
Being a pig and all,
you don't have to worry
about (laughing) falling down
in front of Akane, do ya?
See ya!
[pig squealing]
-That guy turned it into a girl.
-And this guy turn into a pig.
[chatter]
-There you go Ranma.
Now stand up!
Up!
Honestly, Ranma.
How do you expect to
skate with me in the match
if you can't even stand up
on the ice on your own, huh?
-I'm doing the best I can.
[laughter]
-Stand up!
Are you a guy or aren't you?
-I'm a girl right now, OK?
Doing this as a
guy, I'd look dumb.
-I've got some news
for you, Ranma you
look pretty dumb either way.
-[sighs]
-Azusa Shiratori.
-Oh no, did I do that?
-Hey!
You did that on
purpose, didn't you?
-Azusa did no such thing.
Wow!
You partner can
really skate fast!
-Huh?
-[screaming]
-Ranma!
-[groans]
-[gasps] Huh?
-Are you all right, miss?
-It's you.
Hey, you're Mikado Sinzenin.
-Excuse me, but how
do you know my name?
Have we met somewhere
before, maybe?
Well now, this is very
unusual, isn't it?
I'd never forget the face of a--
-Do your girl-chasing
later, Mikado.
It's time to practice the
assault of a hundred foes.
-A-assault of a hundred foes?
In figure skating?
-Stay here, beautiful.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Attack!
-Let's get 'em men!
[music playing]
-Now I see.
-94 95 96 97 98 99 100 Finito.
-Nine seconds flat.
A new record.
-That long?
We can do better that that.
-That's why they call the
Golden Pair of martial arts
figure skating after all.
-Hey, martial arts?
I- I can do that.
If it's got martial arts
in it, I can do anything!
We've got him Akane.
We can beat him for sure now.
-Hm hmm.
Just as soon as you learn
how to stand up. [sighs]
-(OFFSCREEN) Oh, how cute!
-[laughter] [PIG SQUEALING)
-Ryoga!
P-chan!
-My Charlotte!
-P-chan, come here!
[pig squealing]
-Charlotte!
-No!
-Here, Charlotte!
Azusa's got a present for you!
[giggles] Oh!
So cute!
-What did you do to him?
You leave him
alone, you here me?
What is this?
Don't worry I'll get
it off of you, P-chan.
-Oh, no!
Azusa locked it
with her little key.
If you want it off,
first you'll have
to defeat Azusa in the match.
-Huh!
Golden Pair, shmolden pair!
I don't care who you are.
Ranma and I don't
intend to lose!
-Akane, help me!
Make me stop, I'm going to fall.
Come on, you've gotta help me!
Oh I feel dizzy Akane.
Don't just stand there,
hurry up and help me!
-Don't worry my
pigtailed pretty.
I'll show you how to skate.
-Oh.
You again.
Stay out of my business
and put me down!
I don't need your help.
-Oh, well I can't do that.
You still owe me.
A reward for saving
you earlier, remember?
-Get lost!
I'll give you a fat lip
if you-- [struggling]
-(OFFSCREEN) Ranma?
-Ah! [crying]
-Ah, to be moved so by my kiss.
She's such a pure and sweet and
innocent, naive, young child.
-(TO HERSELF) You'd cry too
if you realized who you just
kissed.
-[crying]
-That stupid jerk!
(angrily) How dare he?
How dare he?
And in front of Akane, no less.
-I'll get him!
-Are we on candid
camera or something?
Huh?
-Oh, toying with that
sweet child's emotion
like that, I really should
be ashamed of myself.
[laughs]
-Mikado!
Come on, fight me right now.
You've gone too far
this time, buddy!
-Ranma!
-Where did you come from?
Why you so angry?
-Now you've done it!
For the first time in
my life, I'm really mad!
-[muttering]
-That rice ball is cute!
Josephine, Josephine!
Gimme!
Ugh!
Ah!
-Hmm.
-Josephine, Josephine!
Give Azusa back her Josephine!
-How about it?
Let's fight.
Or are you just
going to stand there?
-I don't know what your
grievance is with me.
But damaging the rink
is a serious crime.
I accept your challenge.
Come on!
-I'm gonna make you
sorry you were ever born!
-Josephine, Josephine!
You monster, you
ate my Josephine!
Give me my Josephine back!
Josephine, Josephine!
-I'm sorry!
[music playing]
-Ranma, it's your own fault
you got kissed like that.
You left yourself wide open!
These two look like they
won't be easy to beat.
Next time on Ranma
1/2, Close Call:
The Dance of Death on Ice.
See you there!