[theme song]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Ranma goes
back to Jusenkyo at last!
[crow cawing]
-Huh?
It's Jusenkyo!
Jusenkyo!
After all these years,
I finally made it!
At last, I can get
rid of my curse!
All right!
No.
No fair!
That's no fair!
-It's the middle of the night.
What's wrong with you?
-Huh?
It was just a dream.
-Stupid boy.
[snoring]
-Pop!
-Wha?
Snap out of it!
-But-- but Pop!
Jusenkyo was all dried up!
-It was what? [laughing] It's
just another silly dream, boy.
-But listen, if those
cursed springs dry up,
we're stuck with
these dumb bodies
for the rest of our lives!
-But it was just a dream.
-And if it wasn't?
-Hm.
Hm.
Then I guess we'll have
to do some research.
-All China Training
Grounds Travelogue?
Hm.
You think that book
will be able to tell us
what we're looking for?
-Hm.
-You better not say again
that you can't read Chinese.
-Ding dong!
-Well, if you couldn't
read it, why'd
you even bother looking
at it in the first place?
I guess the only thing
left is to go to China.
Pops, gimme cash.
-Foolish boy.
I'm way ahead of you.
Don't you think I plan
for every contingency?
-Whoa.
Way to go, Pop.
-Boy, do your stuff.
-328 yen?
Ugh!
-Now, don't you worry yourself
about your old dad, son.
Oh, sure, you're taking
his life savings,
but he'll muddle
through somehow.
Doesn't he always?
-Why I oughta--
-Boy, wait!
-Huh?
-I just got me an idea.
-[snoring]
-But what if he's
already thrown it away?
-Once that little troll
gets hold of something,
he never lets go of it.
-[snoring]
-Jeez, I didn't
need to see that.
-Eureka.
-Huh?
What do you want?
-Ha!
The old goat's magic mirror.
I bet he even forgot
that he had it.
-Now we can go
anywhere, anywhen,
and it won't cost
us a stinking yen.
-Aha!
Stealing an old man's magic
mirror while he sleeps!
You oughta be ashamed.
At the very least, you
better take me with you.
-Quick, Pop, get the onion!
-The onion?
-[laughing]
-I wanna go 10 years
into the future.
-Wha?
-[screaming]
-Where the-- hey, we're in
the same place we started!
-I don't know.
Something seems strange.
-Now that you mention it, the
place does look kind of run
down.
-Yes!
I knew it!
We're 10 years into the future!
-Hush, somebody's coming.
-That's odd.
I could've sworn I
heard voices in here.
Honey!
-Honey?
-You see?
We are 10 years into the future.
Akane and I have become an item.
[laughter]
-Akane, where are you?
-Ryoga?
-So here's where you kids are.
Why don't you go ask
Grandpa to play with you?
[laughter]
-Somebody shoot me.
-Oh, Akane, how
could you betray me?
-Giddyup, horsie!
Giddyup!
-Again?
What the-- is that me?
-Panda!
Panda!
-Now boys, don't play too rough.
-That's right, kids.
Grandpa's an old panda.
-Anyway, dear, I'm off
to do some shopping.
Keep an eye on the
boys for me, will you?
-Piggyback ride!
Yeah, yeah!
-One at a time, kids.
I-- whoa!
-Well, now.
I guess that
answers the question
of whose kids they are.
-No fair!
No fair!
I don't want to
be old like that!
-You think I do?
-Well, hey, you guys,
what are we waiting for?
Let's get out of this crazy
future and go to Jusenkyo!
-Here you go, boy.
-Hey, that's enough already!
-I want to go back to
the same day we first
arrived at Jusenkyo!
-What-- no fair!
You stupid bird, come back here!
Huh?
Pop, come quick!
-Huh?
-Look!
Jusenkyo's right over there.
I'm sure of it!
-Huh?
-Well, I'll be.
If it isn't the Bayankala Range.
-What are we waiting for, pop?
Let's go!
-Not so fast!
-Huh?
-Now what is it?
-Look at that!
-We're almost there, boy.
-Are you sure you can read that?
-Oh, ye of little faith.
Of course I can't read it!
Oof!
Kicking your father.
You should be ashamed.
-Oh, shut up, old man.
-Why you little--
-Do you realize this means we
haven't fallen in Jusenkyo yet?
-True, but there's
still no time to lose.
We've got to stop them!
-Let's go.
-Hey, why do I gotta
help you stop them?
Why should I care if
they fall in or not?
-Because if you do, I'll set you
up with some girls' underwear.
That's why!
-Woohoo!
Yahoo!
-Come back, boy!
-This way to Jusenkyo.
Yah!
-I said wait up, boy!
-Nyah nyah, catch me if you can!
-Why you--
-That was close.
-When I catch you, I'm gonna--
-Hey, you went the wrong way!
-There goes that idea.
-OK, looks like it's up to me.
-Hahaha!
Whoa!
-[growling]
-What the heck are you?
-Handsome fellow for a panda.
You hungry, boy,
or is it just me?
-Yeah, I'm starving, actually.
It's been kind of slim
pickings lately, hasn't it?
-[growling]
-Come back here,
you pile of protein!
-So much for plan B. Well,
I guess it's all up to me.
-Come on, pop, slow
down a little, huh?
It's not like Jusenkyo's
gonna go anywhere.
-Foolish boy!
With it finally being so
close, how could you not run?
-Hey!
Hey, slow down, will you?
-Hm?
Boy, look!
-What is it, pop?
-Take a look at that!
-Is that Jusenkyo?
-You ready, Ranma?
-Oh yeah.
-Help me!
-Hey.
Are you all right?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): It's
a kind of weird feeling,
looking at yourself.
-What's this?
Boy, that girl
looks just like you.
-Oh, yeah, right.
--[nervous laughter]
Oh, my stomach!
-Gee, lady, when's the
last time you ate anything?
-I was saving this for
an emergency, but here.
-[screaming]
-What's the matter?
You don't like snake?
-I thought I told you get
rid of that thing, pop.
What are you still
carrying it around for?
-Let's get a move on, boy.
-Right behind you!
-But I--
-Now what?
-I'm being pursued
by some bad guys.
I could be wrong, but I think
their camp's back there.
-Sorry, lady, but
we're headed thisaway.
-Well, you can come with us
to Jusenkyo, if you want.
-And why the heck do you
want to go there, you morons?
-Hey, there's no
need to be rude.
Shall we go, pop?
-But you can't!
Come back!
There could be bad guys!
Ugh, for crying out loud!
Huh?
-Ranma!
-We ain't got time for that, OK?
-Ranma, baby!
How long's it been?
-Not long enough.
-Wait!
-What?
-Why don't you let your old
gramps handle this, huh?
I's got me an idea.
-Listen, old man.
Once we get to Jusenkyo,
you're gonna pay!
-Yeah, right, boy.
But you're about 100 years
early for this old ma-- man!
-Heya, Genma.
How's it going?
-M-m-m-master!
GENMA (VOICEOVER): It can't be.
We left him resting peacefully
in the mountains of Hida.
-Hey, pop.
Who's the old man?
-Show some respect, boy!
-Ow!
What did I do?
-M-master, I never expected
to see you-- I mean, uh.
-Genma, I bring you
tidings of great joy.
-You do?
-You see this?
Genma Saotome, on this
day, you are hereby
graduated from the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts
with honors!
In other words, you are
no longer a student.
You may now return to Japan
a fully accredited member
of the Anything Goes School,
free to do as you please.
So you see, there's no need
to go to Jusenkyo at all.
In fact, I'd turn
back-- how dare
you treat your master that way?
-Be quiet, you impostor!
-I-impostor?
-My real master would
never be that nice.
Why, he hasn't a kind
bone in his entire body!
He lives to drag others
down to his own level,
even to the depths of hell!
My master would never do
anything to make another happy!
-That's not true!
-So who is he?
-One of the little
people, maybe?
Doing mischief?
-I am not a little person!
-Say, boy, you hungry?
-Sure I am, pop.
-What do you say
we make us a stew?
-Now we're cooking.
-[crying]
-The nerve of that
jerk, eh, pop?
-You gotta get up pretty
early in the morning
to fool Genma Saotome.
[laughing]
-Those miserable little cowards!
Why, if they hadn't teamed
up on me, I would've--
--[inaudible], we come to the
training ground of the cursed
spring Jusenkyo.
-This is it, boy.
Are you ready?
-This place ain't so impressive.
-You very strange one, sirs.
Yes?
This place very dangerous.
Nobody use now.
Is more than 100 spring
here, and each one
have own tragedy happen there.
-Ranma, follow me.
-Right behind you!
-Uh, sirs, what are doing?
I no finish my tragic story!
You no go there!
-I won't go easy on you.
-That's just the way I like it.
-Please, sirs!
Very bad you fall in spring!
-That starnge.
Why do you think they did
not fall in cursed spring?
-Whoa!
-[shouting]
-Say, Pop, let's stop now, OK?
-Sure, why not?
I was getting kind
of bored anyway.
-Good, good.
You keep going, and sooner or
later, someone fall in spring.
Was somebody there?
-I knew it!
So it was you who kept
us from falling in?
-Aiya?
-Aw, man.
What a letdown.
Legendary training
grounds my butt.
-Well, we'll just have
to find another place
to train, eh, boy?
-But sirs, it no was my fault!
Sirs, wait!
It no was me, I-I tell you!
Sirs!
-All right!
Those two losers will never
have to go to Jusenkyo again!
You better enjoy being a panda
while you still can, pop,
because after this,
it looks like Saotome
and son are back to normal.
-Does this mean
that you won't turn
into a girl anymore, Ranma?
Does this mean these will
be gone with you, too?
No, no, no! [crying]
-Get off of me,
you little pervert!
-[screaming]
-Shall we go back to
our own world now, pop?
Aw, not the onion again.
-Ranma!
No!
Don't leave me!
Traitors!
You left me behind!
-[panting]
-I guess this means we
finally made it back, huh?
Hey!
Pop, you know what this means?
-Even when we're soaking wet,
our bodies no longer change.
[laughing]
-[laughing] All right!
All right!
Woohoo!
-They'll be here any minute.
The two of them have been on
a training journey, actually.
I hear they even did
some training in China.
-Ooh, China.
-So they trained in China.
Wow.
Big deal.
-So how old is Ranma, father?
-Is he cute?
-Younger men are so young.
-What kind of guy is
this Ranma, anyway?
-[laughing] I-- I don't know.
-You don't know?
-I've never met
the lad, you see.
-I'm home!
-Ooh, it must be Ranma!
-Ah, Saotome, my friend.
How we've been waiting!
-Please let him be older.
-I think I hate him already.
-Yo, Akane!
-Get me a drink, will
you, Kasumi, dear?
-What the--
-So you're Ranma?
-Huh?
Ha ha, Mr. Tendo.
Very funny.
-Hey, don't talk to
my dad like that!
-Butt out, will you?
You'll never catch a
husband at this rate.
-Well, for a complete
and total stranger,
you sure act like you've been
around this family before.
-So I'm a complete and
total stranger, then, am I?
I've been living
in this house ever
since-- hey, Akane, what
happened to that short haircut
you had?
-It's always been
long, you moron!
Besides, who are you to call
me by my first name, anyway?
-Psst, old man, come here!
I think maybe we came
back to our own world
a little too early, don't you?
-Looks like it.
That would explain why no one
here seems to recognize us,
anyway.
-What a pain in the butt.
-Don't worry, boy.
They'll just get to
know us all over again.
[clears throat] I'm Genma
Saotome, and here's my son.
-Ranma Saotome.
It's, uh, nice to meet you.
-Come on, put me down, will you?
-Sounds like more visitors.
-What's all the fuss about?
-[gasp]
-Mm?
-Oh, come on, pop!
Put me down!
You're scaring them spitless!
-Who is it?
It can't be!
-Augh!
-Friends of yours, daddy?
-Not-- not mine.
Saotome, speak up!
Tell them that these are
your friends, will you?
-I, uh, I've never
seen them before.
-[cackling]
-M-m-m-master!
-Whoa!
-If you hadn't
let me back there,
things now wouldn't
be so messed up!
Listen here, Ranma,
no matter what you do,
you can never change history!
Don't you know that? [cackling]
-But-- but that's no fair.
After everything we went through
to get here, it's not fair!
It's not fair!
-It's the middle of the night.
What's wrong with you?
-Wha-- huh?
Pop!
It's Jusenkyo!
I-- ow!
-Don't you realize
what time it is?
-I'm trying to sleep here.
Do you mind?
-Ugh, what's the matter
with you, anyway?
-Now I get it.
I was dreaming, right?
Oh!
[laughter]
Wait!
What if this is a dream,
and I'm dreaming right now?
[theme song]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Because of you,
the English version
of Ranma 1/2 has
become one of the most
popular anime series ever!
And coming soon,
there's gonna be
yet another whole new season.
If you thought we had some
crazy characters last time,
you just wait!
We'll see you there.