[opening theme]
-Hey, did you hear?
The school principal's
coming today.
-Hah, principal, huh?
Come to think of it, I've
never actually seen him.
-Yeah, I hear he's been in
America researching, you know,
education and stuff.
-Wow, America.
-Wonder what kind of guy he'll--
-Huh?
-Welcome, headmaster.
-Headmaster, headmaster.
Oh, I see.
Means, "principal."
-Principal, he says.
-Wow.
Guess they must all
take helicopters
to school in America.
Do you think?
-Hanging out his own
welcome banner though?
That's just plain tacky.
PRINCIPAL: Aloha, everybody!
-Did he just say "aloha?"
-What part of America
is he from anyway?
-Am I the only one who's got
a bad feeling about this?
PRINCIPAL: Aloha wahine.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): The return
of the Hawaiian headmaster
from Hell.
-Hurry, Ranma.
Hurry.
-Oh, we've got plenty of time.
-You said that yesterday
too, after you'd
overslept and made
us late for class.
PRINCIPAL: Socks
too long-- check.
Untucked blouse-- check.
-What is it?
What's wrong?
Huh?
-Uncombed hair-- check.
Non-regulation
schoolbag-- check.
Homework-- check.
Check, check, check, che--
-'Scuse me?
-Check.
Check.
-Isn't the weather
too warm for snowmen?
-No worries, little brother.
Now, give me that pigtail.
-Think again, Frosty the Freak!
-Bad keiki.
It's not nice to
hit your headmaster.
-Master of what?
-Give me that!
Give me!
-Keep your hands off the hair.
-Aloha, everybody.
Me the new principal.
-So this is American education?
-Think again, you
macadamia nut job.
-Wait, Ranma honey.
I'll help too.
-No, no, no.
You got me all wrong.
Here.
I bring you gift.
-What?
-From the island?
If you like ukulele lady.
You see, little keiki?
You see what happen
when student no follow
the rules of Furikan High.
Check.
Soon you be good
little keiki again.
Che-- No, never hit th face.
Bad keiki.
-What's the matter with you?
-Hm.
Bad keiki.
Bad.
Very bad.
Hey, kid.
How's about a nice
Hawaiian-- Aloha.
You wahine called Akane Tendo?
-Why do you ask?
-Come with principal.
-That's it.
He's going down.
-Attention, all students.
The Principal has called an
assembly in the main gymnasium.
Please report immediately.
-Aloha, everybody.
[chuckling]
BOY: Are you sure
he's the principal?
I mean, maybe he's--
PRINCIPAL: Aw, shut up.
Today, me am having very
exciting news for you all.
As you know, me when
coming back from Hawaii,
and me say to myself--
me say, headmaster,
you gotta bring extra special
present for all your keiki.
Yeah!
GIRL: What kind of present?
-Yeah.
BOY 1: I hope it's
not another pineapple.
BOY 2: Hey, you never know.
-And now for moment you
all been waiting for.
From now on, here's
new school rules.
All brothers get them buzzcuts.
All sisters get them bowl cuts.
-No!
-If you think I'm cutting my
hair like that, you're crazy.
-Perish the thought.
I can't go on stage
with a buzzcut.
-How am I supposed
to destroy Tokyo?
-I don't see what's
so wrong with 'em.
-Yeah.
I think they look pretty good.
-Unthinkable!
-Boys get buzzcuts.
Girls get bowl cuts.
If you think that
bad, wait till you
see the new rules me be making.
What this school need is order.
Bad keiki!
Bad.
Hm?
-Is this your idea of
payback for this morning?
The only one who needs
order here is you.
And what's with that
stupid outfit anyway?
-Don't you mind, little keiki.
Look up.
-Huh?
-Ho-ho!
Yeah!
Ranma Saotome, freshman
class, homeroom 1.
Me be doing research
on you, pigtail keiki.
If you want save
your wahine, you
be first brother in the
school getting a buzzcut.
-Why you no good,
dirty, little-- Hah-hah.
OK.
-Ouch.
No, no, no.
Please don't hurt--
-And you dare call
yourself a principal!
-Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, you no listen whole story.
Once you hear that,
you understand better.
Everybody, you go and fight
for your own freedom, Yeah?
Me hide here inside this coconut
this pardon from all school
rules.
Any brother, sister, which
can get from me this coconut
-Ah-hah.
Hurray.
-Doesn't need to get a haircut.
Isn't that right?
-You there, little
pigtail keiki,
if you no want me to cut
off that pigtail of yours,
then you come find coconut
the next three days.
Me be waiting in my office.
Yeah!
[laughter]
-Why you!
-You can't do this to us.
-Three days, huh?
We'll get it back
if it kills us.
-Or him!
-He hasn't changed a bit.
-He's always been like this?
-Oh sure, he'll do anything
to annoy the students.
-Hey, let's get while
the getting's good, huh?
-Now he's gonna pay for sure.
To the Principal's office!
-Yeah, he can't just
make us get buzzcuts.
-Or bowl cuts either.
-Where is the Principal's
office anyway?
Ever since I transferred
here, I haven't had a chance
to go there yet.
-You haven't?
-Me either.
-Or me, for that matter.
-Hasn't anyone been there?
-Fear not, fellow students.
So long as Tatewaki Kuno is
enrolled at Furikan High,
the institution of
buzzcuts and bowl cuts
shall never become a reality.
Stand and delivery,
perverted Principal.
-Who are you calling a pervert?
-We found it.
-All right!
Way t to go.
-Hey, there's a Principal
office here too.
-And here.
-There's another
one over here too.
-And here.
-They're kidding.
-Oh, looks like that
nut job's at it again.
Huh?
-Let's just check 'em
out one by one, OK?
-What is this place?
-Aloha, everybody!
Welcome, my little
keiki, to the big island.
Please, feel right at home
in the friendly Hawaiian
atmosphere.
[growling]
-Ranma!
-Ramna honey's not here.
-What?
-Oh no.
We're locked in.
-Barber shears?
-Take that, that, and that!
-Please, don't hurt us anymore.
-Is that a teacher?
-Those animal sounds
must have been taped.
-You could hurt
somebody, you know?
-It was the Principal
who made us.
-Please, I've got three
cubs of my own to feed.
-Boohoohoo.
-No fair, Principal!
-Yeah, one way or the
other, he's gonna make sure
we get those dumb haircuts.
-If we can find that coconut
though, we may not have to.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): That
stupid Ranma, of all the times
to disappear.
-Such persistent keiki.
If at first you don't
succeed-- How did canoe-- oh?
You kid or girl?
Wahine?
Hey, wahine?
Pigtail?
Bowl cuts for girls.
-Alas, I am not your student.
You see, I've been sent from
a neighboring island in search
of a very special coconut.
-You have?
What?
It's for your poor,
sickly father?
-That's right.
And if he doesn't have a coconut
with a get out of rules free
inside, he may
even-- he may even
come down with a
case of the scurvy!
[crying]
-What a dutiful wahine you are.
OK, then.
Me will help you.
-So then you'll give it to me?
-No, no, wahine.
I mean, me go with
you on journey
to find coconut with get
out of rules free inside.
-Huh?
Wait a sec.
Are you telling
me don't have it?
-Dumb kahuna me am.
Me forget where me hide it.
-Here it is.
The real Principal's office.
-Be careful.
Huh?
-Where did these come from?
-The paper could
be in any of 'em.
-But we've come too
far to turn back now.
-We're not beat yet.
-Next.
-Hi-yah.
-Cowabunga.
Look at that keiki go.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Huh,
always doing it the hard way.
-Hi-yah!
-Here's the last one.
-Which means the
get out of rules
free paper's gotta
be is this one, then.
Here goes.
Hi-yah!
It was a fake.
-Meaning the boys have
gotta get buzzcuts.
-With bowl cuts for girls.
-He still hasn't beat us.
If we can just find
where he's hiding.
-She's right.
If he won't give us
the coconut, then we'll
just beat it out of him.
-Let's get 'em.
-Principal!
-Too bad this big kahuna
too smart for you.
PRINCIPAL: Bad wahine!
You betray me!
-I don't recall ever
teaming up with you.
-Huh?
Was that Ranma's voice I just--
-OK, now tell us where
the coconut is, or else.
-Aw, too bad, keiki,
but I no remember.
-You don't, huh?
Maybe we can help
refresh your memory.
-So what's it gonna be?
One slab or two?
-OK, now me remember.
-Well?
-In the Principal office.
-Which Principal's office?
-Well, that be the one with
t the name on the door.
-You're not leaving till you
tell intelligence us, you know?
-The big kahuna need
a big office, yeah?
Me make different ones
for different days.
-Get to the point.
Which is the one that's got the
coconut with the note inside?
[crash]
-So why don't you just beat
him and get it over with?
-Inconceivable.
Now hear this, thou foul
obscenity of an administrator.
Not a single hair
is to be trimmed
from Akane Tendo's darling head.
Not while I, Tatewaki
Kuno have breath
in my body to prevent it.
-OK, OK, me no cut!
Me not cut!
You break the rope!
Haha.
-How dare you blow
your vile kisses at me!
What?
My sword.
-This is the way we stop
swords on the big island.
-You, you may have fooled
me once, but never again.
-Keiki, how about
a nice Hawaiian--
-Why, thank you.
-Look out!
It's a--
-Moron.
-He's gone.
-He won't get far.
If we check all of
his offices, I'm
sure we'll find him eventually.
-OK, we'll split into groups.
Ranma, you coming?
-Do I have a choice?
Huh?
What the?
-Aloha, keiki!
Feel free to take
the souvenir, yeah.
-How many rooms has he got?
-That plane just
took my top knot!
-Oh, me must be the luckiest
principal in the whole world.
-We'll be running
outta room soon.
Then what?
-Ranma.
-You find him?
-Not yet.
It's possible he
could be hiding,
but unless he's in the room Ukyo
and the others are checking,
there's no sign of
him or the coconut.
-Or maybe he's just been
lying to us all along.
-Oh, don't even say that.
-Ranma.
-Any luck?
-No.
We can't find it anywhere.
-That means we're doomed.
-Wait.
I just remembered someplace
we haven't looked.
-But where?
-Yeah?
Where?
AKANE: The gym?
UKYO: But just this morning we--
RANMA: Exactly, which is why
it's the perfect hiding place.
All this time we've been
concentrating on the offices.
It never occurred to us
to come and look here.
UKYO: You are so smart.
RANMA: Let's go get 'em.
-Yeah!
-Hm?
-Ranma's right.
This has gotta be it.
-Who knows?
Maybe we'll even find the
real Principal's office.
Watch out!
They're after out hair.
-What kinda nut
trains a lobster?
[laughter]
-It's the Principal!
-Yo, headmaster from Hell!
Where are you?
Huh?
Well, what do you know?
It looks like
there's nobody home.
-Like I'd really
fall for that one.
Playtime's over, Hula Hair.
Now stop before you
make me really mad.
-Why you no let me help you?
Huh, keiki?
Maybe me even remember where
me hide the coconut with the
get out of rules free
note inside, yeah?
-I don't want it anymore.
I don't care if you
are the principal.
You ain't cutting
my hair, got it?
And while we're at it, I
think you owe me an apology.
Mind if I beat it out of you?
-Wait.
Wait.
Let me think.
OK.
Me think about it.
What side you want
me to cut first, huh?
-Now where's Ranma gone off to?
Huh?
-OK, little pigtail keiki.
Now we're ready for the big fun.
-I call that one, Coconut Crush.
-You did that one on purpose.
-Gee, what do you think?
-Me think, me give you
the pepper balloon.
-Boom!
-If not for you meddling
keiki, me woulda--
-Yeah, yeah.
Give it up, Principal.
We've got you surrounded.
-Phew That was close.
-Look.
There's the stupid coconut.
-It's a homer, yeah!
-Why you!
-Vile, evil, wicked,
naughty Principal.
Your reign of scholarly
sadism is at an end.
Take this!
And this, this, this!
-Hey, watch where
you're hitting.
-Ranma?
-Hey, I said watch it!
-Hey, look at this.
You wanna get back big
kahunas lucky coconut.
For reward, I be giving
you the buzzcut--
-If it's shaved
heads you want, I'll
be certain to invite Buddhist
monks to your memorial service.
-Somebody help me!
-Oh no.
No, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey.
Get away from me.
-Black justice is at hand!
-You're hitting the wrong guy!
Nah-nah, you missed--
-When you come back, me
give you the buzzcut, yeah.
-Think so, huh?
-I've got a big [inaudible]
Me give you Special Aloha
Sword-Shredder technique.
-The dreaded Aloha
Sword-Shredder, a technique
from the Pacific Islands
in which an opponent's
wooden sword is destroyed
as his hair is sheared?
Amazing.
-But true.
When it be done all proper like,
it be over before it begun.
-Hey, you kno what they say.
Everybody's got a plan, until
they get kicked in the head.
-Akane Tendo, I--
-Finally, after
all that trouble.
-You promised, no haircuts
if we could get it.
Remember?
-OK, OK.
Me give up, wahine.
You no hold against me, yeah?
I only wanted the keiki should
have the big fun at the school
like me do.
Keiki seemed bored, so me
say, big kahuna give them
keiki the big fun, yeah?
[crying]
-I'm touched.
-We forgive you.
So don't cry, OK?
-Huh?
What about the pigtail keiki?
Will he forgive me too?
-So what do you say, Ranma?
Do you forgive him?
-Malo!
Oh me went wrong when me
called you the bad keiki.
So now, me give you all
the new present, yeah?
Huh?
-Are you ready for the big fun?
-Come back here.
-No, now we have an
all new school rule.
All brothers get them top knots.
Alll sisters get
them geisha cuts.
-I ain't going
through this again.
-I still think he
needs a beating.
-Oh Yeah.
RANMA: Come here, I said.
PRINCIPAL: As we say on
the big island, Aloha!
[ending theme]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Grandfather
Happousai is training Kuno.
But I wonder.
Are those nasty little
habits he's learning really
gonna make him invincible?
Next time on Ranma 1/2, Enter
Kuno, the Night Prowling Night.
We'll see you there.