[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
Huh?
Where's that mailbox!
Oh, boy.
I just cannot believe my luck.
I must have made a wrong
turn at that corner store.
You dummy!
VOICE: And today
was the day I was
going to tell her how I felt.
Who's there?
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Who is this kid?
You were-- you
were just wondering,
who is this kid, weren't you?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Huh?
He can read minds.
That one was easy.
You thought to yourself,
he can read minds.
That's pretty good, huh?
Amazing.
This kid can read minds.
For real.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Akane's
unfathomable heart.
What are you doing
out here following me?
Ha, you're right.
I am following you for a reason.
It's because a few
miles back there
I noticed that you
dropped this in the woods.
Hey, that's my-- huh?
It's gone.
Huh?
The girl's name
is-- Akane Tendo.
RANMA: Ha, yeah.
It looks like you're
right again, kid.
Can I have my
picture back, please?
Tell me, where
does this girl live?
Why would you want to
know where Akane lives?
Oh, now I see.
She doesn't live very
far from here at all.
What?
I think I would
like to meet her.
What?
Wait!
[bell ringing]
[students talking]
See you later!
Wow, I'm so glad that's done.
Hey, what are you
doing tomorrow?
AKANE: Ranma, when
you get home, can you
put this on the
coffee table for me?
Sure.
But what is it?
It's for the puppet show.
A monster?
It's a princess, you idiot!
Oh, now I see it!
It-- it's a princess, all right.
Hurry up, Akane.
Oh!
I'm coming.
I've gotta go.
So can you just do it, please?
Hm?
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
I was wondering
what she's been trying to
sew the last few nights.
You gotta admit, though,
it's still pretty ugly.
Ugh!
Ranma, you go out
on date with Shampoo?
I'm busy!
So the answer is no!
OK, then.
Shampoo help you, and
then we go on date.
I've gotta drop
something off for Akane.
Hm?
Huh?
Ah!
Oh, no.
Is that your errand?
So, Shampoo, do
you always carry
around needles and thread?
Shampoo always
prepared for anything.
Oh.
[humming]
I finish.
Awesome!
Hey, thanks.
No.
Huh?
Not until you promise to
have date with Shampoo.
But I-- I promised Akane I'd
take the puppet home for her.
Does Akane mean
that much to you?
Get serious.
Huh?
OK, then we can date!
First, I think we
should have lunch, OK?
Sorry, Shampoo.
But my first promise was
to deliver this for Akane.
Ranma!
Oh, good.
Akane isn't home yet.
Huh?
Who's this for?
There you go.
VOICE: Akane would be
mad if she found out.
Huh?
VOICE: I better
keep it a secret.
You can try to get
me, but you'll just
be wasting your time.
I'm way too fast.
Come here, you little creep!
Why, you little--
Too slow.
Come back here!
Oh, my.
Punch of the tiger dragon!
SATORI: Akane's puppet got--
Ooh-la-la.
VOICE: So I had Shampoo--
You better shut your trap.
Or else.
I see you're getting
along just fine.
Like birds of a feather.
Would somebody please tell
me who the little brat is?
Oh, Nabiki.
Thanks again for the tea.
He says he's a
friend of Ryoga's.
Ryoga, you say?
Why, I haven't seen
him around for a while.
And I always thought he
didn't have any friends.
Well, to be perfectly
honest, I only just met Ryoga.
What is it with all
the racket out there?
Don't you realize that I'm
trying to, uh-- meditate?
OK, Ryoga's friend.
You got a name?
Well, you're not gonna
believe me when I tell you.
Huh?
OK.
Here it is.
My name's Satori.
Tendo, did he say
his name was Katori?
No, Saotome.
It sounded to me like he
said his name was Hatori.
Oh, he must be a ninja.
No!
My name's Satori.
Sa-to-ri!
Well, that's a very nice name.
Uh, thanks a lot.
Hang on.
Doesn't your name come from
some character in a fairy tale?
Exactly!
And I'm that boy who
can read people's minds.
Oh.
Interesting.
A mind-reader, eh?
Pretty impressive.
You know, kids say
the darndest things.
Oh, boy.
But I can read minds!
Huh?
Hm?
Ahh!
Hey!
Help!
Someone help me!
Snap out of it.
Huh?
What the heck is
the matter with you?
I think the boy's
a little tired.
I'm not tired!
I just went too
far into her mind.
I'll prove it.
Old man, this time I'll tell
everyone what you're thinking.
Well, all right.
Uh, Satori, let's say,
for the sake of argument,
you really can read
people's thoughts.
Well, with that in mind, might I
suggest you pick someone else's
brain to read?
Trust us on this one, kid.
RANMA: Hey, kid, what's wrong?
WOMAN: Oh, my.
TENDO: What happened?
GENMA: What's the matter?
TENDO: Get some ice, quickly!
He must have seen
something horrible.
You should really
lie down, Satori.
Why don't you believe me?
It's because the people in this
house are strange, that's all!
Well, what do you say
we give him one more
chance to prove himself.
AKANE: I'm home!
[music playing]
I'm home!
What are you all doing in here?
Come in, Akane.
Yes.
Grab a seat and join us.
Well, everyone, it seems we've
just found our next victim.
Huh?
Akane, this is Satori.
He's a friend of
Ryoga's, and he claims
he can read people's minds.
He-- hello.
Hello there.
So, you're a little
psychic, huh?
TENDO: Why don't you
try reading Akane's?
Huh?
Mm-- huh?
I can't.
Do you know what we
do to little boys who
tell fibs around here?
He's teasing.
Why don't you turn in
for the night, Satori?
AKANE: Oh, Ranma, thank you!
Hm?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Oh, man.
Shampoo did too
good of a job on it.
Yeah, no problem.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Good, she didn't notice.
You just thought,
good, she didn't notice!
Hm?
Stop that!
Quit following me!
You don't want me
hanging around you.
Gee, what was your first clue?
You know I can
read your thoughts.
Back off!
And what if I don't?
Shut up!
Hey, you two.
Breakfast's ready.
Oh, good morning, Akane.
Ranma's hiding a
secret from you.
Huh?
Ranma?
Hey, what's the big idea?
We don't want our breakfast
to get cold, do we, Satori?
TENDO: Kasumi, perhaps
we need to ration food
for the rest of the month.
As you wish, Father.
What is up with you always
stealing my food, you cheat?
But that's not true!
That little creep doesn't know
who he's dealing with yet.
Hm?
Now what?
Oh, nothing .
Then get lost, kid.
OK.
Hm?
Ah!
No, wait, come back here,
you little smart aleck!
What's going on?
Keep it down, boy!
Come on, open this door before
I start to get really mad, you
little fairy tale freak!
SATORI: Leave me alone.
I'm busy.
Now you're asking for it!
GENMA: Sometimes I hate
to admit he's my son.
Now, now.
Never mind him.
And besides, we both
know his bark is
bigger than his bite, Saotome.
Oh, I think I've got you.
I knew you were gonna do that.
Now try to get out of this.
Huh?
Oh, Satori, please
don't surprise us.
You scared me out of my mind.
I agree.
Mister with the head wrap, the
mister with the dumb mustache
was expecting that
move, you know.
It's not dumb!
What?
I'll do something different.
Maybe like this.
Oh!
I didn't see that.
Don't worry, Mr. Mustache.
The man with the head wrap
just did that without a plan.
It's just a fluke.
Then I've got nothing
to worry about.
It looks like I'm going
to win another one.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
The kid's just
playing with the both of them.
TENDO: So, Satori, where
should I make my next move?
GENMA: Hey that's not fair!
You're cheating.
Are you going out, Akane?
Yeah.
I have puppet practice.
Well, you have fun.
[bell ringing]
Ni hao, everyone!
Shampoo?
What are you doing here
so early in the morning?
None your business.
Shampoo here to see Ranma.
Shampoo?
Remember your little
promise with Shampoo?
What little promise?
Uh-- it's like--
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
I'm in trouble.
Akane, you like
the puppet, yes?
Uh-- nothing, really, Akane.
Shampoo, could you step
outside for a minute?
What about your date?
Why, you-- you're
gonna pay for this!
SHAMPOO: Look,
Shampoo made lunch.
Is that so?
Hang on.
I can explain.
You know, I'm not in the
mood for any excuses.
Huh?
Wait, Akane.
It's not how it looks.
You know, this doll looks
too nice for me to have made.
That's because, Akane,
Shampoo fix ripped puppet
when Ranma asked me yesterday.
She's right.
This nice lady really
did mend your puppet.
See?
I told them I really
could read people's minds.
Hey, yeah!
And you know you're the best
mind-reader Shampoo ever met
in whole life.
Gee, thanks.
Um, well, uh--
Is that the truth, Ranma?
Well, uh-- I mean, it
really was an accident.
Ah.
But Rama still hiding something
even more important from you.
Go ahead and ask them about it.
Hey, what are you
saying, you little brat?
I told her everything
there is to tell,
and that's the end of
it, you understand.
Ranma, you know you haven't
told her the whole story.
OK.
That's just about enough
out of you, kiddo.
You should be
ashamed of yourself
for the way you've acted, Ranma.
You're disgusting!
Akane--
Take that!
I'll get you, Satori!
I never thought Ranma
could sink so low.
[knocking]
Who is it?
Oh.
Oh, Satori.
What can I do for you?
I kind of thought you might
be feeling a little down.
I'm all right.
Are you telling me you don't
mind if the guy you're engaged
to wrecks your puppet?
That has the nerve to go
behind your back and promise
to go out on a date
with that Chinese girl?
I-- I don't know.
I guess I should hate him.
Are you sure?
I'm very sure.
I can't-- I can't
read her thoughts.
Akane did work really
hard on this doll.
I suppose I should go
and apologize to her.
SATORI (VOICEOVER): I just
can't seem to read her mind.
If you wanna know
why, I'll tell you.
Huh?
Na-- Nabiki?
Listen, if you really want to
know the reason why you can't
read her, just let me know.
But if not, then
don't waste my time.
So, tell me!
Hm.
First you'll have to tell
me my thoughts, Satori.
Huh.
How interesting.
It looks like you really
can read people's minds.
You see, the reason why
you can't read her thoughts
is because you have
a crush on Akane.
Are you saying you can
read people's minds, too?
Oh.
Well, maybe.
Huh?
Now what?
Akane hates you!
She hates everything about you!
Hey, don't tell me you
have feelings for Akane.
You really shouldn't
have said that, Ranma.
I want a duel!
You want a fight?
Well, fine by me, pipsqueak.
I'd be more than
happy to meet you up
on the roof and mess
with your puny pea brain!
It's so nice to see the
mature side of Ranma.
I'm ready.
But honestly, I don't think
you're fast enough to catch me.
You're just a
spoiled little brat
who thinks he's pretty tough.
Well, I'll teach you!
You're not gonna win.
I can read all of your moves!
He's right.
He can read all my moves.
That's enough, you two.
What do you think you're doing?
Huh?
Akane?
Satori!
I wish you'd just leave
and never come around Akane
ever again, you bully!
Ha ha!
Now I've got you.
Hey, let me go!
Ranma!
You put him down
this very instant!
Stop it!
Hey, you don't know what I've
been through with this kid.
Ahh!
[screaming]
Huh?
I can read Ranma's secret.
And Akane, yours too!
Akane!
Wait a sec-- you're both liars!
[groaning]
I'll see ya.
You take care.
See you around, kid.
Yeah.
And maybe one day I'll meet
a girl just like you, Akane.
Huh?
Uh-- never mind.
Well, gotta go.
Bye.
See ya.
Adios.
Take care.
Goodbye!
Huh?
Where's that blasted mailbox!
[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I guess
it's my fault for buying
a notebook at the
secondary school store,
but I never expected
this to happen.
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
A Teenage Ghost Story.
We'll see you there.