[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Case
of the Missing Takoyaki.
NARRATOR: This is Ramna Saotome,
16 years old, a high school
freshman.
Akane Tendo, 16 and a freshman.
Nabiki Tendo, 17 years of
age and a high school junior.
Kasumi Tendo, 19 years
old, occupation, homemaker.
Soun Tendo, mid 40s, manager
of the Tendo Training Hall.
Genma Saotome, also in his mid
40s, occupation, freeloader.
Happosai, age estimated at 400
years, he too is a freeloader.
These are our main characters.
-Hey, Kasumi, perfect timing.
-Good morning.
I just got in a fresh shipment
of Takoyaki octopus buns.
-I'll take I'll six-pack
if you don't mind.
-And because you're so pretty,
I'll throw in an extra one.
-Thanks.
[phone rings]
I'm coming.
NARRATOR: And this is how
the Tendo Seaweed Sprinkle
Incident began.
-OK then.
Goodbye.
Huh?
[scream]
-I assume you're
all wondering why
I've called everyone
in our little household
to this meeting today.
A situation has been
brought to my attention that
must be dealt with
straightaway, a situation
so grave it could
possibly jeopardize
the future of this family and
destroy relationships among us.
Sometime this morning,
Kasumi purchased
a pack of fresh Takoyaki,
but somehow those
octopus puffs have vanished.
Our only witness to
the crime is Kasumi.
She was the last person to
see the missing Takoyaki.
-Uh, well, It was around 3:00
when I came into the kitchen
to start dinner.
About 10 minutes later, I
went to answer the phone.
Then when I returned
the Takoyaki were gone.
The back door had
been left half open
and a cup of water on the
table had been tipped over.
It was dripping onto the floor.
Maybe there is a
simple explanation.
However, I thought
I'd ask you all first.
If anyone has eaten
them or knows who did,
now is your time
to step forward.
-Um, well--
-Huh?
-It's not like I
saw him taking them,
but I did, in fact, see
Ranma in the kitchen.
-Huh?
-So are you accusing me of
eating the Takoyaki, Nabiki?
Huh?
-Please, Ranma, sit down.
Nobody's accusing
you of anything.
So before you get upset, let's
hear what Nabiki has to say.
-Yeah.
Let's here it.
-Well, a little after
3:00, I came home
and went into the kitchen.
Hm?
Huh?
Ranma?
I wondered why she
was in such a hurry.
What's this?
Huh?
Aha!
-I just went into the kitchen
to get a drink of water.
-And was that all?
-Aha!
Then it with you who came
in through the back door
and left it open.
-Excuse me, but you still
haven't answered my question.
-What question?
-I was wondering why
you were in such a hurry
when you ran out of the kitchen?
-Huh?
Listen, when I went in there,
the Takoyaki was already gone.
I saw the empty pack myself.
-Hm.
Hm.
Oh, I just thought of something.
-Hello?
-Ah!
The Takoyaki!
Someone.
Stole them.
-It's a possibility.
-Hm, hm.
-So did you eat them?
-Oh please.
Don't worry.
I still haven't played
my trump card yet, Akane.
-What do you mean
by that, Nabiki.
like
-Oh come on tell us what your
trump card is, for Pete's sake.
-All right, I will.
And to back up my
story I have evidence
to prove that what
I'm saying is true.
And here's the proof.
-Huh?
-What is it?
-Ah!
-Oh.
-Akane, tell us.
-It's the wrapper from Takoyaki.
-Where did you get that?
-Let me explain it to you.
Ranma was thirsty and decided to
go get a drink of water, but--
-Ah, man.
Takoyaki.
Awesome.
But I'm still hungry.
Hey.
I've got it.
If I become a girl, my stomach
will shrink I'll be full.
-Oh yeah, that did the trick.
-So, it was you after all.
-Wait a second.
All she showed you was
the wrapping paper.
-Duly noted, Ranma,
but personally,
I believe your defense
to be rather weak.
-I have to agree with Happosai.
-Come on, Akane.
You gonna take that
pervert's word over mine?
-Why don't you just confess?
After all, you do
admit that you changed
into a girl in the
kitchen, right?
Well, did you?
-Huh?
I didn't want to say this
but, you left me no choice.
I confess I saw everything.
-OK.
It's time to give Ranma the
chance to tell his version.
I remember right
after my workout,
I went into the
bathroom and a shower
and then after I was
finished, I noticed
some running down the hallway.
-Huh?
Akane.
I wonder, what's her rush, huh?
She must have dropped
this rubber band.
-It seems as though
we may have yet
another suspect in
our little mystery.
Uh.
-Oh, how dare you even
include me as a suspect?
-But, Akane, you know I didn't
make the whole thing up.
Just tell us the reason why
you were running up the stairs.
-Well, I guess I was
in a hurry, that's all.
-Akane, to avoid any
misunderstandings,
why don't you tell
us your alibi.
-How come you're on
Ranma's side, Dad?
-Hold on there.
I'm not on any one's side.
Can't you see I'm just
trying to be fair?
-Fair?
Then explain to me what you
were doing in the kitchen.
-Oh?
-Huh?
-But, Dad.
-During the afternoon
in question,
I was busy doing some
intense research.
[phone ringing]
-Oh, I'll get it.
[chewing noisily]
Ah!
All that remained at the scene
of the crime, was a toothpick.
It was the one piece of
evidence that Soun left behind.
-Big deal if there
was a toothpick
on the floor in the kitchen.
It doesn't mean anything.
Way to go, Sherlock.
-Why you little--
here's the evidence.
[gasps]
EVERYONE: It's seaweed.
-That's right.
And as we all know,
you can't have Takoyaki
without seaweed on top.
-OK we can see that, but
what's your point exactly?
-Whoever used that toothpick
ate the top Takoyaki.
-Bingo!
At first I couldn't believe
that the head of this household
could stoop so low.
But the evidence clearly
shows us otherwise.
I rest my case.
-No.
It wasn't me.
Really.
Ah!
-Well, I wonder who the
real culprit is then.
-Hey.
-What?
-On Happosai's lip.
-Huh?
There's seaweed
on Happosai's lip.
Take a look.
-Huh?
-There must be some
kind of mistake here.
I--
-Get him.
-I swear.
I'm innocent.
I didn't do anything.
Innocent, I tell you.
-Why should we believe
a pervert like you?
-Yeah, we all know that
you're the one who did it.
-You're such a liar.
-I'm sorry, Master,
but as you can see,
we simply have no choice.
I suggest that you confess
your transgressions to us now
and just maybe we'll
go easy on you.
-Hey , why don't we tie him
up in a tree for awhile?
-Wait, Ranma.
Wait until you've heard
my side of the story.
-You mean more excuses?
-Stay away from me.
-You know, maybe
we should listen
to what he's got to say,
at least for a laugh.
-I agree.
And from what I
understand of the law,
shouldn't we at least hear
him out before we hang him?
-Yeah, she's right.
-Oh, all right.
Let's hear it.
-It began a long time ago,
when I was just a lad.
There was an old
woman in out village
who told us a story
about a seaweed child.
It's The Seaweed Legend.
EVERYONE: The Seaweed Legend?
-The legend has it that the
child would steal anything
with seaweed on it, from
Takoyaki to Yakisoba noodles
to even Okonomiyaki
KASUMI: How scary.
[child giggles]
HAPPOSAI: If you think
that's scary, just listen.
The seaweed child was known to
put seaweed sprinkle on those
who were asleep to make it look
like they were the guilty ones.
That kid was pure evil.
But to this day, no
one has ever seen him.
[giggling]
And from that, we can't
rule out the seaweed child
as a possible suspect.
Ah!
-We've heard enough
of your stupid story.
-How do we know the
seaweed child isn't you?
-I'm telling the truth.
-I don't know what
to believe anymore.
For someone who we
trusted as our master,
and to hear nonsense
is so pitiful.
Now you must face
about whip of justice.
-Not the whip of justice.
Ow, that smarts?
-Take that and that
and that and that.
-On, my.
-Ah, don't you think
he's had about enough?
-I know what it may look
like, Nabiki, but believe me,
it hurts him a lot
more than it does me.
-No, I was just
wondering what that was?
-Huh?
-Hey, Pop, look
this way for second.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Hold still.
Aha!
Look!
So, you and the old man
were in this together.
-You're disgusting.
-The horror.
To think of the
shame my own father
will bring to this
training hall.
The master and the pupil, guilty
of stealing Takoyaki and then
blaming it on some crappy
make-believe monster.
Ah!
I don't know what
to believe anymore.
-You should win the Oscar
for that performance.
-Why you.
-It was just a little
seaweed on my teeth
and you think I'm
guilty because of that?
Hey, just a few minutes
ago, you accused
Happosai based on the
very same evidence.
-Now you've forced me to tell
you of a legend so horrible,
it's never been told before.
It all began many,
many years ago
when Takoyaki and Yakisoba
and even Okonomiyaki
began to go missing and who
was the culprit, you ask?
Why, a repulsive monster who
ate anything with seaweed on it.
[evil laugh]
KASUMI: How scary.
SOUN: But what's even worse, is
the fact that he would sneak up
on unsuspecting villagers
AND put seaweed on them
as they slept, so they would
be blamed for his crimes.
And that's the legend
of the seaweed monster.
-Pretty scary huh?
-That's the same
story Happosai told.
-And we're sick and tired
of hearing about it.
-You two have some imagination.
-Look, everyone.
Up there.
-Hey, stop.
-All right, who are you?
-Sasuke?
HAPPOSAI: Good work, Akane.
The man servant from Kuno House.
-And why were you
hiding up on our roof?
-Sasuke, but why?
-But, but, but, I wasn't.
-Master, master, look.
-What's the problem?
-I found this in the kitchen.
-Let me see.
Look, the crest.
-Sasuke.
-I don't understand.
-Well, it looks like
we've got another suspect.
-He is not a suspect.
He is the one who did it.
Ah!
[laughing]
-Guilty.
-And we have the irrefutable
evidence right here.
-The chopsticks case.
-And it has the crest of
the Kuno family on it.
[crying]
-And this proves,
beyond a shadow
of doubt, that's you
were in the kitchen
when the crime was perpetrated.
-We all know you're the one who
committed the heinous felony.
-It's time to punish
the filthy little thief.
-Please, wait.
I don't even know
what's going on here.
Would somebody please
tell me what I did?
[drumming]
-Sasuke,
-Please wait.
I don't even know
what's going on here.
You have taken the
Tendo family's Takoyaki,
and in so doing, you nearly
destroyed this household.
Leave this place and take
only your shame with you.
-I am still not getting this.
-Are you saying you're innocent?
-I don't know.
-Well let me put it
another way then.
Are you saying that you were in
the kitchen but no one saw you?
-I wish I knew.
-Then I think it's clear
to everyone here that
you're the guilty--
-You'd forgotten
about me, didn't You
-It's the pigtail girl.
-You remember.
-Ah, the pigtail girl.
Oh boy, I can hand here for the
rest of my life and watch you.
This is a dream
come true for me.
-Who's there?
[blubbering]
-All right, you little creep.
You want to change your story?
-OK.
Hold on a minute.
Don't I get a chance to
speak in this kangaroo court?
You gotta at least give me the
courtesy of doing myself in.
-OK.
But hurry up and
spill your guts.
We generally like
to tar and feather
the guilty before dinner.
-Maybe I can help solve
this little mystery of yours
because I was hanging from
the ceiling the whole time.
-Oh.
And the key to your
puzzle are these photos
I hold before you in my hand.
Here see for yourself.
Well, what do you think?
Hm?
-I've had enough of this
mystery business for today.
-I think I'll just watch
some TV or read a book
or maybe I'll just sit.
-I think I'll join you, Ranma.
-But I thought you wanted to--
-Oh, Nabiki, wait up.
Maybe I'll join you
and Ranma and we
can watch a nature
show or something.
-So, Saotome, how about a
friendly little game of shogi?
-Why that sounds like
a great idea, Tendo.
-But this time, don't cheat.
-What do you mean, me cheat?
-Oh, that reminds me.
I must continue my
important research.
I don't want to fall
behind, you know.
-Hey where'd everybody go?
Kasumi, Oh, Miss Kasumi.
Did you see my lovely pictures?
Look familiar?
-I suppose it's time I started
making dinner for everyone.
-But what about my photos?
Miss Kasumi, wait.
-Doesn't anyone want to
come see my pictures?
You wanted evidence.
I got evidence.
I've got negatives too.
I'll even blow them
up if you want.
Oh, please.
It's starting to
get chilly out here
and if I can't catch a
cold, it's all your fault.
Then I'll take pictures
of me with a thermometer
and improve it in
a court of law.
-Ah, never even had a chance
to score that Takoyaki.
-You can say that again.
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Ranma gets hold
of some Chinese
incense that allows
him to train against a
shadow image of himself.
What in the world
is he thinking?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Ranma versus Shadow Ranma.
We'll see you there.