[theme music]
Hey, Ranma.
Let's go watch the
girls' volleyball game.
Think I'll pass.
Akane's out there playing.
Well, if she's playing, our
team will win hands down.
What's the point in watching
when the sides are so uneven.
Don't you wanna see Akane
in those hot gym shorts?
Not really.
This is terrible.
We're losing the big game.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Bring It On.
Love as a Cheerleader, Part 1.
What the heck's going on here?
Akane's the only one on
our team left standing.
Is the Seishun High
team really that good?
As for their volleyball
team, they're pretty average.
That was very impressive.
Nice dodge, girly.
Who rocks the house?
I say Seishun rocks the house.
And when Seishun
rocks the house,
they rock it right
to the ground!
S-E-I-S-H-U-N. S-E-I-S-H-U-N.
One, two, three, four--
we're declaring volleyball war.
S-E-I-- huh?
She's cute.
Yeah, she's hot.
You should be
rooting for our team.
You said it.
That one cheerleader's
baton has practically
knocked out all our players.
Let's go Seishun.
Go, go, Seishun!
What do you think you're doing?
Explain yourself!
Who?
Me?
C-H-E-E-R.
C-H--
Cheerleading!
By the way, I noticed
your gym shirt.
It spells out F-U-R-I-N,
meaning floozy.
Girls in high school
shouldn't walk around
with things like
that on their shirts,
no matter what their
lifestyle choices are--
Hmm?
Flooz-- Furin!
As in Furinkan High!
How dare you insult
my high school name!
If you call yourself
a cheerleader,
why don't you just
stick to cheerleading.
You twinkies are
kidding yourself
if you think these mind
games are gonna psych us out.
Oh yeah?
Well, let's just see about that.
CHEERLEADERS: Give me an E. E!
Give me an I. I!
Give me an S. S!
Give me an H. H!
Give me a U. U!
You're a cheater.
Sports are supposed to be
played fair and square,
not by knocking
the other team out.
In that case, maybe
you better stop talking
and get back to the court.
REFEREE: Game and set.
Seishun wins.
Yay!
Seishun rocks.
We're the best.
We will put you to the test!
Seishun rocks.
Go Seishun!
Hey, look at that cheerleader.
Doesn't she look kind
of familiar to you?
Yeah, that's Mariko
Konjo, isn't it?
So that's what that cute
little hottie's name is, huh?
She's considered the
goddess of Seishun High.
They win every single
game she cheers for.
I heard somewhere they're
called the Martial Arts
Cheerleading Team.
Martial Arts Cheerleading Team?
Over here, Mariko.
I'm so famous.
Hm?
I can't believe we lost.
Don't cry, Akane.
You played great.
Yeah, you have
nothing to cry about.
But it's so unfair!
Come on, Ranma.
Can't you do something to
try and cheer Akane up?
March right over there,
and take her in your arms,
and tell her there, there.
I'm here for you.
Yeah, like that's
ever gonna happen!
There, there, Akane Tendo.
Kuno's here for you, girl.
Tell it to the foot!
Man, what a jerk.
Ranma?
Come on.
That's enough crying.
I wonder what's the
matter with Mariko.
You'd think she'd
be happy that we won.
Hmm.
Feels like something's missing.
It figures.
Mariko's always
depressed after we win.
Why's that?
Seishun cheerleaders, our
victory is my own F-A-T-E--
my fate.
But girls, I still feel there's
something missing from my life.
That's L-O-V-E-- love.
A life without love
is like a cheerleader
with half a pom-pom.
Oh, Mariko!
Ugh.
Uh-oh.
That'll hurt.
Here you are.
Please, forgive my intrusion and
good luck with your welt. Beg
your pardon.
No, wait!
Won't you tell me who you are?
Tatewake Kuno, the captain
of the Furinkan Kendo Team,
age 17.
MARIKO (VOICEOVER)::
K-U-N-O-- Kuno.
It's the first time any boy
has ever been this nice to me.
F-I-R-S-T L-O-V-E-- first love.
Man, a makeup test in
the morning really blows.
Things just get better.
How I've longed for
you, my pigtailed girl.
It's too early in the
morning for your bull, doofus.
Please, I need
to speak with you.
One, two, one, two, one, two.
Next week, we will be
having a kendo tournament
at Furinkan High School.
Am I supposed to care?
Of course I can count on
you cheer for me, right,
my pigtailed girl?
Yeah.
Huh?
Who are you?
I'll T-E-LL you.
I'm Kuno's personal cheerleader,
and the name is M-A-R-I-K-O--
Mariko.
Got a problem with that?
Wow, cheerleaders!
Kendo Team!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): She's the one
that made Akane cry yesterday.
What's the deal
with you and Kuno?
We're lovers.
I don't think so.
What happened to you, Kuno?
Just a love tap.
So if I were to
cheer for Kuno, then
what would you do about it?
If so, then you and I
would become enemies.
Suits me fine.
Oh, Kuno?
When's the match?
V-I-C-T-O-R-Y.
Mean V-I-C-T-O-R-Y--
that's V for victory.
My, wonderful.
Think you can
outdo me with that?
I know I can beat you.
I guarantee it.
Ranma?
So what'll it be, huh?
What else?
Martial arts cheerleading, OK?
Fine.
See you a little later, Kuno.
Wish me luck.
Good luck then.
Wait for us, Mariko!
M-A-R-I-K-O-- Mariko!
I'm so happy, my
pigtailed girl,
you'll be cheering for my
victory at the upcoming--
W-R-O-N-G-- wrong.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ranma's
challenged Mariko Konjo?
MAN: I heard the pigtailed girl
is going up against the Seishun
cheerleader.
What?
A cheerleader competition?
Cheerleader competition?
Cheerleaders?
Yes.
One, two, three, four.
Pigtailed girl!
The pom-poms of my heart
quiver with excitement
that you should
practice so hard for me.
Nice shot.
Great baton attack.
All in a day's work, friends.
OK, Kuno.
Up on your feet!
K-U-N-O-- Kuno!
The stars are lovely.
MARIKO: Kuno, snap to!
Hello, who are you?
I'm Mariko Konjo.
I'm a sophomore and a captain of
the Seishun Cheerleading Team.
You must remember who I am.
It's coming back to me now.
I'm so glad, Kuno.
Get a life.
You don't stand a
chance against me.
Cheering is L-O-V-E.
If you care for someone,
a smile is all you
need to cheer them on.
Are you saying my cheerleading
is all style and no love?
That's right.
Finally, you've got it.
I'll do anything you
tell me to, Kuno.
Kuno.
Do what you will with me.
Oh man.
Lucky guy.
What's he got over us?
I'm not gonna take this.
I'll teach him a lesson.
Would you seriously do
anything for me, Mariko?
Yes, I would.
Then close your eyes.
[heart beating]
Uhh, Kuno, baby?
Huh?
[humming]
Hmm?
Oh, Kuno, you big silly.
Just kidding!
He wrote all over her face
and she didn't even get angry.
[grumbling]
I'm truly impressed.
And now the kiss.
Don't worry, Kuno.
Watch this!
L-O-V-E-- I love you, Kuno!
Let's go, Kuno.
Let's go.
She's strong.
She took out all the
school sports teams.
Sure, I did.
The Seishun Martial
Arts Cheerleading Team
does what's necessary
to support our side.
Let me explain.
We root for our team
like this and like this.
Our martial arts cheerleading
Team is the best there is.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): She won't
get away with this, not
after what she did to Akane.
Ranmaa, don't compete with
Mariko, I'm begging you.
Just power isn't enough.
In order to beat the Martial
Arts Cheerleading Team,
you need to prove your skills
by undergoing a horrible test!
What do you mean "test?"
There.
Take a look at Kuno.
I truly feel encouraged
by her cheers.
K-U-N-O-- Kuno!
Mariko, I've come to see how
deep your love runs for me.
Is it my imagination or is
he getting more competent?
I think Mariko's cheering
is doing it to him.
Yeah, right.
Go, go, Kuno.
That's it, girl.
Keep it coming.
Why you presumptuous little--
Well, there goes
his confidence.
'Cause nobody's
cheering for him.
Cheer up, Kuno.
Go get 'em, Kuno.
Yes, I'm back!
His confidence is back.
If you wanna beat
me, you'll have
to prove that you care
for Kuno more than I do.
Oh, Kuno, I love you.
Oh yeah.
Who's the man?
Oh no!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
The only way to beat
Mariko is to prove I care
for Kuno more than her.
Right.
That must be the nasty test
Akane was talking about.
Can I muster up the strength
somehow to love Kuno?
Oh, Kuno, wait for me!
Oh, my pigtailed girl.
Kuno?
Pigtailed girl.
No, I can't do it.
Imagining it was
more than enough.
Ranma.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Must be strong.
Must have guts.
She's getting up.
OK, I'll prove that I
love him more than you.
But be warned.
I've never lost a single
fight in my entire life.
And I don't plan
to lose this one.
Even better.
Don't forget to bring
your crying towel.
Say what?
You heard.
I'm so loved.
The winner gets Kuno's
love, and the loser
ends up with nothing.
That's way too harsh.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ranma, what
are you getting yourself into?
This is crazy.
Tell Mariko you're backing out.
Cork it.
You don't stand a
chance against her.
There's less than a week left
to get ready before Kuno's kendo
match, you know?
How do you expect to
fall deeply in love
with Kuno in such a short time?
Hmph.
You don't need time
to fall in love.
Ranma?
Huh?
Ranma, how dare you turn your
back on my lovely daughter
here and give yourself to
another man, of all things.
Can you leave us
alone for once?
Here.
But Akane!
Hmph.
Ranma, what are
you planning to do?
I'm not really sure, but I
don't want you to question me
on this one, Akane.
I can't afford to lose this
competition with Mariko Konjo.
This is crazy.
So what if you win?
Why is this so important to you?
Huh?
You moron!
Who do you think I went
into this competition for?
You mean it's for me?
You're doing all this for me?
You would go that
far for me, Ranma?
Well, it's nothing like that.
Huh?
In the name of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts--
What's going on?
I'll prove I can love
Kuno with the best of them.
And you'll see.
I'll win this competition.
Give him all your love, Ranma.
Oh my.
I'll beat him.
I'll bust him, 'cause
that's Ranma's custom.
Go Ranma!
That's what I wanted
to hear, pigtailed girl.
Good luck, my little
pigtailed girl.
I love you!
Man, that guy gives
me the heebie-jeebies.
Ranma.
G-O-O-D-N-I-G-H-T-- good
night, my sweet Kuno.
No one will ever love
you more than I do.
Ranma.
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Oh, Ranma, please stop
trying to love Kuno.
That's It.
If you have to love
someone, why not me?
Next time on "Ranma
1/2," Bring It On.
Love as Cheerleader Part 2.
We'll see you there.