[music playing]
[theme music]
Where have you gotten
to, my sweet Shampoo?
Shampoo, where are you?
At least answer me, Shampoo.
Oh, there you are, you
naughty little vixen.
Huh?
I don't remember you
feeling so cold and rigid.
[scream]
Mousse, why you
talk to clay cat?
Oh, Shampoo!
That's where you were.
Mousse want something?
Deliver this.
[groan]
Shampoo busy reading book.
Mousse make delivery.
But the guy who called
wants you to deliver it.
Customer want Shampoo?
[meowing]
The cat temple on Fifth Street.
This is it.
Ni hao!
Noodle delivery!
[meowing]
That funny.
No one here.
Yoo-hoo!
Noodle delivery!
Rude to order food
and no be home.
Anybody in here?
[creak]
[gasp]
Huh?
[rattling]
Hi-ya!
Glad you could make it.
[gasp]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Shampoo's Cursed Kiss.
Man, I'm so hungry I
could eat your food.
Shampoo!
Where are you, my sweet Shampoo?
[gasp]
Thank goodness I
finally found you!
Look again, wiz kid!
They work better when
they're on your face.
Ranma!
Setting up Akane as Shampoo
was a dirty stunt to pull.
Listen, goon.
AKANE: Are you serious?
RANMA: Shampoo's missing?
That's right.
She hasn't come
back from a delivery
I sent her on this morning.
But it's already
late in the afternoon.
Without her, the shop
is practically doomed.
No.
It's not the business.
It's Shampoo's safety
that I'm worried about.
Oh, Shampoo!
Mousse, you already checked out
the delivery place, didn't you?
Uh.
Hey, how come I
didn't think of that?
[groan]
Why is it nothing
he says surprises me?
Come on, Mousse.
Let's go to the delivery
place and see if she made it.
You lead the way.
You mean, you're going
to come there with me?
[crying]
Oh, thank you, Ranma.
Thanks!
[groan]
Give it a rest.
Once was more than enough.
[meowing]
So Shampoo hasn't
come back since she
left to make a delivery here?
Nope.
But it doesn't make any sense.
This temple has been
closed down for ages.
Has it?
Huh?
Come on, guys.
Yoo-hoo!
Ranma!
Huh?
Shampoo here, Ranma, darling!
Look.
She's right in front of us.
We've been looking for you!
[groan]
Ranma come for Shampoo?
Huh?
Hey!
That's a little too close.
Hands off him, Shampoo.
Yeah, Ranma here.
Whatever.
Come on, Ranma.
Let's get out of here.
Huh?
Uh, yeah.
Wait!
What is this?
Hang on, Akane.
What?
Look!
I-- I can't get out.
Quit fooling around, would you?
But I'm not fooling around.
I'm stuck in here.
[sigh]
Ranma never escape
as long as Shampoo
hold Ranma tight in arms.
What?
Huh?
Don't be stupid, Shampoo!
Let go of him!
SHAMPOO: No!
Shampoo no let go.
You're killing me.
[gasp]
[coughing]
Shampoo never let go!
What's gotten into you?
[laughter]
Huh?
You're too late.
I've cast a spell on
Shampoo, and soon she's
going to be my lovely bride.
[scream]
You did what?
I know you.
You're Maomolin,
that spirit who's
been looking for a bride
for over 3,000 years
but could never find even
a single woman to accept
your proposal because you're
just a good for nothing,
shaggy, old ghost cat.
Hey!
You're blowing my cover, girl.
You did this to her?
[laughter]
I've made myself the
temple master here.
Shampoo will never be
able to escape from me.
You hideous monster!
Why are you keeping
my Shampoo from me?
The obvious!
I've trapped Shampoo in my
temple to make her my bride!
That flea bag just doesn't
know when to give up.
Shampoo!
Tell me it ain't so.
[sigh]
Shampoo must stay
this temple and be
stuck with evil monster cat.
Oh, this terrible tragedy!
[laughter]
Isn't there some way
to break the spell?
Only one way break spell.
No.
Nothing will break the spell.
What?
Listen.
[scream]
Glad you could make it.
[laughter]
[gasp]
[scream]
What you say now?
Call for your uncle?
Uncle!
But it's too late now.
Because I cast the
spell on you the instant
you stepped into the temple.
What you talk about?
I'm the only one who
can break the spell.
I'll never let you
leave this temple again.
You'll stay here
and become my bride.
[scream]
Hitting me won't
change anything.
[stick dropping]
Huh?
Why so quiet?
No resist.
Huh?
Shampoo stop
resisting her destiny.
I knew you'd come around.
But Shampoo no become cat wife.
Shampoo choose this fate.
[scream]
No!
Don't do it!
You're too lovely!
And I don't want to start
searching for another bride!
Please!
If cat feel that way,
then let Shampoo go.
You're taking tough
love to new heights.
[whimpering]
Tell me what you want.
Anything!
Shampoo have young prince
she deep in love with.
If Shampoo get
kiss from that man,
then Shampoo want ghost
cat to break magic spell.
[groan]
I can't do that.
[gasp]
That leave Shampoo one choice.
[scream]
All right!
I'll go along with it.
OK.
Then chop-chop and
make deal official.
You're a tough cookie.
This requires snake
eye concentration.
[meowing]
Oh, Ranma, my prince.
Hurry and rescue Shampoo
form this temple.
Huh.
I don't think so.
Ranma, you help Shampoo
and give big kiss on lips.
Wait!
What kind of deal's
that, Shampoo?
Shampoo can no change spell.
Now official.
But you're the one
who suggested it.
Why'd you rope
Ranma into it for?
Hi-ya!
You want Shampoo to
explain real reason?
Jeez!
Would you two knock
it off already?
Shampoo, I'm your
handsome prince,
and I'm here to break the
magic spell cast on you!
You no handsome prince.
My love!
[ringing]
Huh?
[scream]
Oh, good, cats!
[humming]
Yoo-hoo!
What's going on?
Something happen to you, Ranma?
Huh?
A herd of cats.
My, so you left Shampoo
back there at the temple
after the cats mauled you?
Yeah, sort of.
You ran away with your
tails between your legs.
So much for your backgrounds
in martial arts, you two.
We can rescue her
tomorrow or something.
Ranma, can't you grow up
and be a man just this one?
Lousy ghost cat.
I won't let him
get away with this.
The ghost cat?
You called?
Huh?
[scream]
That cat!
How'd it get in here?
You're Maomolin--
the cat that's
been looking for a bride
for over 3,000 years
but can't find anyone crazy
enough to accept his proposal.
Uh-huh.
I forgot to mention something.
Good timing.
We've got something
to ask you, ghost cat.
What's that?
Is kissing Ranma
the only way Shampoo
can break that magic spell?
Ah, a kiss, huh?
Oh, my.
[groan]
Why is it that Ranma always
gets the most enviable jobs,
and the rest of us are
left with the crud?
Dad, will you two
stay out of this?
Huh?
Ghost cat, what's your answer?
Let me explain a few things.
Take a seat.
By the time the temple
bell rings 108 times
tonight, if she's not
kissed by her prince,
she will never
escape from my temple
and will be completely
and permanently a cat
and can never turn
into a human again.
[laughter]
AKANE: You're not serious!
GIRL: Sounds pretty
serious to me.
GIRL: Oh, what a cute kitty.
So stay away from
the temple tonight.
Meow.
Huh?
Stay away from me, cat.
[coughing]
What kind of powder was that?
Powder?
Ah.
Ranma, are you OK?
Lousy flea bag,
busting into our house
like a common cat burglar.
[animal sounds]
[humming "here comes the bride"]
[laughter]
(VOICEOVER) Ranma, hurry
up and rescue Shampoo.
Now, now, Shampoo.
There's no reason to be afraid.
Meow.
We're going to make
a beautiful family.
[scream]
[groan]
That what you think!
Sorry, my sweetness.
RANMA: Shampoo!
[gasp]
Ranma!
Where are you?
He's come.
Shampoo!
Shampoo waiting for
you, my darling Ranma.
Some things just can't
be helped, Shampoo.
I'll kiss you this
time, but don't
go getting any funny ideas!
[gasp]
[scream]
Let's make it some other time!
I will return!
What's his problem?
Ranma no like kitty?
[laughter]
That catnip really
gets them worked up.
[gasp]
Wait.
That'll stop you from
getting close to Shampoo
until the bells have tolled!
[laughter]
Hi-ya!
Tragic turn of event.
[bell]
Huh?
(VOICEOVER) The ghost cat said
that when the bell had run 108
times, Shampoo would
completely turn into a cat.
[bell]
[groan]
AKANE: A catnip outfit?
[laughter]
The scent of
catnip on this shirt
is a lot stronger than the
scent of that catnip powder
I got all over me.
Wait.
Hold on a second.
If you wear that shirt,
then the cats, uh-- huh?
Huh?
While you're busy distracting
the temple cats away from me,
I'll go and kiss Shampoo and
break the ghost cat's spell.
Oh.
Now I get it.
Hm.
I hope these people
appreciate my intelligence.
Huh?
Hm.
(YELLING) Why don't you
wear the stinking shirt?
[scream]
Ah!
The humanity!
[music playing]
A fishy ball?
[laughter]
Cats like nothing better
than toys that move.
And to make it more appealing
and totally irresistible,
I have covered it in
the scent of fresh fish.
I'm going in!
[grunt]
[meowing]
Later, suckers.
Shampoo!
Huh?
Come here, my beloved.
I'll save you with my kiss!
Don't think so.
[groan]
You're not still here.
Out of my way!
[gasp]
[groan]
[muffled scream]
[scream]
[meowing]
[music playing]
I was so close, too.
If only Mousse
hadn't interfered.
[bell]
Huh?
How many times has
the bell rung now?
I haven't really
been keeping track
but about 40 or
50 times, I guess.
That many?
We're running out of time.
[gasp]
Damn it.
Ghost cat's rigged it so I can't
even get anywhere near Shampoo.
Hey, Ranma, look at me.
[sigh]
That Maomolin's going to pay.
I'm talking over here!
What do you want now?
What do you think of this plan?
What if you took off those
stinky catnip clothes
and went in the temple
in other clothes?
Then maybe you could get in
without the cats licking you
to death.
Aha!
Moron.
Shampoo, I've
come to the rescue!
[gasp]
Ranma!
Nah, nah.
You've made it
inside, but you're not
going to take my bride!
You'll have to get rid
of me first, I'm afraid.
Mommy!
Pathetic.
You monster!
[grunt]
Let me at you!
I'm sorry!
No hard feelings!
Pucker up, Shampoo!
Your prince is a-coming.
[groan]
Shampoo!
Why'd you kick your prince?
Shampoo need kiss
of prince she love!
Not some frog prince!
I know that.
And I'm telling you I'm
your prince, not Ranma.
Mousse no prince!
[scream]
What do I have to do to get
you to understand my feelings?
[sigh]
Oh, well.
Guess I'll just have
to help them out.
[gasp]
What is that?
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come on, kitty, kitty, kitty.
The lure of a cat toy.
[scream]
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come on, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come here.
Come here, kitty.
Oh, good, kitty.
That's a good kitty.
Now's my chance.
[groan]
Ranma come for Shampoo.
Come on.
Let's get it over with.
Oh, Ranma.
[gasp]
[scream]
Bad Mousse!
Not you again.
You've interrupted me
one too many times.
Ranma, you're going to
have to get through me first
if you think you're
going to kiss Shampoo.
Don't you get it?
Shampoo says it has to
be me who kisses her.
Oh, yeah?
Well, if you insist!
[groan]
[sigh]
Serves you right, you bozo.
Come on.
Let's do it, Shampoo.
Ranma.
Shampoo.
[music playing]
[cat humming]
Um, how about
closing your eyes?
Mhm.
[gulp]
[gasp]
It's just a kiss.
Don't get carried away.
Tell it like it is, Akane!
[whining noise]
[ringing]
Cat toy attack.
Very sneaky strategy.
[groan]
What?
This battle has only just begun!
Posession's--
Ranma--
9/10 of the law.
Do love Shampoo.
And Shampoo belongs to me!
[meowing]
[scream]
How dare you ignore me!
RANMA: I'll never
forgive you for this!
AKANE: If it weren't
for your stupid idea,
this would never have
happened in the first place!
[scream]
[groan]
Now where were we?
[bell]
Huh?
[groan]
Listen!
The sound of the bell.
Oh, no.
I forgot Shampoo!
Hi-ya!
[gasp]
Shampoo!
Look!
She's got cat ears.
No, wait!
[bell]
Huh?
Ah.
Shampoo will turn
completely into a cat.
[gasp]
I don't want to say this.
[groan]
But just this once,
I'll let you kiss her.
Ranma, hurry and kiss her.
But what about the cats?
Forget the cats
and kiss Shampoo!
63.
64.
Five, six.
He's striking the
bell faster and faster.
Lousy cheater.
Oh, no!
Look at Shampoo!
[meowing]
[gasp]
[groan]
[scream]
Ranma!
What's taking you so long?
74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79.
[sigh]
Akane, Mousse, kick my
back as hard as you can.
What?
Just do it!
Hurry!
All right, Ranma.
Here goes nothing.
[groan]
[scream]
That makes 107.
That smarts.
[groan]
[meowing]
And here's 108!
[gasp]
[meowing]
[scream]
[purr]
[bell]
Ranma.
[groan]
The cat.
Just in time.
The spell's been broken.
Ranma, one more kiss.
How dare you kiss
my Shampoo, Ranma!
Just in the nick of
time, eh, Shampoo?
Meow!
Another keeper,
and she got away.
I want a bride!
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): As the
spring slowly fades into summer,
a stranger comes, asking
Ranma to grant a dying wish.
Are you sure you're
going through with this?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Run Away with Me, Ranma.
We'll see you there.