[music playing]
Ranma: C'mere, you stupid freak.
-Don't wanna.
-This is it, ya hear?
You're going to get
what's coming to you.
-Yeah, yeah.
What else is new?
Hah, you're too slow
and you know it.
-Will you quit talking while
I'm trying to punish you?
-What's the matter?
You out of breath?
Here, have a drink.
Ha-ha.
Anything Goes Founding
School Final Attack.
Have no fire burns.
[yelling]
[laughing]
-What'd I tell you?
-Anything Goes Martial Arts
Founding School Final Attack?
Whoa, count me in.
NARRATOR: A formidable
new disciple appears.
Ranma: Stupid old freak.
Here I'm trying to
take a bath and you're
trying to splash
me with a bucket.
-Oh, don't be such a wuss.
-I'll teach you to play your
dirty tricks on me C'mere, you.
-Try and catch me punk.
[laughter]
-If this goes on-- If th--
if things don't change--
[bear yawning]
-How can the Anything Goes
School be expected to continue?
[grunting]
[laughter]
MAN: Anyone home?
-Good news.
A visitor.
Coming.
[laughter]
-Father.
It seems you have
a new disciple.
-Huh?
-Hm?
-Soun Tendo, owner and
proprietor of the Tendo Dojo.
So I hear you're interested
in becoming a disciple?
-Yes, sir.
My name's Genji Heita.
I'm not sure I'm worthy,
but, uh, well, I'm
hoping you'll accept me.
I promise you will
not be disappointed.
-May I ask, young man, how
you came to choose this dojo?
-Well, sir, today in town,
I had the great privilege
of seeing the one and only
master, Happosai, in action.
Heita, I said, if you could
learn technique like that,
then you'd be a real martial
artist, now, wouldn't you?
-I-- I don't think
you understand--
-So you want to be like me, huh?
-(STUDDERING) Great Master.
-I got a bad feeling about this.
-It's not going to
be easy, you know?
You ready?
-Sir, yes, sir.
I'm ready to do anything.
Just ask me.
-Well, I'll just have to
hold you to that, kid.
-Where are you going?
Shouldn't we warm up first, sir?
-Whoa, hold on a minute, son.
You don't want to distract
a great master now, do you?
-So you mean it's
part of the training?
Well, why didn't you say
so in the first place?
If it means a chance to study
Anything Goes martial arts,
there's no sacrifice in
the world too great for me.
-You-- you really feel that
strongly about learning
our techniques then?
[sobbing]
-Oh, father.
Congratulations.
-Uh, excuse me, but aren't
keeping pandas as pets illegal?
-You noticed, huh?
Well, it's not what you think.
-Me and my pop are guests.
You got a problem with that?
-I know you.
You're that guy that got
beat up by the great master.
I just want you to
know that I haven't
come to your dojo empty-handed.
This oughtta last
ya quite a while.
-Oh-- oh my.
-My goodness.
What a lot of rice.
-And when that's
gone, don't worry.
My folks run a farm, so--
-Young man, allow me
to be the very first
to welcome you to our dojo.
-I don't know what to say.
-Come along, son.
Come along.
-Sir, yes, sir.
-Geez, your dad'll take in
just about anyone, won't he?
-That's true.
He did take you and your
dad in after all, Ranma.
-Excuse me?
-Never mind.
-Man, she is so uncute.
MAN 1: Hi-ya!
MAN 2: Hi-ya!
-Hi-ya!
-Hi-ya.
OK, now you try it.
A really good kiai,
or battle yell,
is essential to the
Anything Goes technique.
Without it, you'll
never build yourself up
to the proper pitch.
-But oughtn't I learn first
the techniques of Great Master
Happo--
-All in good time, son.
All in good time.
-Right.
First things first--
or so I always say.
-Well, I guess you
know best, right?
OK, then.
Well, how about I just go
through my normal warm-up?
-There you go, son.
That's the away.
-And what would
that they be, eh?
-Oh, nothing too hard.
Punches, 2,000 Squats, 3,000.
Push-ups, 4,000.
Sit-ups, 5,000.
How many do you two do?
[grunting]
-What do you say we-- oh.
-That looks like the hole
in the roof's getting worse.
-If that keeps up, the rain's
going to ruin the floor.
-Well, that looks like
it's it for the day then.
-Or maybe I'll just go fix it.
[hammer pounding]
-Huh?
Hey.
Heita, what are you doing?
-Who, me?
Oh, I'm just fixing the roof.
-Well, you could just put
it off till later, you know?
Was it my dad's idea?
-Oh no.
It was my idea.
You see, I figure
it this way-- we
won't have to worry about the
days when it rains anymore.
-You're so responsible.
-Oh, shucks.
It was nothing.
SOUN: You still up there?
-Huh?
SOUN: I think it stopped.
-OK.
[yelling]
-Oh no.
Are you OK?
Uh, should I go get a doctor?
-Ah, don't be silly.
There's a reason they called
me Heita the He-man, you know?
[laughter]
-That was so funny.
I should've have worried.
[laughing]
-Yeah, right.
Like they're really-- huh?
[throat clears]
[laughing]
-What are you looking at?
How am I supposed to
read with you sitting
there making them
cow eyes at me?
Go find someone else's
room to sleep in, you hear?
-So why the heck's he gotta
stay in here with us, huh?
-It's part of the training,
boy, so deal with it.
-Oh dear, you needn't do that.
-Really, it's no problem.
I like doing it.
-I must say, that new
disciple is really something.
He's such a help.
-Yeah, it's true all right.
That strong and humble type's
pretty rare these days.
-He's like the complete
opposite of your current fiance.
Say, why don't you and he--
-(SHOUTING) That's enough, OK?
-What did I say?
-Perhaps your timing is bad.
But you must admit,
Akane, she has a point.
-You stay out of this.
-You gonna sit there and let
him talk about you like that?
-Like I really care.
-You will care when we get
thrown out on our butt.
-Hey, Mr. Dumber than Ox wants
to marry Ms. Built Like an Ox,
let him do it.
They deserve each other.
-What did you say?
Hey, come back here.
Ranma, I'm talking to you.
[music playing]
[gasping]
-(SHOUTING) Akane!
-Hey, look out.
-Ryoga, you stupid--
-(SHOUTING) Ranma,
this is gonna be it!
Here's for what
you did to Akane.
-You're the one who started
it, you stupid jerk.
I'm gonna--
-You're finished, Ranma.
I'm gonna-- huh?
-Hm?
-What do you think you're doing?
Put me down.
-Ryoga, Akane's
told me all about
how you and Ranma
always seem to fight.
-And?
-Is fighting all the time the
way you really want to live?
Don't you realize, the
best part of being young
is making friends
and not enemies?
Don't you?
-Huh?
-Isn't there something
else, something important
you'd rather be
doing with your life?
-Something else I
should be doing?
-Please, don't be a fool
and waste your life.
Youth comes only once.
You've no time to waste.
-(GASPING) He's right.
I have been a fool.
Why have I been
wasting time when
it's been obvious all along?
HEITA: Then you understand
what it is I'm telling you?
-I've missed
something, haven't I?
-You want to run with
me into the sunset?
-I do.
-(TOGETHER) One, two one, two,
one, two, one, two, one, two,
one, two.
-Hm.
What a bunch of losers.
Who needs them, anyone?
-If I to pick someone,
I'd say you do.
-If you're suggesting
I couldn't have kicked
Ryoga's butt without
dum dum, you're wrong.
-Am I?
I guess we'll just see
about that, won't we?
-What did you just--
[grunting]
-Uncute, Unsexy, un--
[grunts]
[music playing]
KASUMI: Time for breakfast.
Would you like--
HEITA: Let me finish
off the hall first, OK?
-Such a hard worker.
-One might even go so far
as to say he works too hard.
Especially for someone
who doesn't pay any rent.
[chuckling nervously]
-Are you calling
me a freeloader?
-Did I say that?
-But your eyes,
Tendo-- your eyes.
-Hey, this is good.
-Is this one of your
new recipes, Kasumi?
-Believe it or
not, Heita made it.
-Wow.
A martial artist who
can actually cook.
-Can I be excused?
Well, he's a lot better than
you, Akane, by a long shot.
-What did you say?
[grunting]
-Akane.
Runma.
It's not good to fight.
-Gee, what gives you that idea?
-Oh boy, did I say
something to make him mad?
[GRUNTING
[music playing]
-I'm done with the shopping.
-Oh my.
[music playing]
[sighing]
[footsteps approaching]
-Hm?
-Ranma, this can't go on
much longer, you know?
-Why can't it?
-The more he does
for this family,
the more you and I start
to look like a couple
of no good freeloaders?
-Aren't we, though?
-For all we know, he could
even be planning steal Akane?
-And I should care?
-Well, perhaps
you've forgotten what
it was like before
we came to live here.
[music playing]
-Why can't you follow Heita's
example and make yourself, huh?
-Well, if it's a
handyman they want,
they're better off without us.
We're supposed to be martial
artists, not a couple
of suck-ups trying to
prove what god in-laws
we could be because we can
cook dinner and clean windows
and sew hems.
-(SHOUTING) Do you
want to be homeless?
-Pop, why not just admit
you're worried for yourself
and you couldn't
care less about me?
-Course not.
(STUDDERING) Let's
just a minute, boy.
Let's talk it over.
[shouting]
[bear grumbling]
KASUMI: Heita's late.
I'm worried.
-How can it be sukiyaki
without the meat?
-Perhaps he's, uh, merely lost.
-Why don't you go and
look for him, eh, boy?
-Sorry.
Too hungry.
Eh.
-It's OK.
I'll go.
-Ignore him, will ya?
He'll be back.
-Oh, like you even care.
HEITA: OK, I'm back.
-Hm?
-Well, am I right or what?
[stomping]
-So hungry.
-I could eat a horse.
-A cow even.
-Did somebody ask for beef?
-Now that's what
I call a disciple.
-Forget it.
I don't want to know.
[fighting grunts]
-He's gotten a lot
better, hasn't he?
-Maybe, but he's still
not as fast as Ranma.
-Ah, but speed's
not the only thing.
Mental discipline's
important, too.
Here, let me show
you what I mean.
-(SHOUTING) Hey,
what do you know?
A pork bun!
-Where?
Where is it?
Where?
[yelling]
-Where is it?
Where'd he go?
-Saotome, would you please?
-The pork bun.
Where did it go?
-You gluttonous fool.
I can't believe you fell for
a stupid trick like that.
-But pork buns are my favorite.
-Shut up, rube.
Genji Heita, I, Great
Master Happosai,
do hereby acknowledge your
powers of concentration.
-Sir, may this lowly
disciple be allowed
to finally spar with you then?
-Yeah, right.
What kind of program do you
think I'm running here anyway?
Come on, follow me.
-Where are they?
Where's the pork buns?
Where are they?
Where?
Where'd they go?
Where are they?
Where?
-Saotome, please!
-Here.
-What is this for?
-That, my boy, is the key to
unlocking your full potential
as a martial artist.
Take care of it and
it'll take care of you.
Here, let me show
you how it's done.
First you unfold it.
Then you flip it
around like this.
Not bad.
Not bad for your first time.
Looks pretty good on
you, too, I must say.
-You really think so?
You don't think it makes
me look like a thief?
-Don't criticize what
you don't understand.
So you with me or not?
-Great Master, wait up.
-OK, did you get that?
Your advanced training's
going to start over there.
HEITA: "Girls dressing room"?
HAPPOSAI: Shh,
what are you trying
to do, blow the whole deal?
-But Great Master, are
you absolutely sure
we've got to do my
advanced training here?
-Now listen.
You don't think that I got to
be the great martial artist I am
today by questioning teachers
and ignoring instructions,
do you?
-It's not that I
don't trust you.
It's just--
[gasps]
-Obedience, opportunity,
an eye for quality.
These are the things
a martial artist must
learn if they're to be
a success a-- what the?
-I'm sorry, but Great Master,
stealing is just plain wrong.
-Stealing?
Stealing?
How dare you insult the craft?
-But I--
-No buts.
Why I oughtta--
[girls giggling]
-Uh-oh.
GIRL 1: OK OK.
GIRL 2: See, what?
Gee, I'm sorry,
but you're a loser
and I can't see you anymore.
[groaning]
[women gasping]
-Amateur!
How could you?
-Gross.
It's that dirty old man again.
-Shame on you.
-Don't leave me.
[yelling]
HEITA: It's not what you think?
It hurts.
-Boy, you can do it.
Hang in there.
-How dare you do that to me.
-Would ya lower your voice.
Why, if it weren't
for you, my haul
would've been twice that big.
-Are you crazy?
You can't just go around
stealing girls' underwear.
Don't you know that it's wrong?
-You know what these are?
These aren't just
girls' underwear.
They're a symbol of something
as big as the world itself.
They're fireworks in summer,
presents at Christmas,
a nap when you're tired.
These panties, my boy,
are a work of art.
-I, uh, guess I never really
thought of it that way before,
Master.
-Obviously not.
If you had, you would
never have challenged me.
Well, shall we be off?
[music playing]
[girls yelling]
-Great Master, please.
-Well, how many did
ya-- hubba hubba!
Come to papa.
You're forgiven.
Good job, Heita.
You--
[gagging]
-You moron.
Where's the artistic
sense in these?
-I'm sorry, Great Master.
-Huh?
Hey, how's it going?
-Akane?
-Training to increase
concentration.
-It's the final
step in my training.
Unless I can meet
the challenge, I
won't be allowed to spar
with Great Master Happosai.
-Hey, I can see why
you're depressed.
Don't be.
I just know that you can do it.
You're not going to
give up, are you?
-Akane, I--
-Have faith in yourself.
Think of everything that you've
accomplished up until now.
-You-- you give me
hope that I can-- OK.
I'm going to do it.
Just watch me.
-Now that's more like it.
[girls yelling]
GIRL: Get out of here!
Get out of here!
[yelling]
-Which one of you
took my underwear?
-Geez, Akane.
Don't look at me.
-Ours have gone
missing, too, you know.
-Would ya quit yelling?
It's early.
-Well, I don't suppose
you took our underwear.
-Me?
I wouldn't touch your toxic
jockeys if you paid me.
Go ask the freak, why don't you?
Freak.
Hand over that under--
[sobbing]
-It's all gone.
-Just give them back
their stupid undies.
You should hear the way
they've been complaining.
-(SOBBING) You haven't
seen them, have you?
My collection's gone
without a trace.
-(TOGETHER) Gone?
-You mean yours are gone, too?
-Wow, I think he's serious.
-Well, who would've
taken them then?
[rumbling]
-Oh dear, earthquake!
-What was that?
-The garden.
Quick.
-What the--
-Geez. it's huge.
-Oh my.
-What's going on back here?
-We heard a noise.
-What in the--
AKANE: Oh, gross,
those are mine.
HAPPOSAI: Hey, that's
part of my collection.
RANMA: But who the
heck would've--
Hello, Akane.
Hello, Great Master.
-Heita?
-How sweet it is!
Oh.
-Well, master, does
this mean I passed?
-Heita, my boy, consider
yourself an A student.
-OK.
That's it.
I give up.
He can have it all.
So you and him taking
over the dojo, huh?
-Now, now, son.
Don't rush.
I just know you and Akane
can work things out.
-Akane?
If it wasn't for
your pep talk, I
would've never
had the confidence
to steal all that underwear.
I don't know how to thank you.
-But that wasn't the reason
I-- say something, Ranma.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
RANMA: Guess you need me
more than you thought, huh?
[music playing]
AKANE: Would you
cut it out already?
He's just a kid.
And besides, his
health is so delicate.
You don't want to hurt
his recovery, do you?
Next time on Ranma
1/2, "Step Outside."
We'll see you there.