[music playing]
HAPPOSAI: Ta-da!
Take a peak.
Did I get me a haul or what?
-Incredible.
In just one night?
-Master, please, please.
May I remind you
that some of us still
have to live in
this neighborhood?
-How could you?
How could you be so cruel as
to take away the one and only
pleasure of a lonely,
feeble, dying invalid?
[crying]
Is torturing an old man
that much fun for you?
Take me now, I
don't want to live.
I'd rather be gone--
gone, I tell you.
-But master, we only--
-Some invalid-- that
nasty little pervert
is going to outlive all of us.
-Nabiki!
--[sigh] Just so you
know, young lady,
I was gonna give you a present.
But now, I'm gonna have to
give it to Akane instead.
Where is Akane?
-She's upstairs--
-With Ranma.
They're all alone
doing who knows what.
-The-- they're-- they're what?
ANNOUNCER: "Ryoga's Tendo
Dojo Houseguest Diary."
[fast footsteps]
-I'm very disappointed in you.
How can you let a loser
like him into your room
when you've got me?
OK, you two.
Break it up.
Break it--
-And what makes you think
I invited you in here?
-Ow, that really--
-Hey, I remember this stuff.
It's math.
-Well, duh.
What did you think
we were doing?
Ranma's behind in his studies,
so I'm tutoring him for a test.
OK?
-Oh, yeah right.
Like I'd choose spend time with
her if I didn't really have to.
-It's a good thing I've got
P-chan here to keep me company
and not you.
Who needs you anyway?
Right, baby?
[gasp]
-Oink.
Oink.
-How gross!
-Hm?
Hm?
-Go sell it somewhere else.
-It's OK, baby.
He's all gone.
-Oh, like we wouldn't
really notice it was him.
-Look, let's just go
back to studying, OK?
-Oh, come on, Akane.
It's not like I can figure
out what's going on.
-You just gotta
keep trying, Ranma.
That's all.
Why don't you play by
yourself for awhile.
OK, baby?
-[squeal]
-You just go like this, see?
-But I thought--
wait, now I get it.
-You see, was that so hard?
-P-chan, what's the matter?
-Ain't you got it easy.
You ain't gotta do algebra,
ain't gotta go to school,
ain't gotta do nothing but
eat, and sleep, and shake
your little butt for attention.
-[squeal]
-Hey!
Cut it out.
What-- what are you doing?
-Ranma!
Cut it out.
What's the matter with
you?-- picking on a pig.
-Don't look at me.
I didn't start it.
-I'm sorry, P-chan.
Next time Ranma's
mean to you like
that, I'm gonna beat
him up personally.
OK?
-[squealing]
-P-chan?
What was that all about, huh?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Oh, Akane.
Even if I do get to spend time
with you as your pet, P-chan,
there's a whole other
side to your life
I don't know-- your
life as someone
who enjoys her
studies, who enjoys
being with her friends,
who's a part of campus life.
FEMALE STUDENT: Come on!
[laughter]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Campus
life-- now that brings me back.
Who knows, if I'd
never met Ranma,
I could have had a
whole different life.
[laughter]
-Stop it!
What the heck am I thinking?
I've gotta concentrate on
defeating Ranma right now.
There's no time
for anything else.
-That was close.
From now on, I
gotta keep my mind
on what I'm doing--
namely, beating Ranma.
OK, no more distractions.
[laughter]
[screaming]
-How's it going, girls?
Did you miss me?
-Why you dirty old man, how
dare you come to this school?
-You pervert!
-He's always doing this.
-You're so gross.
What's the matter,
can't meet our eyes?
-Uh, Ryoga?
-So what are you doing here?
-That was great.
Thank you.
Without your help,
we would never
have been able to catch
that nasty old man.
-You didn't catch me for long.
-Hey, you come back here.
-So what school are you from?
-Huh?
Well, I-- I, uh--
-With all the
perverts around here,
we could sure use more
like you at this school.
-You should come here as
transfer student or something.
-Huh?
-Akane, I'm guessing that he
must be a friend of yours,
right?
You should try and
talk him into it.
-O-- OK.
-Akane, I--
-Hey, why not?
You never did tell me
why you quit school.
But you know it's
never too late.
You can come back.
Why don't you try to take
the placement test for here
and see if you can get in?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Me, going
to the same school as Akane?
Tha-- that would be--
-That would be the
ultimate dream!
-Uh, what?
Oh, well I, uh-- I, uh--
[laughing hysterically]
KASUMI: A placement test?
AKANE: Uh-huh.
I'll tutor him myself.
I figure he can stay over for
a while in order to get ready.
-What's one more freeloader
at this point, right?
Although, I suppose that--
-It's the least we can do
for a fellow martial artist.
Besides, hospitality is
practically our motto.
-If there's anything
you need, let me know.
-Thank you.
I appreciate it.
-I've been living here is
P-chan a long time now.
Finally, I'll be under one
roof with Akane as a man.
-Well, you know, I gotta
hand it to you, man.
Figures you gotta pick
our school, right?
Of all the places for
dropout to drop back in,
you want the one where
the principal's nut
job and the girls either dress
like boys or act like them.
[laughs]
-So I take it this
means you'll be
studying for that
test on your own?
So Ryoga, you ready to
go upstairs to my room?
-Oh, OK.
I'm leaving now.
-[groaning]
-Did you hear that, Ranma?
They're going upstairs
to be all alone.
Well?
Come on, admit it.
Aren't you jealous?
Not even a little bit?
Well?
Well?!
-Not even.
If you're so jealous,
why don't you
transfer and start
studying, huh?
-Don't mind if I do, actually.
Happy and Akane sitting
in a tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G.
-Why, you-- ain't you
never heard of shame?
-Apparently not.
-Come here before I--
-Can't you see
what's going on here?
That delinquent is
using this opportunity
to get close to your fiance.
Can't you see that
she's a danger?
-You're the only one who's
dangerous around here.
-Oh yeah?
Then tell me what
those two are doing.
-What?
Excuse me, would you
mind getting off my lap?
[screams]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Oh no,
I forgot I wasn't P-chan
and I did what I usually do.
-[screaming]
-Ryoga, you no good,
dirty little sneak.
-Ranma, cut it out!
He's trying to study, OK?
-He's trying to do what?
-Does this look
like he's studying?
-How sweet.
-Wh--where did you get those?
-You don't come across sparklies
like these every day, you know?
It must be a gift
from the heavens
on account of my good behavior.
-I'll give you good behavior.
-Gotta go!
-Oh no you don't.
Now will you be good?
-We should probably
just try to ignore them.
Is that OK?
-Sure.
Uh-huh.
RANMA: Get back here, you
little-- why you little freak.
HAPPOSAI: You gotta
move faster than that.
-[growls]
-You see?
Now she's locked the door.
[heart beating]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
Alone, at last.
Here, with her.
In her own room.
-So you see, x plus y equals 4.
Easy, huh?
-What?
Oh, oh yeah.
I see.
-Then let's keep going.
-Akane?
-Yeah.
-Can I-- can I ask why
you're being so nice to me?
-Huh?
Well, because I like you, silly.
-You-- you-- you like me?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): She does.
She really does.
-Oh, Ryoga.
-Ry-- Ryoga?
-Huh?
[screams]
-Would you sell
it somewhere else?
-Honestly?
AKANE: Morning.
MALE STUDENT: How's it going?
-Listen, I'm gonna
tell you one more time,
I'd better not catch
you interrupting Ryoga.
-You listen, because
I'm not you're problem.
The old freak's the one who
won't let them study, not me.
[growling]
-Kasumi?
-Yes?
-What's Ryoga up to?
-Well, when Akane's
in school, he
goes to the Dojo and studies.
-He does, does he?
Well, what an
admirable young man.
HAPPOSAI: What's that?
Hey, let me see.
Come on.
Where?
What's that?
Will you just let me-- hey!
-Would you mind
cutting that out?
I'm trying to get
some studying done.
-Well!
You won't mind if I
show it around then.
-Do it and you're dead.
-I am, am I?
Ready when you are, punk.
-[growling]
-What's the matter?
Don't you want to fight?
-What'd I say?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): With
you beside me, Akane,
I can't seem to concentrate.
Oh, Akane, just put me in a
corner and forget about me.
Is that too much to ask?
-Uh, excuse me.
Which way is Furinkan
High School again?
-Well, first you go
straight this way.
-Thank you.
STUDENTS: Bye.
See you tomorrow.
Don't forget your homework-- oh!
-[groaning]
-Jeez, what's the
matter with you?
I finally made it.
--[chuckles] If it's Akane you're
looking for, then she's already
gone home.
Ironic, ain't it punk?
-Ranma!
Is it that much fun
for you to laugh at me?
-Yeah, bring it on, pal.
-[groaning]
-Hm?
-OK, listen.
I've got a great idea.
Just keep this on
your hand until you've
passed the placement exam.
And then you won't be
distracted by fighting anymore.
Promise, K?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
She's so good to me.
How can I possibly go
back on my promise?
-Hey, hey, where'd you go?
Snap out of it.
I said, what's the
matter with you?
Huh?
-Aw man, you're grossing me out.
Suit yourself.
Huh?
-Hey-- hey, whe--
where you going?
Wait!
-If you want to fight,
then let's fight.
Otherwise, leave me alone.
-I-- I know you don't
like me, but please,
could you at least just
show me the way home?
-Huh?
[laughter]
-Seriously.
Just like a kid.
-So Ryoga, how are
your studies going?
-Uh, not so good.
-He'd be fine if it
weren't for certain people.
-I ain't bothering him, OK?
-I've got it.
Ryoga, why don't we just pull
an all-nighter in my room?
[gasping]
-Should I make you some
snacks for later then?
-A cute teacher and
room service to boot.
Ain't you got the life?
[chuckles]
AKANE: Ryoga, come on.
I'm waiting.
-Um, well-- I'll
be right there, OK?
Soon as I can remember
which way your room is.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Just the
two of us alone 'til dawn.
I can't afford to
blow this chance.
-Huh?
OK.
There it is.
Akane, I--
Hey, this isn't Akane's room.
[crash]
[knocking]
AKANE: Come in.
It's you, right, Ryoga?
[door opens]
Don't be shy.
Come on over.
[door closes]
-Just a sec, K?
I'm making some quick
math problems for you.
Hm?
[screams]
-Huh?
Akane!
Are you OK?
Ryoga!
What'd you do to Ak-- huh?
Akane?
Akane, w-- what's wrong?
Huh?
Ryoga?
-[chuckles]
-The freak.
Why you-- what'd
you do to Akane?
-Just made sure she'd
sleep through the night.
-You what?
-Listen, stupid.
Given the chance, anybody would
take advantage of a girl alone
at night, much less
what's-his-face.
That's why I'm here.
To make sure nothing happens.
Because if anything does, it's
gonna be me who does the doing.
Sayonara, sucker.
Hoo-hoo!
-Come back here!
I said, come here!
Where the heck do you think
you're taking her anyway?
-Jeez, you're stubborn.
-[screaming]
-Now that you're a girl, do
you want to come play too?
Here I come.
Admit it, isn't this
nice for a change?
-Think again.
-Now what?
You here to cause trouble?
-I hope you can
forgive me, Akane,
but I can't stand it anymore.
[yelling]
-Hey!
Ha ha!
-Come back.
Where are you taking her?
-The one to protect
Akane's gonna be me.
-She's mine!
-Come back, freak.
I said, come back.
-You'll have to do a lot better
than that, you little punk.
-Listen you, now you've
made me really mad.
I'm going to get her back
if it's the last thing I do.
[screaming]
-Hmm, gotcha.
-Goodnight, Akane.
I hope the bed bugs don't bite.
-Ranma, you're heavy.
-I can't help it, OK?
I think my legs
have stopped moving.
-How about it?
You jealous yet?
[chuckling]
-Why you--
-What are you doing?
No, don't.
I-- I wanted that there.
-Tell me something.
She usually this bad, or--
-Nope.
Usually she's a lot worse.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Oh, Akane.
I'm sorry I had to
break our promise.
Forgive me?
I should have realized that
defeating Ranma is always
gonna be my first priority.
-Oh, Ryoga.
-Whoa.
Hey, look at this.
He sent us a pineapple.
Coming from Ryoga,
that's pretty cool.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
Oh, and by the way,
I'm training in Hokkaido now.
The weather's real hot.
And I almost got bit
by a snake yesterday.
For a northern country,
this place sure is--
-It sounds more
like Okinawa to me.
KASUMI: Akane!
Would you mind going
out to the market?
-I don't mind.
-So how was the
weather in Hokkaido?
Look at you.
You got a tan, didn't you?
Didn't you?!
[squealing]
ANNOUNCER: [laughing]
You're kidding!
Happosai in love?
Well, who is she?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Happosai's Happy Heart."
We'll see you there.