[theme music]
(SINGING IN JAPANESE)
-What lovely weather.
-Do over.
-Sorry, Saotome.
No can do.
-Come on, Tendo.
Don't be so strict.
Give your old pal a break.
-Saotome, is that really any way
for a martial artist to behave?
-Huh? -Huh?
But Tendo, isn't mercy also a
quality of the martial artist?
-Once or twice, yes, Saotome.
But in your case--
-What exactly are
you implying, Tendo?
Tendo?
-Implying?
I'm not implying
anything, Saotome.
-So what is it you're
trying to say to me, Tendo?
-Not a thing.
(LAUGHING)
-Yeah, that's what I thought.
-They're such good friends.
-Genma Takes a Walk.
-Hmm.
-Geez, Pop.
It's just a dumb game, you know.
-You, too, Dad.
(GRUNTING)
-Look!
Pork pot!
-Where?
Where Is it?
You sneak.
I can't take it anymore.
That's it, Tendo.
As of now, I'm out of
your life for good.
-Hey!
Ranma, don't let
him go like that.
-Leave him alone, Akane.
It's not like he's going to
go stomping off by himself.
-That's right, because
you're coming with me.
-Wha--
-So why in the heck I
gotta go with ya for, huh?
-Because I say so.
-Ranma?
Hey, Dad!
Say something.
-Could it be that he's
choking on that potato he ate?
-Do you think we should
call the ambulance?
-(SIGH) See ya.
-Sure thing.
-I bet the hour's pretty late.
Still, even I
should-- What's that?
Who's out there?
Oh my!
-These will be our new
digs for awhile, boy.
How do you like them?
-Pop, come on.
Are you really OK
with all of this?
It's still not too late
to go home, you know.
-Ranma, my boy, listen-- forget
the Tendo Dojo ever existed.
-Huh?
-From now on, it's just you
and me boy-- on our own.
Indebted to no one, completely
in charge of our own destiny.
We'll form a completely
new kind of martial arts.
They'll write songs about
us, movies, novelizations.
-Pop, your head's on fire.
(SCREAMING)
-Well, it means
that much to you,
then I guess I got no choice.
Ah!
At least change back
first, would ya?
(GRUNTING)
-I should go inform Master Kuno.
-Hey, shut up!
-Do you know what time it is?
-Hey, do you want
me to call the cops?
-Hey, Pop-- if you want to play
the victim, throw me a rope!
-Does everyone have a specimen?
Good.
Now the next step will
be the intestines,
and specifically our
goal is the stomach.
(STOMACH GRUMBLING)
-Huh?
-Don't eat the frog, man.
(LAUGHTER)
-Let's go eat.
-Yeah, or they'll run out.
-So, how's it go-- Ah!
(STOMACH GRUMBLING)
-Poor Ranma.
-Stupid Pop.
Didn't think about
the food part.
Akane, I um--
-Yeah?
-Yeah, now what?
-Move along.
It's quite obvious the lady
doesn't wish to be bothered.
-Ha-ha.
-Hands off!
Do you really think
I wouldn't find out
about your taking up
residence in a public park?
-Yeah, so what's your point?
-My point, you ruffian, is this.
(SCREAMING)
-Huh?
-Dear Akane Tendo, he
who has kept us apart
is no longer an obstacle.
Surely the gates to heaven
are wide open to us.
It is our destiny.
My lady, wilt thou travel
with me upon the path of love?
Should I take this as a no?
(DOG BARKING)
(SIGHS)
-Huh?
Wha--
Hi-ya!
-Watch where you're
hitting with that thing.
-Ranma?
(SCREAMS)
-Don't you want to hear
what I have to say?
-What?
-Well, Ranma-- what
were you going to say?
-Move over.
I can't hear you.
-I said, what is it
you want to tell me?
Couldn't you have waited?
-Don't worry, I'm not
going to try nothing.
Look, Akane, what I came
here to tell you was--
-It's about her dads, isn't it?
-What else?
They may look happy on the
outside, but inside they're--
-They're sad.
-That's right, if we
don't think of something--
-So why don't we try to
get them back together?
-Well what I was
thinking was, I'll
wait for a chance
to get my dad alone,
and then you can wait for a
chance to get your dad alone,
and they'll accidentally
run into each other.
-That's a great idea.
That way you'll be able to
come back home, too, won't you?
-Hey, don't get me wrong.
This about my pop, not about me.
-Uh-huh, and when did you
become so self sacrificing.
-I, uh, I gotta go.
(GRUNTING) Oh, man.
I feel faint.
Ah!
I didn't mean it, OK?
I didn't!
-You sneaky, lying pervert!
[inaudible]
-Dummy.
(LAUGHTER)
-Now watch kids, as the panda
jumps through a flaming hoop.
Let's hope he doesn't burn up.
(LAUGHTER)
-Well, Pop, do your trick.
Ah, just do it, will ya?
-Hey, that was really mean!
He's on fire!
(SCREAMING)
-Stop!
Where are you going?
Hey, don't come crying to
me if you want a refund.
-And how was that supposed to
help with our training, again?
It helps in all kinds of ways.
For one thing, we
learned self-reliance.
And in another, we use the money
to build our own Saotome Dojo.
-And what about being on our
own, indebted to no one, blah,
blah, blah?
-Ah, if we had our
own Dojo, though,
we'd never have to worry about
money problems ever again.
-Why not, if it meant
we could eat regularly.
I'm sorry, the Panda
show is over for the day.
-Oh, my poor Ranma.
-Huh?
-But don't worry, darling,
if it's a mere Dojo you need,
I'd be more than happy to--
-Kodachi Kuno!
Ah!
-Ranma, darling!
-Dad?
You look sad?
-Who's sad?
Not me.
-It's OK, I understand.
You can't fool me, I know you.
Wouldn't you just
rather patch things up?
-Don't wanna.
-Don't be stubborn.
-Akane?
You've got a guest.
-I wonder who it is?
-'Tis I.
-Kuno?
-What's he want?
-Greetings, esteemed
future father-in-law.
Tatewaki Blue Thunder Kuno,
aged 17, at your service.
-I'm sorry, but you're
no son-in-law of mine.
-Ah, but I will be.
I intend to take your
daughter to wife.
-Have you forgotten
who you're talking to?
-Not to mention, forgetting
about right Ranma.
-But I haven't forgot.
How could I, when he and
his lay about father are now
residing at my home?
-They what?
-Are you sure?
-Uh, yes.
-Let's see you try this.
(LAUGHING)
-Chestnuts roasting
on an open fire!
(MOANING)
-Tell me, did it
ever occur to you
that you'd be better
off practicing
than building dumb gadgets?
-Ranma, darling, you
were magnificent.
-Ah, it was nothing.
-Does him like the Dojo
Kodachi built for him?
-It's OK.
-But--
-Like it, we love it.
How could I ever thank you for
the kindness, the generosity,
the fully stocked refrigerator?
-You needn't thank me.
As your future daughter-in-law,
putting a roof over your head
is the least I can do.
-Then as your future Pa Pa,
welcome into the family.
-Having you here with me
tonight, it's like a dream,
I tell you.
-Ah, the dream is
all ours, my dear.
We should be thanking you.
-Ah.
Now this is the life.
(HUMMING)
(SINGING) I'm just
a poor country girl,
with no place to go.
But now I've lost my man,
oh, how I love him so.
-Stupid show off.
(GRUNTING)
KUNO (VOICEOVER): Oh, what
an utter lack of taste.
I'd sooner fast than
eat those things.
To have enjoyed seven-course
meals, three times a day
as I have, and then
to be reduced to this.
-Akane Tendo!
-Huh?
-Once you are my wife,
you'll never again
have to eat such
disgusting foodstuffs!
(GROWLING)
-We'll tear down
this miserable Dojo
and build a new future,
placing your father
in a position of honor where
he'll live out his remaining
days in ease.
-What a strangely
perverse young man.
-You could say that again.
-Psst-- Akane.
-Huh?
-Arrange for your dad to
be outside the front gate
tomorrow.
-Ranma?
Is it really true that you're
staying over at the Kuno?
Oh?
Thank a lot, dummy.
(PANTING)
-What's a matter, Pop?
Can't keep up?
-Speak for yourself.
Whoa.
-Is there something
I can do for you?
-(CLEARS THROAT) Oh, nothing.
Just thinking over old times.
-Old times, eh?
We've really gone through
a lot together, haven't we?
Through the bad times,
and the good times.
-What did I tell
you, it's working.
-Yeah, you're right.
-For example,
Saotome, I'm thinking
of the first time
you stole my pastry.
-Huh?
-Actually, Tendo, I
was just remembering
how you stole my rice crackers.
-Uh!
-Because you stole mine first!
-Only because you
wouldn't share it with me.
-You just can't let it
go, can you Saotome?
-Akane, didn't I
tell you to make sure
he was [? soft ?] up first?
-(GASP) Oh, no!
I knew there was
something I forgot!
-Ah!
You [inaudible]!
I specifically told you to--
-So I forgot!
Since when are you so perfect?
-What's all the fuss?
-Kuno!
-Saotome!
-Akane, you planned
this, didn't you!
-As if.
He invited himself, if
you really must know.
And what about you and Kodachi?
Did you think I
wouldn't find out?
-Look, that's different, OK?
-We're leaving, boy.
-But, Dad!
-A letter of challenge?
How dare he.
-If he thinks I'm going
to apologize to him,
then he's sadly mistaken.
-Why the nerve of that man.
He wants me to apologize to him?
TOGETHER: Well he'll
just have to think again.
Grr.
May the best man win.
-This may be the
last chance we have.
-You don't mean that
you wrote that letter?
-What else could I do?
I mean, they've got to figure
this out, one way or another.
-I wish they weren't
both so stubborn.
You know what I mean?
-Look, I know what
you're thinking,
Akane, so you can
just quit it, OK?
I'm only doing this
because of the old man.
You got it?
-OK, OK!
-I'm only doing this because
you forced me to it, Tendo.
You got that?
-I'm only doing it because
you forced me, Saotome.
Do you got that?
(COUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
-Ah, note the exquisite form.
That's my future
father-in-law, all right.
-Au contraire, he isn't half
the father-in-law mine is.
-Excuse me?
-Now, now, now.
-Saotome's School
of Special Attack!
I am the raging tiger!
Roar!
-Tendo's School
of Special Attack!
Claw of the furious dragon!
(ROARING)
-Saotome's School
of Special Attack,
fist of fearless fatality!
-Tendo's School
of Special Attack,
kick of casual conflagration!
-Saotome's School of Special
Attack, slap of shameless
scorn!
-Tendo's School
of Special Attack,
pinch of persnickety
provocation!
Oh, curses!
-I've got you!
Saotome's super special attack,
flight of the feckless firefly!
-Oh no!
He's fighting for real!
-Wha--
(YELLING)
-Do over!
-No do overs, right Father?
-Oh, yeah.
I guess that means we're even.
(LAUGHING)
-Huh, pretty sneaky.
(GROANING)
-I brought refreshments.
-Say, Tendo, how's about
sharing some of that bean jam?
-Saotome, you glutton.
Look, you've got twice
the portion that I do.
-Don't be paranoid!
-Who's being paranoid?
-You are.
-I am not.
-Hm, such good friends.
[theme music playing]
(SINGING IN JAPANESE)
-The dashing young man on
a prancing brown steed.
-Hey!
Hey, come back here!
Where are you taking Ranma?
-Next time on Ranma
1/2, the Gentle Art
of Martial Tea Ceremony.
We'll see you there.