[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
"Akane's Lost Love.
These Things Happen, You Know."
-Running errands today, Kasumi?
-I'm going to Dr. Tofu's.
-Kasumi?
-Dr. Tofu is completely in
love with my sister Kasumi.
-Oh?
Well, are you sure
about Dr, Tofu?
I mean, he didn't
make an announcement
about it or anything, did he?
-Uh-uh.
But it's so obvious that
anyone could see it.
-Hm.
-Somebody in there?
Hello, you two.
What can I do for you?
-Huh?
Uh-- us?
Nothing right?
-Ranma, why don't you
come into my office,
and let me take a look
at that cheek of yours.
-OK.
-You too, Akane.
-Well, I should--
um-- get going.
-But Akane, I've
already made tea.
-I'm really sorry.
-Hmm?
-Well, OK.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Oh, great.
Now I'm stuck here.
-So let me see
that injury, Ranma.
Hm.
If I didn't know better, I'd
say this was Akane's work.
-Huh?
Well, how did you know that?
-The angle of the ball.
That and the depth of the
stitch marks on your cheek.
-Whoa, even the junk
she hits people with
has Akane's name all over it.
-Don't act like I did
it on purpose, Ranma!
It was all your fault!
-Oh, no.
Akane, I didn't know you
really hit that ball.
-Huh?
-I was only joking with you.
-Moron.
-It doesn't matter.
It's nice to see
Akane full of spirit.
-But-- but I--
-It makes you what you are.
-Yeah, it makes you a tomboy.
-Why don't you shut up, Ranma?
-Ooh, I hit a nerve.
You're even more like a
tomboy when you're angry.
-Hmph.
You're a pervert.
-Hey, watch it.
-Dr. Tofu, can't you see
what a pervert Ranma is?
-Hey, I thought I told you
to stop calling me that.
-It's true.
You always look at me.
Admit it!
-Ha.
You wish.
There's not much
there to look at.
-So you're saying that
you never look then?
-Well, why would I?
You're just boring.
That's all.
AKANE: Hey!
RANMA: Hey, what?
[yawn]
-Oh, good afternoon.
-Oh, Kashumi dear.
How are you?
Lovely weather we're
having, don't you think?
I-- I think left
the kettle on, dear.
Buh-bye now.
Oh, good grief.
Don't tell me you're
gonna go in there.
-Well, yes.
My back's bothering me and--
-You'll be making
a grave mistake
if you know what I mean.
She's in there.
-Not her.
I guess I'll have to reschedule.
My back pain and me and all.
-All right, Ranma.
Now, let's have a look.
KASUMI: Hello.
-Kasumi.
-Hello there.
Good afternoon, Dr. Tofu.
-Hi, Kasumi.
What an amazing
coincidence that we
should meet here of all places.
-I guess.
What was that horrible
cracking noise?
-Noise?
No, I never noticed any noise.
-Ranma, what's the matter?
-Kasumi, are you a
friend of Ranma's too?
He's one of my regulars.
Lately, he keeps getting
these bruises from somewhere
and his joints keep dislocating.
Isn't that right, Ranma?
So, Kasumi, what's up?
-I came to return the book that
I borrowed from you, Dr. Tofu.
Also, I'm not sure if it's
a fitting gift or not, but--
-Well now, thank you so much.
Oh look, everyone.
It's a mask.
Actually it's fitting
very well, Kasumi.
-But that's the wrapping
for the present.
Here.
-A dish of candy.
Oh, how sweet of you, Kasumi.
Oh, dear.
Kasumi, if I'm gonna
wear this lovely mask,
I won't be able to eat this.
-Uh-- Doctor.
-What exactly is
the problem, Akane?
-I'm Ranma.
-OK, what is it, Ranma?
-My neck is killing me.
-Another injury?
Oh, what'll I do
with you, Ranma?
Let's see now.
There.
you're cured.
-It hurts.
-Mr. Saotome, do me a
favor and bring Kasumi
some tea or
something, would you?
-Akane?
-Huh?
-That Dr. Tofu is such a
character, don't you think?
-You think so?
You might not believe this,
but he's completely different
when you're not around.
-Oh, you don't say?
Why is that?
-Buh-bye.
-Hm?
-I gotta go.
See you.
-I wonder if something's
bothering Akane.
She's acting very strange.
-Well, I'm outta here.
-Betty, Betty, be a dear and
go fetch Kasumi some tea,
would you?
Thanks.
-I heard Kasumi's in there.
-So much for our golden years.
-Hello.
Bye.
-Akane!
Hey, Akane!
-To go in there now for an
exam could cost you your life.
-And he's usually such
a fine young doctor too.
-Huh?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): What?
Is she crying?
-What are you doing here, Ranma?
-Now that's more like
the Akane I know.
-Just what did you mean by that?
Surely you don't
expect me to believe
that you're here to cheer me up?
-What's the big deal?
Why should you believe it?
Hey, I'm cured.
-How nice for you.
-There now.
I'm glad to see you're back
to your normal self again.
-What's did you say?
-Now that's the ticket.
-Hmph.
Why are you following me?
-Why should you care?
-Don't tell me you're
worried about me?
-Why should I be worried
about someone like you?
-You shouldn't.
So stop following me already.
-Who says I'm following you?
-You're annoying me.
-Well, that's OK.
-No, it's not OK.
-Well, sorry.
-Now I get it.
-What do you get?
-Oh, I see.
I think you really
do like me after all.
-What?
-Admit it.
That's why you're following me.
-Akane, wait.
How could I ever like a
non-cute girl like you?
-Catch me if you can!
-Wait!
Huh?
Whoa!
You tricked me.
-Haha.
Gotcha.
-So what'd gotten
into her today?
Thanks to you, now I've
gotta go take a bath.
Say--
-Huh?
-I've got a better idea.
How much money do
you have on you?
-Why do you ask?
-Lend me some 'cuz I'm starving.
let's go and get some food.
-You really are acting
different today, Akane.
-If you lend me some money,
it'll be my treat, Ranma.
-Ranma.
-Whoopee.
-Still hungry?
so I'm not all dainty
and delicate like Kasumi.
Big deal.
-Hey, that is not what I said.
-Well, for as long
as I can remember
Dr. Tofu's been in love
with my sister, Kasumi.
-How do you know?
-I just do.
Weren't you watching
him back there?
He was out of it.
Whenever Kasumi's around, Dr.
Tofu always gets like that.
He's been like that
for a while now.
-Akane, if you put all
your time into practicing,
you won't ever have any
time to get married.
-I'll find the time.
-Knowing you, the
man you'll marry
will have to be even
stronger than you are.
Where will you find him?
-But I've already
found him, doctor.
-Who is he?
-Is anyone here?
-Kasumi.
-I made some red beans and rice,
and thought I'd bring you some.
-Hello, Kasumi.
What an amazing
coincidence that we
should meet here of all places.
-I hope Akane isn't
too much trouble.
-Oh, no trouble.
I was working out some of
the kinks in her muscles.
-And-- and it gets even worse.
Akane, you've certainly
lost a lot of weight.
-Oh.
There's lint all over you.
-Kasumi.
You really shocked me
there for a moment, Kasumi.
Ow.
-And then, Dr. Tofu
ran all over town,
carrying Betty on its back.
-Haha.
Tell me you're kidding.
-I wish I was.
-Dr. Tofu would never
do something silly
like that for my sake.
-Come on.
You're pulling my leg, right?
-It's the truth.
-Man, he's really
got it bad, don't he?
-It's all true.
-Stupid jerk.
-He's really in love.
-And that leaves you with
a really broken heart now,
doesn't it?
Uh-- I-- Uh--
-I'm going home.
-Oh, OK.
I'll--
-By myself, Ranma.
If it's the same to you.
Stupid me.
It's not like I
didn't know better.
-Hey, you never know.
I mean, it could happen.
It's not impossible, right?
-Would you just stop trying
to cheer me up, Ranma?
I've got a broken heart, or
have you forgotten already?
-Well then--
-Then what?
-You gotta realize
these things happen.
Just give it up, Akane.
-And who are you to
lecture me on love?
You don't know a thing about it.
-I'm only trying to
help you out here.
-I don't need your help!
-Oh, is that so?
-Yes, it is.
-Fine, then!
Just don't come crying
to me the next time
you get all weepy and
mooning over some dumb guy.
-How can you say that?
RANMA: Get used to it.
You don't need my
help, remember?
-That's right.
I don't!
And don't tell me
how to live my life!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Oh great.
My school bag, I forgot
it at Dr. Tofu's clinic.
-Pop, give me some hot water.
Thanks, Pop.
-Wait.
Ranma, tell me.
What happened to Akane?
-I dunno, She's probably
boo-hooing her eyes
out somewhere, I guess.
-You fool!
-What's your problem?
-Listen, Ranma.
Let me tell you is this-- how
his thoughtless words broke
my heart.
Have you heard
these words before?
-Where'd you hear
something cheesy like that?
-I read it in that magazine.
-So what're you telling me for?
-It means that sometimes
we hurt the ones we love.
When Akane's feeling
bad about something,
you should be the
one to comfort her.
You're her fiance after all.
-Which I wouldn't be, if you'd
bothered to ask me first!
-What's done is done, my boy.
Look after Akane.
You're old enough to know
how women are sometimes.
Listen to me, Ranma.
Sometimes people hurt
each other without even
knowing that they're doing it.
Even I, your own father, have
been known to make mistakes.
Why when I was a young man--
-No, it can't be true.
-It's true, Natsuko.
I don't think we can
see each other anymore.
-But why?
Don't tell me there's someone
else in your life besides me,
is there?
-Now that you
mention it, there is.
-But you said you loved me.
How could you be so
cruel and thoughtless?
-Well, I love her
more than I love you.
-Is she beautiful?
-Actually, she's a much better
dresser than you, so yes.
I'd say so.
She's got great style.
It was a hard choice for
me to make, you know.
But she's so kind
and gentle, you see.
And sweet and innocent.
Of course, it doesn't hurt
that her family is very rich.
I guess you can understand
why I love her more than you,
right, Natsuko?
You won't give me any
trouble, now will you?
-Trouble this!
-I gotta snap
myself out of this.
Huh?
If we're gonna fight,
at least get into it.
How do you expect me
to work out my anger
if you won't fight back?
-Akane, don't you ever get tired
of being angry all the time?
-I like being angry.
-Well, that's too bad.
-Why's that?
-'Cuz you're really
cute when you smile.
-Huh?
-Gotcha.
Hey, no fair.
That didn't count.
-'Cuz you're really
cute when you smile.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I wonder.
Did he mean that?
-What're you making
that goofy face for?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
-What are you doing in my room?
-Hm.
Ranma, I thought that you
already had your neck fixed.
-Well, I did, Pop.
but it's gotten worse.
-Looks bad.
This oughtta take about a week.
-Ranma.
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Some new guy's
come to our school to
settle a grudge with Ranma.
His name's Ryoga Hibiki,
and he hasn't got a clue.
I'm serious.
he's traveled half of
Japan on foot just trying
to find this school.
Next time on Ranma 1/2-- "Enter
Ryoga, The Eternal Lost Boy."
See you there.