[music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[low music playing]
[barking]
-Here I am again,
lost in the mountains.
I suppose I should find
somewhere to sleep.
[barking]
-Those wild dogs are
going crazy tonight.
[meowing]
[growling]
-You won't want to eat
me, do you doggies?
As you can see, I'm a gross cat.
And besides not tasting
very good, if you eat me,
you're going to get
seven year's bad luck.
So don't make me hurt you.
[cry]
[crash]
-So what are you waiting for?
Come and get me.
[barking]
-See?
You're perfectly safe.
[meowing]
-You saved my life.
I'm so grateful.
How can I ever repay you?
-A ghost cat?
[music playing]
NARRATOR: Ryoga's Proposal.
-I see.
So you've been out looking
for a bride all this time?
-You're the only person
who's even been nice to me.
That's right.
I should grant you a
wish for saving my life.
-Grant me a wish?
But I don't have
anything I-- wait.
What kind of wish?
[bell ringing]
[laughter]
-I am not your
ordinary ghost cat.
In fact, perhaps
you've heard of me.
I am the famous Maomolin,
legendary 3,000 year old
Chinese ghost cat who carried
a bell to search for his bride.
Make whatever wish you want.
Do you have a girl you like?
-Oh.
Of course I do.
MAOMOLIN: Your girlfriend?
-Not yet.
MAOMOLIN: You haven't proposed?
-Don't be dumb.
She's still attending
high school.
MAOMOLIN: But you've told
her how you feel, right?
You haven't?
You're more shy than I am.
Don't tell me you've never
had a girlfriend before.
[laughter]
MAOMOLIN: I can't believe it.
You're pathetic.
Now I don't feel so bad.
-(SHOUTING) Shut up.
If you're so smart, then how
come you haven't found a bride?
Huh?
What about that?
-OK.
OK.
Jeez.
-I can handle my own problems.
I saved your life
because I wanted to.
You don't have to
thank me for it.
Besides, how's some dumb
cat supposed to help me?
-But I'm a guy, too.
I can't just ignore the
fact that you saved me.
I have to repay the debt.
Ready or not.
Here I come.
[groan]
[music playing]
[bell ringing]
WOMAN: Akane?
Another package from Ryoga.
AKANE: Coming.
-Oh, well.
Golly.
Isn't he the considerate one.
I sure hope you're grateful.
-Your jealousy is showing.
-It what?
-Gee.
I wonder where he's
traveling this time.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Dear Akane.
Just a note to let you know
I'll be dropping by soon.
I need to ask you
something important.
-Huh.
I wonder what that could be.
RANMA: So what did
he send you, anyway?
-Hm.
Good question.
Hm.
-What the heck?
AKANE: Dried fish and cat food?
[music playing]
[heavy breathing]
-That's weird.
How did I end up here?
(SHOUTING) Where am I now?
[music playing]
[thunder]
[growling and barking]
[bells ringing]
-Let's see.
Ryoga's about a week
late, meaning that he's--
-Practically on time.
-I hate it when the
sky's like this.
-Me too.
Let's hurry home.
RYOGA: Can I ask you a question?
-Hey, look.
If it isn't Ryoga.
-Th-- this is the town where
Akane Tendo lives, isn't it?
-Huh.
That's a weird thing to say.
Well, as a matter of fact,
she's right over there.
-Huh?
-Now you're being ridiculous.
MAOMOLIN (VOICEOVER):
There's that Ranma.
He's got Shampoo and Akane.
Why I ought to--
-Hey, you guys.
Looks like Ryoga's back in town.
Bye.
-See you, dude.
-Oh, Ryoga.
-Hey, man.
How's it going?
-Ranma.
What's wrong?
-Nothing that I can--
-We were just on our way home,
so do you want to come along?
-I'd love to.
AKANE: Ranma, come on.
We're leaving.
-Coming.
[thunder]
[suspenseful music playing]
-Don't you think he's
acting kind of weird?
-Well, he seems kind
of the same to me.
-He's like a different person.
-So he's probably just
tired from his trip.
So, how was your-- there he is.
Hey, slowpoke.
Hurry up.
[thunder]
-I guess he's the same.
AKANE: I'm home.
KASUMI: Welcome back.
Ryoga, hello.
I was just finishing up dinner.
We'd love to have you over.
Hm.
Akane, would you mind
helping me in the kitchen?
-Sure.
We'll talk later, OK?
So don't go anywhere.
-I won't.
-Got you.
[spring sound]
MAOMOLIN (VOICEOVER):
You can do it.
Pretend you didn't see it.
I can't stand it anymore.
No.
-Kasumi says dinner's
almost ready, so--
[meowing]
Thank you, Kasumi.
[eating sounds]
-Would you like to eat mine?
-I'd love to, but only
if you don't mind.
Fish is my favorite.
-I don't remember him
liking fish that much.
-Now do you believe me?
-Can I have some more, please?
-Of course.
-Could you maybe mash it all up
in a bowl with some extra fish?
-How funny.
That's just how
kitties like to eat.
RYOGA: That was so good.
KASUMI: I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Would you like
some nice hot tea?
-I'm sorry.
But I don't like tea very much.
Could I have some milk instead?
[spit]
-I always get so
tired after I eat.
Can I take a nap?
[purring snore]
[music playing]
-Listen.
Thanks for coming out
on such short notice.
There's something I've
been meaning to ask you.
Something that just won't wait.
They say they're going
to transform me, so--
NABIKI: Come on, stupid.
Propose.
-It shouldn't be
more than three,
maybe five years at most.
-Do it soon or you're
going to miss your chance.
-Yeah.
I know what you're thinking.
How can I trust a
loser like this?
-Either do it or
don't, your moron.
-Huh?
ACTOR AND RYOGA: What
I want is to marry you.
ACTOR (ON TV): I'm serious.
I can't live without you.
What's the point to it?
[music playing]
-Akane.
Please, would you marry me?
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ry-- Ryoga?
[meow]
[music playing]
[meowing]
-Uh.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
Marry me, Akane.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): When he said
that to me, was he serious?
[sigh]
[meowing and snoring]
-I can't sleep with them
dumb cats out there.
(SHOUTING) Would
you shut up, please?
[loud meowing]
[music playing]
KASUMI: Akane.
Hurry up, or you'll be late.
-Coming.
-Good morning, Akane.
-Morning, Ryoga.
-You're even prettier in
the morning, you know that?
You don't mind if I stay
here a while, do you?
-I'm, uh-- kind of in a hurry.
Excuse me.
-She must be nervous.
[music playing]
-Ranma.
He was even weirder today.
-I thought girls liked
being proposed to.
-Be serious, will you?
Aren't you worried?
RANMA: What, that
you'll pick him over me?
AKANE: I'm worried
about Ryoga, OK?
He's totally different.
What if something's wrong?
RANMA: Oh.
So you didn't like
his proposal, then.
-That's not what I mean.
RANMA: So what do you mean?
-(SHOUTING) Never mind.
[crash]
[groan]
[music playing]
TEACHER: So therefore
what we get is this.
Which you use to get this,
thereby completing the equation
and finishing the problem.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I thought
girls liked being proposed to.
[snoring]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Like
he's such a big expert.
I'll bet he's just jealous.
TEACHER: Wake up.
[crash]
TEACHER: Go stand in the hall.
-Stupid teacher.
I wouldn't have fallen asleep if
it weren't for them dumb cats.
[birds chirping]
[purring sound]
[wings flapping]
[bells ringing]
[wedding march playing]
-Know what, darling?
-Yes, precious?
-I'm so happy, I could just cry.
-But not as half as much as me.
Give me some sugar, baby.
-I'm so happy, Akane.
[gasp]
-Only a dream.
MAOMOLIN (VOICEOVER):
That's right.
If I can get him
married to Akane,
then that would mean that
he would-- that we would--
that I would--
(SHOUTING) Finally be able to
stop searching for a bride.
[wings flapping]
[bells ringing]
[wedding march playing]
-If it isn't Ranma.
-A-- Akane.
-Gee whiz, Ranma.
After Akane and
I became engaged,
we stopped seen you around.
Why was that, do you think?
Well, you do realize you're
welcome to come back and visit,
don't you?
We could always use
company at the Tendo Dojo.
Bye, bye, Ranma.
Take care now, you hear?
-Akane.
Please don't leave me.
[splash]
-Oh, what an awful dream.
Uh oh.
-Saotome?
Huh?
[bells ringing]
[music playing]
RANMA: Akane?
[gasp]
-Ranma.
-Are you thinking about Ryoga?
Well, I know I am.
What are you going to do?
-I-- I don't know.
-Yeah, well, whatever
you decide, Akane, it's
got nothing to do
with me, right?
If you could, though,
I'd ask that you--
-That I what?
-Uh.
GIRL: Akane.
[gasp]
GIRL: Look.
We've got lunch.
-You didn't have to--
-Wasn't there someone
here just a minute ago?
-No.
I mean, uh, I'm alone.
-You sure?
-Come on, you guys.
Are we going to eat or what?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Oh, great.
I'm so tired, I forgot to eat.
And I'm so weak, I can
barely-- got to let go.
-Getting tricky, eh?
-Poor Akane's
daddy, is him tired?
SOUN: Excuse me, hello?
I'm Akane's daddy.
Mm.
Feels good.
-You need to relax.
[bell ringing]
[meowing]
-Just as I was making progress,
that bicycle bell rang and--
-Can someone tell
me how I got here?
[music playing]
SOUN: Hello.
Hello.
You OK?
Ryoga.
AKANE: I'm home.
-Ah.
Akane.
Be my bride.
-But Ryoga, I--
[scream]
-Huh?
Akane.
Ryoga.
What do you think you're doing?
-You mind your own business,
or you're going to be sorry.
[growl]
-Ryoga.
[crash]
[cry]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): That
shouldn't have happened.
Ryoga's much tougher than that.
It's like he's a
whole other per--
[mystical sounds]
-Thanks for nothing,
you big bully.
You nearly knocked me right out.
-Oh, no.
Not you again.
-The ghost cat.
I should have known.
-So he was in Ryoga
the whole time.
-Yep.
I she sure was.
I was hoping you wouldn't
notice, but since you have,
I'm hoping you'll be
able to forgive me.
[groan]
-Oh, my head.
-I-- I-- I get it.
So that's why you didn't want to
eat nothing but-- but cat food,
right?
-Huh?
-Not to mention running
around on all fours
and curling into
a ball to sleep.
-Sure.
And why he'd rather use
sand instead of a toilet.
-Uh, yeah, man.
So, uh, so-- so don't worry
about trying to kiss Akane
and-- and proposing, and junk.
Because that was
the cat and not you.
-I feel faint.
-I was only trying
to do you a favor.
-Embarrassing me like
that in front of everyone.
Why I ought to--
-You never would have been
able to propose without me.
-Shut up.
-OK, then.
How about your feelings?
You could never have
confessed to Akane
if it hadn't been for
me, isn't that right?
[punch]
-Why you little--
-When you kissed her, it was
your lips on Akane, not mine.
[punch]
-Quit it.
-Just think about
how great it would
be if you were to
team up with me.
[punch]
-Why won't you admit
that you need me?
[punch]
-You provide the body and
I provide the willpower.
[punch]
-Maybe I'll propose myself.
(SHOUTING) Be my bride.
-When I do propose,
I'll do it myself.
[maomolin crying]
[heavy breathing]
-I got to go.
-Ryoga.
[music playing]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Oh, Akane.
Maybe I can't say it
now, but someday, I
promise that I am-- uh oh.
[rabbit call]
[birds chirping]
AKANE: OK, we're off.
Aren't you wondering
where that ghost cat is?
-If I never saw him again,
it would be too soon.
Speaking of which,
we're going to be late.
[meowing]
RANMA: I knew it.
MAOMOLIN: Wouldn't you like
one of my little bells?
-Look.
He's opened up a store.
-Oh, man.
I hate cats.
-You won't get rid
of me that easy.
Won't you be my bride?
[music playing]
NARRATOR: Come on, dad.
Fighting over a game?
What?
Mr. Saotome's gone?
Really?
He's joined the circus?
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
Genma takes a walk.
We'll see you there.