THEME SONG: (SINGING
IN JAPANESE)
I want the sweet bread.
I'll have a sandwich, please.
Hey, give me the curry bread.
WOMAN: Just hold your horses.
[chatter]
Oh man, they're
gonna run out again.
Hm?
Huh?
Secondary school store.
Well that's news to me.
That sign back there
must have been a joke.
Ah!
[crash]
Me sensing the trouble.
What's going on here?
Huh?
No entry sign?
Where am I?
That's it!
Hm?
The place is deserted.
Oh man.
Huh?
Ah!
Are you looking for something?
I just came down here to
look for something to eat.
TORAMASA: It's right there.
Huh?
What is this?
It looks like it used to be
a sweet roll or something.
That creeps giving
me the creeps.
I'm outta here!
That's enough.
Ranma Saotome, you
be sticking your nose
where it don't belong.
The Secret Don
of Furinkan High.
STUDENT 1: Did you hear?
There's another school
store at Furinkan.
STUDENT 2: Really?
I wonder where it is?
I heard rumors about it,
but I doubt if they're true.
Come on, let's go find out.
[chatter] out.
He thinks it's true?
I don't know.
I think it's somewhere--
Could be true.
I don't know.
What are you all talking about?
That school store
ripped me off.
I went in and bought a
sandwich, and the whole thing
was covered in mold.
I bought a pair of
gym shorts and look.
Ah, man.
Talk about retro.
Yeah, check out these sneakers.
They're old work sandals.
[chatter]
Whining about it to each
other won't change anything.
Why don't you tell
the principal?
NABIKI: That's a
pretty lame idea.
BOTH: Hm?
OK then.
What's your idea, huh Nabiki?
NABIKI: I've heard tales
about the other school store,
but the real story is about
the vendor who worked there.
They say there's an old
man who lives down there,
and the rumor is that,
if you get too close,
he can cast a bad
luck curse on you.
I suggest you all forget
about, as if the place never
existed at all.
That's just a stupid
fairytale, right guys?
Yeah, it's just a fairytale.
Everyone, calm down please.
Students of Furinkan High, if
you have absolutely nothing
to fear with the brave
Tatewaki Kuno here.
I will debunk these
rumors once and for all!
Ah!
[screaming]
So, the story's true.
The old vendor is
back to haunt us.
No!
And I still don't have a
thing to wear to gym class.
[crying]
This is stupid.
Huh?
Now it's my turn.
No!
Wait, Akane!
Hey, Akane!
Akane!
Are you--
Ranma?
Uh, what are you doing?
You see, Toramasa doesn't
have any relatives,
and he's not feeling well.
[coughing]
Huh?
Are you all right?
Oh, don't worry.
I'm fine, Akane.
OK, what's going on here?
I thought this place was
supposed to be haunted.
That's just a rumor, and it's
the principal who started it.
Yes, he wanted to put
me out of business.
For years now he's had
a grudge against me.
I'd say you put yourself
out of business by selling
moldy old sweet rolls.
[coughing]
Toramasa!
Ranma!
Could you at least
show a little respect?
He is your elder.
Eh.
Old man, you must pay
for what you have done.
No one embarrasses me
and gets away with it!
What do you think
you're doing, Kuno?
Ah!
[crash]
TORAMASA: It pains
me to think that you
are the cream of the Furinkan
High martial arts crop.
Wha-- wha-- what?
Well, back in my day, men
were men, but not today.
[scoffs]
Oh no, everything has
changed for the worst, what
with your rock and roll, wasting
your time dating, and the boys
who look like little girlies.
This whole school
has gone to pot.
What's this world coming to?
[crying]
Boys who look like
little girlies?
You think he means me.
Ha!
You are nothing but a
senile old man, old man.
Ha!
Being in charge of the
store was only a cover.
Hm?
I was the martial arts
instructor at Furinkan High
ever since the first
principal, and you
may have heard of my legend.
I am Toramasa
Kobayakawa, and the time
has come for me to do my job!
Now show your respect!
Yes, master.
Please, I beg of you,
forgive me my insolence.
Well, I guess his
cough cleared up.
I think you're right.
He looks a lot better now.
Hey punk, you better
watch your mouth.
Ha!
Make me.
Well then, you won't
mind if I show everyone
your little secret?
Ah!
You don't think you
can get away with this.
Why don't you try and stop me?
Hey, where are you going?
TORAMASA: And you
think you're so smart?
[laughter]
RANMA: Come back here!
Ranma!
Where the heck did
he disappear to?
[laughter]
TORAMASA: I may be old, but
I'm not as feeble as you think.
[laughter]
Now you're starting
to get on my nerves.
Huh?
Stand aside.
Ranma Saotome, I will not
allow you to fight to Toramasa.
I shall be the one to
smite you in his stead.
Hiyah!
No thanks.
I'd rather take it out on
the old geezer than you.
TORAMASA: I like
your footwork, Ranma.
[laughter]
Oh man.
Where's the little
freak hiding anyway?
Huh?
TORAMASA: It's like the
chicken hunting the fox, Ranma.
You'll never find me!
[laughter]
Da!
What was that you were saying?
Whoa, you're good.
Well, I'd love to stay and
chat, but I gotta bail.
Where'd that come from?
I wonder what's
with the old goat.
Half the time he sounds like
he's half dead, except when
he talks about Furinkan High.
That's right.
Ah!
I hate it when you do that!
My dear boy, I
believe now is the time
that I told you about the
glorious history of Furinkan
High School.
Centuries ago in
Japan, there was
much chaos between all
the different tribes.
Oh, go on.
And during this
time of upheaval,
it was our very
own Furinkan High
School that saved the world.
Under the banner of
the Furinkan High flag,
both teachers and students
battled against fierce foe
after foe.
The wars raged on
over many, many years,
but none of our enemies
were strong enough
to defeat the mighty
boys from Furinkan.
Finally, with the country
once again united,
we rode on into the capital.
Oh, why has history
been so cruel to me?
If only I were born
in another era,
I surely could've been a hero.
Don't stain the carpet, Kuno.
But sadly, as our troops
approached the city of Kyoto,
we found it under attack.
We were too late, as World War
II was well under way by then.
What an interesting
slant on history.
Yeah, it might even
make a good action flick.
Would you shut up?
Huh?
Where is it?
Hm.
Ah great, me wonder where that
foolish old kahuna hid it at.
So what do you
think you're doing?
Hm?
Oh boy, oh boy, cakey.
Yeah, you sure scared me.
Yeah, well, me just be
mopping up the place.
That's all.
Just mopping.
[nervous laughter]
What was that all about?
Me most get rid
of the old kahuna
if it be the last thing me do.
Aloha students of Furinkan.
Me decided to call
everyone to this assembly
to announce to you that
we be ridding ourselves
of that old vendor
once and for all.
ALL: Yeah!
Toramasa, what
are we going to do?
The principal is on his way
with a horde of students.
Ha, that's my cue.
I guess I'll see you around.
Hey, just where do you think
you're going, you freak?
There's but one way
to win this fight,
and that's the
element of surprise.
It reminds me of when my
brave warriors and I fled
to China to hide out during
one of our campaigns.
There we created the
Mongolian empire,
which even the Europeans
couldn't conquer.
You're an idiot.
I have lost face, and
that leaves only one thing
for Toramasa to do--
commit harakiri.
What are you saying?
Please don't try
and stop me, Akane.
Don't worry.
We won't.
Allow the sword
of Tatewaki Kuno
to do the honor of
being your second.
Ah!
Hey!
Are you out of your
cotton picking mind?
But-- I thought--
Ranma, we both
know Toramasa can't
win this fight all by
himself, so we're just
going to have to help him.
Ha, give me one good reason
why I should help the old goat.
Ah!
All right, I get the picture.
OK, me fine young
cakies, it be time
to get the show on the road and
do away with the evil vendor.
Halt, fellow
students of Furinkan,
I order you to cease
your futile offensive.
If you do not, I will be
forced to deal with you each
individually.
And I shall triumph!
[yelling]
No, no!
No!
D-- d-- don't you dare
take another step forward
or it will be your last!
Ah!
[screaming]
Ugh, that hurts.
Ah!
Look out!
All right, men.
Retreat!
And now it's time
to make you dance!
Hey!
Would you quit shoving?
I think my pants are on fire!
[boom]
Huh?
Well, we sure showed them, huh?
You two cakies
think you beat me?
Then you got
another ting coming.
Well, we stalled
'em for now, but
what are we supposed to do
for an encore, Toramasa?
Look at the way
he's dressed, Ranma--
like he's ready for battle.
I wouldn't bet on it.
Would you look at this?
He's sitting here sipping tea
while we're out defending him.
Yeah, what's up with that?
Ha, there is an
old proverb which
says you must become
friends with your enemies
before you fight them.
Right.
And I say that you're too
much of a coward to face 'em.
[rumbling]
BOTH: Hm?
[crash]
Wha-- what the heck
is going on out here?
Aloha to my two little cakes
and a wrinkled old nincompoop.
Me have a little present
to give to you three.
What would we do with
a stupid giant cat?
It be not the cat,
but what be inside.
Ah!
[yelling]
BOTH: Ah!
[screaming]
OK, now I be mad.
Suck on this, suckers.
Ah!
What are you doing?
[boom]
Oh no!
Oh!
Huh?
Ah!
[boom]
AKANE: Ah!
Ranma!
Akane!
[chuckling]
No!
That be far enough,
Ranma Saotome.
Hey, don't you be
nobody's fool now, OK?
Or else the cakey's
hair gets it.
And don't think me not
be doing to her either.
Ranma.
You!
You let go of her now!
The girl doesn't have
anything to do with our fight,
so be a man and release her now.
Okie dokie, you got it.
I wonder what the deal is with
the principal wanting to get
rid of Toramasa so quick.
What-- what's happening, Ranma?
I think they're showing each
other how much power they have.
Let's do it!
Look out Toramasa!
It's time to get rid of you!
Oh no.
Don't tell me you had it with
you the whole time, old man?
That's right, and here it is.
What is it?
What the-- it's just some
dumb old report card.
Huh?
This is the principal's.
[laughter]
Man this is wicked.
The principal never graduated
'cause he got an F in English.
Hey, you give that
report card back to me!
Huh?
[laughter]
I have destroyed the proof!
Think again.
That was just a copy.
I got tons more here,
and here, and here.
I've even got the original.
PRINCIPAL KUNO: I'm ruined.
I thought he was American.
I'd say it looks as
though he was just pulling
a fast one on all of us.
I be vet sorry, Toramasa,
and because you win,
you can stay at the school.
Good.
Now that things are
back to normal again,
I can run the school store.
Oh, revenge is so sweet.
[laughter]
Listen!
It is with great pride that
I announce the grand opening
of the new school store.
So, are you gonna sell
moldy sweet rolls again?
You kids are all spoiled,
not like in my day.
Back then we had to
hunt for our own food.
Why, I remember having to
stalk the great woolly mammoth
during my lunch hour
here at Furinkan
just to make myself a sandwich.
Sure has a wild imagination.
No kidding.
And to think, now we
get to listen to him
babble on every day.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): With oil
drums strapped to their backs,
Ranma, Ryoga, and Mousse
head deep into the mountains.
What could they be up to?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," back
to the way we were, please.
We'll see you there.