[music playing]
[theme music]
(VOICEOVER) I've got to
completely master the Lion Roar
Shot before Ranma does.
Hurry up.
[giggling]
(VOICEOVER) Let's see what
the secret writings here say.
Anyone can do the
Lion Roar Shot.
First, think an unhappy
thought and make your Ki heavy.
There.
You did it.
However, this is merely
the basic technique.
The following is how the
Lion Roar Shot should
look once completely mastered.
Huh, an arrow.
Now I just have to
figure out what it means.
Huh?
NARRATOR: From the depth
of despair, part two.
Are you positive you
don't need to eat anything?
If you lose this match,
will you be my slave?
I had no idea you could
make yourself so gloomy.
Well, now you know.
WOMAN: Oh, no!
Who's down there?
MAN: Are you OK down there?
WOMAN: Someone
call the ambulance.
[chatter]
WOMAN: I'm not sure who's
unhappier-- Ranma or Ryoga.
[chatter]
WOMAN: I'm putting
my bets on Ryoga.
He's about as unlucky
as you could get.
[squeals]
[groan]
So dark.
So cold.
So tired.
So-- so depressed.
So desperate.
My Ki is so heavy.
Huh?
It's Ryoga.
[snoring]
[growl]
Huh?
What?
He's been gorging
himself and now he's
curled up in a sleeping bag
beside a nice, warm, cozy fire?
[groan]
I'm going to clobber that jerk!
Shishi hokodan!
[scream]
All right!
That proves I'm more
miserable than Ryoga is.
[laughter]
That'll teach you!
I win, pal!
I beat you!
Stop this foolishness!
Ow.
[groan]
Ranma, have you already
forgotten your decision
to cut out all food,
drink, and sleep in order
to make yourself miserable?
Oh, no.
What have I done?
Look, Ranma.
Some people have certain
talents that make it easier
for them to master a technique.
Huh?
From what I understand,
unhappy people
can make themselves even
more miserable in order
to use the Lion Roar Shot.
It increases the power
of the move, they say.
Yeah.
Why do you think I'm
going to all this trouble?
I'm telling you!
[groan]
You don't have what it
takes to master this move.
Give up.
Pop, what are you
trying to tell me?
I see his point.
He should know Ranma
better than anyone.
He's been his dad for 16
years, after all, right?
And that's
certainly long enough
to get to know your
own son's downfalls.
[laughter]
So you're telling me not
to even bother trying?
I'm saying I'll teach
you a technique that
suits you better!
Huh?
I never thought I'd
live to see the day when
we'd have to come to this.
Saotome anything goes special
attack Howl of the Demon Dog.
Huh?
Howl of the Demon Dog?
Ready.
Focus your Ki.
Take your distance.
Once you've got enough
distance, then get ready and--
[gasp]
[moan]
[yell]
Na-na-na-na.
Your mom is a mangy mutt.
Na-na-na-na-na.
[yell]
That's Yap of the Beaten Dog,
not Howl of the Demon Dog.
[dogs barking]
Take my advice, boy.
[growling]
Find yourself another move.
Not on your life!
I'm not going to be
able to move forward
until I get through this!
Huh?
Well, I'll be.
[gasp]
His Ki isn't moving.
That's interesting.
This time I'll get it.
[groan]
[scream]
Huh?
Ooh, that's distracting.
What do you think you're doing?
I was just curious to
see what would happen.
Huh?
You won't get anywhere if
a little peep show is going
to distract your training.
Focus your Ki and try again.
Quit interrupting!
I can't take it.
I'm never going to be
able to defeat Ryoga.
Ryoga.
Ryoga!
I can't let that
guy keep beating me!
Huh?
[scream]
What was that?
I call that lack of direction.
Ranma, are you all right?
Ranma!
Huh?
Now I get it.
What?
(VOICEOVER) Since the Lion Roar
Shot is based on depression,
maybe I can find an emotion more
suited to me to come up with
a new move.
[laughter]
There's just no stopping
this genius kid!
His Ki is getting big
as his confidence grows.
It doesn't look very strong.
[laughter]
(VOICEOVER) Does he really have
what it takes to beat Ryoga?
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
[chatter]
Ah, nice hot water.
(VOICEOVER) I don't get this.
I don't get what this
arrow is supposed to mean.
If I can't figure
this out, then I'll
never be able to perfect
the Lion Roar Shot.
If only there was
some kind of hint.
Huh?
[giggling]
Oh, it's just a
kid fooling around.
Yoo-hoo, Dad!
Hm?
Ah.
I wonder.
It sank.
Now I've got it!
The secret of the
elusive Lion Roar Shot!
[laughter]
I figured it out!
Ryoga!
Huh?
Hi, Akane.
Out for a bath?
Uh, yeah.
Ryoga, are you seriously
going to fight Ranma?
Um.
They say the better you
get at it, the more unhappy
the Lion Roar Shot will
make you feel, you know?
[sigh]
Akane, I've got a favor to ask.
Yes?
Look me in the eye and
yell as loud as you can.
Yell what?
Tell me how much you hate me!
If you don't mind.
What?
Ryoga, why would I--
Please, Akane!
You're the only one
who can help me.
(VOICEOVER) If you
say you hate me, then
I can perfect the
Lion Roar Shot.
You really want me to?
I'm sure.
[sigh]
I can't stand your guts, Ryoga.
Goldfish for sale!
Goldfish!
[gasp]
Oh, no.
She said she hates me.
Ryoga, are you all right?
[scream]
That's the last thing on
earth I wanted to hear!
Where are you going?
Don't try and stop me!
I knew you were going
to say you hated me,
but I had no idea it was
going to hurt as much as this!
[scream]
But Ryoga, you're the
one who made me say it.
[crash]
Huh?
[gasp]
[screams]
[excited chatter]
Is it a bomb or something?
[chatter]
Is it coming this way?
Wait, wait, wait.
What's going on?
[chatter]
Wow.
That's Ryoga.
I did it.
I finally mastered
the Lion Roar Shot.
[animal noises]
[inaudible]
GIRL: Oh, they're
having a fight.
[chatter]
[sigh]
I made it.
[chatter]
Ha.
And here I was sure that you
were trying to run away, Ryoga.
[sigh]
[groan]
Has Ryoga mastered
the technique
of the Lion Roar Shot?
Yes.
And it's incredibly powerful.
But poor Ranma.
[music playing]
No prob.
I got this match in the bag.
I don't know why he
feels so confident.
Maybe he's got some new
defense moves or something.
What's the matter, Ryoga?
If I didn't know any better,
I'd think the world was ending.
Huh, good eye.
I've sacrificed everything that
made me happy to have this mach
and win.
So without delay.
[grunt]
I'll finish you
once and for all.
The Lion Roar Shot can only
be used with a heavy Ki.
Only someone as unhappy as Ryoga
can master that move, though.
Oh.
Not that stance.
I'll fight him in this way.
Hm.
He's looking pretty confident.
What's he doing?
Shishi hokodan!
[grunts]
Bride of the Fierce Tiger!
[groan]
[laughter]
What a performance.
Bride of the Fierce Tiger?
I've never even heard of it.
The way you fight
someone with a heavy Ki
is with a confident
Ki like mine.
You're in trouble now, Ryoga.
Confident Ki?
That's why he was so cocky.
[rumble]
Huh.
Thanks for making
me more miserable.
Huh?
You should have given up
while you had your chance.
Then I wouldn't need to do this.
But now I have to use my
perfected Lion Roar Shot
and wipe you out for good!
[scream]
No!
It's just like before.
It's enormous!
Huh?
[scream]
[gasp]
Oh, dear.
That's a big one.
[whimpering]
You survived, huh?
How depressing.
Looks like I'll have to
do it all over again.
[groan]
[yelling]
Huh?
Oh, no, you don't!
[non-english speech]
Oh, no.
Uh oh.
His Ki's gotten weaker.
[scream]
[groan]
The Lion Roar Shot is
to be revered by all.
The Ki is emitted from Ryoga,
rises up, then drops down
lower than before.
It's easy to continue
the vicious cycle.
But I don't understand
why Ryoga is so
depressed in the first place.
I think I might know why.
I can't stand your guts, Ryoga.
(VOICEOVER) Those
horrifying words.
It's enough to keep
me miserable forever.
And now you're going to
pay for this misery, Ranma.
(VOICEOVER) Oh, no!
If I'm the reason Ryoga became
so depressed-- oh, then I've
got to do something
to stop this fight.
Because any way it turns
out, they'll both lose.
Ryoga, wait!
Huh?
Akane, is that you?
Are you worried
about what I said?
What's she talking about?
You're the one who
forced me to say it.
You made me say I hated you.
Please don't try to comfort me.
But Ryoga, it wasn't right.
Because I actually--
I like you, Ryoga!
Huh?
You do?
Really?
[music playing]
I really do, Ryoga.
You're a good friend.
Let's be friends forever.
Huh?
Oh.
Let's be friends forever.
(VOICEOVER) Thanks for
finishing me off, Akane.
So that's where you're
getting all your misery from.
You used Akane so you
could get all depressed
and then turn your
feelings against me.
It's over.
I really have
nothing left to lose.
But Ranma!
You're going down with me!
Oh, Ryoga.
Why are you still so miserable?
Hang on.
Just what did you say to him?
[explosion]
I won't get away with this.
[groan]
It's never going to
turn out differently.
Let's do ourselves
a favor and end it.
(VOICEOVER) It
doesn't make sense.
The Lion Roar Shot should
have crushed Ryoga, too,
on its way down.
But it doesn't seem
to have affected him.
Shishi Hokodan!
What's with that strange
look on his face?
[groan]
Wait a minute.
Maybe--
I win again.
I'm just getting warmed up.
Let's see you try
it one more time.
Huh.
Aren't you the slow learner.
[grunt]
(VOICEOVER) If I'm
right about this,
I just might win the match.
It's all or nothing.
[yelling]
Now's my chance.
Whoa!
I can see Akane's panties!
What?
[scream]
[groans]
Uh-huh.
It's just what I thought.
When you use the Lion Roar
Shot, you go completely empty
of all emotion.
And after that, the Ki
passes right through you.
Loses his Ki?
He was so out of his
mind, he lost his Ki.
So if I can distract you
at exactly the right moment,
you'll destroy yourself.
Huh.
How many times do
you think I'd fall
for that lame trick of yours?
We'll see.
This is where the
real match starts.
The end's near for
you, I'm afraid.
(VOICEOVER) This is
the only way I can win.
Hey, Ryoga.
I gave Akane a kiss, you know?
Huh?
[gasp]
You did what?
That-- that's a lie!
He's just joking around!
We never did anything like that!
It's a lie!
(VOICEOVER) What on
earth is Ranma thinking?
The heavier Ryoga's Ki becomes,
the stronger the Lion Roar Shot
will be.
Why would he try to make
Ryoga even more depressed?
[grunts]
Ultimate shishi hokodan!
[gasp]
Now's my chance.
[grunt]
I'm coming, Ryoga.
Ryoga!
I didn't kiss Akane!
Huh?
Are you serious?
Of course I didn't!
[scream]
[coughing]
I finally beat
Ryoga's Lion Roar Shot.
Ranma!
A distraction just when Ryoga's
Ki was at its all time low.
He didn't stand a chance
against that strategy.
But it's amazing that Ranma
came out unscathed, too.
[groan]
I spoke too soon.
Guess he was just
holding on by a thread.
Like I said-- Ranma just made
all that up about us kissing.
Glad to hear it.
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER):
Honestly, what in the world
does the Ghost Cat
Maomolin getting married
have to do with Ranma having
to kiss Shampoo, anyway?
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
Shampoo's Cursed Kiss.
We'll see you there.