[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
[gong ringing]
KASUMI TENDO: Hurry up,
Akane, or your friends
will leave without you.
AKANE: I'm going,
I'm going, already.
OK, I'm leaving.
-Well, you have fun.
-Hot springs, what
a waste of a trip.
Only old fogies go there.
-Oh, no.
Actually, I here they're
quite trendy these days.
-That's right.
Admit it.
Don't you get sick
of tea kettles?
Why not get some real hot water?
[laughing]
-Or use a tea kettle.
Big deal.
AKANE: See ya.
RANMA: No, don't go yet.
-Now what?
Don't tell me you
want to come along.
-Why didn't I think of it?
Go on, son.
I'll allow it.
Go with Akane.
I'll even let you two take a
bath together, if you like.
-Are you crazy?
-Are you?
-Yeah, why would
he ever think I'd
want to take a bath with a
tomboy-type like you, anyway?
-Excuse me?
-Where you go is
none of my business.
You got that?
[grunting] And neither is who
you go with, for that matter.
-Hey, how did you--
[groaning]
-Oh, I sure could use
a therapeutic soak
in a nice, hot spring
right now. [sobbing]
-Don't worry, Gramps, you'll be
dead before it gets much worse.
-What did you just say?
Ah!
-Whoa, more therapy, Gramps?
-Give that back!
Hand it over!
It's mine!
-No, it's mine!
-It's mine, it's mine, it's
mine, it's mine, it's mine!
AKANE: No, it isn't!
[sobbing]
-Mine, mine.
-Have fun, Akane.
-I will.
-Aren't you going along, son?
-It's none of his
business where I go.
-Just go, already, or
the springs will dry up.
-You're right, I'm late.
Buh bye!
-Ah!
Hey, hey!
-Where do you
think you're going?
-Please Master, try
to control yourself.
-I don't wanna, I don't wanna!
I wanna go to the hot
springs with Akane!
[music playing]
NARRATOR: Rub-a-dub-dub,
There's a Pervert in the Tub.
-I'm sorry, Master, but you
cannot be allowed to tag along
to that hot spring.
-Traitor!
How dare you show
such insolence!
-Shut up, pervert!
Shut up!
Whoa, huh?
Hey!
-Woo hoo!
Back to the beach!
SOUN TENDO: Get him!
-Get ready, Akane, here I come!
[speaking japanese] [crash]
-Ah!
Oh, uh.
-Hya!
[punching sounds]
-You suckers!
Hoo hoo!
Girls' dressing room?
When did that get here?
Hoo hoo!
Ha!
Uh!
-Eek!
A pervert!
-Good work, son.
-Nothing to it.
[grunting and laughing]
-Ooh.
HAPPOSAI: Look what you've done.
You've broken my-- my bath pail.
Now how are Akane and
I gonna-- how are--
why are you so mean to me?
-Shut up, you!
You had it coming!
-You're the one
who's got it coming.
How dare you use that tone?
I won't allow it!
For the sake of all
mankind, I promised
I'd never again
use this technique.
But--
-Please, not that technique!
-By the power vested in me,
as Master of the Founding
School of Anything
Goes Martial Arts,
I, Happosai, do hereby invoke
my most powerful and mighty
technique!
Happo-Fire Burst!
-Please, Master!
I don't want to die!
-You should have
thought of that before.
Hya!
[wailing]
[blowing away smoke]
-I, uh--
-Technique?
Technique?
I don't see no technique.
-Oh!
HAPPOSAI: Maybe I did it wrong.
I should have gone
real big, like-- uh--
and then I should
have gone real low.
OK, I admit it.
I forgot!
SOUN TENDO: You, you have no
idea how close we just came.
Son, when the Master
says special technique
you've got to listen.
GENMA SAOTOME: Trust
us on this, boy.
-Ha!
What's the worst he can do?
Bwow us all up with
is wittle burst?
-Yes, that is exactly
what he could do.
Maybe if you'd trained with him,
like we did, you'd understand.
-Woo hoo!
What a haul!
MAN: Stop, thief!
-They've stolen from
me for the last time.
MAN: Block all the
exits out of town!
HAPPOSAI: [laughing]
Ooh, I bet you
they never figured we'd be
escaping this way, huh boys.
GENMA SAOTOME: Unfortunately,
or fortunately,
depending on how you
look at it, the villagers
somehow knew the
Master's only weakness.
HAPPOSAI: Ah.
Ah.
It's a brassier!
How sweet it is!
Ha ha!
-Master, no!
GENMA SAOTOME:
And that's when it
seemed that our poor Master
would tragically be--
-Wait for my signal, Tendo.
-Let's see him get out
of this one, eh Saotome.
-Huh?
HAPPOSAI: And
that's when I-- you
don't mind if I butt
in here, do ya boys?
That's when I noticed
the big boulder.
What else could I
have done but unleash
the ultimate attack
of The Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts?
-Happo-Fire Burst!
[crash]
GENMA SAOTOME: That
white light was
the last thing we remembered.
When we came to, it was like
something out of a nightmare,
or one of those horror movies.
Fortunately, the Master--
-Oh, what a fool I've been.
How?
How could I have
been so selfish?
Abusing a poor, defenseless
brassier like that.
Never again.
Never again will an innocent
undergarment be made to suffer.
GENMA SAOTOME: The Master
was as good as his word.
He consigned the
Happo-Fire Burst technique
to the mists of time, wherein
he promptly forgot all about it.
[laughing]
-Huh?
HAPPOSAI: Ah, but now
I've remembered it again.
All I've got a do is find that
scroll and you three traitors
are going to be
my first victims.
[squawking]
-Cut it out, you guys!
-Guys?
What guys?
-Just us chickens.
[squawking]
-Come on, I'm serious, here.
He needs that dumb
scroll, right?
Well what if he don't got it?
If we can track it down before
he does we can use it on him,
see?
-That's the spirit.
-That's my boy.
You'll get our
revenge for us yet.
[laughing]
[chirping]
GENMA SAOTOME: I'm sure he
hid it around here, somewhere.
Look, it's under there.
Oh!
-Huh?
What is it?
-The-- the-- the-- the Master.
He--
-Ah!
Where?
-Now you're just seeing ghosts.
I'm going.
-Ah
[crashing and screaming]
-Did you hear that?
-What did you think it was?
-Maybe wild animals?
-It-- it's in the
middle of a hot spring.
-I don't remember
anything about-- uh--
What are we going
to do, Saotome?
-(VOICEOVER) Ha ha!
Just where I left it.
SOUN TENDO: Ah.
So close, Saotome.
So close, and yet so far.
GENMA SAOTOME:
Don't worry, Tendo.
We'll get to that scroll
before the Master does.
I have an idea.
-I ain't doing it.
Besides, turning into
a girl is no good.
I'd only change back when I
hit the hot water, anyway.
[splash] Hmm?
Huh?
-Disguising with paint.
Oh, Saotome, how clever of you.
[shrieking]
-What we know to be
a perfectly harmless,
friendly panda will
appear to those girls
as a man-eating grizzly bear.
-Hey, hey!
Way to go, Mister Tendo.
That plan of your
ain't half bad.
-It's a bear!
-Run for your life!
[roar]
-Huh?
-Jeeze, how dumb do
you think we are?
-Polar bears in Japan?
Please.
[grunting]
-Uh, ow!
-What next, genius?
-Nice try.
-You stinking amateurs.
-Master, I--
-I'm very disappointed.
I know I've taught
you better than that.
Ha!
Watch carefully, and let a
Master show you how it's done!
-Huh!
-Oh!
-Huh?
[splash]
-Hmm?
Ah, look, how cute,
it's a monkey.
-I've never seen one
u up close before.
-Hey, this is just like
a nature show on TV.
-What-- what skill.
-Observe how he didn't just
dress up as the monkey.
He actually became the monkey.
-(VOICEOVER) Now do you get it?
The secret to
successful voyeurism
is to imitate the
chameleon, to blend yourself
naturally in with
your surroundings.
Once you understand that,
it's simple, really.
-Oh, what a smart
Master we've got.
-Truly we don't deserve you.
-(VOICEOVER) About
time you realized it.
Hmm.
-Thank you, Master.
-Thank you.
-Hey, don't you think you're
forgetting something here?
If he gets that scroll
first, we're as good as dead.
[squawking]
[music playing]
[splash]
-Why you--
-Why didn't you go out there
in the first place, boy?
-Gee, I wonder.
-Show some respect
to your father.
-Yeah, show some respect
to your-- uh-- to me.
-You're our only hope.
-What he said.
[music playing]
-(VOICEOVER) Why do I
let them do this to me?
Oh, well.
All I gotta do is get
to that rock and--
-Oh, I'm in heaven.
-Uh oh
WOMAN 1: Pass me that
bath pail, will you?
WOMAN 2: Hey, do you want
me to scrub your back?
WOMAN 3: Gee, would you?
Thanks.
-Look at him, like a deer
caught in the headlights.
-I see nothing.
I see nothing.
I'm a girl too, so it's OK.
Oh?
Ooh!
-Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ah!
RANMA: Why you
disgusting little-- uh!
Oh!
-One splash of that hot
water and he's through.
[squawk]
-Think again, you little puke.
One splash in this
hot water and you'll
be singing a whole new tune,
now won't you, pig-tailed boy?
-We'll see about that.
Look!
A bra!
-Huh?
Where?
WOMAN 1: Did that
monkey just talk?
WOMAN 2: Now we know where
those wild animals came from.
-Eww!
It's a dirty old man
in a dirty old suit!
-How dare you insult
my suit like that.
[screaming]
WOMAN 1: Get him,
girls, get him!
-That scroll's mine!
-Oh, no you don't-- ah!
-Ah, uh!
[splash]
[gasping]
WOMAN 2: Oh!
The pervert escaped.
WOMAN 3: Geeze, that was quick.
WOMAN 1: Next time, though,
we'll be ready for him.
-Hmm, the little lecher.
Uh!
What are you, a mole?
-You embarrassed me
in front of the girls!
You meany!
Meany!
AKANE: Wow, it's
so peaceful here.
I've never been to
a hot spring before.
-Isn't it great?
It's girls only.
-Who want's to get in first?
-Of all the hot
springs for her to--
-Oh my stars and garters!
Akane!
-Hey!
Get back here!
-How did she--
-Small world, ain't it?
-Hey, watch where you're going.
-But what?
I thought that-- what
about the scroll?
-Drop a fish in
it, for all I care.
-Oh, well I guess you won't
mind if I go and get it, then.
-Help yourself.
RANMA: No, wait.
I changed my mind.
-A peeping Tom?
WOMAN 4: That's disgusting.
WOMAN 5: Oh, how gross!
-If he comes back,
I'll take care of him.
Huh?
Ya, ya!
WOMAN 5: What?
Eww!
-Uh huh.
A deer smoking a pipe.
Please!
-There should be one more.
-Let's split up
and look for him.
-I ain't got much time.
That dumb scroll ought to
be under here, somewhere.
Huh?
-Akane!
-What the--
-Huh!
[splash]
-You really didn't think
you'd get away with-- oh!
Uh!
-Uh.
-Akane, I-- I--
-Better start talking.
And you better make it good!
RANMA: I can explain!
Just [crash] wait! [crash] Wait!
Come on, don't--
[laughing]
-Too late, sucker.
The secret of the terrifying
Happo-Fire Burst is mine again.
-Now look at what you've--
-The terrifying what?
HAPPOSAI: Sucker!
-Take that!
-Ah!
-You fiend!
[splash]
-Ha ha.
Hey, all right, it's the scroll.
GENMA SAOTOME: Ranma,
you're absolutely
sure this is the
Master's scroll?
You're positive?
SOUN TENDO: It's
completely illegible.
-I, uh-- um--
-Jeeze, you could have
just told me, you know.
-And just how often is
it that you actually
listen before hitting me, huh?
-I can't make heads
or tails of it.
It must be authentic.
-Will the Master
translate it for us?
That's the question.
RANMA: Hey, I told ya
I'd take care of it.
SOUN AND GENMA: Thank
you, Ranma, thank you.
-(VOICEOVER) We'll see who
takes care of who, you traitors.
[music playing]
AKANE: I came here to use
the hot springs, Ranma,
not play tennis.
RANMA: Look at it this way,
until the old goat's gone,
you can't use them anyway.
AKANE: But isn't it too early
to be hitting the courts?
RANMA: If we wait
until later, he'll
be too busy peaking up
everyone else's skirts.
-We're counting on you, son.
-We'll be cheering for
you from the sidelines.
-But Ranma, are you sure you--
-Trust me, he'll come.
-But that's not what I meant.
-Have a little faith, will ya?
[giggling]
RANMA: (VOICEOVER) How can
he resist a proud bosom?
Flashing ankles,
slender as a fawn?
Frilly tennis shorts,
pure as the driven snow?
[giggling]
-Oh, a pair of dancing angels.
-I'm telling you, Akane,
it's a picture perfect plan.
If he don't come,
I'll be worried.
-You're the one
I'm worried about.
HAPPOSAI: Hi-a sugar cakes.
Hows about a game of love-love?
Oh, they really are
pure as the driven--
-Gotcha!
-Good work, boy.
-I knew it was a trap.
I just knew it.
Ah!
SOUN TENDO: Now
Master, if you'll
be so kind as to
translate this for us.
-Uh, but isn't this the
scroll with the secret
of the Happo-Fire Burst?
Won't he just turn
around and use it first?
[squawking]
-Oh, so now you mention it.
-You wouldn't listen to me.
You said I should
just trust you.
SOUN AND GENMA: Run away!
[music playing]
-Hmm?
Hmm.
I can't read my handwriting.
[wailing]
-You can't read your
own chicken scratches?
-I'm sure it's a writing
system of some kind.
-Maybe it's some
kind of hidden code.
-Would you two please shut up?
Can't you see I'm
trying to read, here?
Cock-a-doodle-do--
RANMA: It is chicken scratches.
-What kind of Master are you?
-You're a disgrace
to the martial arts.
-Stop yelling at me!
You're making me nervous!
How am I supposed to
read when I'm nervous?
Tell me that, huh, smarty.
Ay, ay, ay.
-Well, what do you know, Tendo?
-It seems the Happo-Fire Burst
is no longer a threat, Saotome.
-I'll give you a
dreaded technique.
I've been waiting for this.
Take that, and that.
-And that!
[breathing hard]
RANMA: Hey, hey,
he ain't moving.
-Then to finish the job--
-That's enough.
Aren't you being a little--
HAPPOSAI: Do it.
Finish me off.
Without my Happo-Fire
Burst technique
what is the point of going on?
I just don't--
-Come on, Gramps.
I can think of
plenty of reasons,
like being able to kill
you all over again!
-Na, na, na-- oh!
Oh, ah, I don't feel so good.
Ah ha!
I just remembered my secret
technique, Happo-Fire Burst!
[music playing]
-Ah, the Happo-Fire Burst.
We never did get a
chance to learn it.
-I hate to say it, but perhaps
it's for the best, Tendo.
HAPPOSAI: Would you
really like to learn it?
RANMA: I got it!
Uh!
SOUN AND GENMA: Ah!
-Huh?
What was that screaming?
Dad?
RANMA: Hey, you little freak,
now what have you done?
-Ranma, you brought
this on yourself.
Happo-Fire Burst!
[music playing]
-Ya!
Uh! Ah!
-Please don't try to tell
me that that was supposed
to be the dreaded
Happo-Fire Burst.
[coughing]
-Ha!
-Uh!
[explosion]
-You'll be sorry.
Uh!
-Yeah right.
Ultimate technique, my butt.
Uh!
-I told you you'd be sorry!
[music playing]
RANMA: Ah!
Run away!
HAPPOSAI: Ha ha!
That's right, you little puke.
Run!
AKANE: Ranma!
-Happo-Fire Burst.
Who does he think he's kidding?
-I can't believe we lived
in terror of a fire cracker!
-Let's just worry about
Ranma, right now, OK?
HAPPOSAI: Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha!
-I didn't wanna do this,
but you asked for it.
-Oh!
How sweet it is!
-Let's see you get
out of this one.
-Ranma, you shouldn't have.
Oh!
Huh?
Uh oh.
[music playing]
-Huh?
-What?
-He-- he to stopped it.
-Incredible.
-Gee, he ain't half bad.
OK, Gramps, you made your point.
Uh!
HAPPOSAI: Ah!
No!
Ah!
[explosion]
SOUN TENDO: Farewell, Master.
Farewell.
What a way to go.
AKANE: A martial
artist to the very end.
RANMA: Hasta luego, pervert!
KASUMI TENDO: Fireworks, huh?
Isn't that unusual
for this time of year?
-Yeah, those were the
best looking fireworks
I've ever seen in
my entire life.
Right, old man?
-I'll say.
-Let's have a
drink to celebrate.
-Why not?
By the way, how was it, Akane?
Having Ranma and the
others along for your trip
to the hot springs, I mean.
Was it fun?
-I'm tired, OK?
-Well, before you turn
in, where's my souvenir?
-Hmm?
Oh yeah, I almost forgot.
OK, for you, Nabiki--
hey, what's this?
-Hmm?
Oh no!
It's a--
-Ranma, don't you know
you shouldn't play ball
in the house?
-Then take it!
-Ya!
-Ha!
[music playing]
[explosion]
-I can hardly wait
for the summertime.
How about you guys?
Huh?
SOUN AND GENMA:
Thank you, Master.
Thank you!
[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
NARRATOR: Excuse me,
Tsubasa, are you listening?
Ukyo's a girl, OK?
A girl!
You understand?
Then stop chasing
her around like that.
You're almost as
stubborn as she is.
Next time on Ranma 1/2, I Love
You, Oh My Darling, Uchan.
We'll see you there.