[music playing]
THEME MUSIC:
[non-english singing]
(SINGING) So sweet I found you.
[non-english singing] No.
No.
Don't cheat.
[non-english singing].
Carry on.
Can't stop it.
No way out.
You can't stop it.
[non-english singing].
How can you hold me on?
[wind blowing]
[leaves blowing]
[crunching]
Now an update on the typhoon.
The winds in the
area are rapidly
gaining strength, and
the anticipated time
for the center of the typhoon
to pass over-- [static]
Hm?
Uh-oh.
[static]
[wind blowing]
[murmuring]
Hey, shouldn't this line
be plugged into the antenna?
Hurry up and plug
it in, Saotome.
I'm going as fast
as I can, Tendo.
Now, let's see.
What if I stick
these two together?
[static]
[singing]
The sharks are out and
there's blood in the water.
[static]
We come from Planet Pelala.
Take us to your leader.
[static]
I guess there's no
more TV for awhile.
TENDO: Ready, Saotome?
Here goes.
SAOTOME: That's it.
Straight up.
Keep going.
Perfect.
That's the way.
It's a sad day having to admit
that these two numbskulls are
my martial arts disciples.
Oh.
If you're so wise then
you could always lend us
a helping hand, you know.
Yeah.
That's right.
(YELLING) Are you nuts?
I don't have time to
help you with your chores
around the house!
Not on a wonderful
day like this.
This is a wonderful day?
Sure.
See?
Here comes something
wonderful now.
Ha ha.
Oh.
This is sweet.
Nothing like a
blustery day to warm
the cockles of a man's heart.
Pervert.
Figures.
A typhoon is a big panty raid.
Who knows what evil lurks
in the hearts of men.
[music playing]
NARRATOR: The Tendo
Dragon Legend.
Not only did you get detention,
you got homework to boot.
It's ridiculous
considering all I
did was have a little
shut-eye during class.
And why didn't you wake me up?
I was going to, but you looked
like you could use the sleep.
This isn't my day.
Now I've got to write some
stupid report on nature.
Akane, help me!
Don't startle me like that!
Sorry.
But I'm begging.
Will you help me
with my homework?
You got that homework
for sleeping in class.
So why should I
help you with it?
That's obvious.
Because you and I are, um--
Yeah?
(LAUGHING NERVOUSLY) Right.
I guess you shouldn't have to.
Huh.
Come on.
Don't be like that.
Huh?
Hey, watch where you're
aiming that thing.
Look.
What's that?
Ew.
What is that?
[splash]
What's a seahorse doing here?
I don't know.
Your guess is as good as mine.
We're nowhere near any water.
Maybe someone dropped
it on the way home
from the goldfish shop.
Does this look like
a goldfish to you?
Hello, you two.
Oh, Dr. Tofu.
You know, you should go home.
The rain's going to
start any minute now.
Hm.
What you got there?
What?
This?
We found it in the puddle here.
What a strange-looking fish.
Is it a seahorse, Dr. Tofu?
Uh, it's similar,
but I don't think so.
We should check it out, though.
All right!
I'm going to write
my report on it.
Jeez.
Isn't that convenient?
Good idea.
It looks pretty weak.
So you take it home and take
care of it for the time being.
KASUMI: Hello.
Hi, Kasumi.
Have you been shopping?
Yes.
I thought we'd better stock
up before the typhoon hits.
Are you making a
house call, Dr. Tofu?
Uh, yeah.
[crack]
My, it's beautiful weather
we're having, isn't it?
Oh.
That reminds me, Ranma.
Your father was looking for.
He needs some help around the
house before the typhoon hits.
Oh, right.
I guess we have to
nail things down.
OK.
KASUMI: Hey, I know.
Dr. Tofu, do you
mind coming over too?
You're so much more
reliable than Ranma.
RANMA: Hey, I do my
part when I have to.
Grab a brain.
Sometimes you're so dense.
Huh?
[laughing]
Oh.
I get it.
What do you say, Dr. Tofu?
Will you come out to our place?
Uh.
Well, I--
KASUMI: Please, Dr. Tofu?
We'd all enjoy your company.
Now, this is
getting complicated.
(SINGING) [inaudible]
little dinner.
He'll fall in love.
It'll be--
Here you are.
Thanks.
There you go.
Great.
Excuse me, everyone.
I've made some tea for you you.
--[gulp] (NERVOUSLY)
There you go.
Here you are.
We got to go.
Huh, there you go.
Ha.
Here you go.
And, uh--
Uh.
Excuse me, Dr. Tofu.
Ah!
[crash]
[beeping]
[grunting]
Could you listen it
a little, Mr. Saotome?
Mr. Tendo, I'm going to need you
to tighten your side up a bit.
Considerate it done.
[crack]
Huh?
DR. TOFU: (STRAINING)
Tighter, please.
OK.
If you say.
Hey.
Not my tree!
[grunting]
Not too shabby.
Next one.
[grunting]
Whew.
All done.
No!
I can't get out!
[banging]
--[grunting] Why can't
I open the door?
Hm.
Something tells me Ranma must
have had a hand in this mess.
(MIMICKING) I'll protect you
from the dangerous typhoon,
Akane.
That's why Ranma did this.
Hey!
Let me in, please!
I'm your father.
You can't do this to me.
[gasp] Ranma!
Hurry and open up.
RANMA: I'm trying!
I'm trying!
(CRYING) Hurry!
Please!
Oh!
Ah!
[wind blowing]
[clanking]
[raindrops falling]
Thanks for dinner!
We sure got a lot
of work done today.
And just in time before
the strong rains hit.
Dr Tofu, your
dinner's getting cold.
Don't wait for us.
You just help yourself.
I will.
Thanks.
Please.
Well, thanks again
for inviting me.
Oh.
This is good.
[laughing]
He has good days and bad.
DR. TOFU: Delectable.
Huh?
[splash]
Water.
Water?
There's a leak in the ceiling.
[gasps]
[splash]
Paper, scissors, stone.
Aw.
Hurry back, now.
[growling]
Hm?
Oh.
[thunder]
Huh?
Grandfather, you're
just in time for dinner.
What are you doing
in this dark room?
Why didn't you come
and eat with us?
What is that?
Someone took a tile off
the roof on purpose?
Yeah.
That creeps me out.
Hey, Saotome, are you sure it
wasn't some kind of mistake?
[grunt]
[scream]
Huh?
[gasps]
[panting]
The door was open so I
thought it was grandfather.
And when I looked in,
the room was like this.
I see.
Now it makes sense.
What Mr. Saotome told
us must be true then.
[grunt]
Hey, look.
It's wet.
The ceiling in
here isn't leaking.
So it must mean someone's come
in wet from the rain and is
in the house now.
Ranma!
Hm.
I don't know who's behind
all this weird stuff,
but it looks like we've
got a mystery to solve.
--[humph] I say we get moving
and flush this joker out.
Hm?
It's wet here too.
And inside here.
All the way up the stairs?
Where's this water coming from?
Huh?
All right!
You're safe!
No one would break it
to get a stupid fish.
Huh?
Yeah?
Well, excuse me for caring!
He's going to be my report.
right?
[zing]
[sigh] Hm?
These are fresh!
Huh?
[click]
[zap]
Huh?
Stop!
I'll find you sooner or later.
[grunt]
[scream]
Akane!
That's Akane!
Huh?
[grunting]
[yelling]
Huh?
They're frogs!
[yelling]
[grunt]
I got to all his
vital pressure points.
So for the time being,
he's completely paralyzed.
You're not hurt,
are you, Akane?
Uh-uh.
Akane, honey,
are you all right?
Huh?
Wait a sec.
I've seen this old guy before.
Oh.
Now I remember.
It's the frog hermit.
[squawking]
[gulping]
[chomping]
I'll have some more.
Right away.
What did this guy ever
do to deserve seconds?
Tell me that!
He sneaked into the house.
He got everything sopping wet!
And on top of that,
he attacked Akane!
Ludicrous!
I never attacked anybody.
That's just my way of saying
a friendly, how do you do?
[chomping]
That's good enough
reason for me.
Besides, we can't just
kick the poor fellow out
on a night like tonight.
[grunt]
Then how do you explain
that he broke into the house
instead of using the door?
Oh, this is yummy.
Let it go.
Will you?
Besides, maybe he'll give
us a free frog performance.
Right, froggy?
Hm?
What?
Were you talking to me
just now, young lady?
[music playing]
Oh.
Very good.
Cute.
[grunt]
Those frogs have
some kind of talent.
[clapping]
And that's our
performance for today.
I hope you enjoyed the
talented Men in Green.
I usually charge admission,
but today it's on the house.
Huh?
Nothing but a bunch
of cheap skates.
Uh.
Speaking of pets,
I heard somewhere
that you people have a rare pet.
Do you think I could
take a look at it?
Oh.
I bet you must mean that
unusual fish Ranma brought home
with him today.
It seems to be a
very rare species.
Right, Doctor?
Yes.
A very rare species indeed.
FROG HERMIT: Is that so?
Well, I'll excuse myself
if you don't mind.
He doesn't look too healthy.
He hasn't eaten
anything all day.
I think he needs to
have a bigger tank.
What the heck are
you doing in my room?
Oh, this is an
extremely rare species,
so you have to take
good care of it.
What's it got to do with you?
Come off it, Ranma.
He's just giving
some friendly advice.
I don't know.
Maybe I should ask Dr. Tofu to
take a look at my fish here.
Ah!
[crash] [grunt]
Are you OK, Ranma?
Thanks a lot!
Oh.
That's such a shame.
You should be more careful.
You're the one who
tripped me, jerk.
Oh, well.
Accidents happen.
I put the little
guy in the pond.
No need to thank me. [laughs]
Like someone was gonna!
Creepy frog.
Go, Ranma!
Right.
Hold it!
I think he's going to
release him into the pond.
Yeah.
I need you to grow a little
bit bigger for me, friend.
[gasp] No!
Hm.
Nope.
I'm not getting
anything here, Saotome.
Maybe you should go
back up on the roof
and check on that antenna.
[snoring]
Yo, Pop!
Tea's on, everyone.
Oh, where did Dr. Tofu get to?
He said he needed to look at
some of Happosai's old biology
textbooks.
So he went into the
old goad's room.
Huh?
KASUMI: The power's off.
TENDO: [sigh]
Wouldn't you know it.
The candles are all upstairs.
AKANE: No probs.
I'll go get them.
I'll go with you.
Thanks, Ranma.
That's much better.
Did you find anything out?
Yes.
I think so.
I'm not entirely
certain yet, but this
might be quite a bit more
serious than we first thought.
How do you mean?
A baby dragon?
That little fish?
Are you saying
it's a real dragon?
I couldn't believe it myself,
but now I'm quite confident.
Take a look at this.
Incredible!
This dragon grows as the
storm builds and rises
to the sky like a giant tornado.
Uh.
Like at tornado?
Are you sure it's
not just a legend?
It's a legend based on truth.
And there's one other
legend surrounding
the gigantic dragon.
What is it?
Eating the dragon's
flesh gives eternal life.
[gasp]
A single bite of the
dragon's flesh, and your life
is extended by 100 years.
That's why the dragon has
been sought after and slain
for many generations.
Man, if even some of
this stuff is true,
then I'm going to
totally ace that paper
I've got to do for
homework this weekend.
You know, your homework marks
aren't really the issue here,
Ranma.
First, we have to make
sure it is the dragon.
Man, what a gross night.
Look!
There's the frog hermit!
Get over here!
Oh.
It's your dad!
What are you doing sitting
out here in the rain, Pop?
Way to go, Mr. Saotome!
You were eavesdropping.
Weren't you, Pop?
Uh-uh.
Ha!
[growl]
That proves that
you were listening!
Jeez, you'd think he'd
have better things
to do with his time.
Oh, no!
Ranma!
We've got to do something
or the baby dragon
will be washed
away by the storm.
Got ya!
Akane, go get me a
bucket on the double.
Right!
Hold on, you two.
A bucket's not going to be
nearly big enough anymore.
My little fish is enormous.
I knew it.
So it really is a dragon.
You're going to
make me a fine feast,
aren't you, little dragon.
I knew you had something up
your sleeve, you poison toad!
Ah.
Very clever.
I came all the way from
China to get my hands
on this baby dragon.
Too bad for you.
I need this dragon so I
can finish my homework.
Will you forget about
your dumb homework
and just concentrate
on the issue?
I can't help it.
That paper's for a lot of marks.
I know.
You've told me.
Now.
[grunting]
[yelling]
Ranma!
Akane!
I'll get them! [grunting]
My frogs!
Now, it's your
turn to have a nap.
Let me take care of this guys.
[grunt]
Ha, ha, ha.
[yelling]
Ranma!
Now that you're
out of the way I'll
help myself to my delectable
little dragon dish.
[yelling] Oh.
If you think we're going
to subject this baby
dragon to such a
horrible fate then you've
got another thing
coming, frog hermit.
Huh?
Let's just see about that.
[yelling]
--[blah] You have a lot
to learn, science boy,
if you think you stand a
chance against ancient Chinese
fighting traditions
such as this one.
Dr. Tofu, I believe
this is your weak point.
Hm?
Uh.
Hello, Kasumi.
Beautiful weather.
Told you I'd win.
No!
Dr. Tofu!
[grunt]
We could do this
all night, you know.
Go!
This time things are going to
turn out a little different.
Ah!
[boom]
[yelling]
Got it!
Way to go!
Oh.
Nice work.
[thunder]
[explosion]
[crash]
Now what's going on out there?
[grunt]
Oh.
Oh, no!
Look.
What's that?
Oh, my.
[gasp]
[roar]
What a haul!
I'd sell my soul for
a week of typhoons.
Hm?
Oh.
A dragon.
[grumble] Ruh-roh.
You're bye.
[growl] Huh?
Oh, wait, my lovelies.
I'll save you.
Ha ha.
[music playing]
[laughing]
FROG HERMIT: Gather
around in the guineas.
CHILD: Parade! [laughs]
My pet frogs and I have a very
special show lined up for you
today.
And believe me, you'll never
see anything like this on TV.
[laughs] Don't worry.
I'll pass the hat later.
Gather around now.
The show's about to begin.
Look.
The frog hermit's still in town.
That's him all right.
But he looks a lot
happier somehow.
Yeah.
You're right.
What do you say we
check out the show?
Good plan!
[music playing]
NARRATOR: When we were
all little, looking up,
you could always count on the
smiling face of your mother.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Boy Meets Mom, Part One."
We'll see you there.