[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): "Ranma
Meets Love Head-On!
Enter the Delinquent
Juvenile Gymnast!"
MAN: You're so cute, I thought
I'd give you an extra scoop.
-Yay!
Hey, mister, thanks.
-All right, here you go.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Yep.
When it comes to eating
out, being a girl's
the only way to go.
-Why, you must be
from Furinkan High.
I'm so looking
forward to next week.
Sure, our school's may be
rivals, but, well, I do
hope we'll still be friends.
After you've lost, I mean.
-You're such a liar.
-We'd never be friends with you.
FURINKAN GIRL 1: Don't think we
don't know what you're up to.
FURINKAN GIRL 2: You're
trying to stop us
from competing in
the tournament.
FURINKAN GIRL 3: Why
else would you ambush us?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Hey, I
think they're in my class.
FURINKAN GIRL 1: We're
going to give you
a taste of your own medicine.
-Let's get her.
-Now, now, girls.
If I weren't a lady--
if I weren't a lady,
I'd have to teach you a lesson.
And then you'd
really be in trouble.
How lucky for you that I
was reared better than that?
-Come on, cut it out.
I think you made
your point already.
-You stopped my ribbon.
That's never been done.
You're no ordinary
girl, are you?
-Well, ah, yeah.
I guess you could say that.
-It makes no difference to me.
Well then, I won't
go an easier on you.
Oh!
You are quite formidable.
Well done.
I am the flower of St.
Hebereke High School.
A rising star in gymnastics.
I'm Kodachi, the Black Rose.
You will keep that
in mind, won't you?
[maniacal laughter]
[crying]
-Huh?
Aw, don't cry.
-Akane.
-We got beat up.
-All of you?
The entire gymnastics team?
-She jumped us in the
middle of the night.
-We can't fight like this.
We'll have to forfeit
the tournament.
FURINKAN GIRL 2: Please, Akane.
We asked everyone we know.
You're our last hope.
-Me?
You want me to fill in for you?
-We're begging you, Akane.
We're really desperate.
Please!
-Yes, it's our most
important event.
-Martial Arts
Rhythmic Gymnastics.
-Martial Arts Rhythmic what?
-Don't tell me
you haven't heard?
-It's our gymnastics team
against St. Hebereke High
School.
-Nickname St. Bacchus.
-Hm.
I don't know how good I'll
be, but I'll give it a try.
-Thank you, Akane.
-Thank you.
-Don't worry.
I'll avenge you all.
-Th-- th-- thank you, Akane.
-That was pretty stupid of you.
Akane, you'll never
learn all this junk.
-We'll just see about that.
[oink]
-Hm?
-Huh?
-Oh, look.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Ryoga.
-Where have you been?
I've been so worried, P-Chan.
-P-Chan?
-You know, "Pig Cute."
Be a good boy and stay here.
Ranma, don't bully him.
-Every time I think you
can't sink any lower,
you go and surprise me again.
-I told you not to pick on him.
HEBEREKE GIRL 1: Come on,
try a back hand spring.
HEBEREKE GIRL 2: OK.
Give me a hand over here.
I need some help.
HEBEREKE GIRL 1: OK.
That's great.
HEBEREKE GIRL 2: OK.
HEBEREKE GIRL 1: Do it
one more time and turn.
HEBEREKE GIRL 2: No,
mo-- turn it around.
HEBEREKE GIRL 1: Yeah.
-Right.
That's all today.
-Whoa, that was rough.
I'm exhausted.
-Oh yeah, that reminds me.
Who's supposed to
lead tonight's ambush?
-As long as we've got
Kodachi on our side,
our team's invincible.
Why do we even practice?
We always win be default anyway.
-You'd better not let
Kodachi hear you say that.
KODACHI (VOICEOVER):
Fear not, Miss Tendo.
I'll be dealing with
you very shortly.
[maniacal laughter]
-You just watch.
-Hey, aren't you supposed
to catch those things?
-I'm trying, OK?
Maybe I'll try the ribbon.
-You uh, supposed to tie
yourself up like that?
-Who asked you?
-Are you supposed to
break the hoop like that?
-No, no, no!
-Aren't you supposed to be
just a little bit graceful
when you're doing this stuff?
-I don't believe this!
[door opening]
[door closing]
-OK, I'm not good at it.
I'm a klutz.
A klutz, a klutz, a klutz!
-Well, what do you
want me to do about it?
RYOGA: Would you
like me to train you?
-Huh?
It's Ryoga.
-Hey, how's it going, P-Chan?
Oh.
Uh oh.
-Who you calling P-Chan?
-Wouldn't we all like to know?
-Thanks, Ryoga.
OK That's really nice of you.
-Really?
The first technique
is the ribbon.
-Huh?
-That's-- that's cool.
[grumble]
-Why you.
KODACHI (VOICEOVER): So
they've asked for help.
What poor loser those
Furinkan girls are.
Akane Tendo, you'll soon rue the
day you crossed the Black Rose.
[maniacal laughter]
-La la.
[panting]
-I think we've done
enough for today.
-Thanks, Ryoga, for training me.
-Your ribbon's
coming along nicely.
I'm certain you'll
master it soon.
-D-- do you really think so?
-Aw, man.
He's lying through his teeth.
-Shut up, Ranma.
Only one more week until
the Martial Arts Rhythmic
Gymnastics Tournament.
I should never have
volunteered for this.
-You know, she's so
hopeless, it hurts to watch.
I guess you're pretty
proud of yourself, huh?
You're not helping.
I wouldn't keep buttering her
up so much if I was you, Ryoga.
-Hmph.
Male jealousy is a pitiful
thing to see, Ranma.
-What?
J-- jealous?
Who's jealous of-- huh?
Oh no, you don't.
Think you're going to sleep
in Akane's bed again, do you?
-Oh.
I could sleep for a week.
Oh.
Huh?
-Akane Tendo, prepare to die!
-Who are you?
-I'm from the St. Hebereke
rhythmic gymnastics
team, of course.
I'm Kodachi, the Black Rose.
-Kodachi who?
-There's only one
more week before we
face each other
in the gymnastics
tournament next week.
So let's both fight fair, OK?
-Fair?
Compared to what?
I didn't ask you to
sneak into my room.
And I never asked you to
attack me in the dark.
-In the dark?
Utterly ridiculous.
I came merely to size up my
opponent before the big match
next week.
That's all.
-Don't you give me that.
-You're finished, dear.
Die!
-Come here, you little runt.
Get-- Come here.
Get back-- Come-- come here.
Hey!
Get off.
-Hey, wait a minute, you guys.
Ranma, leave him alone.
Hiya!
-So you really do
have some skill.
I shall return.
-What?
Rose petals?
And who's going to clean
up the mess you made, huh?
You wait, Black Rose.
Next week at the match,
I'll give you the same.
KODACHI (VOICEOVER): Just
you wait, Miss Tendo.
This time next week, you'll
be begging me for mercy.
A pig?
RANMA: Come here, Ryoga!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Huh?
It felt like the kettle
just smacked into something.
Whoa!
Are-- are you OK?
KODACHI (VOICEOVER): What a man.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Uh oh.
It's what's her face--
Black Petunia or whatever.
-Ah, I--
-Huh?
-Hold me.
-Um, hey.
What's going on here?
I mean, uh-- oh man.
-Honestly, I don't believe him.
Here I am, being attacked
by some crazy girl,
and all he cares about
is chasing after P-Chan
so he can pick on him some more.
That's it.
It's over.
Huh?
Oh, no.
-Well, since you're not hurt,
guess I'll be taking off.
I'll see you around maybe, OK?
Bye bye.
-Oh!
Oh, my head.
The blow, it-- it was more
dreadful than I thought.
KODACHI (VOICEOVER):
And here I was
beginning to think I'd
never meet any eligible men.
Guess an all-girls school
was the wrong place
to look for Mr. Right.
And now that I've met him--
-I'll, uh-- I'll go get you
some aspirin or something.
Oh!
-Don't go.
[creak]
-Huh?
An earthquake?
-How could I have known that
when I came here tonight,
I'd meet the man of my dreams.
Your name, kind sir.
-Hm?
Ranma, Ranma Saotome.
-Ran-- ma Saotome.
Dearest Ranma, take these.
-Huh?
-I put a bit of paralysis
powder into the flowers.
-What'd you do that for?
I never did anything to--
-Now, my darling.
Be brave and take that
which you most desire.
Seize these ruby lips of mine.
I-- I mustn't.
This one sweet kiss puts an
end to my colorless school girl
life.
But before I close that
chapter of my life--
[grunting]
Ranma, darling, thank
you for waiting.
-I'm not waiting.
I'm paralyzed.
-And now, my darling.
make me your own.
-Akane.
-Right over my
bedroom of all places.
-How unsporting of you.
-I wouldn't talk if I were
you, you-- you-- you cheater!
-Hm.
I know when I'm not wanted.
Ranma darling, I'll
make this up to you.
Farewell, my sweetums.
Until we meet again.
[maniacal laughter]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Honestly.
Looks like the party's
over for tonight.
Good night.
-W-- wait.
KODACHI (VOICEOVER):
Yes, darling, yes.
Draw the sweet nectar
from these honeyed lips.
-Now she's done it.
I don't care what I
have to do to beat her.
[snoring]
[dog barking]
-Somebody help me!
--La la.
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Even
though I kept telling myself
I won't lose, I messed
up and hurt myself.
So now he has to
fight in my place.
Ranma, you better not lose.
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
"A Woman's Love is War.
The Martial Arts Rhythmic
Gymnastic Challenge!"
See you there.