[music playing]
[music - ribbon, "little date"]
NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hey, let go!
-Hai-yah!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma is
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
FEMALE VOICE (ON LOUDSPEAKER):
Thank you for your patronage.
To celebrate the China
Festival this weekend,
many of the Center's
merchants are
offering special sales
and one-day-only bargains.
Be sure to stop by, and
mention the China Festival
for an additional 10%
off your purchase.
Kasumi!
-Huh?
Look what I got!
I used some coupons
and got this for free!
-Oh!
Well, that's good
for you, Akane.
--[giggles] I've wanted it
since the store opened.
[mean laughter]
-Huh?
GUY: Akane Tendo,
betrothed of Ranma Saotome.
[laughter]
-OK.
So, uh, who are you?
[gasp] Look out!
[laughs]
-Huh?
--[laughs] When they ask who
has taken Akane Tendo from you,
tell them it was the
mysterious masked man.
-Huh?
Hey, what's going on?
-Give this message to Ranma.
If he ever wants to
see Akane Tendo again--
-Go on.
-He'll make sure he's
sitting front row
center at the Chinese circus.
-He'll make sure he's what?
-Everything you need to
know is on the ticket.
Parking is extremely
limited, so please
be sure to use public
transportation,
if at all possible.
-Hey, you!
Come back!
[laughs]
-My, what an odd boy.
For some strange
reason, he seems
to think you're that
stuffed pig, Akane.
-Ugh!
He can't talk to me that way!
That jerk!
NARRATOR: The
Abduction of Akane.
RANMA: What do you mean,
Akane's been taken hostage?
GENMA: You've got to
go after her, boy.
-I told you, I'm fine!
-But why the heck do
I have to be the one
to go and rescue her?
AKANE: I'm right here!
GENMA: Eyes front!
[splash]
[gasp]
[sigh]
RANMA: Huh?
GENMA: This is the kind of
sloppiness I'm talking about.
Prove you're worthy of
carrying on the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
Rescue Akane from that fiend.
It's the least you can
do for your fiancee.
-(SHOUTING) I told
you, I'm fine!
[band playing]
-Akane, why'd you have
to drag me here for?
-I've already told you.
We've come to get my
stuffed animal back.
-[giggles] Oh, ni hao, Ranma!
-Sh-sh-shampoo.
-Oh, Ranma, Shampoo
so happy to see you!
Ranma date with
Shampoo now, yes?
-Uh, sorry, I gotta
go rescue Akane.
You see, some creep's
holding her hostage.
-I'm right here, stupid!
-Aw, man!
Like I got nothing better to do.
-Hai-yah!
Look, Shampoo found
exact same ticket
left at restaurant already.
-You got the very same ticket?
-Wonder why?
FEMALE VOICE (ON
LOUDSPEAKER): That's it.
Step right up.
Come see the greatest
acrobat troupe on Earth.
-I don't think I know
anybody in the circus.
-Not Shampoo friend.
[menacing laugh]
-Huh?
Well, well, what a coincidence.
Ranma Saotome.
-That's him!
That's the guy!
--[laughs] I think we're in
for an especially good show
tonight.
-It's you!
-Hai-yah!
It Mousse!
-Ranma Saotome, out until
you release your evil hold
on Shampoo, Akane Tendo
shall remain my woman.
[squeak]
-Hey, cut it out!
You're making her cry!
All
-All right, you!
In what way does
that look like me?
[grunts]
-Huh?
Huh?
[squeak]
-Aaaaahhh!
Akane Tendo's become a pig!
-It's a doll, moron.
--[giggles] You are
stupid as ever, Mousse.
-[laughs] Maybe even stupider!
[gong]
[music playing]
[applause]
-Wow!
That was great!
-Hai-yah!
We so lucky to get free ticket.
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER): Enjoy it
while you can, Ranma Saotome.
By the time the
show's over, you'll
know what it feels like to
have your true love stolen
by another.
[drum roll]
-Attention lady and gentlemen.
One member of audience,
please volunteer.
Whoever come down to
ring get special prize.
It's very cute toy pig, no?
-Hey!
That's mine!
-Akane!
How'd you get there?
-That does it!
-Aaaaaahhhhhh!
[cheering and applause]
-Ah, thank you!
-Ah, that honeyed voice!
It is my beloved pigtailed girl!
-Please, Master Kuno,
everyone's watching.
ACROBATS: (CHANTING)
The show must go on.
[cheering and applause]
-No worry!
This trick safe.
Volunteer get killed
only one time.
[gong]
[drum roll]
-Thank you, nice assistant.
-Aaaagghh!
-Hai-yah!
-Hey!
-My love!
-What'd you do that for?
-Please allow me to
present big star of show.
This one duck you never forget.
So lady and gentlemen, I
very proud to present to you
the amazing Mumu-chan!
Please to give big round of
applause for amazing Mumu-chan.
now!
[cheering and applause]
[both giggling]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
That's no ordinary duck.
[growls]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
It's gonna knife me!
[growls]
[gasps]
-So that's how you
wanna play it, eh?
[crowd roars]
-Why, you--!
[growls]
[gasps]
-Aaaaauuughhhh!
-Aaaahh!
I can't stand it anymore!
Be brave, pigtailed girl!
I'll prove my love now!
[shouting]
-Dropping bombs!
-Look out, Ranma!
[explosions]
[coughing]
-Where have you
gone to, my love?
-Ranma?
Where he go to?
-Don't know.
[faint cheering and applause]
RANMA: Ha!
I just knew that dopey
duck looked familiar.
--[laughs] Why, the
show's only just begun.
That was just a taste
of what you'll get.
Prepare for death,
Ranma Saotome.
-Huh.
You paid for this
ticket here, so you
can bet I'm going to enjoy it.
-Oh, you'll enjoy it, all right.
I want to share
everything with you.
Yes, I wouldn't dream of
keeping all the fun to myself.
Huaaah!
Can you guess what I've
got in the bucket, Ranma?
-HuH?
-Can you guess what I've
got in the bucket, Ranma?
-Um, water?
MOUSSE: It's spring water
from a certain training
ground in China.
-Training ground?
-Don't play dumb.
After our battle, I went back
to my home in China-- and began.
-Here, sir, we come to
famous training ground
of cursed spring, Jusenkyo.
-I'll train here and put
an end to the evil Ranma.
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER):
As it turned out,
the only thing I ended was
my life as a normal man.
-Uh, no, sir!
Where are you going?
Practice on pole,
not in cursed spring!
-Hm?
Aaaaghhh!
-Uh-oh, you fall Yahzuniichuan,
the Spring of Drowned Duck.
[struggling]
-Story of this duck very tragic.
Legend say 3,000 years ago,
duck drown in Yahzuniichuan.
It is very cursed spring.
Whoever fall in take
body of unfortunate duck.
It's very cursed spring.
I no want swim in there.
[quacking]
-Oh, sir, in many, many
year I work as guide,
no one ever go in
spring on purpose.
What you do that for?
[quacking]
-You, Ranma Saotome!
From the moment I fell in the
spring, I've thought of nothing
but how I could destroy you!
[monkey hoots]
-Hey, watch it.
-Hm?
[monkey growls]
-Ranma?
Just when did your
face become so hairy?
[crunch]
-Aaaaahhhhhh!
You bit me, Ranma!
-Hey!
I'm right here, moron!
-Hm?
Auuughhh!
-Yo.
-Hm?
-So all your training
was for this, huh?
-Aaaaaghhhhh!
So
-Hm?
[wind whistling]
-Oh, no.
No!
You mean this water's from--
--[laughs] That's right,
from Yahzuniichuan.
Hyah!
Have some Spring
of Drowned Duck!
Final attack, [inaudible]
Dagger Strike!
-Aaaahhh!
-At last the end draws near!
Auughh!
-Huh?
-[angry quacking] Quack.
-Mousse!
Shampoo sorry, but no
can let you hurt Ranma.
-[frantic quacking] Quack.
-Hmf!
Shampoo never date
with stupid like you.
[sad quacking]
[plates shatter]
[groaning quack]
-Hmf!
[angry quacking]
-Hey, watch it.
Hey!
[angry quacking]
-Hai-yah!
Ranma!
[angry quacking]
[screaming and shouting]
-Doesn't that idiot quit?
[balloons popping]
Aaaauughhh!
-Huh?
-Look out!
[quacking]
-Mousse!
Cut it out, idiot, before
you really hurt somebody!
Hunh!
[frustrated quacking]
Listen up, Duck Boy.
Don't try and pin all
your problems on me.
Besides, I got about as
much interest in Shampoo--
[clang]
-[pants angrily] Huh?
[pointed quacking]
-Shampoo!
-Stupid.
Shampoo was actually
worried for you.
-Well, I appreciate
it, Shampoo-- agh!
-Ooh, you!
[angry meowing]
RANMA: Waauughh!
Go away!
Leave me alone!
Scat!
[angry meowing]
[quacking]
[grumbly quacking]
-Oh, where can my
pigtailed goddess be?
-Now, Master, the course of
true love never did run smooth.
-Well said.
Well said, Sasuke.
AKANE: (CALLING) Ranma?
Ranma, where are you?
Ranma!
Honestly, Shampoo's
nowhere to be found either.
Where can the two of
them have run off to now?
That jerk.
MOUSSE: [quiet laughter]
[gasp]
[screams]
-The monster!
Take that, and that, and that,
and that, and that, and that,
and that, and that, and that!
MOUSSE: Don't hit me,
Akane Tendo, it's me!
-Oh, yeah, your
name's Mousse, right?
[laughs nervously]
-Huh?
[bang]
-Oh!
[sigh]
[thud]
-This time, Akane
Tendo, you really
will be the bait that
lures Ranma Saotome to me.
SASUKE: Come, Master Kuno,
let's call off the search
till tomorrow.
KUNO: Bite your tongue, man!
Until I find my beloved,
there is nothing I-- oh, look!
There is Akane Tendo.
[chuckle]
-Fiend!
-Leave this to me, Master Kuno!
-AAaghhh!
[mean laughter]
-Drat.
That wasn't supposed to happen.
[growls]
FEMALE VOICE (ON LOUDSPEAKER):
Ladies and gentlemen,
over at the Big Top, the main
event is just about to begin.
Please take your seats.
FESTIVAL-GOER: A girl
that turns into a duck?
FESTIVAL-GOER:
She's kind of cute.
Let's go check it out!
-Get it offa me!
[meowing]
-Auugghhh!
[hissing]
[angry meowing]
-Whoa!
Whoooaaaaa!
[crash]
[thud]
[groaning]
[purring sweetly]
-Huh?
Huh?
He wouldn't dare!
Oh no.
Akane!
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER):
Hurry, Ranma Saotome.
If you don't rescue
her soon, Akane Tendo
will spend the rest
of her life as a duck.
RANMA: If you think I'm gonna
let you do that to Akane,
you've got another
think coming, pal.
[cheering and applause]
[crowd gasps]
[satisfied chuckling]
EMCEE: Lady and gentlemen, now
for show you all waiting for.
After magic water
poured into tank-- oh,
so incredible--
beautiful young girl
become duck before very eye!
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER):
Ranma Saotome,
the minute you
dive into the tank
to save the woman,
it's all over.
[panting]
-(SHOUTING) Akane!
[MUSIC - ETSUKO NISHIO, "DON'T
MIND CHINA BOY"]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
You just don't
know when to give
up, do you, Mousse?
I'll help you, but
just this one time.
Ranma, are you listening?
You just have to
pretend to lose.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Ranma versus Mousse-- to lose
is to win!
See you there.