[music playing]
[theme music]
[thunder]
Why did you summon me here?
I'd like an explanation.
Me be a needing you to act
as the Furinkan High School
substitute principal.
Substitute principal?
You be getting it.
Me be needing some recreational
education time away
from this place.
So me be choosing you
to take over the school
while I be getting jiggy.
No deal.
[inaudible].
Me not be saying
this as your daddy.
Me be giving you a chance
to prove you as a man.
You know me wouldn't
be asking if me
think you couldn't be doing.
[thunder]
You're asking me man to man?
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER): Tatewaki
Kuno-- Substitute Principal.
[chatter]
Boy, this weather
sure is weird.
I hear the principal's
going to be away for a while.
Wouldn't it be great
if he never came back?
I know I wouldn't
miss him at all!
Huh?
What the?
Can't you do something
about that guy, Akane?
It's a hopeless case.
Heh.
Allow me to present the
Furinkan Enforcers Squad.
Time to learn some
discipline, Saotome.
Enforcers squad?
[laughter]
As you can see from
this, I've been designated
as the substitute principal.
Now I am in charge, and we're
going to tighten things up
around this school.
Saotome, for slandering
the principal,
you shall receive a
caning of 100 lashes.
Now!
[yelling]
[screaming]
[grunt]
Oh, man.
There's a bad omen,
if I ever saw one.
[laughter]
What a perfect
chance this will be.
Saotome, I'm going to
join the Enforcers Squad
and finally get my turn
to pay you back but good.
Great theory, except for
saying it in front of me.
[screaming]
It looks like you could
probably use a hand.
I'll help, depending
on the terms.
Nabiki Tendo.
Right.
You'll receive
500 yen every time
you report a
student misdemeanor.
1,000.
You're on.
MAN: Who goes?
GOSUNKUGI: I'm on
your side here.
You-- you guys got me all wrong.
I just want to be one
of you enforcer guys.
Oh, can it.
Time to initiate phase one of
the Enforcer Squad's takeover.
Let Operation Ferocious
Typhoon and Tsunami commence.
Yeah!
Uh, yeah.
[music playing]
How is it, Taro?
I made it special
for you, poopsy.
Oh, Hinako.
Your lunches are always
the best, honey bear.
[sigh]
Taro.
Hinako.
[moan]
Furinkan regulations,
section two,
article one--
close relationships
with the opposite
sex are prohibited.
Further, males and
females are not
permitted to consume
lunch under the same tree.
You're guilty of both crimes.
I hereby order you
to wear these wigs
for one week as punishment.
For one whole week?
No!
[crying]
Hm?
AKANE: Hey, Kuno!
Huh?
Would you toss the ball
back over this way, please?
[gasp]
It is Akane Tendo.
Nothing would give
me more pleasure
than to throw this
ball back to my love.
Huh?
[laughter]
Of course, I would never be
in an illicit relationship
with a female student.
Move out!
Sir!
(VOICEOVER) It is with a heavy
heart that I turn away my sweet
Akane.
But the future of
Furinkan High School
wears heavily on
these shoulders.
You there!
You're missing a button!
And you!
Your pants are too long!
[yelling]
[groan]
One week with the skullcap!
Attention, you delinquents.
I want your personal
belongings on the desks now.
Aha!
As punishment, I sentence
you all to one week in a wig.
What?
That's not fair!
Come on!
[chatter]
I definitely can't go
outside looking like this.
That's for sure.
Well, then just
take the thing off.
But if Kuno finds out--
What if he does?
Yeah, so what?
Huh?
Ranma's making a
valid point here.
There's really no reason to be
afraid of the Enforcer Squad,
now is there?
Hey, there's a change.
You're right for the first time.
He is?
[groan]
Quiet, baldilocks.
OK, I give.
I give.
Ranma!
Enforcer Squad, Gosunkugi here
reporting that Ranma Saotome is
messing with Daisuke's
skullcap and--
Drop that!
I'll need backup.
Mercy.
Have mercy on me.
[whimpering]
Ranma Saotome.
This time, I cannot let your
indiscretions go unpunished.
Your point?
It is not out of
personal satisfaction
that I mete out your punishment.
It is solely for the future
of our country, which
rests with the youth of
the Furinkan High School.
Justice, love, and passion
motivate my severity.
I have no course but to act
while my heart cries out
for your pain.
Why do you have such a
problem understanding that?
Speaking of mental
pause, did it
ever occur to you that
the principal's just
using you to get back at us?
What?
This will teach you!
Whoa!
RANMA: Thanks for the lesson!
Now I've had enough!
Just who the heck
do you think you are?
You're going to pay for this.
I forbid you from buying
lunch at the school snack
shop for the entire week.
Huh?
[laughter]
[gasp]
STUDENT: Hey, come on.
I was first.
STUDENT: No, I was first.
I've been here for,
like, half an hour.
Have at it.
Give me a chow mein sandwich,
one bun, and a meat and veggie
sandwich.
I'm afraid I can't.
I'm not allowed to
sell you anything.
[chatter]
Huh?
I've got to pay the
bills, too, you know.
He may only be the
substitute principal,
but his word's the law.
TATEWAKI: Hey!
No opening umbrellas
inside the school.
You, girl!
Polka dot raincoats are
against regulations!
Hm?
[sigh]
Those loud footsteps are
against school regulations.
[gasping]
Out of the way!
I've got to go!
Aha.
It's that deviant Saotome.
I've gotta go!
Halt, Ranma Saotome.
Furinkan regulations, section
two, article one, part three--
walking in the corr--
[groan]
Passing through.
The substitute principal.
Are you all right?
This is the sub principal.
Come in, boys' restroom,
third floor north.
BOY (ON RADIO): This is boys'
restroom, third floor north.
We copy.
Over.
[groan]
What's this doing here?
I'm terribly sorry.
I've got to make a living, so
I can't disobey the substitute
principal's orders, either.
[groan]
[screaming]
Do you really expect
me to fall for that?
Oh, man.
Stupid Kuno.
I'm sure that it's just
me that he's out to get.
You gonna get him, Ranma?
Course I am.
Huh.
But Ranma, if you attack
Kuno out in the open,
then you'll just end up
falling into his trap.
Got any other ideas?
Hm.
It just so happens that I do.
[animal noises]
RANMA: We can't let the
enforcers treat us this way.
BOY: If we don't stand
up for ourselves now,
they'll just get more
and more carried away.
Let's do something then.
I'll round up some other
students who hate him, too.
We're going to make that fake
principal sorry he ever met us.
Huh?
I am the swordsman Kuno,
Furinkan High School's
substitute principal.
Get em.
[screaming]
No, please, have mercy.
Justice is served.
Kuno, baby, I've
got some good news
you might be interested in.
Oh?
Your 10th report already.
Give me the details.
Pay up first.
Hm.
Someone's posting
pictures of girls
here where I've
marked on the map.
Oh!
Let's move, men.
Yes, sir!
It can't be.
This is our clubhouse.
[groan]
How come I'm the one who
has to do this, anyway?
Now what's your problem?
It was my idea, so you've
got to put it into action, K?
She's right, Ranma.
Now get in touch with your
feminine side, and be strong.
But I'm a guy!
Keep it down!
Hey, wait a sec.
Did you hear something just now?
[groan]
Don't say a word.
I've been duped.
Something has gone
awry in my kingdom.
Forgive me, pig tailed
girl and Akane Tendo.
But mark my word,
the day shall dawn
when we will be free to hold
discourse as in days of yore.
[sigh]
Farewell, my loves.
Huh?
It's me, Kuno!
Ah!
It's the pig tailed girl!
[grunt]
Still got my touch.
How about a date, Kuno?
Jeez, Ranma just had to go and
boot him-- now, of all times.
A date?
I'd be honored!
Let's go, pig tailed girl.
So far, so good.
Wouldn't you say, Akane?
Furinkan regulation,
section two,
article one--
close relationships
with the opposite
sex are prohibited.
[gasp]
Wait just a moment.
As substitute principal,
I must set an example.
Oh, but Kuno, come on, huh?
Wouldn't you rather
spend time with me?
(VOICEOVER) Forgive
me, pig tailed girl.
It sorrows me to turn you away.
But history is being written.
Ow, that's hot!
It's hot!
For now, suffer this
hot embrace as a prelude.
Oh, disgusting!
[groan]
Sorry about that, Ranma.
But my own life is at
stake here, too, you know?
It's that scoundrel Saotome.
Come back here!
[groan]
Uh oh.
Thanks a lot, Nabiki.
Whose side are you on?
Just out of curiosity.
Who, me?
The money side, of course.
You just about had
Kuno trapped, too.
Drop it, because
I'm not trying again.
The problem here is
really your sister.
You mean, Nabiki?
It's not easy talking her
out of doing something.
While we're stopping
her, we've got
to get Gosunkugi in the process.
All we've got to do is convince
them to come over to our side.
Yeah, right.
Like that's going to be easy.
I'll take care of things.
There are two ways
to people's hearts,
so I'll convince them to
see things like we do.
Two ways?
This is on the house.
So eat up, OK?
Oh, I see.
So you're buying us off.
I get it.
So food is one of the
ways to win people over.
Ukyo said there were two
ways, so the other one
must have something
to do with love.
GOSUNKUGI: Uh, listen, guys.
I don't want anything to
do with that kind of stuff.
Forget that, Gosunkugi.
We need your help.
Oh, sure.
You can definitely count on me.
I'll take care of that
substitute principal right now.
What?
Time to repent!
Ah!
Ow!
[groan]
Huh?
He won't be needing this one.
You guys want to hear
something really juicy?
What do you mean?
Well, the principal's
coming back tomorrow morning
during the homeroom period.
You serious?
See, what did I tell you?
Buying people off
really does work.
If there's anything I've
learned, it's that money talks.
And the timing was impeccable.
I see your point.
You must be raking
in a serious profit.
Better believe I am.
[laughter]
(VOICEOVER) If only they knew,
I've been eavesdropping this
whole time.
If there was any
trouble during homeroom,
it'd be the sub principal's
fault, wouldn't it?
Yeah!
So I'll make sure
there is trouble.
Don't be stupid.
If you got involved,
you'd be blamed, not him.
But if I don't stir things up
during homeroom period, then
who will?
Hm.
This is the perfect time to
dust off a secret weapon.
Secret weapon?
RANMA: What do you mean?
What is it?
NABIKI: You'll have
to wait and find out.
(VOICEOVER) This
sounds foreboding.
I'll have to tell
Master Kuno right away.
The elements are simple,
but the overall effect
will blow you away.
Do you really think that
this secret weapon thing
is going to get here on time?
Let's hope so.
The Monday morning homeroom
period shall now commence.
To begin with, allow me
to take this opportunity
to introduce myself.
I am your substitute
principal, Tatewaki Kuno.
I have several
proclamations this morning.
It's been one week
since I've become--
(VOICEOVER) About that time.
TATEWAKI: --subsitute principal.
And as far as your
behavior is concerned--
It's here.
Huh?
Where's my bride?
[inaudible].
Oh, that-- that voice!
My bride!
Where's my bride?
[inaudible]
[stuttering]
Me statue be falling.
Oh, my god, the horror!
[screaming]
Huh?
What be happening to me school?
[screaming]
Scoundrels!
How dare anyone interrupt the
sacred Monday homeroom class!
[interposing voices]
Huh?
You can't treat
Master Kuno that way.
[screaming]
Don't you think this is going
a bit over the top, Akane?
Yeah, a bit.
Nabiki's gone way overboard
with this secret weapon thing.
OK, I guess you're right.
Maybe I overdid it a little.
So what say I run
plan B by you, Akane?
I think our only
hope at this point
is to get Ranma into the
mix, working for the cause.
Huh?
You're right.
There's really only one way
we're going to be able to quiet
down this riot.
[gasp]
You-- you don't mean I--
Do it for the
kids, Ranma, honey.
[gasp]
My darling!
Oh, happy day.
We found Ranma.
Soon to be my bride.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
[screaming]
My bride.
Meddling interlopers,
you won't escape my wrath.
[screaming]
Come back, my luscious
bride. [inaudible].
Stop, you scoundrels!
And face your punishment.
Oh, me Buddha.
I make you the
make-do principal,
and you let this cat and
this freaky old man into me
school while I be
recreating, man?
[screaming]
The boys and the girls
should no be associated
and not be playing tag.
Oh, they running
straight for me.
Oh!
Come back here, and
face your punishment!
[screaming]
Oh, this looking
dangerous, man.
Me best be going.
[screaming]
My [inaudible]!
Come back here, you!
And there they go.
You think Ranma will be OK?
Mhm.
Well, if he makes it
back in one piece.
Maybe I should go
easy on him, for once.
That might be a good idea.
[screaming]
[music playing]
There's a secret tradition
amongst martial artists
known as the Ogre
Festival of the Dark.
No, Ranma!
Don't do it!
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Ranma's Greatest Challenge.
We'll see you there!