[music playing]
[theme music]
BARKER: Hurry, hurry!
Step right up.
A winner!
-Ah!
I won.
-Good for you, Akane.
-"Hot Springs the way they
used to be-- obstacle courses,
three-legged races."
Huh?
What the-- "Fun for all ages.
Winner receives
all-expense-paid trip
to the resort of their choice.
-Oh, my goodness, Akane.
Might that include
a trip to Jusenkyo?
AKANE: My gosh!
What if you're right?
"Hot Springs Battley Royale."
-H-- Hot Springs Resort?
-Yeah, do you want to come?
Its' already paid for?
And if we win this contest
they are holding, we're--
-Hold it right there.
It's okay.
I want you both to go.
I give you my blessing.
[boing]
[music playing]
AKANE: It's so quiet.
RANMA: And we're alone.
[music playing]
Akane.
AKANE: Oh, Ranma.
-I'm counting on you, son.
-T-- to do what?
-Ranma.
-I-- I'll do my best.
-Who are you kidding?
You won't even be able to
come if I disinvite you.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, who'd want to go with
a tomboy like you, anyway?
[splash]
-Fine, then don't come.
See if I care.
-Akane, come back here.
I thought you'd be thanking me.
-Poor father, always
the last to know.
-But that's what I'm
trying to tell you.
We are practically
halfway there.
All we got to do is enter.
Hey!
-OK, I go.
-You-- you mean it?
[splash]
[quacking sound]
-Heya!
BARKER: Another winner!
RYOGA: Hot Springs Resort?
Oh, come on.
Give me a break.
What am I?
An old man or something?
No, thanks.
It's probably some
corny, old country.
Oh, corny old country?
Oh!
"A romantic setting for you and
your date to--" d-- d-- date?
AKANE: It's so quiet.
ROYOGA: And we're alone.
[music playing]
Oh, Akane.
AKANE: Oh, Ryoga.
AKANE: Oh, Ranma, you jerk.
If only you'd hear
me out for a change.
I'm not that thrilled
to go with you either.
Oh, well, if that's
the way you-- uggh, oh.
Ranma?
--[straining sound]
What is it this time?
-I want you to have it.
Like I was saying, you know?
If you win, you can--
[crash]
[boom]
-Today is your lucky day, yes?
Shampoo agree pair up with
you at Hot Springs, Ranma.
-I already told Akane
I don't want to--
-[whispers]
-Really?
The winner gets an
all-paid trip to Jusenkyo!
Woo hoo!
-That means yes?
-Oh, yeah!
-[straining sound] Ah!
-Ah!
What'd you do that for?
Hey, that's no fair.
-Idiot.
-Is that really necessary?
-Hey.
-Ha ya!
Next time I won't even bother.
[sighs]
-Would you be my date for the--
there must be a better way
to-- let's see-- more casual.
Hey, Akane!
Guess what I just
happened to come across.
-Hot Springs?
Oh, Ryoga, I'd love too!
Ah!
You would?
That's it.
Casual.
Be nonchalant.
Hey, Akane, guess what
I just happened to--
She-- she left.
Shampoo!
Why?
Why won't you pair with me?
Shampoo, why?
-What did you call me?
-Hmm?
-So that's how it is, huh?
Well, do you want to go?
-Where?
-Here.
-You've got the free pass?
--[chuckles] Well,
if you'd rather not.
-Ah, are you kidding?
You're not my first choice.
But, yeah, I'll go.
-Well, aren't I the lucky one?
-[sighs] Why can't I say it?
It's so simple.
Come to the Hot Springs with me.
I'm begging you!
[music playing]
[boom]
-Get your mind
out of the gutter.
-I would but--
-Huh?
Hot Springs Resort--
how perfect.
I'll bring my card
and make a killing.
-So you and Mousse
are an item, eh?
-[quack].
-I'm so happy for you.
-We are not.
-[quack, quack].
-Never going to be a
girl again-- never going
to be a girl again.
Ooh, yeah!
[laughs]
-Shampoo is happy too!
-Harder, harder-- push harder!
-I'll make it up to you, Akane.
I promise.
-Come on, Hibiki.
Time's a wasting.
ANNOUNCER (ON LOUDSPEAKER):
Hello and welcome to
Jusenkyo Hot Springs.
All contestants please
report to the main square
with souvenir hand towels.
I repeat.
Please report with towel
in hand to compete.
That is all.
-It's so crowded.
-[chuckles] Get ready, suckers.
-That's what you think, Saotome.
-Mousse.
Ah-- a-- Akane, what are
you doing here with--
-Ah, what do you care?
-Akane, so you and
Mousse is couple now?
-Yeah, you wish.
-[inaudible] Namayaki!
-Ukyo you come too?
-Sure, I'm a business
woman, ain't I?
-Ryoga, you too?
-I, uh, just kind of--
-You going to compete?
-Ha, now don't be ridiculous.
-Hmm?
But I thought you'd
want to go to Jusenk.
-What?
"Winner gets choice
of all-paid trip
to any hot springs
in the w-- w--"
I've been cured of the pig!
[fireworks]
-OK, listen up.
Here's the rules.
The first thing is to tie
your towel around your ankle.
-You mean that's all?
-Yes, that's all.
-This is going to be easy.
-As for the first goal,
you'll be reach it
by riding logs through
rapids right over there.
-R-- rapids?
Riding on logs?
-I'll be cured of the pig.
I will.
-You ready, Shampoo?
-If you is.
ANNOUNCER: Get set-- Go!
[gunshot] And they're off!
[running sounds]
[music playing]
[water flowing]
[crash]
ANNOUNCER: Use these to steer.
RANMA: Don't mind if I do.
[music playing]
-Man, they're
dropping like flies.
-It's good news for us.
-That's what you think.
There's still me to deal with.
[crash]
[fighting sounds]
-[screams].
You guys please cut it out.
I can't swim!
-What matter, Ranma?
You jealous?
-Huh?
Yeah, like some tomboy
chick could ever make me?
[boom]
-Oh!
-Way to go Akane Tendo!
-Oh, you started to run
the wrong way, you jackass.
-It's not over yet.
COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN: You're
kidding-- they're still going?
-What are we going to do?
I mean, if they win,
they get a prize.
I mean, we've got to come
up with the cash to--
-You know we don't
have the budget.
We're too unpopular.
What are we going to--
--[chuckles] You're
forgetting something.
Of all the many springs
we've got in this joint,
there ain't one of
them that's safe.
Them contestants
ain't got a chance.
-Whoa.
The village elder's on fire.
-Yeah, literally.
[music playing]
-Sir, they passed
the second goal.
-[chuckles] Goodie for them.
[music playing]
-It's too easy.
Make it a challenge at least.
[music playing]
[panting]
-It's your own fault, Ranma.
If you'd only heard me out
instead of getting all-- Ah!
-[screams].
[crash]
-Coming through.
Ah!
-Yeah, it's all your fault.
Your legs are too short.
So we can't run to keep up.
-Excuse me.
[crash]
-Ah!
-How dare you insult Akane?
[panting]
-Here's where we take the lead.
-Come on.
-Not yet, you don't.
-Ah!
Oh!
[crash]
-What was that for?
-Ah!
-Oh!
[crash]
-[interposing voices]
-You better tell
Akane you're sorry.
You've got a lot of nerve.
-[inaudible]
-Ah!
-La, la, la.
How's it going, Akane?
-Oh, fine until you interfered.
-What?
AKANE (VOICEOVER): He'll pair
with anyone to win, won't he?
-You know, we make a good team.
-Huh?
-Together we can't lose, Akane.
-If I'd have picked you,
we would have won by now.
Can you ever forgive me?
-There's no need to--
-Ranma says forget
the cute type.
What you need is the brute
strength of an Akane.
[boom]
-One of these days I'll
remember why I put up with you.
-[groans]
-But until then it's goodbye!
-Akane, wait!
It's not what I--
bad, crocky, no bite.
Stay back.
[wind sounds]
-Why do I put up with him.
He can stay a girl for his
whole life for all I care.
Geez!
Why do I even--
-It's that dumb Akane
always got to-- huh?
Huh?
What?
He scores!
Ugh, iron geta?
Lead-weighted obi?
Yukata woven with chains?
-[scream]
-Huh?
-Oh.
Oh.
--[straining sound]
Akane, what are you--
-Ranma.
-Hang on.
I'll be right there.
[straining sound]
-Oh, just leave me alone.
I got scared, that's all.
I don't need your help.
I'm a brute, remember?
-Akane, you're making a
big deal out of nothing.
What's important
is I want your--
-No.
-Huh?
-What's important is I invited
you because I-- oh, never mind.
It's not me you want anyway.
It's my brute strength.
-Huh?
I-- I don't remember any--
-I said never mind.
-Akane, Akane, wait.
At least tell me why you're so--
-I told you.
Oh!
ANNOUNCER: (LAUGHING) Welcome
to the bath of shifting sands.
-You're standing too close.
-No, I'm sinking too close.
And if you hadn't made me follow
you, then we wouldn't be here.
Hey, it stopped moving.
-Oh.
I really am sorry.
You're right.
It's my fault.
-Huh?
-Go on.
Get out of here.
-Ha!
You're such a kidder.
I almost thought you
were like-- serious.
-I mean it, Ranma.
Get out of my face
while you still can
or I swear to you you're
going to regret you ever--
-Oh!
Hey, stupid.
You still haven't
said what I did to--
-I invited you because--
-Uh, oh.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
You want to come?
It's already paid for.
And if we win this contest
we're holding, we--
-Oh, please.
This is not supposed
to be happening.
All I ever wanted was for Ranma
to win that trip, you know?
So we--
-If that's true--
-Huh?
- --then why are you trying
so hard to make me angry?
-Me make you angry?
How dare you?
-I'm sorry, OK.
I didn't realize
you'd invited me.
-You-- you came back
to say you were sorry?
-Sorry.
Yep.
Uh-huh.
And for what it's worth ,
I accept your apology too.
-Gee, isn't that
generous of you?
Huh?
[boing]
-Man this is easy.
-Oh, oh, great.
They're ahead.
Look, there's no time to fight.
Just trust me, OK?
-What?
Oh, what are you doing?
-What's it look like I'm doing?
First, I'm going to throw you.
Then I'm uh, then I'm, um, oh--
-Ranma!
Oh!
-[coughing]
-What is it?
What's wrong?
-The rope's too heavy.
-But-- oh, I get it.
Here I'll--
-Oh--
-See this?
-Wait!
-Here it goes!
Ah!
[straining] Oh, there,
that ought to hold.
-You're, uh, kind of
good at this stuff.
[music playing]
-Oh!
-Oh, no, They're
heading this way.
[panting]
-Unless something happens,
they're going to win, Akane.
[panting]
-Let a couple of
punks like that win
after what we've been through?
We ain't beat yet, are we boys?
-No, sir!
-Yes!
-Oh, it's running away.
-Faster men.
Run faster!
-They're insane.
-Move it, Mousse.
-Let's do it.
[music playing]
-Hey, you guys!
-Wake up!
Oh!
-This is it.
We're almost there.
-Ranma, I'm so happy.
-Akane, thank you.
I owe you big time.
-Sure.
-Ready or not,
Jusenkyo here we come.
[straining sounds]
-I told you we shouldn't
have come this way.
-What?
-Huh?
[music playing]
-What?
What?
-We were almost there.
-Yeah, thanks for
nothing, Ryoga.
--[laughter] Hey,
tough luck, Saotome.
And I'll see you when
I get back, Akane.
-He must have really
have wanted to go.
Did you know he was such
a fan of Hot Springs?
-Hmm.
[music playing]
-Which way is Jusenkyo?
-I can't get over the fact that
you picked here of all places.
-But which way's Jusenkyo?
[electric sound]
[music playing]
-It's a campus-wide fight.
And guess who's invited.
What's this connection
with Kuno, though?
I don't get it.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
me as Kuno's daddy me is.
We'll see you there.