[music playing]
[gong sounding]
-[speaking japanese]
-I love you my dear, dear Ukyo.
[chimes ringing]
-You're kidding, right?
Another challenge letter?
-Yuppers.
Prepare yourself.
I'm coming soon
to take your life.
-Coming to take your life?
That's a little
extreme, isn't it?
Who's it from?
-Tsubasa Kurenai.
Is that a girl's
name or a boy's name?
I guess it could be either.
I wonder if it's someone I know.
-Ranma.
-What?
-So what do you do now?
Steal?
Eat without paying?
Get engaged maybe?
-Jinkies, Akane.
I'm glad you think
so highly of me.
-Charge!
-Huh?
-Ranma Saotome, prepare to die!
-What the?
-Ranma, what on Earth did
you do to that mailbox?
-I don't know.
Forget a postage
stamp or something?
-Charge, I say.
-Yah!
-Oh!
Oh, ugh.
[groaning] Ah.
-Oh, she's a girl.
-Ranma.
Ch-charge.
Charge, I say.
Oh, oh.
-Well, you gonna
tell me who she is?
-Hmm.
Well, no idea.
-I was right, wasn't I?
You did go and get
engaged again, didn't you?
-What are you talking about?
Oh, hi, Ucchan.
-Huh?
-Dear, dear Ukyo.
-Tsubasa Kurenai.
-Hey, that's the one
who sent me the letter.
-A friend of yours, Ukyo?
-Hardly.
Hurry, hurry.
-Whoo.
Oh, great.
I never thought anyone
would follow me here.
-Funny how that works, huh.
-Tsubasa and I were in the
same homeroom at my old school.
-OK.
But then why-- why is
Tsubasa so mad at me?
-I was pretending to be a
boy when I first got here.
Remember?
-Dear Ukyo.
Here.
-Tsubasa, I don't want
to hurt your feelings,
but I've already got a fiance.
Fiance.
-Oh.
[crying]
-Oh, that's hot.
-But rejection
only spurred me on.
I decided to put my
thoughts on paper,
sending Ukyo letter
after letter,
until the skies were filled
with pretty pink envelopes.
-I needed some way to
take the heat off me.
Which is how I came up with
the idea of sending Tsubasa
your picture, Ranma.
-[crying]
-Which Ranma was
it in the picture?
-The girl Ranma, of course.
What did you think?
-The girl?
-Tsubasa thought I
was a boy at the time.
OK?
I didn't want anyone
thinking I was a pervert.
-Hmm.
-What are you looking at?
-You're butt ugly.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Butt ugly?
Butt ugly.
But ugly.
But ugly!
-What's wrong with you?
Ranma, I don't believe this.
Are your feelings hurt?
-Ukyo, catch.
Ukyo sure doesn't seem to
think that I'm but ugly now,
does she?
-Oh.
-Who?
Ranma?
Never.
-So nice to see you.
Buh-bye.
[giggling]
-I will show all of you.
-Na-na na-na-na.
Na-na na-na-na.
-I'll teach you
to make fun of me.
Charge!
Darn, I missed her.
-Tsubasa.
-Oh, don't hurt me.
-Prepare to fry.
-I've got a better way.
Look.
Now do you get it?
-What are you doing?
-Do you get it?
Ukyo is a girl.
A girl.
-Well, why didn't you just
say that from the beginning?
-Oh, yeah.
-Huh.
What kind of fool
do you take me for?
Don't you think that I
already knew that my dear,
dear Ukyo was a girl?
You got it?
It's because Ukyo's a girl
that I'm interested in her.
And you, Ranma
Saotome, do you really
think you can make Ukyo happy?
If you're serious, you'll
meet me at school tomorrow.
I'm going to take
Ukyo away from you
if it's the last thing I do.
Oh, by the way,
you're butt ugly.
-Oh.
-Seeya.
[laughing]
-Tsubasa already
knew I was a girl?
-So it seems.
-Why that-- that pervert!
[chimes sounding]
-Today from 12:30 to
1:30 Ucchan's okonomiyaki
is having a bake sale?
-Hey that one on the
left's kind of cute.
-That one looks so familiar.
-An okonomiyaki bake-off, huh?
-It's still not too late
for you to back out of this.
-You know me better than that.
Besides, accepting
challenges is what
the Anything Goes
School is all about.
Akane, it's my duty.
-How dare you involve
my [? sister ?]
without permission.
But I have to admit a campus
bake sale is a great idea.
-Do you really think so?
I'm so happy.
-We're agreed then?
-That's fine with me.
-Whoever loses has to
give up on Ukyo forever.
-I'm glad you're
taking it so well.
-Ready, set, go!
-You take it well, Ranma,
because I intend to win.
-I hear that girl Tsubasa
isn't interested in boys.
-With all the perverts at the
school, does that surprise you?
-Oh, Ranma, why are you letting
that girl get to you like this?
-But ugly, am I?
Ha.
A hot little tamale like me?
I don't think so.
-Don't push me.
I'm full of chocolate.
-Come and get it.
-Buy your okonomiyaki from
the one you think is cutest.
-Huh?
-Huh.
How did you do?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I lost?
-Guess beauty wins
over butt ugly.
But don't feel so bad.
I hear they're doing
wonders with plastic surgery
these days.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): And here I
really thought I'd win, too.
Can it be?
Can it be that I
really am butt ugly?
-Fear not my Venus.
Thou art still the goddess
of love and beauty.
See how I worship you, my love.
-Get off of me.
[panting] I think
I'm gonna puke.
-OK, Ranma.
You're being ridiculous,
even for you.
I mean, you don't
really think you
could win against a
real girl, now, did you?
-Aha.
So that's it.
Just you wait Tsubasa.
This ain't over yet.
-That's not what I-- Ranma!
BOY: Whoa, what a babe.
BOY: Whoa, is she new?
-Step right up, boys.
Get your okonomiyaki.
-Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
-Me too.
Me too.
-Oh.
Thanks, fellas.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I just
wasn't sexy enough before.
Now they don't
even recognize me.
BOY: Well, if I buy one,
will you go out with me?
RANMA: Gee, I dunno.
I'll have to check my calendar.
Ow.
What are you doing?
-Move it, funny girl.
-Let go.
You're hurting me.
Let go.
Lemme go.
Ow.
Ow, I said.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Where are you talking me?
Ow, you're bending my ear.
Let go.
-What is wrong with you, Ranma?
Do you like having
guys chase after you?
RANMA: Be quiet.
All's fair in love and war.
Ugh.
Shoot.
And I only had one left to sell.
-You're making me crazy.
-Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
-Tsu-Tsubasa.
-Nice try, but you still lose.
Now promise you'll give up
Ukyo just like we agreed.
-Tough luck, sugar.
-Huh?
-That last okonomiyaki
is being saved for me.
I asked her to save
the last one for me.
Guess that means the
contest is a draw.
-Ucchan.
-Dear Ukyo, how cruel.
Why don't you just admit it.
You don't-- you don't want to
go out with me at all, do you?
Why?
Why couldn't you just tell
me that from the beginning?
-I did tell you, remember?
But you still wouldn't give up.
-[wailing]
And that's it.
Don't worry, Ukyo.
You won't hear from me again.
Farewell.
[crying]
-Tsubasa.
-Ranma.
-Ran-chan.
[thunder]
-[panting]
-Tsubasa, I didn't want to
admit it, but you won, not me.
-You're not butt ugly at all.
-Tsubasa?
-I was jealous of you.
You were so cute, I knew
I didn't stand a chance.
I'm sorry.
Ukyo must hate me.
Why does life always have
to get so complicated?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): You don't
know the half of it, sister.
-Cheer up.
You're pretty cute yourself.
I'm sure you'll find a
boyfriend in no time.
-[sighing]
-Huh?
-Dear Ranma.
-Hey, hey.
Cut that out.
Quit it.
-I, Tsubasa Kurenai,
have fallen in love.
All over again!
-Never mind.
I take it all back.
Leave me alone!
-Is Tsubasa fickle or what?
-I'll bet almost
any non-boy will do.
Still, Ranma's secret
will be out soon enough.
Poor Tsubasa.
-Actually, it's Ranma
I feel sorry for.
-Come on Tsubasa.
Cut it out.
My life's complicated
enough as it is.
Leave me alone!
Ugh.
[interposing voices]
-Hey, you OK?
Hey.
-Durn.
She got away.
Dear, dear Ranma,
why did you leave me?
Why can't you love me back?
What is wrong with me?
-I'd get rid of the crazy
costume for starters.
-Ah, Tsubasa.
--[panting] It's almost
better being ugly.
-But thou art not ugly, my love.
Thou hast-- a strong kick.
-As if I didn't have
enough to deal with.
Now I've got both these
nut cases chasing after me.
-Tsubasa is persistent.
Once you've been
targeted, it's all over.
You'll be tracked to
the ends of the Earth.
Then your only hope
is to move away.
-Or then again, maybe I'm
going about this all wrong.
TSUBASA: [crying]
-Seriously, Tsubasa,
you're better off
without hi-- I mean her.
I'm sure you can find
yourself a more normal person.
-Never.
Never.
I hate boys.
-You do?
That's funny.
So do I.
-You shouldn't.
-But you just said--
-But I'm differ--
or maybe you just
want Ranma all to yourself.
-Huh?
Who?
Who told you that?
-So you don't want her.
Oh, what a relief.
-Can we talk about you?
You're the one
I'm worried about.
-Huh?
Worried about me?
Oh, Akane, my dear, dear Akane.
-Upperclassman Kuno.
-Who's he?
-Fair ones, no.
Lacking suitable
male company, now
doubt you have in your
innocence turned to each other.
But I can allow it no longer.
Oh.
I, Tatewaki Kuno, shall
single-handedly deliver you
from the bonds of spinsterhood.
Come, be my loves.
And together we shall--
-Boys.
I hate them.
A message for me?
Listen to this, Akane.
To my dear, dear Tsubasa.
Meet me in the park
on Sunday and I'll
give you a big surprise.
Signed, your own dear Ranma.
Oh, oh, oh.
What'll I do?
What am I gonna wear?
What am I gonna say?
-Does he mean girl-girl?
[birds chirping]
-Ranma's not really gonna--
-I know, I know.
He's-- she's taking
Tsubasa on a--
-You're kidding, right?
You don't think that
Ranma actually likes--
-Be serious.
Even he can't be that twisted.
-(SINGING) I met her on a
Monday and my heart stood still.
Ra-ra-ra-Ranma, Ra-ra-ra-ran.
-Oh, Tsubasa, dear.
-Ranma.
-May I say that you are
looking exceptionally lovely?
Yes, I know, I know.
I seem too good to be true.
But I'm not.
How's about we go live
happily ever after?
-P-ew.
Somebody get a shovel.
-Who the heck are you?
-I'm your knight in shining
armor, baby, your prince,
your one and only
heart's desire.
Hark, I hear true
love calling us.
-Beg your pardon, your highness,
but may I have a word with you?
-Ugh, what did I do now?
-I thought this was supposed
to be a girl-girl date.
-It's part of my strategy
to make her fall out
of love with my girl side.
-So it's better she
loves you as a boy?
-Hey, I never said it
was a perfect strategy.
-Why you--
-Hmm.
Oh, gimme a--
-Wait.
Don't go.
Don't interfere if you
know what's good for you.
Hey, angel, wait up.
You don't want to leave
without me, do you?
-Buzz off, bozo, before
I forget I'm a lady.
-Stop thief!
-Hmm?
-Hey, you come back here with my
fish, you lousy, stinking cats.
-[screaming]
-I thought I told you
to buzz off, you bozo.
Do you want me to get mad?
Do you think I
want to be grabbed?
How about I grab you, huh?
What kind of girl
do you take me for?
-Tsubasa really does hate boys.
-Even more than you.
-There.
That ought to teach him.
-Oh, Ranma, dear, dear Ranma.
What brute did this
horrible thing to you?
Let me take you somewhere safe.
-I can't go on.
-Hush.
Be brave, dear Ranma.
-My-- my dying
wish is a hot bath.
-Your wish is my command.
-[humming]
-In you go.
-Argh.
Excuse me?
-Dear, dear Ranma.
-Aww.
So it's you again.
-Too bad, huh?
You disappointed?
-[groaning]
-Uh, excuse me--
-I told you I have
no interest in boys.
Akane, here I come.
-No, wait.
If you would just
give us guys a chance.
-That's your way
of asking me out?
I'm not interested.
-Excuse me.
Excuse me.
-What's the matter?
You never seen a
real guy before?
-Yes.
Well.
So that's how it is, huh.
Let's see.
Oh, yeah.
It was all to compete
with you, wasn't it?
I did a little of this.
I did a little of that.
I did even more of that.
-[giggling]
-A boys' school?
-Well, yeah.
-But you said--
that school you guys
went to was a boys' school?
-Didn't I tell you?
-No, you didn't.
Then Tsubasa isn't a pervert.
That is, unless you
count the cross-dressing.
-Come back here!
-Sorry to be so boring, but
I'm no more of a pervert
than Ranma is.
-Yeah.
And we all know how
normal Ranma-honey is.
-You could have said
something to us, you know.
-He ain't normal.
He's some kind of pervert.
-Oh, don't be angry with me.
After all, we both
like to dress up.
-Hey, it's different in my case.
[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
-[speaking japanese]
-[laughing]
-No, Gramps.
Don't do it.
That brassiere is cursed.
Ahh.
You didn't listen to me.
Well, you're on your own now.
Next time on Ranma
1/2, "The Witch
Who Loved Me," a
Japanese ghost story.
See you there.