[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Shampoo's Revenge.
The Shiatsu Technique That
Steals Heart And Soul.
[birds chirping]
-Mm hmm?
Mm, Ooh, Aah.
Good morning, P-chan.
[oinks]
-Akane, would you go
and wake up Ranma?
-Why do I have to wake him up?
-Don't be angry.
-Oh look, she's still sulking
about Ranma and Shampoo.
-Am not.
-Akane, why don't
you just come out
and admit your true
feelings for him?
-No way!
-Kasumi, she-- she yelled at me.
-That's it.
Just let it all out.
-He doesn't have
to cry about it.
Ranma, wake up or I'll--
[SNORING
-Wo airen.
[growls]
-Oh, that's cold!
Jeez, Akane, what'd
you do that for?
-Humph.
-What did I do?
-Wo ta airen.
-Sh-- Shampoo?
What are you doing here?
[SIGHS
-Is Ranma awake?
-Aw, come on.
You could at least
wait until I wake up.
-Girl-type Ranma, I kill!
-Oh look, Shampoo's here.
That's nice.
Would you like some breakfast?
-Huh?
Hmm.
Huh?
-I'm really getting
tired of this.
-Wo ta airen.
Haya!
Boy-type Ranma, you I love!
Ooh!
Haya!
RANMA: Leave me alone.
Get away from me!
SHAMPOO: Ranma.
-OK, that's it, I
have had enough!
-Enough!
You heard her, Shampoo.
Leave me alone!
-Mm-hmm, Mm-hmm.
[boing]
-Huh?
-Ranma.
You no run.
-Hey.
Come on.
Cut it out now.
[grunts]
-Oh.
Airen.
-Well it's your own fault.
I tried ignoring you,
but that was even worse!
-Why you do this?
-Why?
Because you're always
causing trouble!
-You unhappy because
we're having fun.
-Fine.
Have fun.
But have it outside.
-Why you so jealous?
-I'm not jealous.
Hmph.
I haven't got time for this.
I'm late for school.
[upbeat music plays]
-I told you already,
it's not like I
asked her to come and
sleep with me or nothing.
-Don't waste your breath.
I couldn't care
less how disgusting
you are in the morning.
-Boy, once you make up your
mind about something-- Ugh, ah.
-Why do you have to
be such a pervert?
I guess you and Shampoo
deserve each other.
[baby voice] You're the who
sleeps with the little piggy.
-Be quiet!
You leave P-chan out
of this, all right.
-Humph.
-Honestly.
You're jealous of a little pig.
-Aah, who'd be jealous
of a tomboy like you.
Uh.
-Ugh, that's right, I forgot,
we're not engaged anymore.
I hate you, I hate
you, I hate you!
So what if I sleep with a pig.
Go away, you stupid jerk.
I hate you!
Leave me and P-chan alone.
Get lost!
Just go.
-Akane, the time has come
for me to leave you forever.
I'll never be anything more
to you than your pet P-chan,
will I?
-Wake up.
Ranma just gave you the
chance of a lifetime.
What are you waiting for Ryoga?
-No, but-- what-- Uh, ugh.
-Sorry, Ryoga, but
it's Ranma that I love.
-OK, so she wouldn't say that.
If she did, my poor
heart would be--
It'd break into a
thousand pieces.
Aah, farewell, Akane!
Ooh?
[tongue clicking]
[laughs]
-Lai, lai.
Lai, lai, lai, lai.
Good boy.
[oinks]
[laughs]
[bell rings]
[chattering]
[crash]
MALE STUDENT: Hey,
there it is again.
-Oh no.
[crash]
-It's coming closer.
STUDENT: I'm out of here.
[scream]
[chinese music plays]
-Boy-type Ranma.
-Shampoo, come on in.
But next time you might
want to use the door.
[giggles]
-Mm-hmm.
RANMA (WITH HIS MOUTH
FULL): OK, what is it?
-Dutiful wife make
husband delicious lunch.
Canton-style pork with hibiscus.
Look.
[bong]
[screams]
-P-chan!
Ooh?
-This lunch for
husband, not you.
Aah.
-Just a minute.
Ryoga.
Hey, hey.
[oinks]
[squeals]
-P-chan.
Oh, P-chan.
Poor baby.
[spooky music plays]
-Huh?
[clang]
[boom]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
The kiss of death.
A promise to track Akane to the
ends of the earth and kill her!
-Womans what interfere
is for killing.
Is Amazon rule.
-That's fine with me.
I will accept your challenge.
-Come on, the pigs OK.
Why don't we just
live and let live, OK?
AKANE: Butt out!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): This is my
chance to get even with her.
-Akane, give it up.
There's no way a slowpoke
like you can beat someone
like Shampoo.
AKANE: Slow?
Who are you calling slow?
-Ugh, uh, ugh, oh, ugh.
-Akane!
-She went out that way.
-She did what?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Akane.
Akane.
There's no way she's
going to beat Shampoo.
She's going to get
herself killed.
Ah, this is all my fault.
Akane.
I gotta get there.
Akane!
[squealing]
-That was Ryoga.
Aah.
Akane.
Hey, wake up.
Come on, wake up.
-Huh?
Uh.
That's odd.
-You idiot!
I told you not to fight
with her, didn't I?
-Do I know you?
-Huh?
[music plays]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Shampoo
challenged me and we fought.
I can remember it
clearly up to that point.
But then, as for
what came next--
[clang]
-Huh?
RANMA: Akane.
-Why do I feel so refreshed?
-Hey, Akane, wait up.
-Akane, Akane.
Why do you keep saying
that like you know me.
Who are you anyway?
-Listen, Akane--
-Have we met somewhere before?
-Huh?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): She's
got that-- whatchamacallit--
Amnesia!
-There she is.
Akane.
-Hi, you guys.
-Akane, we were so
worried about you.
-Yeah.
Are you OK?
-Of course, I'm OK.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): That's weird.
I thought she couldn't
remember anything.
-That Shampoo girl
looked really strong.
-Huh?
Oh, nothing I couldn't handle.
-Akane, you were
out cold though.
-Do I know you?
-I get it.
You're paying me back.
-Is he a transfer student?
-Um, not exactly, Akane.
-Well, who is he, then?
-He's been staying with your
family for a long time now.
-He's Ranma.
-Have you really
forgotten about him?
-Ranma?
[mysterious music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): It does
have a familiar ring To it.
-Ugh, ah, ugh.
Ooh, oh.
STUDENT: What's wrong?
-Ooh, ugh.
Oh, now I remember.
I-- it's that, uh, famous
German Field Marshal,
the one called Desert Fox.
-That's Rommel.
-The company that sells
Ginsu knives, right?
-That's Ronco.
-Computer memory that
can't be changed.
-No, no.
That's RAM.
-Ooh, that song
by the beach boys.
-That's "Help me Rhonda."
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Can it be,
the only thing she's forgotten
is me?
[OINKS
-Ryoga, you're coming with me.
-Hey!
Hey, you can't just
take him like that.
-I gotta talk to him.
-P-chan can't talk.
Don't be so stupid.
You give him back
to me, right now!
-Hey!
-You come back here!
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Who ever he is,
he's no ordinary
transfer student.
-Does anyone know who that was?
-You know.
-It's Ranma.
-Ranma?
Do I know him?
[sigh]
[SQUEALS
-Ryoga, what did
Shampoo do to Akane?
Spill it!
Because I know you were there.
-Hmph.
Nice try.
Me help Akane to remember
an idiot like you?
Not if my life depended on it.
ALL: One, two, one, two--
-Ryoga, come on.
-Well, for once I've got you
right where I want you, Ranma.
ALL: One, two, one, two, one--
-Ooh, well what do you know?
Maybe I can change your mind.
ALL: One, two, one,
two, one, two, one--
-Hey, you guys, you want to
see something really funny?
ALL: Sure.
Yeah, what is it?
-Come on, hurry up.
Come and see.
-I'll talk!
Close the door.
Let me tell you,
Ranma, just thinking
about those legs
of hers gives me
cold shivers right
down my spine.
[clang]
-You asked what I saw.
-Ah, you jerk.
You should of told
me in the first place
you didn't see nothing.
-Get lost.
Leave me alone.
-You really have forgotten
all about me, haven't you?
-Forgotten what?
-Me, that's what.
-Don't tell me you're a--
-Now do you get it?
-I-- I just can't-- I can't
believe that you really are a--
-Mm.
-Cross dresser?
[screams]
-I'm Ranma!
Are you making fun
of me, or what?
-I don't even know
you, you pervert.
-I'll make you remember me.
Just you wait.
SHOPKEEPER: Thanks.
Have a nice day.
RANMA: Akane, wait up!
AKANE: Who are you?
Stop following me!
RANMA: Come on,
just hear me out!
-Oh my.
It's Akane and Ranma.
-Come on, I can
explain everything!
-I'm not interested.
-Just five minutes, that's all.
-Don't be long.
And make sure you're home in
time for dinner, all right?
-Stop!
Just stop for a minute, OK?
AKANE (VOICEOVER): He's
easily keeping up with me.
-Who are you anyway?
[heavy breathing]
-Ugh, uh.
-Whoever you are, you should
watch where you're going.
[running]
-Took you long enough.
-Huh?
-You're about as
obvious as they get.
Uh, ugh.
Since you're here,
you might as well
ask Dr. Tofu to
take a look at you.
-And how do you know Dr. Tofu?
Who are you, anyway?
-I can't go through this again.
DR. TOFU: Hmm.
You don't seem to be injured.
When you came to,
how did you feel?
-That's the funny part.
I felt strangely refreshed.
-Hmm.
That's it.
It's got to be.
-What?
What is it?
Come on, tell us Dr. Tofu.
-A dreaded technique, the Xai
Fang Heng Gao shiatsu attack.
-And what does this dreaded
attack do to a person?
[grunts]
-Mr. Saotome.
-Pop, tell us exactly
what happened.
[grunting]
RANMA: Aah, you're
driving me nuts!
Hurry up and change back.
-I saw the whole thing.
I'll carry the memory
for the rest of my days.
She attacked Akane from the
rear, the speed of her hands
was beyond human.
It took five or
six seconds, tops.
-Wow!
Incredible.
-No wonder my head
felt so refreshed.
-So what does this
attack do to you?
-By applying rare Chinese
herbs and extracts, combined
with finger pressure
in strategic locations,
the Xai Fang Heng
Gao shiatsu attack
can selectively erase memory.
-Ooh, so that explains why
you forgot all about me.
-Do I know you?
-Dr. Tofu, isn't there
anything you can do for her?
-If we could find
that herbal solution,
we might be able to
reverse the effect.
RANMA: Well I can do that.
Akane, come on.
-Hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
[screams]
Help!
Stop!
Put me down.
What do you think you're doing?
Put me down right now!
RANMA: Shampoo, where are you?
Shampoo!
-Oh my.
It's almost time
for dinner you two.
[crash]
-Dr. Tofu, I home.
[grunts]
-Oh, that's right.
Let me introduce
Shampoo, my new nurse.
She'll be staying
here at the clinic.
-Nihao.
[grunts]
RANMA: Shampoo, where
the heck are you?
Come out, Shampoo.
-Why are you doing this?
Put me down!
-Shampoo!
-Why won't you tell
me who you are?
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Ooh, it's no good!
Why can't I remember?
Huh?
Ranma?
My fiance?
That's not even funny!
But wait a minute, if
he's not my fiance then
why is he-- Next time on
Ranma1/2, "I Love You, Ranma.
Please Don't Say Goodbye."
See you there.