[MUSIC HAYASAKA YOSHIE,
"ZETTAI! PART TWO"]
DELIVERY MAN: Delivery!
NODOKA: Come in.
Akane!
AKANE: I wonder what it is.
-Kuno?
Could be anything.
-Wait a sec.
Hm.
Uh!
-Surprise!
[screaming]
P--please, would you stop that?
-What are you?
-Master Kuno himself has sent
me to deliver an important gift.
-And w--what's that?
-That you shall have to
discover for yourself.
Farewell!
Whoops, almost forgot
my samurai undies!
-Man, what is that?
NABIKI: Who cares?
Just open it.
-Hmm.
[gasping]
-Akane Tendo, pig-tailed girl.
Greetings.
I regret to inform you
that I, Tatewaki Kuno,
will be absent from school
for the next few days.
Feel free to bestow
upon this replica
the usual loving kisses, tender
caresses, et cetera, et cetera.
[groaning]
Et cetera, et cetera,
(SLOWLY) et cetera.
-Jeez, ain't it dead yet?
[groaning]
-Kuno baby has such bad taste.
-I wonder where
he's going, though.
-I don't know, Akane, and I'm
not sure that I want to know.
[groaning]
NARRATOR: "Ranma and
Kuno's First Kiss."
MASTER: One man, one
chance, and that's--
SASUKE: I say, Master
Kuno, what a turnout.
-Hmm.
-(VOICEOVER) Legendary
sword Manganmaru,
soon you will be mine.
SASUKE: Manganmaru,
samurai sword of legend.
Each year, those
who would draw it
gather, each hoping to be
granted its three wishes.
MAN: Forsooth, let me try it!
[chanting]
SASUKE: Try as they
may, none could pull it
from the stone, not even
the greatest of shoguns.
Thus it remains to this day.
[grunting]
-Next.
Move along.
[grunting]
[heavy breathing]
[chuckles]
-Nice try, son.
Look, to pull the
sword you're going
to need more than
brute strength.
Manganmaru can't be pulled
out by just anyone, you now.
You have to be the chosen one.
Perhaps if you were to
convince yourself of this,
you would have better luck.
-OK, next.
Next!
[grunting]
Move it along, buddy.
Next!
[gasps]
-Master.
Could he be the one?
-Oh!
-The prophecy.
-The chose one as
foretold in our scrolls.
-Only he is worthy enough to
draw the legendary manganaru.
-I, Tatewaki Kuno,
the chosen one?
-You see, Master Kuno?
There.
What'd I tell you?
-That I, Tatewaki
Kuno should be chosen,
singled out of all
the men in the world.
It's-- it's-- it's-- it's just
what I would have expected.
Ah!
Ha, ha, ha!
[laughs]
[yawns]
-Man, it feels like I've
been awake for hours.
-Quit complaining Ranma.
Being a little
early once in awhile
is not going to kill you.
-True.
And neither will
be seen walking--
-(MUTTERS) Who asked you?
---with Akane, right?
-Besides, how I schedule my
time's my own busi-- bah!
Why you, what'd you do that--
[grunts]
Oh, Oh, yeah.
Hey, thanks.
I just don't think you
should hit me that hard!
[grumbling]
Oh, yeah?
-Oh, well.
So much for being early.
Isn't that Kuno, baby?
-Huh?
TATEWAKI (VOICE
OVER): Manganmaru,
magic sword of three wishes.
STUDENT: Yo, look who's back!
OTHER STUDENT: Wasn't
he on vacation?
-(VOICEOVER) But here's the rub.
On what to use them?
I'm already smart, already
handsome, already charming,
already fit.
I'm rich and I'm wealthy.
-Why, what else can a virtually
perfect human such as I need?
Alas!
What am I to do with such
a profusion of wishes?
Ah!
-He seems a little different.
-Maybe, but I'm not sure how.
-Yo, Kuno!
Where ya been, man?
We really missed ya.
-(GROANING) R-- Ranma Saotome.
Where do you think
you're standing?
-Gee, I don't know.
On top of a moron?
-Which is where I'd
usually explode.
But now, I've got this.
First wish, defeat
Ranma Saotome!
MANGANMARU: Your
wish is my command.
-En garde!
[fighting grunts]
-Again?
You can do it.
[yelling]
Huh?
Ah.
-Ranma!
-Good grief.
-Well, well, well.
I hope this means you've
learned your lesson.
-Ow.
-Hey, are you OK?
[groaning]
That-- that sword.
-Where'd he get it from?
[maniacal laugh]
[growls]
-Come on you guys.
You want to play
ball with me or not?
-Yeah.
-You know we do.
-Magic sword that grants
three wishes, huh Pop?
-Mhm.
Listen up boy.
You do realize the full
implications of that sword,
don't you?
-Implica-- hey, hey!
-Hm.
IE now more becoming a panda.
-No more girl!
[laughing]
-Let me get this straight.
You're the swords chosen one?
-That's right.
-No way.
-So you're sure that
it's not a mistake?
-Hm.
Oh ye of little faith.
I have the certificate of
authenticity right here.
-You're kidding.
-I never kid, Nabiki Tendo.
You know that.
What that is proof
positive Manganmaru
chose me to draw
that from a stone.
-Is it?
[gasping]
Th-- this is-- I'm sorry.
What was it again?
-You know.
[celebratory sounds]
[cheering]
-Hey, you made it!
You're the 1 millionth guy
to draw and pull it out.
[laughing]
-Oh happy day!
I shall never forget it.
Not for the rest of my life.
-So you won it in some kind
of lottery, is that it?
-If he started
with three wishes--
-There's only two left.
-My dear classmates.
What you fail to realize is
that with Manganmaru at my side,
nothing is beyond my reach.
Not even world domination.
[crazed laugh]
-Somebody stop him.
-I hereby make my second wish.
[chatter]
My second wish is for a date
with the pigtailed girl.
MANGANMARU: Your
wish is my command.
[groaning]
-We're saved.
-It's a good thing
he's an idiot.
-Hm.
What, an arrow?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): My
darling, dearest Kuno.
Date me this Sunday, won't you?
Signed, your every
loving pigtailed girl.
[excited panting]
-Oh, can it be?
[high pitched squeal]
What can I say but
it's great to be alive?
-Hmpf.
-Ranma, you're not really
going to date him, are you?
-What's its to you?
-OK, listen up.
He's already blown two wishes.
So if we're going to use
one, we're going to have to--
-Yeah, yeah.
-Don't you yeah, yeah me, boy.
If we don't get that sword--
-Then we're both doomed.
Listen, if it means never
having to be a girl again
then I'm totally ready
to go the distance.
[giggles]
-And then when he's distracted--
-That's when we get our
hands on that magic sword.
-You know it!
-You're forgetting
something, you know.
-Hm?
-This is Kuno, remember?
What if he can't
control himself?
-Aw, she's right.
What if he--
-Magic swords, make me one
with the pigtailed girl?
-You want it, baby?
You got it.
Mm.
-Here I come!
[screaming]
-Hey!
Don't even joke about that, OK?
Do you think I should shave?
-You want, I should help
you with your makeup?
-Ranma.
[music playing]
[waves splashing]
[yawns]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Stupid jerk, dragging me
out here first thing
in the morning.
Still, there's
nothing I wouldn't
do to get that last wish.
-Pigtailed girl.
The sunrise.
Tell me, have you
ever seen the like?
-Oh, you're right.
Oh, wow.
(MUTTERING) Somebody shoot me.
-That's right, boy.
Keep up the good work.
-What kind of date is it?
-Pigtailed girl.
-Huh?
-Have you a wish ready?
-Who, me?
[giggles]
Actually, I'm just happy to
be spending the day with you.
-Truly?
If so, then allow me
to make it a reality.
Ugh!
-Oh no you don't!
-Uh, jeez, he almost wasted it!
-Well, all right then, my dear.
Race me to that hilltop.
[laughing]
-Wait up, silly!
-Ha, ha.
Slowpoke!
Ha, ha.
-(BREATHY VOICE) Wait up.
Oh!
I twisted my ankle!
[gasp]
-Pigtailed girl!
-It hurts.
-What can I do to help you?
-Ow, ow.
Ow.
-Oh.
-Now I've got you.
And that--
-No, no, no, my Darling.
I know that you're eager, but we
mustn't get ahead of ourselves.
We barely know each other.
-Eh?
-Which is why I'd like you
to start keeping a diary.
[chuckles]
-I think I like him
better when he's crazy.
-Let's have breakfast, shall we?
Do you like it?
I made it myself
late last night.
-Oh!
Oh!
-Please eat anything you like.
-I will!
[chuckles]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): While you'll
be eating some sleeping powder.
-OK.
Say, Ah.
-Ah!
-Down the hatch!
-Mm.
-It's good?
-Mm, you minx.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Ha, ha.
Go to sleep, stupid.
-Mm, mm.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Huh?
It's not working?
Oh.
[snoring]
[gurgling]
RANMA (VOICE OVER):
Geeze, what a freak.
Still--
-Got it!
-Pop!
What are you doing?
-Sorry, boy.
But a man's got to do
what a man's go to do.
This sword can only
cure one of us.
And it sure as heck
ain't gonna be you.
-Why you dirty cheat!
[laughing]
-Ah!
-So, pop.
What was that you were saying?
[nervous chuckle]
-Eh, not-- not so fast boy.
I-- I got an idea.
Hear me, oh sword.
My wish is to have more wishes.
-Hey, why didn't I think of it.
MANGANMARU: I'm sorry, that wish
cannot be granted at this time.
Please try again or ask an
operator for assistance.
-Cannot be granted?
RANMA (VOICE OVER):
Oh, I get it.
The voice.
It only knows Kuno's voice.
In other words, I got to
get Kuno to ask for me.
-I was just dreaming of you.
-You're awake!
-Akane Tendo, what a surprise.
Driven mad with jealousy over
my date with the pigtailed girl,
no doubt.
-I am not!
-Now, now.
Don't be upset.
I wish for Akane Tendo
and I to-- blargh!
BOTH: Oh no you don't!
-Come on, you.
We've got a date to finish.
[sighs]
-For all the good it'll do him.
TATEWAKI: Come out, come
out wherever you are.
RANMA: (GIGGLING)
Try and catch me.
TATEWAKI: OK!
[laughing]
-How's Ranma going to
bring up the subject?
-Pretty please help
me cure my problem?
-OK pigtailed girl.
Your wish is my command.
-Yay!
-Well, then again, who knows.
I could be wrong.
[laughing]
RANMA (VOICE OVER):
Keep chasing, chump.
I'm halfway to being cured.
-Come here, you!
Oh, playing hard to get, huh?
OK, then.
I guess I'll have to
wish to catch you!
-Will you quit it with
the dumb wishes already?
-Just kidding.
-Please don't, OK?
It's just that you only
have one wish left now.
And I just don't want
you to go wasting it, k?
-Course not.
I'd be you'd like some
tea after that run.
-Well, y-yeah.
-Perhaps if I wished for some.
-Cut that out, I said!
-Now say ah.
-Ah.
-Is it good?
-Mm, mm, mm.
RANMA (VOICE OVER):
Ugh, I'm gonna puke.
Guess I gotta use the big guns.
-What shall we eat next?
-Um, can I ask a favor?
[speechless noises]
I've got this problem.
Wha-- What problem?
-It's uh, problem of the body.
-Da-- da-- the body?
-If you use your sword
to grant my wish then
I'll do anything
that you ask me to.
[gulping gasp]
-Uh, duh, duh-- Anything?
-Uh-huh.
-Ranma!
Don't you have any shame?
[crying]
-Uh, Akane Tendo.
-And what are you doing here?
TATEWAKI (VOICE OVER):
She's she's jealous
of the pigtailed girl.
Which means--
-You do love me!
-I do not!
-Butt out, Akane!
-Do you want to be
a guy that badly?
-Duh, stupid.
Come on Kuno, got to go!
[groaning]
-Can't we talk about it?
-Forgive me, Akane Tendo!
-Ranma.
-(GIGGLING) Come on, over here.
-(LAUGHING) I won't
let you go to his time.
Wait up!
[laughing]
Oh, look out!
Pigtailed girl,
are you all right?
-Oh, Kuno.
RANMA (VOICE OVER):
Almost there.
-What you said earlier.
Were you serious?
-Mhm.
Anything you want.
Just say it, Kuno.
[gulps]
-Uh, very well.
Cl-- close your eyes.
-[gasps] I-- what?
-The first date
and the first kiss.
[hysterical laughing]
What an auspicious occasion.
-Ranma, my boy.
I know I can't
talk you out of it.
So I won't even try.
But if you're going do a
thing, do it right, dammit.
-Meaning what?
-I won't bother
you either, Ranma.
I Do what you want.
-Akane!
-Weep not, Akane Tendo.
Your turn is next.
-(SCORNFUL) I'd
rather not, thanks.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Just one
minute and that'll be it.
I'll never have to
be a girl again.
[strained kissing noises]
[gasping]
AKANE (VOICE OVER):
Ranma, you idiot.
-I can't do it!
Ah!
-Ah!
Aw.
Why so cold, my love?
-Um, Ranma.
-Stay back!
Leave me alone.
I couldn't do it.
It's over.
All of it, it's over!
-Ranma!
-Wait.
-Huh?
-Pigtailed girl.
Our date today was wonderful.
-Huh?
-The third wish.
I was planning on giving
it to you all along.
-What?
Really?
-Huh?
-Oh, K-Kuno.
-Manganmaru, my
third wish is this.
RANMA (VOICE OVER): Here it is.
This is it!
At last, my real body!
-Whoa!
RANMA (VOICE OVER):
Or, uh, maybe not.
-What's going on?
[laughter]
[yelling]
-Behold, pigtailed girl.
May we never forget!
Ha, ha, ha!
[sighing groans]
[music - yawmin, "friends"]
-Shampoo?
Oh, what's the meaning
of that red thread?
You don't mean it's finding
you and Ranma together?
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
"Shampoo's Red Thread."
We'll see you there!