[music playing]
[theme music]
Come on, Kasumi.
Can't you find some other place
to dry out all this laundry?
It's starting to feel like
we're a bunch of Bedouins living
in a tent city or something.
Right behind you, Saotome.
I know, Father.
But it's been raining for weeks.
So it's far too wet
to hang them outside.
Here, Ranma.
Have another bowl of rice.
Great, thanks, Kasumi.
Aw, man, how am I
supposed to eat?
That reminds me.
Why isn't Happosai here?
The usual reason, I guess.
He's probably out on
one of his panty raids.
Hm.
He won't have much luck stealing
lingerie from clotheslines
today.
Not in this rain.
NARRATOR: The Horrible
Happo Mold-Burst.
[crying]
Oh, lingerie, where are you?
My pretty panties.
My beautiful bras.
[crying]
I can't stand this rain!
[grunt]
Hi, Ranma.
I figured you might
be practicing.
Yeah, I had to do something.
And there's no way I'm
going out in that weather.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
How about we work out together?
Sure.
Hey, I wonder why they don't
hang the laundry in here.
It's certainly big enough.
Yeah, it would dry way faster
in the hall than in that house.
KASUMI: Oh, hi.
I didn't know you
two were in here.
Hi, Kasumi.
This training hall is a lot
older than you might think.
So you'd better be careful of
all the leaks in the ceiling.
What leaks?
[scream]
That explains
why you don't hang
the clothes to dry in here.
Maybe I should have
warned you a little sooner.
[sigh]
All that hard work and
not a thong to show for it.
Hm?
What's this?
No men allowed?
[gasp]
Bikinis.
Halter tops.
So far as the eye can see.
So this is where
you've all been hiding.
AKANE: Happosai!
Hm?
Uh oh.
What are you doing in here?
Uh, you see, I, uh--
[fighting sounds]
[scream]
[groan]
This turning into a girl
stuff sure is getting old.
Huh?
[scream]
[groan]
Thanks a lot.
Now I'm going to have
to take another bath
to turn back into a guy.
Sorry, but you'll have to do
a lot better than that if you
want any sympathy from me.
Then how about this?
[grunt]
Now I've got you
right where I want you!
Hey!
What's going on?
What's all the commotion?
[gasp]
Take this!
Keep it down.
[grunt]
What's going on out here?
[scream]
Huh?
A dud?
I don't get it.
Why didn't it go off?
This time you won't escape
the Happo Fire-Burst!
Hm.
These explosives will wipe
the smile off your face, Ranma.
[scream]
That's impossible.
Every one of them was a dud?
No!
They're soggy!
[laughter]
Your bombs are useless.
Too bad, you old freak.
[crying]
The horror.
Now it's payback time!
[groan]
Ranma beat Happosai.
Hm.
My.
[laughter]
That was hardly
even a challenge.
SOUN: Hang on, Ranma.
Huh?
How do you propose
to fix this leak?
[groan]
RANMA: Come on.
You can do better than that.
No slacking off, old man.
Poor Master's been
reduced to a cleaning boy.
How pitiful.
He deserves it.
And don't forget to
separate the colors.
Yes, sir.
Get a move on.
Chop-chop.
Anything you say, sir.
Put your elbows into it.
Yes, sir.
AKANE: Ranma, don't
you think you're
being a bit too hard on him?
You talking about
the old freak?
It's not fair.
You're treating him like
he's your slave or something.
COLOGNE: Hm.
Happy did that?
Yeah.
And now he's in shock
because apparently he
thought he'd be able
to beat everyone
with that bomb trick of his.
Pardon me.
Cold noodles to mark
start of new season.
Shampoo make them extra
special for Ranma.
Eat up.
You get strong.
I'll tell you one thing.
If I know Happosai, I'm
almost certain he won't
take this insult sitting down.
I'd watch your back.
No prob.
This stuff rocks.
Shouldn't you be at
least a little worried?
[grunt]
[mutters under breath]
[grumble]
Oh.
Potent.
[laughter]
I finally succeeded.
This time my performance
will blow you away.
I guarantee it.
Happo Bomb-Burst!
Get off!
It's not me you're after!
Oh.
This ought to do it!
Whoa!
Oh, no!
[scream]
[groan]
Maybe I need a little break.
Ah, for crying out loud!
My strawberry rice cakes!
Look at them.
They're covered in-- huh?
Mold?
[laughter]
[man talking on tv]
Hey, old man!
We need to channel changed!
[man talking on tv]
Hey!
Old man!
[knocking]
Huh?
[laughter]
Ranma, you've shown
nothing but utter disrespect
for me for the last few days.
But now I'm going to make you
regret that you ever crossed me
with that attitude.
I don't get it, Master.
I've never seen you look
so confident before.
You're not yourself.
[laughter]
Not that old trick again.
It's getting really tired.
Wait!
That bomb.
It's the Master's new weapon.
[groan]
What?
A new weapon?
Take this, Ranma!
Happo Mold-Burst.
What?
[explosion]
Darn it all.
Ranma must have escaped.
Wait!
This must be karmic retribution
for that junior high experiment
that went so wrong.
What did I ever do to
deserve such rude treatment?
[groan]
Wait, you coward!
Come and get your
fistful of fungus.
(VOICEOVER) Jeez.
I can't even breathe
with all that mold.
Now what's going on?
Run, Akane!
Huh?
Get back here!
Oh!
What's all this?
He's got me cornered.
[laughter]
Why don't you just give
up now while you can?
If you model this
for me, then I just
might consider forgiving you.
Think again, you old freak.
[yelling]
All right!
Have another Happo Mold-Burst.
[scream]
AKANE: Ranma!
Maybe you should have given
my offer more thought, huh?
[scream]
The Happo Mold-Burst
is utterly invincible.
[laughter]
Ranma.
[animal sounds]
[sigh]
Finally, Mr. Sun shows
shiny, happy face today.
[gasp]
[coughing]
Huh?
Hi-ya, Ranma!
Whew, that feels better.
Thanks, Shampoo.
That better.
Now Ranma no look disgusting.
I have to say, I've never
heard of that mold trick before,
though.
Trust the old man to come
up with a moldy old trick
like that.
There must be
something I can use
to counter that move, Granny.
Hm.
I'm sure if we put
our heads together,
we could come up with a plan.
Huh?
AKANE: Jeez, this is
getting ridiculous.
Kind of livens things up,
though, don't you think?
Not a chance.
And where's Ranma?
He hasn't even come back
since Happosai turned him
into a mold ball.
Aha.
So that's why you're
in such a bad mood.
It is not!
Don't worry, Akane.
I'm sure Father and Mr. Saotome
will think of something.
Hm.
[chatter]
Hm?
Thank you for coming to the
Tendo Living Museum of Mold.
Be sure to tell all your
friends, and please come again.
Nabiki, what on earth do
you think you're doing?
Making some money.
Huh?
How could you be so greedy
at a time like this?
Akane, one must never,
under any circumstances,
forget her aspirations
and goals for the future.
Now I mustn't keep
the crowds waiting.
Back to work.
[groan]
Please, Master,
have mercy on us
and return our house to
its former moldlessness.
We're begging you.
I didn't do it.
It must've been a
rogue mold spore.
Then talk to it.
HAPPOSAI: No chance.
Why won't you help us?
It feels so cushy.
It's like sleeping on
a bed of fluffy clouds.
I bet you two haven't
even tried it out yet.
If we don't stop
him soon, our house
will be completely
covered with mold.
We've got to go
straight to the source.
Yes, for world peace.
As peacekeepers.
You monster!
Enough's enough!
Happo Mold-Burst!
[groan]
And over there,
ladies and gentlemen,
we have Tendo Living
Museum's famous mold
statue, Rhapsody in Green.
[chatter]
COLOGNE: Are you ready, Ranma?
I'm going to release
these boulders now.
Imagine that they're
the mold bombs,
and try your best to dodge them.
Then climb your way to
the top of this cliff.
That'll be a snap, Granny!
Hang on.
You mustn't inhale the
poison of the mold bombs,
so you'll have to
hold your breath.
And of course, you mustn't have
any contact with them, either.
Now let's commence with
Operation Mold Buster.
Right!
Ready when you are.
Shampoo!
Shampoo ready!
Here goes!
Come on, Ranma!
Just one more!
Shampoo know you can do it!
[groan]
That boy needs a
lot more practice.
[groans]
Hi-ya.
Ranma still not good enough.
[grunts]
[scream]
COLOGNE: Not even close.
SHAMPOO: Come on, Ranma.
[groan]
COLOGNE: You don't stand
a chance against Happosai.
RANMA: OK.
Once more.
[chatter]
RANMA: Old man!
HAPPOSAI: Oh, Ranma, it's you.
You freak!
Happosai!
What you doing here?
Long time, my friends.
What's with all the backpacks?
You people been away
on a trip or something?
I've been training so I
can defeat you, old man!
Huh?
Hi-ya.
Look at his feet.
They're covered in mold.
[laughter]
It's more comfortable
than the best shoes
I ever slipped my dogs into.
This mold attack
is the greatest.
[groan]
How dare you do this--
spreading that filthy mold
in my restaurant where we pride
ourselves on customer service.
Now Ranma's not the
only one who's mad.
Oh, yeah?
So you want to fight.
I'll be glad to take you on.
[explosion]
He's more powerful
than I thought.
[laughter]
Here I come, Happosai.
[grunts]
[yelling]
Come on!
Right!
[yelling]
What's going on?
Master, what is it?
Granny, is that you?
Darn it all.
I'm too late.
[laughter]
Welcome to my crib, Granny.
[groan]
Oh, no.
I can't stand mold.
[laughter]
Sounds like a white
flag, unless I'm mistaken.
Take this!
My infamous Happo Mold-Burst!
[scream]
[groan]
Nice move, Granny.
I'll take over.
We're counting on you.
Ranma!
Old man, I'm not going to let
you have your way, anymore.
Here I come!
Huh.
Want to try your luck as a
walking Petri dish again?
Sorry, old man, but your
luck's run out this time.
[grunts]
I knew Ranma could do it.
He must have come up
with a new and better way
to attack Happosai.
Shampoo no convinced.
Huh?
Ranma's new move
never work in practice.
How would you know
if it worked or not?
Shampoo help Ranma to
practicing hard and work out.
Shampoo know everything.
You've been practicing
with Ranma every day?
[laughter]
[groan]
Happo Mold-Burst!
Ha!
Take that!
And this!
Ranma!
Come on!
Pretend you practicing
with Shampoo again!
Hm.
There's a lot of big talk
coming from you, Ranma.
Yet I don't see
you doing anything
except trying to
dodge my attacks.
Pretty cowardly.
(VOICEOVER) Darn.
If I could only find a
way to crush that bomb.
But if I did that, I'd get
completely covered with mold.
Huh?
No.
This rain will only help
Master's mold attack.
He couldn't have planned
it better himself.
Have this and another!
And another!
Here!
Ha!
Come on.
Take that.
Ranma.
Oh, my.
It's starting to rain again.
What's going on, Kasumi?
What on earth have you
dragged out of the closet?
What's that gizmo
supposed to be for?
Oh, it's just
something I found.
And I thought it might
come in handy for Ranma.
Yeah?
I just found this mold spray.
And I was wondering if you
could use something like this.
Oh, yeah!
(VOICEOVER) Here goes nothing.
Super Anti-Mold Spray!
Nice try.
Just try and survive
my Mega Mold-Burst!
[scream]
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-ha!
Impossible.
My Mega Mold-Burst.
You're through, [inaudible].
[scream]
Not again.
Ha!
So much for him!
Well, Ranma.
Very impressive, my boy.
Way to go, my son.
Wicked move, Ranma.
I knew you could do it.
That because Ranma and
Shampoo practice together.
[giggle]
You think I care?
RANMA: Hey, what's the
old man doing out there?
He's trying to save
his precious lingerie
collection from all
that nasty mold that
got through the house.
Doorknob.
Yep.
You got that right.
[laughter]
Silence!
I don't have to take this!
Hm?
Come on.
Not one of these old
soggy bombs again.
Uh oh.
Oh, yeah.
The rainy season's
over now, isn't it?
[groan]
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER):
What do you mean
Kuno has an album full of racy
pictures of Ranma as a girl?
And what's that got
to do with Kodachi?
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
The Kuno Sibling Scandal.
We'll see you there.