[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Back to the Happosai.
-Step right up.
The treasures of the
Orient lay before you.
-Don't you got
any game software?
-Well, I got Chutes and Ladders.
-Ah, it's nothing but junk.
-Come on, let's go.
-Punks.
You just watch what
you're calling junk,
you little-- heya, baby.
-Huh?
-You'll buy something
from me, won't you?
-What?
-I'll gladly take
underwear in lieu of cash.
-Oh, please.
Hmph.
-Hey, I thought girls were
supposed to like shopping.
-Yo, Gramps, what'cha doing?
-Business, obviously.
-Business?
-What kind of business?
-Oh, I get it.
You're selling off all that
underwear you stole, ain't ya?
-Ha!
I'd sooner sell a kidney than
part of my precious collection.
SHAMPOO: Delivery.
-What?
A delivery?
That's weird.
I didn't think we'd
order anything.
-Great Grandma to
bring brand new kind
of ramen for free
taste test today.
-Hey, you didn't put
nothing in it, did ya?
Another dose of that
love potion or something?
-Sorry.
Only it's just ramen
noodle this time.
It's too delicious.
-Would you look
at all this junk.
-Do you mind?
I'm right here.
Oh, come on.
What do you say?
What if I give you my
word, I'll be good.
-Hmph.
-RANMA: Yeah, right.
-OK, OK, already.
SHAMPOO: Everything's so old.
Grandmother, this
one is nice antique.
Maybe I buy it.
-Hey, how'd this get
into my junk drawer?
I thought it was long gone.
-I give you 10 yen for it.
-My magic mirror's not for sale.
-Magic mirror?
-You got it.
I'm told it was once owned
by Alexander the Great who
brought it to Japan
along the Silk Road.
Why, I wouldn't part with
it for all the tea in China.
-Do tell.
Next thing, you'll be
telling us it was a gift.
-Wherever it came
from, it's beautiful.
-Yeah, I wonder where
he stole it from.
-Bite your tongue.
It was more like--
well, more like a gift.
Yeah.
-What'd I tell you?
-At the time, I was but
a lad of 18 summers.
I was traveling in China
on a training journey.
And then one day, I came
upon a virtuous maiden.
But our love was not to be.
My warrior's heart had
no time for romance.
-Farewell.
-Oh, my Lord Happosai,
at least take
this in remembrance of our love.
-At least-- [sigh] At least I
have this to remember her by.
Hey, I'm taking here.
-Yeah, yeah.
We're listening.
Then what happened?
-And then I never
got to see her again.
-Wow, that's too bad.
-She remembers me
still, I'm sure of it.
Pining for me in her
lonely spinsterhood.
Oh, how could I have done it?
How could I have
left her behind?
[laughter]
-Oh.
Oh, that's a good one, Gramps.
Why don'tcha tell
us another one?
-Not even pine tree
pine for that one.
-No kidding.
Why waste over some
teen romance when
she's moved on with her life?
-Pah.
That's the problem with
you youngsters today--
no romance in your soul.
-Now that you mention it,
this story does seem familiar.
Something very similar once
happened in my village.
However, in my version.
-Wo ai ni!
GRANDMOTHER (VOICEOVER):
This so-called fool
for love made passes at
every girl in the village.
Then he plundered
all our valuables
and headed for the hills.
-Come back, thief!
-My jewelry!
-Thief!
-What do you mean thief?
Sounds more like an
adventurer to me.
-No.
When I say thief, I mean thief.
-Simmer down, will you?
You're acting like you're
the one that got dumped.
-Stop it.
-My-- my-- my wall!
Why can't you two
just get along?
-What did we miss?
-And you, Grandmother, you're
old enough to know better.
-Enough of this nonsense.
Give me my mirror.
-Well, I'll be.
It's not the mirror
that's the antique here.
It's you, the owner.
Don't tell me you're Cologne.
-Nice to see you too, Happy.
-Did she say Happy?
-Cologne?
-What?
You know know Grandma
the real name?
-The only way that you
could know that nickname
is if you were there,
live and in person.
-Happy, she says.
-Cologne, he says.
-Great Grandmother,
why you never
say you know him before now?
-It's not the kind of thing
one likes to dwell on,
if you know what I mean
-What's your excuse?
-Call it a mental block.
Is it my fault I didn't realize?
It was long ago.
All this time, I've been
living on hopes and dreams,
praying for the day
when I could be reunited
with the young girl who
took charge of my heart.
Who could've known that that
beautiful girl would grow up
to look like the crypt-keeper?
Ah, the tragedy.
Farewell, oh, light-hearted
days of youth.
-Uh-oh.
-Wha--?
-Huh?
-Oh.
-Wha-- what the heck's going on?
-Huh?
-Now you've done it.
KASUMI: OK, everyone.
Time for lunch.
Huh?
Hm, now that is really odd.
I could've sworn I
heard them talking.
RANMA: Somebody wanna tell
me what's going on here?
-You don't think
it's a dream, do you?
-What do you make
of it, Saotome?
-So what are you
asking me for, Tendo?
Master?
-Uh--
-Oh, just as I feared,
the very worst has come.
-What worst is
that, Great Grandma?
-We've traveled back
in time to China.
-What?
Back in time to China?
GRANDMA: Just so.
If, while holding
the magic mirror,
a tear should happen
to fall, a window
opens up to the
bearer's heartland,
bringing him or her back
where they'd most like to be.
Like I said, the worst has come.
-Worst?
What are you?
Kidding?
Since we've come
all this way, we
might as well look
around a bit, eh?
-Hey, Ranma, you're right.
Maybe we can pick up
a souvenir for Kasumi.
-You don't suppose
they'd have hot springs?
-Why not live it up?
-Say, I could really
use a long soak at--
[screaming]
-He's following us.
-Where you going, girls?
I'm offering you all
this marriage here.
Be reasonable.
Stingy.
-What a moron.
Serves him right.
-Say hello to young Happosai.
-What?
-Don't make me laugh.
In the past, I looked like--
why'd you do that for?
-Do we look like we just
fell off the turnip truck?
-It's me, I tell you.
Me!
-Hear that, Tendo.
-Sure did, Saotome.
-Wh-- why are you looking at me?
-Prepare yourself.
-En garde.
Prepare for your final
reckoning, you evil runt.
-What are you doing?
-We did it.
We beat the evil master.
-Justice comes at last.
-Don't make me laugh.
Why, you two little ingrates.
Don't you know
there's no difference
between hitting
him and hitting me?
-Oh, yeah?
You don't say.
-But we thought
you looked like--
-You go, Tendo.
-You there, weakling.
On your feet.
Are you a man or a mouse?
-Back off.
What's an old fart like
you gonna teach me?
-Old-- old fart, you say?
Big words for an amateur.
What's the matter
with you anyway?
Chasing after sweet and
innocent girls like that.
Don't you know that kind of
stuff's bad for your character?
-I'll say.
-You'll get no argument here.
-Butt out, Gramps.
Wow, hey, baby.
What do you say we get hitched?
What are you doing?
Let me go.
-I'm gonna teach you the
error of your evil ways.
-Aw, but I like my evil ways.
-Teaching himself to be good?
Now this I gotta see.
-And here's the house
where I grew up.
-Wow, really?
-It seems like only
yesterday that-- look.
There's me when I was 18.
Would you mind making your lies
a little less obvious please?
-If you think I'm
lying, watch this.
Hey, Cologne.
-You called?
ALL: Oh my god.
-There.
That ought to teach you
the error of your ways.
Now, once more.
-Give me a break.
I pooped.
-You really are
pathetic, aren't you?
You want to end up
a dirty old man?
-Speak for yourself.
Some of us are still in
the prime of our youth.
-And what would you
know about youth?
What you say and do now
affects the rest of your life.
Don't you know that?
What?
What you looking at?
-Be honest.
Which would you prefer--
a long training journey
or stealing women's underwear?
-Stealing underwear.
-Which do you think is
more fun-- training so hard
you peer into the
mouth of hell itself
of looking at women in a bath?
-Looking at women.
You're right.
I got nothing to teach you.
-I already told you that.
Go back to where you
came from, you old fart.
-Come back.
-Please to drink.
Maybe fathers prefer
rice wine instead?
-What a charming hostess.
-You said it, Saotome.
-I feel awful.
Here we are, complete
strangers, and yet--
-Oh, no.
I have crazy feeding we
meet somewhere before.
-Boy, I'll say.
-Sorry?
-Uh, nothing.
-Cologne.
-Why you here, Happy?
-Come on, baby.
Don't be that way.
-Go home.
-But Cologne, I only--
ah, now I get it.
This is your way of
showing affection.
Throwing tea is some kind
of Chinese tradition, right?
-Jeez, how clueless can you get?
-Go away.
Shoo.
-No.
I'm not leaving until
you say you'll marry me.
-But I--
-What's the matter?
You heard the lady.
-You'd best go, or we'll be
forced to hurt you, little man.
-Why I ought to--
-You want to start something?
-Mark my words.
Someday, I'll be the
one bullying you.
-Say, you really care
about him, don't you?
-While everyone eat appetizer,
I go make main course, OK?
-All right.
-I knew it.
She really does care
about the little guy.
-What?
You mean the freak?
-Well, Great
Grandmother, is true?
-Well, I-- I don't actually hate
him, if that's what you mean.
-Wish I could say
I was surprised
but-- aw, quite moping
around, will you?
I told you I'd help you, but
first, get me some more rice.
-You just ate it all.
[clatter]
Huh?
Hello?
Hey.
Huh, what's this?
Hey, what do you know?
Pork buns.
-I knew it.
-Maybe we can help get
those two together.
-Well then, time to
inventory my collection.
-C-- collection?
-How sweet it is.
How very sweet.
Hands off.
No fair touching
the merchandise.
HAPPOSAI (VOICEOVER): If I was
this much of a pervert at 18,
then what does that make me now?
-Time for a crash course.
-Come on, let me go.
-I won't let go
unless you follow me.
-No fair, you old fart.
-Thanks to you and
your perversity, women
think I'm a freak.
You've got to straighten
out before it's too late.
-What are you talking about?
Huh?
Oh.
What's this?
"Meet me by the lake.
I'll be waiting for you.
Cologne."
She wants to meet me.
-"To my dearest Cologne, there's
something I must tell you.
Please meet me by the lake.
Happy."
-Oh, sound very important.
-You'd better hurry.
You don't want to keep him
waiting too long, do you?
[sigh]
-But I no can go.
-Huh?
Why not?
-Because I no like Happy.
-You're lying.
Why can't you just be
honest with yourself?
-Why you no be
honest about letter?
-Wha--
COLOGNE: Everyone know
Happy no can write Chinese.
SHAMPOO: Huh?
AKANE: Oh.
So much for that idea.
-What were you two thinking?
You trying to cause some kind
of time paradox or something?
If it was meant to
be, don't you think
she would have married
him the first time?
-Well, I suppose so.
-To be in love is
important thing.
Womans can be happy
whole life with that.
-Isn't that the truth.
-Right?
-Hm?
Hey, Granny, where you going?
-I-- I've been thinking, if
she won't go to meet him,
maybe I should.
-What?
[rustle]
-Happy.
-Ni hao.
GRANDMA: Ugh.
HAPPOSAI (VOICEOVER):
How dare he
try to take my
place with Cologne.
Hey, since when can
Cologne write Japanese?
WOMAN 1: Curse you, Happy.
WOMAN 2: Hey!
WOMAN 1: Come back here.
-Hey, it's the villagers.
-Where is he?
Did you see him?
-He must've run away.
-I swear, when I
get my hands on him,
he's going to pay
for those vegetables
he stole if it's
the last thing I do.
-What are you going
to do with that?
-This mirror been in Cologne's
family for many generation.
To sell it pay for
many vegetable.
-Come on, don't be stupid.
Why would you want to do that?
-Maybe you not know Happy
so well as you think.
-Huh?
You know something
about him that I don't?
-If you could have
seen him on that day.
What is wrong?
-She needs you more than I.
COLOGNE: Here is Happy
on brink of death,
and all his worry
is for little bird.
Cologne never meet such
kind person in whole life.
-A stuffed animal?
Whoa.
You know, I'll give him credit
for nerve if nothing else.
-You no understand.
Because he too
tired from training,
he mistake toy
bird for real one.
-If you like him so
much, why be so mean?
Why don't you just
marry him then?
-Right now, he hard at training.
He no have time for
someone like me.
-Cologne
-Happy.
-I knew that letter was a lie.
How can you date someone like
him when you've already got me?
-Oh, shut up.
-Come outside if
you're man enough.
-If I'm what?
-Honestly.
-Oh, I feel sick.
-Hmph.
Not half as sick as I feel.
-Wah!
Why you--
-Oh, no you don't, you little--
-What you doing to my Happy?
-Cologne
-Happy.
-Cologne!
-Happy!
Oh, wait a minute.
I'll be right back.
Hey, babe!
Cologne, you know you're
the only one for me.
Hey, oh, somebody help me.
[villagers screaming]
-Oh, great.
Now even Cologne is
running me out of town.
-Give me back my magic
mirror, you little thief.
HAPPOSAI: Nya, nya.
Sorry.
I'm out of here.
COLOGNE: Give me back my mirror!
-Gee, why is it
I'm not surprised?
-Eh, so I exaggerated a little.
Who cares.
The important thing is
I got the magic mirror.
-Shame on you.
-Bad man.
-And you call
yourself our master.
-Maybe we should find a new one.
-Miscreant.
-No fair.
It's not fair that you all gang
up on me like that, you know.
I want to go home.
Give it back, thief.
-Don't be ridiculous.
It's my mirror.
-I've gone through too
much to give it up now.
-That's not my problem.
Besides, you can't have it.
I won't let you.
-Man, doesn't he learn anything
from his past mistakes?
-Speaking of which,
why didn't you
visit Jusenkyo while
you were in China, son?
-Ah!
Give me that mirror!
-Why this always happen?
RANMA: Give it to me.
Give it to me.
-You got me.
-No!
-Give it back.
Give it--
-Are you guys having
a garage sale?
What a bunch of junk.
[ending theme]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Kodachi, the Black Rose.
Just who do you
think you are anyway?
What do you mean you're
Ranma's new bride?
Next time, on "Ranma 1/2"--
"Kodachi the Black Rose.
The Beeline to True Love."
We'll see you there.