[theme music]
-Enter Shampoo,
the gung-ho girl.
I put my life in your hands.
MALE BROADCASTER
(ON TV): Welcome
to mainland China, where
3,000 years of history
meets 3 million
miles of mystery.
-Oh right.
You know, I've always
wanted to eat one of these.
-Don't tell me you've
never had ice cream.
-Guys would never eat this kind.
It'd be embarrasing.
Mm!
-And you're not embarrassed now?
-Hey, I'm a girl now.
It don't count.
[giggle]
-Well, a real girl would not
be eating ice cream like that.
-Aw, be quiet.
I'll eat it however I want to.
Here.
This one.
I wanna try this
chocolate one next.
-Hm.
-Hey!
Are you crazy?
Don't waste that on him.
If you don't want
it, give it to me!
[oink]
-Who ever heard of a pig
eating ice cream anyway?
It'll probably make
you sick or something.
MALE BROADCASTER (ON TV):
Only a stone's throw away --
-Huh?
MALE BROADCASTER (ON TV): from
the legendary Bayankala range
of the Qinghai province.
FEMALE BROADCASTER (ON
TV): Oh, very impressive.
MALE BROADCASTER
(ON TV): The peoples
of this area revere
China's White Rock
Mountain as a local deity.
What hidden secrets lie buried
within its stony depths?
Let's take a closer
look with our exclusive
on the scene reporter.
-Ah, I've been there.
REPORTER (ON TV): Well,
the conditions here
at this Amazon village
are very-- Agh!
Look at that!
-Huh?
Look.
What's that?
-Ranma.
-Huh?
-Sha-- Sha-- Shampoo!
-Ranma, you know this girl?
-Ranma, die.
-Yo, Shampoo, when did you--
-Die!
-Hey, why don't you just get
over it, and let me alone
already?
-Huh?
Ranma?
-Yeah, he ran out that way.
-Running again?
Ranma!
-Hey, lady, watch it!
-Who was that-- that girl?
Huh?
[whimpering]
-Did you have a fight
with her or something?
-It's kind of hard to explain.
-Awfully cute, wasn't she?
-Yeah, real cute.
-What are you gonna
do about this mess!?
Who's that girl?
Is she your friend?
I demand you pay
for all the damages.
Your crazy friend
wrecked my restaurant!
-That crazy girl
is not my friend!
She's trying to kill me!
I'm not paying for
nothing, got it!?
-Who-- who-- who are you people?
-Tell me the truth, Ranma.
Who is that girl?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): A
couple of months ago
I was passing through her town.
-I'm so hungry.
-Here, sirs, we come to
rustic village, New Chezu.
-New Che-- what?
What kind of food is that?
-Ooh, sirs, this is
town of Amazon womans.
-Huh?
-Ohh, very lucky.
Today the womans
have tournament.
RANMA: That's a woman?
GUIDE: Here, that
one more pretty, no?
-Haiya!
-You watch this one, sirs.
Win tournament is
a very good honor.
-That girl's was got
some serious strength.
-Ooh, sirs, what
you eating there?
-Rur?
-Uh--
-Hey.
[speaking chinese]
-Hey, little woman and big
panda, why you steal my prize?
What are you doing?
That's what she say to you.
-What prizh?
[speaking chinese]
-Today a fighting tournament,
what only come once a year.
Now I become a champion!
That's what she say now.
-Ha.
Well, If I defeat you,
you've got no problem right?
-What, She say.
[gasping]
-Haiya!
-Ah, too bad.
He win.
[giggle]
-Hm.
-So that's it.
You just kissed her then?
-Hey, I ain't finished yet.
-Agh!
Oi, run, sirs!
Run, run run!
-Now what?
-That one just give
you the Kiss of Death!
-She gave me what?
-Womans of Amazon Tribe
has much pride, sirs.
Losing to outsider
is worst thing
that can happen to those womans!
Kiss of Death is promise
to chase to ends of Earth,
and kill!
Ooh, terrible tragedy, sirs!
Very terrible.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): And
that's what she did.
Everywhere we went in
China, there she was.
-And now she's
found you in Japan.
It's his own fault,
isn't it, Bee-chan.
Hey, at least the girl
trying to kill you is cute.
-If you're trying to cheer
me up, it ain't working.
Why do you always gotta--
-Your father's brought
over a visitor, Ranma.
Wasn't that a sweet
thing for him to do?
-Have you gone crazy?
Well, have you?
-Uh-uh.
-Ranma?
[gulp]
-Nihao.
-Uh-- Nihao.
-He's man.
-Uh-- yeah.
That-- that's right.
I'm a guy.
Ha.
I'm sorry about that.
You see?
-Oh, don't tell me you never
showed her your manly side
before, Ranma.
-Huh?
You think you're
real smart, doncha?
Eh, P-chan?
Huh?
-Oh, I wouldn't talk that
way if I were you, Ranma.
-Hey, don't joke around.
-She came all this way
to find a girl, Ranma.
You don't want to
disappoint her!
Well, now what?
-Ranma, where she?
-I-- I-- I don't know.
-You hide, Ranma.
You too must die!
-Akane?
OK, that's it.
You've done enough damage!
Huh?
-Hm?
-Oh, my.
-That poor girl defeated
by male Ranma this time.
-Huh?
It was an accident.
-Yeah, you beat her fair
and square, all right.
-He's right.
You did win.
Don't be so modest now, Ranma.
-Mhm.
-But then that would mean--
-That would mean she's gonna
be after the male Ranma too.
[stuttering]
-Wait.
You didn't lose.
It was an accident.
-Be a man, and take
your Kiss of Death.
-Wo ai ni.
-Wo ai ni?
It's you I love?
-Huh?
-Love?
-What the?
-Oh my.
-Ranma.
-Huh?
-Hm?
-Airen!
-Hmph.
-Huh?
-Oh.
-Hmph!
-Huh?
-That's enough.
What's the fuss?
What's going on?
-Oh, father.
-Hm.
-Well, father, I-- I don't
know all the details,
but it seems this girlfriend
of Ranma's followed him
all the way from China so
she could finish him off,
or so they could
finish something.
Yeah, something
like that I think.
-Girlfriend?
Well?
-What do you mean, I don't know?
That's not how it happened.
-But it's mostly
how it happened.
Right, Ranma?
-She has never seen me
as a guy before, OK?
-So you say.
-Hm?
-Still, you two seem to
be very close friends.
-Oh, great.
Are you trying to tell
me that you see me
that way too, Mr. Tendo?
-I can't see you any other way.
[moaning]
-Ranma, as far as I'm concerned,
our engagement never happened!
-Well, then, son.
Tell us again how you
got yourself into this.
-Hey, I already told you.
I got no idea.
-The book of Amazon Tribal law?
Huh?
-What?
What does that book say?
-You know perfectly well I
can't read a word of Chinese.
-Well, then why didn't
you just say so?
-Hm, good idea.
-The laws of the Amazon
Tribe are as follows.
-Well, hello, Nabiki.
Welcome home.
-In the event an Amazon is
defeated by an outsider,
and if that outsider
is a woman, the Amazon
must give the kiss of death
and kill without delay.
However, if that outsider is
a man, she must marry him.
-Oh.
-Huh?
That's a joke!
No way.
-Do I look like the
kind of girl who'd
joke about a thing like this?
-Maybe.
-Do go on.
-You can't read that.
Just admit it.
-Read Chinese?
Of course I can't.
-Ah-hah.
So were you joking then.
-Wrong.
I don't joke.
Look.
It's written in
Japanese right here.
-Huh?
-What?
-And I missed that completely?
-Ranma, you-- you dummy!
OK.
That helped.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
That fiance stuff
was all their idea anyway.
All we ever do is fight.
It's not like we're
in love or anything.
-Listen up, Akane is my fiance.
You touch her,
and I'll kill you!
-OK, Shampoo, let me
explain it a different way.
That Amazon stuff is all
right when you're in China.
But you're in Japan.
Now forget about that kill the
girls, and marry the guys rule.
-Rules?
In other words--
-She's trying to catch
herself a husband, Akane.
-Oh, you two.
-Why don't you go and make
up with him now, Akane?
-You don't really think he's
got the guts to cheat on you,
do you?
-So now you understand, Shampoo?
-Mhm.
-You didn't listen
to a word I said.
-Wode ailen.
-Hm, wode airen--
my beloved husband.
-Grr.
-Stop that.
I know you don't want to
hear this, but listen.
[giggle]
-You-- you and I, we--
-Oh.
Guess he forgot what he
was gonna say, eh, Akane?
-Ma-- marry you?
I mean, I can't 'cuz--
-Wo ai ni.
-Hm, wo ai ni.
I love you, it says, Akane.
-Enough!
OK?!
-So we-- well, that's
why we should--
you know-- just get to
know each other better.
Yeah, that's--
that's what we-- uh--
-Airen.
-Stop and listen
to yourself, son.
It's sad.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): It's funny.
She's been trying to kill me all
this time so I never noticed,
but that Shampoo
really is kind of cute.
Man, if only Akane
were that nice.
-Ryoga, why'd you do that?
-You know, watching Akane
get jealous over a jerk
like you really makes me sick.
-What?
Hey, stupid, if Akane's
jealous, then that's her--
-Me?
Jealous?
Never.
We were never engaged in
the first place, remember?
So go ahead!
And get to know her
better all you want!
-Uh-- Akane, wait.
Akane.
Hey!
You coulda hurt
somebody with that!
[scream]
-Huh?
Eek!
-Ranma, I kill!
Ranma!
-Wait a minute!
-When he's a boy,
she just wants him.
When he's a girl,
she wants him dead.
-Come on.
-Ranma!
-Well, they really do need to
get to know each other better,
now don't they?
-Mhm.
Ha.
-Stay-- stay away!
Stay away from me, I said!
-Ranma!
-Hey, watch it.
-I figure 2000
yen will cover it.
-Huh?
-I just saved your life, silly.
-Airen.
-I don't believe this.
I'm outta here.
Now what?
Ryoga?
What'd I ever do to you?
Huh?
-Airen!
-Aw, man.
Being a guy has gotta
be safer than this.
-Pss, Ranma.
How would you like this?
-Hm.
Hurry it up.
-With tax, your
total is 5,000 yen.
-Hey, kinda steep, isn't it?
-Do you want it, or, don't you?
-Ah!
OK, I'll take it.
Don't pour it out!
Hurry up, and give
it to me. hurry!
-Come again.
-No, wait!
It's me!
-Airen?
-Ha.
-Wode airen!
-That's worse!
-Ryoga!
Did Nabiki put you up to this?
Huh?
-Ranma!
-Somebody help me!
Help me, please!
-Ranma!
-Leave me alone!
-I kill!
-Go away!
Help!
-You know, Saotome, with you
and your son in this house,
there's never a dull moment.
I'm so glad you're here.
[crying]
-Ranma.
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Shampoo, what do
you think you're
doing with P-chan?
Huh?
Kiss of Death?
Fine then.
I'll accept your challenge.
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
"Shampoo's Revenge.
The Shiatsu Technique That
Steals Heart and Soul."
See you there.