[music playing]
AKANE: Put down a monster?
Sure, why not?
Well, it seems that one's
appeared at a seaside resort.
They were nice enough
to invite us to take
care of their problem for them.
Hm.
Now you three be sure
and come back safely.
But, uh--
ALL: We will!
(SINGING) Ho hi, ho hi,
we'll make the monster die.
We'll eat his brain
and drink champagne.
Ho hi, ho hi.
I wish I were going
to the hot springs.
I don't like this.
Have a good trip.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): "Mystery
of the Marauding Octopus Pot!"
[music playing]
[bubbling]
Got it!
Yay!
We have a winner!
[laughing]
The monster's called the
marauding octopus pot?
That's what they say.
We'll know more once we meet
with the town council members.
MERCHANT: Hurry, hurry.
Step right up.
Get your rice cakes!
From the monster's name,
one assumes it must be a type
of octopus or--
Four rice cakes for me, please.
Coming right up!
Hey, no fair, Tendo.
Give me some rice wine.
Suddenly, I understand
why you two guys
agreed to take this assignment.
WAITER: Marauding octopus pot!
What?
Hey, that must be it!
WAITER: Let go of my dumplings!
The octopus pot.
It doesn't look at all
like I imagined it would.
NARRATOR (ON TV):
The octopus pot.
Sunk deep in the
sea, these vessels
are used to trap and
retrieve sleeping octopi.
What the?
[grunting]
[screaming]
That hurt.
Quickly.
After him, boy.
Go on.
Gotcha.
Defeated them all.
Man, that's one
fast octopus pot.
Hm, now this is weird.
Searching for something?
Oh, just an octopus pot.
Yes, we're the experts
hired to bring the marauding
octopus down, actually.
Dear me, you mean that
monster's on the prowl again?
How scary.
Scary?
When you've got two strong
martial artist like us,
monsters are a specialty.
Now that we're here, you
can just sit back and--
[coughing]
BOTH: Huh?
Are you OK there, Miss?
I-- I'm sorry.
[cough]
I'm-- I'm very ill, you see.
I must be going.
Please, don't run away.
I have some nice rice wine.
And look, I have
some nice rice cakes.
If you insist.
Are you--
[coughing]
Goodbye.
Take care now.
Oh.
[coughing]
Who was that?
That, son, was a girl whose
house is covered in shells.
We could say more,
boy, but you're
far too young to understand.
Give me a break.
WAITER: Not only is this
so-called marauding octopus
pot we called you here
to stop bad for business,
it's stealing food, it's
ruining relationships,
and it's engaging in
indecent behavior!
Business in town
is falling off.
At this rate, we'll
go bankrupt withiN--
Um, are you listening?
Should we charge them for food?
You can leave everything to us.
Your monster troubles
are as good as gone.
As a true martial
artist, I you my word.
I just knew you were the
right man for the job.
BOTH: Thanks for the eats.
Hey!
My tempura!
My sashimi!
You ate it!
Ah!
Stupid jerks.
They talk this big game, then
they end up going to bed early.
And what's worse-- I got
a really bad feeling.
WAITER (VOICEOVER):
The octopus pot
seems especially
drawn to young women.
WAITER (VOICEOVER): If you lay
in wait in the women's bath,
therefore.
Let's see.
It's little.
It likes girls.
It's sneaky.
It fits in a pot.
And I think it's
sneaking up behind me!
[screaming]
OK, octo-pot!
Let's see what you got.
Ah!
Tricky little thing.
Get back here!
Yah!
Ah.
Now you got nowhere to run.
[chuckles]
[screaming]
Hey, what the--
[muffled screaming]
RANMA: Get it off!
Help!
That hurts!
GIRL: So, did they tell you?
Supposedly the
octopus is in here.
Must be why it's so empty.
ALL: You pervert!
[snoring]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I
don't feel so good.
Huh?
[screaming]
GENMA: What's this?
A person inside the pot?
That's right.
No monster.
Just your run of the
mill human being.
But, son, surely
no normal human
can fit inside such
a small container.
No normal human, no.
And you don't mean to suggest--
That it might be--
Well, time to go.
We had a few drinks.
Ate some nice fish.
Ready, Tendo?
Right behind you, Saotome.
Yo, yo, yo!
[exclaiming]
Hello there, boys.
BOTH: Master!
So you're the bozos they
hired to put down the monster?
SOUN: Yes, Master.
That would be us.
GENMA: We're not worthy.
Would you please
stop doing that?
WAITER: The octopus pot!
WAITER: It stole my sashimi!
Sounds like they're onto me.
SOUN (VOICEOVER): Not good.
If they discover our
connection to the Master--
GENMA (VOICEOVER): This could
be the end for our heroes.
Tell me, has the octopus
pot come through here?
May we help you?
WAITER: The octopus pot.
Is it in here?
What gave you that idea?
There!
On the table!
That sign on the platter.
What's it say?
Hm.
How did that--
That's the sashimi just
stolen a few moments ago.
Tendo, look how
contentiously he treats us.
The octopus pot
must be close by.
We'll crush that
pesky 'pus yet.
BOTH: Crush him dead!
Crush him dead!
[maniacal laughing]
Here we go again.
There.
Thanks, Kasumi.
I wonder if the
three of them are OK.
Well, seeing as
the three of them
are practically monsters
themselves, I wouldn't worry.
Nabiki!
Hey, a good omen.
SOUN: Yo, octopus pot!
GENMA: Come out, come
out, wherever you are.
You can't hide, you know?
You ran away because you
were scared, didn't ya?
WOMAN: Did you hear that, dear?
The octopus is back.
MAN: But those martial
artists will protect us.
Hey, octopus pt.
Where you at?
[bouncing]
SOUN: Hello?
Octopus pot?
[interposing voices]
Where could that thing be?
HAPPOSAI: Here.
Right here.
Where are you?
I'm right here.
Here.
Here!
If you want me so bad,
why don't you catch me?
SOUN: Penalty kick!
Look!
Up in the sky!
Well, I'll be.
Could that be the octopus pot?
GENMA: It got away.
SOUN: My goodness, it's fast.
GENMA: What a shame.
Ah, curse that stupid
Soun and Genma anyway.
Pretending not to know me.
Don't think I don't know that
that's what the two of you
are up to.
I think I know just how
I want to deal with that.
[screaming]
Gah!
[laughing]
Let's see them not try and
pretend not to know me now!
OK, now you happy?
How dare you!
Have you forgotten your place?
Uh-oh.
Allow me to remind you.
Hey, everybody!
Listen up!
He doesn't want
you to know this,
but this kid and
I are Master and--
Talk a little
louder why don't you?
Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
We're leaving town is what.
But are you sure you want
to let the old freak get away
like that?
SOUN: Let who get away?
GENMA: Who, that perv in a pot?
Never met him.
[laughs] Let's go.
Hey, at least let
go of the hair.
Come on!
That does it.
[thunderclap]
[exclaims]
The three of you
have disrespected me
for that last time.
Prepare to face
the consequences.
Happo Fire Burst!
[screaming]
And if that weren't enough,
Happo Rapid Fire Bursts!
[exclaiming, screaming]
You're all dead to me now.
Do you hear?
Why do I need you anyway?
I've got someone special.
Someone special?
No time for that now, Tendo.
We'd best make our escape.
Right as usual, Saotome.
WAITER: Leaving so soon?
Oh, oh.
Um, uh, we--
Wish you were as good
about getting results
as you are with making
us a pile of bills.
Not trying to escape, are ya?
Oh, no, no.
No.
And you've never met
that octopus before?
What, are you kidding?
No, never.
Tendo, you hear that?
This man thinks we
know the octopus pot.
Know the octopus?
Why, we've never even met him.
Have we, Saotome?
GENMA: No, never.
[nervous laughter]
Now that's a good one.
We must redouble
our efforts, Saotome.
Come on, boy.
We're going.
Hey!
Not so hard!
Ow!
Come on, I told you not
to yank on the hair!
Talk about you being
stuck between a rock
and a hard place, hey, Saotome?
Somehow, we--
So why don't you just
gravel like you always do?
Foolish boy.
He's so mad at us right
now, he's just as likely
to pluck our heads off
like petals on a daisy.
Basically, you just
want to be paid.
BOTH: Yeah, of course.
RANMA: Well, I guess you'd
better find him then,
hadn't you?
Well, he did mention
a special someone.
Didn't he, Saotome?
I believe he did, Tendo.
Yes.
[chuckling]
CUTE GIRL: You're so nice to me.
HAPPOSAI: [inaudible]
Hmm?
That shell-covered house.
Where that girl lives.
The one who sells seashells.
You know, down by the seashore.
BOTH: It's her!
RANMA: So, this is where that
little stink pot's been hiding.
One might even
call it his lair.
Hm, you don't
suppose the Master--
Prepare to be boarded.
Aha!
[scream]
That is disgusting!
We've got to stop him
before it's too late.
It's not so bad.
BOTH: It's not?
HAPPOSAI: Look here, dear.
See what I've brought
to make you feel better?
How can I ever
thank you? [coughing]
Have whatever you like.
Some fish cakes,
perhaps, or dumplings.
My goodness.
There's so much.
[coughing]
Oh, my dear!
Are you all right?
I--
[coughing]
I'm just so afraid.
I don't know how I'd
get by without you.
Well, you needn't
worry on that account.
I'll always be here
for you no matter what.
I knew somehow that you'd
always look after me.
I will.
I swear.
Such a mack daddy, you mean.
SOUN: Ranma, be nice.
Isn't there anything
else I can do for you?
Oh, no.
I--
[coughing]
I would like some
melons, though I
don't care for what they have
around here seeing as they're
covered in pesticides and--
[coughing]
If that's what
you want, then I--
Oh, no.
It's not that I--
although I am ever
so fond of organic produce.
Then I'm off, my
dearest, to steal--
I mean, to buy you your melons!
And you're sure
it's no trouble?
[giggling]
HAPPOSAI: All right.
I'm off.
Be back soon.
Aha!
Gotcha!
And what do you think
you three are doing?
Well, it's obvious, ain't it?
Now stay still
while we tie you up.
Kiss my crockpot!
Oh, no!
I don't think so.
Come here!
Don't let him get away!
Our reputation-- no, our
honor-- depends on it!
Yeah, yeah.
I'm chasing him, ain't I?
Now, Master?
We warned you.
You're the ones who
ought to take warning.
Now take this.
Happo Fire Cannon!
[screaming]
[laughing]
I told you, didn't I?
RANMA: OK, freak.
Now me!
Hi-ya!
Darn!
Gotcha.
Come here!
You little--
Now, that's just great!
Now which way did he--
Here I am.
Over here!
Over here, look!
Here!
Over here.
Come on.
Peek-a-boo!
Aha!
There, Ranma.
How'd you like that?
Anything goes special
attack octo-pot.
(MUFFLED) Get it off!
And now for the big finish!
Let go of me!
I don't think so!
Wow!
Where did you get those?
What?
Oh, big mistake.
I-- I'm blown up.
So much for the
marauding octopus pot.
HAPPOSAI: Hey,
it's dark in here!
Let me out!
Way to go, Ranma, my boy.
We're safe now from
dishonor and the food bill.
That's not why I did it.
Ranma!
Soun!
Genma!
BOTH (STUTTERING): Yes, Master?
Won't you please have a heart?
BOTH: What?
With me tied up, I won't
be able to get around
to get her the thing she needs.
She's gonna starve!
Who, that girl?
She needs me.
ALL: Octopus?
[coughing]
Please, you mustn't
worry about my welfare.
It's true, I'm too weak
to rise from my sick bed,
but that's no excuse to impose.
Although I do believe
I'd feel ever so much
better after a little
foie gras or caviar.
Or-- [coughs]
You really are too kind.
Well, what do you know, Gramps.
You've been replaced
by a cephalopod.
Now that, my friends, is sad.
This can't be happening.
Fine!
If that's the way things are!
Master, what is all this?
Souvenirs, obviously.
Can't come back from a
trip empty handed, can I?
He's got a point.
I'll leave it to you
to get them out of town.
You what?
WAITER: I knew not to trust you.
Just what kind of fools
do you take us for here?
Calm down.
No need to hate.
Don't be looking at me.
[screaming]
KASUMI: Oh, so you
were there, too.
Your move.
Check mate.
Here you go, grandfather.
HAPPOSAI: There's no
better care for being tired
than a cup of your tea.
KASUMI: Uh-huh.
So, did you put
down the monster?
No, not yet.
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Step right up!
Come and see the
magical paper dolls!
Just write a command
on it and then place it
on the target and presto!
Your wish is my command.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2"--
"Gosunkugi's Paper Dolls
of Love!"
We'll see you there!