[music playing]
[theme song]
[birdsong]
GIRL: Grandfather, a
parcel's arrived for you.
HAPPOSAI: I'm on my way.
GIRL: Here you are, grandfather.
Hm, I wonder who sent it?
There doesn't seem to be
a return address on it.
Ha, hm, hm.
[gasp]
So, what's in the
box there, master?
[grunting]
Oh.
Hm.
Hm?
Oh, dear.
Hm.
Mind your manners.
Come on, master.
It's too much to ask of a man.
Let us see.
There are no secrets between us.
Father's right.
We'd be honored if you were
to tell us what's inside.
When I'm ready.
Ugh.
MAN: Stingy.
You're a tease.
What could have
gotten into him?
Yeah.
At last, the timer's
finally arrived.
NARRATOR: Ranma's
greatest challenge.
[music playing]
Hey, what's going on?
What's gotten into Happosai?
How come he's locked
himself into his room?
A parcel came for
him, and it seems
to be something
pretty important.
An important parcel?
Wonder what it is?
I don't know, but the master
won't even talk to me about it.
He's been acting strange
ever since that mystery
package arrived here for him.
Listen, Tendo.
Hm?
I don't know about
you, but I'm getting
a bad feeling about this.
TENDO: You are?
Well, so am I.
It's probably something
sick the old freak ordered.
HAPPOSAI: Ranma?
Huh?
Grandfather?
My friends, the Ogre
Festival of the Dark
will be held before too long.
[gasp]
What?
Ogre Festival of the Dark?
It sounds so scary.
Take a look at this.
Oh, that was in the box.
HAPPOSAI: Precisely.
This is what was in the
parcel I received earlier.
Huh?
Ugh.
It's hard.
What's in it?
Get your teeth off of it.
Uh, uh, uh.
It's the festival's
Corpus Christi
that's been handed
down over generations.
BOTH: Corpus Christi?
Ranma, let's see.
Just looks like an
old tin can to me.
On the contrary.
The Ogre Festival
of the Dark has
been celebrated for over a
thousand years among masters
of the martial arts.
Only a select few
are able to attend.
[grunting]
And the one who
successfully fights his way
through to the end of the
festival is cloaked in glory.
This festival is like a gateway
for those aiming to become
serious martial artists.
Do you know about
this stuff, dad?
No, I have to say,
it's news to me.
I'm almost afraid to ask,
what happens to all the losers
in the festival?
It's the end of
life as they know it.
[gulp]
Huh?
[scream]
HAPPOSAI: And their
long-cherished dream
of becoming a martial
arts master is finished.
Imagine the anguish
of a martial artist
who sees his dream shattered
before his very eyes.
I'm sure you two can at
least sympathize with him.
Well, what kind of match is it?
What kind?
The rules are very
straightforward.
Whoever is the ogre
must protect the Corpus
Christi from the opponent.
And who would this opponent be?
HAPPOSAI: All those who
arrange the festival.
But they never actually
reveal themselves.
In other words, all the
opponents are invisible?
Uh-huh.
Oh, that reminds
me of a game we used
to play when we were little.
Remember?
The one with the tin can.
Hm?
Oh, you mean kick the can?
That's the one.
Whoever's it is the ogre.
Huh?
You don't mean?
Are you suggesting that I
go and play kick the can?
[chuckles]
Too afraid?
Hm.
No.
I'll give this contest a shot.
[grunting]
[panting]
[shouting]
Oh my, look at all the dust.
Ranma and grandfather certainly
are getting rough up there.
I don't know, you guys.
Don't you think Happosai
is going at it lot harder
than usual this time?
Especially considering that
Ranma's practicing with him.
But it is just kick
the can, after all.
How long could that be fun for?
Think they'll get bored?
[panting]
[music playing]
That wasn't too shabby
for a little warm up,
but now we're going to
start some real training.
You must be mentally
prepared with a focused mind.
Yeah, focused mind,
sure, whatever.
Now just tell me where I start.
First, we'll start
off with the road work.
What?
You don't mean I have
to do basic training?
Enough of that lip.
You got to build up
your stamina first.
You'll never win if you
don't have any stamina.
Got it?
Move out.
RANMA: Quit busting
my butt, I'm going.
[panting]
Huh?
[clatter]
He's close by.
Ah!
Awh!
Hm?
That old ninja trick.
[music playing]
Hey, that's your
firecracker trick.
[shouting]
Maybe I should rethink
this training thing.
Huh?
I should have known!
Ah.
Not bad at all, for
a freaky old man.
[music playing]
Wha?
[shouting]
Ahh!
[whimpering]
[birdsong]
Ah.
Oh, dear.
And we've only just
gotten started.
This just won't do at all.
GIRL: Poor Ranma.
He's getting torn to shreds.
Ugh.
Uh, ah, ah.
[groaning]
Hm.
Huh?
Ah!
Wha-- what was that?
[music playing]
[sighs]
Huh?
It's empty.
Hm?
TENDO: Check.
Huh?
How can that be?
Oh, you're not trying to
cheat me again, are you?
[rustling]
Hm?
Take this.
Looks like you scared it off.
Uh-huh.
And pretty fast, too.
What's this?
Saotome?
Where'd my man go?
Did you throw away
my check piece?
[grunts]
Don't play innocent, you.
Hi, I'm home.
Dad, something's not right.
What do you mean?
What's the matter?
[panting]
Daddy did you hear that?
I'm sure I heard something
underneath the floorboards.
What?
Hm.
Now that you mention it, Saotome
and I heard something strange
outside just awhile ago, too.
[grunts]
Oh, is something going on here?
[laughter]
Happosai?
Quit acting like scaredy-cats.
You must have expected this.
The members of the
Ogre Festival have
started arriving for
our planning meeting
here at the house.
[gasp]
[shouting]
[slurping]
[chewing]
More rice.
Ah, coming right up.
My, Ranma, you're
in high spirits.
Unreal.
You got an even bigger
appetite than normal,
even though you're hurt.
Got a point?
[laughs]
Us extreme fighters
have to eat well.
Especially when we're injured.
Eat like there's no tomorrow.
Ranma, if you lose
this competition,
it would mean the
end of the Anything
Goes School of martial arts,
as well as the Tendo Training
Hall losing its heir.
Saotome, come on.
There's lots of time for that.
I'm afraid not.
We'll talk about it
before the match.
What's the big deal, anyway?
We've got Akane.
Hey, you can handle running
the training hall without Ranma
around, can't you?
Ah, don;t be ridiculous.
I'll take that to
mean you do want Ranma
to be the training hall heir.
How's this any of
your business, anyway?
Hate to miss a good cat
fight, but I'm stuffed.
Time for a nap.
[receding footsteps]
Humph.
[howling]
[clattering]
HAPPOSAI: Now, Ranma,
the time has come
that we test your true ability.
[chuckles]
One thing's for sure--
with all this training,
I'm a lot better at taking hits.
HAPPOSAI: First of
all, a word of prayer.
We vow to do our best to
protect this until sunrise.
We will not let our opponents
take this, nor shall
we let it drop from the rooftop.
And if I do, then
I've lost, right?
Exactly, Ranma.
Got any more questions?
[grunts]
No.
Very well.
The Ogre Festival of the Dark
will begin on the signal.
Be very careful.
[barking]
[music playing]
[grunts]
Huh?
Ranma?
Oh, It's just you.
Is your cut getting any better?
Forget it, it's no big deal.
Uh, a-are I'm sure you want
to stake your entire future
on this one competition?
[music playing]
(WISTFULLY) Ranma.
[knocking]
[sighs]
Hm?
Kasumi, what are you doing?
You're still up?
Akane, I'm sure Ranma
will be just fine.
Uh-huh.
Why don't you rest?
[door closing]
[clattering]
[wind blowing]
ANNOUNCER: Time
for the festival.
Time to begin.
Who will be the
ogre, who will be it?
[panting]
Looks like they've arrived.
Hm, It sound like the
competition's started.
Uh-huh.
It does seem that it has begun.
[footsteps]
Huh?
[grunting]
[disembodied laughter]
MALE SPEAKER: He's it.
He's the new ogre.
He is the chosen one.
Huh.
Where are those creeps
hiding out, anyway?
Huh?
Ha.
Guess he figures I can
handle this on my own.
This will be fun.
Keep your eyes on
the tin can, old man.
Ah!
[shouts]
What?
[grunts]
Th-they just disappeared.
[snarling]
Huh?
A cat?
[meowing]
[whimpering]
(THINKING) This cat
gives me the creeps,
and it's hunting me down.
Get lost, cat.
Go find a rat or something.
[meowing]
[music playing]
Huh?
That isn't even a
even a real cat.
[angry meow]
Ah!
Ahh.
I owe you one, old man.
Ranma, you're not taking
this seriously enough.
[barking]
I was trying.
Are those guys monsters?
What's the deal?
MALE SPEAKER: He's
not up to par, yet.
[chuckles]
MALE SPEAKER: Which
makes it dull for us.
MALE SPEAKER: The ogre
has to be stronger.
[grunts]
I hear you, monsters.
Ugh.
And I'll prove you wrong if
you lose the dirty tricks
and fight me like a man.
[derisive laughter]
[music playing]
[yawn]
[panting]
You've shown yourselves.
You're never going to beat me.
Old man, how about
lending me a hand?
I don't believe you.
You fell asleep on me.
You're going to regret this.
And don't bother coming back!
Huh?
The can!
[panting]
[yells]
All right, then.
Ugh.
I'm going to protect
this thing on my own.
[music playing]
Almost dawn.
Just a little longer.
You can do it, Ranma.
[panting]
[grunting]
(THINKING) It's almost sunrise.
I have to get rid of
these guys somehow.
I know.
This will get them.
[grunting]
I need you to give me those
firecrackers, old man.
My firecrackers?
What would you need
firecrackers for?
Just give it to me.
Ugh, ugh.
[grunting]
Try this one on for size.
[explosion]
Oh.
Those sure came in handy.
Ugh.
[grunt]
And the tin can is safe.
Very impressive
sparring, son-in-law.
Huh?
It-- it's you?
I knew you had it in you.
Congratulations.
I haven't seen that kind of
fighting spirit in decades.
Huh?
Wait, what's going--
don't tell me you guys--
[laughter]
The game goes to you.
It's hard to swallow,
but this time, you win.
You mean you guys were
my opponents tonight?
That's right.
Look, the sun's coming up.
Oh, what a lovely sunrise.
It's as if the sun is
celebrating your victory.
[music playing]
[laughter]
What a lovely night that was.
I can hardly remember the last
time I enjoyed a game so much.
Hm?
What do you mean, game?
This was supposed
to be a competition
that my whole future
was staked on?
Your future?
What you talking about?
Sounds to me like
old Happosai's
been messing around
with your head again.
Hm.
Here you be.
Seeing as you're the
winner, it's only fair
that you accept the prize.
Hm?
Uh.
Hey, this is--
[boing]
Shame on that old
raisin, lusting
after this stuff at his age.
I don't know what we're
going to do with him.
What?
You mean this match was--
Just a game we've been
playing since we were kids,
and still play
once every 10 years
when we get together
to relive old times.
We had an even better
time than usual,
seeing as you came
and played with us.
I figured it might be
special this year, seeing
as how you were in charge
of organizing it, hm?
[laughter]
That freak.
He's going to pay for this.
He's pulled a number on
me, and there's no way
he's going to get away with it.
[growls]
Hm?
Wha?
Ah, what a great sleep.
Oh, is the game
finished already?
Huh?
Oh, this is so sweet.
[laughs]
Oh, lucky day, they
all belong to me.
[growls]
Enjoy them while
you can, you freak.
[shouting]
(SHOUTING) It's the last
time you mess with me.
[theme music]
While walking in
the shopping mall,
Ranma and I come across
the guide from Jusenkyo.
What's he doing in Japan?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," Nihao!
Jusenkyo Guide.
We'll see you there.