[music playing]
[theme music]
RANMA: You'd better
stop right there!
[laughter]
Come and get me!
[groan]
Hey!
You're not getting
away with that, Pop!
That'll teach you for
not staying on your toes!
[laughter]
What's your problem, boy?
Giving up already?
You call yourself my father?
Huh.
I keep you in shape,
put food in your mouth,
and make sure you
don't get too lazy.
Oh, no, you don't!
RANKA: Why are you
always going out
of your way to get on my nerves?
This turning into a
panda and girl thing
is getting to be a part
of every meal around here.
They're at it day
in and day out.
Well, I'm done.
I don't even think they
want to turn back to normal.
What?
No!
You can't stay
like this forever!
[fighting sounds]
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): Ni
hao, Jusenkyo Guide.
Bye.
See you later.
Bring my notes
back tomorrow, OK?
Sure, no prob.
Bye.
See ya!
Gotta study hard for that test.
Yeah, right.
What's wrong with you?
You sick or something?
We gotta talk.
Can you hang with me
for a little while?
What's with all the mystery?
I need you to do
a favor for me.
Why are you asking me?
[sigh]
WOMAN: Here's your order.
All right.
I'm famished.
You needed me for this?
Sorry, Akane.
But when I get a craving,
there's no sense even
trying to control it.
One of the hazards of
being a girl, I guess.
[groan]
[yelling]
Don't you have
any pride as a boy?
Was it something I said?
You just turned into a girl so
you can eat a chocolate sundae!
Aren't you embarrassed?
Uh-uh.
And I'm loving it.
Get real, Ranma.
Don't you even want
your normal body back?
Yeah, sure, Akane.
But the cure's at
Jusenkyo, remember?
Oh, yeah.
Hey!
Since that's out
of the question,
let's make a trip
to the cake shop.
Just feast your eyes
on my radishes, ladies.
You won't find any fresher.
I think I'll take this one.
Hm?
[chatter]
GUIDE: I'm very sorry.
A thousand pardons, lady.
Make way, please.
Very important business.
Oh!
Lucky spot right here.
[groan]
I'll get my tool.
[gasp]
Oh, this heavy!
The higher I lift,
the heavier it become!
Oh, thousand pardons.
This heavy.
Whoa!
[screams]
[gasp]
I don't know who you are,
but thank you, mister.
Better watch where you're
swinging that thing, huh?
Xiexie.
Will be careful.
I'm sure I've seen that
old freak somewhere before.
Hm?
[scream]
You him.
You that boy!
[scream]
Quit pointing, and
tell me who he is!
It's old what's his name.
Is he someone from
around the neighborhood?
[scream]
He's the guy-- he's the
guy-- he's the-- got it!
He's the guide from Jusenkyo.
You're the guide from Jusenkyo?
Not me.
I know you from somewhere?
Huh?
You mean, you forgot me?
Huh.
Why, you!
How could you forget me?
[grunt]
[scream]
Ah, yes!
Now I remember.
Every year so many
boy fall in spring,
I cannot remember
every one of them.
But I remember you--
that clumsy redhead girl
with pigtail and panda.
Hey!
Watch who you're talking to!
Lay off!
So what are you
doing around here?
Finally you ask me.
Well, I come from Jusenkyo all
the way from mainland China.
And now-- now I must go.
Beg pardon.
Not so fast.
Wasn't there an explanation
you had to finish?
This ordinary tour.
Nothing more.
Do you always take a pickax and
a divining rod on your trips?
Digging my hobby.
And my hobby is none
of your business.
Hm?
GENMA: What?
The Jusenkyo guide?
[squeal]
Haven't seen him
for a long time.
He said he was
just here on a trip.
Huh.
You don't say.
So this is going to
be your big chance.
Huh?
I'm not following.
You gotta be forceful.
Forceful?
What are you talking about?
Don't you get it at all?
The guide's going to go
back to China one day.
Hey, yeah.
Maybe he can take you
back there with him.
Huh?
Yes!
The answer's so simple.
I don't know why I didn't
think of it sooner.
[laughter]
That's great news, Ranma.
So where's the guide at?
Huh?
Where is he?
I don't know.
Don't you realize how
important that guide is to us?
You didn't until
just now, either!
Huh?
Cut it out.
Stop fighting, you two.
[squeal]
GUIDE: Look delicious, Granny.
Eat up.
Can't have you go hungry.
Xiexie.
Nice blue hair girl
your granddaughter?
Eat soup.
It healthy.
I still find it
hard to believe you
come all the way from China
considering you rarely
leave Jusenkyo.
[quack]
Pipe down.
So why have you come
all the way to Japan?
I'm glad you asked me that.
What's wrong?
You sick or something?
Oh, sorry.
I just fall asleep.
I come Japan on vacation.
Bring many luggage for my hobby.
Ooh, yes.
This roast pork look good.
(VOICEOVER) Hm.
Something smell fishy about
fatty with thick face.
Let go of me!
Shampoo!
What you doing?
Finally, I hit golden jackpot.
Must be other side of wall.
Good.
[grunting]
Too many wontons at suppertime.
[scream]
Oh, that very kind gesture.
No need for thanks.
Actually, I came
looking for you.
You look for me?
I need a favor.
Favor?
What favor?
Please.
[scream]
Why you bow?
I-- I know you?
You've got to take me
back to Jusenkyo with you.
I'm begging.
Huh?
[scream]
It's no fair!
You no take guide and
go to Jusenkyo alone.
If anyone's going, it'll be me.
Think again, duck boy!
[scream]
Guide belong to Shampoo!
Huh?
Yoka!
[laughter]
[scream]
Very close to happy jackpot.
OK.
Who's making all the
racket out there?
[screams]
Why are they here?
[grunt]
Knock it off!
What do you think you're doing?
Get your hands off.
He's trying to get the guide
to take only him to Jusenkyo.
Jusenkyo?
You found the guide?
Huh?
GUIDE: Found it!
Ooh, I found it!
Double fortune happy spot!
Yah!
Look who's here.
Hey.
If it isn't the Jusenkyo guide.
So that's the guide.
Oh, yeah?
It right here.
This is pond I been looking for.
All right, mister.
Time for an explanation.
[gasp]
Yeah.
And you're going to tell
us the truth this time.
What's the deal with
this filthy little pond?
There's no need
to get rude now.
[gasp]
All right.
You quack like noisy duck
so OK, I might as well
tell you all truth.
Right now this is ordinary pond.
But it going to be very special.
Because soon it will be
connected to Jusenkyo.
[gasp]
So the reason you were
digging around the dirt was--
To examine the
condition of the ground.
Hm, the real reason
I came to Japan
is to search for the other end
of the Jusenkyo spring water
channel.
Huh!
If this pond's
connected to Jusenkyo--
Then we won't have to
go all the way to China.
If we jump in this pond--
[music playing]
I won't have to be a girl!
I won't have to be a duck.
Nor I a pig.
Congratulations.
This is great news.
Yeah, yeah.
It's almost too good to be true.
Ah!
Congratulations, Ranma.
Maybe I'm dreaming.
Shampoo, pinch me or something
so I know if I'm dreaming.
How this?
Now I know it's real.
Thanks, Shampoo.
[groan]
So how are you going to
connect this pond to Jusenkyo?
Who cares?
Just hurry and do it!
Ancient proverb say fool that
rush have head full of mush.
[animal noises]
[banging]
Ooh, very nice sanding.
Ranma and Ryoga, get
nails in straight.
I know what I'm--
[scream]
Would you quit jiggling around?
Don't blame me for
being so clumsy!
Am not!
SHAMPOO: Time for tea, everyone!
You boys working so hard.
Oh, time to refresh
body and mind.
[chatter]
This is the spot.
Ow.
This our shop speciality
steamed pork buns.
Eat well.
Get many energies.
Tell us.
So how exactly is this
going to connect up
with the cursed
spring of Jusenkyo?
Mhm.
Yeah, tell us.
I explain now.
Many water channel
under Jusenkyo.
So Jusenkyo can connect
to many other ponds.
But not just any pond--
match is very important.
This diving rod
detect perfect match.
And the perfect match the rod
found was our little pond here?
Precisely.
But first must finish altar.
Then water channel from Jusenkyo
be connected to your pond,
and sparkling water flow freely.
So when do we do it?
Timing most difficult
part of plan.
It a small island
in Asia Pacific.
Latitude 35, east longitude 139.
Huh.
Mhm.
Oh.
Solution now clear.
I consult lunar fortune almanac,
zodiac, Oracle of Changes,
and other honorable sources.
Also tried palmistry, tea
leaves, interactive divination,
and spin the bok choy.
Now I blessed with answers
and know when to open waters.
[gasp]
Two sacred waters best
joined on next lucky day
of Japanese calendar.
Nabiki, you seen Dad around?
He went to the training
hall with Mr. Saotome.
Huh?
Dad, Mr. Saotome-- uh, for
dinner, do you want a--
Oh, Akane, grab this
end for me, will you?
Sure!
What's this thing for?
Obvious, isn't it?
A decoration to celebrate
Ranma's Chinese curse
being broken.
Don't you think you're
getting carried away?
Hm.
No!
Don't pull that!
[scream]
[gasp]
AKANE: Marriage?
Jeez, Dad!
Is that what you've
been planning all along?
I don't believe this!
Honestly!
GENMA: Akane, can't
you understand
your father's feelings?
He wants his
daughters to be happy.
Why is it so hard
for you to see that?
Huh?
Uh.
I realize that I'm asking
a lot of you, Akane.
But the day that
you and Ranma wed
is a new start for the
Anything Goes School.
I've even lost track of how many
years I've waited for this day
to arrive.
But I suppose that it
means nothing to you.
[gasp]
[crying]
Dad!
Akane.
Which isn't to say that I'm
going to go through with it.
Why not?
Told you she didn't understand.
AKANE: Finally, we can
have normal bodies again.
Yeah, I can hardly wait.
It's been a heck of a ride.
[groan]
We've had our share
of humiliation.
Hey, Ranma, you got
any special plans
for after you turn
back to normal?
Yeah, maybe.
Like taking a cold shower
without having to worry.
You call that a plan?
What about you?
You got something planned?
Who, me?
Kinda.
(VOICEOVER) If I don't
have to be a pig anymore,
I'll devote my entire
life to Akane--
a love life lined
with fragrant roses.
What are you
blushing for suddenly?
Ah, nothing!
Oh, I get it.
Too bad your days as
a pig are numbered,
because that's the only time
you can ever cuddle with Akane.
[gasp]
(VOICEOVER) He's right.
There's a lot to be gained.
But not cuddling with her
is a huge price to pay!
You got your whole
life to worry.
Soon Ranma no become
girl, even with cold water.
Maybe after the
guide changes it
into a spring of drowned
men, he could change it
girl, then maybe you
wouldn't be turning into a cat.
That good idea, Granny.
Then son-in-law wouldn't
be afraid of you anymore,
and I'd be more than happy to
make you your bridal dress.
[gasp]
Shampoo so happy.
Once this curse is broken
and I've returned to normal,
Shampoo will be mine!
[music playing]
Then I'll be happy.
Mousse!
What you doing
outside Shampoo door?
You come inside and help.
[quack]
AKANE: So this is the night.
RANMA: Yeah, the night I
become an ordinary guy again.
I can hardly wait!
AKANE: Hey, Ranma.
Yeah?
How would you describe
what this day means to you?
Well, like I said, it's the
day that I turn back to normal.
That's it?
Mhm.
Don't you have
anything else to say?
Like maybe you'll do your
best for the Anything
Goes School, for example?
Nope.
You're unbelievable!
You still have no idea
how this change is going
to affect your life at all!
Oh, you're the worst!
What's her problem?
Wait!
You forgot your bag!
Hm.
I'm so nervous,
my heart's racing.
Yeah, mine, too.
Looks like this is
the moment of truth.
Water, water everywhere.
And all was cursed and black.
Drowned ones cast bad spell,
and out come pig, girl, duck,
panda.
Swirl, swirl, slithery pond,
and join with magic spring.
Swirl, swirl, dirty pond.
And rid the cursed sting!
Hear my prayer.
I beg you, please.
Now turn these curses back!
Huh?
[scream]
[cheers]
Make way!
I'm coming through!
[laughter]
[groan]
Wait for me!
[gasp]
That worked well.
[groan]
[quacking]
[gasp]
[scream]
Why chant not work?
Someone broke the
rope to sacred circle
before pond connect to Jusenkyo!
[scream]
That why it no work!
[gasp]
What a dirty trick!
How could you have done
a thing like this to me?
What?
Ryoga, you're the one who
cut it when you tripped!
Quiet!
Want a piece of me or what?
Can't you try again and
give it another shot?
It's very important!
Shampoo begging you.
All right.
Thousand year from now.
[gasp]
Next time identical
condition as today come
is 1,000 year from now.
Must wait til then.
[gasp]
[scream]
[grunt]
Too bad this no work for you.
But I must be going
back to China now.
You come visit me at Jusenkyo.
[humming]
[sigh]
Oh, no!
I forgot to ask him to
take me along with him!
[scream]
Come back!
[groan]
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER): It all started
from those mysterious old parts
Kasumi bought at the bazaar.
[gasp]
How can this be happening?
There's six Happosais!
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
Pick-a-Peck o' Happosai.
We'll see you there.