[music playing]
-(IN UNISON) Come on.
[humming]
-Hmm?
Boy, that stinky little goat.
I'll show him.
-Huh?
Watch this.
[groaning]
-Take that, you pervert.
And this.
And some of this.
-No, please, the stinky feet.
No.
That hurts.
Get off of me.
-He had it coming.
-Ranma Gets Weak.
-Look what you've done.
-What's happened to you?
-Hey, old man, you're home.
We were just starting
to worry about you.
-Why, you.
It's all your fault.
-Sautome, quick, do something.
The master's getting angry.
-Huh?
-Sautome.
-You've really made
me mad this time.
Now you're going to pay.
Are you listening to me?
Let's see you try
to ignore this.
-And what's this supposed to be?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hmm?
That's hot.
Hot, hot, hot, aww.
Aww.
-Told ya.
-Mess with the master at
one's own peril, I always say.
-So what did I ever
do to him, huh?
-You want I should make a list?
-OK, we're off.
-Oh, man.
It still hurts.
-Oh stop complaining will you?
You got off lucky if you ask me.
-That's true.
The freak don't usually
let you off so easy.
-Ranma Sautome, today's
the day you die.
-What that?
-Is that Kuno?
-Prepare to receive
my mighty blow, you.
-Good morning to you, too.
Geez, talk about your--
-If that was supposed to be
a kick, I didn't feel it.
-Why don't I believe you?
-Enough play already.
Put some back into it.
-You asked for it, pal.
That hurt.
-Ranma, hang in there.
-I--I did it.
I beat Ranma Sautome.
So in other words, date
with me, Akane Tendo.
-Thanks, but no thanks.
Ranma, what's wrong with you?
How could Kuno just beat you?
-Oh, man, that hurt.
Something's wrong all right.
The day Kuno beats
me is the day I--
it's the day that
I stop being a man.
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god, what have I done?
-What have you done is right.
-Hey, you OK?
-Of course he's not, stupid.
-You say something
mister poo-poo head?
-At least he's OK.
-Sure.
That's the-- that's the
important thing, right?
-He what?
Weak in what way?
-So, do you know what's
wrong with him yet?
-Let's see.
The bones and muscles
are fine, but hmm.
What's this burn mark?
Why, I haven't seen one of
these in over 100 years.
[speaking in a foreign language]
Here it is.
I'm sure it's in here somewhere.
Aha, what'd I tell you?
According to this
ancient text, whosoever
be burned by this moxibustion,
let him, be he howsoever strong
or howsoever great in his art
become weak as a mere babe.
-That's it.
Why, that little.
-There is a way you can cure
him, though, isn't there?
-Akane, I'm not
sure how to say it.
-Say what?
Come on.
Tell me.
-Tragically, at least for
now, this strength-sapping
moxibustion has no cure.
-But that would
mean that Ranma--
-Is weak for the
rest of my life.
-Ranma!
Ranma?
Doctor, please.
I just know you can find some
way to help him, can't you?
Doctor Tofu?
-OK then.
I can't promise anything,
but let me see what I can do.
-Oh Doctor Tofu,
you're the best.
-Good heavens, what is this?
-A letter?
-As if I did not know.
-Oh, happy happy day.
-Extra, extra,
read all about it.
Extra.
-Freak!
-What's this?
Did I just feel a feather?
-Hey, no fair.
I'll teach you to
play dirty tricks.
-You ain't seen nothing yet.
My real revenge
is just starting.
-Real revenge?
-That stupid Ranma, now
where'd he go and run off to?
What the-- Pea-chan.
What are you doing here?
Huh?
A letter?
Ranma is what?
-The best part of my revenge
is I don't have to do a thing.
Your enemies will do it for me.
-That's a good theory,
but how's about I beat you
into curing me instead?
-It's ready to go.
It's ready to go.
-Honestly, must you
encourage him like that?
Really?
-Sautome?
Sautome?
Is Ranma Sautome absent today?
-He's uh, here.
But that is--
-Yes?
-I mean, he's not in his seat,
but he's definitely here.
-Thank you for clearing
that up, Ms. Tendo,
I know I feel enlightened.
-(MUFFLED) Come on!
Please!
Someone get me out of here.
Help.
Please, come on!
I'm gonna--
-I'm sorry, but until
we figure out a cure,
you've got to lay
low for a while.
-Stupid Akane.
[struggling]
-That was risky, but if she
thinks I'm just going to go
into hiding--
-Hello!
Why you need such big hair?
-Oh, not you again.
-Who's that supposed to hurt?
Let Nikauno give you a
quick buzz cut, yeah?
Do it again, boy.
I can't feel a thing.
-So you really are weak, just
like the letter said, huh?
-Let me go.
Let me go.
-Die!
-Why you--
-For shame, Sautome.
We both know why I won.
And this alleged weakness
has naught to do with it.
-I'll show you who's weak.
-Yield, cretin.
-I'm done for.
-Die, you.
Cut that hair!
-Punish.
Punish.
-Huh?
-Idiots.
Riyoga?
I guess you must have come
to beat me up, too, huh?
-Hey, don't get me wrong, Ranma.
I'm only here because it's
not right to bully the weak,
you know.
-Huh?
I'll show you who's
weak, you jerk.
-That felt like a baby's kick.
You know, there's
a Japanese word
for those punches of
yours, and that work
is [speaking in japanese].
-He said it.
The W word.
Weak.
-Call me a romantic,
but I just can't
bear to see you like this.
-I thought you weren't
here to hit me.
-Do you really think
you can cure him?
-Sure.
I've done some
research and it seems
there's a certain chart
which reveals the pressure
points for the moxibustion cure.
-Oh Doctor Tofu, you
really are the best.
-So you see, once we find that
chart, all we'll have to do
is apply pressure to
the proper points.
-I can't wait to tell
him the good news.
-OK.
And now to open
the rest of-- Huh?
What in the-- huh?
Ranma, honey, you
just hang in there.
OK?
-Ranma?
[screaming]
-You'll never get your
old strength back.
Never.
They'll be lining up all
over town to beat you.
-Ranma Sautome, victory is mine.
-You lose, Ranma.
You lose.
-If you have to be like this,
I'd rather see you dead.
-Enough.
This coal's hot.
I'm burning up.
-Oh, finally awake, are you?
-Hot!
Okio, what happened?
-You were in the trash can.
-I what?
-You know, I've
been hearing rumors.
Guess this means they're true.
-I can explain.
-I understand perfectly.
You don't need to explain.
-I don't?
I mean, have you got some
kind of plan or what?
-I got something
better than that.
-You beat me fair
and square, youngin'.
-You're weaker
than a possum, Pa.
-Y'all go easy on your
poor, weak daddy now.
You just wait til you hear
when else I've got to say.
-Haven't you said enough, Okio?
-You might as well
face it, you know.
Without that strength
of yours, you're
in no shape to take
over the Tendo Dojo.
And without that, you're in no
shape to marry Akane, are you?
-The only thing I
care about right
now is getting my strength back.
I don't care about Dojos.
And I especially don't care
about that stupid Akane.
-That's it, then.
Guess you won't be needing
my stupid cure, then, either.
-I won't?
[yelling] You know it was
only a joke, right, Akane?
Right?
Here, let me do your shoulders.
You look fantastic today.
-Don't bother.
Grow a spine, will ya?
[crash]
-Shampu, Shampu, where are you?
-What's all the racket?
-I did it, Shampu.
I finally beat Ranma.
That means we can
finally be married.
You're glad, aren't you?
Aren't you?
-It's just all so sudden.
-Who said that?
You're not Shampu.
-Gee, you don't say.
Hmm?
Ranma is weak.
So the rumors are
true after all.
-Strength-sapping moxibustion,
here now in Japan?
-We are sorry to
bother you, but we've
heard that the pressure point
chart might be in this temple.
So we thought--
-So let us take a look at it.
OK?
We just need to borrow it.
-I think he's fainted.
-Maybe he's just
meditating or something.
-Yo, snap out of it, would you?
Where's the chart?
Hmm.
Yo?
-I'd like to help,
but that chart
ain't around here no more.
-What?
-We used to have it,
but it was stolen.
Nigh on a hundred years ago.
-That's it then.
I might as well give up.
Without any clues
as to where it--
-Did I say we didn't
have no clues?
Looky here.
-Huh?
This is--
-That there is the likeness
of the rascal who stole it.
I reckon if you find him,
you'll find the chart too,
sure as day.
-That's Grandfather
Haposai, isn't it?
-Sure is.
If I can just get that
chart from the old freak,
I can go back to being
strong like before.
-Why, you're practically good
as cured already, aren't ya?
-We'll see.
-Grandfather, if you have
any trash for me to burn,
would you please
bring it out to me?
-Got to keep this.
Got to keep this.
Keep this, too.
What's this piece of junk?
Can't be that important.
Kasume.
-Not yet.
Not yet.
There it is.
The chart with all the
mark se-- whatever points.
-So that's what it is?
I'd almost forgotten.
Better hang onto it.
-Why you little freak.
Hand it over.
-A little slow,
ain't you, Ranma.
What's the matter?
Can't you catch me?
-Fine.
We can do it either way, freak.
Easy or hard, it's your choice.
-Kasume, Kane, thank goodness.
Look.
-Oh, yeah.
Getting serious, eh, punk?
Don't expect me to
back down either.
-But Ranma's far too weak.
He can't possibly.
-Akane, honey, he is.
-No problem.
[yelling]
-Ranma!
-Ain't beat yet.
How's about these apples?
-Hubba hubba.
-Ha, I tricked ya.
-What's the matter, Ranma?
-I'll clobber you in a minute.
OK?
Hang on.
-No thanks.
Why go for a clobber
when I can go for these?
-Quit it.
-Come on, Ranma,
give up already.
You're too weak.
-Ranma!
-Curse you.
-How pathetic.
Is tearing your shirt open the
only thing you could think of?
-What?
Give it up, why don't you?
You're in my power
now, and you know it.
-That's enough.
Don't you know when to quit?
-Even Ranma deserves to be
treated like a human being.
-All right.
Hand over that chart.
-I don't wanna.
Ranma, you can stay a weakling
for the rest of your miserable
life for all I care.
[laughing]
-Oh, come on.
You know how he is.
I'm sure he'll come around.
Ranma?
Ranma, you OK?
-Ranma.
-Hey, what's the
matter with you?
-Stop trying to cheer me up.
-But-- but I--
-Now what?
Is he mad at me now?
And here I was trying
to help him, too.
Fine then.
If he wants to be
that way, then hmm.
-Father, they're gone.
Both Ranma and Mr.
Sautome have left.
-Hmm?
-They must have packed last
night while we were sleeping,
and then--
-But why?
-Perhaps he felt
that being weak,
he could not take over the Dojo.
-Oh, the humanity.
-I don't believe it.
Ranma's no coward.
He would never run
from a real fight.
You believe that,
Dad, don't you?
Don't you agree?
-Of course.
He's a lot of things, but
Ranma's never been afraid.
-So what if he left
without saying goodbye?
Who needs a jerk like him?
I'm better off
without him anyway.
-Akane.
-Ranma?
Oh, Ranma, you idiot.
Where are you?
[music playing]
-Oh, Ranma, this
is no time for you
to be dancing around like that.
What?
You mean it's all
part of his training?
The next time on Ranma,
Eureka, the desperate move
of desperation.
We'll see you there.