[music playing]
WOMAN: Ah!
It's the underwear thief!
What a haul!
Ha, ha, I'm set for life.
Ha, ha!
That's him!
He stole our underwear!
Here you go.
[yelling, crashing]
How do you like getting a
taste of your own medicine,
you dirty old freak.
I'm disappointed in you, Ranma.
Is this any way to
respect your elders?
It's payback time with
the secret medicine
of the Shujyugan.
The master gets the red
tablet for good luck
while the disciple gets
the white one for bad luck.
And when the disciple wakes
up, he won't know what hit him.
In just a minute, it
should take effect.
[groaning]
I'm stuck.
I'm stuck to him.
Ow!
[snoring]
I can't breathe.
I can't--
AKANE (VOICEOVER): "Master
and Student-- Forever!?"
[humming, brushing]
What the?
Hey, what are you doing here?
Isn't it enough
that you creep out
half the girls in this town?
Hey, that's cold!
(MUFFLED) If we're going
to be stuck together,
I'd rather you be a girl.
[screaming]
RANMA: I've had it with you!
ALL: Shujyugan?
Excuse me, but what
might that be, Master?
Do I have to explain
everything to you?
Let's see here.
"Shujyugan-- a medicine that a
master administers in pill form
to his disciple.
And no matter where the master
will go, his pupil will follow.
Whether it's out for a simple
walk or even when he eats."
Yeah.
But the part I
can't figure out is
why do I have to be
stuck to Ranma like this?
But it clearly says the
Shujyugan pill is magnetically
charged, and the master and
pupil cannot be separated.
How could you miss that, Master?
Well, someone obviously
didn't read the instructions.
HAPPOSAI: I'll figure
this out somehow.
But for now, maybe
something to eat.
Ranma, would you
stop teasing him?
What do you think you're
doing, you crazy old freak!
Get off of me!
Ah!
Until we figure out a way
to get you two separated,
why don't you try to
be nice to each other?
Ranma!
Huh?
Hey, Ukyo.
You must forgive me for
asking, but what is that thing?
Believe it or not, this
thing is actually stuck to me.
Huh?
Are you serious?
Just don't let go of the fence.
[groaning]
Ah!
My most expensive
spatula is ruined.
Gee, I'm sorry, Ukyo.
No, Ranma.
I'm sorry that I
couldn't help you.
[sigh]
At least now we know
using physical force won't
do the trick.
There's no way in the world
that I'm going into school
and letting everyone see
this lump stuck to me.
I never thought about that.
Hey, you don't have to
worry about a thing.
Just leave it all
up to me, Ranma.
Isn't he adorable?
So, what do you think, Ranma?
I think you've lost it.
Excuse me?
Yeah, yeah.
He's adorable.
OK.
Let's get going or
else we'll be late.
Ha, ha!
[growling]
Get out of my face!
All right.
I can move, but--
[screaming]
RANMA: You are driving
me completely nuts!
HAPPOSAI: Hang on and
enjoy the ride, kiddo!
Let go!
[yelling, crashing]
I should have you surgically
removed without anesthetic.
You're in so much trouble!
I've had it with you!
And I've had it with you!
AKANE: What?
Are you absolutely
sure about that, Dad?
We don't have
any time to waste.
We have to get those
two separated at once.
We'll meet you there, Akane.
Oh, my gosh!
Would you quit shoving me.
Exactly what I wish you'd do!
AKANE: Ranma!
Uh-oh.
Stop it, Ranma!
Akane!
Why, you sleaze!
How dare you even
try anything, Ranma!
Hey!
It's not me doing anything.
Never mind that.
If we don't separate you
two, you'll be stuck forever!
Seriously?
Say it ain't so.
[yelling, crashing]
SOUN: Ranma!
Akane!
Good news!
I've discovered a way we
can get those two detached
from each other.
All right!
Well hurry up!
HAPPOSAI: Come on, already.
Tell us, tell us,
tell us please.
Right.
There's only one way, and I
believe it's quite simple.
I'm waiting.
All that needs to happen is for
the master-student relationship
to end.
So if Ranma beats the master
in battle, they can separate.
It's the only way.
Hm.
Fair enough.
If you say that is our only
hope, then so it shall be.
Ranma, do your worst.
Oh, I'm going to enjoy this.
Let's get started.
Get ready!
[yelling]
RANMA: Get ready!
Hm?
What?
So what'd you have to go
and move for, you nimrod?
Hey, you can beat me up,
but I don't want to get hurt.
Why, you little fake!
How are we supposed
to come apart then?
HAPPOSAI: Any way you
want but without pain!
RANMA: Why don't you be a
man for once in your life,
or is that too much to ask?
HAPPOSAI: Because
I don't want to.
Unhand Ranma, Master!
Why don't you two grow up?
[crashing, muttering]
Would you please hold still.
HAPPOSAI: I don't think so.
How are we supposed to help
you if you won't help yourself!
Maybe we should give
this whole thing up.
I mean, I could be
stuck to someone worse.
Besides, I'm so old, I
don't have much time left.
But I don't think
that works for Ranma.
All right, I give up.
We'll stay stuck together.
What are you saying?
Are you nuts?
[muttering]
From now on, we'll live
together like conjoined twins.
Do you mean that, Ranma?
You must be joking.
[ringing]
Isn't this peaceful, Master?
Yeah, sure.
Whatever.
What does that Ranma
think he's doing anyway?
Maybe I'm wrong, but am I
sensing a hint of jealousy
here?
First of all, I'm
not jealous, OK?
I'm just trying to figure out
Ranma's little plan, that's
all.
You don't think they'll stay
like that forever, do you?
[bridal chorus playing]
Ranma, darling.
Yes, my love?
[laughs]
This just can't be.
It might be OK now,
but I could never
live with the two of them.
RANMA: Ukyo, you want
me to wash your back?
UKYO (VOICEOVER): How romantic.
I'd love it.
And I'll do your front.
[exclaiming]
Akane, we don't have
any time to lose!
We've got to get
those two apart!
Yeah, sure.
RANMA: So, Master, are
you enjoying the massage?
Oh, I've gotta tell you, Ranma.
You've got magic fingers.
Oh, please.
You are too kind.
I'm just honored to
be around you so I can
absorb your great knowledge.
You know, I think I
underestimated you, my son.
I don't get it.
How come Ranma's being
so nice to the old loon?
I think he's just biding
his time until he can
catch that pervert off guard.
Do you think so?
Huh?
Oh, man, what am I doing?
Hey, quit messing with my head.
That really hurt me.
Well, if you think that
hurt, then just keep it up,
you freaky old nut case.
You're asking for
trouble, and trust me,
you don't want to
get me too angry.
Because if you push me too far,
I'll-- have to say I'm sorry,
and hope that someday
you'll forgive me for being
so unbearable.
Now is there something
I can get for you,
like a nice cup of tea?
Oh, Ranma, you sure
have a way to make
an old man feel warm and fuzzy.
I think there's something
wrong with Ranma.
You're right.
I know he's not that
good of an actor.
He could never pull it off.
Ranma, the answer to
question four is "carbon."
Oh, Master, I bet I'd be a
complete failure without you
around.
[laughing]
Yeah, you got
that right, kiddo.
[snoring]
AKANE (WHISPERING): Ranma!
Ranma!
Huh?
(WHISPERING) Do it now!
Do what now?
Now is your chance to get
rid of that old weirdo.
Oh, really, Akane?
I would never do anything
to harm my master.
Prepare to die, you leech!
I've had it with you.
Ugh!
Saotome, not in my class.
Huh?
Did-- Did I miss anything?
[giggling]
[growling]
So what are we
going to do now, Dad?
I don't know, Akane.
The problem seems to
be Ranma succumbing
to the effects of
the Shujyugan pill
that the master has given him.
You mean he's--
he's been drugged?
Ranma is changing into
exactly what the master wants
him to become, and there's only
one way I know how to stop it.
If we don't get them
separated, there
won't be any hope left for him.
The power of the
Shujyugan is to be feared.
Oh, I only hope we're
not too late to save him.
RANMA: This is so sweet.
HAPPOSAI: Well done, Ranma.
[screaming]
RANMA: I love stealing
women's underwear!
HAPPOSAI: That a boy, Ranma!
Ugh, this is bad.
Set!
Spike!
Ow!
That really hurt.
You didn't have
to hit it so hard.
If I were your age,
that is the kind of girl
I'd fall for, Ranma.
I think I know what
you mean, Master.
OK, good.
We practiced enough for one day.
OK, sweet.
Excuse me, Ranma.
What?
I'd like to ask you something?
Sure.
Anything you want, Master.
(FEMALE VOICE) I never would
have thought of that, Master.
Now we can get into
the girl's locker room
without freaking everybody out.
You are quickly becoming
my star pupil, Ranma.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, Ukyo.
I can't bear to see
you like this, Ranma.
And I'm going to do
something about it.
Ah!
My favorite spatula
is bent again
and I just had it fixed too.
I give up.
There you are.
Huh?
Akane?
Ranma, you've got to wake up.
Just look at yourself.
I know you don't realize it, but
he's got you under his spell.
You've got to
listen to me, Ranma.
Ah, come on.
I think you're the one
who's got to wake up.
I feel fine.
Well, OK, but you're
sure acting strange.
Never mind.
I'll just go.
If you ask me, she's losing it.
Come on, we can't leave all
those young girl's waiting now,
can we?
Oh, yeah.
I almost forgot.
It's just me.
Huh?
(IMITATING FEMALE) I'm so
glad you could make it, Ranma.
(IMITATING FEMALE) Why don't
you come on in and introduce us
to your little friend.
What in the world's
going on here?
Ah.
Ranma, now's your chance!
Hurry up and make your move.
Oh, yeah.
They're right.
That's what you get
for being a freak.
Hey, Dad.
How'd it go--
[barfing]
(IMITATING FEMALE)
Did you just see that?
I can't believe my eyes.
(IMITATING FEMALE) Honestly,
brute force always gets me
in a tizzy.
[barfing]
BOTH: How could we do this?
So, uh, what's the deal?
They were trying to
help you, that's all.
Well, I guess I
owe you one, Akane.
No, I think you owe everyone.
She is right, you know.
Yeah, you owe us big time.
[barfing]
RANMA: Gross!
Now I know how much
trouble you can get
into having a useless master.
How do you know the
mater was useless.
Hey, don't even go there, girl.
At least you're helping him.
Told you I was a nice guy.
[giggling]
RANMA: Time for
dinner, you old freak.
You have to eat something
to get back your strength.
Hey, Akane.
I've got an idea.
Why don't you bring
his dinner in here,
and I'll feed the
pervert myself?
Here you go.
OK, old man.
Let's see what's on the menu.
How about we start with
Akane's homemade soup.
Isn't this like the old days?
Just you and me together?
This is gonna be so much fun.
You know, I'm not
very hungry, I--
How is it?
RANMA: Well?
Wait a sec, don't
tell me you're saying
you don't like Akane's cooking?
No, I'm not saying that at all.
I'm just not hungry, that's all.
I just--
RANMA: Keep eating.
Please, how about a
little compassion here?
I love her cooking!
RANMA: Good boy.
Have another.
Nice work.
Almost done.
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
What in the world
was the principal thinking when
he put Kuno, of all people,
in charge of the school.
Next time on "Ranma
1/2"-- "Tatewaki Kuno,
Substitute Principal."
We'll see you there!