[music playing]
ANNOUNCER: "Here
Comes Ranma's Mom."
CLOWN: Hurry!
Hurry!
Step right up!
The greatest show in
Furinkan is about to begin--
with thrill rides for the
brave, side shows the curious,
and free balloons for the kids.
Hurry!
Step right up!
Here you go, kid.
Yellow OK?
What?
-En garde!
-Oh yeah?
Take this.
[grunting]
-Say uncle!
Say uncle!
Uncle!
You've been a bad boy, Ranma.
Haven't you realized yet
that making me punish you
is like punishing my so-- Oh!
-No can do, Pops!
-Hey, haven't you ever
heard of recycling?
-Sure I have, old man.
Metal and glass separate, right?
Be seeing you.
-No so fast, boy.
-Do you think you're
poor old dad has finally
lived to see the day when his
one and only son has finally
become a man?
-Yeah, yeah.
Can we go home and
get some food now?
-Gotcha.
-I knew it!
I just knew you were
going to try that.
-Look, a 100 yen piece.
-Look, right in front
of you, a 500 yen piece.
-It must have fallen out of my--
-Oh, like you really
have that much.
-Think you can take me, huh?
-You know it old man.
-Why you gotta be
so disrespectful?
-Hey, you're the
one who started it.
-Oh.
[grunting]
-Uh, Ranma, would you
mind moving from my seat?
-Haven't you two been
fighting long enough?
-Why don't ask him?
-As soon as he
apologizes, I'll--
-I what?!
-I'm waiting.
WOMAN (OUTSIDE): Anyone home?
KASUMI: Coming.
[growling]
-Mr. Saotome, you
have a visitor.
-Who, me?
-Knowing you, it's
a bill collector.
-That would not surprise me.
KASUMI: Actually, it's an
attractive older woman.
-Say it ain't so.
There's got to be
some kind of mistake.
Right, Kasumi?
My old friend,
Saotome, the recipient
of an attractive female visitor?
Has the world gone mad?
-Gee, Daddy.
What's the matter?
Are you jealous?
-Well, um, [clears throat],
um, you know.
HAPPOSAI: What's with all
the bowing and scraping?
Why don't you show
some guts for a change?
Well, are you a man
or are you a mouse?
Personally, mice have
their advantages.
-Cut it out, will you?
-You won't let me
speak with him then?
-Huh?
-I'm sorry, but I'm not
sure it's such a good idea.
-But I-- Ranma, dear,
I need to talk to you.
-Hey, why'd she
just call you dear?
-Jeez, what are
you asking me for?
-P-- please!
Wait!
Ranma's in the dark about this.
It'll be better if I can
break it to him in my own way.
-I'll only take a minute.
Please, you've got to--
-I'll let you talk to him.
OK?
Just let me soften
him up a bit first.
-Dear!
GENMA: Oh, for crying out loud.
Ranma, I gotta go
out for a while.
I'll explain when I get back.
WOMAN: Ranma, dear!
-So what was that all about?
Whatever it was, he
is up to no good.
HAPPOSAI: His past has
caught up with him.
Of course, Genma was but
a mere youth at the time.
As I've told you many
another time, the three of us
walked the earth in order
to polish our skill.
As it so happened,
Genma fell in love.
The name of the young maiden was
Sakura, as in cherry blossom.
Nature took it's
course, and in due time
the beautiful
Sakura was delivered
of a healthy baby
boy whose name was--
-Wait, you don't have to say.
It was Ranma, wasn't it?
-Huh?
-Fate, however, had
not finished with it.
The girl's parents
opposed match and decided
that they should be separated.
Genma and the baby
went back on the road
while Sakura stayed
behind, forever by herself.
Their union was
reckless and impulsive.
However, I cannot find it
in my heart to blame them.
-Odd how I've never
heard that story before.
-Yeah, you know, I'm
surprised that Pop never
said nothing about it.
-Oh Ranma, it's it obvious?
I'm sure he just wanted
to spare you the misery.
-Well, jeez.
I mean, if he was going to go
to all the trouble of being
a single father, at least he
got to sow the wild oats first,
right?
Don't you agree Akane?
-Be quiet.
-In other words, she has come
to reclaim her long lost son.
-No wonder she was so
desperate to see Ranma again.
-How could she remarry
after something like that?
Imagine being alone
all these years.
-We've got to do
something to help her.
-I agree.
Somehow we've got to bring those
three together as a family.
-You can count on me.
-On me too, son.
-On my too.
-Why, you must be the
luckiest boy on Earth.
-Hip hip hooray for me.
-Oh, you cynic, you.
-Stop wasting time
and go straight
to your mother's bosom.
RANMA: Akane, wait up!
Hey, I said wait up.
-Hey, Akane.
There's a new
movie, just opened.
Do you want to go see it?
-Mm.
-Huh?
-Jeez, Akane.
If that's how you're going to
be, next time I won't bother.
-I know it's hard
on you right now,
but don't you think
it might be smart
for you to lie low for a while?
-Why are you making such
a big deal out of this?
TATEWAKI: I heard
the whole thing.
If you think to escape the
rightful wrath of my most
puissant self with your feeble
plots and schemes, think again.
-I'm not trying to--
-I don't care what
trouble you're in.
You're not leaving until
we settle the score.
You got that?
-Ryoga.
MOUSSE: Yeah, who gave you
permission to go sneaking off?
-Listen up.
I don't know what's gotten
into you all of a sudden,
but if you want
to fight, come on.
KODACHI: Ranma, honey!
-Ranma, honey, is it true?
Are you really going away
to live with your mother?
-Some day, she be
Shampoo mother too.
Why you no introduce
so far, Ranma?
-I'm not in the mood for--
-You know I'd follow you
anywhere, don't you darling?
-Come on.
Let him go.
He's turning blue.
-Silence, you insolent wench.
What knowest you of a
woman's finer feelings?
-Plenty, you snob.
-After all, he was
my fiance first.
-What you talking?
He belong Shampoo
as much as you.
-I can't breathe.
Akane, help me.
I can't breathe.
-But Ranma, why do you
need me when you've got
those three cute fiances.
TATEWAKI (VOICEOVER):
Now wait a second.
If he's going to
be leaving anyway,
why don't we let him go?
Once the current Saotome
is out of the picture,
Akane Tendo will become
mine-- physically, mentally,
inevitably.
-He must be set free!
-He must be kept here!
-Give him liberty!
-Or give death.
It don't matter because--
-It works either way.
All for one, and one for all.
-We guys gotta stick together.
-Will you please
quiet before I hit you
upside the head with my spatula?
-Let's solve this
democratically.
All those in favor of
Ranma taking a hike,
raise your hands.
Sorry girls, the majority rules.
-Oh, give us a break.
-What a bunch of losers.
How are you gonna beat
me when you can't even
beat a bunch of girls?
-Ranma, darling?
-Ranma, honey!
-Ranma!
HAPPOSAI: Stop right there.
-Grandfather Happosai?
-Listen here, girls.
Helping to choose a
future daughter-in-law
is the sacred duty of
all Japanese mothers.
Don't tell me you're trying
to take that privilege away
from her.
-Do you really think
she'd choose one of us?
-I'd say that's
entirely up to you
and how willing you are to be
an obedient daughter-in-law.
-I will be the most dutiful
daughter who ever lived.
-I'll set a world
record for humility.
-Shampoo make Ranma proud.
HAPPOSAI: Listen
carefully, girls.
In order to better your chances,
the role of Ranma's mother
will be played by yours truly.
To work!
Oh my, my.
Would you look at that?
Girls these days, I tell you.
Nothing wrong with them a
good switching wouldn't cure.
[panting]
Chop chop, girls.
The floor isn't going
to clean itself.
[panting]
Over here.
You missed a spot.
What about over here?
And what are you
doing here, my child?
-What do you think?
-Well, bless your heart, dear.
And the very best
of luck to you.
Why aren't you working?
-I'm done.
-What, already?
You can't have done
a very thorough job.
Oh yes, well what
about this, then?
What's this I see?
You're not disrespecting
me, are you?
I'd simply hate to pull
you from the competition.
-What a lucky girl am I to
have a mother-in-law who
cares for me so.
-That's it, girls.
Put some back into it.
If there's one thing
mothers-in-law hate,
it's sloppy housekeeping.
Why, when I was a
girl, we didn't even
have feather dusters.
We had to go out into the forest
and fetch ourselves pine bows.
True, the sap stuck
to everything.
But it sure did smell nice.
[laughing]
RANMA: Aw, man.
I thought they'd never go home.
What was the old
freak thinking anyway?
AKANE: You've got more
important things to worry about.
-Oh yeah?
Like what?
-Like maybe the fact that your
mother seems to want you back.
And it's only natural she'd
want you to go live with her.
Will you quit that?
She's not going to
go away, you know?
-Yeah, yeah.
I know.
-Then why won't you agree to
meet with her and talk over
your--
-Is that what you want?
If it is, I'm sure that I--
th-- th-- that we can-- is
that what you want
me to do, Akane?
Leave?
-It's just that your
mother hasn't seen you--
-Fine then.
I read you loud and clear.
I should've known an
uncute girl like you--
-Oh, here we go again.
Whenever you get
upset about something,
I end up being called uncute.
It's none of my business
what you do anyway,
so you may as well live
with whoever you want.
-Fine then.
Maybe I will.
[howling]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I'll never
fall asleep at this rate.
[grunting]
AKANE: Ranma.
-It's hard on him too, you know.
He tries hard to
hide it, but I'm
sure it must be getting to him.
-Hey, and where the heck
have you been all this time?
-If I had to guess, I'd
say on a quest seeking
that which he most desires.
-Is it me, or is he
putting on weight?
-One might think he's
binging in secret, hmm?
-Thanks for the food.
-Huh?
-[sigh]
-Hey, where are you going?
Hm?
Oh!
-Mr. Saotome seems sad.
-Tell me, girls,
how would you feel
about asking Ranma's mother
to come live with us?
-Why, daddy, you are a genius.
That way he and Akane
needn't be separated.
Right, Akane?
-Well, I'd say that's not
really my decision to make.
Right, Dad?
-The next and then
is a man-to-man talk.
-This I've gotta hear.
-I can't take it anymore.
Pop, it's time that you and I--
-Think before you speak, son.
-But why can't I?
-It's not that I don't know
these past few days have
been rough on you, son.
But they've been pretty
hard on your dad too.
You say you can't take it
anymore, but what about him?
Have you bothered to think
what it's been like for him,
knowing that your mother was
back but afraid to tell you.
Please, son, do the right
thing and let me handle this.
Fine weather we're
having, hey, Saotome?
Look the truth is, it's about
this woman from the other day.
Most you really go
off with her or--
-[snore]
-It's like that.
You intend to help out
with the family business?
Then I guess our
job is to find a way
to accept your
decision no matter
how much we don't like it.
-Mr. Tendo, I'm sorry, but
I'm not just going to sit here
and listen to all of this--
-[snoring]
-That's the old man for you.
-[groaning] Saotome!
Why is it that every time
I put myself out for you,
you end up making
me wish I hadn't?
-Hm?
What the heck kind of bamboo
leaf is this supposed to be?
-I'd say it must be imported
all the way from China.
-Don't want to be late
for a very important date.
-What date is that?
-I've got some talking
of my own to do.
-Dad told me the whole thing.
Guess you'll be
moving out soon, huh?
-The old man will anyway.
-There you go again, putting
on that stupid Mr. Cool act
like it really impresses anyone.
-Listen, I'm not
trying to impress any--
-Then what are you doing?
-Why do you even
care anyway, huh?
-I don't for you, but your dad--
-Jeez, why don't you just
go and marry him then, huh?
-OK, Ranma.
Now you're really being stupid.
-Ranma!
-Ranma, honey!
-Ranma, darling!
-Take Shampoo with you.
Great-Grandma to say OK.
-I can run my shop
from anywhere.
You know that.
-So long as we have
love on our side,
no matter how strict your dear
mama may be, we can't fail.
-Oh, just what I needed.
Man, as if one girl yelling
at me wasn't enough.
-Maybe we just fight to
decide once and for all.
-Winner goes off to live
with Ranma and his mother?
Sounds good.
-Ranma, darling, it'll
take but a moment.
-Hey, doesn't anyone here
want to ask me what I think?
-Kiai!
-Just leave me out of it, OK?
Just settle it
amongst yourselves.
Hey, watch it.
Ow!
[screaming]
-What have I ever
done to deserve this?
Huh?
Hi, Pop.
-It's time we had a
father-to-son talk.
-Gee, no kidding, genius.
Tell me, why did it take you
until now to figure that out,
huh?
-Ranma?
-Tell me, Ranma, have you any
memories of the woman at all?
-It's got nothing
to do with me, Pop.
So why don't you just
leave me out of it, OK?
-Son, you couldn't
be more wrong.
As it turns out, you've got
everything to do with it.
Then you mean, you
and her aren't gonna--
-Oh, no, no, no.
Helping her get you
is all I'm good for.
-Did-- did she really
say that to you?
-Son, I meant to
keep you out of it.
I really did.
Then she started crying.
And then I knew
what I had to do.
She got through to me, boy.
Promise you'll meet her.
Just listen to what
she has to say.
Then if you don't like
it, you can just--
-I--
-You mean you'll do it?
You will?
I don't know what to say.
-[gasp]
-I'm your son, ain't I?
This is where she works?
-Yup.
-Yoohoo!
Ranma, dear.
Over here, sweetheart.
So does this mean
you'll come with me?
-I-- uh, I'm kind of not
sure how I should feel.
I mean, I'm glad
you're Mom and stuff,
but it's kind of
hard to leave where
I am since I don't
really know you.
-Ranma, you make as much
sense as your father.
Speaking of whom, there
he is now over there.
-Hey, panda, you're gonna have
to do better than that if you
want this bamboo.
-Hey, it's that same bamboo.
-Ranma, think about it.
Have you any idea
how much people
would pay to see a
shape-changing girl or panda?
-Girls being
preferred, of course.
-Is that what you
call performing art?
Do it again!
Don't you give me that.
I, sir, am an artist.
-Hey, what's going on here?
It says, it was your ability
to change into a girl
when splashed with cold
water that the circus wanted
all along.
Knowing that you
were also needed
to carry on the Anything
Goes school of martial arts,
I tried to take your place.
But unless they can
balance atop balls,
it seems they have no interest
in transforming pandas.
Why, I ought--
[screaming]
Now tell me what you're
really up to, Pop, or I'll--
-Ta-da!
There it is-- the
boy turns into a girl
when splashed with
cold water trick.
Name your price Mr. You
can have all the bamboo
leaves that you want.
-A-ha!
-How dare you make
my tender feelings
the butt of your jokes.
[scream]
-Did somebody say butt?
-And you, you disgusting,
lying little pervert.
If it hadn't been for that
lame forbidden love story,
I'd never have come
here in the first place.
-Genma lied too!
-Come here!
-[sigh]
-All's well that ends well.
-In what way did this end well?
Huh?
Tell me.
-Oh, come on.
Don't be that way.
-Excuse me?
-I forgive--
-That's right, run.
You're going to think balancing
on balls is heaven on Earth
when I'm through with you.
[music playing]
ANNOUNCER: Oh,
Ryoga, are you really
that bothered by the past?
Huh?
What do you mean you've
come to a decision?
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
"From Ryoga With Love."
We'll see you there.