[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Bonjour, Furinkan!
-Hey, you guys.
I got chow mein bread!
-That's great.
Let's go have lunch.
Huh?
-Ah!
-Uh!
-You cut that out!
-That's crazy!
-Give it back!
-Uh, now what am I gonna eat?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Better
watch out for this one.
-And who are you?
-You avoid me.
[crying]
-Now you've made him cry.
Give it back.
-Zut alore!
Unfortunately, that
is not possible.
Voila!
-And what's all that for, huh?
-The invite says
all you can eat.
I'm all over that.
-Courtesy Picolet, [audio out].
-Even I've been invited.
-Tres bien!
Pour vour, mademoiselle?
-Picolet, I presume?
-Un toast to my lovely
brides of the future!
[gasping]
PICOLET: For three more lovely
brides, I could not ask.
-It disappeared.
-Impossible.
-You, monsieur,
interrupted my toast.
-Yo, Jacque, you got
seaweed on your mouth.
Catch!
-Hey-- hey, it only
looks like it's gone.
I guess he just eats super fast.
-Have another.
-Blech!
-Hmm.
-Monsieur, I call you out.
-I kind of thought you would.
--[french] monsieur, to
martial arts dining.
-Martial arts dining?
From hors d'oeuvres to dessert.
First one finished
is the winner.
-What he means, then,
is speed eating.
[groaning]
-The loser pays for
both dinners, of course.
-Hey, when it comes
to speed anything,
I'm about as fast as they get.
PICOLET: Begin!
BOY: It's all a big blur.
Oh, man.
Are we sure he's even eating?
-And look at that!
The plates are sparkling clean!
BOY: What's he doing?
Licking it?
-What unbelievable speed.
-They've reached dessert.
-Ranma's pretty
fast, too, you know?
His hands are, anyway.
PICOLET: Fin.
Monsieur, you are defeated.
I suppose you would
like to know the secret?
It is to make the
mouth like this.
For now, au revoir.
But do not wait too long.
I shall be expecting you.
-Huh?
-Expecting us?
For what?
-That is something only
your father can tell you,
mademoiselle.
Furinkan High School,
I bid you aideu.
-This is far from over.
-I'm more confused
now than before.
-Ranma, that dinner you
had was 100,000 yen.
[groaning]
-Oh, boy.
Fresh food really is expensive.
SOUN: What?
Picolet Chardin
here in this town?
-OK, what did you do now?
-I don't know.
-Dad.
-What's all this about
being future brides?
-Father, we're waiting.
-It's, um, um-- well, it would
have been a good 20 years ago.
Saotome and I were starving.
Finally, we came upon
the restaurant of Picolet
the First, or
should I say, dojo.
What?
It's free if you win?
-But you lost, right?
-We haven't any
money, but please,
let us make it up to you.
-Am I your [inaudible]
martial artist?
-Oh, Father, you promised to
give him one of your daughters?
-Dad!
-How was I to know
back then that I'd
father three daughters?
[sobbing]
-Great.
So now what?
-Now one of you three must
volunteer for bridal training
at Chateau Chardin.
As for which of you three--
-Hey, last time I checked there
were four girls living here.
Send me!
I've already fought
the guy, remember?
-Ranma!
-Atta boy.
SOUN: We're here.
-This place is huge.
-I'm proud of you, son.
It's a noble thing you
do sparing my daughters.
-Hm.
Hey, no prob.
I figure it'll take three days
to learn this battle dining
thing.
But then, I'm going to
lay the smackdown on him
like you won't believe.
[speaking french]
-And welcome to Chateau--
and who is this?
-Bonjour, Mr. Picolet!
Ranma here reporting for
bridal duty as you requested.
Shall we begin?
-Tres bien!
Welcome, mademoiselle,
to my humble abode!
Indeed, mademoiselle.
It would seem that
you are very shy.
-Oh, well, you now.
PICOLET: Care for a [inaudible]?
-Oh, [french].
Don't mind if I do--
-Incoming.
[exclaims]
-What the--
-Zut!
Tell me, mademoiselle
Were you reared in a barn?
-Mademoiselle Ranma, may I
introduce Madame St. Paul.
-So are you the one who
will teach me battle dining?
First, you must
show me how you eat.
Alore!
Non, non, non.
-Ranma!
-It is part of the training.
-I wasn't that bad, was I?
What did I do?
Tell me.
-Indeed, mademoiselle.
There is a trick to eat.
-He ate it.
-And without using his hands.
-This time I do it
for you more slowly.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
That's right, pal.
Show me your secret.
-Un, deux, trois.
[speaking french]
-Now I've done it.
-You sure have.
-Battle dining.
How terrifying.
AKANE: Come on, Ranma.
You're not really going
through with this are you?
RANMA: Akane, I have to.
I said I would.
-Honestly, you're so stubborn.
Take this.
-Hm?
What is it?
-It's for luck.
If you get in
trouble, just open it.
It oughta help you.
-She does have her cute side.
-Akane, don't worry.
He'll be fine.
Knowing Ranma, it shouldn't
take him more than a few days
to learn the techniques.
Don't you think?
-What I want to know is
why would he want to?
[music playing]
[grunting]
-No, no, no!
The baby does not
scream like the banshee.
-What is this?
-The iron costume.
Until you learn to behave like
the lady, you will wear it
and I will keep the key.
[speaking french]
PICOLET: Well, Mademoiselle
Ranma, what do you think?
All these people
here just for you.
-Very nice, Monsieur Picolet.
I was just getting
hungry as well.
Just a teensy piece.
Huh?
Good thing there's more.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
They're monsters.
I get it.
It's battle dining, and
they're all combatants.
But they know that
tongue thing and I don't.
If I got any chance at all.
It's this.
The speed of my hand.
-OK, jerks.
If that's the way
you're going to be.
Ha, too slow.
MADAME ST. PAUL: No, no, no, no!
The lady does not
use the hands to eat!
-Lucky Ranma, huh?
We're eating this while he's
got all-he-can-eat French.
-I sure do hope he
won't become ill.
-Well, even if he does, it's
all part of the training.
A full stomach won't hurt him.
[giggling]
[growling]
-Oh, man.
I'm starving.
-If you are truly hungry, you
will master the battle dining
-Guess I'd better
master it, then.
-It's for good luck.
If you get into
trouble, open it.
-Huh?
Candy?
It's a sweet thought, but that's
not going to help very much.
So good.
-Ranma, I bet you've opened
your good luck charm by now.
It'll help you digest.
[growling]
-Oh, man!
I'm even hungrier than before!
MADAME ST. PAUL:
Un, deux, trois.
[french] Now
straighten the posture.
Un, deux, trois.
And again, mademoiselle!
And again!
Zut, why do you not eat?
Un, deux, trois.
-Poor Mademoiselle Ranma.
She has not had the
bit of food all week.
-I can't reach the stupid plate.
-[inaudible], I feel your pain.
-There!
Feel your own pain for a change!
-You do not hit your fiancee!
For that, no dinner!
-But she did not have it before.
-Who would have thought
I'd lose to my stomach.
Oh, man.
I'm hungry.
AKANE: Ranma?
-Akane?
How did you--
-Guess they've been
pretty hard on you, huh?
Why not just give up
and come back home?
-Wow.
Hey, where'd you get the outfit?
-I work here now.
It was Dad's idea.
Also, I feel kind
of responsible.
Um, here.
This is for you.
You know, I wish
I had more, but--
-Akane, you're a lifesaver.
You have no idea how hungry I--
-Ranma, what's wrong?
Hurry, before someone comes.
-Thanks, but no thanks.
It was nice of you to
think of me, though.
-Ranma?
-I'd like to eat
it, but I can't.
Because if I do, it means battle
dining is too tough for me.
-What?
Ranma.
[growling]
-Food.
Food.
The fridge.
Where's the food?
-I just love a hot
bath after a meal.
-And what are you doing here?
-There's no shame in asking
for a father's help, you know?
I've come to look after you.
To learn this
battle dining thing.
-And I suppose the food's
got nothing to do with it.
-Certainly.
If Ranma were to marry
Picolet, I'd be in French food
for the rest of my life.
But what kind of a father would
even think of such a thing.
-You would!
That's who.
I ain't marrying nobody.
So if that's your plan,
pop, then maybe I better
show Picolet who I am right now!
It's tight!
-A-ha!
-He forgot the corset.
-Somebody-- water!
-Ranma, are you OK?
-Oh, no.
If I can't get this corset off,
then I can't be a guy again!
-Ought we be going through
grandfather's things like this?
-You kidding?
It's all stolen anyway.
-Wow, he sure does
have a lot, doesn't he?
-Hm?
What's this?
A who's who in
martial arts dining?
Those pictures are
over 400 years old.
-And my, what--
[clears throat]
SOUN: Distinguished gentleman.
HABIKI: More like
freaks if you ask me.
-It seems that large mouths
and extra long tongues
are required for victory.
Let's see.
-Wait.
What about that guy?
-Hm.
HABIKI: Hey, he's
practically normal.
-That means you can win
even if your mouth is small.
-Hm.
-End of the dining interval.
-Wait!
I'm not finished.
Come back.
I still need--
-Too slow!
[sigh]
-OK.
Why is this battle dining
stuff so tough for me?
I'm usually really
good at this stuff.
It is not!
There's more to it than that.
Battle dining is--
whoa, that's it.
I've been so busy trying
to eat that I forgot
the most important thing of all.
It's still just
another martial art.
And what's martial
arts but attack?
-And that's why
you're been losing!
-Gah!
What are you doing
in that outfit?
-I work here, but that's
not important now.
This is what's important.
-Hm, who's who in battle dining
SOUN: Here, I
bookmarked the page.
In 400 years of
battle dining history,
there was once a small
group of radicals
known as La Petite Bouche.
As the name implies, their
mouth was very small.
But that didn't stop them.
Instead, they developed
a special technique--
the terrifying
Parle du foie gras.
-Parle du foie-- what?
Where is this
terrifying technique?
Hey--
-Exactly.
Someone's torn out
the pages we need.
-Oh, man.
-Unfortunately.
-Ugh.
So, Monsieur Picolet,
would you do me a favor?
-But of course,
Mademoiselle Ranma.
-Have you ever heard of
the Parle du foie gras.
-Foie-- foie-- foie-- gras?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Please.
He does know it then,
but why would he
make such a big deal about it?
-I've never heard
of it in my life.
-You're such a liar!
I mean, you wouldn't
lie, would you, monsieur?
-Pardonne moi,
Mademoiselle Ranma.
But would this mouth lie to you?
-I would like to go
home now, please.
-Mademoiselle, wait!
Do not go, I beg you.
Since it means so much to you,
I will tell you the secret.
As you may have guessed,
it involves foie gras,
that most famous jewel
of French cuisine.
It is made from the liver
of the fattened goose.
Indeed, it is prized
all over the world.
[speaking french], such as I.
-And then?
And then?
-And that is it.
If he's hiding some kind of
secret, I sure can't see it.
-I just know there's
more to it than that.
Maybe if I just taste
it, I'll figure it out.
-My entire mouth is
embraced with the taste
of this rich, velvety goodness.
-The taste is all you need, but
I feel I could eat it forever.
-Rich taste, velvety texture.
You take a bite, you want more.
Hm.
Where's the secret?
MADAME ST. PAUL: What--
what did you say?
The mademoiselle asked
about Parle du foie gras?
[screaming]
-Madame St. Paul!
Calm yourself!
MADAME ST. PAUL (VOICEOVER):
The Parle du foie gras?
The most devastating technique
in the battle dining arsenal?
How can this mere girl
have heard of this?
-Monsieur Picolet,
it seems apparent we
have no time to waste.
-I agree, Madame.
-We must stop her.
-There's but one thing.
-Saotome, you give
that back! [inaudible].
I'm not eating it
because I want to.
I'm doing it for Ranma!
-Just shut up.
I'm trying to think here.
SOUN: You ate it!
You piggy panda.
PICOLET (VOICEOVER): It
is made from the fattened
liver of the goose.
-That's it!
-Ranma?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I see it.
I know how to use it.
The only question
is-- do I dare?
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): The
winds call the clouds.
The cloud calls the storm.
Battle dining's
ultimate technique's
about to be revealed?
What is the Parle du foie gras?
Next time on "Ranma
1/2," Dinner at Ringside.
We'll see you there!