[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): The Daimonji
School of Martial Arts Tea
Ceremony-- the
elders, Matsu, Take,
and Ume, and their
successor Sentaro.
The Miyako Oji School of
Martial Arts Tea Ceremony--
the elders, Ino, Shika, and Cho,
and their successor Satsuki.
Sentaro and Satsuki
fell in love and it
seemed their
marriage would bring
the Orthodox and the
Unorthodox School
together to make
everything all right.
I'll just take this
opportunity to point out
this has nothing to do with me.
Quit staring and get
me off this thing!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Battle
for the golden tea set.
Bingo.
Come on, Tendo.
That wasn't fair.
Take it back and give
me another chance.
No, sir.
You've used up your
chances already, Saotome.
Hey, Kasumi.
Bring some tea.
KASUMI: Coming.
Thanks, dear.
I'll leave it right over here.
How do you find the tea?
Like it?
Here's your tea.
Right.
Thank you very much.
Oh dear.
You should think about changing
dishwashing liquids, Kasumi.
TENDO: We've got witches!
SAOTOME: Witches!
Help me!
Hmm?
We're looking
for Ranma Saotome.
Would you kindly
bring him out to us?
Please?
TENDO: Ranma!
SAOTOME: Your friends
are here to see you.
Those are my friends?
Hello.
You're the three elders
of martial arts tea.
Matsu.
Take.
Ume.
We're the elders of the
Daimonji School of Martial Arts
Tea Ceremony.
Huh?
Ranma?
Hey, I dunno why they're here,
but I'm not getting involved.
We three elders of
the Orthodox school
have a favor to ask of Ranma.
Hey, do I look like a
charity here or what?
It's a serious matter for we
three elders of the Orthodox
School.
Man, nothing good ever happens
to me when they show up.
Yeah, but the
least you could do
is ask them what
they want from you.
Ranma!
The Orthodox School is here.
Pathetic.
No self respect.
And no manners when it
comes to asking for a favor.
The Unorthodox School!
Miyako Oji School of
Martial Arts Tea Ceremony.
Ino.
Shika.
Cho.
Huh?
Oh no.
My troubles just doubled.
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
There's nothing to
be worried about.
We'll take care
of Ranma Saotome.
We'll take care of the boy.
We couldn't allow such a thing.
This matter is between we three.
There's no need for
you to interfere.
Something tells me trouble's
brewing down on the homefront.
Who we gonna call?
Witchbusters?
INO: Don't interfere.
CHO: Ranma belongs to us.
MATSU: We three got here first.
He's ours!
INO: You depend on us.
Hand him over.
MATSU: You depend on us.
CHO: You're being selfish.
This is getting
way out of control.
Ranma, you've gotta
say something to 'em.
Ranma!
TENDO: Ranma, do something!
All right.
I'm going.
I'm going!
Oh my.
I can't remember the last
time we had a tea party.
I certainly hope they brought
some cakes or something.
[gong chimes]
Nabiki, what are you doing?
Hey, this cake's
not too shabby.
All right.
How about we get down to
business and you tell me
what this is all about?
I haven't got all day.
Great things are
not born of haste.
Huh?
The guests must be
served before all else.
It's the way of tea ceremony.
Come on.
That's what I don't
like about their school.
They're always so
hung up on rules.
They're rude and
completely oblivious
to their guests' feelings.
MATSU: Pardon me.
INO: Pardon we three.
CHO: Our school has rules and
we three must observe them.
This tea is delicious.
Thank you.
How impertinent, young lady.
Don't gulp it down like a soda.
There are rules for
drinking it properly.
I'm terribly sorry.
Satsuki told me to
feel at home, so I
suppose I forgot my manners.
Satsuki said that?
I didn't hear her speak.
You did.
Right, Satsuki?
Satsuki, don't make
me laugh so hard.
How can she hear her?
They must both be using ESP.
What the heck is
this all about?
And now they say
they're gonna get
Sentaro to tell me everything.
Why didn't they
just get him to talk
to me right from the start?
Speaking of Sentaro,
it's been a long time
since we've seen him.
It has been a long time.
Quit sneaking up like that!
No anger, please, Ranma.
It's such a negative thing.
I've had enough of this place.
I'm splitting.
No!
Please, come back.
This time it really
is a serious problem.
I promise!
Ranma, at least listen
to them, won't you?
O my sweet Akane.
I knew you'd understand.
You're so soft
and you smell so--
I bet Satsuki would
want to hear about that!
Some things never change.
Ranma, I'm picking up
negative vibes coming from you.
Can't you just get
down to business
and tell me what
this is all about?
Huh?
Hmm.
It all began three days ago.
I found this letter shoved
under the door to my room.
What's this supposed to say?
It looks like a poem.
It's so flowery I
can't read what it says.
OK.
Enough suspense.
What does it say?
On a full moon night,
the [? enishi ?] teapot
will take flight.
Signed, Toko Otome.
teapot will take flight?
What's an [? enishi ?] teapot?
What does Toko Otome mean?
Toko Otome is a
traditional nickname
taken by a woman whose legendary
youth and beauty are eternal.
The teapot of [? enishi ?]
is a genuine golden teapot.
And a treasure passed down
in the Daimonji Family.
Genuine gold, you say?
In the wedding ceremony
of the Daimonji Family,
it's our tradition to
offer tea to the bride
with the golden pot.
In other words, that
letter is a declaration
of someone's intent to steal
our sacred [? enishi ?] teapot!
Hey, Satsuki, isn't
this sort of exciting?
If you're serious, then
start acting the part!
Listen, Ranma, Akane too.
You've got to help them.
They can't have their wedding
if the golden teapot is missing.
Yeah, I could care
less about Sentaro,
but think how poor
Satsuki must feel.
O Akane, Satsuki and i
will wed, but fear not.
My love for you will never--
Hey!
Oh my.
That's not very ladylike, Akane.
Tonight, the moon will
be full and Toko Otome
will come to steal
our golden teapot.
I'm scared.
Why don't you call
the cops and ask
for a guard to stay overnight?
That won't do.
The Daimonji Family's
name would be tarnished!
So how about letting us
see this golden teapot?
As you wish.
Follow me, and
I'll show the way.
Hmm?
SENTARO: Sentaro
here, grandmother.
I've brought Ranma
and his friends.
You may be my grandson, but
you're such a disappoint.
I understand you're asking
many favors of Ranma.
But grandmother--
Enough.
I don't want to hear anymore.
Welcome back to
our house, you two.
As my grandson has explained,
he desperately needs you help.
I must apologize for him.
He's always causing
you such trouble.
No problem at all, granny.
We'll do everything
that we can.
Gee, Sentaro.
I've never seen your
grandma look so glum before.
Well,I guess she's
got a good reason.
Ranma.
Hmm?
This is the golden
teapot of [? enishi. ?]
Whoa.
That's unreal.
It looks like a treasure.
OK, so what's the plan?
Stay on guard
watching it all night?
No.
I've decided to put
the golden teapot back
to the safest place
in this whole house.
What?
You mean like a
safe or something?
Even better-- the symbol of the
Daimonji Family, the five story
tower!
Don't worry, Satsuki my dear.
As long as I'm here,
no one can steal
our precious golden teapot.
And no one will dare interfere
with our upcoming wedding.
Ranma?
Kasumi be made you
something to nibble on.
Feels like we're
on a picnic up here.
Kasumi made a lot since she
figured it'd be a long night.
Here.
Great.
Help yourself, granny.
That's very kind of you.
I wonder if this Toko
Otome thief will really
show up tonight.
Seems a little over the
top for a practical joke,
wouldn't you say?
On a full moon night,
the [? enishi ?] teapot
will take flight.
Signed, Toko Otome.
This letter is the
only clue we have.
Yeah.
CHO: Welcome, solitary stranger.
The game is over, I'm afraid.
Ume of the Orthodox School
will allow you to trespass
no further.
Nor will Cho of the
Unorthodox School
Get out, evil thief!
Lucky block, but you won't
get away so easy this time.
Excuse me.
Do you have to stand on my head?
Oh dear.
How on Earth did I get up here?
Just quit yapping and get off.
You look a lot like my step
stool at home if you ask me.
Who are you to talk?
I know mushrooms
taller than you.
And I know toadstools
that have fewer spots!
M-- m-- m-- master.
Hmm?
What does that mean?
Looks like our thief
has made her appearance.
The old ladies on the second
floor tried to stop her,
but she got past 'em.
I wonder if Take and Shika
are OK on the third floor.
This is as far as you're going.
This is it I'm afraid.
Hey, granny.
Maybe teaming up one Orthodox
lady with an Unorthodox lady
wasn't such a hot idea.
I'm older.
I go first.
Think again there, granny.
Back off, you Unorthodox wench.
Why I oughtta!
Uh-oh.
Three floors down, two to go.
I should known this
wasn't gonna work.
I proposed it as a challenge
for the Unorthodox and Orthodox
Schools.
Considering the
wedding and all, I
thought it would give
them a good chance
to team up and work
together for a single cause.
It would be the
first time in history
that the two schools
ever cooperated.
You must think you're
clever making it all
the way to the fourth floor.
But this is as far
as you're going.
As a member of the
orthodox school, I, Matsu,
will not allow you to--
As a member of the Unorthodox
school, you'll go no further!
Excuse me, but I believe I
was doing the talking here.
The strongest have
to stay in front.
Everyone knows that!
MATSU: Raw courage is the
only thing that counts.
Courage?
You jumped a foot
straight up when you saw
that cockroach earlier tonight.
Hah!
I suppose we could always
settle our differences later.
Good idea.
Let's save our
fighting for later.
She's pretty good.
There's only one thing
left for us to do, Matsu.
I hear you, Ino.
May the two schools--
Unite!
Better luck next
time, Toko Otome.
That's a lot of work just to
steal Akane's handmade pig.
It's a zebra!
Really?
I thought it was a wild boar.
You can't get at the
teapot you're looking for.
'Cause if you think
you're going on the roof,
think again! 'Cause you
gotta get through me first.
On the roof?
What are you saying?
Ranma, zip it.
Way to go, genius.
You told her where
the teapot is hidden.
I don't believe this.
Well, she's still
not gonna get past me!
Hey, whose side
are you on, granny?
There she goes!
So glad we could finally meet.
I've been waiting
for you, Toko Otome.
I will not allow you to steal
the golden [? enishi ?] teapot.
I'm bound by my
lover for Satsuki
and I'm bound by the
family crest on my fan!
Bigger doesn't
always mean better.
As I was saying, you won't get
one step closer to-- one step--
ahh!
Huh?
That was sheer luck!
Satsuki!
Please return our
golden teapot to us.
She talked.
Please return our teapot.
All right.
That's enough.
Granny.
Grandmother.
A fine example of
the Miyako Oji style.
You don't really
want to continue
fighting with your
granddaughter,
do you, Toko Otome?
[chuckling]
Your skills are
improving, Satsuki.
Master!
The Unorthodox Master?
So you two masters put
this whole thing together.
Yes, we were behind it all.
First, let me apologize
for all the trouble we must
have caused you all lately.
As you know, we're preparing
for the marriage between Sentaro
and Satsuki, after which the
two fighting tea schools will
be united for the first time.
But we were concerned about
whether Sentaro and Satsuki
were qualified enough
to becomes successors,
and I wanted to make sure
that everything would work out
for the best.
Sure.
Trust a bunch of
old teatotellers
to come up with
something like this.
Wait a sec.
I think I just figured out
that letter from Toko Otome.
The top characters of each
row spell out the word
for matriarch-- i, e, mo, to.
Very clever, young lady.
That's precisely the
one and only clue
that we gave our grandchildren.
So grandmother, how
did Satsuki and I do?
Did we pass your test?
Satsuki passed indeed.
She did have fine job of
blocking Toko Otome's attack.
I'm looking forward
to offering tea
to her as the
beautiful new bride.
Grandmother, that means
we can get married soon.
Not so fast, young man.
We have yet to grade your
performance, grandson.
What did you think of him,
Unorthodox tea master?
If I'm not mistaken, it
looks like the weather
will clear up today.
Yes, you're right.
But we still have a spell
of hot weather ahead of us.
With all that running
around, my ankles are the size
of an elephant's.
Oh no, dear.
You're still in much
better health than I am.
Excuse me.
Give it up.
If they're talking
about their ankles,
it means you didn't pass.
Sentaro, you must start
your formal training right
from the beginning.
We two masters
and the six ladies
of the Orthodox and
Unorthodox Schools
will spend every spare moment
working you to the bone.
Understand?
Man, and to think we all could
had a good sleep last night.
We couldn't have
known it was a setup.
And besides, it was
nice to get away.
I had a bad feeling about this
right from the very beginning.
Excuse me, everyone.
I hate to interrupt
you, but if you're done,
I've made some tea.
Start all over again?
Thank you, Kasumi.
Shall we join you over there?
Yes, please do.
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): On
a cool summer night,
an old friend comes back
for a one night visit.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Gosunkugi's Summer Affair.
We'll see you there!