[music playing]
[chatter]
MALE VOICE: Come on.
Hustle it up.
We gotta hurry.
MALE VOICE 2: Don't
worry about it.
We're working as hard as we can.
[hammering]
[music playing]
[chatter]
Oh.
Darn thing ripped again.
NABIKI: Very sad.
Why don't you show
me how, Nabiki?
Sure.
Bullseye.
Oh, golly, the
carnival! [laughs]
Would you quit moving
around so much, Master?
Don't you love it when
the carnival comes to town,
eh, Tendo?
Hey, this looks fun.
Let's go.
"Curse of the Scribbled Panda."
CARNIVAL BARKER: Step right up.
See 3,000 year-old cursed
Chinese wall scrolls
right before your eyes.
[gong]
What you are about
to see may shock you.
Gaze upon them freely, but
tell no one what you have seen.
Because if you do,
you shall be cursed
with a lifetime of bad luck.
Please heed my words, children.
Here is the first one.
One to go, please.
You got it.
Hurry, hurry.
Huh?
When my great-grandfather
finished painting this,
he mysteriously passed away.
He was 95.
Number two.
After my 98-year-old father
finished this one, he too died.
Oh, my.
Huh?
But prepare yourself,
because I have yet
to show you the last one.
Why, thank you.
Hey, come back here.
It is time to reveal the
third work of evil art!
Give me back my takoyaki!
Huh?
Thanks, Pop.
[groans]
Oh, no.
The seals!
The horror!
[wails]
What's happening?
I think something came
out of those wall scrolls.
Do you realize
what you've done?
You can't possibly understand
what you've unleashed.
For 3,000 years those
cursed wall scrolls
have been painted
by cursed artists
using cursed brushes
on cursed scrolls
by cursed thought in their
minds, on a cursed day.
But now you've
removed the seals!
OK.
So what?
For generations
my family has kept
the evil trapped in
those wall scrolls
and now you've released them.
Hmm?
[worried cries]
They've left the building.
This is very, very bad.
What is that?
I have no idea.
They look like those Chinese
monsters I've read about.
Yeah, right.
Let's go.
They don't know what
they're dealing with.
[yelling]
Hey, look.
There's Daddy!
That's it, Father.
You show them!
Prepare to meet your maker.
Because you're going down.
Good luck!
Over there!
You're gonna burn!
Let go of my sword!
We've got to help.
That must be the third one.
Be on your toes, Ranma.
[growls]
[giggles] Yes, I'm free!
What the--
Oh no.
This is the third cursed
painting come to life!
You're kidding.
What is it?
Are you blind?
It's a panda.
How abstract.
It's a doodle, Kasumi.
[grunts]
So how in the heck are we
supposed to get rid of him?
Place this seal on
the panda's forehead.
And then they will all
return into the scrolls.
All of them?
Yes, but you must do it
before the hour of the ox,
or they're here for good.
Hour of the ox?
Around 2:00 in the
morning your time.
Oh.
Oh, it's so wonderful
to be free at last!
And it was you who set me free!
Oh, thank you kind stranger.
Thank you.
Huh?
No!
Please!
I can't go back to
living in that picture.
Never!
That panda-- it's
not female, is it?
Can't you tell by looking?
I'm finally free Oh, please.
Please don't send me back.
Just one night.
That's all I ask of you.
I just want to live
my dream of having
a date with a wonderful man.
That-- that is my
one and only dream.
I feel so sorry for her.
What harm would
it be in letting
her be free for one night?
You think?
Hmm.
If your dream comes
true, will you leave?
Uh-huh.
[chuckles]
Hey, what are
you scheming, boy?
I think you know.
But you can't mean--
Aw, don't you
feel sorry for her?
Hey little panda--
[gasps]
Look!
I think I found you
the perfect date.
No!
This is my worst nightmare.
I don't want to date
a fat and ugly panda!
But he's the only
other panda I know.
Hmm.
[grunts]
Check out that couple.
That's a couple?
[giggles]
Aren't they cute?
Well--
Oh, please.
Don't tell me you're
jealous, Akane.
As if.
Open wide!
I have a surprise for you!
Your favorite, takoyaki.
Well?
Did you like it?
Mmm.
Excellent.
He's just being nice.
You try one.
I would, but my
mouth doesn't move.
I see. [laughs]
Oh, look.
I just love balloons.
What's your favorite color?
Your favorite is mine too.
[laughs]
Try and catch me.
Oh, you little vixen.
I'm right behind you!
I'm gonna get you!
What the heck am I doing?
What's wrong?
You've had enough fun, right?
What are you talking about?
Hey, don't go!
I've had enough of that
little furball's tricks.
The seal?
I, uh, lost it.
What?
I though I put it in here,
but maybe it's in here.
You--
Oh, Ranma!
There is another
way to put her back.
What do you mean?
You could try persuading her to
go back into the painting using
all your manly charms.
Who, me?
But time is
quickly running out.
Remember the hour of the ox.
Let go of my sword.
I'm still waiting, my sweet.
[music playing]
How big do you think?
That's it.
Go, Father!
Oh.
Please put your
money into the can.
Thank you.
Look, it's a giant panda.
You go for it, Saotome.
Your money, please.
[grunts]
I love the way
cotton candy feels.
How about you?
Want some?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
You like it?
Not bad.
I'm so happy when I
see that you're happy.
Really? [laughs]
I can't believe he's
flirting with her.
[giggling]
It's OK, Akane.
He's just putting on an act.
That's all.
He's just--
RANMA: You are such a tease.
PANDA: Oh, stop it.
That it.
I've had enough.
I've got to put a stop to this.
Ranma--
Akane.
What's up?
Don't you remember?
We had a date.
We did?
You idiot.
Stop fooling around and do
what you're supposed to do.
If she isn't back in
the painting soon,
we'll never get
rid of any of them.
Ranma, who is she?
Is she your girlfriend?
Of course not.
Give me a break here.
Why, just look at her.
She's way too uncute
to be my girlfriend.
How's that for
uncute, you jerk?
I can't believe how much
cash I scammed today.
Normally this would
take me a whole week.
Huh?
Was what you said the truth?
What was it that I said?
Is that girl really
not your girlfriend?
Of course she isn't.
That's just what
I wanted to hear.
I wish you and I could
be together forever.
Geez, is Ranma still only
at this phase of his plan?
He's such a slowpoke.
Aah!
Nabiki!
Oh, Ranma?
I have an idea.
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
I have never been so happy.
Huh?
Nabiki, have you seen Ranma?
Yeah.
He's at the park putting
on the performance
of his life for that panda.
Huh?
[sobs] Oh, the pain.
It's tearing me up.
What's wrong?
You can tell me.
It suddenly dawned
on me how completely
fragile and temporary
our love has to be.
What do you mean?
It doesn't matter that
we're two crazy kids in love.
It's just that you're a
panda and I'm a human.
Oh, no!
It breaks my heart,
but you're right.
It wouldn't have ever worked.
You can't blame yourself.
It was fate that brought us
together and tore us apart.
Don't worry, Ranma.
I understand.
Are you sure?
Yes, Ranma.
And now it's time
I said farewell.
I don't know if I'll have the
courage to say farewell, kid.
Then I'll say it for us.
Farewell, Ranma.
Boy, he could work
on a soap opera.
Yeah.
[whirring noises]
[explosion]
Ranma, oh, Ranma.
Now it'll work.
Well she does have a point.
[growls]
I never figured
this would happen.
[screeching]
Aw, man.
And I thought they
were superheroes.
I've had way too much to drink.
(PANTING) I can't
take it anymore.
You know, I'm going to
have to start to work out.
At least you tried your best.
OK, now I'm totally confused.
I have had it with
that stupid idiot Ranma.
[screams]
Akane!
Ranma!
I'm coming!
[grunts and groans]
[screams]
Someone help me!
Let go of Akane!
[screams]
Akane!
Attaboy, Ranma!
The three of us combined
don't have enough energy
to fight them, so we'll
have to rely on Ranma.
Ranma.
Caught your
attention, Amaguriken?
[grunts]
Ranma!
[groans]
Akane!
You let me go!
Let me go, or you'll be sorry!
Akane!
The time has come for me to
return to the wall scroll.
Come on, you two.
We're going home!
Ranma, you made my dream
of having a date come true.
I got to ride on
the merry-go-round,
and I got to have a balloon.
It was so wonderful.
But the time has come
for me to say goodbye,
and I thank you,
Ranma, for everything.
Was it really that
much fun for you?
Can I ask you one last favor?
You go ahead and ask
me anything you want.
Uh, OK.
How about a kiss?
Hmm?
Huh?
Oh.
Why not?
She's only a doodle.
[grunts]
PANDA: All I ask for
is just one little kiss
and then my life
would be complete.
Oh, please?
Oh, pretty please?
Ranma, you can't
be serious about--
Oh, Ranma.
You're so shy and naive.
OK, then.
Let me help you.
No, you can't!
Yes.
[moans]
Head butt.
Huh?
Thank you, and
goodbye to everyone.
Was it fun?
Yeah.
Then it's time.
OK.
Thank you.
She wanted a kiss
on her forehead.
I've got to say, I'm
proud of you, boy.
CARNIVAL BARKER:
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Get your tickets.
For the first time ever,
witness my latest piece
of Chinese art, seen
for the first time.
[gasps]
Pretty impressive, don't
you think? [laughs]
Yes, I think he's
captured Ranma rather well.
I'd say he's
right on the money.
Yeah, right.
[laughter]
[music playing]
NARRATOR: Near the beach, where
the Tento family's vacationing,
lies the mysterious
Watermelon Island.
What secrets does it
hold, and why did Kuno
lose his memory there?
Next time on "Ranma One
Half," the date monster
of Watermelon Island.
We'll see you there.