[theme music]
[boiling]
KASUMI: You know better.
-Oh, quit torturing me, Kasumi.
-It's not quite done yet,
so just leave it, OK?
-But all I wanted was
an itty-bitty taste.
KASUMI: I said no.
-But why?
KASUMI: Because.
Now why don't you take a nap?
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
"Into the Darkness."
-This is so boring.
[sighing]
[boiling]
[sniffing]
-Smells so good.
Kasumi, is it ready yet?
KASUMI: Not yet.
-Oh, nuts.
[sighing] Oh my,
what a pleasant day.
[snoring]
-Here it is.
And may your soul
now rest in peace.
[music playing]
[snoring]
WOMAN: Happosai.
Happosai.
-Who are--
-I am what you wished for.
-Somebody pinch me cause
this can't be happening.
-Here, I have bought
a gift for you.
-No, really-- well,
maybe just a taste.
[laughing] Yes.
Yes.
-Do I make you happy?
[laughing]
-Oh, yes.
Oh, yes.
[laughing]
-Hm?
I wonder what the
freak's dreaming about.
Hey, taking a nap's
not a bad idea.
[sniffing] Mm.
[boiling]
-Something smells good.
[snoring]
[music playing]
-Today is your last
day on earth, old man.
That's it.
You're going down.
I thought you were
tougher than that.
[laughing]
-I can't believe these two are
sleeping the afternoon away--
such a shame, especially
on such a beautiful day.
Well, it is a little cloudy.
[yawning]
[boiling]
RANMA: Whoa.
Does that ever look good.
-Eat as much as you like, Ranma.
-This is excellent, Akane.
You're the best
cook in the world.
-Oh, well, it was nothing.
-A wicked cook,
smart-- what a girl.
-Ranma.
[giggling] You stay here.
I'll make you some more.
What's happening?
HAPPOSAI: Hey, get out my dream.
-Huh?
[laughing]
-You'll never beat me, old man.
Never.
-Don't you know
this is my dream?
-No!
No!
-Huh?
Akane?
-Ranma?
So where-- where are we?
HAPPOSAI: You're in my dream.
-Huh?
-So how did we end up in your
stupid dream anyhow, you freak?
-Yeah, how?
I'd rather be in my own dream.
-Cause I was the
first to fall asleep.
I thought you'd figure
that one out for yourself.
-You--
[laughing]
-Pathetic excuse
for a leprechaun.
-I'd say this is no
different than real life.
[laughing]
-One at a time, girls.
Oh, and remember to put your
phone numbers neatly this time.
-I take that back.
This could only be his dream.
[laughing]
-Whoa, this place is so tacky.
-I know.
Huh?
Hey, these are mine.
[laughing]
-And so are all
these other pairs.
-That's right.
Why, you'll find
every single pair
you've ever worn,
including a few diapers.
Don't forget this is my
dream, sweetie. [laughing]
-Why would you do that, huh?
-I tell ya, everybody
needs a hobby.
And this one's mine.
-Gross!
-Oh, Ranma, look what
I've got for you.
-You-- you're disgusting!
-Hey, you put this on, or else--
AKANE: Hey, Ranma.
Now you can fight
him like a man.
-Hey, what gives?
I'm still a girl.
[laughing]
-How many times do
I have to tell you?
This is my dream.
And in my sick and twisted
little imagination,
I call the shots.
So if I want Ranma
to stay a girl--
-Hurry, Ranma!
-Remember, you can
run, but I'll find you.
[panting]
-Come on, Akane.
We have to find a way
out of this dream.
-Yeah, cause I don't
want to find out
what happens if we stay.
RANMA: What do you mean?
-Cause he's crazy.
-OK, I'll give you that.
But where are you headed to?
-I have absolutely no idea.
-Why, you-- I
should've known you
didn't have any kind of plan.
-Oh, yeah?
Then let's hear your plan.
-Hey, I was following you.
[grunting]
[sighing]
-OK, we just got to
think this thing through.
-I agree.
Akane, look!
-Huh?
-Hey, how did Nabiki's dream
end up inside this one?
[sighing]
-Her dream's bound to be
better than the freak's.
AKANE: It sure is dark in here.
RANMA: Yeah.
AKANE: And it doesn't look
like there's much here.
[inaudible]
[gasping]
-Hey, what's that?
-You think we
should check it out?
-Let's go!
What's this?
-Ranma, look.
-Hm?
-Hey, you think this could
be a way out of here?
-Oh.
Hm.
[beeping]
[gasping]
-To proceed, please
insert 1,000 yen.
To proceed, please
RANMA: Insert this!
Paid in full.
Oh, Ranma, that area's
off limits unless you pay.
-Nabiki.
-There's no way I'm
paying you a single yen.
-OK, that's fine with me.
But in my dream
it's pay-as-you-go.
-So how much is it?
You name your price,
and I'll pay it.
-3,000 yen.
-What?
3,000 yen?
-That's just to open the gate.
Another 3,000 to point
out the right one.
-Well, thank you.
-Well?
-You'll find the gate
right over there, Akane.
-Well, see you later, Nabiki.
-Look!
-Huh?
[laughing]
-Welcome to my nightmare.
-She tricked us.
-Well, well, it's not very
nice to talk about someone
behind their back.
-N--Nabiki?
-Now you must ask
Master Happosai.
-Nabiki, can you rub my back?
-Coming, hun.
-I think I'm going to be sick.
-Isn't this great?
I have never been this
happy until I decided
to move into Happosai's
little fantasy world.
-Open wide, my sweet.
-Ahh.
-Oh, please, Nabiki,
would you stop it already?
-You'll figure it
out for yourself.
There's no point in
fighting him in his dream.
-You know that Nabiki's
smarter than she looks.
Huh?
-By the way, you still
owe me for dinner.
-Maybe a bit too smart.
-Oh, boy.
-Ranma.
-Huh?
[whispering]
-There's no way.
Do it yourself, Akane.
-You want to stay here forever?
Let's just hope you
like modelling underwear
for him, Ranma.
-[grunting]
NABIKI: Here you go.
HAPPOSAI: Oh, ho.
Oh, why thank you.
[slurping]
-Yoo-hoo.
Maybe we can come to
some kind of arrangement.
That is if you're
willing to wake up
from this little fantasy.
-Name it.
-Well?
GROUP: Happosai!
-No, I'm staying right here.
-Why that little-- ah!
[laughing]
[interposing voices]
-Nabiki's our only
hope out of here.
-3,000 yen.
-Huh?
But what for?
-You want information, you pay.
-But that's all I've got.
-Thank you.
You know, I'm making some
pretty good cash in here.
-OK, I paid.
Now tell us how to
get out of here.
-I don't know.
-What'd you do that for?
-Please, Ranma.
I'm just as weirded out in this
pointless fantasy as you are.
-Well, you sure seem
to be enjoying it.
-Give me back my money, Nabiki.
-But Akane, you only
paid me with dream money.
[growling]
-OK, OK, OK, I'll tell you.
Just promise you're not
gonna hurt me, all right?
-OK.
[laughing]
-What?
Fainting?
-Yeah, if you can get
him to faint somehow,
then he'll snap out of it.
-Oh, man, this is gonna be easy.
-Don't be so sure.
[moaning]
GROUP: Oh, you're so big
and strong, Happosai.
-Ahh!
Ahh!
[screaming] My back.
[laughing]
-I love it when they play rough.
-That should take care of him.
GROUP: Oh.
Happosai!
[gasping]
-Should've used a
be bigger mallet.
[laughing]
-I'm back.
There's one thing I should
tell you about my dream.
It's impossible to wake me.
[laughing]
-Check.
And it looks like
there's nothing
you can do about it, my friend.
[laughing]
[snoring]
-Saotome, I said check.
[yawning]
[boiling]
-Hm?
[laughing]
-Look who's here.
-What happened?
-How did we get here?
-You're in my dream.
-We're in his dream?
GENMA AND SOUN: Excuse us.
-That really hurt.
-It sure did.
[laughing]
-It's like I said,
you're in my dream.
And everything I
dream comes true.
GENMA AND SOUN: Huh?
-M--M-- M-- Master are you
sure you're comfortable?
GENMA AND SOUN: How about
a quick massage, Master?
-Oh, knock it off.
Huh?
What?
[snoring]
-Wake up you perverted
little twerp.
-Ah, that was close.
-I thought you were going
back to wake him up, Ranma.
-Hey, would you get off my case.
-Oh!
And I thought I
could count on you
to get us out of this nightmare.
-Huh?
Akane, look!
I think it goes this
way. [laughing] Huh?
Oh, well.
That's enough
excitement for one day.
[boiling]
-Nice to have you back, Genma.
-Oh!
We were all counting on
you to wake him up, pop
-Don't worry about it, Ranma.
I know what I'm doing.
[laughing] Huh?
-Oh, man.
I gotta figure out a way
to get that little munchkin
to pass out.
-You don't get it, do you?
There is another way.
-Huh?
Oh, great, Nabiki,
let's hear it.
-1,000 yen.
-500.
-OK, you got a deal.
-Tell us!
-Happosai isn't necessarily
the only one that has to faint.
-Now I get it.
-Yeah, so do I.
[screaming]
-Would you stand still?
Don't you remember
what Nabiki just said?
It doesn't have to be Happosai.
-Get real.
-You are such a wimp, Ranma.
-Psst, Akane, if you
faint in this dream,
then will you wake up too?
-Huh?
-But the Master says he
doesn't want to wake up.
-Please.
That's because he's
having the time
of his life with those girls.
-What now?
-We must--
GENMA AND SOUN: Give him an
old-fashioned wake-up call.
-Huh?
-If this doesn't wake him
up, I don't know what will.
-Look, Saotome, I
think the Master's
starting to snap out of it.
Hey, I'm starting to enjoy this.
-And it's good exercise too.
-[inaudible].
-Hey!
Would you two quit
hogging all the fun?
-I got ya.
-Saotome!
-Hey, stop!
Time to fight back.
-All right.
-He's gonna make us faint.
-It's working.
[moaning]
-Huh?
GENMA AND SOUN: Huh?
-What the--
-You fools!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
You can't escape my dream.
Even if you or I faint, it
doesn't make any difference,
because you're trapped
in here for eternity.
[gasping]
[moaning]
-Ranma!
-Well, I suppose that's
pretty much the end of Ranma.
-You mean--
-I'm kidding.
Nobody's going to bite
the big one in this dream.
-You sure?
[moaning]
ALL: Huh?
Huh?
-On the downside, this
could go on forever.
ALL: Huh?
-Hm?
-What's happening?
-Hey, everyone.
Lunch is ready.
[snoring]
-Huh?
I just had the best dream ever.
But it's such a shame that
I had to wake up from it.
-I'm glad to hear it.
-So you gonna tell us all
about it, you old goat?
-Huh?
-There's no way it was
as good as my dream.
-Don't be so sure
about that, Nabiki.
-Yeah.
GENMA AND SOUN: Please
forgive us, Master.
-Huh?
I just had a little dream.
Is that so wrong?
ALL: We know about your dream.
Take that!
-Please hurry back, or
your lunch will get cold.
-OK.
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Well, if
Nabiki wants him so much,
then fine then, she
can be Ranma's fiance.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2",
Nabiki, Ranma's new fiance.
We'll see you there.