[theme song]
[birds calling]
A secret sauce?
When's it ready?
Can I taste it?
Would you quit jumping around?
Can't you see that I'm
trying to work here?
I just hope Father
doesn't find out
I borrowed his special little
recipe, or I'm in big trouble.
[grunting]
Well, I guess this is it.
Time to test my secret sauce.
This secret
okonomiyaki sauce has
been aging for the last decade.
The moment of truth has arrived.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Ukyo's
Secret Sauce, Part One.
[clock chiming]
I wonder what was
wrong with Ukyo.
She's never missed a
day of school before.
I don't know.
Maybe she got sick.
You're saying you're depressed
because you ruined some sauce?
You mean you skipped
school for that?
Ukyo!
Hmm?
Care for a taste?
It's disgusting!
How could I have
failed like this
after devoting my entire
life to making okonomiyaki?
I still remember
the day I made it.
There!
Now all we have to do is
let it cure for a few years.
[laughing]
I don't understand
what went wrong.
I'm positive I followed my
father's recipe exactly.
Ranma, honey, do you
remember if I made
sure the lid was sealed tight?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure it was.
So you're saying this is the
same sauce from back then?
[sigh]
I want to get a little taste.
[scream]
Oh, I really did it now!
A little of this, and this,
and some of this, and, oh!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
[laughing] Man,
if Ukyo ever found out what
really happened, I'd be toast.
Oh, don't worry.
I think you should just calm
down and have some porridge.
I just made it.
You made it?
Are you-- are you
trying to kill her?
Oh, thank you, Akane.
I will have some.
[groaning]
Ukyo!
Because you live
on your own, Ukyo,
I think it's in
your best interest
to stay with us for a while.
At least until you
feel well again.
Thank you so much for the kind
offer, but it's not that bad.
Hold on.
Uh-uh.
Not only are you suffering from
the psychological distress,
but you ate Akane's food.
[groaning]
Hey!
Don't worry about it, Akane.
I'm sure I'll feel better soon.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, and-- and if you need
anything, you can just ask.
Huh?
Ranma?
How come you're suddenly
being so nice to me?
Uh, no reason.
No reason at all.
Why do you ask, anyway?
Come on, Ukyo.
We've been friends for
a long time, right?
[growling]
Saotome.
Well, if I'm going to
stay, will you help?
And I think that
should go over there.
Sure.
Is that all her junk?
So is she moving in here?
Ukyo, are you planning on
moving into Ranma's room?
Of course not.
I'm only going to
stay until I get out
of this depression from
ruining that sauce.
Ranma, are you OK?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Um, I'm fine.
[laughing]
Hey, Ranma, are you trying
to hide something from us?
[crash]
So now what are
you going to do?
About what?
And why is it you're suddenly
being so nice to Ukyo?
I don't know what you're
talking about, Akane.
I am starting to smell a rat.
Are you sure there
isn't something
you're not telling me?
Huh, Ranma?
Yeah.
Now, would you quit asking
me so many questions?
Are you sure about that?
Anyway, it's kind of hard
to explain the relationship
between me and Ukyo.
You wouldn't understand.
Huh?
Oh, man, I never thought
Ukyo would get so depressed
over stupid sauce.
I've got to think
a way out of this.
Ranma, honey, want
me to scrub your back?
I can't just stay here and lie
around doing nothing at all.
[gurgle]
OK, sit up, Ranma, honey.
[whimpering]
How come so shy?
Come on, we grew up together.
Well, uh, you know, I, uh--
Huh?
[growling]
Man.
Why won't Akane ever
listen to what I
have to say before she hits me?
Huh?
Ranma honey.
I've been waiting for you.
It'll be just like when we were
little kids, sleeping together
when we were camping.
Uh, I think I'd better not.
What are you waiting for?
And please, don't tell
me that you're shy again.
This-- this is not good.
[screaming]
Hey, I didn't do
anything, Akane!
But you were going
to, weren't you?
--[laughing] Well, now, Ranma,
for a person who's living
in his fiancee's house for
free, what are you thinking?
But it's not what
it looks like!
[growling]
I don't care if they
are just friends!
It just isn't right having
a girl sleep in his room!
Why you--
[shouting]
[scream]
Now what?
Don't tell me you
slept up in the tree.
Yeah.
And to think that
Ukyo's probably
all nice and comfortable,
all snuggled up in my bed.
If you keep this up, you're
going to catch a cold.
Well, I can't do anything about
it until Ukyo feels better.
So when do you think
Ukyo will leave?
You listening?
[gagging]
What is that smell?
Oh, it reeks!
What is going on out here?
[growl]
I hope you don't
mind, but I thought
I'd make breakfast for myself.
Even if it is a mistake
I made a long time ago,
you all have to understand,
I still have my pride.
And while everyone might
think this sauce is revolting,
I still have got to eat it.
I've never witnessed
anything quite so brave.
Hey, don't do it!
Ukyo!
Ranma, honey.
Ranma?
[growling]
Delicious.
Oh, no!
Ranma, honey!
Ranma, are you OK?
I'll go make him a bed.
Oh, brother.
So, Ranma, what
happened to your face?
It looks like you've been
trying Akane's cooking again.
UKYO (VOICEOVER):
Ranma honey saved me
from eating that okonomiyaki.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Something isn't right.
So, Akane, what do
you want to talk about?
Um, don't you think
that Ranma's been
acting really strange lately?
Well, I guess
maybe a little bit.
I thought so.
What I can't seem to figure
out is the reason why.
To be honest, I never
really thought about it.
According to the
recipe, we have
to make sure the vat
is sealed, and then we
have to let it sit for 10 years.
What?
We have to wait 10 years?
That's right.
But don't worry.
When it's done, I promise
you'll be the first to try it.
That is, for a price.
Then what?
I seem to recall making a
really important promise.
Huh?
OK, if it tastes good--
Hmm?
Then you have to promise
that you will look after me
for the rest of my life.
Yeah, OK.
That must mean that Ranma
still remembers the promise
he made to me back then.
And that's the reason why
he ate that disgusting sauce
at breakfast.
Because he wants to spend
the rest of his life with me!
But I go and ruin that sauce.
Oh, another stupid
Ranma promise.
That's what you get
for eating that sauce.
Oh, man, it hurts.
Maybe that's because you
have some explaining to do.
What do you mean?
Like what you did
when you were little.
Huh?
Then-- then-- then you know?
Then it's true.
Hmm.
Something I'll never
be able to forget.
But-- but Ranma, when
you two were little,
didn't you think Ukyo was a boy?
So?
What does that have
to do with anything?
I guess that's true, but--
Listen.
Even if it's something
that happened
when Ukyo and I were still kids,
I still can't hurt her, OK?
Hmm?
[gagging]
Ukyo.
I have decided to
dispose of my sauce.
[gasp]
So please, tell me honestly
that it tastes horrible.
Ranma, I have to put
being an okonomiyaki chef
over my happiness.
UKYO (VOICEOVER): And
I can leave this behind
if I hear you say it.
All I have to do is eat this
one last time and I'm free.
One, two, one, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two, one, two,
one, two, one!
It's actually pretty tasty.
Serious?
You-- you really liked it?
I'm touched!
Ranma honey!
[groaning]
Well then, now you'll have
to spend the rest of your life
with Ukyo!
Huh?
I'm going to have to put
my happiness over being
an okonomiyaki chef after all!
What in the world are
you two talking about?
Don't play dumb, Ranma.
But I--
I'm so happy you remembered.
Huh?
When we were little
kids, the promise we made!
OK, if it tastes
good, then you have
to promise that you
will look after me
for the rest of my life.
Yeah, OK!
[laughing]
Huh?
I may not be much of
a woman now, Ranma,
but I promise to be a good wife.
[nervous laughter] Um.
Uh, Ukyo, are you sure we
made this promise back then?
Ranma, honey, are you
telling me you don't remember?
[nervous laughter]
Is this true, Ranma?
What a stench!
[groaning]
Ranma honey ate this
horrible okonomiyaki
with the ruined sauce and
said that it tasted good!
He couldn't have done it
if it wasn't for love!
Come back here, you
worthless little cheat!
Come here!
[crashing]
Oh, my.
This just gets
more complicated.
Ranma, you idiot!
Honestly, saying that
he'd take care of Ukyo
for the rest of his life?
Wait a minute.
He can't be serious.
But then again, he did remember
that promise with Ukyo.
Ranma, if you want to keep that
promise and take care of her,
fine!
Ranma, honey,
Akane says it's OK.
Well, Akane, you were still
uncute until the very end,
weren't you?
Good bye, Akane!
Huh?
No, Ranma, wait!
You can't leave without me!
I'm sorry!
Huh?
Wait a minute.
I'm not the one who
should apologize!
[screaming]
You've got to believe me!
I'm sorry, Mr. Tendo!
I'm sorry!
It's just a
misunderstanding, really!
I-- I--
Huh?
Now why in the world am
I apologizing to you?
I really don't know.
Maybe it's because
you're a complete idiot.
You mean you're the
one who made that sauce?
Yeah.
Because I was the one who
spilled the first batch.
So what made it
taste so rotten, huh?
It could have been either
the insect wine or maybe even
the powdered cuttlefish.
Then what about the
promise you made with Ukyo?
I forgot.
You moron!
Don't worry about it.
I'll just explain it
to her and apologize.
I really hope this works.
Man's got to take
responsibility for his actions.
I'll do it.
Huh?
Ukyo, we gotta talk.
Oh, Ranma, honey, you're
just in time for dinner!
Huh?
Uh.
It'll be just the two of us.
I'm so happy.
The bride and her
husband to be, all alone.
But-- but you don't understand.
Ahh!
Ahh.
[laughing] See?
I'll make a good wife for you.
[laughing]
Ahh.
What would you
like to try next?
Uh, how about the sauce broth?
Ranma!
Weren't you going
to explain things?
Or was your little promise to
me like every other promise
you seem to make?
Am I sensing a conflict here?
Remember what you told me?
[nervous laughter] Oh, right.
Ukyo?
Ahh.
Ow!
And so I'm the one.
After I spilled your sauce,
I concocted a new one.
Look, Ukyo, what
Ranma really means
is that he was being nice to you
because he was feeling guilty.
Ranma.
Hey, if you want to kick me
a few times, go right ahead.
--[sigh] Oh, you
poor little thing.
It was Akane who put you up
to this, wasn't it, Ranma?
Huh?
No.
It's not like-- what I
mean is, Akane never--
I just knew you
were behind this.
What do you mean?
If you think Ranma's
just going to run back,
you're in for a
real disappointment.
I'll do whatever it takes
to protect what's mine.
Why would I--
Yeah, and I'm not lying!
Just hold on.
Huh?
It's time you
told her the truth.
I don't get it.
Ranma, Akane, you
both know you haven't
told her the entire story.
Huh?
But Nabiki, we just
told her everything.
OK, Ukyo.
Here's the deal.
You probably already knew
these two were engaged,
but here's the part
you don't know.
Your attention!
Our happy couple are,
in fact, married!
It's the truth.
Oh, my.
Huh?
We're what?
[screaming]
Come on, go along
with the program.
What have you got to lose?
You're right.
I've got nothing to lose.
I'm so happy for you two!
I'm so sorry, Ukyo.
We should have told you.
Huh?
Lies!
They're all lies!
We can't hide the
truth anymore, darling.
Have you gone nuts?
[crying]
Akane!
Just play along, OK?
OK, I will.
I mean, I'd do anything to
help you get out of this jam.
To help me out of this jam?
Huh?
Hm?
So just what are you
two talking about?
Well, we're just
your average couple.
And we had a little argument.
Oh, darling.
Would you stop it?
[laughter]
I get it.
Aren't you two cute?
Shut up.
I'm so happy for you.
Oh, Akane.
How I've waited for this day.
UKYO (VOICEOVER):
I'm not backing down
until I can expose
them of their charade.
[theme song]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): He's
a make believe husband,
and I'm a make believe wife.
Oh, how long are we gonna
have to keep this up!
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
Ukyo's Secret Sauce, Part Two.
We'll see you there!