[theme song in japanese]
-Ah, here we are.
What a day.
Hmm.
The air is fine, the
cherry trees are blooming,
there's peace in my
household, and all
is right with the world.
What could possibly go wrong?
-Aaah.
-Hmm?
Well, good morning, Father.
-Uh, hello.
She's not cooking
breakfast is she?
-Oh, no.
-Thank heavens.
-She's asked to
borrow the kitchen.
It seems she's finally ready
to begin bridal training.
-Ah, that's wonderful.
-Go away, Dad, you're
distracting me.
-Sorry.
Hmm?
Potstickers.
AKANE: Ranma,
you're such a jerk.
-Everyone, it's time to
come in for breakfast.
-Don't mind if we do.
-Morning.
-Good morning.
-Akane, don't you
forget to eat now.
AKANE: I can't.
I'm too busy.
-What is she doing
in there anyway?
-Bridal training.
-She's whipping up something
delicious all for you, Son.
What do you think of that?
-You're a lucky kid.
-I hope you appreciate it.
-Well, if you're all so
excited, why don't you eat it?
-No.
No, no.
-Hmm.
-Give me the pickles,
you little freak.
-Get your own.
You got Akane.
-So give me back the
pickles, and you can have it.
-And why should I have to die?
-Come here.
-I don't wanna.
-Ah, OK, now he's done it.
Ha, now I've got ya.
Aaaah.
-Oh.
-Uh, Akane.
I-- I-- I swear it
was an accident.
Akane, you gotta believe me.
-Don't smell like
potstickers to me.
-Can't you see we're
being serious here?
-What'd you hit me for?
Besides, it wouldn't
have happened
if you hadn't hogged
all the pickles.
-Do you know how long
that took to make?
-Look, I said I was sorry.
And besides, there's no use
crying over spilt milk, right?
-Here, here.
-Kasumi, dear, we're
out of soy sauce.
-Oh, all right.
Akane, serve the rice.
-Can I have seconds?
-Seconds, please.
Ah, eh.
-Well, I'm glad it's not
me who ticked her off.
-Oh, come now, Akane.
Isn't it time you gave
poor Ranma a break?
Forgiveness is a virtue.
Isn't that what
they say, Saotome?
-Ah, but arguing is what
couples do the best.
-I'd rather be coupled to
an ox, thank you very much.
-Say what you want, Ranma,
it's not like I care.
Excuse me.
-Guess this means the
engagement's over.
-Oh, but, but then we'd
be out on the street.
-Ah, but you'd still
have your pride.
-Here, Father, soy sauce.
-Stupid Akane could have
got me up before she left.
-Hey, boy.
Boy, you forgot your lunch.
Come back.
Or if you don't want
it, then I'll-- Uhhh.
-Uh, I forgot my lunch.
Akane won't share hers.
Ukyo's absent from school.
Maybe I could ask
Hiroshi or Daisuke.
Ah, that's it.
Good thing I remembered
to bring money.
-So what's wrong
with Ranma today?
-I don't know, and
I really don't care.
-Did you have a fight?
-Not at all.
-I got dibs on the
Korean noodle bread.
No way.
VOICEOVER: Dear
customers, in order
to attend the All Japan
Okonomiyaki Concourse,
I'm taking the next
three days off.
[inaudible]
-Oh.
I ain't even got enough
for octopus puffs.
-I'm home.
-Akane.
Thank goodness you're back.
Father and Mr.
Saotome, they're--
-Hmm?
-This would never
have happened if you
trained your son correctly.
-Like you never made a mistake.
-Oh, honestly.
Now what is it?
-Akane, thank
goodness you're here.
Your father says he's
protecting your honor.
-Thanks, Dad, but
you needn't bother.
-I'll be the judge of that.
Standing up for his little
girl is a father's duty.
-Oh, man, I'm hungry.
-That's right.
And so is defending
his son's honor.
-Defending his son's what?
Uh, never mind.
Forget it.
I take it all back.
-No, Son, you mustn't stop me.
What I do, I do for your sake.
-Aaah.
-What are you doing?
Don't just stand there.
Stop them.
-Saotome.
-Tendo, at last.
This is it.
-Dad, don't!
Aaah.
-Aaaah.
150 yen?
But, but Saotome.
-Ah, we'll finish the
play later, Tendo.
-The play?
-What play would that be?
Tell me, Pop.
-Uh, well, you see,
we-- um, uh, um.
-Oh, save it, Dad.
Hmph.
-Give me that.
-Genma, you idiot.
They would have
fallen for it if you
haven't blown your character.
Ah.
-And we were so close, too.
-Go, before I get--
-Aaah.
I'm sorry.
-Oh, my Father, do cheer up.
-I'm listening.
My pot, are you--
-Yessum.
-May I be excused?
-No, you may not.
-What?
-If you'd just listen
to reason, Akane,
you'd know that Ranma's
very sorry, and he-- Akane!
Please, please listen to reason.
I swear, I'll never make
fun of your cooking again.
I promise.
-Man, this is bad.
Akane, I'm sorry that I--
-Forget it.
-Hmm?
Good idea.
Just make a new one.
-Oh, I can just make
a new one, stupid.
The one you wrecked I made to
celebrate you and your dad's
coming here two years ago.
But if you're too
dumb to appreciate it,
then I-- I guess I shouldn't
even have wasted my time.
You know what you are?
A jerk!
-Oh, I wish Akane were--
-She's what?
Akane is gone?
-She's not in her room,
the Dojo, the bath.
Oh, where can she have gone?
-You don't think she--
-Could have possibly--
-Akane, run away from home?
Perish the thought.
-True, true.
But where else could she be?
-And who's fault is that?
No, no, it can't be.
I won't believe it.
You should've taken me with you.
Whatever will I tell your
poor deceased mother?
-I'll never get to
sleep on her lap again.
-So quit crying,
and do something.
-Ah, I made it, and before the
expiration date on these bean
jam buns, too.
Oh, Akane, I--
-Akane.
-What's going on?
Did something happen to Akane?
-Ryouga.
-Huh?
-Akane.
Ranma.
Where are you Akane?
Ranma, why won't you answer me?
-Akane.
Akane.
There she is.
After her, I say.
Faster.
Don't go.
Don't go, Akane, please.
I take it all back.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Wait up, please.
Akane.
Don't forsake me.
Please, Akane.
-Huh?
-That's not my name.
I'm Noriko.
[clock chiming]
-Akane.
You did something
to her, didn't you?
-What's done is done.
I couldn't help myself.
And besides, the idiot didn't
have to overreact like that.
-The only idiot here--
-Huh?
-Is you.
-Hey, get it out.
Ranma, this time you've
really gone and done it.
You have really done
it this time, you jerk.
-Look, I made a mistake, OK?
-You think it's a joke?
You call the disgusting thing
you did to her a mistake?
-What are you talking about?
-That does it.
-[inaudible].
-[inaudible], come back here.
-Akane.
Akane.
-Any luck?
-No, not yet.
Akane.
Not in here, is she?
-Akane.
Akane.
-Back off.
We can finish this later.
-[inaudible] Sidekick Jitsu.
-Hey, where you going?
-Look, I ain't got
the time for this.
-Silence.
First you get yours, then
I go find Akane by myself.
-Oh, yeah?
You and what sense of direction?
-Shut up.
-Are you crazy?
Ryouga.
-Akane.
-Ryouga.
Oh, geez, what a blockhead.
Come on, snap out of it.
Ryouga.
-Get off of me, man.
Get off of me.
Dah!
Get up.
This is no time for a nap.
Get off of me.
Stupid jerk.
Oh, man, that was a close one.
Uh, wait a minute.
Don't break.
Aaaah.
-She's still not back?
-I guess she was serious.
-Once she makes up her
mind about something.
-Kasumi is she-- Well, there's
not much else to search.
-Do you think maybe
she's left the area?
Wait for me.
-I guess maybe I can find
a few more places to check.
-Oh, good job, stupid.
Now you've done it.
Akane could have run off
almost anywhere by now.
Still not back.
Oh, Akane, you idiot.
Where did you run off to?
Don't you know that without
you, I'm just-- Huh?
AKANE: Achoo.
-Akane?
Akane?
You mean, you've been
up here the whole time?
What's the matter with you?
You had the entire
family thinking
you'd gotten into
some kind of accident.
-And what gave you that idea?
-Now wait a-- Huh?
Come here.
-Hmm?
-You want to get
down, don't you?
You're going to catch a cold.
-I don't need your help.
Aaaah.
Aaah.
[crash]
Hey, you OK?
-So you don't need my help, huh?
-Hey, what do I know?
I'm just an idiot, remember?
-Oh, well, that was
just, uh, you know--
-It's OK.
How can I stay
mad at someone who
admits he'd be lost without me?
-But I never--
-P-chan.
Hey, cut it out.
What did P-chan ever do to you?
You poor baby.
How'd you get that
bump on your head?
It was Ranma who
did it, wasn't it?
You are so pathetic.
-Well, he had it coming, OK?
-There, there, baby.
Don't worry.
Mommy will beat him up for you.
I'm sure he's got
it coming, too.
-Oh, poor Father's
still out there.
Oh, well, it's time
to start breakfast.
-You what?
-The whole night?
-On the roof all along.
-Do you know how hard
I tried to find you?
The sewers I had
to crawl through?
-You poor thing.
You must be exhausted.
Here.
Have some soup.
-So all your worrying
was for nothing.
-There, Pop, did you hear that?
-And what'd we ever do to you?
-Are you saying
we had it coming?
-I'm cutting school today.
-I'm sorry you guys, but look,
I made you some potstickers.
Have some.
What?
You're not hungry?
Here, Ranma, you try some.
-Huh?
-Come on, have some.
-Hmm, yeah, great.
-Ha, ha, very funny.
Come on.
Help yourself.
-Uh, uh, uh, Akane,
you, uh, you wouldn't
mind running away
again, would you?
-Huh?
You jerk.
How come you're always
so sensitive, huh?
-Look, you got it wrong.
I'm just being
honest, that's all.
-[inaudible].
-Ow.
-Come on!
Hold still!
-OK, stop it.
[theme song in japanese]
AKANE: Ranma, what's
this Dragon Whisker?
And what's it got to
do with your pigtail?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Give me that pigtail.
We'll see you there.