[theme song]
[humming]
[groaning]
-Huh?
are you OK?
What's wrong?
-Oh, feel so weak.
So sick.
Rub back would make
feel so much better.
-Poor thing.
Here.
Is this better?
-More to right.
-Here?
-More lower.
Ha!
[screaming]
[laughing]
-What the--
[yell]
NARRATOR: Ling-Ling and
Lung-Lung Strike Back!
-Huh?
Who's there?
Oh!
Ugh!
Not you two again.
-Me Ling-Ling.
-Me Lung-Lung.
-Aren't you two
supposed to be in China?
-We no can stay in China.
-Not when big
sister in disgrace.
That why we come back Japan!
-To get revenge on
Ranma and embarrass her.
-We wait for
Shampoo get married.
-But you never do, so we
come and make sure Ranma
keep promise whether he want
to marry big sister or not.
-Even in China we hear
rumor of Ranma many fiancee.
-So we thinking maybe if we
get rid of other fiancee,
he marry only one what is
left-- big sister Shampoo!
-Now you only one what is left.
[gasp]
-Other ones before
this was too, too easy.
We beat them before they
realized we attacked, remember?
[laughing]
-So you're saying
that you've already
beaten Kodachi and Ukyo?
BOTH: [laughing]
One we beat first
was cry, cry like
little baby when
she realized how strong we was.
-It can't be.
[scream]
-Now that we catch you!
-Aah!
-We beat you good!
-Ugh!
-OK, who are ya, and
what do you want?
-We sorry!
-We only make joke.
No be mad!
-Oh, no!
I forgot!
[gasp]
The hand-baked
heart-shaped okonomiyaki
that I made for Ranma!
-You hear?
-Now she can no trick Ranma
into fall in love with her.
-So far fiancee break
up plan work perfectly.
-Maybe there no need to
beat her up after all.
BOTH: [gasp]
-Wait.
Let me get this straight.
You're gonna beat up me?
-Ugh.
-Humph.
-Wait 'til you hear
what we do to next one.
-Even think about it make
Lung-Lung scare all over.
[yelling]
-You there.
What do you mean by this
invasion of Mr. Scaly Green's
pond?
[gasp]
-Watch out!
Ugh!
Ah!
-How we supposed to know
Japan have Jusenkyo Spring?
Good thing we have
quick think feet.
-Girl turn into crocodile
no can surprise us!
-Ugh.
-Now it's your turn Akane Tendo.
-Now we beat you up like we
already beat up other ones!
-I don't believe it.
Would you just wait a sec!
If you'd let me explain
you'd understand why I--
-You is one what no understand.
If big sister no
get married soon,
then we no get married either.
Is law of Chinese Amazon tribe!
-And we want big sister
Shampoo get married!
That why we come Japan!
To make sure she happy!
-Ugh.
You can tell
yourselves that all you
want if it'll make
you feel better,
but don't expect
me to believe it.
-See?
We knew you no understand.
-You already have fiance.
[humming]
-What the--
-Come on, give me a break!
That's enough already!
-You afraid we beat
you so you run away.
-Coward!
-Call me whatever
you want, I just
don't wanna get mixed
up in this again.
-Hey, there.
How's it going Akane?
-In fear for my life
thanks to you Ranma.
-Oh, yeah?
From who?
BOTH: Ranma Saotome.
-Ha ha!
Hey, if it ain't good old
Ling-Ling and Lung-Lung.
What's going on?
-I wouldn't be so
happy if I were you.
-Argh.
You have big nerve Akane Tendo.
You lucky we not
suspicious type,
or we think you keep
Ranma all to self.
-I'm missing something
here aren't I?
-Oh, nothing much.
They've just come to kill
me and marry you to Shampoo.
That's all.
-Th-that's all?
-Listen Ranma, I don't
care how you handle it.
Just leave me out of it, OK?
-How I handle wha-- Ah!
-Well, I wish you luck.
[laughs] See ya!
-Hey!
BOTH: Come back!
-Oh, no you don't!
-Why you try stop us?
-Yeah!
Maybe you like Akane
Tendo better after all.
-What's that got to do-- look,
we're talking about you guys
here, not me.
BOTH: Just answer
question Ranma.
-I-- ugh.
-Mommy!
Mommy!
What's that?
-Pretend we don't see them.
LUNG-LUNG: Well,
answer question!
LING-LING: Which
one you like better?
-Well?
-Shampoo?
-Or Akane?
-Uh.
Not that it's any
of your business,
but we just happen to live
in the same house, all right?
Are you happy now?
Huh?
-You hear?
Ranma Saotome no
like Akane after all.
-And Akane say she
hate Ranma, so--
-Well, yeah.
I mean, technically
that's true but--
LING-LING: So that mean
Ranma big sister Shampoo
get married no problem now.
-Huh?
LUNG-LUNG: Ay ya!
[laughs] That mean
we get married now
no problem too.
-Big sister Shampoo
be too too happy
when she hear exciting news!
-Wait, wait you can't do that!
-And why you say that?
-It's, uh, because
I, uh-- look, I
ain't got nothing
to be ashamed about.
[gasp]
-Then, that mean that--
-Ling-Ling, what you mean?
- --that maybe Ranma
Saotome like someone else?
Somebody else like--
[gasp]
-Huh?
BOTH: [exhale]
-Why we no realize?
-It's so obvious all along.
-Hey, hey.
What's this all of a sudden?
Hey.
-Is too too tragic story.
-Now we is ones go
home in disgrace.
-Why don't you let me help?
-Oh, if only we
not so beautiful.
-We no can help it.
Please no hate us.
BOTH: We never know
you feel that way.
-How we tell big sister Shampoo?
-Ugh, me and my big mouth.
-Ranma!
I don't believe you!
Here you've got a
wonderful girl like Akane,
and yet you still--
what I do, I do
in the name of the
girl you betrayed!
-Ryoga, Wait!
You don't understand!
-There is nothing to understand!
-If you just slowed
down I could explain!
-I doubt it!
Hya!
BOTH: You no touch him!
-We no let you hurt Shampoo
groom you big bully!
-Before fight him you
have fight with both us.
[laughs]
-You know what?
I'm gonna let you two
guys explain this to him.
Sorry man, gotta go!
-Ha!
Better move.
-Is better you fight us now
then try fight us later.
-We have special attack
we saved just for you.
BOTH: Ugh!
-Huh?
BOTH: Ling-Ling Lung-Lung
strike back attack!
Super Phoenix!
-How'd do that?
[screams]
[exhale]
-Huh?
Oh, jeez.
-Ranma!
We finished fight
just like you say!
-Now you stop running
and give us answer!
-So me, what'd you guys
end up doing to Ryoga?
BOTH: [laughter]
-Hi ya!
Why is it that all of Shampoo's
acquaintances are so violent?
Huh?
Ah!
An arrow!
And what's this?
A message.
-Akane Tendo, we challenge
you have fight with us.
-When lose you give up Ranma
Saotome, you understand?
-Come on you guys!
How many time have I told you?
Ranma and I--
-We already take care of Ranma?
-You what?
-This way you accept
fight challenge for sure.
-For womans of
Chinese Amazon tribe,
fight to death for man what
woman loves is only natural.
But for woman of Japan,
maybe is different.
Womans of Chinese Amazon
tribe think way too much
of themselves if you ask me.
[bushes rustling]
Huh?
Ryoga?
-Huh.
Ah!
-Ryoga!
Oh.
-One would get in
way is obstacle.
Obstacle is for killing!
-Too too tragic story.
-Huh?
Oh!
Th-the kiss of death.
-We be waiting Akane Tendo.
-No run away!
Ha ha!
[groaning]
-Ryoga.
-The Phoenix.
-Can it be true?
Did those girls
really do this to you?
If so, how would they possibly--
COLOGNE: From the look of that
scar, it can be only one thing.
-Huh?
A-and when did you get here?
[music playing]
-Note how even Ryoga is helpless
in the face of their attack.
Ling-Ling and
Lung-Lung's Super Phoenix
is nothing short
of extraordinary.
-Super Phoenix Attack?
-Hmm.
Tough to explain.
Desperately in need of a
way to prevent an attacking
army from crossing the
Great Wall of China.
A small group of
women got together
and devised a technique
of amazing effectiveness.
In a single blow,
this [chinese],
or Great Dance of
the Super Phoenix,
disabled their entire force.
It's no wonder they were able
to subdue Ranma so easily.
In fact, I wouldn't be surprised
if their ingenuity took him out
of action completely.
-Oh, Ranma.
[bird noises]
-So you come after all.
-'Course.
-Before fight though,
you agree to promise
if you no can win us, then
you no see Ranma no more.
-If I can't?
What have you done
with him anyway?
BOTH: Ha ha.
-Get ready because--
-Now we beat you!
BOTH: Hmpf!
-Ugh!
[gulp]
-Oh, man.
If this is what it means
to be out of action,
I'm-- [gulping] I'd
be a prisoner any day!
Ha ha ha!
BOTH: Ah!
-Humph.
[gulp]
BOTH: [shout]
BOTH: [groaning]
-Phew.
-Ugh.
Maybe womans of Japan no is
such weaklings after all.
-But you no can win
against special attack.
BOTH: [laughing]
-Hmm.
-Lung-Lung Strike
Back Special Attack!
-Just like Cologne said.
BOTH: Made in China
over 3,000 year ago.
Great Phoenix Fire Dance!
-Ah.
Huh?
-Ha ha ha.
Those two crack me up.
First it was the fire dragon
and now it's the Phoenix.
You sure gotta give them
credit for trying though.
-Ranma, you're alive!
-Well, of course I--
and why wouldn't I be?
-Ranma!
-Hmm?
-Go away!
We busy!
Fight Akane now!
-Why you no eat
picnic we leave you?
-After we win Akane,
we come find you.
Is OK?
-Then you marry
big sister Shampoo!
-Are you gonna tell me what--
-Don't get the wrong idea, OK?
It's not for you.
If I can't beat a
couple of Amazons,
then I don't deserve
to be a Tendo.
[crying]
BOTH: Ugh, we fight!
-Bring it on!
[yelling]
[panting]
-Good girl, Akane.
That's my girl all right.
You sure showed them!
[bear murmuring]
-Ugh.
Fight not over yet.
-Just started in fact.
-Huh?
-Ah!
This must mean the Super
Phoenix is coming up soon.
-Now you be scared
for sure this time.
-Here it come!
Ugh!
Ah!
-Akane, look out!
-Ugh!
Ugh!
[coughing]
-A-Akane.
-Those idiots!
-Not so fast!
It would be better for
you not to interrupt.
Wait and see what happens.
-Almost there.
-Now for finish.
Hya!
-I'm ready to finish
whenever you are.
Huh!
Hya!
-Not that I'm complaining,
but why don't they explode?
-That's Akane Tendo for you.
-Ugh!
Hya!
-Can't you see, son-in-law?
She's accurately
knocking them away
without hitting
the explosive tips.
-So basically she's so awkward
she probably couldn't even
get them to blow
up if she tried.
Ah!
[screaming]
-Hi ya!
BOTH: [screaming]
[coughing]
-Hey!
No fair!
She no supposed to hit
smoke bomb back at us!
-Cheater cheater!
-Ling-Ling, quick!
Quick!
Pedal more harder!
-Lung-Lung, is no good!
Pedal broken!
Ah!
What we do?
BOTH: Ah!
-Nothing can do!
BOTH: [screaming]
-Well, so much for
Ling-Ling and Lung-Lung.
Guess we've seen
the last of them.
-You've summoned the
wrath of the Phoenix.
-Ah!
[gasp]
-Now we use super,
super special attack!
-Super Phoenix--
BOTH: Fire Dance!
-Ah!
Is that the attack
they used on Ryoga?
[trembling]
-Ling-Ling hate when we need
use this special attack.
-It's too too scary
for Lung-Lung.
BOTH: [screaming]
-I can't quite believe it.
-Hya!
[screaming]
[crash]
[groaning]
-So, that was your so-called
super secret special attack,
huh?
-We missed aim by
little bit that all.
-By little, little, little bit.
-According to who?
[groaning]
-What is the meaning of this?
-Phew.
-The match goes to you my dear.
Ugh.
Well, actually, seeing as
Shampoo was never involved,
I wouldn't really
call it official.
Also, if Ranma hadn't saved
me, I-I would've-- well,
never mind that.
I've got no intention
of marrying him anyway.
[laughs]
-Whatever you say dear.
I was young once too, you know.
[laughs]
-Tell me something.
-Yes?
-As you say, the duel's
over so you may as well
fess up, and tell me the truth.
What was the point
of all that anyway?
-Huh?
Oh, well.
It is a legitimate
technique you know.
Just not a very
effective one that's all.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: What?
Oh, come on Ryoga.
You can't be serious.
Marriage?
Why now, a- and why so soon?
Next time on Ranma
1/2-- Ryoga's proposal!
We'll see you there!