NARRATOR: True Confessions,
A Girl's Hair Is Her Life
-Don't bother.
I really couldn't care less.
From now on, I want
nothing to do with you.
-(Softly) Uh.
-Huh?
-Oh, Akane.
-I think she's in shock.
-Of course she is.
Caught in public with
a haircut like that.
I bet you'd be in shock
too if it happened to you.
You should know that.
You're a girl too.
-Uh.
Sure.
Yeah.
A girl's hair is
her life, right?
CLASSMATE: Who are you anyway?
-Huh?
-Yeah I don't remember seeing
her around here before.
-Me neither.
Well, who is she?
And where did Saotome go anyway?
-This is no time to be worrying
about that now you guys.
Right now, we need
to worry about Akane.
-Calm down.
Just relax.
Well, it's not like she
was cut or anything.
-She wasn't cut, but her hair
just got the cut of it's life.
Go ahead and hit me Akane.
I can take it.
-Hit me, too.
-Come on Akane, you'll
feel much better.
Go ahead.
Wack me as hard as you like.
-Hit us really hard Akane.
Get rid of that anger.
-Huh?
-Eager to please, isn't she.
-Sure is.
-Uh, I must have twisted
it when I tripped.
Guess I'll have to pay
another visit to Doctor Tofu.
-Huh?
[gasp]
She's even madder
than I thought.
DR. TOFU: All better now Akane.
Bye Bye.
-Thank you.
-You be careful
crossing the street now.
-Bye Bye Dr. Tofu.
See you later.
KASUMI: Akane?
What are you--
-Oh hi, Kasumi!
-Another fight Akane?
I'm terribly sorry Dr. Tofu.
-Huh?
He's no problem.
-I'm sorry Akane,
but sometimes I
feel like I got a
boy for a sister.
If you don't start acting
more like a little girl,
Dr. Tofu won't like you anymore.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Huh?
Maybe if I grow my hair as
Kasumi, he'll like me again.
[knocking]
-Thought you'd catch
me crying Ranma?
-Well, uh--
-Sorry to disappoint you.
Now, get out of here.
-Uh-oh.
-Hey, Kasumi.
-How was your day Akane?
-You don't have to make such
a big deal out of it Kasumi.
-What happened to
your hair Akane?
-Actually, it was--
-Well, I thought I'd give
myself a little haircut.
And I guess I messed
it up a bit though.
I was wondering, could you
even it out for me Kasumi?
RYOGA: (ANGRILY)
Curse you Saotome.
I don't care if I have to camp
out on the Tendo's doorstep,
we're going to finish this
fight once and for all.
Where?
Where is that stupid
house of theirs?
-Oh excuse me?
-What?
-Could you tell me how to get
to the Tanaka's residence?
-Huh?
-I've come to visit my
grandchild, you see,
but I'm lost.
-Don't ask me.
Go to the police
office and ask them.
-Just point the
way, and I'll go.
Come on Sunny.
Show me the way and I'll
get out of your hair.
-Guess I'd better go
tell her I'm sorry.
-She hurt her ankle
this afternoon,
so naturally she
went to see Dr. Tofu.
Did something happen
at school today?
Oh my!
-Akane Uh.
Oh, sorry thought you
were someone else.
-Who were you looking for?
-Huh?
-What are you looking at?
-Is it you?
-It's different, isn't it?
-Akane, I'm sorry.
-Gee, aren't you being
nice for a change?
-Well, yeah.
-It's OK.
You're off the hook.
I was going to cut it anyway.
-Hey, uh how's your ankle?
You want a piggy-back ride?
-Stop being so nice, Ranma.
You're scaring me.
-Hello there.
-Good afternoon Dr. Tofu.
-Hey, you're hair
is short again.
-Yes.
-Don't worry.
This will heal in no time.
It's not too bad.
-Dr.Tofu You like my hair?
-Oh, it's very cute.
You know short hair looks
very good on you Akane.
-I knew it.
-Hm?
-Oh, Akane does
it hurt that bad?
I'm sorry.
-Huh?
No.
It's not that.
It's just they won't stop.
-Talk to me.
-Dr. Tofu
[sobbing]
-A good cry really does
make you feel better.
Hm?
Ranma?
What is it?
What's wrong?
It-- He said cute.
That's what he said.
I heard him.
I'm happy for you.
-Oh, who cares.
It's over
-Hey, what do you
mean who cares?
Dr. Tofu is in love
with Kasumi, not me.
It's OK though.
I think I'm finally over him.
-Wait up.
I wanted to tell you, your
hair really does look cute.
-Huh?
-What?
What are you looking at?
-Are you feeling OK Ranma?
-Hey, I was just trying to--
-You can cut it out now.
You don't have to cheer
me up anymore dummy.
-Oh that's not what I meant.
OK then, I take it back
about you being cute.
-Go right ahead.
Who cares if I'm not cute?
-Anyway, I like you
better in short hair,
not that you should
care what I say.
I'm just a dummy, right?
-Ranma, thank you, even
if you don't mean it.
-Woah, can it be?
She really is cute.
-Got you!
-Why'd you do that?
-Now we're even.
Don't you just feel the burden
of guilt just washing away.
-You're not cute.
I take it back.
-Who cares?
-We wouldn't happen to be at
Mount Aso in Kyushu, would we?
-Shut up!
-Well, this is it, the
Tendo Training Hall.
I made it.
But oh, the horrors I had
to endure along the way.
-Officer, were could I
find the Tanaka residence?
-Oh, it's right
over there ma'am.
-Congratulations to you.
You found it.
-(ANGRILY) Are you
out of your mind?
How dare you drag an old woman
all over Japan for a week,
you little whipper snapper ?
-But tonight is when
my suffering ends.
Ranma Saotome, today is the day
you go to your final reward.
-(WHISPERING) Wake up.
Ranma, it's me.
Let's fight.
Come on.
Wake up already.
(ANGRILY) Wake up!
(SHOUTING) Wake up stupid!
-Ryoga!
What the heck are you doing
here in the middle of the night?
-You shut up.
Does revenge know night or day?
-This has gone too far.
What could I have possibly
done to make you so mad?
-Listen, these may be your
last moments on this Earth.
After you skipped
out on our dual,
I followed you all
the way to China.
-Oh Ryoga, you didn't
go to Jusenkyo?
You fell in a lake,
now you change?
-Not another word!
You've done enough
to ruin my life.
-What's going on out there?
-Akane, are you awake?
-It sounds like an intruder.
-I'll take care of him.
-It might be a prowler.
-I doubt it.
-It is a prowler.
Look, he's got a big sack.
-Well, wait 'til I
get my hands on him.
-Akane, it's too dangerous.
Here, use this.
-Mhm.
-Come back here.
-Ryoga!
-Ryoga?
-Oh look!
Why it's only Ranma's
little friend.
-What a pain in the--
-Ryoga!
Oh.
So, he really did
take the plunge.
Ah, the poor slob.
[growling]
-(VOICEOVER)They sure
make a lot of noise.
I just wish they'd
finish their silly fight
and stop waking us
up at all hours.
Somethings in my room.
Hey!
Who's there?
Show yourself!
Ow!
A little pig.
Wonder how he got in here.
Come here.
Come on piggy.
That's right.
Come on.
Come here.
Oh you poor little thing.
You're all wet from the rain.
Are you lost little fella?
Oh, look.
there's a bow.
-I feel bad for you Ryoga.
I really do.
But you've got to stop attacking
me in the middle of the night,
OK?
You see, this ain't my house.
They got rules here.
-Where'd that dog come from?
What happened to Ryoga?
-Hey, where'd you get
the weird looking pig?
Shh, baby.
Be a good piggy now.
We'll get some nice medicine
and put it on your boo-boo, OK?
-Hey, I think it's blushing.
-Don't be stupid.
-You dirty little pig.
Ha!
It's a he.
-You're right.
-Hey!
Cut it out you--
-Come to think of it Ranma, I
know I've seen that dog before.
-Yeah?
(VOICEOVER) Don't worry Ryoga.
I'll keep your secret.
It's the warriors code, right?
It's funny though,
even when you're a dog,
you still look like Ryoga.
Those bloodshot eyes
are a dead giveaway.
-Ah, now I remember.
That's Yomada's dog.
-Huh?
-I'm sure of it.
Here Bess.
-Look away for a sec, will you?
Well that's odd.
And here I thought.
Oh well.
-Hey.
Where are you going?
-Take a bath.
All that running
around in the rain
practically froze
me half to death.
[sneezing]
-Well then can you
take him with you?
-Take a bath with a pig?
-Take him.
-So if he's not the
dog, then where'd
that idiot, Ryoga, run off to?
Come on.
Settle down.
A bath's not going to kill you.
In you go.
Ryoga?
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ranma,
are you fighting Ryoga again?
Well, cut it out already.
Why is Ryoga so
mad at you anyway?
Next time on Ranma
1/2, Pee Pee Pee-chan,
He's Good for Nothing.
See you there.