[music playing]
[MUSIC - COCO, "FULL OF
MEMORIES"]
[gong rings three times]
[speaking japanese]
[gong]
NARRATOR: "Ranma and
the Evil Within."
[rain falling]
[running footsteps]
-You know, there's
something wrong here.
How is it that I end up
paying for your food?
-(LAUGHING) Hey,
somebody's gotta pay.
-Hello?
You shouldn't be
eating like such a pig.
-I shouldn't?
-No, you shouldn't.
You're a girl.
-Now that you
mention it, I guess
I never do eat
this junk as a boy.
Why do you think
that is, anyway?
Why do girls get all the breaks?
-Oh, gee, I don't know.
Why not ask yourself?
-(LAUGHING) Maybe I will.
Huh?
-Have another parfait--
on me, of course.
-Wow!
You mean-- that
is, as in for free?
[laughs nervously]
RANMA: Akane, come on!
Wait up!
Now what are you mad at?
-Oh, now what reason
would I have to be mad?
-(LAUGHING) You're mad cause
I got free eats, ain'tcha?
Hey, now what did I do?
GUY: Hey, good-looking.
-Leave me alo-- hm?
-Say, uh, how's about a
cup of coffee or something?
-I don't know.
Is it your treat?
-Sure, sure.
-Then in that case, I accept.
Akane, I'll catch
up with you later.
-Mmm.
Honestly, what is
that moron thinking?
NABIKI: If you ask me,
I think he's a genius.
Think about it.
Wouldn't you do the same thing?
KASUMI: But Nabiki--
-What kind of an idiot
spends their money
when they don't have to?
You don't think I spend
my own money, do you?
-Ah!
-Come on, you
guys, that's wrong.
-Hear, hear, Akane's right.
After all, there's no such
thing as a free lunch.
[splashing]
Hm?
-Ah!
What did you do that for?
-Pish tosh.
Who needs their
bourgeois values?
Just don't forget your old
dad, that's all I'm saying.
-Um, Saotome.
[sigh]
[laughs]
-I'm getting tired of
changing back to a guy.
-Well, if that's how you feel,
why don't you just stay as-is?
-Huh?
You-- you mean-- that's right!
Maybe I'll just stay this way.
Oh, ho, ho, ho!
-Cut it out!
You're making me sick!
-So you want to be a girl, huh?
[cackles]
[dog howls]
[floorboards creaking]
[snoring within]
HAPPOSAI (VOICEOVER):
You've no idea
how long I've waited for this.
Without your consent,
conscious or not,
this mystic incense hasn't got
a chance of working. [chuckles]
Now that you've finally come to
realize the value of your girl
side, however,
separating your two sides
ought to be child's play!
[light snoring]
[wind rustling trees]
-[gasp] An evil omen.
Something bad's about to happen.
[snoring]
-Huh?
Aaah!
It worked!
The 3,000-Year-Old Founding
School of Anything Goes
Ying-Yang Thank You Ma'am
Personality Splitter Technique!
Ranma, listen to me.
From this point on, you're all
girl, 100% girl, do you hear?
And so in thanks
for the great favor
I've done in liberating
your better half,
you can start by
slipping this on.
Come on, here it is.
Come and get it.
Don't keep me waiting.
-[laughs]
-Huh?
Wha-- what-- she-- hm, now
why wouldn't she listen to me?
Hm.
[door rattling]
Hm?
That you, Ranma?
[screams] Oh my
god, it's a monster!
-Who are you calling a monster?
[sniffs] What is that smell?
You haven't been using
that incense, have you?
[snoring]
COLOGNE (VOICEOVER): Mm,
I hope for all our sakes
that it's just my imagination.
[snoring]
[wind rustling trees]
YING RANMA: Awake, my love.
Awake.
Awake, my love.
-(MUTTERING) What do you want?
Mm?
YING RANMA: Ranma, my love.
-Ahhh!
Who are-- [sighs]
-Ranma, I guess now you've
finally come to see it my way.
[cackles]
-(MUMBLING) Mm, give
me a bite of that.
So hungry.
-Hey!
[snoring]
-Come, my love.
Come, let us go.
Come.
HAPPOSAI: [grunting]
Please-- oww, oh god!
AKANE: Honestly.
Here I come!
Ranma, what are you doing?
We are going to be late.
RANMA: Go away.
Let me sleep.
-Oh, no.
I don't think so.
Come on! [gasp] Ranma!
What were you doing
all night, anyway?
Are you there?
-So cute.
-I-- I'm sorry,
what'd you just say?
-She really is the cutest.
-What?
Who's this "she"
you're talking about?
You don't mean Shampoo?
-Hm.
None of your beeswax.
-Huh?
RANMA: [whistles]
-Hmf!
[sigh]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): She
really is the cutest.
Hm.
None of your beeswax.
-Oh.
[gasp] What was that?
Hm.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
That's Ranma's room.
[running footsteps]
-Uhhhahh!
-Aaaah!
-Aaaahh!
HAPPOSAI: [moaning]
-Huh?
Hey, what are you doing here?
-R-- Ranma just-- aaaahhhh!
-Ranma did?
[snoring]
-Mr. Saotome, where's Ranma?
-(MUMBLING) Oh, so tough.
AKANE: Honestly!
Huh?
(CALLING) Ranma!
[panting]
-Come on!
We gotta hurry!
-Wha-- uh, what's going on?
-There's no time!
Come on!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I'm gonna
get to the bottom of this.
-Huh?
-Hurry, child, hurry.
There's not a moment to lose.
-Hai-yah!
Is emergency!
-I guess I wasn't
imagining it after all.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): If that "she"
Ranma mentioned wasn't Shampoo,
then who?
-Hey, what's going on here?
-Later!
Don't let them get away!
[panting]
-Oh, I know they've got
to be here somewhere.
-Ranma!
-Huh?
Ranma's with-- Ranma?
[music playing]
What's that?
It's all Happosai's fault?
-That old man do very bad thing.
Why he punish Ranma?
-When I found him in
Ranma's room the other night
with that smell of
incense in the air,
I should have known
he was up to no good.
And yet the only reason it
worked was because Ranma
himself willed it.
-Oh!
-Oh, ho, ho, ho!
Then maybe I'll just
stay this way, huh?
-The moment he allowed the
vigilance of his yang, or male,
side to subside, his
ying, or female side,
was able to assert
itself and break free.
-But still, it stay with Ranma!
GENMA: Hm.
As a father, it seems now I have
a duty to both of my children.
For Male Ranma, my duty
is to see him wed Akane
and inherit the Tendo Dojo.
For Female Ranma, it's to
catch her a rich husband.
Heh.
Yes!
That way I'll have it made
in the shade! [laughs]
-Hm?
[growls]
-Uh?
Ugh!
Huh?
SHAMPOO: Hai-yah!
-Wha?
[crash]
-Mm?
YING RANMA (VOICEOVER):
[disdainful laughter]
-Ugh!
If that's the way you
want it, then fine.
-Shampoo fight, too!
-You mustn't!
This isn't an enemy
you can defeat.
YING RANMA (VOICEOVER):
[disdainful laughter]
[gasp] Ugh!
[strangled cry]
-She's gone?
-What is she, some
kind of vampire?
-Ranma?
Ranma!
I
-Mm?
Whoa-- whoa!
Whoa!
[thud]
-Unh!
Anh!
-What has she done to you?
-Oh, Ranma, Shampoo
here for you.
-Do you mind?
-What evil can have
befallen my poor boy?
-Now that is the question,
isn't it, Saotome?
Are you sure there's nothing
the boy wants to tell me?
GENMA: Bite your tongue, Tendo.
He's just an innocent
victim of circumstance.
SOUN: Oh, is he now?
-The boy side of me separate
from the girl side of me?
Just what the heck
is going on here?
-All humans have two sides
to their personality.
That girl side of yours is the
embodiment of your evil side.
AKANE: So you're saying
that Girl Ranma is
kind of like his bad
side come to life?
COLOGNE: That's exactly
what I'm saying.
-I don't think the two sides
can stay separate forever.
-Hm, and they do seem
attracted to each other.
Oh, no you don't!
That's enough of that.
-You're darn right it is!
-That not funny!
-J-just kidding girls.
Uh, you know, a joke?
-All joking aside, unless
we do something soon,
Ranma will become the
slave of his evil side.
-But what can we do to help him?
COLOGNE: For starters,
we've got to make sure
that evil girl
stays away from him.
AKANE: But how are we gonna--
COLOGNE: You just
leave everything to me.
[dog howling]
[cats meowing]
[cats shriek]
-Ranma, my love.
[gasp]
Spirit wards!
Against me?
Ranma, my love, how could you?
My love!
[grunting with effort]
-Don't let her fool
you, son-in-law!
Once she lures you
to the outside,
she'll make you her slave.
-You've got to resist her!
-You can do it, boy!
-Hooray!
Go!
-Oh, my love!
Oh!
Uh?
-I have kept the two of
you apart long enough.
Was it so wrong of
me to want to get
in touch with
Ranma's better half?
Still, I should have
asked permission
before I called you forth.
Ranma, please forgive me.
Uh-- huh?
What'd I say?
-If you grant me one
teeny-tiny request,
I'll let you have
the bra I'm wearing.
-[gasp]
Vile temptress!
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Heh.
-Argh!
Hey!
-What you doing?
-Something I should have
done a long time ago!
YING RANMA: Come, my love.
My love.
[evil laugh]
[all gasp in horror]
-Ranma!
[grunts] Aaah!
[all cry out]
-Ranma!
-Hey, what happened
to your promise?
-Ranma!
-I'm coming, son!
-Soon, my love.
Soon, we two will be one.
[laughs lightly]
-They seem like
a perfect couple.
-Well, after all, they are
two sides of the same person,
of course.
-Of course.
-Will you two cut
it out already?
-Well, my love, you do want
us to be together, don't you?
-Sure.
YING RANMA: I'm so happy.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Would
you look at those two?
-Cut it out!
This is a public park!
YING RANMA: [growls]
[gasp]
-[growls]
-Hey!
Young ladies shouldn't
date without a chaperone!
-And young men should
be with the fiances
their father picked for them!
[rumbling]
[gasps]
[all shouting]
[crash]
-Uh?
Ah?
Ranma, please!
You've got to wake up!
R-Ranma?
[hissing roar]
[screams]
[cat yowls]
[panicked screaming]
-[gasp] Sh-- Shampoo?
But when did--
-Grrr!
-Rowr.
Meow.
-[yells]
-Meow.
meow!
-Here you go.
-Meow.
-Are you OK?
-Wha?
Mm-- wha?
What-- what are all
of you doing out here?
-Thanks to Shampoo,
you back to self.
-Thank goodness!
YING RANMA: Aaaahhhhhhh!
-Huh?
-Take this, you fiend!
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
-[grunts] OK, you!
[fighting grunts]
-You've had this coming
to you for a while!
-Aaaahh!
-Hai-yah!
-Hooray!
-Aaaahhhh!
Oh, my love, help me!
My love!
[strangled cry]
-Aahh!
-Stay back.
Stay where you are.
-My love!
My love!
Save me!
Aaaahhhhhh!
-She-- she disappeared.
[wind rustling in trees]
[dog barking]
[snoring]
--[chuckles] Nice try,
but I ain't stopped yet.
Come on, girl side,
come to Happy!
RANMA: Yeah, right.
I ain't falling for that again.
-Ranma!
-Oh, no you don't,
you little freak.
I ain't breathing
that stuff in again.
-Wait, no, cut it out!
[snoring]
-Uh?
-Uh-oh.
[panda growling]
-Oh no!
[both yelling]
[MUSIC - TOKYO SHONEN,
"PRESENT"]
NARRATOR: Ranma
fighting against Ranma?
I know one of them is an
imposter, but which one?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," "Enter
Ken and His Copycat Kerchief."
We'll see you there.