THEME SONG: [sung in japanese]
NABIKI (VOICEOVER):
This is a record
of a girl who has
devoted her life
to the cooking of okonomiyaki.
A secret sauce which she
had been aging for 10 years
turned out badly.
But in fact, it
was Ranma's fault
as he had replaced her
sauce with one of his own.
So to recover from the anguish
of ruining what she thought
was a sauce of her
own making, Ukyo
began to stay at
the Tendo residence.
I am starting to smell a rat.
Are you sure there
isn't something
you're not telling me?
It's kind of hard to explain
the relationship between me
and Ukyo.
You wouldn't understand.
NABIKI (VOICEOVER): But there
was still one more surprise
to come for Ranma and Akane.
OK.
If it tastes good, then
you have to promise
that you will look after
me for the rest of my life.
Yeah, OK!
NABIKI (VOICEOVER): When
Akane found this out,
she was infuriated.
Not only had Ukyo
moved in, but now she
realized Ranma had
pledged himself to her.
It was up to me to
diffuse the situation.
Our happy couple
are in fact married!
Well, we're just
your average couple,
and we had a little argument.
Oh, darling, would you stop it.
[laughing]
NABIKI (VOICEOVER): "Ukyo's
Secret Sauce, Part Two."
RANMA: Finally, lunchtime.
I'm starving.
Hey, want to grab something?
Yeah, OK.
Sounds great.
AKANE: Ranma!
I brought your lunch.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Oh
yeah, that's right.
Akane and me are
supposed to be married.
Sorry, uh, I brought lunch.
Too bad.
Akane, I'm so happy
you brought me lunch.
Has he gone nuts?
It's like he's under her spell.
Made it just for you.
Here you go.
You made it?
[laughs nervously]
Excuse me, we're married!
[groans]
Or did you forget, darling?
I'm sorry.
What did she say?
Sounded like married.
Yeah, that's what I heard too.
Man, you gotta feel for Ranma.
Wait a sec.
Come on, you guys,
you gotta believe me.
This is not what
you think it is.
[whimpers]
[laughs nervously]
We're married, right?
RANMA: Yeah.
Right.
Sure.
[laughs]
I don't believe this.
Could somebody please pinch me?
AKANE: Doesn't it
look delicious?
Ah!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Oh well, gotta eat.
So, how is it?
Putrid.
What was that, hon?
Why, it's delicious!
Then have another bite.
Thanks, but I think I'm full.
So?
Your love alone has
filled me up, OK?
[sighs]
Why, thank you.
[laughs]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Man, you look good.
Don't they seem
a little awkward?
Ranma looks strained.
Happy couples fight
a lot, so they say.
Everybody's different, I guess.
Or that they really
don't get along.
Hmph.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
The whole world
might think we're just engaged.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): But the
truth is we're hitched.
UKYO (VOICEOVER): I'm
sure the only reason Ranma
honey is putting up this act
is because Akane's forcing him.
I'm not going to give
up without a fight.
RANMA: But I don't get it.
You're really giving up
okonomiyaki for good?
Why?
Is there something bugging you?
UKYO: This is my
battle as a woman.
I'm shutting down
my okonomiyaki shop
because a real woman
only cooks for her man.
Catch my drift, Akane?
[groans]
Ah!
[grunting]
[laughs nervously]
[bell rings]
AKANE: Oh, darling!
Ranma, honey!
Open wide, sweetheart.
Come on, hon, try mine first.
She doesn't give up, does she?
Oh, Ranma looks so happy.
And isn't this all because
you made an arrangement
with Ukyo's father to betroth
Ranma to Ukyo, eh, Saotome?
Uh?
I thought so.
AKANE: Nabiki, what
are you doing here?
OK.
If you're going to play
the married couple bit,
you two are going to have
to share the same room.
Huh?
You're out of
your mind, Nabiki!
Yeah, come on!
Why the heck would I
want to room with her?
Back off, jerk.
Are you two splitting up?
Hm?
Oh, honey, don't you
think it's time we turn in?
Why, yes, of course, darling.
Good night.
They're joking.
Well, I suppose there's really
only one way to find out,
isn't there?
Huh?
1,000 yen, please.
AKANE: Where are you going?
Oh, I'm gonna
sleep on the roof.
That's what you want, isn't it?
You don't have to.
Huh?
What?
Were you hoping for something?
Give me a break.
Heh.
So you say.
AKANE: You idiot!
Come on, you two.
You're married, remember?
You'll blow everything
if you're not careful.
That's why I brought this.
Only 500 yen a bucket.
RANMA: That's it.
If I'm a girl, problem solved.
I still don't believe
they're married.
[gasps]
Take a look.
Nabiki, whose side
are you on anyway?
The side with cash.
[gulps]
Oh, man that was refreshing.
Thanks, Akane.
[growls]
[heartbeat]
[mutters]
[gasping]
RANMA: Hey, do you mind?
This is ridiculous.
Let's turn in.
You're right.
I mean, really.
We can't exactly
stay up all night.
[heartbeat]
Hey, Akane, you don't have to
worry about me trying anything
'cause you're not even my type.
Oh please, Ranma
like you scare me.
[groans]
Go for it.
Oh, you are really starting
to get on my nerves.
And you're getting on mine.
[heartbeat]
[sighs]
[grunts]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Can't sleep.
Oh man, will you look at her?
Sleeping like a little baby.
[gasps]
[sighs]
I oughta--
[gasps]
[groans]
AKANE: Oh, P-chan.
Where have you been?
You've got the wrong--
[squeaks]
Oh man, I can't take this.
I've gotta get Ukyo to
leave before I go crazy.
Morning!
Huh?
Good morning, dear.
Breakfast is all ready.
Wha?
UKYO: Come and get it
before it gets cold.
Uh, um, Ukyo?
Can I get you some rice, dear?
Wait, we gotta talk.
Don't you worry about that.
If it's about last night,
every man has an affair or two.
Huh?
Last night?
No, no, wait!
Nothing happened!
But I do understand.
I don't want to hear
your excuses, Ranma.
Huh?
But don't you think I'm
not hurt by your actions.
I'm nobody's fool!
[cries]
Hey, wait!
You got to let me explain!
I-- I never thought
you were a fool.
And to think I trusted you.
[cries]
And it's because of you I
closed down my okonomiyaki shop.
I thought you were going
to look after me forever.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Oh, man.
I've got to get myself
out of this mess.
Ukyo?
Huh?
Don't worry.
I'll keep my promise
no matter what.
Do you really mean that?
Mm-hmm.
[whimpers]
[growls]
AKANE: [inaudible screaming]
UKYO (VOICEOVER): A little
tear goes a long way.
[giggles]
[laughs nervously]
Hey.
Almost free and clear.
I better finish my shopping.
I don't have much time to
make Ranma honey's dinner.
Huh?
[whimpers]
Takoyaki here!
Yah!
[groans]
Hiyah!
TAKOYAKI MAKER: Uh, excuse me?
Would you back off?
I'm almost done.
TAKOYAKI MAKER:
Sure, take your time.
Hit the road!
I do this for a living.
Huh?
Oh no.
[crowd chatters]
UKYO (VOICEOVER): I forgot.
I retired.
CROWD MEMBER: Where's she going?
[crowd chatters]
UKYO (VOICEOVER):
I gave up my career
so that I could spend the
rest of my life with Ranma.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I'm gonna
get Ukyo to dump me, and dump me
right away.
I'll look after
you forever, Ukyo.
UKYO (VOICEOVER): I'm so happy.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
And then I'll be
the worst husband in the world.
UKYO (VOICEOVER): I
can't take it anymore.
I'm leaving, you Ranma.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Yeah, the perfect plan.
[sneezes]
Hey, I must be allergic to her.
So what are you making, Ukyo?
Oh, hey there, Kasumi.
Mm, a little bit of everything.
Everything is so
uniquely shaped, isn't it?
Huh?
I guess I'll fix it.
NABIKI: Akane, aren't you even
going to try to stop Ranma?
I don't think so.
Honestly, I don't
think he's worth it.
Are you sure you won't
regret it later, Akane?
I, uh--
Well, sure, Ranma may
be stupid, wishy-washy,
inconsiderate, and a real jerk.
Huh?
You know, maybe
it's best this way.
[sighs]
UKYO: Everyone!
Dinner's ready!
Wow, who whipped
up all this grub?
You know, Ranma, Ukyo
is a really good cook.
Hm.
OK.
This is a bit extreme,
but I have to do this.
Here goes.
[screams]
I can't eat this crud!
What do you think you're doing?
[gasps]
What in the--
Ranma?
[pants]
[sobs]
I did it.
[chuckles]
AKANE: What do you
think you're doing?
Huh?
Uh, uh.
[chuckles nervously]
It's a good thing we
managed to save the dinner.
I don't have any idea why you
did what you just did, Ranma.
But in my house, I
won't stand for it!
[munching]
Could either of you
please pass me the sauce?
Huh?
Sure.
Here you go, father.
SOUN: Thank you.
[whimpers]
Ahh!
[grunts]
KASUMI: Ukyo?
Huh?
[pants]
Where are my manners?
Sorry.
[groans]
Well, I guess it's
time I try plan B.
[stomach rumbles]
Hey, what's up?
I'm going to go for the big
score at the horse tracks.
I'm selling this
stuff for seed money.
I know you'll probably
want to dump me now
that you know about my
gambling problem, won't you?
(LAUGHING) Oh, if it's money
you need, I'll give it to you,
Ranma.
How much do you need?
[gasps]
[sighs]
I'll go next time.
Well, time for plan C. Mwah.
First, the evidence
of infidelity.
Ranma, what are doing out here?
[screams]
You'll catch cold.
I won't be home tonight.
Where are you going?
Duh, I'm gonna go
see my mistress.
AKANE: (ANGRILY) Who are
you calling your mistress?
[bang]
Ahh!
Hear me out!
You're despicable.
You're trying to get
Ukyo to hate you?
Yeah, and here I thought it
was the perfect plan, too.
You're so stupid.
Hm?
Why don't you just act the
same way as you do around me?
Hm?
You're uncute, unsexy, clumsy,
and built like a brick!
Hold on a minute, Akane.
Have I been hurting
your feelings?
Hm.
Are you saying you
don't like me at all?
Uh, don't be silly.
I was just using
it as an example.
I'm fine, really.
Hm, I thought so.
After all, a dimwit
girl like you--
(ANGRILY) Now go act
that way in front of Ukyo!
[screams]
UKYO (VOICEOVER): If he
thinks he can leave me,
he's got another thing coming.
Hmph!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): OK.
All I gotta do is
pretend Ukyo is Akane.
Yo, Ukyo!
Huh?
Ah!
[grunts]
She must have eaten her sauce.
What you do that for?
Because it's what brought us
together, and together forever.
But why in the world
were you eating it?
Don't you remember when I
told you I spilled your sauce
and made the replacement
with whatever?
It doesn't matter, Ranma.
Ukyo, I never knew that
you felt so strongly--
[screams]
Get on with it, Ranma!
Why are you so
darned wishy-washy?
Um, uh, well, you know.
She's right.
(IN UNISON) Huh?
Who do you want to be with?
Well, uh-- OK, then.
I'll settle this matter.
(IN UNISON) Huh?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Everything
started with this stupid sauce,
and that's how it's gonna end.
R-- Ranma, does this mean--
This is how I'm gonna
make up for this sauce.
[grunts]
[gasping]
[clears throat]
Ranma.
Oh my, no.
[gulps]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[crash]
Ranma!
Is he dead?
[growls]
[groans]
Are those?
They're noodles.
[grunts]
Now what?
Seaweed and bonito.
[grunts]
[whimpers]
Why is she grilling
him like that?
This is a--
Yes, it's a
conditioned response.
KASUMI: Then that means--
That the sauce
is triggering it.
So now that Ranma drank
all that okonomiyaki sauce,
he's like batter
ready to be cooked.
That's not okonomiyaki
you're frying.
Can't you see it's Ranma?
Huh?
Wha-- What am I doing?
She brought out all of
her okonomiyaki utensils.
She even went as far as to
put on her okonomiyaki uniform.
Well, I think she's loopy.
She sure likes to make
okonomiyaki, doesn't she?
I tried to quit
making okonomiyaki,
but I always had this
empty feeling inside.
RANMA: Ukyo.
Huh?
It's OK.
UKYO: Ranma.
When you're making okonomiyaki,
you look the happiest, Ukyo.
[whimpers]
Ukyo?
I'm so sorry, Ranma, for
being a cook before a woman.
Some day, when I'm the
best okonomiyaki chef,
I'll come back for you.
OK, Ramna?
(WEAKLY) OK.
[growls]
And when that time comes,
Akane, we'll settle this.
You can try, but Ranma's
not going anywhere.
Well, until that time,
I'll see you all later.
NABIKI (VOICEOVER):
And so the woman
who devotes her life to making
okonomiyaki, Ukyo Kuonji,
left to continue her training
to become the best okonomiyaki
chef in all of Japan.
[groans]
If anyone else drank that
much sauce, they'd be dead.
NABIKI (VOICEOVER):
Ranma, on the other hand,
is far from recovery.
But he's a tough boy, and it'd
take a lot more than bad sauce
to put him down for long.
[whimpers]
THEME SONG: [sung in japanese]
ANNOUNCER: The matriarch of
the School of Martial Arts Tea
Ceremony has been kidnapped.
What's Santaro going to do?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
the missing matriarch
of martial arts tea.
We'll see you there.