[music playing]
[MUSIC - COCO, "FULL OF
MEMORIES"]
[gong rings three times]
[speaking japanese]
[gong]
NARRATOR: "Enter Ken and
His Copycat Kerchief."
[digital beeping]
RANMA: Ow!
Come on, man!
I thought we'd
already settled this.
-Shut up!
You haven't beat me yet!
[fighting grunts]
-Come on, man, give
it a break, will you?
-Aaahh!
-Oh!
-Hah.
As if we didn't already
know who was going to win.
-Oh yeah?
Rrrr-- we'll just
see about that!
Bakusai Tenketsu!
[camera shutter clicking]
-Huh?
-All right, if
that's the way you
want to play it, Kachu
Tenshin Amaguriken!
Huaaahhhh!
TATEWAKI KUNO: Ranma
Saotome, en garde!
-Hm?
Oh, not again.
-[laughs] Prepare for battle!
-Don't you learn?
-Yahhh!
-Hunh!
[camera shutter clicking]
[fighting grunts]
-Oh, Ranma!
Come on, put this on for me.
-Fat chance, you
sick little pervert!
-Come on, sweetie,
let's see you in it
before gravity takes effect!
[camera shutter clicking]
-Huh?
AKANE: What?
Someone took a picture
while you weren't looking?
-I would practically
bet money on it, Akane.
-Get real, Ranma.
Why in the world would
anyone go to the trouble
of taking secret
pictures of you?
Honestly, you've got
such an ego sometimes.
Don't you get tired of it?
-Hey, is it my fault that
I'm the kind of person
that people are attracted to?
After all, here I am, a
girl only half the time,
and I'm still twice
as cute as you.
Kinda funny, huh?
-Sure.
And it'll even be funnier
if we meet someone
who doesn't think
you're a total jerk!
-Aw, come on, you
know I'm kidding.
-(SINGING) La-la la-la, la.
Gee, you don't say.
-Aw, jeez.
Hey, wait up.
Man, you are so uncute!
-Look who's talking!
-Ohp!
[camera shutter clicking]
-Huh?
Aaah!
There's that click again.
You must have heard it for sure.
-Huh?
Wha?
-Say cheese!
-Cheese.
-Mm.
Now just a-- you're a guy
who's been taking my picture!
Hand over that film!
[camera shutter clicking]
I'll teach you to spy on me!
Rrrr!
Why, you--
--[laughs] You best prepare
yourself for my return,
Ranma Saotome.
OK, then.
And in the meantime, say cheese!
[gasp]
-Come back here!
Nnnghh!
GENMA: I see.
So you suspect he was no
ordinary picture thief then,
eh?
AKANE: Yeah, and as he
left, he swore he'd be back.
RANMA: What I can't figure out
is why is he taking my picture?
AKANE: Good question.
SOUN: Oh!
What'll we do if it turns
out to be Copycat Ken?
-Copycat Ken?
No, anything about the
dreaded Copycat Ken!
-Copycat Ken?
Who the heck is he?
-Don't tell me you've never
heard of Copycat Ken, boy.
The notorious thief and bane
of the greater Tokyo area
who steals your best martial
arts moves from under you
just by taking a photograph?
-Aw, jeez, Pop, why do you
gotta be so melodramatic all
the time, huh?
He's probably just
some loser too stupid
to come up with
moves of his own.
That's all.
-Have it your way.
Copycat Ken'll
win just the same.
-Ranma?
-Uh?
Who's there?
[laughs quietly]
-Ryoga?
So now what do you want?
-Hm!
Take this!
-Unh!
[boom]
-[laughs] Hey, you see that?
Pretty cool, huh?
-Jeez, man, what's
the matter with you?
Did you eat something
bad or something?
Huh?
Ryoga!
Wait a second.
[splash]
Mr. P!
-[laughs] Uh?
[sneezes]
-Aha!
I know it!
You're that Copycat
Ken guy, aren't you?
-[laughs] Bingo!
-Whoa, you copied all Ryoga's
moves, just like Pop said.
-Bingo!
One guess who's
next, Ranma Saotome.
Huah!
-Hmm.
Huh?
-Come on, man.
I'll take care of you like I
took care of that other guy.
Hunh!
[fighting grunts]
-Honestly, he says he's just
running off to the vending
machine and then he ends
up taking half an hour.
RANMA: Rraahhhh!
-Wha?
Ranma, what-- what's going on?
-Don't let him trick you, Akane.
He's that Copycat Ken guy.
-Shut up, jerk!
You're the copycat, not me!
-What did you say?
[fighting grunts]
-I can't tell which one's which.
It's just like Mr. Saotome said.
Not only does Copycat
Ken take the shape
of the person he's
impersonating,
he takes their strength, too.
-Stronger than me?
Yeah, right, I don't think so.
-Funny, I was about
to say the same thing.
-Cheater!
-Fake!
-Look who's talking!
-Fine, then.
If that's the way you want it,
I'll prove who's the real one.
Kachu Tenshin Amaguriken!
-Kachu Tenshin Amaguriken!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
tHIS is impossible.
How the heck can he be copying
the Chestnut Fist technique?
-Hah.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Uh-oh,
why is he laughing?
Unh!
-Ha-ha, you see?
I told you couldn't copy
my secret technique.
-Ranma!
-Akane!
-I can't-- I can't believe he
beat me with my own technique.
Oh.
-Oh, Akane!
-What are you doing?
Come on, let me go!
[squealing]
-Aaahh!
-P-Chan!
SOUN: Now are you ready to
start listening to me, boy?
The true terror of Copycat
Ken lies not in his own power
but in the fact that he turns
your own power against you.
Naturally it goes without
saying that to a martial artist,
there can be no greater defeat.
-I understand that,
but I still don't
see how an imitation can
beat out the real thing.
I-- I mean--
SOUN: Makes you
think, doesn't it?
Ask yourself, boy, how is it you
were defeated by a mere copycat
impostor?
The truth is, you
defeated yourself!
-Excuse me?
I what?
[military music playing]
[fighting grunts]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I
still don't get it.
How could I have lost
to someone like him?
[fighting grunts]
Hey!
Copycat Ken!
Why, you little jerk!
How dare you
interrupt my training!
ALL: We're not!
Copycat Ken is our enemy, too!
-Hah, let me take a wild guess.
He's not just impersonate
Ryoga, but Kuno and Mousse, too?
-As though I could
forget the indignity.
-Hyah!
-Ohh!
-He used my own
attacks against me.
-Fist of the White Swan!
-No self-respecting martial
artist copies someone
else's fighting style!
-Didn't you learn
your Bakusai Tenketsu
by copying in the old ghoul?
-That was different!
-How so?
-Come, come, gentlemen, at ease.
Allow I, Tatewaki Kuno, to
adjudicate this dispute.
We have but one
objective and one enemy.
Can we not join forces, cast
aside our own petty rivalries,
and train together for
our own greater good?
-I got no real problem with it.
-The more of us that there
are, the easier that it'll
be to train.
-It'll be like a
temporary truce.
-Very well.
We're in agreement.
Gentlemen, we have nothing
to fear but fear itself.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I got
a bad feeling about this.
KUNO: Come, gentlemen,
there's no time to lose.
Find a partner and let
the training begin!
[music playing]
-Here I come!
-Yahhhh!
[fighting grunts]
-Are you ready for this?
-En garde, Monsieur Mousse!
[fighting grunts]
-You think you can beat me?
We'll see about that.
-It ain't over till it's over!
[fighting grunts]
KUNO: Stay still, will you?
I can't practice.
MOUSSE: You stay still!
How would you like this?
[fighting grunts]
-Why, you quackhead!
-How dare you stomp the head
of Tatewaki Kuno, miscreant!
[fighting grunts]
-Why aren't I surprised?
I shoulda-- known!
MOUSSE: Oh no you don't.
-Come on, you guys, cut it out!
Oh!
-Why you--!
-Hey, guys, cut it out already!
[fighting grunts]
-Why you--!
-We're supposed to cooperate!
Dahh!
OK, you jerks, now
you've done it!
If you want me to fight
back for real, you got it!
[music playing]
[birds calling in distance]
[all breathing heavily]
-[groans] I'm so hungry!
-Somebody help me.
-If only there was
something for us to eat.
-Ah.
Huh?
-Huh?
-Something smells good!
[all moan appreciatively]
KUNO: Mmm, how stimulating
to the appetite
is the aroma of a
well-cooked cut of beef
to the nostrils of an athlete.
-Oh, ho, gee, Kuno,
don't mind if we do.
Aaah!
What did you--
-Do that for?
-Mm.
Would that I might
share my good fortune
with you, but in concern
for your well-being,
I must, in good
conscience, refrain.
The effect of rich
European cuisine
upon an unrefined palate
is unsalutory at best.
[laughs]
-I thought we were
supposed to be comrades!
-Share and share alike!
-Yeah, what he said!
-Pearls before swine,
my dear gentlemen.
Pearls before swine.
Speaking of which, ahh!
-No, thanks!
What do we look like to
you, a bunch of pigs?
Huh?
[ryoga and mousse chowing down]
-Come on, you guys,
what are you doing?
BOTH: We're eating!
-Yahhh!
RYOGA: I got dibs on the salad!
KUNO: Unhand that
lettuce, you fiend!
MOUSSE: No fair!
RANMA: Hey, you guys,
save some for me!
[fighting grunts]
MOUSSE: Back off!
It's mine!
KUNO: Don't you
have any manners?
RANMA: You better
not eat it all!
MOUSSE: Hey, that's mine!
RYOGA: Has anyone seen
the salad dressing?
MOUSSE: Let go of that steak!
RYOGA: You're all
a bunch of pigs!
RANMA: Come on, you guys!
[girl gasps]
GIRL: Oh!
It's that dirty old man again!
[girls screaming]
-Ooh!
Real cotton!
[cackles] How sweet?
-[cackles] How sweet!
-What?
[cackles]
-[cackles]
-Now I get it.
You're that Copycat
Ken guy, aren'tcha?
-Bingo!
-So you think you're ready for
the big league then, are ya?
Ha!
-What's going on here?
-Hey, look, there's two
of the little perverts.
-Yeah, but which one is which?
-Well, try this.
Now for something
a little harder?
All right, well, try this.
And this.
BOTH: Ow!
Oh!
-Why don't you try this?
BOTH: Oh, but it's his fault.
He's the one who started it.
-So now you're impersonating
Grandfather Happosai, huh?
BOTH: Yes!
Oh, yeah! [inaudible]
cry in your-- aaahh!
-Dry up and die,
the both of you!
-Now look what you've done!
You've gone and made my poor,
sweet Akane get mad at me!
Take this!
Founding School of Anything Goes
Martial Arts Happo Fire-Burst!
Yahh!
[boom]
OK, I'll say it.
You're pretty good.
I'll bet you can't
do this, though.
-Wha--?
HAPPOSAI: Breathe it and weep.
Try and match that
for realism, huh?
Look at that lace.
Look at that bow.
Hah!
I'd like to see
you try and imitate
that one, Mr.
Monkey-See, Monkey-Do.
-I'm not worthy!
-Not everyone can be a
master of perversion.
Don't let it bother you, kid.
-Please, sir.
Please make me your disciple!
-Mm.
You may call me Master.
-Thank you, Master!
AKANE: [screams]
Get out of here!
[both cackling]
BOTH: Kasumi!
[screams]
BOTH: Nabiki!
-I've had it.
You two have got
to do something.
-(WEAKLY) I'm feeling faint.
-[moans]
[both cackling]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ranma.
RANMA: [panting]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Geez, a guy could
starve to death with
those guys around.
Hey, that's my breakfast!
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
I saw it first!
KUNO (VOICEOVER): This
is all the cash I have!
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER):
Oh, no you don't!
-You jerks!
I hope you all starve to death!
Anybody home?
-Ranma!
Oh, Ranma, I'm so
glad you're back home.
-(STAMMERING) Well,
l-let go of me!
AKANE: Ranma!
-Akane?
Then-- then you're-- aahhhh!
Copycat Ken, it's you!
-Bingo!
What's the matter?
You didn't think I knew
how to impersonate a girl?
Aaah!
-Ranma, now's your big chance
to use your new training!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Uh-oh.
We spent so much time
fighting, we never
got around to training!
-Nyah, nyah!
I thought you ran away
from me, you chicken!
-Hah!
Yeah, right!
The day Ranma Saotome runs
away from a dumb copycat
like you is the day he stops
being a martial artist!
[fighting grunts]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): His
training did him good!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
I thought I was only
fighting with those guys,
but really I was training!
-Take that, you copycat!
-Watch this, show-off!
Huah!
Transform!
Aha!
Bakusai Tenketsu!
Yyaaahh!
-Nnngh!
-Or maybe you'd like this one!
Fist of the White Swan!
-Unh!
-Hyyyahh!
Ranma Saotome, en garde!
Ohhhaaahh!
-Hah!
Looks like you picked the
wrong guy to turn into.
-You haven't beaten me yet!
How's this?
[cackles] Let's see how
you do against your master!
-Jeez, you even
turn into the freak?
RANMA: Ranma!
Here's some water!
[splash]
[sighs appreciatively]
-You're just like him, ain'tcha?
-Uh, my hand just
kinda went there.
-I still don't want you on me!
-How dare you strike
a poor little old man!
-Aaah!
-Happo Fire-Burst!
-Ow!
Ah!
Ow!
[boom]
-Jeez, you didn't
have to go that far.
So, who's next?
-Ta-dah!
Hah!
Come on, pal, what the
heck are you waiting for?
What's the matter?
Afraid I'll turn your Chestnut
Fist against you again?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Great.
Now what'll I--
-My boy, the only power he has
over you is what you give him.
The truth is you
defeat yourself.
-He's right.
It never fails to amaze me
when he says something useful.
-Come on.
Come on!
If you won't start this, I will.
Hyah!
[fighting grunts]
Vo: Ranma!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): The mistake
I made was underestimating him.
-Come on.
Come on!
What's the matter?
Am I too much for you?
Running away, eh?
Huh?
-Ranma!
-The Chestnut Fist is a lot
more than just speed and power.
It's also about the amount
of soul you put into it.
-Uh?
-So how's about now I give
you a taste of the real thing?
Kachu Tenshin Amaguriken!
Aaaahhh!
-Aaaahhh!
[gasp]
BOTH: Mmmm.
-Aaaaaahhhh!
Unh!
-Ranma, you did it!
By concentrating your focus
on nothing but fighting,
you were able to produce
a technique that even
Copycat Ken couldn't imitate.
It just goes to show
that a copy's a copy,
but the real thing's authentic.
-That's our Ranma, all right.
-Shucks, t'weren't nothing!
[grunting ]
-Huh?
--[grunting] It's a little
early to be celebrating.
-Oh, jeez, what's
the matter with you?
Don't you ever quit?
-I'll show you the most
terrifying copycat trick yet!
[fighting grunts] Ta-dah!
[all gasp]
-But that's incredible!
-Hm.
I'm not sure "incredible"
is the word for it.
-Ahhh!
Oh, no!
Hey!
Gah!
-If you ask me,
it's his own fault.
-Help!
Please!
Please, stop!
Please stop me!
Help!
Please stop!
Please!
[music - coco, "present"]
NARRATOR: Wait, wait!
You get splashed with cold water
but you don't turn into a girl?
And what does Ryoga's
soap have to do with it?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Ryoga's Miracle Cure!
Hand Over That Soap."
We'll see you there.