[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): "Enter
Ryoga, The Eternal Lost Boy."
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): I don't
think that this is the place,
but I better go
and check anyway.
-Agh!
This is a disaster!
A wild boar is coming!
[screaming] :
-Lordy, what are we gonna do?
-That boar's gonna tear
this here village to pieces!
Huh?
Hey, you!
Look out!
Run for it!
Huh?
-He stopped that wild boar
with a bamboo umbrella!
-Well, hot damn.
-He's dang strong!
-Do you reckon he's human?
-Do y'all do the martial
arts or something?
-Hey, y'all OK?
Huh?
-Tell me, where is
Furinkan High School?
-Furinkan High School?
Hm.
Hey, don't you know?
That there's a map of Tokyo.
-Well, of course.
The school's around
here somewhere.
-But this here's Shikoku.
-Shikoku?
Very well.
Goodbye.
-What was that?
-This is a battle of
honor between men.
You won't hide
from me any longer.
Just you wait, Ranma Saotome!
NABIKI: Ranma, you
come back here!
Come back here, I said!
-No way.
Uh-uh.
Absolutely not.
-You can't keep running around
the house half-naked, you know?
-I'm a guy, OK?
There's no way I'm gonna let
you dress me up like a girl.
So forget it!
-But all your clothes
are in the wash.
It's only for a
little while, Ranma.
-I'm sorry, Ranma.
-Let me go draw you a nice bath.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
There's no way. .
-Listen, Ranma.
Remember, you're a
guest in our house.
-Uh.
-Your hot baths are heating
us out of house and home.
We can't afford to
pay the gas bills.
You see what I'm saying?
-Yeah.
-OK.
So you'll wear this, right?
-OK
NABIKI: I think not, Kasumi.
KASUMI: But the frills
on this one are so sweet.
-I don't know.
I really think this
one is much better.
-But--
-Kasumi, you've
gotta be kidding.
-Hey, you guys.
Why does Ranma have to
borrow my clothes anyway?
-Forget it.
I ain't wearing no skirt.
No way!
-Look at that.
It's a perfect fit.
-Well?
-It's too tight.
Look at this.
It pinches my chest.
-What about the waist?
-Too baggy.
-Uh-oh.
-Ahh!
Die, Ranma!
RANMA: Hey, cut it out, stupid!
NABIKI: Girls, girls.
Let's not fight.
RANMA: I told you.
I'm a guy!
-Furinkan High School?
This here ain't Tokyo, boy.
-This wouldn't be Hokkaido?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Why?
Why can't I ever
get where I'm going?
What's wrong with me?
-That there road there,
boy, goes straight
to the Seikan Tunnel
just up the way.
Now if you really
wanna go to Tokyo,
y'all gotta go straight
down that there road.
-Go straight, you say?
-Yes, sir.
Straight as the
crow flies, you bet.
-Thanks for your help!
-Y'all come back now, you hear?
-Straight it is!
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): I can do it!
I can make it to Tokyo!
Gotta get to Tokyo.
[groaning]
-Just you wait, Ranma!
AKANE: Just you wait, Ranma!
RANMA: No way.
Leave me alone!
-Stop running!
-Hold it a minute!
-Cut it out!
-Give it up, Saotome!
-Wait!
I told you I'm a guy!
-Who-- Whose crackpot
idea was that anyway?
-Maybe I'd better
ask for directions.
Where is Furinkan High School?
-Well, howdy there.
I didn't know you
was all still here.
-Sorry to bother you.
-I have a feeling
he'll be back again.
-Uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
-Damn it all!
It seems like I've
been traveling forever.
Why can't I make it to Tokyo?
Ranma Saotome, I will
never allow you to escape!
Just you wait, Ranma!
AKANE: Just you wait, Ranma!
-Which way you heading home?
-I'm going by the store.
Are you gonna come with me?
-Wait up, guys.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Maybe I
should find out where I am.
-Hey, where is
Furinkan High School?
-Huh?
-I said, where is
Furinkan High School?!
Fu-rin-kan High School.
At last, I've-- I've
finally made it.
Tell me I'm not dreaming.
-Mm-hm.
Mm-hm.
-Now tell me where I
can find Ranma Saotome.
-Uh-- Saotome?
-Wait, Ranma!
How dare you!
Come back here, you jerk!
You heard me!
-Ranma, prepare to die!
I found you, Ranma Saotome.
-Ranma.
-So I still you're still good
at running away, Saotome.
-You know this guy?
-I feel as though
I've been waiting
for this moment for
thousands of years.
-Hey.
You do know him?
-Are you still
feigning ignorance?
-Come on.
Do you know him or what?
-Hm.
-What?
You mean you really
don't remember?
-Ah!
-You remember?
-Do you remember?
-Uh--
-I wouldn't want you to
strain your brain, Ranma.
-Enough.
But answer me one
thing, Saotome.
Why didn't you come to fight
me at the appointed time?!
-A fight?
-Oh!
I remember.
You and I were classmates
in junior high, right?
It was uh-- um--
-It's Ryoga Hibiki!
-Yeah, something like that.
Yeah.
-Ryoga Hibiki?
-Long time no see!
Huh?
-Just answer my question.
Tell me!
Why didn't you
come to the fight?
-But I-- Ryoga, I waited
for you at the agreed place
for three days.
-Three days?
-Oh, sure.
You waited three days, but when
I got there on the fourth day,
you already turned tail and ran!
-Fourth day?
-Uh-- Ryoga, Let me
ask you a question.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but the place where
we agreed to meet
for the fight was
the vacant lot behind
your house, right?
So why the heck did I have to
wait for three days for you
to show?
-Don't patronize me!
Do you think I
was just strolling
around Japan for my health?
-So what were you doing?
-Listen, you have absolutely no
idea the troubles I've endured.
Ranma Saotome, today is
the day I shall break you!
-What?
No, this is Yamashima.
-No, you idiot!
This is Asakusa.
Can't you read a map?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Where did
they move that cursed lot?
-What?
Are you nuts?
-You gotta be kidding.
This is Yokohama.
-I finally-- I finally--
finally made it.
Finally made it.
Damn you, Ranma Saotome!
You coward!
-No sense of direction, eh?
Can't read a map.
-What's with this idiot?
Can't find his way anywhere.
-You went and broke
a man to man promise.
And then you dare to run off
to China with your father?
-So let me get this
straight-- you came here
to finish the fight?
-I don't wanna to finish it!
The fight has just begun!
This is revenge!
-Revenge?
Revenge for what?
What did I ever do to you to
make you want revenge on me?
-Don't play dumb with me.
I'm going to destroy
your happiness.
You got it?
-My-- my happiness?
Akane, tell me something.
Am I happy?
-What are you asking me for?
Just what did you do to him.
Tell me, Ranma.
-That's what I'd like to know.
AKANE: This isn't any
old grudge, Ranma.
He's furious!
RANMA: Hm.
-Enough stalling already.
Let's fight, Ranma!
-Watch out!
-Ryoga.
-That's amazing.
-Excuse me for a sec, huh?
Wait here.
-Hey, come back here.
-I'll be back in a sec!
-Ranma.
-Mr. Saotome, you are
a very hard worker.
Oh,, what have you got there?
Ah, some bread.
You're the breadwinner,
aren't you?
-Curry bread?
What the?
Tell me, Saotome.
Now what are you?
-How's about it?
Forgive and forget.
What do you say?
-You mock me.
-Jeez, you're greedy.
OK, here.
Chow Mein bread, croquette
bread, melon bread,
cutlet sandwich, meat
bread, seaweed bread.
Happy now?
I didn't forget anything, did I?
-What do you take me
for, Ranma Saotome?
-Yeah, Ranma.
What do you take him for?
-Hm?
Oh well, I went to an all-boy
junior high school, Akane.
You got no idea what it's like.
Lunchtime was just
like a battlefield.
It was terrible.
-All right, boys.
That's it.
Here it comes, the last
curry bread of the day.
-Gimme some bread, please!
-I got it!
TEACHER: Five bean jam buns.
When these are gone,
there ain't no more.
Who wants 'em?
-How dare you?
Who are you?
-Ranma Saotome.
-Saotome, I will
never forgive you.
You stole my bread!
You lousy thief!
-You were blubbering
over a piece of bread
for crying out loud.
-Oh, shut up.
-But I don't understand.
I mean, bread's not
such a big deal, is it?
-Yeah, that's what
I thought, but--
TEACHER: Smell it
and weep, boys.
The last Chow Mein
bread of the day.
RANMA: And.
TEACHER: The last
croquette bread!
RANMA: And.
TEACHER: The last melon bread!
Cutlet sandwich!
Meat bread!
-Let's see, seaweed
bread, egg bread--
uh-- salad sandwich,
soup bread-- no wait.
There's no such thing.
-Sounds like the straws
that broke the camel's back.
-Yeah, whatever.
-For your information, this
goes far beyond bread, Saotome.
-Does it really?
-Of course it does!
-So what is it now?
-Don't play dumb!
-Tell me what this is all about.
-Because of you,
Saotome, I've seen hell.
-I wish you'd just talk to me
-As if mere words could
convey my suffering.
I missed him.
Ranma, where are you?!
Ranma!
Where are you?!
-Now where did he go to?
Is he lost?
-Ranma!
where are you?
Where did you go?
Hey, watch where
you're-- A-- a panda?
[gulp]
-Now what do we do?
Where did everybody go?
-It seems they've all
gone home, I guess.
-Ranma, where are you?
I better ask for directions.
Where is Furinkan High School?
-Well, y'all came back.
You poor youngin.
-By the looks of it, y'all
must be halfway to starving.
-Uh-huh.
-Listen here.
Why don't y'all
forget about Tokyo,
and stay with us here
in this here village?
-Uh-huh.
-Ugh!
No way!
Out of the question.
Sorry for bothering you!
-That boy could darn well
be this town's first tourist
attraction.
-Uh-huh.
-Curse that Ranma Saotome.
He's fled from me once again.
I'll get you for
sure by next week.
Just you wait!
Ow!
[grunting and groaning]
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Hey,
Ranma, what are you gonna do?
Looks like Ryoga
sent you a challenge,
and he looks so strong.
Doesn't it seem like everyone's
out to hurt you, Ranma?
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
"School Is A Battlefield.
Ranma Versus Ryoga"
See you there.