THEME SONG: (SINGING
IN JAPANESE)
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Back to
the way we were, please!
[groaning]
Ah!
Hey, Mousse, are you OK?
It's still a long way,
so do you want to rest?
I'm sorry, you two.
Go on ahead.
No point in me slowing you down.
I'll catch up with you.
Hey, don't worry about it.
It's just us guys, remember?
Yeah, let's not stop and
maybe we'll make it to the top
by morning.
All right?
BOTH: All right!
You're probably wondering
what the three of us
are doing carrying old oil
drums on our backs, right?
Well, it's a long story that
all started three days ago.
ALL: What the?
The powder of the spring
of the drowned men?
Hey, why would I
lie to you guys?
I'm a salesman.
Then that means--
If we use it--
We'll be cured.
MOUSSE: No more duck.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
No more P-chan.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I
will be a girl again.
So are you interested?
Need a few minutes to decide?
Wait a second.
I remember one time I took this
stuff that was supposed to cure
me, and it only worked once.
[giggling]
I remember.
That was bad medicine.
Trust me.
I guarantee you this
is completely safe.
You don't have to
worry about a thing.
Are you sure?
I'll take one.
That's everything I have.
One?
That's only 30 yen.
RANMA: That should be
enough for all three bags.
I'll give you
everything I've got.
Me too.
You're all incredibly
poor, aren't you?
Well, you boys drive
a hard bargain,
so here's what I'm going to.
Now, I know I'm losing my shirt
here, but they're all yours.
[laughter]
All mine!
I so happy for you.
SALESMAN: it was a
pleasure with you boys.
Thanks a lot.
You too!
SALESMAN: Oh, and
just one more thing.
What is it?
I suppose you want more money.
Not that it's important, but
I should tell you only one
of the three bags
contains the real powder.
I have no idea what's
in the other bags.
ALL: Say what?
[strangling]
RANMA: Why, you dirty--
RYOGA: You cheated us.
We our money.
Wait, I can explain.
Just let me go, and I'll
tell you everything.
Come back here,
you stupid old man!
Ah!
Hiyah!
So as you can see, because
of that idiotic panda
and the psycho young
girl, all the labels
for my spring of
drowned man powder
with some of my other powders
washed off in the river.
And I hope that explains why
I sold them to you so cheap.
What I gave you for 30 yen
is worth at least 3,000 yen.
Uh, well I guess
a deal's a deal.
Ranma!
This is your fault!
Uh-oh.
Ah!
This is important.
Just dissolve the powder
into a tub of hot water
and jump in right away.
You three stop
fighting right now!
[groaning]
At least we know one of the
bags has the real powder in it.
Well, yeah, but we
don't know which one.
All three bags look
exactly the same.
There is no reason to be angry.
You should share the
powder, then nobody loses.
Yeah, I guess so.
At least that way, it
would be fair to everybody.
Yeah, what else can we do?
Just count me out.
What's your problem?
What, do you have
a better idea?
MOUSSE: I don't need you too
because my bag is the one
containing the real powder.
I'm outta here.
Well, what do we do now?
The only thing we
can do, and that's
to see if one of our bags works.
And if that doesn't
work, what do we do then?
Let's not worry about that now.
Let's see if just
maybe Mousse was wrong.
Later.
What now, Ranma?
Well, my powder I
guess, because there's
nothing else I can do.
Ranma.
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER): I'm
sure this is the right bag.
SHAMPOO: Mousse!
Shampoo!
That is the real one?
If you're sure, why don't you
come with Shampoo and try it?
Sh-- Shampoo!
I didn't know that
you cared about me.
[laughter]
[crash]
Why, thank you, Mousse.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Now let's see if it works.
What if he's right?
My sweet Akane
would never love me
if I turned into a
hideous hippopotamus.
SHAMPOO: Ryoga!
Huh?
[crash]
[groan]
Just for me, Ryoga.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I wonder
what the chances are that this
will make me normal again.
It's no use.
I can't take the chance.
Let's not worry about that now.
Let's see if just
maybe Mousse was wrong.
I don't think I
even have a choice.
Pops?
If this powder turns me into a
panda, I'll be even worse off.
I quit.
SOUN: So this is spring
of the drowned man powder?
That or some kind
of powder that'll
turn me into something else.
I've always dreamed of taking a
bath like that once in my life.
Maybe we could all do it.
Are you OK?
But
Kasumi, if we all
did that, we wouldn't
know what we might turn into.
Oh, I realize that,
but wouldn't it
be fun just to throw caution to
the wind and see what happens?
I think you've lost it, Kasumi.
Ranma, why don't you try being
a man for once and test it out?
Yeah, I mean it couldn't
get any worse, could it?
There's no way.
Come on, would you please stop
your complaining and go for it?
I mean really Ranma, what
do you have to lose anyway?
Oh man, would you all
just get off my back?
Why can't I just make
up my mind and do it?
AKANE: Ranma.
Hm?
Yeah?
So what do you want?
Have you decided?
Well, you see, I'm not even
sure I'm confident enough
to take the risk.
On the other hand, I guess I'm
tired of changing into a girl
all the time.
It really doesn't matter.
Even if you turn into
a pig or a duck, that's
OK, because deep down inside
you'll always be Ranma.
Yeah, you're right.
And no matter what happens,
I'll always be your--
SHAMPOO: Ranma!
Shampoo?
Ranma, Shampoo has the
other two bags for you.
Come and I show you.
You're kidding.
Way to go, Shampoo!
Ranma!
Honestly.
Well, here they are.
Man, it sure was nice of Ryoga
and Mousse to them to you.
I told them that Shampoo
wanted Ranma to try it first,
and without saying a word,
they each gave me their pack.
Wow, this is the best
news I've had all day.
Now it's just a
matter of finding out
which one is the real one.
Huh?
Ah!
Now you lose, Ranma!
What did you do that for?
They no belong to you.
Huh?
Hiyah!
Ryoga, now what?
You're a coward, Ranma.
Using Shampoo to do your
dirty work makes me sick.
I have never seen
anything so low.
Wha-- what do you mean?
[giggling]
Shampoo would really love
to stay and chat with you,
but Shampoo still
have deliveries left.
Bye!
Shampoo!
Listen, I've got no idea
what's going on here.
Would somebody please tell me?
Yeah right.
You're a liar!
Wait a sec.
After all this mess,
we're back to square one
because we still don't
know which pack it is.
[gasp]
Yeah, that's true.
OK, I say it's time we all work
together and try and figure out
what powder is in which pack.
I guess so.
All right, that's great.
Now let's all be buds again.
I think we should
do our experiment
where no one can bother us.
I agree.
Like up in the mountains.
Yeah.
It sure is great to be out here
and spend time with you guys.
We've known each
other for a long time,
but we've never really
hung out together.
Yeah.
Come to think of
it, I never really
had any close friends to
hang around with before.
Most of my life
I've always been too
busy training and stuff to ever
go out and meet any new people.
I'm kind of like that too.
As a kid, my family spent a
lot of time away from home,
and I ended up
playing by myself.
Oh man, I never really
realized how pathetic you were.
So why don't you
tell us about you?
Were you happy traveling
around when you were a kid.
I don't know.
We just did a lot
of traveling around.
That's all.
It was really pretty boring.
I wish I remembered something
exciting that happened,
but I can't.
Well, I'm turning in.
BOTH: Good night.
[snoring]
ALL: Which pack holds
the real powder?
[groaning]
Let's wait till morning.
Good idea.
I'm a little tired.
ALL: Good night.
Hey, what's the deal here?
Get these ropes off of me.
We voted you to
be our guinea pig.
Let's see what happens.
BOTH: So, now we know
which is the real pack.
We did it.
We did.
Ah!
[heavy breathing]
Huh?
Just a dream.
Come on, you guys.
Will you untie these ropes.
We voted you to
be our guinea pig.
Let's see what happens.
BOTH: So, now we know
which is the real pack.
We did it.
We did.
Ah!
Huh?
Just a dream.
Come on, you guys.
Would you untie these ropes?
We voted you to
be our guinea pig.
Let's see what happens.
BOTH: So, now we know
which is the real pack.
We did it.
We did.
Ah!
[heavy breathing]
Huh?
What a dream.
[chirping]
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER): I'm
starting to get the feeling
that mine isn't the real power.
RANMA: All right
guys, let's do it.
RYOGA: Yeah.
Look!
A UFO!
Huh?
Wait.
Hey, what do you think
you're doing, Ryoga?
Ah, you thought you'd
try and pull a fast one.
But I didn't!
I saw you.
What are you doing?
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER): Oh no.
Now I get a feeling that my
original drum was the real one.
Which one is it?
I see it again.
BOTH: Huh?
What are you doing?
Would you leave them
where they were, Mousse?
Hey!
Hey.
[heavy breathing]
OK, this is getting us
nowhere, and after all that,
we still don't know which one
has the real powder in it.
You are right.
Let's do it.
This is it, men.
Let's begin.
Ready.
Set.
Go.
Huh?
Oh.
Ah!
[meowing]
[barking]
[whimpering]
Hey guys, I guess that
means mine's the real one.
You don't have to be so smug.
And with all that switching
around, who says that's yours?
How could you!
Hey!
Let me at it!
Come on, you guys.
Would you cut it out?
[gasps]
My drum!
What do you mean your drum?
Wait up!
Oh no you don't!
Ah!
I got it.
Oh no you don't.
What do you think you're doing?
Hey pal, I don't
see your name on it.
There's no way you're
getting away from me now.
Ah!
Would you two give
me some room here?
I was here first, jerk.
Would you two cut it out?
Ah!
Hey, I was here first.
All right, you jerks?
Give me some room,
'cause this is mine.
I don't know what you're--
ALL: Ah!
[screaming]
[laughter]
All right!
I'll never turn
into a pig again!
Shampoo, I'm coming home!
[splash]
Ah, this is just great.
That idiot ripped us off.
[squealing]
[quacking]
Cheater!
Cheater, cheater, cheater!
Ugh, it didn't work.
[quacking]
I so sorry to hear that.
I didn't know we were supposed
to get in the water right
after the powder went in.
That creep who sold
it to us should
have explained it better.
Ranma, you no worry about it.
Besides, everything
is back to normal.
Would anyone like a cup of tea?
What's that?
Now with the latest on
that biological discovery
we go live via satellite.
It's hard to describe
the mayhem, but up here
in the mountains,
there have been
various sightings of
a saber toothed tiger
and, yes, an actual pterodactyl.
Now-- ah!
Ah!
Oh my.
NEWS ANCHOR (ON TV):
This is studio calling.
Are-- are you still there?
Hello?
Can you-- can you hear me.
[gulp]
Oh boy.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): May I
have the envelope please.
The one to carry on the
Saotome school is Ryoga.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," Ryoga
inherits the Saotome school.
We'll see you there.