[theme music]
[speaking japanese]
[screaming]
-Woo hoo hoo.
What a haul, what
a haul, ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha.
-Stop you dirty old man.
-Catch me If you can you
snot-nosed little punk.
-Nobody should have to
put with this every day.
-This makes then pairs
of shorts he stolen?
-Faster girls.
Let's teach him a lesson
he'll never forget.
-What do you say, girls,
same time tomorrow?
-If you live that long.
-Take a hike, pig-tailed boy.
I was talking to Akane
and the others, not you.
-I'm going to make you eat
those words you old freak.
-Toodle-ee.
Running away, huh?
-Final Facedown!
Happosai vs. The Invisible Man.
[squeals]
-Hey ya cutie.
How's about let me treat
you to a cup of tea?
-Ahhh!
-Come on.
[crash]
-What do ya think?
Come on.
-How pathetic.
You're no help to us at all.
-A fiance in name
alone, methinks.
Akane Tendo in dire peril and
Saotome does not but cower.
It's a sad day for
chivalry indeed.
Come, my love.
Make me your true knight.
As Lancelot did come to the
aid of his fair lady Guinevere,
so too shall I.
-Cut it out, I said.
-Come on, girls.
Just one lousy cup of tea.
-Feel the might of Tatewaki
Kuno, oft times known
as the Blue Thunder of Furinkan
High, whose strength is
that of ten and whose heart
is pure as the driven snow.
-Do you mind?
I'm trying to work here.
-Perhaps I shall
smite thee later.
-Ha ha ha.
Anytime chump.
-You coming, Ranma?
-Right behind you.
Wonder what's for dinner.
-Honestly, with dad and
Mr. Saotome out of town,
Happosai just gets more
and more out of control.
-Yeah, you ain't kidding.
What's the matter with
those two jerks anyway?
Every time Happosai
looks at them
cross eyed, they make a
break and run for the border.
-Yeah, they're just
like a couple of kids
running away from home.
If they're not to do
something about how Happosai,
then maybe it's time we did.
-Don't worry.
I'm one step ahead of you.
I've already been
working on a plan to--
-AH!
-Huh?
-What is it?
What's wrong with them?
You OK down there?
-Ew, what do you
think happened to him?
-Ohh, that's harsh.
-Ahh!
-Just hang in there a
little longer, Saotome.
I know you're weak
with hunger, but we
don't dare go back
to the Dojo, no, not
until the Master is ready to
forgive us our trespasses,
even if it is our own home.
-It's the old man.
-And my dad, too.
Grandfather, Happosai and I
have had a good, long talk
about why we musn't bully
those weaker than ourselves.
So please stop running away.
-Maybe you could try
locking them in their rooms.
-I wish you'd stop the
bowing and scraping, Pop.
It don't look good.
-Hm?
-Actually, son the truth is uh--
-Happosai: You don't mind
if I borrow your iron again,
huh Kasumi?
-What do you know?
Ain't you home early?
What's the matter?
You get hungry?
-You're unworthy student
abases himself before you,
oh great and terrible master.
May I say that your're
looking exceptionally spry
this fine day.
-Bleah.
-Does this mean you won't be
giving me any more trouble?
-SOUN TENDO: No, Master.
We're sorry Master.
It'll never happen
again, Master.
-What a bunch of suck ups.
-Little do you know son,
it's not just sucking up.
It's part of our strategy.
-What strategy?
SOUN TENDO: Those
times we left home
without warning, we
weren't just running away,
we were doing it for a reason.
-What reason?
SOUN TENDO: Well, since you ask.
We're talking nothing
less than complete
and utter defeat
of the evil master.
-What was that again?
Nothing less than complete
submission to our master.
-OK, then.
-Why, I can almost
remember it all as
though it were yesterday.
Saotome, I'm so hungry.
If we don't get
something to eat soon,
we're going to die out here.
-You're right, Soun Tendo.
Maybe we can challenge
that Dojo up ahead
and get some food money.
BOTH: This is a challenge.
Open up.
SOUN TENDO: It was as
though destiny itself
had guided us to his door.
Arriving in the Dojo
of Master Chingensai
was a blessing from the gods.
-Huh, don't get many
visitors out in these parts.
Well, boys, what
are you waiting for.
If you're going to
come at me, come at me.
BOTH: OK, we'll be right there.
-We'd better double team
him just in case, eh Tendo?
-OK.
Chingensai, super
secret special attack.
BOTH: What?
-Now you see me, now you don't.
-Whoa.
Oooh. [crash]
SOUN TENDO: After we came
to, Master Chingensai
told us his technique was a
small part of the skills he'd
acquired as a member of a secret
society of Chinese assassins
dating back over 3,000 years.
It should go without saying
that even here in Japan
with our own proud
ninja tradition,
Master Chingensai's secret
ninja tricks were without equal.
Naturally we begged
for the privilege
of becoming his disciples, and
soon began the long process
of self purification
to make ourselves
worthy enough to study
at his venerable feet.
Sometimes he'd have us sumo
wrestle the local wildlife.
Other times, we'd work on
our strength exercises.
The training was very
difficult, wasn't it Saotome?
-Ninja tricks, huh?
-RIght.
-The time has come to put those
ninja tricks to use and throw
down the evil master
once and for--
-Soun, Genma, how's
about the three of us
throw down a couple of drinks?
[laughing]
-Looks like you boys picked up
a few new tricks along the way
this time, huh?
-Nonsense Master, nonsense.
Why the student's only
as good as the master,
or so I always say.
Here, Master.
Have a drink.
Kasumi, the Master's not
getting any younger you know.
KASUMI: I'm coming.
-What ninja tricks?
I don't see any.
-Yeah, unless he means a new
way to suck up or something.
-Son, It's not sucking
up, it's strategy.
One, all things come
to he who waits.
[laughing]
-We'll be waiting a while.
-No kidding.
-Super secret ninja trick
number two, to fool your enemy,
it's first necessary
to fool your friends.
[laughing]
RANMA: The only one
he's fooling is himself.
-Super secret ninja
trick number three,
blessed is he who
expects nothing,
for he shall never
be disappointed.
-Now I'm confused.
-And you weren't before now.
SOUN TENDO: Go Master, go.
There he is, the
best master in Japan.
-Well boys, I'm off to work.
-Please be careful
out there, Master.
We'll be praying for
your safe return, Master.
HAPPOSAI: Ha ha, ha, ha.
Whoo, ha ha ha.
[doorslam]
-Super secret ninja
trick number four,
don't fix it if it ain't broke.
-Um hmm.
-So much for their
so-called strategy.
What a laugh.
-Last night was a new
low, even for them.
-Hey it's like you
said before, Akane.
If those two suck
ups ain't going
to put a stop to the old
freak, then maybe we should.
So you remember the plan?
I'll distract them
and then you--
AKANE: Don't worry
just leave it to me.
-Aah!
-Here he comes.
-Ha ha ha.
Ooh, hoo, hoo.
Woo.
How sweet.
-Sucker.
Hand them over, pervert.
-What are you doing?
It's made of paper.
Why, how dare you
fool an old man
with a paper bra
trick like that.
Give me back my
collection this instant.
-Mah.
-Why you little puke.
You won't get away with this.
Give it back.
Well give me back my precious.
RANMA: Ha, ha.
Make me, gramps.
HAPPOSAI: Oh, give it back.
That's it.
Look what you're going make me--
RANMA: Make you what?
HAPPOSAI: Make me cry.
RANMA: Cut it out.
No fair for you to start crying.
-Wait, I'm not ready yet.
HAPPOSAI: I'll teach you to
mess with me, you little punk.
Give me back my collection
this instant or I'll--
-Huh?
-I yi, yi.
I never knew--
-Never knew what?
-I never knew you shared my
enthusiasm for underwear.
AKANE: Dry up and die, you.
Honestly, shared his
enthusiasm for underwear.
Like I'd want to share anything
with that little creep.
-Man, for a runt,
he sure hits hard.
Did you do it?
-Yeah, I think so.
But do you really think your
plan's going to work Ranma.
-Trust me, Akane.
[music playing]
-How sweet it is.
Once again I've managed to
score myself some top quality
merchandise.
When it comes to
lacy under things,
only the very finest will do.
Like these frilly
undies, for example.
[coughing] Oh, Hey.
So now what did I do?
-Ha, sorry to disappoint
you gramps, but them undies
ain't undies at all.
They're jock straps from
the guys rugby team.
-What about these?
Some, some cuties leotard from
the gymnastics team, right?
RANMA: Close.
How about a member of
the wrestling team?
The these.
This would have to be
a sash from some guy--
RANMA: Sumo outfit.
Yeah, you've got it.
And the best part
is none of them
have been washed in a week.
Check it out, Saotome's
school of anything
goes martial arts final
attack, the terrifying men musk
project.
-Ha, ha, ha ha, ha.
-That was cruel.
Is it all guy's
underwear, all of it?
Oh, what have you done with it?
-With what?
The undies that were in there?
Gave them back, that's what.
-You won't get away with this.
Oh, dear, I'm suddenly dizzy.
I gotta go.
RANMA: Let's finish him off.
AKANE: My pleasure.
-Hey, freak.
What happened your dizzy spell?
You little--
-Hey, dizzy or not,
it's going to take
more than some
little punk like you
to-- it was the smell
of those underwear.
-Who would've thought
the stinky little goat
would get so grossed out by
a pair of some stinky guys
underwear.
AKANE: Ranma, he's
stopped moving.
-Serves the little
pervert right.
-Grandfather Happosai,
please I'm worried about you.
-Akane, help me.
I can't--
RANMA: Akane not this time.
Akane only let you get
away with that junk
because she feels sorry for you.
But I ain't got that problem
so you better start shaping up
or you're going to regret it.
-No more stealing, you got it?
-What've I ever done
to deserve this?
If I can't steal women's
undies, or look up their skirts,
or grab a girlies,
you might as well
kill me and get it over with.
[laughing]
-Dad?
-Hello, children.
We know you must be
wondering by now why
we weren't here to help you
bring the Master to justice.
But please don't think
it's because we don't care
or that we don't have complete
faith in your abilities.
No, it's more a matter
of a overall strategy
as in uh-- Help me
out here, Saotome.
[grunting]
SOUN TENDO: Enough talking.
Let's finish off the
Master, and be done with it.
-Why, you ungrateful little--
-Jeez, I think even a five
year old could finish up
the freak at this point.
SOUN TENDO: Super Secret
Ninja Trick Number
Five, if it is broke, make
sure it stays that way.
-Good thing I
brought this along.
All I need is a little of this
baby and I'll be back to myself
in no time.
Close thing too.
Woo.
For a while there I
thought I was a goner.
Ha ha, ha.
SOUN TENDO: That's
our Master, all right.
-There you go.
Suck it up again.
-Ohh, can't I just keep one?
-I said no stealing, remember?
Or have you forgotten all ready?
-Please Akane, please.
-She said no, and she means no.
-Oh, I feel the
dizzies coming on.
-Guess that bra
didn't last long.
-Behold, knowing that
the best place to hide
is in plain sight
in the Chingensai
school of martial arts,
even kitchen items
become deadly weapons.
-Take these whirling
blades for instance.
I gotta a couple of tricks
of my own up my sleeve.
Happo fire.
-Don't look!
SOUN TENDO: Hungry for
more punishment, Master?
Have some pot sticker bombs.
-Pot sticker bombs, huh?
-Now why didn't I think of that?
Why?
Why are you all picking
on me like this?
-Through 3,000 years
of Chinese history,
behold an invisibility
technique so deadly
even the assassins
of the Chingensai
school of martial arts
couldn't master it.
Now you see us,
and know you don't.
-Ranma, they--
-They d-- disappeared.
HAPPOSAI: When did those bozos
learn that dangerous technique.
Personally I'd rather
stick to the basics,
you know, things that I do best.
AKANE: Now it's your
turn to disappear.
HAPPOSAI: I'm back.
Thanks.
I needed that.
-I guess grabbing at you
brought the old freak back
from the dead, Akane.
-Bingo.
-How dare you use
me as a battery.
SOUN TENDO: I can breathe again.
I knew it.
-You're our last hope, Saotome.
I'm counting on you.
HAPPOSAI: Come out, come
out, wherever you are.
-Hiding yourself in the
dirt with a hand trowel
is not what I would call
an invisibility technique.
-Hey, I did the
best I could, OK.
Do you think it was easy
to dig a trench this large.
It took me most of the week.
I tried didn't I?
Isn't that what counts?
-It makes me sick
to even look at you.
How dare you call
yourself my disciple.
-Hey, looking at it you makes
me sick, but am I complaining?
Ahh.
-Why you little--
-Happo fire burn.
No mercy.
-Come here you little freak.
-Ranma.
-Hey, thanks.
AKANE: Ranma.
SOUN TENDO: Good job, son.
-What the-- The freak's gone.
-He's what?
-Saotome, that total
submission routine
isn't going to get
you out of this one.
-Quit that bowing and scraping.
-Ranma, over there.
RANMA: We got you now, freak.
Give it up.
-You've caught be
fair and square.
As you said before,
the student's
only as good the
master and I guess
there's nothing else
I can teach you.
Before I go, allow
me to share with you
one last ultimate
technique as a parting gift
before I make my way
into the next dimension.
-Ultimate technique?
-Next dimension?
-Now you see me
and now you don't.
-He really did disappear.
-And here I thought he
was just making it up.
HAPPOSAI: Anything
goes founding school
of martial arts
ultimate technique,
extra-dimensional warp.
By becoming one with
your surroundings,
you become impossible to attack.
Are you two following all this.
-Go on, Master.
We're listening.
HAPPOSAI: On your knees, worms.
Frankly I'd heard
that you boys would
think that I didn't have a few
disappearing tricks of my own.
-We're sorry, Master.
Please, Master can you ever
forgive our doubting you?
Please take pity on us, and
grant us a merciful death.
HAPPOSAI: I'll agree
that you're pathetic,
but if you think you're
groveling your way out
of this one, you've got
another thing coming.
-If we can't see him
we can't attack him,
and that means we can only--
Please, Master, please.
We're not worthy.
HAPPOSAI: You can
sure say that again.
Ha, ha, ha.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't my own
disciples, Sohn and Genma.
I'd recognize that
crying voice anywhere.
I know that voice.
-Master Chingensai.
-Master Chingensai?
SOUN TENDO: It's him, he's come
to save us, good old Master
Chingensai.
CHINGENSAI: Ha, fat chance.
Ha.
You got that right.
You'd think these two
would've figured out
by now that the
now you see me, now
you don't technique's
nothing more
than a cheap trick,
a silly bit of razzle
dazzle designed to
frighten the locals
and impress gullible
martial art students.
Come and save them,
huh, what a laugh.
Sure it's impossible
to attack someone
whose using the technique,
but you can't attack either,
so it kind of balances out.
-I get it.
If you're invisible,
you can't fight, right?
Master Chingensai.
-Hi ya.
Don't tell me you didn't know
that the now you see me now
you don't technique
was developed
to spy into girls locker rooms.
-Bingo.
The same thing goes for
the extra dimensional warp.
Hey, there are Chingensai.
How's it going?
-Oh, I'm hanging in there.
-How are you?
-How long has it been any way?
-Jeez, I don't know.
Let's see, January,
February, March--
I don't know what
it's been too long.
-We sure had some great
times together, remember?
-We even ate our rice out
of the same pot, remember?
-Don't tell me, those
two trained together?
-So, the master they
ran away to study under
turns out to be a friend of
the master they ran away from.
Must be a weird kind
of fate or something.
-And not only that
there's a college dorm
right near my dojo.
-Really?
-And the best part
is, you can see right
into the bathing area.
-Let's go.
What are we waiting for?
Sohn, Genma.
-Yes, Master.
-Stop groveling
and give us a lift.
-Right away, Master.
RANMA: Yet another pervert
rears it's ugly head.
AKANE: I guess there's
no escaping fate, huh?
[music playing]
-Oh, come on, upper
classman Kuno,
stop picking on poor
Susuki like that.
Now look what you've done.
You've made him
run away from home.
Next time on Ranma one half, Les
Miserable of the Kuno Estate.
We'll see you there.