NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the anything
goes school of martial arts.
And here's Akane of
Tendo Training Hall.
AKANE: What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by they're
loving parents.
RANMA: I didn't ask for this.
AKANE: Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
RANMA: What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma's
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
[thunder]
Sleep.
Yes.
Sleep on good people of Japan.
For a greater evil than you have
ever known is about to awake.
[menacing laughter]
Enter Happosai,
the lustful lecher.
-Nothing like spring
cleaning, eh Saotome?
There.
Spic and span.
-Oh if we could
only straighten out
our children as
easy as this, eh?
-We'd end their bickering
once and for all, wouldn't we?
-You bet.
Let this dojo be our witness.
Everything we do, we
do for their sake.
[crash]
-The alter.
An omen.
-Alter goes smack,
demon comes back.
-Demon?
Ah, you mean that
sleeping demon, don't you?
[laughter]
-Don't tempt fate.
-Just a little humor, Tendo.
-I don't find it funny.
-What could happen?
[uneasy laughter]
[thunder]
[noisy eating]
-More rice father?
Oops.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
-It's just a bowl, Kasumi.
-Saotome.
Bad luck.
-Please.
Rice bowl goes
crack, demon attacks.
You don't believe
those old wives tales?
RANMA: Did you hear
those two last night?
Were they weirder
than usual or what?
-You're right.
Dad's eyes were all
bloodshot this morning.
I don't think you
slept a wink all night.
I wonder what's
got him so worried.
RANMA: Ahhh.
AKANE: I'm going ahead.
-Jeez.
TV didn't say
nothing about rain.
-Here's your pork cutlet again.
-Marvelous.
-Hey, hey come back here!
Thief!
-Hey he left a note.
Calm down.
WAITRESS: Send the
bill to the Tendo Dojo?
-One, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two.
-Akane!
-Achoo!
Am I catching a cold?
I guess I'd better
take a hot bath.
-What's that thing on her?
-Ew.
Gross!
-That's disgusting!
What do we do?
-I can't get it off me.
-Go away.
Leave me alone.
Shoo!
Go away!
-Hey whachoo guys doing?
-Oh, Akane.
-Go away!
-Akane?
-You know this creep, Akane?
-I don't know.
Do I?
-It's me Akane.
You don't remember me?
How cold hearted of you.
[crying]
-Come on.
Give me a minute.
Maybe I'll--
-Too late.
Too late.
I know when I'm not wanted.
Just allow me to have a good
cleansing cry-- in your bosom!
-Yuck.
Hey, where'd the
freak come from?
-Akane!
-You dirty old man.
What do you think you're doing?
-Oh, yeah.
You're Soun Tendo's
daughter, all right.
You're so high spirited.
-Hey, how do you know my father?
-Then you mean you
really are Akane?
-Hey you didn't know who
I was at all, did you?
-No, life sure is
funny that way.
Now ain't it, girlie?
AKANE: I'm home!
RANMA: Yo, Mr. Tendo, the
old goat says he knows you.
Is he lying?
-Heya, nice to see ya.
-Master, thank
heaven you're safe.
-Fit as a fiddle as you can see.
-Did he say master?
-Master I was beginning
to hope-- I mean lose
hope that I'd ever again see
your blessed smiling face.
-Oh, it's great to see you
looking so spry Soun, old boy.
Ho ho, if it isn't
Genma Saotome.
You haven't changed a
bit, now have you Genma?
I'd recognize those beady
little eyes of yours anywhere.
-If I'm going down, I'm
not going alone, you know.
-Just like always.
One for all, and all for one.
-What's wrong here?
-They've been replaced by pods.
SOUN: It all started
10 years or so ago
when we were training
under master Happosai.
- Stop!
Thief!
-You know what to do boys!
-Master, no!
SOUN: We'd wash dishes
for three days and nights
after he'd eat a meal
and leave without paying.
-Oh no you don't!
-Soun, Genma!
Do your stuff!
-Master, please!
SOUN: Sometimes we'd have to
clean dress dummies to pay
for the-- uh-- ladies
unmentionables the master would
borrow .
And then other times--
-Hey!
-Run, boys!
Run!
All in all, it was
extremely rigorous training.
Until one night.
SOUN: Master, here's
the sake we stole
for you from the villagers.
-Ah, well done!
-Ah, that's it.
Drink hearty .
Drink deep, master.
-Hey, keep your snoots
out of my hooch.
-Yes, master.
[snoring]
-Heave ho heave ho heave ho
heave ho heave ho heave ho
heave ho heave ho heave
ho heave ho heave ho.
Yes.
-Saotome!
-Yes, Tendo?
GENMA: As of tonight,
master, we forgive you.
SOUN: May you rest in peace.
-I'd almost forgotten
all about that.
-Oh Kasumi!
More sake for our guest.
-Maybe you should've used a
little more plastic explosives.
-Well it ain't human, I tell ya.
-Yes, right here.
-It's your own fault
for not finishing me off
when you had the chance.
-He's got a point.
-Quite right.
-But again it's still
not too late, is it?
-I've got the sake.
-Just kidding, master.
It was-- it was all a joke.
-Yes, but of course it was!
HAPPOSAI: Come on.
I was young once.
I know what it's like.
But I didn't come here for
revenge, so you two can relax.
The truth is, boys, I'm
not getting any younger,
and it's high time I
pick myself an heir.
It's about time one of you
two volunteer to take over
the anything goes school
of martial arts and then--
and just where do you
think you two are going?
-I just recalled
I'm moving to China.
-Yeah, I'm with him.
-You guys are so pathetic.
I can't believe you're letting
this old fool scare you
like that.
-Here master.
Why don't you take
this one for your heir?
I'll sign all my parental
rights over to you.
I know he's not much to look
at, but he cleans up nice.
-How could you?
My goodness.
A beautiful young
girl like that?
She'd never survive
the training.
Ahh that's hot!
-Don't worry master.
As you can see, he's
also a healthy young man.
-He's what?
-You dirty old man!
-Well now, if he's boy
that's a whole other story.
OK, I suppose he'll have
to do, at least for now.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
That old pervert.
Take over as his heir?
Yeah, right.
I'd rather take up
gardening or basket weaving,
or-- [gargles] he
can find a new--
-Good morning!
-And what's so good
about it, you old freak?
Hey!
Where'd he?
OK.
You want a fight?
You got one.
-Ah, how round.
How firm.
How fully packed.
RANMA: Do you know how
disgusting you are?
-My this tea is very fine today.
-It's the best I've had
in at least 10 years.
-And we owe it all to Ranma.
-Get off of me I said!
-I've got to admit
the boy's really
come through for me this time.
I guess I'm not such poor
father after all, eh Tendo?
-Wild animals could've raised
me better than you did.
AKANE: More rice please.
KESUMI: Here you go.
Would you pass the soy sauce?
-I like you so much
better as a girl.
The world is full
of too many boys.
Who needs 'em.
-That's my fried egg.
-If you don't change
back soon, things
could get ugly around here.
-Look you, tell us what you
came for and then get out.
-Ah what is that?
-It's you're
reward, sugar cakes.
My heir can't be seen in
some ratty old training bra,
now can she?
-Who do you think
you're talking to, huh?
-You mean you don't like it?
Do you know how much
that thing cost?
The sales girl even
modeled it for me.
Akane couldn't even hope
to fill those laces.
-Well aren't you lucky, son.
It appears that the
master has taken
a personal interest
in your welfare.
-Com one, Ranma.
Don't be such a poor sport.
He's perfectly harmless.
-Right, you think so.
Let's see how
harmless you think he
is when he's grabbing
at your chest.
[screams]
-Ranma, where are you?
You forgot your bra.
-That's it.
Somebody's got to put a stop
to that crazy old freak.
-Ranma!
Ranma!
Ni hao, I ran.
-I ran.
I ran.
-How dare you touch
chest of amazon girl.
Only fiance have
permission to do that.
My grandmother!
-Shampoo, you best
leave this one to me.
An old goat like you
chasing after young girls.
You ought to be
ashamed of yourself.
-Whoa, it's the
ghoul of the Amazons
versus the freak of
nature in an anything
goes fight to the finish.
This I gotta see.
-You get him, great grandmother.
-Oh, doesn't that
look sweet on you.
Those super bras are really
something, aren't they?
They even make an old crone
like you look like a teenager.
Good luck.
-I tell you that freak
just ain't human.
-He is good.
Son-in-law, I would not tangle
with that one if I were you.
Come along, Shampoo.
-Bye bye.
See you later.
-That old ghoul, she's just
trying to scare me, that's all.
Look you.
-Hey there, sexy.
Aren't you forgetting something?
-Shut up!
-Why can't you be reasonable?
Now you're really making me mad.
-Aha, this a challenge?
-Yeah, you got it old man.
-I'm waiting.
-Here's the deal, freak.
If you lose, you quit
bothering me, OK?
-And if you lose, you give
me a little fashion show.
What do you say?
-Come on.
Don't you ever give up?
-Hold your horses , sonny boy.
I'll let you know when
it's time for us to fight.
-I'll be looking forward to it.
-So where's the freak?
Do you think he got
scared and ran off?
-You sure about this, Ranma?
-What?
-This is the guy who trained
our fathers, remember?
Even Shampoo's great grandma
was no match for him.
-I can handle that
old freak, got it?
-Hey what's that?
-Stop!
Thief!
Somebody catch him!
RANMA: It's him!
The old freak!
What do you think-- Gym shorts?
-What's the big idea?
You set me up, you freak.
-Is that any way for you
to talk to your master.
We had a deal, and
you're not my master.
-Let's see.
I don't remember an actual deal.
Something about the terms.
-Oh well maybe I can
refresh your memory.
-Ah I remember.
You challenged me.
OK, now you've done it.
-Come on, Ranma!
Come and get me!
-Fight me like a man,
you little freak.
-What's in it for me?
-Excuse me?
-Is it so unreasonable?
All I ask is that you change
into a girl a wear this?
-You give me that!
-Ah you're no fun.
-Get back here.
-Catch me if you can, Ranma.
-You little, coward.
-Wait up, you little--
-What do you think you're doing?
-Is enjoying a duel so wrong?
-You call this a duel?
-It's not my fault.
Don't look at me.
If Ranma would just be
reasonable and put the bra on,
then I'd be--
-Do you have to say it so loud?
-Is it really such
a big deal, Ranma?
Why don't you just
give him what he wants?
-What?
-After all, it's just a bra.
-See?
What'd I tell ya?
-Listen you, I'm
a guy, and I ain't
wearing no stupid bra
for you, understand?
-Aye, but you're just
afraid you'll lose.
-What did you say?
-If you're not afraid,
then why not agree?
-I'll probably regret
it, but you got a deal.
-So do you promise?
Cross your heart
and hope to die.
If you trip me, I'll cry.
-Will you just shut up and
fight me, you old freak?
Hey, where'd he go?
-Thought I was a goner.
Guess I'll have to get serious.
-Yeah right.
Like you haven't been
serious until now.
-Of course not.
How much fun would it be without
a little dramatic buildup?
-He we appreciate it.
-Oh, you're gonna pay.
-Behold, you are about to
witness one of the world's most
powerful forces, the founding
school of the anything
goes martial arts.
-Wow what a battle aura.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
I-- I can't move.
-Something wrong, Ranma?
AKANE (VOICEOVER): He's
frozen like a deer caught
in the headlights
of an incoming car.
-Ranma, you can do it!
-Do you want it over or under
your clothes, my pretty?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I would
rather die than wear that.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I can't
get through his defense
with the chestnut fist.
GRANDMA (VOICEOVER):
Son-in-law, I would not
tangle with that
one if I were you.
-Despite my impressive
battle aura attack,
you're still ready to fight, eh?
Maybe you're worthy of
fighting me after all.
Ranma!
Prepare yourself!
-One, two, one, two, one,
two, one, two, one, two, one,
two, one, two.
-He-- he disappeared.
-Ranma!
Are you OK?
-Well he's not your
average dirty old man.
-But why did he
run off like that?
I thought you wanted to see
you in that bra so badly.
I don't understand it.
-Like I said, he ain't your
ordinary dirty old man.
[screams]
-Get off me you-- you pervert.
-Hey, I threw a challenge
match to follow you in here.
The least you could do is
show me a little gratitude.
Now come one girls.
-He's an extraordinary
dirty old man.
-He's something else all right.
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Oh gross, Ranma.
I thought only your
body was perverted.
You mean your mind is sick too?
What do you mean there's spring
of drown man beneath locker
room?
Next time on Ranma 1/2, assault
on the girls locker room.
See you there.