[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I
don't understand why,
but every time summer
comes, I get depressed.
-OK class, it's time to
announce this year's class
representative.
And I've decided on Akane
Tendo to represent us
at the regional
swimming tournament.
-With you representing
us, Akane, we can't lose.
-Yeah, I guess you're right.
We can't lose.
-Why didn't she just say no?
What did you say yes for?
You can't even swim.
-How did I know he
was going to pick me?
-This tournament's gonna
be one big disaster.
-Akane, I came as
soon as I heard
the good news, my beloved one.
The vision of you
wearing a swimsuit.
My prayers have been answered.
Until then, my sweet.
-There is no way I am
letting anyone see me
in a bathing suit.
-Excuse me.
I know you can't swim,
Akane, so why don't you
just let me compete for you?
-What a great idea.
I mean, Ukyo is the best
swimmer in the school.
And besides, she
can be your body
double, if you catch my drift.
-And from what I've
seen in gym class,
she definitely
needs a body double.
[laughing]
-That's it.
I've changed my mind.
Swimming with psychos.
ANNOUNCER: And now
it looks like we're
set for the women's
50 meter freestyle,
representing Furinkan
High in lane number three,
it's Akane Tendo.
In lane number four it's--
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Great.
Now what have I
gotten myself into?
Huh?
-No way, Akane.
Don't do it.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): So
what's up with him?
-Help!
Please!
I can't swim.
-Oh, my.
What have I done?
-Akane!
-Are you OK?
[coughing]
-If you no can swim,
then why you jump in?
That the most stupid
thing me ever see.
-You're the one who
pushed me in, you idiot.
-But me thinking you
know how to swim.
Me sorry.
Is the policy of the school
that no kid cam pass the gym
until they know how to swim.
Me just assume you already know.
-Yeah, right.
You just made that
rule up, didn't you?
-Me just get a great idea.
Me could be giving the
personal swimming lesson.
-Huh?
-Good for you, Akane.
-You'll finally
learn how to swim.
-So you're telling
me the principal's
going to teach you how to swim.
Now this should be interesting.
-Uh, huh.
It'll be great.
Yeah.
Hey, Ranma?
-I can't believe you're
taking lessons from him.
-Because ever since I was
little I wanted to learn how.
Every summer there was one
thing that kept bothering me.
It didn't matter if
I was at the beach
or even if I had a
new bathing suit on.
I'd get so--
-Hey, don't let it get to you.
Even if you are a little,
a little overweight.
-Ahh!
-Star light, star bright,
first star I see tonight.
I wish I may, I
wish I might, learn
how to swim and win
the lousy tournament.
-I still think Ukyo's
idea was better, Akane.
-I want you stay
out of this, Ranma.
Even if I sink like a rock,
I don't want you butting in.
-A rock?
-Therefore we can conclude
that Shakespeare was--
-Excuse me, cretins,
but class is in session.
Make way.
Back.
Move it.
-Hey, baby, how'd you like to
buy on of these for 1,000 yen?
-How dare you?
-This just seems to
get easier every time.
-She was serious
about that rock thing.
-So what does she think
she's doing anyway?
-Lesson number one,
getting into the pool.
-How am I supposed to
learn with this on?
-Oh, to be swimming
with the fishes, Kiki.
But you must be trusting.
Into the pool.
-Huh?
[singing tropical song]
[scream]
-There is a shark in the pool.
-That's right.
Little Kiki wins a kewpie doll.
Is the 20 foot blue shark.
Roaming mainly in
the warm waters,
the blue shark be caught then
be boiled into the delicious
paste be eating by all
peoples of the world.
-Hello!
There's a shark in the pool!
-No be worried.
He be the friend to
come for the visit.
-I'm gone.
-Kiki wait.
If you be leaving now, you
never learn how to swim.
-Huh?
-In the islands,
everybody be learning
to swim with the
rock on their back
and the shark nipping
at their heels.
-I'd say he's nuts.
-Yep.
Certifiable.
-Yes.
I'm beginning to understand.
Oh, principal.
-Take my hand and
let me guide you.
-Why don't you show me first?
-Oh, boy.
-I'd say he's shark bait.
-He's not coming up.
-Maybe he's dead.
-Now what?
-I think I'll just go home.
-Oh, I've got to save him.
-Hey, what does she
think she's doing?
-What?
I thought you were drowning.
Ah!
-Akane!
-No.
If you jump in there, you're
going to turn into a girl.
-Oh, right.
I forgot.
Huh?
-Kiki, Akane, me know you be
coming through to save me.
Hey, Mr. Sharky, is it
time for the dinner?
-Ranma.
-So what do you
think you're doing?
-Hey, you be killing my shark.
-Ranma?
-How dare you be
interfering with me?
-You can't teach her like this.
What you think she is, huh?
Some kind of total
idiot or something?
-Hey, Miss Akane be learning
to swim and me be teaching it.
-Are you nuts?
She's way too much of a
klutz to learn your way.
-Yes, she will.
Yes, she will.
-No, she won't.
No, she won't.
-Ranma.
-Don't worry.
I'm OK.
-I've made up my mind.
Come on.
Let's do it.
That the spirit, Kiki.
-Now we be getting to work.
ANNOUNCER: Your
attention please.
-Huh?
-Nice rubber band he's wearing.
-Uh, the delicate
Akane Tendo is not
suited for swimming
Western style.
Back in the 5th year
of the Kacho Age,
Yashita's fate was
determined by the swimming
ability of his opponent.
-Come on, Kiki, we no be
needing the history lesson.
-Don't you get swimming
is not a sport?
Swimming is a
military art, one that
should be learned from a
master, through discipline
and concentration.
Yield not to false
instructors, Akane Tendo,
but learn from a true
student of the arts.
This guy's the biggest
flake I've ever seen.
-Now you try it, Akane Tendo.
-Kuno, you're embarrassing.
-Aren't you forgetting
something, my love?
In order to marry one
such as I, the bride
must first master
the art of swimming.
-You must be nuts.
Huh?
Ah!
-Look, Ramna.
-Akane's done for.
-Ah!
Oh!
Ah!
-Now you will be
forever in my debt,
once I have saved
you from that beast.
-Look, the palm trees,
straight from the island.
-Ranma!
-Take that!
And that!
Ah!
How dare you break the
sword of Tatewaki Kuno?
-Try this!
-What?
What do I do?
-Nice work.
-How dare you?
Circus work is beneath me.
-Look!
Look!
[scream]
-So, what's your problem?
-Ah!
Oh!
Ah!
-Boy, I didn't know
Kuno could swim so good.
-I can't hold it any longer.
-Ah!
-Oh, getting tired.
-That was a close on, Ranma.
You almost got
caught, didn't you?
-Yeah, thanks, Ukyo.
-Ahh!
-Don't you think it's
about time you quit, Akane?
-Not until I learn.
-Oh, man.
I'll be killed before
you learn to swim, Akane.
-I said, not until I learn, I
think it's time we continue,
Principal.
It be time to take
me beloved Kiki
to the next level
of the learning.
Me call it the swan project.
-Yes, swans.
Like swans on a
crystal clear pond.
-Well, if you ask me, she looks
more like the ugly duckling.
-The best results
in the training
try the latest Indie fashion.
which Big Kahuna designed.
-You made this just for me?
-Uh, huh.
Yes.
To be learning the swan
project, you gotta be one.
-Just for me?
-Oh!
I'm not a swan.
I'm a duck!
You are an idiot!
-It's all a misunderstanding.
-Don't touch me.
Wait a second.
He did this all just for me.
[singing]
-I didn't know.
-Now you be understanding.
-That thing's supposed
to be a bathing suit?
-That's it.
I can't watch anymore.
-Get your Okanomiyaki here.
One at a time.
-What I wouldn't do for one.
-Miss Akane, Go!
-Akane!
Come on.
How do you expect her
to learn like that?
This is completely insane.
-Observe.
Switch on.
-What's happening?
-Hey, hey, look somehow
Akane's able to stay afloat.
-Just like he was talking about.
-Yes, and a graceful
swan at that.
-Yeah, right.
-I'd say she's lost it.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Now what do I do?
-Get your stuffed
polar bears here.
Just 300 yen.
[coughing]
-I was just trying
to help, Akane.
-You nearly gave
me a heart attack.
-Well, then, I guess this means
you're going to pack it in,
right?
-Not on your life.
-Who are you?
-A transfer student?
-I uh, hate to
interrupt but isn't
it time for my next lesson?
-Ah!
Yes, Miss Akane.
Me almost forgot.
Me hope you be ready be ready
for the lesson number two
which me be calling
the mermaid project.
-Good luck.
-Quiet.
He'll hear you.
Ready.
-Let's begin.
Switch on now, please.
-Ah!
Ah!
-Got it girly.
-Me be thinking she had enough.
-Ah!
Keep be in the paddling, Kiki.
Don't worry.
Me be holding.
-Right.
-You could see that one coming.
-Too bad he didn't.
-Where's Akane?
Oh, no.
I don't see her.
Akane!
-Wait for me.
-Oh!
-Thank goodness you be awake.
-What happened to me?
-Me sorry.
-What are you doing here?
-Me try teaching.
But me be failing even though
should be simple, Miss Akane.
-Man, I don't think I've
ever seen him serious before.
-Don't worry about me.
I'm all right.
-Miss Akane.
-Oh, and Ukyo, good
look in the tournament.
-Akane?
-You know, I just realized,
swimming isn't everything.
Even if a tidal wave
hit, I'd still be OK.
Because I'm a good runner and
I'd just jog up Mount Fuji.
-You be sure?
-I'm very sure.
Thanks.
[crying]
-Miss Akane, come back.
-I just wanted to
swim like a swan.
Huh?
Ranma.
-I wanted to make
sure it was really OK.
-Yeah.
yes I--
-Are you just going
to quit and walk away?
Well?
-You can't give up, Akane.
-Huh?
-We won't let you.
-We're right behind
you all the way, Akane.
-100%.
-Really?
-We all be proud of you.
-Thank you, Principal.
-You be ready lesson three?
-Yes.
-This one's the final lesson.
The sure thing
that no be failing.
-Show me, please.
-We use this.
-Oh, boy.
-Slip this on.
Let's go.
-Go for it, Akane.
-One by one, me give up.
-Ah, man.
-We'll never win.
-Her head's too heavy.
-Well, by the looks of it,
at least she has strong legs.
That's it.
ANNOUNCER: It looks like we're
ready for the women's 50 meter
freestyle, Introducing in
lane number one, Akane Tendo.
-Don't you simply adore
Akane's new bathing suit?
-Yeah, it's all the rage
if you like wearing tires.
-Do you really think
she can win this, Ranma?
-Sure.
-Go for it!
ANNOUNCER: We may have a
record-setting race, folks,
with Akane Tendo
pulling up the rear.
Wait a minute.
Akane Tendo is catching up.
Now she's passing the field!
This is unbelievable!
Akane Tendo has taken the lead!
-You be doing it, Miss Akane!
Akane Tendo wins!
-Akane won!
-Way to go, Akane.
-Yeah, but that bathing suit
you're wearing still bites.
-I did it!
I can swim!
[music playing]
NARRATOR: On one
of his journeys,
Ryoga meets up
with a brave girl,
working on her father's
ranch with their cow, Birdy.
Is Ryoga the savior
they've been waiting for?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Ryoga, Run Into the Sunset.
We'll see you there.