[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
Akane, nothing
in this world has hurt
me so much as loving you.
Countless times I've
tried to forget about you,
but without any success.
Now there is only
one thing left to do.
As I cannot forget
you, dear Akane,
as you mean the world to me,
I have made my final decision.
From this day forward,
I refuse to run away.
Instead, I've decided
to put an end to it all.
ANNOUNCER: "Ryoga,
Run Into the Sunset."
[music playing]
AKANE: Ranma, have you noticed
Ryoga isn't around much?
RANMA: Oh, he's probably
just out on another journey.
-Come to think of it, I
haven't seen P-chan either.
-Of course not.
Who do you think feeds
the little porker?
-That's weird.
-Hmm?
-How come we never see
Ryoga and P-chan together?
-It's because they-- because
they-- oh, come on, Akane.
I don't know.
-Hmm?
-Can't we just watch TV?
-Hmm.
-You ain't got the gumption
for being an outlaw, partner.
So I'd think twice before
you ask me to draw.
-Hey, Akane.
I'll bet you Ryoga's
gone out to the old west
to fight for law and order.
-Oh, please.
[music playing]
[gunshots]
-Freeze, partner!
Make one false
move and you'll be
wishing you hadn't
met up with Ryoga.
[mooing]
[music playing]
[scream]
Ha.
[crash]
Huh?
What?
"This cow property
of Farmer Brown."
FARMER BROWN: You killed my cow!
[music playing]
-But, but I didn't know!
-I'm plain tired of city
folk killing my cows!
-Aah!
Would you listen to me.
I didn't kill your cow!
-There's two of us.
I'm sure we can take him, Pa.
-You can do whatever
you want to me, boy.
All I ask is you leave
my daughter alone.
Is that understood?
-Hey, take it easy.
I'm not going to hurt anybody.
Hey!
Ugh.
-Huh?
Well, I guess I showed him.
-You sure showed him good, Pa.
[laughter]
[music playing]
-Hey, let me go!
-I would surely love
to oblige you, son.
However, that just
ain't gonna happen.
I got big plans for ya, 'cause
you's coming back to the ranch
to work for me.
Right, honey?
-We don't get too many
good-lookin' hired hands.
-Hmm?
[approaching vehicle]
-No!
It's them again!
Hurry up, Gertie!
Run like the wind!
-Come on, boys.
Let's ride.
[music playing]
-What's going on here?
OUTLAW: Yee-haw!
[shrieking]
[music playing]
-No!
Someone help!
-You can do whatever you want
with this here city feller.
Just leave me and
the girl alone.
-Are you trying
to get me killed?
-One false move and
it'll be your last.
-Right, like I can even move.
-Y'all know what to do, boys.
[laughter]
[music playing]
So you wanna play rough, do ya?
-That's enough!
It's my legal obligation
to warn you, try anything
and I'll hurt you.
Don't say I didn't warn you!
[music playing]
-Oh my.
Could he be the one, Pa?
-Could be.
-I think it's best if
I continue my journey.
I'm really sorry if I
caused you any trouble.
Well, we'll see you around.
FARMER BROWN: No, wait!
-Well, at least
tell us your name.
-I'm a simple man on a journey.
Besides, my name wouldn't make
any difference to you anyway.
-You hear that, Anna.
-Yes.
I am so sure of it.
It's Joe!
Oh.
-What?
Who's Joe?
-Mmm.
[music playing]
-Boy, this place is isolated.
-Oh, once this here
ranch used to be
a well-known spread
in these parts.
But ever since they
came and started
sticking their nose
into our business,
we haven't even been left with
a moment's peace around here.
-You mean those outlaws?
-Now me and my daughter Anna are
stuck in the middle of nowhere
and we're barely managing
to make ends meet.
[crying]
-But we have faith!
There's a legend in these parts
that whenever there's trouble,
a man named Joe suddenly
appears from out of nowhere
and manages to save them.
We've always heard this story
because it's been passed down
from generation to generation.
But now we finally met you, Joe!
[music playing]
-I guess we're blessed.
-Yes, Pa.
We're truly blessed.
-Hey.
I hate to break up
your little party.
But I'm not the
man you think I am.
I'm just a guy who's passing
through, you understand?
I think I'd better leave.
[music playing]
-Aah!
[laughter]
-Oh, that Joe is a regular
comedian, now isn't he, Pa?
[laughter]
-I suppose he's
just a little shy.
[laughter]
-I'm not Joe.
My name is Ryoga.
I didn't come here
to save anybody.
And all I want to do
is get out of here, OK?
-But we don't want you to go.
Who's going to protect us
from those evil outlaws
once you leave us, Joe?
[crying]
-There ain't no point
in cryin,' Anna,
'cause if them varmints are
set on taking over what is
rightfully mine,
well, mark my words,
they got another thing comin'!
[coughing]
-But you wouldn't stand
a chance against them.
-I'm sorry for putting you
through all this, Anna.
But don't you worry
none, 'cause soon
I'll be watching you from above.
[coughing]
-No, Papa.
No!
-Oh, all right.
I guess it wouldn't hurt if I
stayed here for a little while.
-Good!
Now let's go run
up them varmints!
-Attaboy, Joe!
-Aah!
[mooing]
-Hurry it up!
We gotta infiltrate
their hideout!
-Don't worry about a thing,
Joe, because in the end,
the good guys always win.
[music playing]
-That's right.
Come and get it.
-It is time to show
'em what you got, Joe.
-Aah!
-Why, it's him again.
-So you think we oughta
help the little feller out?
-I think we better.
-What?
What the--
-Hang in there, Joe!
The cavalry's a-coming!
-This is gonna be fun!
[laughter]
-Huh?
Wait!
-Is it hot enough for you?
-Uh, uh--
FARMER BROWN: I take it that's
city talk for "crank it up."
[laughter]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Oh.
I can't get out of this thing
with Anna standing here.
-Hmm?
Oh, I must be gettin' old.
Where are my manners?
I best be leavin'
you young-uns alone
to get to know each other.
Hey, Gertie, how 'bout a
quick game of Crazy 8s?
-Oh, come on, Pa.
You're embarrassing me.
-Well, it's getting late,
so I reckon I'll turn in.
[yawn]
-No, wait!
Don't go!
-Oh!
-Oh.
[music playing]
AKANE: Hey, look.
Here's a postcard from Ryoga.
-So what's he say, huh?
-"Howdy, partner.
How are you, Akane?
I'm out in the middle of nowhere
helping an old rancher fight
hombres from taking
over his land.
Out here, they call me Joe."
You think he's lost it?
-Don't think so.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): And
since I've been out here,
I get a feeling
I've matured in ways
I didn't think I knew I could.
[music playing]
-Well, what can I get ya?
OUTLAW: Butter corn.
Noodles on the raw side.
-I'm very sorry, sir, but
we're fresh out of noddles.
-Hmm.
Then I suggest you
find some if you
want to see the sun come up.
-Oh!
No, please!
I got a wife and kids!
-Everybody stay
right where you are.
[music playing]
-I just thought
you'd like to have it
back, with a side of ramen.
-Say, you're pretty
good for a greenhorn.
My name's Ushinoske Chumanbe,
but I didn't catch yours.
-Ryoga Hibiki.
Hmm.
-Ryoga, huh?
That there's one name
I won't never forget.
[music playing]
-My Ryoga.
Oh!
Hey, Ryoga!
-[laughter]
--[breathing heavily] I'm
definitely in The Twilight
Zone.
FARMER BROWN: Ryoga!
Them varmints kidnapped Anna!
[mooing]
RYOGA: Where is she?
-Look!
-"If you ever want to see
your daughter alive again,
come to Hell Canyon."
-Them no good
no-accounts think they
can do whatever they want now
that Ushinoske's back in town!
-Huh?
Ushin?
-He's the meanest outlaw
in these here parts.
A few years ago, he
just plain vanished.
And now he's back.
Oh, what are they
gonna do with my Anna?
[crying]
She's the only
thing I have left.
Anna!
Oh, my dear little Anna!
-There's no time to lose.
Take me to Hell Canyon.
[music playing]
-It's Ryoga!
[caw]
-We meet again, stranger.
I wasn't expecting you.
But this time, you're
gonna be the one with ramen
on your face.
-I suggest you hand over
Anna before anyone gets hurt.
-I suggest you hightail it
outta here before you're just
a stain on the desert floor.
Now here's you two
choices, partner.
You can either
put up or shut up.
-I'll make a deal with you.
If you win, I'll leave.
But if I win, you promise
to leave Anna and her father
alone!
-It's a deal.
[music playing]
-Anna!
-Aah!
[music playing]
-Why, you good-for-nothin'
little snake!
[music playing]
RYOGA: No.
Here we go again!
[music playing]
-Take this!
I got you now.
Skedaddle, Bossie!
[mooing]
[music playing]
-Oh!
No, Ryoga!
No!
-I hope you remember our deal,
kung fu kid, 'cause you lose.
[laughter]
-How am I gonna
get outta this one?
Wait!
-[laughter] Hmm?
-I hope you don't
mind if I jog along.
I do need my exercise!
-Come on, Bossie.
Step on it!
-Just remember this, if
you give up, you lose!
[music playing]
[screaming]
[crash]
-That hurt.
-Yes!
[mooing]
-Thank you, Ryoga.
[music playing]
My Ryoga!
I'm comin', my sweet!
-Hold it!
That is far enough.
-Huh?
[music playing]
-Are you OK?
-Oh!
Oh, Ryoga.
-I'm so happy for you, Anna.
You too, Joe!
[music playing]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): I don't think
I've ever been so much in love
before.
And what scares me
most is if I leave,
I might never be
loved like this again.
Akane.
I'm-- I'm--
ANNA: Penny for your
thoughts, Ryoga.
RYOGA: Anna!
-Ryoga, I've never been
this happy in my whole life.
And I just wish things would
stay the same forever and ever.
Is there something wrong?
-Anna, I'm really sorry.
But I, I must
continue my journey.
-Oh!
[music playing]
RYOGA: My name is Ryoga Hibiki.
I'm not Joe.
And I love another.
Her name is Akane.
And I must return to her, Anna.
-Ryoga, don't go!
You can't leave!
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
Don't look back, Ryoga.
You mustn't look back.
You have to go home, home to the
woman you love, home to Akane!
-I guess the
weddin's off, Gertie.
-No!
Don't go, Ryoga!
You can't leave me!
RYOGA: Please Anna, forgive me!
Whoa!
-Ryoga!
[music playing]
Ryoga.
Ryoga!
How could he just leave?
[crying]
FARMER BROWN: There,
there, little lady.
Joe's gone now.
But I gotta feelin'
one day he'll be back.
Or it could be gas.
[oink]
[squeal]
-Huh?
P-chan?
[moan]
-Hey, what's wrong, P-chan?
Come to Akane.
[squeal]
Oh.
Where were you?
I was so worried.
[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
-No, no, no!
I refuse to live
inside Happosai's dream
for the rest of my life.
Someone do something!
ANNOUNCER: Next time on "Ramna
1/2", "Into the Darkness."
We'll see you there.