[music playing]
[MUSIC YOSHIE HAYASAKA, "NO WAY! PART 2"]
[waves crashing softly]
[moaning]
-Kumahachi.
Kumahachi!
Wait!
Don't go!
Come back!
Aaah!
Kumahachi!
[gasp]
NARRATOR: "Step Outside!"
[wind howling]
-It's looking like a
white Christmas this year.
-Even though we
happen to be in Japan?
-It'll be fun.
Right, Ranma?
-How fun's it gonna be
with him laying around
all day like some
kind of turtle?
The freak's gotta come out
of his shell sooner or later.
-Please do not that
way about your elders.
It's too cold this
year for cruelty.
-Huh?
-Uh?
[screams]
-Ah!
Hey!
Oh!
-What was that
again about cruelty?
-So I used her lap as my pillow.
It's my privilege as a
senior citizen, I tell you.
RANMA: OK, then, if that's how
you want to think about it,
consider this a gift
of free airfare!
-Aaaah!
[coughing and sputtering] How
dare you disrespect the old
and infirm?
-Old and infirm, my butt.
GENMA: Master?
[running footsteps approaching]
-What fool would
dare such a thing?
Ranma!
-Huh?
[both yell]
-[sputters] That's cold!
Really cold!
What'd you do that for?
-There, Master, now
you're both even.
Please forgive my foolish--
-Forget it?
No way!
Not a chance!
Genma, this is all your
fault for not teaching
your ingrate son proper respect.
If you think you're
gonna bow and scrap
your way out of this one,
you've got another think coming.
-Why not?
It's worked before.
-Please, Master, please.
Anything you want, just name it!
I'll do anything, anything,
if only you'll forgive me.
-Is that so?
In that case, I suppose I
wouldn't mind a really, really
big Christmas tree, one I could
decorate with my collection.
Wouldn't that be something?
-Oh, that's it, freak!
Say goodbye to--
GENMA: Come on, boy, let's go.
-Aah!
Hey!
Where are we going?
-To get the Master's
Christmas tree.
-What?
GENMA: Ready to
leave immediately?
RANMA: Yes.
I mean, no!
[wind howling]
So why do we have to get
the old goat's stupid tree?
-'Cause we'd never have survived
the Master's wrath, that's why.
-Yeah?
Well, I'd take the
wrath of the Master
over the wrath of
this storm any day.
-Why can't you just shut up
and act like a man for once?
--[frustrated growl] You're
the one who couldn't say no,
remember?
Jeez, you're such a-- huh?
Hey, Pop!
You there?
Answer me!
Where are you?
Pop?
Pop, where are you?
[phone ringing]
AKANE: Hello, Tendo Dojo.
Oh, hi there, Ranma.
What can I do for you?
Huh?
Come home?
No, not yet.
-Is that so?
I-- I was, um, kind of
hoping that-- yeah, no.
I-- I just thought
that, uh, maybe he
would have come home by now.
-It's been three days
and he still hasn't?
-You-- you don't think that
he might be in an accident,
do you?
RANMA (ON PHONE): Who, Pop?
No, I'm sure he's fine.
It's just he's
kind of, you know--
-Stay where you are.
I'll be right there.
-(SHOUTING) Pop, where are you?
-(SHOUTING) Mr. Saotome!
-Like I said, I'm
sure he's fine.
It's just he's kind
of old, you know?
-Poor guy.
-Aaah!
[both panting]
-Is there something out there?
-Hey, look, it's a house.
Come on, let's go take a break.
Um, maybe they'll
give us some tea.
[waves crashing]
[low growl]
-Irresponsible jerk!
Come here!
How dare you make
us worry about you?
-He's right, you know.
We were really
getting concerned.
YOTARO: No!
-Huh?
-Please!
Please don't hurt my Kumahachi.
-Kuma-what-chi?
-Here, Kumahachi.
Come here.
-You mean that he's not Pop?
-Here you go.
-Unh!
I should have
known that was you!
Why, I oughta--
Oh, goody goody.
I can hardly wait.
[crockery breaks]
Wha?
-The panda, does--
does he belong to you?
-Mom!
[crying loudly] Kumahachi's
my panda, right?
-Oh, Yotaro.
-Mama!
[gulls crying]
YOTARO'S MOTHER: My son
Yotaro, he's very frail.
He refuses to go out and play.
If only he would, I'm
sure he'd improve.
But quite frankly, I'm
completely at my wits' end.
-I'm sorry, but where exactly
does the panda come in?
-Ah, yes.
The panda.
-Mama, guess what?
I had a dream.
It was me and a panda
playing outside.
Oh, if only I had
a panda, I'd go out
and play every single day.
-Naturally, I was
at a complete loss.
Where on Earth would
I find a panda?
But then, three days ago--
Oh, dear.
A prowler!
You, there, what do you want?
-Huh?
-A panda?
Oh, thank heavens!
The answer to my prayers.
Thank you, thank you!
-Uh-huh.
So that's how you
wound up here, eh, Pop?
-I'm so proud of you.
[low growl]
YOTARO'S MOTHER: And so
was I, until I realized
he was interested only
in eating and sleeping
and refused to go outside.
-Why, you-- how come
I ain't surprised?
Come here, you!
We're out of here.
I don't believe this junk!
What a load.
And here they say--
-Wait!
Please wait!
-I'm the one who's
undisciplined.
Huh?
-Please!
Please don't take my Kumahachi.
Please!
-Mother is so sorry, but we
have to give the panda back.
-No, no!
I don't wanna!
He's my panda, mine!
-Put the crap down, you pig!
-Mommy, Mommy!
Don't let them
take my Kumahachi!
-My poor, poor, poor baby.
But every little cloud
has a silver lining.
-It wha?
-This nice young girl here says
she'll play with you instead.
-And when exactly
did I say that?
-Oh!
Thinking him an angel
for three days straight,
I fed him all his
heart's desire.
Caviar, abalone, sushi,
sashimi, giant shrimp, tempura,
filet mignon-- he
wanted it, he got it.
And here I thought pandas
were naturally vegetarian!
[weeps]
-What's the matter, huh?
You never heard of
"share the wealth"?
-Well, we can't hope to
pay back all the food he
ate, uh-- but maybe we
could just stay a while
and you could play with him.
-Well, it's not like
we got a choice.
OK, fine.
-Oh, do you really mean it?
-Yeah, OK, but just for a while.
-Did you hear that, honey?
Look at all the nice
friends you've made!
Aren't you lucky?
[music playing]
[gulls crying]
[snoring]
-Hm.
-Be reasonable.
You don't want to go and
worry your mom, do you?
Besides, I mean,
how much fun can it
be, staying in
your room all day?
Wouldn't it be more
fun to go outside?
-But I like it here in my room.
What do they got outside that
I don't already have inside?
Here, I'll show you.
-Aw, jeez, that's not
even the latest model.
[video game music playing]
[scoffs] Lame.
Why even bother playing
such a dumb game?
-Why don't you try it
and see for yourself?
OK, now you try it!
-Oh, OK.
Of course, with my superior
speed and reflexes,
a cheesy game like this
ought to be child's play.
[video game music playing]
[explosions]
D'oh!
-Don't worry about it.
You still got two guys left.
-I do, huh?
Uh--
[explosions]
Aaaah!
Ow!
What'd I do to deserve that one?
[muttering]
-Wha?
Hey!
[explosions]
-Now he knows how to play.
-Excuse me, not
everyone's had three days
to sit around and
practice, you know.
-Ooh, look what I've brought.
Nice, hot milk.
Uh?
[GENMA AND RANMA GRUNTING AND
GRUMBLING]
RANMA: Hey!
Get-- get out of-- oh!
Hey!
Gah!
AKANE: What do you
think you're doing?
Yeah
--[laughs] I got a
little carried away.
-Oh, honestly.
-Hey, stop hogging it!
-Hey, let's go outside, 'K?
We can run, and
jump, and I'll even
teach you all kinds of
really, really fun games.
-Like what kind of
really fun games?
-Well, like breaking cinder
blocks with our bare hands,
and punching each other
in the stomach, and--- oh!
-No, thanks.
It's OK.
-You keep forgetting that
he ain't no normal kid.
-I, uh, guess so.
-Hey, if you let
me keep Kumahachi,
I'll go outside
however much you want.
-What?
-Huh?
-That's it.
This time--
-Unh!
-You've gone too far!
You see, kid?
This is what your
panda's really like!
Oh!
So now you fall asleep!
GENMA: Alley-oop!
[splash]
[growls]
-ome on, let's go outside.
And you don't really want to
stay inside all day, do you?
I said, come here!
[both grunting with effort]
-Uh, um, guys?
[both panting]
-Oh, I see.
I get it now.
You're not weak.
You're just lazy.
-I am not!
I'm-- I'm just-- I'm just
delicate, that's all!
[cries loudly]
-Stop crying, will you!
Jeez!
[yelling and crying]
[crashing]
RANMA: Why, you-- that's it.
I've had it!
Step outside.
-You're scaring me!
-Uh?
[sobbing]
[sigh]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
How do you beat
a kid you're not
allowed to beat?
I mean, there must be
something that I can-- aha.
-Say, you know what?
I've got an idea.
You know what I'd
really, really like?
I'd like for you and
me to go on a date!
[giggles]
[laughs]
We'll have the beach
all to ourselves.
We'll run in the sun
and play in the waves,
and it'll be just the
two of us out having fun.
Won't it be won-- dah?
You little--
-I don't need you
to tell me that, OK?
Why don't you try helping
me out, instead of playing
video games and sitting
around eating all day?
Now this is what
you're going to do.
You're going to take
him outside and you're
going to play with him.
You got it?
-Mm.
Mm.
-Yippee!
[laughs] Whee!
Yay!
-Come on, giddy-up, boy!
Go!
YOTARO: [screams with delight]
-There you go!
YOTARO: Yahoo!
Whee!
-That's the way, Pop!
YOTARO: Yahoo!
[laughs]
RANMA: What the--
YOTARO: Yay!
RANMA: Hey!
YOTARO: Wheee!
AKANE: Where are they going?
RANMA: You're asking me?
In here!
-Good, you're just in time.
I fixed a small
snack for the boys.
Come in and help yourselves.
[genma eating with gusto]
-You can eat all you want!
-Shouldn't they be back by now?
They said they'd--
-They're probably on
their way right now.
-Who cares about them?
Where's my Christmas tree?
-For his age, he
sure is stubborn.
-Not half as stubborn
as Pop, though.
And what I'm worried about is
whether he'll even come home.
-You don't think he
plans to stay here?
[snoring]
-Pop!
-He really does live
for eating and sleeping.
I take it all back.
-Oh, I can't take it anymore!
Get up, Pop!
We're leaving.
Come on, wake up!
I'll drag you if I have to.
-Kumahachi!
Don't take him away.
Please!
-That's it!
No more.
This is where it ends.
-Kumahachi!
[gulls crying]
[sigh]
YOTARO: (SHOUTING) Kumahachi!
-Yotaro?
-[gasp] He's outside!
For the first time ever,
he's running outside.
He-- he seems so healthy!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you, whoever you are,
for answering a poor mother's
prayer.
YOTARO: (SHOUTING) Kumahachi!
Kumahachi, come back!
Please!
Come back!
[crying] Kumahachi!
RANMA: Go home, will you?
-My goodness.
You've run all the way home
from the seaside, then.
Here you go, Akane.
-(BREATHLESSLY)
Ah, thanks, Kasumi.
-It's gotta be something like 20
kilometers from there to here.
So what kept you guys going?
[panting]
-I'm tired.
-Delicate constitution, my butt.
You are just a lazy
little brat, that's all.
Huh?
-I'm tired of waiting.
Where's my Christmas tree?
You-- you mean-- All my dreams!
I-- [sobbing]
-Like you said, that
ingrate'll never
learn proper respect
for his elders.
Right, Kumahachi?
HAPPOSAI: (CRYING)
It's not fair!
I want my tree.
I want my tree!
-Kumahachi.
[sleigh bells jingling]
[music - yawmin, "friends"]
NARRATOR: Come on, Ryoga.
You can do it.
You want to get into Furinkan
High School, don't you?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Ryoga's Tendo Dojo Houseguest
Diary."
We'll see you there.