[music playing]
[MUSIC KUSU KUSU, "EARTH
ORCHESTRA"]
-I'm leaving.
Grrr!
-Akane, I said, wait up!
-And I told you, Ranma,
if I wait any longer,
I'll be even later!
-What about me?
Aaah!
[chomp]
I wouldn't have been late if
you'd woken me up in time!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): "Me
is Kuno's Daddy, Me Is."
PRINCIPAL KUNO:
Shake, shake, shake, .
shake.
Shake, shake!
-Oh, no!
-Shake!
Me so sorry, but
Keke cannot have.
All must be confiscated.
So sorry.
Santa must be on his way.
And remember--
[speaking hawaiian]
-What-- what did he just say?
-It's Hawaiian for "Toilet doo."
-What?
Aaah!
[laughs]
[speaking hawaiian]
[panting]
[clock chiming]
-Bells-- still-- ringing!
Keke!
Gotta [inaudible].
RANMA: Aah!
-Hey!
Oh-- oh, no.
-Huh?
-Keke!
[students laugh]
-Hey, you guys, check it out.
Looks like Santa overslept.
[laughter]
[sobbing]
-What's the matter?
-Me-- me was just thinking
about my own keke.
-You mean Santa's got a kid?
-What's his mom, an elf?
SANTA: It make me
cry to think of that.
Me love that boy, me did.
Maybe me love him
too much, me think.
Because one day, he
turn him back on me,
and he walk off into Hawaiian
sun and me never see him again.
Three years ago, that was.
Me look everywhere,
high and low.
Me now think he lost forever.
[weeping]
-You can't have
looked everywhere.
-Me did!
But me still no give up hope.
Souvenir of the island.
-Hey, thanks, man.
[boom]
Aaah!
I should have known.
Aaaah!
-Remember, kekes.
Without the discipline
is no education.
Aloha.
-If that's education,
than I'm-- grr!
[clock chiming]
-He's late.
Lunch time is practically over.
SASUKE: Ssst!
Master Kuno, over here.
Aaah.
Uh, here, sir.
-Oh!
You found it!
Oh, ever since I was a
boy, it's just not lunch
without this sauce.
Mm, mm!
RANMA: Come back here!
-[chortling]
-At least wait till
lunch to start this.
[laughing]
-Huh?
Did-- did you see?
-Nothing that maniac
does surprises me.
Now, if you don't mind-- mmm!
-Still, there's
something about--
I think we'll find
what we need in here.
[rumbling]
[metal creaking]
After you, Master Kuno.
-And what is it we
are after again?
SASUKE: It's right
here in this box.
Take a look at this photo.
-Well, I'll be.
If it isn't a picture
of my own noble father!
-Take a good long look at it.
Are you sure you haven't seen
him somewhere more recently?
-Hm.
No.
-Unh!
Perhaps another look?
-I tell you, I haven't.
-And you don't find
the resemblance
between your missing father
and the new principal
incriminating, Master?
-Hyyyahhh!
[groans]
-That sociopath is nothing
like my dear old missing Papa.
-But Master Kuno, the evidence.
I took the photo myself.
I'm sure that if you
just compare the two,
you'll have to admit that--
-Hahah.
I will have to do no such thing.
Observe.
My father has a samurai topknot.
The principal,
you'll notice, has
no knot, but a coconut tree.
Further, the glasses
are different.
So is this lei!
So they're nothing alike.
My father is far
superior in taste.
So, are we clear?
-I, uh, uh--
-Well?
-Y-yes, sir.
-Shame on you, to think
that you would even
suggest such a thing, Sasuke.
-Sir, I-- [whimpers]
[gulls crying]
[playing ukulele]
(SINGING) Me keke very bad.
Me need to set the example.
Otherwise, they be delinquents.
Especially that Ranma Saotome.
That one need the
big discipline.
Me think maybe me have idea.
Which is why me always say,
if the keke want assembly,
then that's what the keke get.
-I didn't want assembly.
Did you want assembly?
-No way!
-Now for the rules.
All you kekes going to compete
in martial arts tournament.
Keke what win get this--
coupon for no-limit
"get out of all
school rules free."
[students gasp]
-Yeah, right!
Now tell us what
you're really up to.
-I think you one very
suspicious keke, you know that?
Unh!
-Your point being?
-Point being, girl keke who lose
get bowl cut, and all boy keke
get buzz cut.
-Then forget it!
We're not playing.
-You no want no rule pass?
-Oh, I want it, all right.
And to get it, I'm
going to kick your--
[kids shout]
PRINCIPAL KUNO
(VOICEOVER): Sucker!
[fighting grunts]
-Whew!
Your turn, Nabiki.
-You have got to be kidding me.
-But aren't you worried?
NABIKI: I would be, if I didn't
have Kuno Baby in my class.
RANMA: She's got a point.
-Huh?
-You know, it's a sure thing,
as long as he's got his-- aah!
Cheek!
Huah!
Hah!
-Master Kuno!
-That you, Sasuke?
I'm trying to practice.
-B-b-but Master Kuno,
it's about your father.
-Tell me, quickly.
-I-- I looked into
it, like you asked.
His last known
residence was Hawaii.
Therefore--
-Hm.
Nonsense.
-But don't you see?
That's where--
-While it is true he
left to go abroad,
it's not Hawaii he's
at, but-- the sky.
-The wha?
[sigh]
TATEWAKI KUNO
(VOICEOVER): Daddy?
[fireworks exploding]
--[scoffs] What have
we got to worry about?
There ain't nothing that he
can do that the three of us
can't handle.
-He's right.
All for one, and one--
[students gasp]
-Huh?
[marching]
What the-- heck are those?
[music playing]
-OK, now I'm getting worried.
PRINCIPAL KUNO:
Aloha and welcome!
-Who are those guys?
What do they want?
-Oh, you mean the new
transfer students?
Everybody give big welcome.
Of course, they be
competing in the contest.
-OK.
Now I'm really, really worried.
-Is everybody ready
for the big fun?
On your marks, get set, go!
[students shouting]
[inaudible]
Which is the class that will
win the "get out of rules free"
pass?
[inaudible] don't know.
Be brave, my kekes.
The Big Kahuna is
cheering for you!
[fighting grunts]
[screams]
-Wow, people are
really getting into it.
-Well, I mean, with a
"get out of rules free"
pass on the line, wouldn't you?
-You know, I feel bad
for the losers, though,
because they gotta get
those dumb haircuts.
PRINCIPAL KUNO: Next
up are Year 1 students.
Homeroom F.
-That's us.
Let's go.
[gunshot]
[all shouting]
[laughs]
[fighting grunts]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Come
on, come on, come on.
[fighting grunts]
-Uh?
[laughing]
-That's enough of that!
-So I said, what do you think?
Do I--
[fighting grunts]
[giggling]
-It is just as we hoped.
And now, time for keke to
meet new transfer students!
[students gasp]
-Man, you can feel the energy.
[wind howling]
-Huh?
Oh, no!
PRINCIPAL KUNO: And now for the
next round of the elimination.
-He-- he can't do that.
STUDENT: Cheater!
STUDENT: Those aren't students.
STUDENT: They're
soldiers of fortune!
-No, no, my keke.
That is where you are wrong.
Rules say you go ID, you
is the official student.
-Those are fake,
and you know it!
RANMA: Aw, who cares?
The stronger they are, the
harder they fall, right?
-Now that what Big
Kahuna like to hear.
-I'm still not sure
what you're up to,
but I'll take that
pass, either way.
PRINCIPAL KUNO:
You mean you try.
-No, I mean I'll take it.
STUDENT: You tell him, Saotome!
-What's this?
A photo?
Looks familiar, doesn't he?
-You're right, but who
do you think it is?
-Now, wait a sec.
Add a little this,
a little that.
-Kuno?
Ah!
-But what's the principal
doing with a picture like this?
SASUKE: My point exactly.
ALL: Huh?
[crash]
NABIKI: Sasuke?
-My theory is that
he's the father
Master Kuno lost
three long years ago.
-The principal's
related to Kuno?
[laughs] OK, then tell me this.
How come they've never
recognized each other all
this time?
-Because they're both insane.
-Huh?
PRINCIPAL KUNO: And now to
continue the eliminations.
[panting]
-Aaaaahh!
SASUKE: Master Kuno!
-Oh!
PRINCIPAL KUNO:
Oh, man, oh, man.
Too bad.
Look like that keke wipe out.
Now Big Kahuna need
new challenger.
-How dare you talk to
your own son like that?
-What?
That one is Big Kahuna?
Tell me, where you find
this picture of Tachi?
-Tachi?
-Short for Tatewaki.
This one no look like
age 14 Tachi, though.
-That's because
he's 17 now, stupid.
-No, no, no, no.
That is keke not
have that haircut.
He be more like this one.
There.
Now he look like
Daddy's little keke.
Oh, Tachi!
Daddy be missing you big-time.
Maybe if you had the buzzcut,
like when you was little--
-Don't touch me!
-You, wake up.
-Is it true?
Is the principal
really your dad?
-That again?
My father was fair-skinned.
-That's because he's
been in Hawaii, stupid.
Better face it.
You two are related.
[students gasp]
-I knew it.
-You-- you mean to say this
psycho, this sociopath,
this missing link--
-Oh, Tachi.
Daddy always knew he'd
find his lost keke.
Daddy missed you, Tachi.
Did you miss Daddy too?
--[growls] Three
years he's been gone,
and he still calls me Tachi!
Well, I've got news
for you, Daddy.
I'm not that little boy anymore.
You can't make it up to me!
-Not even with a
present from the island?
-What's this?
[boom]
Aaah!
I knew I shouldn't
have trusted him.
-I'd say that pretty
much proves it.
-Yep.
They're two of a
kind, all right.
[music playing]
-Ruin Saotome?
-Me think you like
that idea, eh, Tachi?
Daddy admit transfer
students from all over Japan.
And when they defeat Saotome,
all keke wahine get buzz cut,
bowl cut!
[students shouting]
-Hm?
You guys, look out!
-Huh?
-Uh?
Uh--
-Huh?
-Uh--
-Using a cat?
-Ranma Saotome
hate the kitty-cat.
That's why me use it
as a secret weapon.
Kitty-cat is the weak
point of that keke.
-Why, you fiend!
Have you no honor in you at all?
-Oh, then you want
Saotome to win.
TATEWAKI KUNO (VOICEOVER):
Well, he's right.
I have to admit, there
are certain benefits.
-Hm?
Huh?
-Ah?
-Aaah, look out!
-Aah!
-Aaaah!
-Ukyo!
-Whoa!
Wha!
-Akane!
-Akane Tendo?
[grunting with effort]
It's only going to get worse.
-Huh?
Aaahh!
-Now is the chance, when
he's still distracted.
TATEWAKI KUNO (VOICEOVER): True.
If I'm to strike,
the time is now.
And yet, how far can I go?
Is victory worth my pride?
Ungh!
Tatewaki Kuno, age 17, the
Blue Thunder of Furinkan High,
what would he do?
Can cowardice be justified?
Ah, Akane Tendo wakes.
Since you're already
here, perhaps you'd like--
[both yell]
[grunts]
-How the heck can they move
with all that armor on?
Then again--
[grunts]
Let's see how you like this!
Unh!
[electricity zaps and crackles]
-Ranma!
-Unh!
-Huh?
Oh!
Ranma!
--[chuckles] Steel conducts
electricity, you know.
-We won!
Homeroom F's exempt for a year!
[students cheer]
-Oh, no!
Big Kahuna humiliated
before students.
-I would like to
take this opportunity
to disavow any relation.
RANMA: Don't mind if we do.
Huh?
PRINCIPAL KUNO:
[laughs] So sorry.
You lose.
Real one tattooed on keke's
[inaudible] three years ago.
If you give Tachi
buzzcut, then--
-So that's what's on my head?
SASUKE: Now, now,
Master Kuno, behave!
[fighting grunts]
-Jinkies.
Well, I'd say it's yet
another happy family.
-Why were they even reunited.
-Speaking of which,
Akane, what was
the point of this episode again?
SASUKE: Master Kuno,
have some respect.
You only have one
father, you know.
[MUSIC MICHIYO NAKAJIMA, "RED
POPPY"]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): When it comes
to Martial Arts Tea Ceremony,
nobody does it better than
the House of Daimonji.
But why am I-- next
time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"The Matriarch Takes a Stand."
We'll see you there.