[theme music]
NARRATOR: Here's Ranma.
[rain]
-Hey!
You better cut that out.
Uh.
[yell]
[grunt]
[crowd gasps]
-It's a panda.
-Your move.
Well I still say the
whole things sucks.
Taking my fiance from
me without even asking.
I'm going back to China now.
So suck on that, old man.
Uh.
[crowd murmurs]
-[growls]
-At last, Ranma is coming.
How I've waited for this day.
And soon-- very soon--
Ranma will be here.
SOUN: Listen up!
Kasumi, Nabiki, Akane.
Kasumi.
-Yes, what is it father?
SOUN:Nabiki.
-Hm?
SOUN: Akane.
Where is that girl?
-Hiya!
Whew.
That felt pretty
good. [click] Huh?
-There you go again Akane.
This is exactly
the type of thing
that makes the boys
think you're so weird.
-So why should I care, Nabiki?
Not everybody thinks the whole
world revolves around boys!
-No?
Then I guess this
wouldn't interest you.
AKANE: Fiance?
SOUN: Yes.
The son of a very
good friend of mine.
His name is Ranma Saotome.
If one of you three girls
were to marry him and carry
on this training hall, then
the Tendo family legacy
would be secure.
-Hey, wait a minute
here, don't we
get to have some say in
who were going to marry?
-Maybe you should wait
until you meet him.
You never know, he
might be really cute.
Right Daddy?
--[laughs] He'll be
here any minute.
Ranma and his father have
been on a training mission.
Recently they
crossed into China.
-Ooh, China.
-So he hiked all
the way to China.
Wow, big deal.
-Father, how old is this Ranma?
-Is he cute?
KASUMI: Younger
men are so young.
AKANE: Well what
kind of guy is he?
-[laughs] I don't know.
-You don't know?
-I've never met him.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Oh
please, I don't believe this.
RANMA: Let go, you old fool.
I told you, I don't
want any part of this.
Now put me down.
-Sounds like we have visitors.
-Ooh, it must be Ranma.
-Saotome, my friend.
We've been waiting.
-I hope that he's older than me.
-Ah
-Come on, Pop.
You're-- you're
scaring them spitless.
-So Father, this is your friend?
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh
-Oh, so this panda just
decided to drop in.
Is that it, Pop?
-Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh
SOUN: You wouldn't be--
-I'm Ranma Saotome.
Sorry about this.
SOUN: At last, you're here.
-Ooh, he is cute.
-I'm so glad you're here.
Hm?
[gasps] Wha?
-Hm.
-Uh, could you stop that?
-Ranma's not a boy.
He's a girl.
-A girl?
[moans]
KASUMI: Father.
KASUMI: Oh, poor Father.
He must be so disappointed.
NABIKI: He's disappointed?
He's not the only one.
Look at her.
Some fiance.
-Stop it, you two.
He-- she is our guest.
-Look everyone,
Father's coming to.
-This is all your fault, Daddy.
Don't you know the difference
between a boy and a girl?
-I assumed my friend
Genma's son was a boy.
-Excuse me, does this look
like a boy do you, huh Daddy?
-Please, I wish you'd stop that.
-You heard what
she said, Nabiki.
Now why don't you
leave her alone.
A guest is a guest.
Hey, you want to go practice?
RANMA: Huh?
-I'm Akane.
You want to be friends?
-Mhm.
You study kempo, right?
RANMA: A little.
-Well, why don't we have
a little match, then?
RANMA: Huh?
-Come on, just for fun.
AKANE: Don't worry,
I won't hurt you.
Hiya.
Hiya, hiya, hiya, hiya.
What's wrong?
Attack me.
[grunts]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Why--
why am I missing her?
Is she reading my moves?
OK, this time for real.
[yells]
[laughs]
-You're pretty good.
I'm just glad that
you're a girl.
-What?
-It's just, well, I'm just
really glad you're not a boy.
-So that's it.
-Mm.
-The path of a true martial
artist is fraught with perils.
KASUMI: Ranma, you
can use this room.
Would you like to freshen
up and have a bath now?
-Uh, no thanks.
-Here, you've been
exercising, haven't you?
-Yes.
-Hey, Kasumi, who
was that strange man
sitting in our living room?
-Who knows?
-Huh?
-Go tell Akane she
can take her bath now.
-OK
-Uh, that's cold.
AKANE: I guess we can
both take our baths.
-Hm, what to do?
They're bound to find
out sooner or later.
Well, may as well
just go out like I am.
Whoa.
[inhale] [scream]
[scream]
-I'll drown him in the bathtub.
KASUMI: Akane what is it?
What's the matter?
What are you doing with that?
-There's a pervert
in the bathroom.
-Well, gee Akane, why didn't
you just clobber him then?
-Because I got scared.
Is that all right?
-Oh, I do hope Ranma's alright.
I thought she was in there
taking a bath right now.
RANMA: Excuse me.
-Who is that?
NABIKI: Who are you?
-I'm, uh, Ranma Saotome.
Sorry about this.
-I can explain everything.
This is my dear old friend.
-Genma Saotome.
And this is my son.
-Ranma.
-[grunt]
-This gets more
interesting by the minute.
-Are you really her?
The same girl who we saw before?
-I am.
-It's such a long story, I
don't know where to begin.
Well then, let's
start with this.
-Whaa!
What'd do that for?
-Oh my.
-Ranma's a girl now.
-I am so ashamed, I cannot
bear to see my son like this.
-[grunt]
-Ranma Saotome, you break
your father's heart.
-Who are you talk?
My old man's a panda.
-Father, you certainly
have some unusual friends.
-They didn't used
to be like this.
It was training in China
that did this to them.
Something terrible happened
during a dangerous training
exercise.
Maybe we should give
them a few moments
to come back to themselves.
-Ah yes, it all started
one fateful month ago.
Ranma and I were voyaging
across the ocean to China.
We journeyed for many
days and many nights.
It was in China's
Mount Kwanjeng region
in the Bayankala range,
Qinghai Provence,
that we finally found
what we were looking for.
-Here sirs, we come to
famous training ground
of cursed springs, Jusenkyo.
-Are you prepared, Rama?
-Ah, man this place ain't near
as bad as I thought it'd be.
GUIDE: Ooh sirs, you are
very strange ones, no?
This place is a very dangerous.
Nobody use it now, 'cuz
more than 100 spring here,
and each one have own
tragedy happen there.
-Ranma, follow me!
-Right behind ya'.
-Hey, sirs, what are you doing?
I have not finished
my tragic story.
You can't go there.
GENMA: I won't go
easy on you, Ranma.
RANMA: That's just
the way I like it.
GUIDE: Please sirs, very
bad you fall in spring.
-Hey Pop, what's up?
We done already?
-[growl]
-Ah!
What-- what the hell is that?
-That one, Shonmaoniichuan,
Spring of Drowned Panda.
Very tragic story of panda
who drowned 2,000 year ago.
The legend say, whoever fall
in spring take body of panda.
-Hey buddy, you never said
anything about that to us.
[gasp] Ah!
-Oh, too bad.
You fall in Nyannichuan,
Spring of Drowned Girl.
There very tragic
legend of young girl who
drowned in spring
1,500 year ago.
Now whoever fall in the spring
take a body of a young girl.
Haha.
-Ah!
GUIDE: You see,
now you young girl.
-[groan]
SOUN: The legendary ground
of accursed springs.
It's true horror has been
shrouded in mystery, until now.
-What do you mean, true horror?
This is all your fault, old man.
What's the idea of dragging me
to a place like that anyway,
huh?
GENMA: Ranma, you
sound like a girl.
Were you not prepared
to lay down your life
for the sake of the art?
RANMA: My life, yes.
My manhood is another story.
-Ah.
RANMA: Oh, you just had to go
find that training ground, even
though you didn't speak
a word of Chinese.
-How I suffer for you.
Here.
When doused with hot water,
you return to human form.
-It needn't be quite
that hot, thank you.
-When doused with cold
water, you become a girl.
But hot water turns
you back into a boy.
-Hot water, not boiling.
-Well now, your problem
isn't so terrible after all.
Look.
My oldest daughter
Kasumi, she's 19.
My middle daughter
Nabiki, she's 17.
And my youngest
daughter Akane, she 16.
Pick anyone you want,
she'll be your new fiance.
-Akane would seem
the wisest choice.
-Couldn't agree more.
-What?
You must be joking.
Why would I be?
-Because you hate
boys, don't you?
-Well I guess you're
in luck, Akane.
Ranma's half girl.
-Me marry that pervert?
Never!
-Hey, wait a minute,
what do you mean pervert?
-You saw me in the
nude, you lech.
-Hold it, just a second,
you walked in on me.
-Oh yeah, well it's different
when a girl looks at a boy.
-[laughter]
AKANE: Pervert.
Peeping tom.
-See?
They're already
the perfect couple.
-We are not a couple.
We're fighting.
There's no way in the world
I could ever marry someone
like that.
-Oh yeah?
My sentiments exactly.
Goodbye.
-Ranma, where are you going?
-I'm going back to China.
I have to find a way to
change back for good.
This is no time for fiances.
By the way, I noticed that you
took a pretty good look at me,
too.
Besides, it's no big deal
for me to see a naked girl.
I mean, I've seen myself
plenty of times right?
And I'm better built to boot.
-[growl]
-Now that he had coming.
[dog barking]
-Oh, she's awake.
Are you OK?
Don't think too badly of Akane.
She's really a very sweet girl.
She's just a little
high spirited.
-Oh good, Kasumi.
Like that explains everything.
[bath sounds]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): That
nasty-- make a fool of me.
-And I'm better built to boot.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
That-- that boy!
Hmph.
-Ah, ouch.
It still smarts.
What kind of girl
is she, anyway?
-You wanna be friends?
-Friends she says.
So much for friends when
she found out I'm a boy.
Huh?
Uh, um, oh.
-Why you-- you-- ugh.
[smack]
-But you were both girls
at the time, right?
So that makes it OK
then, doesn't it?
-OK?
OK is not the word.
-So she's got spunk.
That makes a fiance
even more cute.
-Cute is not the word.
-Hmph
-She's definitely not cute.
Ow!
[theme music]