[theme music]
UKYO: Well, don't be shy.
Eat up, Ranma.
Alley-oop.
[laughter]
-Ukyo, you're too good to me.
Oh man, am I hungry!
-Ranma, take it easy, will ya?
I know it's good,
but you're, you're
going to make yourself sick.
Uh oh, speaking of
sick, what are they
feeding you over there?
You'd think you hadn't
eaten in a week.
-Well, excuse moi.
We may not be a restaurant,
but we eat just fine.
And you, Ranma.
Stop acting like such a pig!
-Dear me, if it isn't
his former fiancee.
-Former?
-Well, since I'm
the real one, that
makes you either
fake for former.
And I know how you hate fakes.
Right, Ranma, honey?
-Anyway, that's between you two.
Well, I hate to eat
and run, but can I
get an order of
okonomiyaki to go, please?
-Sure thing.
-You know, I just noticed,
business is kind of slow.
[sigh]
-Yeah, it's true.
It has been slow.
All my usual customers seemed
to have jumped ship and found
someplace else to eat.
-Gee, you think they're
at the new place?
-What?
NARRATOR: Revenge,
raging okonomiyaki.
-There.
Do you see the truck?
They sell crepes.
And at school, it's the
only thing they talk about.
RANMA: They're from our class.
UKYO: They used to
be my customers.
CROWD: I want banana cream!
Make mine strawberry!
Red bean for me, please.
-No prob.
And be sure to check
out my technique,
because when the crepe
king cooks, people listen.
-It's like, it's like
a taste of spring time,
of the farm fresh strawberries
bursting with healthy goodness.
-Just note how the
fluffiness of whipped cream
brings out the taste of
banana to perfection.
-Jeez, what the heck
is this, Iron Chef?
-Ha ha ha.
OK, so who's up
for another crepe?
-Hm.
Mister, I don't know
where you learned to cook,
but where I come from,
you're not even on the menu.
-Really?
And I suppose the cooking
you do does count?
-All I know is, because of you,
my restaurant's half empty.
-And what restaurant's that?
UKYO: Ukyo;s Okonomiyaki.
Crepe King, let's
see what you got.
-Ha, if you insist.
Give it your best shot.
-Ahh!
[grunting]
-Ready?
Crush.
But why are they-- hm.
-Hey, come on.
Cheer up, girly.
Just be grateful you've got any
customers in your restaurant
at all.
[laughter]
-Huh?
-I wonder if I might try a bite.
Hm.
Ah, delicious.
But there's more
to it than taste.
What's missing is ambition.
That, perhaps, is why you lose.
-Ambition?
-Come on, Ukyo.
Cheer up.
Next time you'll beat
that creep for sure.
-Thanks for saying it, Ranma,
but we both know it's not true.
-You're not still thinking
about that monk, are you?
-Back when I was
angry at Ranma, I
cast aside my girlhood
to make okonomiyaki.
Now that that's over, I use my
skills to make people happy.
It makes me happy too.
If you take my okonomiyaki
away from me though,
what is it I have left?
I have no revenge.
I have no love.
No wonder my cooking
has something missing,
-You don't have to cry about it.
Your cooking's fine.
It's no big deal.
Don't let it get to you.
Who needs ambition anyway, huh?
-Oh, I get it.
Ambition's fine if
you're a boy, but I
suppose I should just give
it all up and be your wife?
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Who said anything about wife?
-No, no.
You're right.
Who am I kidding?
I can't make decent
okonomiyaki to save my life,
and here I am thinking
of being your wife.
That's it, then.
I have got to train
to improve my cooking,
or I am not worthy of
being Ranma's fiancee.
Listen, Akane.
You'll take care of Ranma for me
while I'm training, won't you?
-Huh?
-See ya later.
-Ukyo, wait.
-Ranma, we can't just
let her leave like that.
-And what is it I'm
supposed to do, huh?
Akane, you know she's
just going to start up
with that wife stuff again.
-But still.
[bell ringing]
[grunting]
-Why bother?
It's no good.
I just don't feel
ambitious anymore.
It looks and tastes OK, but
inside my cooking's empty.
Ranma will never
love me at this rate.
Huh?
-Young lady, you've
come to the right place.
Our temple here has a
many hundred year history
of being visited by
epicures and gourmands.
It was one such
man, in fact, who
gave us our most
sacred treasure.
[gasp]
For over 100 years, this
box has remained unopened,
the pulsating energy contained
within gone to waste.
All this time, the savory,
velvety sauce untasted,
the melt-in-your-mouth
seaweed on top passed over,
the humble cabbage
humiliated, the frolicking,
playful dried fish
flakes gone wasted.
-You don't mean it's--
-Mm.
The golden okonomiyaki,
a gift from our founder,
a man who reminds me of you.
-I knew it looked familiar.
My grandpa-- my great grandpa,
that is-- told me about it.
-If he was your
ancestor, then you
must be the descendant
of our founder.
That makes me more determined
to get you back on track.
You mustn't lose hope,
especially not now.
The golden okonomiyaki
is yours by right.
-If it'll help with my
ambition, I'll do it.
Teach me, oh master, for I am
young and foolish and unworthy.
-The training will
be very difficult.
Are you certain?
-I'll do whatever it takes.
[laughter]
-I hope she's not too depressed.
-She may never come
back, you know.
-We should at least look
after her restaurant for her,
don't you think?
-Yeah right.
And who do you think's going to
do all the cooking here, huh?
Emeril Lagasse?
-You can laugh all you want,
but we've got to do something.
-And who's going to
bring in customers, you?
-I got a better idea.
RANMA: Ah, what'd
you do that for?
It's no fair.
-Wuh, wuh, welcome to--
-Ah, pigtailed girl!
So the rumors I
heard are true, you
are waitressing at this place!
Please, accept these.
-Gee, uh, thanks.
[laughter]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Stupid Akane.
Still, it's for Ukyo,
so I guess I gotta--
-Come on in.
Would you like to hear
about today's specials?
They're really good.
-Akane Tendo, you too?
What have I done to
deserve such an honor?
We'll talk later.
So boys, what'll it be?
Eat hearty because I'm buying.
-OK, but if you got
complaints later,
I don't want to hear 'em.
-Tuh, take it easy, huh?
-You like it, huh?
-Good one.
-So what's the next exercise?
-No, that part of
this training's over.
Now begins the 100 okonomiyaki.
-98, 99, that 100?
-Of ambition, a
wise man once said,
only by losing everything
are we free to do anything.
You must lose yourself
in making okonomiyaki.
Only then will you
find what you seek.
-I'll do it.
If it means not losing
to that crepe guy again,
I'll cook okonomiyaki
100, 1,000, 10,000 times.
-Now, that is the spirit.
-I thought you said the kids in
our class were going to come.
-With the big discount
we're offering,
I would've thought
they'd be there.
Well, maybe they're outside.
Oh my go--
-What?
what?
-What are you guys doing?
-Oh.
Uh, hey, Akane.
Everyone was like,
already here, so we,
you know, we just kind
of, um, I don't know, uh--
-That jerk's got a lot of
nerve setting up his truck
in front of us.
-You've got me all wrong.
I set up here to help
you girls, not hurt you.
-Huh?
-You're in a slump, right?
Why don't you do
yourselves a favor
and become my first ever
Crepe King franchise?
Sounds pretty good to me.
-Nice try, pancake boy.
Why don't you just admit that
you're trying to take over?
-I admit no such thing.
Besides, there's simply
no fighting evolution.
If you're going to
lose to me anyway,
why not lose to me willingly?
-Crepe King, you come out
here and run your mouth,
but let me tell ya.
It ain't over 'til it's over.
-A match, huh?
And while we're at it, let's
make it losers leave town.
You game?
-Mister, I am the game.
-What is this, pro wrestling?
UKYO: 106.
107.
Here's 108.
What's that?
No more, you say?
If that's so, that
means ambition's finally
come back to my cooking.
Booyah!
Thanks for the training, teach.
-You're welcome.
Just no more okonomiyaki.
-Come on, let's go already.
-Ranma, come on.
Think it over.
How can you be sure that this
isn't what he wanted all along?
-Jeez, give me some credit.
I must have a few
tricks, don't you think?
-And as if that
weren't enough, tempura
flakes mixed with gunpowder!
Here, try this
cement batter too!
-Aw man, it's like glue.
-And now for Ukyo's
all new menu.
I learned the cement
part the hard way.
Not to mention these!
The noodles are kind
of rubbery, but--
-Mistake.
Is that the best you've got?
-What do you think?
Gunpowder pellets.
-Crepe envelopes.
And that's not all.
I hope you enjoy these
tasty treats as well.
-Some kind of tear gas.
-Ranma, are you OK?
-Relax, I've just started.
That was only the appetizer.
And now for the main course,
the golden crepe of death.
-Nice try, but I'm not beat yet.
-Sorry, but considering
that crepe's
made of high tech unbreakable
fiber, I must disagree.
Also, there's the small matter
of the highly explosive C4
whipped cream that's
filling the inside.
-C-- C4 whipped cream?
-Yep.
Poor baby.
Don't you want to
ask for seconds?
-May I have another?
-Ranma, snap out of it.
If you lose, it's not just you.
It's Ukyo's store.
CROWD: Crepe King!
Crepe King!
-And now it's time for dessert.
-Ranma!
-How'd you--
-Tag out, Ranma, honey.
Time for okonomiyaki
Ukyo to take over.
-Come on, Ukyo,
bust him wide open.
-Don't you worry, Ranma.
I haven't been making
one after another
after another
okonomiyaki for nothing.
-Well, guess what, girly?
It doesn't matter how
many okonomiyaki you make.
-And I've got
something to tell you.
Just 'cause you say
it, don't make it so.
-We'll see about that!
Yeah!
-Wow.
I can really smell
what Ukyo's cooking.
-You can trash talk me all
you like, but you know what?
When it's all over, when
the smoke's cleared,
and it's all said and done,
you don't have what it takes.
And I've got two words for you.
Eat it!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
OK, great granddad.
Help me out here.
-Guess that means I win.
-You're wrong.
It wasn't the death
crepe that just exploded.
It was Ukyo.
-What?
-Hey, isn't it time you
went out of business?
Ukyo, Kowanji, special martial
arts okonomiyaki attack.
Batter dragon!
-Bang bang.
-One loser to go.
-All right!
-I knew you could do it, Ukyo.
CROWD: Ukyo!
Ukyo!
UKYO: Well, Ranma?
What do you think?
You can taste the
ambition in it now, right?
-Gee, Ukyo, I don't know.
It tastes kind of
the same, actually.
-And just think,
if it hadn't been
for that monk, and my great
grandpa's golden 100 year
old okonomiyaki, I
would have never won.
-Great grandpa?
Golden okonomiyaki?
What the heck are you--
-Oh, never mind that, Ranma.
What's important is that I
finally got my ambition back.
Now I can make okonomiyaki
every single day for you.
-Every day?
-Well, sure, sugar.
Breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
Isn't it great?
Now, be a good boy
for Ukyo and say ah.
-Aren't you lucky, Ranma?
Just think of all the
money we're going to save.
-I give up.
My sushi just ain't as
good as it used to be.
-Before you give up, ask
yourself, have I truly hit
rock bottom?
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Oh, yeah right!
Ranma's going around
hitting on girls?
You're kidding!
Aren't you?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Ranma the lady killer.
We'll see you there!