[theme song]
That's good.
Next.
Huh?
[laughing] Akane.
Hmm.
Huh?
Hey, it looks like you got
some pretty nice shots here.
Don't mind if I do.
Gosunkugi.
Yes?
You'll take one for
me, too, won't you?
Course.
Oh, wow.
What the-- don't tell me
you guys like that stuff.
That's just plain weird.
Yeah, easy for
you to say, seeing
as you already live
together under the same roof
and everything.
You'd think you'd be more
sympathetic, you know?
Us having to make do with
just pictures, I mean.
And so seeing as all
we do have is pictures,
you ought to be more
charitable like.
So tell me, what is
your objection to our
having pictures anyway?
You running a little
monopoly here, or what?
Oh, please.
Don't make me laugh, you guys.
OK then.
So what is it?
It's just-- oh, man,
enough with the photos!
Oh, no you don't.
Cut it out!
Yo, Gosunkugi, keep going!
Sure.
You guys, I said cut it out!
Huh?
[scream]
Akane!
Oh, no!
I'm OK.
It's just twisted, I think.
See?
Akane!
Someone help.
You two, to the
clinic, quickly.
Uh-oh.
Busted.
Yeah, I'll say.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Akane
Goes to the Hospital.
OK, let's have a look.
[whimpering]
I hate to tell you this,
but it may be broken.
We'd better have a
specialist look at it.
Actually, I think I
know just the place.
It's a clinic near here.
[interposing voices]
How is she?
Well, she's been admitted
to the Ono clinic.
They think her leg
might be broken.
[interposing voices]
It wouldn't have happened
if it wasn't for you guys!
Yeah!
Now wait.
It's not like I--
You what?
Had nothing to do with it?
I didn't mean--
Hmm.
Well, the good news
is it's not broken.
But there's
definitely a fracture.
Luckily, it's nothing a
little bed rest won't fix.
So that means that I--
Will be here two,
three days, at least.
Well, if it can't be helped.
Akane!
Hey, sis.
Promise me you won't die.
You look pretty good
for being half dead.
Wow, it's pretty rare that
you cause a scare, Akane.
I'd like to keep
her two, three days.
You know, just to keep
an eye on her recovery.
Huh?
Doctor!
I'm counting on you to save
my darling little girl.
OK.
Here you are.
K-Kasumi!
So, how are you feeling, Akane?
Good, thanks.
Clumsy me.
I'd love to stay
and help nurse,
if that's all right
with you, Dr. Tofu.
R-r-r-right!
Of course it's all right!
More than of course!
[nervous laughter]
Um, doctor?
K-Kasumi!
Perhaps you'd best let
Dr. Tofu handle this.
She-- she may heal faster,
if you see what I mean.
Oh.
Well, doctor, in
that case, I'll, uh--
L-leave it to me, Kasumi.
Huh?
[sigh]
What's the sigh for?
N-nothing.
He's still at school, if
it's Ranma you're thinking of.
Speaking of whom,
where is that boy?
His own fiancee in
the hospital and all.
Oh, it's OK, really.
I--
He's an idiot.
He ought to have been
the first at your side.
Must I tell him everything?
Gee, she didn't
look that bad to me.
I'll come back later
once they're gone.
You need your rest, Akane.
So--
Take care of her for
us, will you, Dr. Tofu?
Well, sure.
I--
[crash]
Ow!
Ow.
Oh!
W-well then, Akane, I'll
come and check on you later.
OK.
Idiot.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): She's
gonna be mad, I just know it.
I guess I'd better
go and apologize.
[knocking]
Come in.
Oh, Ranma!
Hey.
How's the leg doing, Akane?
Well, Dr. Tofu says
it's not too bad.
I'm so sorry.
I--
It's OK, Ranma.
I was careless is all.
It's no one's fault.
Glad you're not mad.
I'm still sorry it happened.
But Ranma, I'm
wondering, how did it even
happen in the first place?
Oh.
Well, you know, that
stupid Gosunkugi
was sort of taking pictures and
all, and I kind of, you know--
Uh, don't-- don't get me wrong!
I don't want you to think-- I
mean, I'm not jealous, I just--
You just?
It's just, I, uh--
It's just, you--
I just--
Whoa, no!
OK, maybe if I
weren't so serious.
[knocking]
Come in.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Real casual like.
Hiya!
Gosh, you're looking good.
Sorry about before.
It's OK, Ranma.
I was careless is all.
It's no one's fault.
Well, hey, I'm just
glad to see that you
weren't more seriously hurt.
Thank you, Ranma.
Your not being able to let
someone else take pictures?
Well, it's practically
the same as your saying
that-- well, you love me.
Wha--?
I
Just knowing you said that--
well, it's practically worth
breaking my leg for.
Akane!
[scream]
Man, I'm doomed either way.
No matter what I say, it's
going to look like I-- oh, jeez!
I-- huh?
That's strange.
Hmm.
You stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid jerk!
Huh?
Come-- come in!
Here you go.
I brought you dinner, Akane.
I'll bet you're hungry.
[laughter] I sure am.
Wow, you made this?
Looks great.
Doesn't it?
Not too bad, huh?
Mmm, it tastes good.
Curse you, Ranma Saotome!
Because of you, Akane
is-- it's your fault!
Your fault!
Yours!
Curse you!
[sneeze]
[knocking]
Hmm?
Yes?
Hi, Akane!
We've come to visit you.
You look great.
This is from all
of us at school.
I think there's a
card inside, too.
Are you two coming or not?
You got hurt because of us.
We're sorry.
Well, this isn't much, but--
Thanks.
I hope you won't worry about me.
I'm fine.
And besides, it
was all my fault.
Well--
Thank you.
So Akane, did Ranma ever show?
He took off after class
today, and I guess
I figured he'd be here, but--
Sayuri!
Huh?
Mm-mm.
Oh, I'm-- I'm sure
he'll come eventually.
[nervous laughter]
Akane Tendo, fear no more!
With this special
appointment, I, Tatewaki Kuno,
will have you on your
feet in no time at all.
Oh, hey So you guys.
And here's a gift for you
from Mistress Kodachi, which
she asked me to bring you.
What's going on?
[screaming]
[laughter]
Akane, hi!
I heard you were injured.
Are you OK?
Remember, if Ranma's too
much for you, I can always--
Nihao!
Look, Akane!
Special ramen!
Shampoo bring you more, too,
every day you in hospital!
One year, two year, three year!
Uh, gee, thanks.
Hello, Akane.
[scream]
What in the world?
[coughing] Here.
Vitamin drink.
I use it all the time.
[siren]
What was that all about?
Collapsing on a sick call?
Jeez.
Hello, everyone.
It's so nice you've
come to visit.
I do hope you'll
let me thank you.
I've made dinner for
everyone back at the house.
[interposing voices]
See you later, Akane.
Oh, I hope I made enough.
[laughter]
[interposing voices]
We are!
We're next!
Come on, Sayuri!
Come on!
One, two, three, four!
(SINGING) Ya pa pa, ya pa
pa, don't know what to do.
My heart is not a game,
it's mahjong to you.
Ya pa pa, ya pa pa, feel like
such a shrew. [inaudible].
Ranma?
Can I talk to you a sec?
I hate to ask, it being the
middle of the party and all,
but would you mind
bringing this to Akane?
It would really be a big help.
Sure thing.
I'm on my way.
Thank you so much.
[meowing]
Hmm?
C-c-cats?
Apparently Ranma's
on his way over.
He's bringing a change
of clothes for you.
Oh, he is?
He should be here any moment.
And if he should decide to
come through the window,
he needn't say hello to me.
Huh?
Tell him, won't you?
See you tomorrow.
G-good night.
[gasp]
Hey.
Ranma?
K-Kasumi asked me to, uh,
bring you some clothes.
So I, uh--
She did?
Thank you.
Well, I'm-- I'm happy
to do it, actually.
So how's the leg?
Uh-- stay where you are!
Don't come any closer!
I see.
So that's how it's
going to be, huh?
Well, excuse me!
Next time Gosunkugi
starts taking
his pervy little pictures of
stupid, clumsy little you,
I'll let him!
How's that?
You jerk!
Just leave, will you?
You don't gotta tell me twice!
Thanks for nothing!
Huh?
Hmm.
Good morning, Doctor Tofu.
How are you?
Good morning, Akane.
So tell me, did we have
a visitor last night?
Uh-huh.
Through the window.
Yep, that's pretty
much what I thought.
Dr. Tofu, I was wondering,
do you always train this hard?
Hey, setting bones is
hard work, you know.
I need to keep up my strength.
Come to think of it, so do I.
I-- I made it!
I've been to every hospital in
town, but finally, I'm here!
[oinking]
Huh?
P-chan!
You came to see me.
I'm so happy!
So, who's in the
mood for breakfast?
What do little pigs like to eat?
That was so good.
You're very welcome.
Oh, that reminds me, I found
some childhood pictures of you.
You want to see them?
Wow, may I?
[oinking]
Oh my goodness, is this you?
I can hardly believe how
cute you were back then!
And I'm not anymore?
You know what I-- huh?
Huh?
Pictures of Kasumi!
And here's some more, and more?
You weren't supposed
to see those!
Oh, doctor!
Please, Akane!
Please don't tell Kasumi, OK?
OK?
Don't tell her, please?
Pretty please?
[laughing] OK.
I won't.
I'll just go put the
closet in the album, OK?
I mean, the album in the closet.
--[laughing] Pictures
of the one you love.
[bell ringing]
[trumpet music]
What, are you guys
gonna party again?
Yeah.
It's rude to impose, you know.
And what is that
you've got there?
Best karaoke hits collection.
We've got a whole routine
all worked out, don't we?
What a bunch of hypocrites.
Until Akane's discharged,
we'll keep it up, too.
Yeah!
How's this pose, Akane?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
No no no, like this.
Oh, what do you know?
[laughter]
You stink!
Get off the stage!
[interposing voices]
Hi-yah!
No fair, Shampoo!
You cheated!
Of course I cheat.
Why you--
[phone ringing]
Can't somebody get the phone?
Hello?
Tendo Dojo?
AKANE (ON PHONE): Uh, hi.
It's Akane.
Look, I'm getting out a day
early, so I thought I call.
Well, I'll-- I'll--
I'll go get your dad, OK?
Just stay on the line.
AKANE (ON PHONE): No, don't!
Uh, that's all.
Good night.
I-- uh.
[laughter]
[sigh]
[snoring]
Done, just in time.
But then again,
if I don't hurry--
[grunting]
That's it.
Careful.
OK.
Congratulations
on your release.
If there's no one
else, I can always
help you make your
way back home.
Oh, thanks for the offer, but
I can probably make it, though.
I'll be fine.
Now that's the Akane I know.
Stubborn right to the last.
Although I think
you've got a helper.
See?
What?
Akane?
Ranma?
[squealing]
Easy, now.
Let's just watch them, shall we?
Did you do that?
Uh-huh.
And I've also got--
What?
Hey, that's when--
Came out pretty good, huh?
Oh, wow.
So you've had it all this time?
Well-- well, yeah,
but not because I--
Aww, ain't that sweet?
I messed up, he says.
I'm so embarrassed.
Now we look stupid.
No kidding.
Way to go!
Would that I were so loved.
What meaning of this?
I swear, the minute
your back's turned.
Never fear, Kuno is here!
Oh, no you don't!
Come on!
They're getting away!
Somebody, quick, after them!
No way we're staying for that.
Hang on tight!
OK.
Hey, what's that?
Don't-- don't do that!
Hey, hey, cut it out!
I can't see!
[screaming]
[theme song]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Catching monsters
is a martial artist's duty.
Oh, admit it, you just want
to go to the hot springs!
Next time on Ranma 1/2-- Mystery
of the Marauding Octopus Pot!
We'll see you there.