[theme music]
Sorry.
Off to work!
Some of us have to work
for a living, you know.
-Jeez, why's he in such a hurry?
-Why must he be this way?
[sobbing]
NARRATOR: The Witch Who Love
Me-- a Japanese ghost story.
[clock ticking]
-Drink your tea, Father.
It's getting cold.
-He's been like this
ever since he got home.
-Today was the day
that the town council
met to decide on
the new chairman.
I wonder if something
happened to Father there?
-Wow.
Do you think Dad
volunteered for it?
-Why would he want to do
something stupid like that?
-But Father would have been
so perfect for the job.
Everyone needs to be
good at something.
And Father certainly
has nothing else to do.
-You've got it wrong!
It isn't that simple.
You see--
-It's like this, gentlemen.
We can't have a summer
festival without a budget.
And we can't have
a summer budget
without a special summer,
uh-- budget chairman, eight?
Can anyone recommend
someone suitable?
-Uh, gee, well, why look any
further when we've already
got the perfect man for the job?
-Oh, no.
-A hero for the masses.
That's Soun Tendo.
-Oh, come now.
Surely you needn't go that far.
-Oh, but you forget how well
we know you in this town.
Your ability to remain
calm in a crisis
is the stuff of local legend.
-Yeah, and, uh, don't forget
his, uh, physical prowess.
-Thank you.
Thank you very much.
-You might say this job
was made for you, Tendo.
-It happened so quickly.
-Dad, that's great!
-Congratulations, Father.
-Sounds more like
you got railroaded.
But congrats anyway.
-You don't know the
half of it, son.
-We're sure you're eager
to assume your new duties.
-Just let me at that budget.
-Budget?
No, first you need to catch
us that underwear thief.
-Did you say underwear thief?
-Surely you've
heard of him, Tendo.
There's been quite a few
complaints, you know.
You won't let us
down, will you, Tendo?
Ha ha!
-It's not that I don't
appreciate their faith in me.
But how am I to stop
the master's crimes?
What if they discover I've
been harboring the underwear
thief all along?
What if the master were to
take advantage of my position
for his own evil ends?
What will become of this
poor, defenseless town?
-Let me guess.
Legal panty raids, more free
meals, and be nice to a freak
week?
-Cut it out.
Can't you see he's upset?
Dad, don't worry.
They'll never connect
those things to you.
And besides, maybe
he'll be good.
-Face it.
If the master finds
out, I'm a dead man.
Ranma, promise me you won't
breathe a word of this
to the master!
You either, Akane.
-Dad, don't worry.
-Welcome to politics.
Gee, Daddy, do I get a
kick back in my allowance?
-Welcome home, Nabiki.
-How did you know that?
-Hey, if you'd
wanted to be modest,
why'd you put that
sign up outside?
-Ahh!
Saotome!
How could you do this to me?
What have I ever
done to deserve this?
-Advertise, why don't you?
-It's a bit too much, isn't it?
-Tell me something.
What if the Master should
happen to see that?
-Chairman Soun, eh?
Way to go.
Atta boy.
-Please, Master.
This isn't easy for
me to say, but I--
-Can the melodrama.
I understand.
You worry you'll be like
to this underwear thief.
-You do understand.
-Then you respect my position?
-Of course.
What, you think
just because I like
to steal women's
underwear that I'm
some kind of unfeeling monster?
[sobbing]
-Oh, what a wise
and clever master.
-That's right.
Which is why I'm coming
along on your nightly rounds!
Hurry up!
You're falling behind!
-Please, Master.
How are we to prevent any
crimes unless we slow down
to see them?
-Don't be an idiot.
We're here to commit
crimes, not prevent 'em.
Hubba, hubba, hubba.
Fetch, Genma!
-Yes, sir.
Ahh!
-Have you gone mad, Saotome?
-Sorry, Tendo.
I guess I got a little carried
away in the heat of the moment.
-Come on, you two.
Time's a-wasting.
All right.
Mm, lacey.
-Please, Master.
Put up the lantern so they
can't make a positive ID.
-How the heck else am I
supposed to do my work, huh?
-But this isn't work, Master.
It's an offense punishable by
state and local authorities.
And if they catch--
-Why you gotta always
be so negative?
That's right.
Load 'em up, boys.
Throw 'em in there.
-Ladies and gentlemen
of the town council,
it's with great sadness
that I, Soun Tendo,
tender to you my
official resignation.
-Nothing like the satisfaction
of a job well done, huh boys?
What do you say?
In thanks for your
help, why don't you
just go ahead and hang on to
your share of tonight's haul?
It's the least I can do.
No underwear thief's gonna
slip by with us on the job,
eh, Soun?
-They won't?
-Course not.
Which is why we'll
do it again tomorrow!
-Tendo?
-They said you were
looking for me.
Hm?
Jeez, what's the
matter with him?
-I don't know.
But my guess is that
Happosai has got something
to do with it.
-Help me.
Please, son.
I've got nowhere else to turn.
-Uh--
-Ah, yes.
Oh, so lovely.
Still, why does it always seem
that there's something missing?
For some reason I'm just
not enjoying it as much
as I used to.
Maybe if I started passing
over the smaller sizes.
Going for silk, instead
of cotton-- huh?
Ranma?
Quit it!
Stop following me!
-Hey, it ain't my idea of
a good time, either, OK?
-Then why don't you leave
me alone and-- oh, hacha!
Will you get a load
of that/ How sweet!
-Oh no you don't.
No you don't!
I said no!
-Why you-- why can't
you leave me to my work?
-I'm sorry, gramps,
but I can't do that.
-Oh, so that's the
way it is, is it?
Well, name your price.
What's it gonna take?
Will one of these
change your mind?
-No thanks.
I can't be bought!
-Hurry up, slowpoke!
-Get back here, you little--
-Catch me if you can!
Woo-hoo!
-Come here!
-You couldn't catch
a cold at that rate!
Oh, Ranma.
Come here, cupcake.
Try this one on.
-That's it.
They'll be coming
for me any minute.
[sobbing]
-Father?
The former chairman's
downstairs to see you.
-I'm ruined!
Hello there.
What brings you here?
-Wait up, you little freak!
-What was that that just
ran by on the patio?
-Nothing.
Nothing.
-Keep 'em shaking--
-You little pervert!
-Excuse me, but you're
kind of hurting my neck.
-Here's your tea.
-Why thank you, my dear.
I'm sorry to bother you at
this time of night, Tendo,
but you know, it's just
the darnedest thing.
When you were elected
into town office
we thought for sure that this
underwear thievery would stop.
But it's only gotten
worse, not better.
We're at a real loss here.
-Sir, I don't know what to say.
I know that I've let you down--
-Now, now, that's
not why I'm here.
The fact is, Soun,
old boy, we're
more worried
something might happen
to one of our local treasures.
-Local treasures?
-You know, it's one of
those historical artifacts.
A lady's brassiere, actually.
It's stored in an
antique shop downtown.
-A lady's brassiere, you say?
MASTER (VOICEOVER): A
lady's brassiere, is it?
-But it's more than
a local treasure.
Some people even believe
it has magical powers.
-Well, them, whose
antique store is it?
-Actually, it's mine.
-So you're the proprietor, then.
-Which is all the
more reason I'm
worried the thief will
attempt a break-in.
You see, I'll be out
of town for a few days.
And I need someone
to look after it.
-Very well.
I'll do whatever I can.
-I knew I could count on you.
Well, then, since
you'll be guarding it,
there's something
you should know.
-I'm listening.
Huh?
-I ain't your doormat.
How dare you step on me?
-Shh.
Lower your voice.
They're just getting
to the good part!
-Lower this, you little-- ah!
-What an amateur.
-What's going on out there?
-Oh, I'm sure it's nothing
we need to be concerned with.
Quickly, before we're
interrupted again.
Whisper it to me.
MASTER (VOICEOVER): Who do
they think they're fooling?
If I want that bra
it's as good as gone.
-Be careful out there.
-It's obvious why
Ranma has to go,
but why do I have to tag along?
-What is that supposed to mean?
-It's a bra, isn't it?
Aren't you always showing
yours off to Happosai?
-You bet she does.
OK if I tag along, too?
-Actually, Master, you're the
one we'll be guarding it from.
-Why, I never!
What are you insinuating?
-I'm sorry, Master.
But the answer is no.
We can't risk letting you near
a bra, much less this one.
-No fair!
No fair!
Why are you being so mean to me?
-Cry all you like, Master.
I'm afraid it'll do you no good.
-Dad, I was so proud of you.
You didn't let him
push you around.
-I was really
something, wasn't I?
Ah, well, it won't do much good.
He'll come.
He can't help himself.
I may have brought us
some time, that's all.
-You know, Tendo,
maybe things are
starting to turn around for us.
-Who knows, Saotome?
You may be right.
MASTER (VOICEOVER):
Laugh it up, boys.
I'll have that bra
before you know it.
-Cursed antique shop, eh?
-Whoa.
Just like that TV show.
-There it is!
The brassiere.
-Uh, you'd better let
me have a look see.
-Hey!
What do you think
you're doing, Saotome?
-Aw, come on.
A little peek won't hurt.
-Absolutely not.
-Don't be so stingy, Tendo.
-You're acting
like the old freak.
[crash]
-Quick, we've gotta catch
the freak before he--
[shouting]
We're too late!
-Master, please.
You mustn't open that box.
-Yeah.
Nice try.
I heard everything you
said, so me and my bra
will be leaving now.
-Wait up, you little freak.
-Master, please.
Listen to me!
Whatever you do,
don't open that box!
-So when do hear the
rest of the story?
-After him!
-Why can't they mind
their own business?
-OK, gramps.
Hand over the bra.
-I don't wanna!
-I'm gonna--
-Gonna what?
-That's enough, you two.
Ranma, that's quite enough.
-What do you mean,
that's enough?
-Yeah, what do you mean?
-Just like I said, children.
Let's let the
Master have the bra.
-You really mean that?
-Of course I do, Master.
Why, you're a martial
artist too, aren't you?
We'll let you guard it.
-What do you know?
I take back those
things I said about you.
I'll take good care of it, boys.
Ooh.
What a beauty!
I was right to pass up
on those smaller sizes.
Oh, whoa, what is it doing?
I can't-- I've got-- ah-- hey!
Who turned out the lights?
I can't--
-[mumbling].
I mean, that's just what
I was worried about.
-Now what are you
babbling about?
-That isn't just an
ordinary bra, Master.
It's a cursed item
said to have belonged
to an evil, jealous woman named
Yohkihi who killed any man who
dared to look at
any woman but her.
Oh, the evil!
Oh, the terror!
-Will he ever be
able to take it off?
-It's Yohkihi's curse that you
never look at another woman
again.
You'll wear that bra for
the rest of your life.
Please forgive me, Master.
You've left me no choice!
-Stop grovelling.
Since it's such a cute bra
I'll let you off the hook
and forgive you.
It really is a cute
one, too, isn't it?
Whoa, what's-- what's going on?
-Who disturbs my slumber?
-What's happening?
-Look!
It's the ghost of Yohkihi!
-Where?
Where?
I can't see her.
-Ugh!
Is he the one who--
how revolting.
Forget it.
The bra comes off.
-Hey!
Put it back!
Huh?
Wow.
What a looker.
Come here, baby!
-Get away from me, you freak!
It's been a while, but
it hasn't been that long.
Ooh.
Now he's more my type.
-You mean me?
-Come to mama, little boy.
-Ranma, what's the matter?
Ranma?
Hey, you leave him alone!
-Stay back, girl!
-Akane!
Huh?
[laughing]
-That's right.
Come to mama.
-Stop!
You mustn't hurt an
innocent bystander.
Allow me to accept whatever
you had planned for him.
-I have no interest
in old men or pandas!
-Ahh!
-Come here, sexy.
-I'm right here, sugar-lips!
So, how'd you like
my instant face-lift?
Whaddaya say me and
you go somewhere-- agh!
-I told you, I'm
not that desperate.
Let's continue
where we left off.
I believe you were
about to kiss me.
Ah!
-Well, are you
gonna kiss or not?
-You're female!
-Sorry to disappoint ya.
What's the matter, your
tricks only work on boys?
-I'm going to silence that
impertinent tongue of yours
for good!
Take this!
-Ranma.
-Foolish mortal!
Taste the wrath of Yohkihi!
Haha!
I'll squeeze the life
out of both of you!
-I can't breathe.
-Akane, hang in there.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): There's
gotta be some way that we can--
-Ranma!
Akane!
-Here!
Bring the hot water, Pop!
-Ranma, don't do it.
If you turn into a boy
she'll hypnotize you again.
-What other choice do I got?
Hurry up.
The water!
-Yohkihi, baby!
Gimme some sugar, baby!
-Oh, well.
Huh?
-My love, it's you!
-Hm?
-Oh, my love.
How I've longed for
you through the years.
-I'm not who you think I am.
I'm just a middle-aged nobody!
-Come back, my love.
-Oh, phew!
What disgusting taste.
-Careful.
She could be your ancestor.
-Ugh.
-That Saotome's one sly fox.
-Unforgivable.
How dare he flirt with
his master's woman?
[scream]
-You're-- a panda!
-Yohkihi, baby--
-Get it off of me!
-We're cursed to be
together, remember?
Come on.
Oh, please, honey.
-I can't bear it!
Bound!
For eternity!
-Get it off of me!
-Look.
Dad, she's gone.
-Yohkihi, baby!
Please come back!
I'll be good!
Oh, at least I have
this to remember her by.
-The bra!
-It's dissolving!
-She-- she won't even
leave me that much.
[sobbing]
I can't stay here.
Gotta go away.
Gotta get myself together.
-Master, no.
-Don't try to stop me.
I gotta go.
-Say it isn't so.
-Don't expect us to stop you.
-Oh, say it isn't so!
-Farewell.
-It's a beautiful day in the
neighborhood, eh, Saotome?
-For the first time in
years, we're at peace.
-Well, the Master is
indeed formidable.
But I'd have to say
this round went to us,
wouldn't you, Saotome?
-And the best thing is
your political career
is now back on
track, like before.
-What do you think, Ranma?
Will Happosai ever come back?
-Oh, sure he will.
I bet you he's out
stealing right now.
-You're probably right.
-Now, now, remember
what they say.
Talk behind his back,
Master comes back.
-What a haul!
What a haul!
Woo-hoo!
I'm feeling much better!
-Ladies and gentlemen
of the town council,
it's with great sadness
that I, Soun Tendo,
tender to you my
official resignation.
[theme song playing]
[speaking japanese]
-Lost to Shampoo?
Oh, I can't bear it!
Mm, these noodles
are pretty good.
Hey, what do you mean,
they'll make me super strong?
Next time on Ranma
1/2, Transform-- Akane,
the Super-duper Girl.
See you there!