[music playing]
[theme music]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Here I am
again back where it all began,
the only place that ever
brings me happiness.
The only place where I have
someone who cares for me.
But can I be content as
nothing more than her pet.
-Oh, if only there
could be some way for me
to let her know of the
feelings I have for her.
GIRL: Why don't you write
a love letter in green ink?
-What?
-Yeah.
I hear that way people can't
help but fall in love with you.
-What a great idea.
I'll go straight to the
supermarket on the way home.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Yeah, right.
Girls will believe in
just about anything.
RYOGA: Give me all the
green ink you've got.
NARRATOR: "Ryoga's Miracle Cure.
Hand Over That Soap."
-Ahh.
I did it.
Aw.
-Aren't you glad we came
to the public bath, boy?
-We wouldn't have had to if
you hadn't have gone and busted
the tub.
-Get him.
Get him.
-Let's make him into a pet.
OK.
-Hm.
To Akane Tendo.
What the--
-Hey, you give that back.
-Dear Akane, I have always lo--
-That's mine.
-The boy's side sure is noisy.
[squeaking]
Shampoo.
-That last time Shampoo be cat.
Start today, Ranma
belong Shampoo.
-Did I miss something?
-You know this one is?
-It's soap?
-No is just soap.
This one magic.
You use soap.
You get wet.
And still you no change.
-You don't change?
-Shampoo no more be cat.
Ranma no more hate Shampoo.
-Can I have a look at it?
-What I look like?
This soap too, too precious.
-Na.
Na.
-Give it back.
-Get it if you can.
Na.
-You deserve that.
See ya.
-Shampoo no can
afford lose that soap.
It's important.
-Wait a minute.
Where are you--
RANMA: Get it off.
Get it off of me.
Come on.
Get it off.
Get it off of me.
RYOGA: OK, Ranma.
Now, you've done it.
RANMA: Get it off.
Get it off.
-That's my boy, all right.
RANMA: Help.
RYOGA: Come back here.
RANMA: Get this off of me.
-There's a letter for me?
GENMA: Mhm.
I found it at the public bath.
-Oh wow.
I wonder who it's from.
Hey, that has my name on it.
Not yours.
-Dear Akane, I have always--
-That's none of your business.
-Oh, what's the matter?
You write something you
don't want me to hear?
-Oh, so then the
letter's from you, Ryoga.
-Just give it back, will you?
-Now, would be a good
time to thank me.
Don't you think?
-Thank you for what?
Trying to embarrass me.
-Ryoga!
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
I'm going to turn
into a pig in front of Akane.
-Why not kill me and
get it over with?
-What the--
RYOGA: I didn't feel it.
I must be imagining it.
-Hey, what's the
matter with you?
Am I the only one who's
noticed you're all wet?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
It's not a dream.
This means-- this means
that I'm cured of the pig.
Which means we're
equal he and I. No.
I'm even more equal.
-Akane, I--
-Yes.
-Read that letter I gave you.
Read it, and you'll
know my true feelings.
We'll discuss it later.
-But why?
Why didn't he change
when he got wet?
Why didn't he?
-The ink's bled
all over the page.
-Why didn't you change, huh?
Tell me.
-That boy.
He use Shampoo's
soap without ask.
-Oh, Akane.
At last our time has come.
I don't know why,
but for some reason,
I'm no longer changing
when I get wet.
Meaning that, in
other words, Akane,
tell me that you'll be my girl.
-I'll finally be able to
ask her to go out with me.
-Check it out.
You really are cured
of the pig, aren't you?
-Ranma.
-So what's your secret?
You wouldn't hold out
on pal, would you?
-Wouldn't I. Besides
there's nothing to tell you.
-Ah, come on.
Don't play hard to get.
Who's your best buddy, huh?
-You're not my buddy.
-I am begging you on my
hands and knees here.
-You're on top of
my head, you jerk.
Jet blast!
I got nothing else
to say to you, Ranma.
The one I want is Akane.
Oh, where can you be?
Where are you, Akane?
-Hi there.
-Ahh!
-I'm, uh, glad we
ran into each other.
So aren't you going to tell
me what was in the letter?
-I've kind of forgot.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): What's
the matter with you?
Do you want her to
think you're a coward?
Why don't you just say it?
Say it.
-Akane, listen.
-I'm listening.
-I-- I-- uh, that is-- ooh, uh.
I mean-- will you-- ahh!
I can't say it.
-Ryoga?
RANMA: Waterproof soap?
SHAMPOO: Used to wash body.
And no change when get wet.
Only Shampoo lose it at
the public bathhouse.
-Which goes to explain Ryoga's
sudden change in fortune.
-Shampoo use anything
get it back from him.
-What-- what are
you going to do?
I mean you're not going
to shoot him, are you?
-Shoot with this.
[sigh]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Akane.
Oh, Akane.
Huh?
An arrow?
To Ryoga Hibiki.
This is-- this
is-- this is-- this
is a letter from
my beloved Akane.
A wonderland of pools and open
air baths, Healthy Leisure
Land.
I Admit one.
This means she's
inviting me on a date.
Ah.
It's good to be alive.
Oh, Akane!
Made it.
It's a good thing that I
left as early as I did.
At least, I think that
this is the right place.
"Meet you on the boy's side.
Love your Akane.
PS-- don't forget to bring soap.
Teehee."
Asking to meet on
this side of the bath,
Akane's not usually like that.
Oh yeah, right.
I almost forgot.
Hopefully, this
guide will tell me
where's a good place for a date.
The most important
thing is mood.
OK.
That sounds-- gah!
-You never fear.
Cupid twins is here.
-T-t-twins?
[giggling]
-She's Cu.
I'm Pid.
Do you want us to
wash your back?
-Buh, b-b-back.
You mean as in mine?
-Oh, what a big
strong back you have.
I'll bet the girls
must go ga-ga for you.
Eh, big stud.
OK.
And now to wash your hair.
There it is.
The waterproof soap.
See you later, alligator.
-Not for awhile, crocodile.
Soap belong me, not you.
Come get if can.
-Ah.
I just want to borrow it.
Come on.
Don't be so greedy.
I'll give it back.
I promise.
Come on, Shampoo.
SHAMPOO: Nuh-uh.
-And with this waterproof soap.
I'll never have to
turn into a girl again.
-Waterproof soap?
-It's cold.
Shampoo.
-Ah-ha.
So this is the reason I
don't change when I get wet.
Ha, ha.
Now that I know what it does,
I'll never let go of this soap.
KASUMI: I guess it
is kind of nice.
-I don't know, Akane.
Therapeutic baths?
Are we kind of young.
-Ah, who cares?
So long as it's fun,
what's it matter?
RANMA: Cat.
Cat.
-What are you doing?
-Akane.
What-- what are you doing here?
-That's what I want to know.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Akane's late.
I sure hope she hasn't changed
her mind about the date.
RANMA: All right.
Sorry, pal.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): So
long as I've got this,
I can splash myself all I want.
What?
What did I do?
RYOGA: [laughing].
Yeah, right, Ranma.
Like I'd let you walk
off with the original.
-Why you.
This soap was a gift
to me from the gods.
I'll never let go of it.
It's from Akane.
Please note new meeting place.
I'm on my way.
-Ranma.
-Shampoo?
-Shampoo fix real date
for Akane and Ryoga.
-Huh?
-If he get Akane,
then he give us soap.
-I suppose you
got a point there.
-Meet at outdoor
waterfalls is OK.
But meet who?
There's no one here.
-Akane.
-Hi, Ryoga.
-Hi, Akane.
Thanks for inviting me
on a date today, Akane.
-Huh.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Him on a date?
But I thought that he--
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER): Meet
at outdoor waterfalls.
Is OK.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Aha.
Now what's Shampoo up to?
-A squid?
-She pid.
Me Cu.
-Otherwise known as the
Cupid twins of love.
That's right get all
that nasty ink off.
-OK.
I'll even use my special soap.
-Sucker.
Hand it over.
-That soap mine.
-Shampoo.
Ranma.
What are you two up to?
-So it's you too.
-So you saw through
our disguise?
-Big deal.
-Ugh.
I may have fallen for your
trick once, but I guarantee you,
you won't trick me again.
-What matter, Ryoga.
You know want kiss me?
-Of course, but--
-OK now.
Close eye.
-OK.
-He fell for it.
-How dare you pretend to
be me, and use my voice.
I sound nothing like that.
-Where'd he hide
the stupid soap?
-Ryoga, are you OK?
-Butt out.
Will ya?
-You butt out.
You set me and poor
Ryoga up on a date,
just so that you
could steal his soap.
-It wasn't like that.
-It exactly like that.
-I'd expect this from Shampoo.
But Ranma, how could you?
-I can explain.
-Consider one thing.
While you and Shampoo
are up to no good,
Ryoga and I will be on our date.
-Akane.
-Ryoga, you're finally awake.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Huh?
I'm here.
Akane's here.
-This wouldn't be
a date, would it?
-Sure is.
-Yes!
So where do you
want me to take you?
-I don't know.
-OK.
OK.
That's what the
guide's here for.
Let me see.
Romantic date spots.
I got it.
Let's go to movie.
-Kind of like a
haunted house, huh.
-Oh wait a minute.
Where's the popcorn?
-Jeez.
That dumb Akane.
Couldn't they have found a
place a little less dark?
-Sometimes, dark places good.
-Ah!
-Akane!
Akane, where are you?
Akane!
Where are you?
Akane?
-Where you hide soap, stupid?
-So now, what are you up to?
-Well, excuse me for breaking
up you and Ryoga's fun.
Here I got a good reason too,
but I bet you won't believe me.
-Reason?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): To
stand here and ignore
all Akane's signals would
mean that I'm not a man.
Oh, Akane.
Here she is taking
the iniative again.
-Waterproof soap?
-Yeah, and if I
get my hands on it,
I'll never have to
be a girl again.
So that's why--
-So that's why I supposedly
asked Ryoga out on a date.
So that you could be
selfish and get your hands
on that stupid soap.
-Right.
Didn't I already say that?
AKANE: Then, in that case.
Don't follow us.
Well, Ryoga.
Shall we?
-OK.
-We still no have soap.
-Come on, Akane.
Can't you just
leave Ryoga behind?
-You know what
you did back there
in that cave meant
a lot to me, Akane.
-It did.
-I want to tell you
that I-- that I--
-It's OK, Ryoga.
I know what you're trying to s--
-No.
Don't speak.
Don't speak, my dear.
Allow me to take the lead.
-Hey, you jerk.
Put her down.
-Look.
Look.
Now, they real couple for sure.
-Oh, why that sneaky little--
-If you want the
soap so much, Ranma,
then why don't you take it?
-Hiya.
You swallow soap.
-Try not to hold it
against me, huh, pal.
After all, with that soap,
you can get other girls,
so you won't mind
if I take Akane.
-You've got it all wrong.
You-- you don't understand.
-Good boy.
Spit up soap.
Good.
-At last, we can be alone.
Oh, Akane.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): He's, uh,
kind of a passionate guy.
-At last, you can be my girl.
Oh, Akane.
-That Ryoga, what
an idiot he is.
Imagine being attracted to
a mule-faced chick like you.
-Well, excuse me.
Who's fault do you
think it is anyway
that poor Ryoga
thinks the two of us
have got some kind
of future together.
-Akane, I found you.
-Why do you keep running away?
Am I doing something wrong?
I thought that in that
in the cave that we--
-I, uh-- I don't know
what you're talking about.
-Why can't we go back
to the way we were.
Akane!
-Check it out.
For a guy who's never been in
love before, he's pretty funny.
-Haha, Ranma.
Why he's so funny he might
just crush me to death.
-Huh?
Akane.
Why does she keep
running away from me?
Tell me why.
AKANE: Ah!
Ryoga, please.
Please be more gentle with me.
I'm scared.
-Akane.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): All
the time I spent with you.
No matter how kind you were to
me, or how much you loved me,
it was never enough
for my man's heart.
For the first time ever, my
Akane, I embrace you as a man.
-Hey, what in the
world are you doing
wearing Ranma's clothes, Akane.
-Not much.
We're going to go on ahead.
All right.
-Oh, Akane.
Akane!
Akane.
Are you--
-Was it good for you too?
Hey, waterproof soap.
-Ranma!
You are a dead man.
-What do you know.
Looks like your soap ain't
so waterproof after all.
-This last time Shampoo
trust Jusenkyo products.
Is rip off.
-Well, you know what they say.
You get what you
pay for-- eh, not.
-I hate to say it, but after
seeing his true feelings
like that, I feel
sorry for whoever
ends up being
Ryoga's girlfriend.
RANMA: Good thing I sacrificed
myself for you, huh, Akane.
[theme music]
AKANE: Do you really get
to go to China if you win?
I think it's great that
everyone's competing, but--
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," "The
Anything Goes Obstacle Course."
We'll see you there.