[theme song]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
"Boy Meets Mom, Part 2.
Someday, Somehow."
Stupid old man, making
that kind of promise
without even asking me.
Come on.
I'm saying it right
now, you furry jerk.
You got me into this
mess, so now it's
your turn to get
me out of it, OK?
I thought you'd say that.
I'll take you out
with Mom's own sword.
Think quick, Pop.
What do you want
on your tombstone?
Take it like a man!
KASUMI: It's so
nice of you to help.
Oh, it's the least I could do.
And where do you think
you're going, huh?
Uh-oh.
Huh?
Lanko, look out.
It's hot!
SOUN (VOICEOVER): Oh, no!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): If he gets
hit with that hot soup, he'll--
NABIKI (VOICEOVER):
Ranma's toast.
Nice catch, Lanko.
I'm very impressed.
SOUN: Any spicy cod roe left?
KASUMI: I'll get it, Father.
NABIKI: It's good.
AKANE: Sure is.
So, Akane, they tell me
that you're Ranma's fiancee.
Is that true?
Yes, but I--
Oh, hey.
My favorite.
NODOKA: Ranma, he--
Here, Father.
Your rice.
Ah, thanks.
So, as his fiancee, would
you say that he's manly?
What?
Uh-huh.
Is he cool?
How about handsome?
Uh-huh.
Is he?
Think you could've stretched
that pause any longer?
You know something?
Ranma looks exactly like you.
Really?
Oh, you're right, now
that you mention it.
Oh, well.
So what?
You're right.
More important, what
hobbies does he have?
Yes, hobbies are nice.
I guess he likes martial arts.
Isn't it more like
girls' clothes?
Girls' clothes?
My son likes girls' clothes?
Oh, so he's a
horticulturist, then?
Oh, good.
OK.
Now what did I do
to tick you off?
Dear me.
Was it something that I said?
Oh, come on.
Maybe you should just confess,
Ranma, and get it over with?
Why?
Cause even blackmail
by Nabiki's better
than having to commit seppuku.
Blackmail?
Come on.
Are you saying you won't?
You're missing
the point, Ranma.
What?
Me and Akane, we-- we'd
like to see our mom,
but-- but she's gone now.
So, Ranma.
Wha-- what is it?
I'll stay quiet for
5,000 this one time only.
Oh, man.
For a while, I thought
she was serious.
Hello, Lanko.
I'm sorry, but it seems I'll
be sleeping in here with you
tonight.
I do hope that's all right.
Uh.
Of course it is.
Uh, but--
The confession
part's up to you,
but she's still your mother.
You can at least spend one
night together as a family.
Mrs. Saotome's going home.
Going home?
First thing tomorrow.
I just thought you
should know, Ranma.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Leaving, huh?
So soon too.
I mean, she just got here.
Ranma.
She's just dreaming.
Even when she's sleeping,
she looks for me.
Mom, I just--
Ranma.
Ranma!
Why, oh, why aren't
you the manly son
I've dreamed of having?
Oh, that poor woman.
She must've had a nightmare.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): For
her sake and Ranma's, this
can't go on much longer.
Well then, I'll be off.
It's really a shame Ranma and
my husband couldn't be here.
You're welcome here any time.
Bye.
We'll see you later, OK?
Goodbye.
It was nice meeting you, Lanko.
Bye.
Take care of yourself, Lanko.
Doesn't this feel good?
Makes you wonder what all the
fuss back there was all about,
don't it, boy?
Something wrong?
Pop, didn't she seem
kinda sad to you?
Ranma?
You treated your
own wife like a bum,
and now you're acting
all proud about it.
You outta be ashamed, old man.
Need I remind you, boy,
how your mother expects
us to commit ritual
seppuku if you
don't become a man among men?
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
That hurt, by the way.
None of this would've
happened if you hadn't
made that stupid promise.
Just get over it
already, will you?
I can't believe I forgot this.
[splash]
Hey, look.
It's that lady.
Why, it's Lanko and Mr. Panda.
Fishing, are we?
You're welcome any time.
Bye.
Yeah, we'll see you next time.
Goodbye.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Mrs. Saotome.
Mrs. Saotome.
Oh, Akane?
What is it, dear?
You said I'd meet her?
What made you do that?
I had to.
I promised.
She's expecting you in
the park this Sunday.
You don't really want your
mom to leave without knowing
who you are, do you, Ranma?
Uh.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Mom, be honest.
Am I the kind of guy
you wanted me to be?
Oh, Ranma.
You're more than I dreamed--
handsome, kind, a man
among men.
True.
As long as she doesn't
find out I change--
Just try not to build
it up too much, OK?
Also, you probably
better not tell your dad.
Um, OK.
OK.
I guess I'll be heading out now.
Ranma, wait.
Um, here.
There were so many left
over, I-- it's for your mom.
Thanks, Akane.
Really.
Why are you looking that way?
Sorry.
I just-- I just now
realized that I-- that I do
have a mom after all.
Well, of course.
We all do.
He's agreed?
Uh-huh.
But um, you should
know that he--
No, no.
Please don't tell me.
I haven't seen him in so long.
But still, he is my own son,
and that's all I need to know.
AKANE: It'll be perfect.
Your mom can't wait to meet you.
Not so fast.
Where are you going?
Back off.
If you wanna get by, first,
you gotta go through me.
If you wanna go to your
mother, boy, first,
go through your father.
Done.
Aw, come on.
Wait up, boy.
Can't you see?
I only do it for your own good.
I only want you to
be a great martial--
Be quiet!
OK, boy, then how about this?
You seem to think
you'd be safe so long
as you don't change right
there in front of her.
What if somebody splashed
you or something?
You're worrying over nothing.
OK, let's say
you're on the street.
What if a water main breaks?
Oh, yeah.
As if.
Then how about this scenario?
You get tripped by a
door-to-door goldfish salesman.
Yeah, right.
Come on.
Why can't you accept
I'm trying to save you
from ritual seppuku?
And you actually have the
gall to call yourself a father?
Mr. Saotome.
I knew you'd try to pull
something like this.
Ranma?
Ranma.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
He's finally here.
You look just like your father.
That's not Ranma.
Is that you, Akane?
Why are you here?
Please pay no attention
to what Mr. Saotome--
No, no.
Don't tell me.
I haven't seen him in so long.
But still, he is my
own son, and what else
does a mother need to know?
You have no idea.
Ranma.
Ranma?
Where?
Ranma, over here.
We've been waiting for you.
Akane.
I told you he'd--
Huh?
Your father must've taken her.
OK, Pop, if that's
how you want it, fine.
Cause someway, somehow,
wherever he's got you,
Mom, I will find you.
They're over there, stupid.
Over there.
Where?
If he thinks he's
getting away with this.
Mrs. Saotome.
He's not coming?
Why not?
WAITRESS: Come on in.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): She's here.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
So let her find out.
I'll show her a me more
manly than she thought.
Ranma?
I-- is that a boy's hand?
Mom, I--
Ranma.
Oh, Ranma.
Oh!
I'm so sorry!
Lanko?
What are you doing?
I thought you
were someone else.
Of course.
Right here if I could.
Something to say, Mr. Panda?
And there's plenty more
where that came from.
That's our cue to go.
Come on.
What's going on?
RANMA: Take that.
Akane, be honest.
It's me.
Rama doesn't want to see me.
No.
I mean, he does.
He mustn't,
otherwise, why would he
keep me waiting all this time?
Well, maybe he's busy.
Why, you coward.
Yeah, right.
Get a load of who's talking.
You're the one who's afraid
of committing seppuku, Ranma.
I am not.
Oh, so you're
ready to die, huh?
Anyway.
The important thing here is
to show mom that I'm a man.
You wait here.
But then again, perhaps
we shouldn't meet.
After all, if he were
somehow-- unmanly,
then I might have to do
something I'd regret.
But we'll cross that bridge
when we come to it, won't we?
Hey, aren't you
going to tell her?
I'm not sure.
Do I have the right?
Can I be so cruel?
A mom's got a right
to dream, hasn't she?
Well, I'll take that
to mean the answer's no.
Akane.
I think that I'll
be going home now.
I know my son, and I'm sure
he's become a fine young man.
That'll have to be enough.
Goodbye.
Ranma.
Now what?
I see now I shouldn't
have done it.
I guess I just couldn't bear
for your mom to be so sad.
I'm sorry.
I had no right to do what I did.
Seppuku is kind of
scary, and please
don't think that I blame you.
That's exactly
what you're doing.
Ranma.
I do miss you.
MAN: The hot spring's a burst!
MAN: Some kinda gusher!
Help!
It's my mom!
Mom!
Ranma!
Ranma, it's you.
Ranma.
It's me, Mom.
Well, I guess she knows.
I hope she's not
too disappointed.
Not at all.
You are wonderful.
Really.
I'm right here.
[thunder]
No.
Lanko.
Tell me, was it you who
saved me back there?
I-- I, uh--
Ah.
So then it was just a dream.
A dream?
I dreamed Ranma saved me.
Dreamed he was a man among men.
Ranma!
That we found each
other at last.
Well, actually, you really did.
But she--
It's OK.
Let her keep dreaming.
Goodbye.
See you soon.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Someday,
I'll be just a guy.
But until then, keep
dreaming for both of us.
KASUMI: Father.
Mr. Saotome.
I've made you some tea.
GENMA: Why, thank you, Kasumi.
You're too good to us.
SOUN: Gotcha.
GENMA: No fair.
I wasn't looking.
SOUN: Now, Saotome, there's no
need for that kind of attitude.
HAPPOSAI: You're still playing?
Sweet sassy molassy,
I thought you
finished that game a week ago.
SOUN: You know your problem?
GENMA: What?
SOUN: You want to know?
HAPPOSAI: Oh, not this again.
GENMA: OK, now you're--
SOUN: You're hilarious.
GENMA: You never change, Tendo.
I'm off.
KASUMI: Have a nice day.
Ranma, come on.
We'll be late.
Yeah, yeah.
I know.
HAPPOSAI: Akane!
We waiting for
something, Akane?
Nope.
We're done.
Shall we?
Yep.
BOTH: See ya!
[theme song]