-Yes, sir.
[gasps]
-Behold these servants.
-I represent a certain clan
in the Koga ninja sect.
-And I represent a rival clan.
-I represent the Iga.
-And I represent their rivals.
-While my clan's opposed
to all of them at once.
[whimpering]
-And so, having now
seen these ninja,
what say you to their worth?
-M-- m-- master Kuno, I--
-As of today, my dear uncle
has asked them to join us.
-In-- in what way?
-It would seem that our
household defenses are sorely
lacking.
-Household defense?
That's my role.
-And so it was, but it
may not be so much longer.
-Oh no!
-It grieves me, Sasuke, but I
have no further use for you.
[gasps]
-Say it's not so.
-It has not escaped our
notice that you have served us
well these many years.
In recognition of
that service, I
extend to you this
one final chance.
-You do?
Oh, thank you.
-It so happens there is
a task in need of doing.
Acquit yourself honorably and
I may consider keeping you on.
However, should you
fail your mission,
your connection with this
household ends permanently.
Be off with you.
You'll receive the
details soon enough.
SASUKE: Yes, sir.
[grunting]
NARRATOR: Sasuke's
Mission Improbable.
[telephone ringing]
KUNO (ON PHONE): The
details of your mission
can be found in the
phone's receiver.
Inside, you will find
the name of your target.
SASUKE: B--b-- but that's--
KUNO (ON PHONE): Arrange
a meeting between us.
You have one week.
SASUKE: Yes sir, Master Kuno.
KUNO (ON PHONE): Very well.
As always, should your mission
be uncovered or should you
be taken prisoner,
the Kuno family
will of course
disavow all knowledge.
This phone will
now self destruct.
-How best can I get close
to the pigtailed girl?
[screams]
AKANE: Wasn't it great
how the pool cleared out?
RANMA: Great for you maybe.
-So what is it now?
-I show up wearing the
girl's bathing suit
so no one gets freaked out,
but then they do anyway.
-Well, when you jump in as a
guy and climb out as a girl,
people are going to get
upset, hon, you know?
RANMA: And I didn't
even get to enjoy it.
SASUKE: I knew I'd find you.
The hottest time of
the year, and here I
am in an abandoned
mailbox full of my sweat
hoping you'd pass by.
Finally, though, my
gambit's paid off,
even if it did take three days,
five hours, and 47 minutes.
You can run, pigtailed
girl, but you can't hide.
[grunting]
[screaming]
-Whew.
That felt good.
Hey, watermelon.
-We've been waiting
for you to join us.
Shall we dig in?
[eating, grunting]
-Oh yes, the humble watermelon.
Amazing how it can
take the heat right out
of the day, huh, Saotome?
-Right as always, Tendo.
[chuckling]
-But the pigtailed
girl lived here
in this same house with Akane.
-Where are your
manners, greedy pig?
-Oh yeah?
-You little--
-Why, you--
-Here we go again.
-I don't think so.
Go fight outside.
It's too hot.
-Well?
-Hm.
Sure.
Why not?
-Thought you got me, eh, boy?
Well, wait 'til you
get a load of this.
Anything goes.
Final attack.
Spit store.
-Try rapid fire.
-What in the world's
going on out there?
-Serves you right.
-Hey!
That's the--
-OK, you jerk.
-Ah, fine dining,
don't you think?
-Yeah, I guess it's OK.
-What a family.
-What's that?
-Hey!
-Oh, this is so good.
Mm.
What's this called, anyway?
[grunting]
KASUMI: Some tea?
-Hm?
RANMA: OK, Pop, if
that's how you want it--
-Thank you.
-Admit say.
Say you lost.
Fine, then I'll get more ammo.
-Whoever it was,
they cleaned us out.
-I don't suppose
you ate it, Kasume.
-Oh, no.
It was Sasuke.
He was just here.
-What?
-Sasuke did?
-And why's he here?
Did you call him?
-Not me.
Mm-mm.
-Ooh.
That was good.
Who'd have ever thought
there was such a thing?
Hello.
Why, if it isn't
the pigtailed girl.
When'd she get here?
-Stupid jerk.
Now I've got to go take
a bath all over again.
-Aha.
She won't be able to
get away from me now.
Still, if I should
take my eyes off her.
I'll just have to make
sure that I don't.
It's kind of hard
to see, actually.
What am I doing?
I shouldn't be spying
on her like this.
Again, I am a spy.
No, I mustn't.
Than again it is professional.
Naughty, naughty, Sasuke.
Uh oh.
Somebody's coming.
-Your turn.
-That sounded like Ranma.
How'd he get in here?
Does that mean the pigtailed
girl wasn't in the bathtub?
Hm.
Let's see.
No one can get past
me while I'm here,
so therefore, no one came in.
Ergo, Ranma Saotome, who
just left the bathroom,
was actually in here
the whole time, i.e.
the person I took to
be the pigtailed girl
was in truth Ranma Saotome.
Which means-- meaning the
one I saw in the bath wasn't
the pigtailed girl but Ranma.
Oh dear.
Sorry about that.
[screaming]
KUNO (ON PHONE): Sasuke.
I've changed my mind.
Your deadline's tomorrow.
-What?
B-- but Master Kuno--
[dog barking]
-Leggo my meatballs!
-Too bad, boy.
Don't you know the old saying?
To the victor the spoils.
-I'll spoil something.
Give me those!
AKANE: Come on, you two.
Cut it out.
[laughing]
-Hand 'em over.
You've got no right.
-They're mine!
-What's this?
I'm right.
It was Ranma Saotome all along.
Good.
It makes things easier for me.
I'll wait 'til she
falls asleep and then,
under cover of darkness--
[snoring]
Perfect.
They're asleep.
Now to close the deal.
[laughing]
Stay still, with you?
Hm.
Now I'll get you for sure.
[yelps]
-Hey.
That's a panda, isn't it?
What kind of place
do they run here?
-What'd you do that for?
-Sorry.
Hm.
Close call.
If she really wakes
up, I'm done for.
-My meatballs.
Give 'em back, you thief.
Those are mine.
-Hey!
What are you--
[screaming]
-That'll learn him.
-I'll retire, go to the
old folks' ninja home.
[dog barking]
MAN: Something wrong?
[gasps]
-Who's there?
-Calm down.
No need to get excited.
I live here, right
at this house.
-He's right.
I have seen him before.
Something tells me, though,
that there's more to him
than it seems.
-You work for that Kudo guy.
Am I right?
-My name is--
-I know who you are.
What's wrong?
Boss kick you out?
-How did you--
-What did you think?
That many ninja could
gather at his household
and I wouldn't notice?
Can't you tell from the signs?
The sunflower
there, for example.
See how it moves?
The wind in the
branches of that tree.
Hear it rustle?
And the cries of those cats.
They're practically
sending smoke signals.
[cats meowing]
As a ninja yourself,
I'd expect you
to be more sensitive
to this sort of thing.
-I-- I had no idea.
I'm so unworthy.
[chuckling]
MAN: So that's it for you, huh?
-Unless I can set up a meeting
with the pigtailed girl,
but she's trickier
than I thought.
She's always one
step ahead of me.
I'm doomed.
-A true ninja would
never give up so easily.
-But I--
-My child, was Osaka
Castle built in a day?
-Master ninja, that
is, if I'm allowed
to address you as Master?
-Don't be silly.
-Or Shining One.
Should I call you that instead?
[laughing]
-I'll have to remember that one.
OK, kid.
Listen up.
I like you, so I'm
going to do you a favor.
I know just the
trick to help you.
Want to hear it?
Come a little closer.
-Huh?
Is that possible?
What else?
Got it.
-Do as I say and I promise your
mission will be successful.
I just know you
won't let me down.
That's it.
I'm out of here.
-He's gone.
What if he's wrong?
What if I can't do it?
Then at least I'll
have tried, right?
Right.
[snoring]
-You hear but you do not wake.
You will do whatever I say.
-Leaving so early?
-I've got to go to the park.
[chuckling]
-It worked, just
like the master said.
[grunting]
-From Sasuke?
What's this?
The pigtailed girl
awaiting me in the park?
You rascal.
[gobbling]
-So where is Ranma,
do you think?
-Huh?
You're asking me?
-I do know he left awful early.
I hope he's OK.
-Oh, he'll be back.
This is Ranma we're
talking about, remember?
MAN (VOICEOVER): If Sasuke
has done as I told him,
the subject's already
in his control,
moving in half asleep, half
awake dream state, completely
susceptible to post-hypnotic
suggestions so long
as the trance remains
uninterrupted.
In fact, Ranma should
be there already.
KASUMI: I think he said
something about the park.
AKANE: Well, whatever it is,
I don't like the sound of it.
The Ranma I know would
never skip breakfast.
-You see?
What'd I tell you?
-It worked just like you said.
Thanks to you, I'm saved.
-But your work's not complete.
-I-- it isn't?
-Haven't you learned anything?
-Huh?
after all the work,
you've done, is
that how you want
him to see her?
-Oh yeah.
-Lucky for you, I
was thinking ahead.
I just happen to have this.
Why don't you have
her put it on?
-Why, you've thought
of every last detail,
haven't you, Master?
-Say, if it isn't
the pigtailed girl.
Right over there.
Here we go.
Good girl.
Now, put the dress on, OK?
-OK.
[grunting, chuckling]
-Hallelujah!
[slurping]
RANMA: What are you doing?
So tell me, how did I
end up here, anyway?
-Oh no.
It's worn off.
-Worn off?
Oh, now I get it.
You and the freak went in
together on some kind of trick,
didn't you?
-I have an excuse, really.
-Really?
-Stay, please, just
a few minutes more.
-Forget it.
-But it's really
important to me.
All I need is 30 minutes.
No, make it 10 minutes.
Just 10 little
minutes, that's all.
-I said forget it.
-But my life's at stake.
-That's your problem.
Huh?
-Ranma!
-Jeez, Akane.
What's the matter?
-Well, you skipped
breakfast, Ranma.
You never do that.
-Dude over there and the freak
pulled some kind of weird trick
on me.
-Huh?
What trick?
-Pigtailed girl!
It is you!
And if it isn't
Akane Tendo, too!
You crazy girls.
You shouldn't have.
-M-- M-- Master Kuno, I
have something to tell you.
I--
For the two of you to
have come here to meet me,
I-- I'm touched.
[laughing]
-I guess it's too late.
-Touch this, you jerk!
-Master Kuno!
I'll be right there!
Master Kuno!
-Guess kicking just
comes kind of natural.
-To me, too.
So what say we go home?
-You betcha.
I'm starving.
-Master Kuno!
[crying]
Oh, Master Kuno.
KUNO (ON PHONE):
Sasuke, that you?
-I just called to say
I'm sorry, Master Kuno,
and I know I failed you.
Well, I guess this is goodbye.
KUNO (ON PHONE): Ha, ha,
Sasuke, you scamp, you.
Today, I met with the
pigtailed girl and Akane Tendo.
I'm happy, not angry.
You have proven yourself to me.
The job is yours if you want it.
-Oh.
Do you mean it?
Oh, Master Kuno.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Oh, I know I'm worthy, but
I'll-- I swear I'll do my best.
KUNO (ON PHONE): Speaking of
which, you have a new mission.
-Huh?
Wh-- what?
Huh?
Master Kuno, I--
KUNO (ON PHONE): Good luck.
[screaming]
NARRATOR: Picolet Chardin.
What kind of name is that?
Did you say battle dining?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Hello, Bonjour, Goodbye."
We'll see you there.