[music playing]
[theme music]
[beeping]
Gyoko.
Gyoko!
Huh?
[groan]
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Run
Away with Me, Ranma.
[dog barking]
[snoring]
[scream]
I had that same
nightmare again.
I can't take this much longer.
Oh, man.
This is starting
to freak me out.
Huh?
[groan]
You look totally
wiped out, Ranma.
Didn't you have a
good sleep last night?
No, not really.
[yawn]
TEACHER: And in this
manner, the event
affected the development of
our country, which had just
employed its new system.
Now if you'll turn to the
diagram at the top of page 63,
you'll see some of the
developments and innovations
which transformed
Japan in this era.
One-- gas light bulbs.
Two-- trains for public
transportation and cargo
shipment.
Three-- the telegraph.
Four--
(VOICEOVER) Wonder
what Ranma's problem is.
I guess I'll ask
him after school.
TEACHER: Is everybody
following this?
AKANE: So this is
the new ice cream
place I keep hearing about.
You sure know all the hot
spots, don't you, Ranma?
Yeah, well, gotta do
what it takes to get
my fill of fruit sundaes.
But eating these girly
things is embarrassing.
That's why I can't be
seen here as a guy.
[snore]
Hey!
Wake up, will you?
Huh?
Uh oh.
I did it again.
I almost had a dream that time.
You've been acting really
weird this last little while.
If you're that tired, then just
stop fighting it and sleep.
Mhm.
Today you stayed awake during
that whole boring Japanese
history class, am I right?
You've never managed
to stay awake before.
Wait.
Did that sound like a
camera going off just now?
I don't know.
Creepy.
I get the feeling
we're being watched.
Whatever.
Hey, Akane?
What is it?
Are you going to eat that?
Listen.
Listen to what?
Nighttime again.
Oh.
[snoring]
I can't take this much longer.
[groan]
Eyelids feeling very-- heavy.
[snoring]
HARUMAKI: (VOICEOVER) Her
name is pronounced Gyoko, not
Gyoza as in the potstickers.
Gyoko!
[gasp]
GYOKO: Harumaki.
Look, Gyoko.
The cherry blossoms
are in full bloom.
I know.
It's as if the blossoms
are falling all around
to bless our love.
Do you remember the promise
we made to each other?
Harumaki, of course I remember.
If only the beautiful flowers
had been blooming then, too.
If only they had.
Then, Harumaki--
Gyoko.
[scream]
[groan]
[growl]
[scream]
[groan]
[growl]
[grunt]
You have the same
nightmare every night?
Yeah.
And it's getting old fast.
So what's it about?
Tell me.
It's so gross, I don't
even want to tell you.
Just thinking about it--
I think I'm going to hurl.
Ranma.
[scream]
[groan]
BOY: Uh, excuse me, miss.
Uh?
Tell me, do you have
a dream every night
about the old man in this photo?
[gasp]
(VOICEOVER) This is him.
I take it from
your reaction then
that you do dream about him.
[gasp]
That means I found you
in the nick of time.
Would you come
with me for a date?
[groan]
What makes you think I'd date
a person I've never even seen
before?
My apologies.
It's not me I want you to date.
Why don't you just tell
us what this is all about?
[beeping]
[heavy breathing]
[gasp]
The old man in my dream.
This is my grandfather.
And I am his wife.
I'm the doctor.
And I fit into
this picture how?
Time will tell
whether he'll make it
through the next few days.
Darling!
Oh, Grandpa.
[crying]
Oh, the poor man.
Yeah, I guess.
[gasp]
Gyoko, my love!
[scream]
A ghost!
Gyoko, how I've longed
for you these many years.
He's-- he's a ghost!
It's not as bad as it looks.
He's just doing a little
bit of soul travelling.
Soul travelling?
How I've longed for
your sweet embrace.
Allow me to explain it.
[clearing throat]
Soul travel is when the
soul of a living human being
separates from the body and
travels independently of it.
Ah.
Wow.
So it's not a ghost at all.
This is no time for applause.
Oh, my precious Gyoko, darling.
Get away from me!
You're playing coy
with me, sweet Gyoko.
I'm not your Gyoko!
Do something about
this freaky old guy!
No!
Not that!
Maybe my grandfather's
diary will help you out.
No!
That's private!
Let me see.
Don't read that!
It's private!
Leave a man's privates alone!
Oh, shut up!
[groan]
"I first glimpsed
her lovely visage
in front of the hospital.
She looks remarkably similar
to Gyoko, my first love.
She went into the
ice cream parlor
in front of the hospital.
She seems to love sundaes.
The next day, she went into the
ice cream parlor once again.
She must have a fast metabolism.
She's so slim and pretty.
That sweet smile of
hers-- how it brings
to mind my precious Gyoko"?
Mm.
Now smile at the birdie.
[groan]
You're just a soul!
How can you use a camera?
[groan]
Calm down now, Ranma.
You'd better keep
reading the diary.
Old coot.
"Ah, my darling, my final wish
is to have a date with you."
What?
A date with me?
Won't you please honor the
last wish of a dying man
and go on a date
with my grandfather?
I beg of you.
[crying]
Did they mention that
you'll keep dreaming about me
if you say no?
Why don't you just go, Ranma?
It's only one date.
That's right.
One date.
I hear you, but--
Don't worry about me.
Just go and have an enjoyable
time with my poor husband.
Oh, please, you've
got to help us.
I don't know about this.
All right already!
But I'm going on one
date, and that's it!
Dealing with spirits is
a martial artist's duty.
Enough with this soul business.
Now how about
calling me Harumaki?
Everything's working out.
Isn't that nice, Grandma?
It's more than I
could have hoped for.
I've got a hot date!
Hot date with a redhead!
[animal sounds]
Wait, Gyoko!
Wait up, darling.
What's the hurry?
Can't we slow down a little?
I always walk fast,
so try to keep up.
Now lose the wrist thing.
You look like a freaky ghost.
Oh, these wrists have
a mind of their own.
I just don't know what
to do with them when
I'm floating around in
the air doing soul travel.
[laughter]
Oh, what an
amusing conversation
we're having, considering
this is our first date.
Isn't this nice, Gyoko, dear?
No.
[chatter]
What a relief.
It looks like they're
having a good time.
[groan]
Hands off, buddy.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
I just got caught up in the
mood watching those two lovers.
What do you mean
by those two lovers?
[music playing]
Here you go.
Ah, well, I guess it's true.
Love isn't just
for young people.
You might be an old man, but you
still think about your old love
from--
[slurping]
[scream]
[laughter]
Ow!
You idiot!
Why can't you control yourself?
Here's another!
Maybe that'll help!
Well, this date
is something, but I
must admit I can't help feeling
like somehow I'm forgetting
an important promise I made.
What important promise?
Grandpa seems to be
having second thoughts
about this whole thing.
Is that you, Akane?
Now what was it?
Uh, hm, let's see.
Uh.
[laughter]
Ow!
Time for the soul train to
hit its final destination.
My poor old grandfather.
Hm?
Wait a sec.
Come to think of it, when I had
this dream before-- Harumaki.
Gyoko.
Uh.
Uh, let's forget the past and
have ourselves a good time!
Wow.
Ranma's sure acting nice to
your grandpa all of a sudden.
Yes, she's too kind.
This'll be good
for the old soul.
[laughter]
Harumaki!
See if you can try and
catch me before I get away!
One, two, three, four.
Left, right, left, right.
That's the way.
Something bothering
you, Harumaki?
[sigh]
We've gone to many places and
done all kinds of things today.
But there's still
something missing.
[sigh]
You creep!
After all the trouble I've
gone to to make you happy.
Hey, calm down, Ranma.
Get a hold of yourself.
But this creep--
[sigh]
It's just that this date wasn't
exactly what I had in mind,
you see.
Well, I think maybe you need to
remember that important promise
that you were talking to
us about earlier today.
Don't get me in any deeper.
Uh, according to my
grandpa's diary here--
No!
Don't read my diary!
Don't read his diary!
"This was a very special day.
Gyoko and I vowed to
elope with one another."
[scream]
No, you mustn't read-- you--
What?
Are you sure about that?
Yeah.
I'm not making it up.
Oh, yes.
Now I remember.
We promised to elope.
I don't believe you.
The promise was to kiss
each other, wasn't it?
And if that's the case, then
why couldn't you have at least
remembered it earlier?
Are you trying to
get a kiss out of me?
[growl]
Old man, you're
the one who roped me
into this in the first place.
I think this would be
the perfect time for you
to go into the light, old man.
Tell us what happened.
Why'd you promised to elope
with Gyoko in the first place?
Hm.
It's like this.
[laughter]
(VOICEOVER) We knew each
other from childhood,
and our parents consented
to our becoming engaged.
Had everything gone smoothly,
we would have married happily.
Unfortunately, Gyoko's
father had invested heavily
in a beans company, and it
collapsed in the stock market
crash.
He lost all his money.
And because he
couldn't pay his debts,
he had to get Gyoko married
off to get her dowry.
In order for Gyoko
and I to get married
as we originally planned, our
only hope was to run away.
[sigh]
The poor things.
Are you serious?
[train whistle]
HARUMAKI: (VOICEOVER) Yes,
that's the way it was.
So we made a promise.
I promised her we'd elope.
Hold it.
Your promise was to be
if the flowers blossomed.
So what happened to the flowers?
Did they blossom?
Flowers?
What flowers were those?
[groan]
Don't ask me!
You're the one who
said it in my dream!
In the diary it says something
about if the cherry trees are
still in bloom late in spring--
HARUMAKI: If the
cherry trees are still
in bloom late in spring,
then let's elope together.
Please, Gyoko.
I will.
If the cherry trees
are still in blossom.
[gasp]
HARUMAKI: But the cherry
blossoms did not last for long.
[crying]
Goodbye.
Gyoko!
So, like, that was it?
What a tragic way to
end your very first love.
If I could just see the
cherry trees flowering late
in the season, I could
die a happy old man.
OK then.
Let's go see them.
Ranma.
We'll see those
blossoms, don't worry.
[sigh]
If they're in blossom,
will you elope with me?
RANMA: Don't push it.
[groan]
[clang]
HARUMAKI: They're gone!
AKANE: They tore
down all the trees.
[gasp]
Gone.
My trees.
My cherry trees are gone.
My youth has vanished.
All my youthful memories
have gone forever.
What are you talking
about, old man?
Your cherry trees
are right there.
Huh?
The cherry blossoms are in full
bloom right in front of you.
Those are your cherry trees.
Huh?
[gasp]
I see them!
My beautiful cherry
trees are in full bloom.
[gasp]
What's going on?
HARUMAKI: This is the end.
Huh?
The dreams I had
long ago in my youth
have finally come to
a natural conclusion.
Thank you for everything, miss.
It was nothing.
I enjoyed our time together.
Uh, hey.
No, wait.
What's happening to you?
Hang on.
Thank you again, miss.
Grandpa!
Don't go!
Old man!
Old man?
Wait!
[snoring]
No!
Poor Grandpa.
Hey!
Can you hear me?
Say something.
Old man!
Please, keep it down.
No amount of noise
will save him now.
Otherwise, I'd be
calling him, too.
Making noise could
save his life.
Huh?
[music playing]
[scream]
[groan]
Will you keep it down?
Huh?
Harumaki!
You must have been worried.
Sorry, Gyoko.
A miracle.
Hold on a second.
She wouldn't be your
first love, Gyoko?
[laughter]
We ended up eloping after all.
Yes.
My husband's as
stubborn as an old mule.
Wait!
Look at her.
She doesn't look
anything like me.
Don't you think so?
Gyoko.
You're a real looker
compared to her.
Oh, behave yourself,
you naughty old man.
[laughter]
RANMA: This is no
laughing matter!
[groan]
Wake up.
Listen.
The azaleas are booming
so we can elope now.
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's go, miss.
I'm waiting for you.
[groan]
Is his soul traveling again?
No, that's him.
He can't even tell a
woman from a man anymore.
I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
The azaleas are out.
Let's elope.
[groan]
Come on, my sweet.
Come on.
I'm waiting for you.
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I knew free
food was too good to be true.
Can love beat the effects
of poison mushrooms?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," Let's
Go to the Mushroom Temple.
We'll see you there.