[theme music]
NARRATOR: My fiance the cat.
It was a dark and stormy night.
-Now in splat-o-vision.
-Nabiki, will you help me?
-I what?
Oh, OK.
-But, uh, wait a second.
Aren't you guys going
to stay here and watch
the movie with me?
-We've got dishes.
-What's the matter, you scared?
-So, how's about a
game of shogi, Saotome?
-Sure thing, Kendo.
-Dad, don't you want
to watch it with me?
-Well, if it scares
you, then turn it off.
-The master just
loves that stuff.
-Yeah, but he left
the house right
after he finished his dinner.
-So why don't you
ask Ranma then.
He's right upstairs.
-Now that's what I
call a good idea.
-Thanks, but I'll manage.
-Suit yourself, but whatever.
-Hmm.
TV ANNOUNCER: As we present
tonight's terrifying tale.
[clock ticking]
-S-somebody help!
[heavy breathing]
-What's wrong?
-I- I think I just saw
somebody without a face.
-What's that, a
man without a face?
By any chance he
wouldn't look like this?
-Bah!
-Ahhh!
Ranma!
RANMA: (LAUGHING) Na- na!
Bet you can't catch me.
-Why do you always have to
act like such a five year old?
RANMA: [grunts]
-Why you!
-[laughing] Blah!
-Huh?
-Ah, Ni hao Ranma.
-Shampoo!
[groans]
-So what is that thing?
-Is legendary bell, Mao Mo Lin.
Shampoo bring a souvenir from
rustic Chinese countryside.
-What's he supposed to
do with a giant bell?
[sigh]
-See?
It make pair with mine?
Ones would hold pair,
is tied by destiny.
-Humph.
-Huh, Tied together huh?
-Object is magical.
-No thanks.
-You think you can take present
Shampoo give from her heart
and throw back in her face?
RANMA: Huh?
-Oh!
-[splash]
-Ah!
Ah!
[panting]
-(ANGRILY) Meow.
-St- stay back.
Don't come any closer.
Stay away from me!
[grunts]
[crash]
[purr]
-Meow.
-Ah!
I-I accept!
I love it, see?
See?
Nice bell.
[laughing uneasily] Nice bell.
SHAMPOO: Meow.
-Humph.
SHAMPOO: [purr] Meow, Meow.
[wind blowing]
[bell jingles]
[sigh]
-Honestly, that jerk is
never going to grow up.
[bell jingles]
-Hm?
-Um.
Must be imagining things.
[floorboards creaking]
[snoring]
[groan]
[floorboards creaking]
[bell jingling]
[door opening]
[floorboards creaking]
-Hm?
[gasp]
[bell jingling]
-I- I didn't imagine it.
-But, that- that
sound, I- [gasp]
[bell jingling]
-A, a bell?
-E meow a bride.
[screams]
E meow a bride.
[snore]
[running footsteps]
[bang]
[grunting]
-What's the big idea,
sneaking up on me like that?
-I what?
I snuck into your
room and pretended
to be some kind of
stupid giant cat?
-You know you did Ranma.
Next, you're going to say
you didn't pop the question.
-And what question
would that be?
-Huh?
I, uh, you know, to marry you.
Marry you mean?
-My dear boy, can it be?
Do it!
-Don't you wish!
-Then who was it
in my room then?
-Ask the bell stupid.
-Bells can't talk moron.
-E meow bride.
-Huh?
[groans]
[bell jingling]
[all gasp]
-Take this you little
tinkling fiend!
Ah!
-Ah, it's running away!
-After it!
-You won't get away.
-I'll get it Just you watch.
[groans]
[bell jingling]
-Huh, now we'll see
it in its true form.
-What the--
-Ranma, don't!
Stay back!
-Well, I can't call myself
a martial artist if I don't.
All right you, time to-
-(SCARED) Meow, meow, meow.
-Huh, c- cat!
-A ghost cat?
-[yawn] How cute.
[screaming]
-I'm sorry, please
don't kick me.
[muffled screams]
[teeth chattering]
-Snap out of it will ya?
-Seeking a bride huh?
-Meow.
Tell me, have you happened
to see me-y little bell?
-Hm.
-Ones would hold pair,
is tied by destiny.
-Oh, I get it.
You mean the other
half of the set.
-Meow-huh.
The little bell will
be held by me-y bride.
Meow.
Are you sure you
haven't seen it?
-I- ah.
-[gasp]
-Delivery!
-Delivery?
I thought this
might take a while,
so I ordered some ramen
from the Cat Cafe.
Well, that's my Kasumi.
-Do you usually deliver
at night or is it just us?
-When ramen for Ranma,
Shampoo deliver anytime.
-Don't look at me,
I didn't order it.
-Oh!
Hiya!
Shampoo see very
scary ghost cat.
Akane, where you find this one?
[bell jingling]
-Meow!
The little bell!
That makes you me-y bride!
Ow!
-You keep paws to self!
-You won't me-arry me just
because I'm a cat, is that it?
-Shampoo marry
Ranma, not you cat.
[screaming]
-Wait, who?
You mean this one right here?
[screaming]
-Meow, then if I beat
him, will you me-arry me?
[screaming]
-Meow!
Meow!
[hissing]
-Ah!
-Meow!
St- stay back.
I'm warning you!
Ah!
-Meow!
-[screaming]
-Ranma!
[boom]
-Meow!
-Ah, I told you!
[crying]
You won't get away with this.
[shaking]
[bell jingling]
-Huh?
[sniff]
-Meow.
I'll be back, me-ark my words!
[bell jingling]
-Hiya!
Ranma, so happy you
protect Shampoo.
-Hey, would you cut that out!
[slurp]
-Formidable, yet stubborn.
[sheet flapping]
-It's an ill wind
that blows this night.
-It'll be dark now
any moment, yes.
-And the ghost cat will come.
-If I beat Ranma,
Shampoo will me-arry me.
-Meaning it'll be it
for Ranma any minute.
-It if were just evil
it wouldn't be so bad.
-Hey, no prob.
I'm sure he's over
that cat thing by now.
-Hm.
[whimpering]
-The kitty-cat is coming.
The kitty-cat is coming.
-Oh, the tragedy.
-It Shampoo fault.
If she no bring legendary
Mao Mo Lin bell from China,
scary ghost cat
never attack Ranma.
-Then why don't
you throw it away?
-Don't wanna.
-Ugh.
[bell jingling]
[gasp]
-Dad, did you hear that?
[bell jingling]
-The sound of the
ghost cat's bell.
[bell jingling]
[humming]
-(EERILY) Meow!
[bell jingling]
[whimpering]
-(EERILY) Meow!
Meow!
-Ah!
Dudes, do something!
-Very well.
The busting of ghosts is
a martial artist's most
sacred duty.
So go get 'em boy!
[grunts]
-Ah!
-(IN PAIN) Meow!
Me-I can't believe you
just did that to me.
-You've got him
on the ropes, boy.
Go finish him off.
-Ah!
I don't wanna!
-Fight for Shampoo sake, Ranma.
You can do it.
-Behold, the final
confrontation has begun.
-Ranma, huh?
-Keep it away from me!
[crying]
-Some fight.
Behold the battle
of the boo-hoo.
[nose blowing]
-Meow!
Me- ow!
[whimpering]
-You leave me no choice.
Prepare for me-y ultimate move.
[bell jingling]
-Meow!
[screeching]
[groans]
-Pop, what's wrong?
-Sa- Saotome?
-You OK?
-Meow!
[hissing]
-Let's see if you can
fight me like this.
-Wh-what the?
-What's wrong?
Can't hit the body of your
own father, is that it?
-You just watch me.
GHOST CAT: You what?
[knuckles cracking]
-Forgive me, but
this can't be helped.
-Excuse me?
-The busting of ghosts
is a sacred duty
of a martial artist,
ain't that what you said?
Yah!
-Ah!
-Right?
-Oomph.
-Why is it I get the feeling
that Ranma was waiting--
-Was waiting for
that opportunity?
-Yeah, how dare you treat
your own father that way,
you little--
-Be quiet you!
It's your own darn fault for
taking over my pop's body.
-Fine.
Then if that's the
way you wanna play--
-Huh?
---I'll just take over Shampoo
and me-ake me-y escape.
-Hiya!
-Ow!
-Meow, meow, meow, meow,
meow, meow, meow meow!
[gasp]
[whimpering]
-Me-I give up.
Shampoo doesn't have
to be me-y bride.
-It's because you know Shampoo
in love with other man.
-Don't listen to her!
-Me-I may look tough, but trust
me, I'm crying on the inside.
[crying]
-Not to mention the outside.
-What?
-Hiya, Ranma!
You fight for woman you love.
-Why would I love a stupid
selfish cat girl like you?
-Shampoo understand.
-I- I didn't mean--
-One what holds smaller of
legendary bell Mao Mo Lin
destined to become bride
of giant ghost cat.
-You're not going to marry
a cat just because you
got dumped by Ranma are you?
[crying]
-You can't.
-Shampoo!
-Shampoo stupid selfish
cat girl, remember?
-Hey, hey, I was kidding.
You know, kidding?
[boing]
-Woah!
-Shampoo selfish, not stupid!
[splash]
-The more they resist--
-The harder they fall.
[bell jingling]
[gasp]
-Uh-oh.
[bell jingling]
-Oh me-y, a brand new bride.
-Ah!
Put me down!
Let me go!
Ah!
[lick]
[yowl]
-That- that yowling--
[kick]
[yowling]
-That's right ladies
and gentlemen,
the move you've all been waiting
for, the dreaded cat fist.
-With the cat fist,
Ranma's invincible.
[yowl]
[hissing]
-Kitty-cat combat, clash
of the killer kittens.
Never in the history of
the sport has there been--
[screeching]
[yowl]
[whimpering]
-And you call yourself a human?
[yowl]
-Me -ow!
[bell jingling]
[gasp]
-I can't me-arry you, you meany.
[bell jingling]
-Defeated at last.
[snoring]
-Huh?
[clap]
-Meow?
[giggle]
-Here kitty, kitty, kitty!
-Meow!
-That's it, here kitty kitty.
-Oh!
-Meow.
-All's well that
ends yada, yada.
I'm starved can we eat now?
-That's right, I almost forgot.
-Huh, dinner?
Of course.
Saotome, dinner's ready!
-Huh?
Dinner, why didn't you say so?
[purring]
-Still I can't help
feeling a little
sorry for that poor ghost cat.
[heavy breathing]
-Ranma, wait up!
-Ha-ha!
What's the matter can't
keep up, slow poke?
-Hey!
Who do you think was
there taking car of you
last night, huh?
[chuckling]
[bell jingling]
-Hm?
[screaming]
-It's back!
-Hey, doesn't one
of you girls want
one of me-y cute little bells?
Come on, huh?
[screaming]
-Meow!
[bells jingling]
-Why does everyone
keep running away?
Somebody come back
and be me-y bride.
Doesn't anyone want
to me-arry me please?
Me-I'll be a good
husband, I swear.
I'll give you tuna everyday.
You can have all
the yarn you want.
You can even sleep
in me-y own bed!
[theme music]
-What does youth mean to you?
What a cool way to put it.
I've always wanted to
have a teacher like that.
Next time on Ranma
one half, Blow Wind.
To be young is to go gungho.
We'll see you there.