[theme music]
[singing in japanese]
Uh, Ms. Akane?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Mr. Sentaro, I'm
really sorry, too.
But I don't think that
we should see each other.
What are you saying?
[sobbing]
Mr. Sentaro, how could you?
You were just toying
with my affection!
No, Ms. Akane!
That's not true, honestly!
My love for you is far greater
than all the cherry blossoms
in springtime.
That's sweet.
But how do I know
it's the truth?
You must believe.
My love for you is boundless.
I am so happy.
Let's seal our love
with a kiss, Sentaro.
SENTARO (VOICEOVER): Akane--
Forgive me for
asking, but how come
you're hugging a lawn ornament?
Look at you.
You're completely irresponsible.
So how in the world do
you expect me to put you
in charge of our school?
I'm too old for this.
Mark my words.
You've got to pull yourself
together and start planning
for your future, or
you'll end up a bum!
There's not much hope.
Special training
begins tomorrow!
And you had better be ready.
No, wait, grandmama.
You don't understa--
[squeaking]
What was that?
Who's out there?
What is going on out here, huh?
Ah!
[mumbling]
Huh?
Who are you, anyway?
I demand that you untie her!
[giggling]
What do you want with
my grandmama, anyway?
And don't think you
can get by me, either!
You bring her back!
They stole Grandmama.
Oh, no.
What am I going to do now?
AKANE (VOICEOVER): The Missing
Matriarch of Martial Arts Tea.
[bell ringing]
Oh, man, am I hungry.
You wanna grab something to eat?
Oh, wow, Ranma.
Are you actually
offering to treat me?
Of course not.
We're going Dutch.
Meanie.
MAN: If you're smart, Ms.
Akane, you'll take my advice
and dump Ranma.
Trust me, you'd be much
happier with a guy like me.
[groan]
RANMA: I've got a
craving for noodles.
AKANE: Yeah, I could
go for noodles.
Gee, I wonder what Sentaro
wanted this time around.
Ah, forget it.
I don't wanna get involved with
him or martial arts tea again.
Every time he shows up nothing
good winds up happening to us.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
MAN: You must listen
to me, Ms. Akane!
Huh?
I'm serious.
Get lost, you freak.
Please, you don't understand.
You must listen to me.
Oh, please!
Gee, it sounds like
you're in trouble.
Oh, Ms. Akane.
I knew you'd listen.
Only someone like
you would understand.
You are so full of it.
Right now in my life
is in extreme danger.
[slurping]
Ah.
Akane, I've had
just about as much
as I can take of this jerk.
Hey, don't leave me!
I'm coming with you!
Wait!
You can't-- agh!
What'd you do that for?
Not so fast.
Pay up, kid.
Ahh!
Strike three!
You're out!
[cheering]
Oh, no.
Not you again.
I'm sorry.
But is that the way
you talk to someone
whose life is in danger?
I have had enough
of your yapping!
Hey, I'm really
sorry about that.
Oh, don't worry.
He'll be all right.
Ha.
Uh, thanks a lot, lady.
You may not believe
this, but that baseball
was really intended for me.
Don't be an idiot!
You've gotta believe me.
I'm not making this stuff up.
I really am in danger.
Honestly.
You can't leave me!
Are you all right?
[honking]
Not again.
Akane.
Oh, man.
What's going on?
Whoa!
So now do you finally
believe me, Ms. Akane?
Well, you might believe
someone's out to get you.
But I think Ranma's just
having a bad day, that's all.
Didn't I tell you that
creep was bad news?
You've got to help me.
I have nowhere else to turn.
You're my only hope.
Well, I don't think
it can get any worse.
I don't know how to thank you.
RANMA: Your grandma
was abducted?
Are you serious?
Mm-hmm.
And then they turned
their sights onto me.
But I bravely managed to escape
just in the nick of time.
But why was she kidnapped?
So they can take over the
School of Martial Arts Tea
ceremony.
Is that true?
Your Backyard is
aesthetically pleasing.
You'd better not
be messing with us.
No, please.
I could tell you who did it.
Well, then, it shouldn't
be too hard to find her.
Tell us who did it!
Uh, well-- it's so terrible,
I can't even say it!
Ugh.
I guess the best thing
is to see for ourselves.
Ranma, you're gonna go?
Well, I figure whoever could
kidnap that old grandma has
to be pretty tough.
And I just love a challenge.
Oh, thank you, Ranma.
Thank you!
This is wonderful.
Now we can start our
wedding plans, Akane.
Agh!
RANMA: Oh, man.
This place looks
completely deserted.
SENTARO: If the students find
out about the kidnapping,
it would cause turmoil.
AKANE: I guess you're right.
SENTARO: Come.
I'll show you Grandmama's room.
WOMAN: Where have you been?
Please, don't
scare me like that.
Oh, it's just the old
trio from last time.
Ranma, your manners!
So, Sentaro, I hope you haven't
said anything to your friends
that you shouldn't have.
Please forgive me.
But I did.
We came along with
him because we thought
we might be able to help.
We don't need any
help from you, girl.
This matter concerns
the Daimonji family,
and no one else.
It's none of your business.
Don't sweat it.
These are people who were able
to kidnap Sentaro's grandma.
There's no way Sentaro
could deal with them alone.
Mm-hmm.
Nincompoop!
Hey!
What did I do?
Goodness gracious.
What will become of
the Daimonji School
if you don't stand up and be
a man for once in your life?
WOMAN: Take a look at this.
Huh?
What are they?
The boar, the deer, and
the butterfly cards?
WOMAN: I found
them in this room.
From the Japanese card game?
Correct.
These depict Inoshishi the
boar, Sheikah the deer,
and Chocho the butterfly.
I didn't know that the
old bag liked to gamble.
Those cards you hold are a
challenge to you, Sentaro.
That's right.
From the Shadow School
of Martial Arts Tea.
You said Shadow School?
What the heck is that?
I've never heard
of this, either.
For centuries, martial
arts tea ceremony
was practiced by two
opposing schools.
One is the Daimonji School
of Martial Arts Tea Ceremony.
This you know.
The other school
of the tea ceremony
is the Miyako Oji School.
The Miyako Oji School.
[music playing]
Onward.
Go to it.
You see, these two schools have
fought over many generations,
trying to better the other over
years of training and practice.
This was one of the
most fearsome rivalries
in all Japan.
But after many
years of struggling,
they soon ran out of
money and disappeared.
But since then, the Miyako
Oji clan had gone underground
and has been continuing
to practice as the Shadow
School of Martial Arts Tea.
It has been a
long, terrible feud.
Sounds like a kids' fight.
The reason why they have
kidnapped the matriarch
of the Daimonji School--
--is so they can take over
our school and become the one
and only school of
martial arts tea ceremony.
But what do these carts mean?
Those cards represent the three
elders of the Shadow School.
Ino, the boar.
Sheikah, the deer.
Cho, the butterfly.
So they are the ones who
kidnapped your grandma?
And that's why we don't
have time to waste.
That's right.
You must hurry.
You must go and show them that
the true school of martial arts
is the Daimonji School.
Uh, well, Sentaro?
So, are you coming?
Huh?
Unfortunately, I cannot.
What?
Huh?
I can't believe this.
Are you too chicken to
save your own grandma?
Yeah.
Up to now, I was beginning to
think you were actually brave.
They cannot trick me.
What do you mean?
My grandmama was kidnapped
by the three elders
from my very own family.
What are you saying?
This is all just
an elaborate plan
they've devised to test me.
Huh?
[cackling]
SENTARO: I saw them
with my own eyes.
Well, I guess the
question is, can you
be sure that it was them?
Are you positive that it was?
Yes, I'm positive.
Then what's with all
the family feud stuff?
My grandmama is testing me.
She wants to see if I'm worthy
enough to carry on the school.
OK.
Then how do you explain
those cards you found?
You know, the deer, the
boar, and the butterfly?
I'm telling you, this whole
thing is just a pack of lies.
You said that your
life was in danger!
I overreacted.
Why, you--
The best thing for us to
do right now is nothing.
The most important
thing now is to show
that I won't easily fall
for their sinister schemes.
Ha ha-- ha!
So, do you think that he's
telling the truth this time,
Akane?
Oh, I just don't know
what to believe anymore.
Whoa!
Ugh.
Hey, look.
It's one of those old bags.
Are you all right?
[shouting]
Hey, what's going on?
[cackling]
Why, you-- ah!
Ranma, look at this.
I just can't figure this out.
So, how they doing?
They're sleeping.
The three of them
looked pretty serious
fighting those other three.
I guess Sentaro's grandmother
really was kidnapped.
So what's the deal?
Say something!
SENTARO (VOICEOVER):
I'm going to do it.
I will be the one
to save my grandmama
and prove that Sentaro
Daimonji is truly a man.
Sentaro.
You need a little help?
Yeah, do you?
Miss Akane, Ranma--
Hey, I don't think this is the
right time to be thanking us.
Right, Akane?
Yeah.
Kind words.
But I must thank you both.
For everything.
From my research, this is the
home of the Miyako Oji family.
Whoa.
Quite the digs.
I thought they were flat broke.
I'd say this place is like
10 times the size of yours.
My name is Sentaro Daimonji.
I demand to be heard!
Now open this door!
I command you to open it now!
[creaking]
What the--
Oh, man.
It looks like some
kind of giant maze.
Where's Sentaro's grandmother?
[laughter]
WOMAN: She is inside.
If you want to see
her, you must enter.
WOMAN: But first
you must negotiate
the Labyrinth of Confusion.
Hey, where are you?
Hm?
Leave them to me.
And you two, head for the house!
But-- but--
I think we should
listen to what he said.
Come on, let's go!
I'm so sorry.
You cannot pass.
If you wish to proceed,
you must first--
Defeat the three elders
of the Miyako Oji School
of Martial Arts Tea Ceremony!
Ahaha!
They look just like
our three elders.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's get it on, you
trading card witches!
OK, you two go on ahead.
All right.
Who's my first victim?
Listen, bub.
Don't you dare--
--underestimate--
--our power!
What happened to
staying seated?
Only the other school
worries about staying seated.
The Shadow School prefers to
have a more freestyle approach
to combat.
WOMAN: OK, girls.
Let's show him our stuff.
Hm?
Hiya!
This attack is old now-- oof!
Ahh!
Oh no.
WOMAN: If you move,
it will break.
Then you'll fall
right through the ice.
[laughter]
Impossible!
Ms. Akane, I'm sure we've
been this way before.
I wonder if she's even here.
If who's here?
Your grandma.
Who did you think I
was talking about?
Oh, right.
Grandmama.
I completely forgot.
How could you forget?
Whenever you are
near to me, Ms. Akane,
nothing else seems
to matter but you.
You're full of it.
But that's OK, because
as long as we're together,
I don't care if I fall
to the depths of he--
Fall by yourself!
Oh, that really hurt.
Huh?
Why, Grandmama!
That's it.
You had better keep running if
you know what's good for you,
sonny.
I could very easily have
escaped here any time
my little heart desired.
But I don't understand
why you didn't try.
Because I was waiting
for you to rescue me.
Can we please go home now?
Well, it isn't that easy.
There is still the little matter
of the feud between the two
families that has
to be cleared up.
And you must accept
their challenge
on behalf of the
entire Daimonji School.
What-- what do you mean?
But I still don't understand.
Well, as the only male
successor in our family,
it is up to you to
accept the challenge.
You're not serious?
Tell me you're not!
Yep, I'd say she's serious.
Good luck, Sentaro.
Please, allow me to
introduce your opponent
for the challenge.
Please enter.
Huh?
WOMAN: Satsuki,
remove your hood.
She is next in line to carry
on the Shadow School of Martial
Arts Tea Ceremony.
Her name is Satsuki Miyako Oji.
Man, I think
Sentaro's in a coma.
Ye-- yeah.
[rooster crowing]
You are so beautiful.
Let's get married.
Then we can carry on both
schools of martial arts tea
ceremony together.
Mm-hmm.
What's going on?
Can't you see that
they're in love, Ranma?
Well, I must say,
my work is done.
Hey, Ranma, we got a letter
from Sentaro and Satsuki.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I just wanted
to thank you for everything.
We've officially
announced our engagement,
although our paths shan't--
Well, I didn't think our
paths would e cross again.
I hope we're not imposing.
Why, you stupid moron!
I never wanna see
you, ever again!
[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Before I could react,
I'd fallen off the balance beam.
And now everyone's dragging
me off to Dr. Tofu's.
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
Akane goes to the hospital.
We'll see you there.