[theme music]
NARRATOR: Mousse Goes
Home To the Country.
-Ahh.
You sure it's OK?
Restaurant is hard work.
-I'm just glad that I can help.
-Thank you, Mousse.
-Shampoo, Mousse.
Shampoo!
[plate slamming]
-Ahh!
What did I--
-Listen.
You're no help, Mousse!
You go home.
But, but I--
-This busy restaurant.
Find other place to take nap.
-But, but, Shampoo!
Ahh!
Hello.
Seven ramens up.
-Don't worry.
I got them.
-Aren't you the little worker.
-I'll have to carry
my own weight,
once I'm married
to Shampoo, right?
-Mousse, maybe you no
should carry so much mugs.
-So you do love me
after all, Shampoo.
Oh, Shampoo!
[crash]
-You ordered this one, right?
-You're so cute.
Did you know that, Shampoo?
-Hiyah.
-Could I maybe take you
to a movie sometime?
-Hiyah.
[crash]
[yelling]
-Bad Mousse!
You stay here and wash dishes.
Fight in restaurant
with customer
is no good for business!
-But all I wanted
to do was help.
-I'm only making her
mad at this rate.
-Mousse.
-Shampoo!
You do need me, don't you?
-This letter come from China.
First do dishes, then read.
-A letter for me?
But who's it from?
Mother.
MOTHER (VOICEOVER): Hello, son.
You haven't forgotten
your old ma, have you?
Well, we're all doing
just fine, but we
can't help worrying
about you there in Japan.
You're still planning
to bring that Shampoo
of yours back home
to China, aren't you?
I'm not getting any younger
and well, let's just say,
a mother needs to know
her son is in good hands
before she moves on.
Don't take too long, gaison.
I can only wait
so long, you know.
-Ma's right.
I've got to stop
being so selfish.
That's it.
Today's the day I finally
beat Ranma or die trying!
Shampoo!
[thud]
-Marry me and come
back to China!
-Ahh!
Let go of me!
Get off my leg, you freak!
-What you thinking,
stupid Mousse?
What Shampoo tell you about
fighting with customer?
-After I defeat Ranma,
it won't matter.
-You no can defeat
Ranma, Mousse.
-But if I can, then what?
Will you promise that
you'll become my wife?
-If you lose, will you
promise to go back to China?
-OK, I promise.
But I've got no
intention of losing.
-You want Shampoo help
start pack your luggage?
-Fine, but only after
you've packed your own.
-Why Mousse act so different
today from other day?
Hmm.
His letter.
Mousse have mother?
[crunching]
[ping]
-Hey.
[sound of kicking]
-Ahh!
-Still quick as ever, I see.
-So is there a point to this or?
-Hmm.
A point, huh?
Well, how's this?
[music playing]
[sound of fighting]
-Prepare to face
my final attack,
the fist of the white-- ahh!
-Will you shut up?
-Ahh!
-That's it, kid.
Play time's over!
[crash]
-Oh, man.
At least try a new
move or something.
-Ranma!
Over here!
[bike bell ringing]
-Shampoo!
Oh, Shampoo!
[crash]
-You were worried
about me, weren't you?
Ahh!
What the--
[crash]
-Go home, Mousse.
There's nothing for you here.
It's not nice to keep
your mother's hopes up.
-But you don't understand.
-Look there.
[chuckling]
-Ranma, you no is hurt, is you?
-I'm fine, Shampoo.
Hey, hey, let go.
You jerk, Saotome!
-Mousse, listen to me.
You're never going
to defeat him.
Can't you see that?
It's time you face
facts and let her go.
Be a man and go home to China.
-Huh?
Hey, didn't you get enough?
She's all yours, Ranma Saotome.
-Mousse?
-It's over.
I'm giving her up,
going back home,
and getting on with my life!
-You're going all the
way back to China?
-Don't try to stop me.
-Oh, we no stop you.
Have safe trip, ok?
Sayonara!
-Well then, I'll be going.
-OK, bye bye.
Bye.
-Wow.
Drop us a line, huh?
-Bye bye.
AKANE: Going home?
Yep, back to China.
-And you didn't stop him?
-I tried, but--
-You know how much
he loves Shampoo.
How could you?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Maybe you don't know what it's
like to be desperate like that,
but I do, OK?
-Did you ever hear of too
much information, Akane?
-Oh!
OK, Ranma.
If you want to
change the subject,
let's talk about
you and Shampoo.
-Now what do you--
-See for yourself.
-Look what Shampoo bring.
AKANE: Ooh, dim sum.
How yummy?
MALE VOICE: Well, well.
-Feed husband's
family is wife duty.
-And who might
that be, I wonder?
[sound of chewing]
[splash]
-Hmm?
-Ahh, did somebody
fall in the pond?
-Better check it out.
Who's there?
Whaa?
Huh, it's empty.
AKANE: Maybe the koi.
-Maybe.
SHAMPOO: Ranma, come eat.
RANMA: Yeah, OK.
[duck squawk]
SHAMPOO: Great-grandmother,
I'm home!
[bubbling noise]
-Shampoo, doesn't that
knife belong to Mousse?
He must have forgotten it.
-You think so?
Poor Mousse.
Why he always so stubborn.
-She's crying over me.
-Hiyah.
Stupid onion really
hurt Shampoo's eyes.
-Don't they?
The fresher the vegetable,
the more stubborn they are.
[duck squawk]
-My!
What a plump little foul.
Poor thing.
You must be shy.
But you mustn't let
that bother you!
Oh, you're a
fighter, aren't you?
That's good.
[laughs]
[dog barking]
-Here, Mr. Scaly Green.
Come meet your new playmate.
-Play nice, OK?
[splash]
See?
[crashing wave]
[duck squawking]
-One might think they'd
been friends forever.
-I knew they'd get on famously!
[laughs]
[sound of struggle]
[splashing]
[duck squawk]
-Ranma!
Where he go running this time?
Ranma!
-Oh!
Oh, man.
Now that Mousse has
gone back to China,
Shampoo won't give
me a moment of peace.
[laughter]
-What the--
-Call me Cupid, champion
of true love and traveler
from a distant star.
-You moron!
I thought you went
back to China.
-I told you my name was Cupid.
I'm here to see that you make
Shampoo happy, whether you
like it or not!
Ahh!
Now stay still, darnnit!
[thud]
-Ooh!
Where'd this come from?
-Cupid of love, my butt.
Oh, I'm so hungry.
-So, how many do you want?
Don't you worry,
it's on the house.
But you know that though, right?
-Sure do.
Well, down the hatch--
[crash]
-Now what?
-Hey you!
Why, Ranma Saotome.
You dirty cheat!
Sneaking behind another woman's
back, just so you could eat!
-I am not sneaking around.
-Silence!
I am here to make sure
you stay faithful to her,
despite this bimbo.
-OK, now you've done it!
The only thing faithful
here is our love.
-You don't say.
Isn't it more like that?
[crash]
-Hmm.
Shows what you know.
Our love is fresh off the
grill six days a week.
-We'll just see about that.
[sound of chopping]
-I see.
So you want to play hard ball.
Is that it?
Fine, consider the
challenge accepted.
It's going to take more than one
little setback to break us up.
Let's see how much of
our love you can eat.
-What happened to my
order of love, huh?
WAITRESS: Full yet?
MOUSSE: No way!
-I give up.
MOUSSE: Not even close.
[chopping sound]
[birds squawking]
-Oh man.
I am so hungry, I could eat a--
KODACHI: Ranma, darling!
-Ahh!
Ahh!
-What can I do for you, darling?
Something must have
brought you all this way.
Ahh, I-- yeah, uh--
[stomach rumbling]
-It's not hunger that brought
you here, is it, my darling?
-You-- you've going
to be kidding--
[stomach rumbling]
-Ahh.
-Goodness, you are
hungry, aren't you?
How would little Ranma
like it if Kodachi
prepare him a
home-cooked meal, huh?
-I'm telling you,
I'm hungry, OK?
-Now, Ranma, are you sure that's
how you want to talk to me?
I do have those pictures
of you, after all.
-Ahh!
She's really taking her time.
-And here it is!
-Hey, it looks great!
-The first course will be-- oh!
-Sneaking around again?
-We are not!
-He's right.
Ranma and I keep no
secrets from each other.
-I knew it!
You're incapable of being
faithful, aren't you?
I can see now not to trust you!
Unless you start keeping
your word to Shampoo,
I'm not going anywhere.
Do you hear me?
-But I never promised
nothing to nobody, you jerk!
-With the exception
of me, darling.
But that's a special case.
Otherwise, yes, you're free.
-Yes, is he?
Give me that!
-Oh!
Oh, now you've done it!
If you think you're getting
away with that, you-- you!
Yow!
[inaudible]
-You little cowards.
How dare you run away!
Stay still and take
your punishment!
-Missed me!
Hey, cut it out!
-Ha!
Some man you are!
-Like some girl could ever
beat me, a master of hi--
[gulping]
[crash]
[laughter]
-Oh, pity you're not more
careful what you eat.
Not everyone has the stomach
for paralysis powder.
Pa-pa-para?
-That's right, Darling.
But only to keep you
from wandering off.
However, as for stupid here--
-Ahh!
[splash]
-Hey.
-It serves him right.
I know you're still
hungry, Darling.
Should I go and remake dinner?
-Uh, let me, let
me ask you first.
What did you mean by pictures?
-Pictures?
And when did I mention those?
[laughs]
-Either way, I
can't just sit here
and let her poison me again.
[duck squawking]
-Mousse, you moron.
I guess I can't
leave you to drown.
Here.
[flash]
[sound of struggle]
-Ahh!
Whoa!
Mousse, you--
-Stupid duck!
Ahh!
Get out of my face, you
stupid overgrown suitcase!
Ahh!
[sound of fight]
[gasping]
-Ahh!
-Oh, pigtailed girl.
What can I do for you, my love?
Something must have brought you
out here to my humble estate?
My love, your teeth
are chattering.
You must be cold.
To the baths, quickly!
[duck squawking]
-Put me down, you jerk!
-Oh!
[splash]
-I don't believe you!
Now you're sneaking
around with a guy?
-It's not how it looks, OK?
-You liar!
-Ahh!
-Oh!
-I know you.
You're that Mousse
person, aren't you?
I get it.
You're in love with the
pig-tailed girl, too!
-With that pervert?
-Watch it.
-Hmm.
Some people never learn.
Fear not, my pig-tailed love.
I yield you to no one.
Unguard, varlet!
-You, too!
This time I'm not
going to hold back.
Ahh!
-Sucker.
Oh, Kuno!
I'll be waiting for you!
RANMA: I'll be right
there, pig-tailed girl!
-That sounds like my cue-- Ahh!
-Did you think you could escape?
-How did you?
-Pig-tailed girl.
-Oh, like it would
have killed you
to stall him while I got away?
-Forgive me, my love,
for now I must die.
-I mean, excuse me
while you kiss the sky!
OK, now you've done it.
Mousse, it's time
you and me settled
this thing once and for all.
-You'll get no
argument from me, you
shameless, good for nothing,
unfaithful, cross-dressing
cheat.
You want it official?
Fine!
-Anytime, pal.
-Good.
Here it goes.
Ahh!
[punch]
-Ahh!
[splash]
-Hey, you cheated!
-I did not!
You've got to be a guy
first, before we can fight,
that's all.
[birds chirping]
-You asked for it.
[sound of fighting]
-Oh no!
And now, the big finish!
[crash]
-Shampoo, forgive me.
-You're not a bad guy, Mousse.
It's just, well, you never
know when to give up.
You know what I mean?
-You're right.
I'm a loser.
I should go home.
-That's not what I meant!
-No, it's true.
Shampoo's too good for me.
-Geez!
If you weren't so stubborn,
then maybe I could help you.
-Ranma!
-What?
-Mousse, you're still here.
I thought you'd already
gone back to China.
You should go see
Shampoo, you know.
She's looking for you.
-She's, she's looking for me?
For real?
AKANE: Yeah.
-Shampoo!
Shampoo!
-Hi-yah!
Shampoo's so glad
you're here, Mousse.
Come on!
Everything all ready for you.
[gong]
-And just in time, too.
-So, what you waiting for?
-You mean all this is for me?
-Silly Mousse.
Who else you think
all this food for?
[sobbing]
-Shampoo!
-It's OK, Mousse.
You watch Cat Cafe for
great-grandmother and Shampoo.
We no know who else to ask.
-Careful minding the store now.
-You care.
You really do you care for me.
Oh, Shampoo!
[crying]
-I feel bad, but--
-Now Mousse is never
going back to China.
-Oh, Shampoo!
I swear, I'll be the
best waiter you ever had.
You won't regret taking me back.
I promise.
[music playing]
-I'm sorry, what
did you bet again?
Don't you know better than
to play cards with strangers?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
the dumbest bet in history.
We'll see you there!