-Clarabelle.
SHOGI STUDENT: Checkmate.
-You took your pawn too lightly.
In shogi, all pieces have value.
SHOGI STUDENT: Checkmate.
-Do over.
-Look, pal.
No more do overs.
That's the third
time you've done it.
-Aw, come on.
Why not?
It's not like it's life
or death, you know.
-I know, but it's not the point.
-So there's to be
no do overs, then?
-No.
-Then you, my friend, have
angered the wrong man.
I challenge you to battle shogi.
-At last, a true master of the
most mysterious martial arts.
To think that here, in
my own shogi parlor,
the great master of whom
we've seen so little of late
should choose to reveal himself.
More challenging
than martial art
checkers, more deadly
than death match Othello,
behold the art of battle shogi.
-Master my butt.
As a player, this guy sucks.
[chuckling]
SHOGI MASTER: Battle
shogi, final attack.
Grand master blast!
[yelling]
-I warned him,
but did he listen?
NARRATOR: Shogi showdown.
TENDO: Come on, Saotome.
What have you got?
GENMA SAOTOME: Only
this, checkmate.
TENDO: Like you
could win with that.
GENMA SAOTOME: It
still beats you.
[laughing]
TENDO: You thief.
GENMA SAOTOME: Once again,
you underestimate me.
[laughing]
But can-- this!
[sneezes]
-I was just a step
away from winning.
Saotome, was that
really fair of you?
-Hey.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Come on, I'll play you again.
-Fine.
But I'm warning
you, do that again
and you'll need a new partner.
-Whatever you say, Tendo.
You know I'll only
beat you again anyway.
I was only playing before.
This time, it's for real.
SHOGI MASTER: Shogi master
Genma Saotome, I presume.
-Hey.
You look kind of familiar.
-It's me.
So now do you remember my name?
-I'm thinking Western
part of the country.
-Uh-huh, uh-huh.
-We wouldn't have skipped out
on that restaurant together,
would we?
-Um, think again.
-Um, you must be that
guy from that time--
-Mm-hm, mm-hm.
-Nope.
Not a clue.
-It began a year
ago from this day.
Checkmate.
-Do over.
-I'm sorry, but no serious shogi
player could ask such a thing.
If you didn't want
to lose, then you
shouldn't have asked to play.
Come on.
I beat you fair and square.
-Hey!
Look!
Up in the sky!
-I-- I don't-- where?
[laughing]
Where?
-How's this?
-I-- I don't believe it.
I lost.
[laughing]
-Sorry.
-You win.
Tell me your name at least.
-They call me the shogi master.
Come look me up once
you learn to play.
[laughing]
SHOGI MASTER: I'd been defeated.
That had never happened before.
I'd hit rock bottom and
there was no way up,
and then my wife, Clarabelle,
kicked me out of the house.
Clarabelle, I need a drink.
CLARABELLE: And
whose fault is that?
You've shamed our name.
I can't live with you anymore.
SHOGI MASTER:
Clarabelle, please.
-Farewell forever.
-Clarabelle, please,
don't leave me.
Shogi was my life,
and then it was gone.
I never saw Clarabelle again.
After that, I did the only
thing that I could do.
I trained for a year.
Then I came to find you.
GENMA SAOTOME: Gotcha.
TENDO: On the
contrary, I've got you.
-I bare my soul and
you're playing games?
-Yeah.
So?
-So fight me.
-OK.
Like a moth to a flame.
SHOGI MASTER: Checkmate.
[screaming]
-Now be reasonable, Saotome.
You got lucky last time.
That's all.
-I'm almost sure I
can win this time.
-Hey!
What's that?
-Nothing.
That's what.
-There's a pig!
-No, there isn't.
[gasps]
Well, I'll be.
You really do have
a pig in your yard.
It looks good, too.
GENMA SAOTOME: Checkmate.
[gasps]
-You-- you beat me again?
-Now really, Saotome.
-If you don't want to get
beat, then don't play the game.
-Can I have another?
[gasps]
What's that?
It's not enough that
you've taken my pride.
You take my dignity, too.
-Now, now.
It's just a game.
-To you maybe,
but I'm different.
To me, it's a way of life.
If it's battle shogi you want,
it's battle shogi you'll get.
-I can hardly wait.
-You beat me once,
you beat me twice,
but now, I start to fight back.
Genma Saotome, get ready for
the toughest shogi of your life.
GIRL: I'm home.
RANMA: I'm starving.
AKANE: Me, too.
-Clarabelle.
AKANE: Huh?
-So here's where you been.
-And who are you?
-Checkmate.
-What's that for?
-That's for stealing
my wife, Clarabelle.
RANMA: Your what?
-Just like her picture.
-That looks nothing like me.
-You act all bossy
like she does.
-I do not, and who
are you, anyway?
Dad, is this guy
a friend of yours?
-Well actually, he's
more like my disciple.
-Now you're insulting me.
-I'm done with
shogi, so let's go.
-Saotome, please.
-Make all the jokes you want
because your doom is at hand.
[yelling]
-Somebody call for a hand?
-You're awful.
-Clarabelle, you've come back.
-Don't touch me.
-Clarabelle!
[chewing noisily]
-I have to say you've really
done it this time, Saotome.
Now you'll have to
reap what you've sown.
I hope you're happy.
-I love chewing ice.
-Nice try, pops.
-So what is martial
arts shogi anyways?
-Gee, how is it I know
what you're going to say?
-Martial arts shogi, AKA battle
chess, the most dangerous
of all Japanese board games.
In this real life version
of the traditional favorite,
real people are used
for game pieces.
-Promise me, boy, that
you'll be extra careful when
you're out there.
-And this relates to me how?
-Now see here, boy.
My battles are yours.
Yours are yours, too.
That's what family means.
-Fine.
I'm going to go take a nap.
[gasps]
[chuckling]
-So let's see how
you do on this board.
-So someone tell me again
why we're all in this corner.
-Because if we enter the
board, we'll get attacked.
-I'm home.
What's going on?
-Attack!
-Nabiki, quick!
Get off the board!
-Hm?
Hey, hey.
What is this?
Did I miss something?
-Clarabelle, you've
come back to me.
-What kind of name is
Clarabelle, anyway?
-Hey, everybody.
I'll have dinner ready soon, OK?
-Clarabelle, thank
goodness you're back.
-Huh?
-You look just the
way you used to.
Did you remember
the tonic water?
-Every woman that he meets
is Clarabelle, isn't she?
-Kasumi, be careful!
-Attack!
-OK, you jerks.
That's enough!
-Oh.
-Clarabelle, don't
leave me again.
-I'm sorry, but
my name is Kasumi.
-Oh, what a shame.
-I think you should
be safe up here.
-Oh no.
What about my shopping basket?
-Hey!
Our dinner!
-Gotcha!
-You come back here!
-Somebody stop him!
-Give me back my
filet mignon now!
-Give me back my lobster!
-Like you really live that well.
-Oh, we've got to
get a piece of this.
[yelling]
-Take him!
-He's mine!
-I got the onions!
-Cabbage!
-Potato!
-The eggs!
-Sardines!
-Tofu!
-My filet!
-Oh.
What a beautiful sunset.
-Hey!
Ladies first!
-Not when it's life
or death, it's not.
-Look over there.
There's a pig.
-You already tried that, pops.
-This is beyond pathetic.
-I'm an old man.
I need my nutrition.
Come on.
-Well, I think food's
wasted on the old.
-Tea, anyone?
Here.
I've got the hot water for it.
-Back off, sis.
I was here first.
-Hey.
-Waste not, want not, I suppose.
[whimpering]
That was good.
I'll get tea leaves, OK?
[sobbing]
Oh hey.
What's the matter, Father?
-I can't stand it.
This is his fault.
If not for him, we'd
be eating right now.
[laughing]
-He's out in the garden.
-Hasn't he done enough
damage for one night?
[laughing]
-Thanks to our game, as you can
see, I've gone up a ranking.
What do you think?
-I think it's stupid.
You look ridiculous.
Stop messing around
and play for real.
You could take him,
can't you, Saotome?
[grunting]
What do you mean, what?
-If that's what you
want, you've got it.
Meet me at noon tomorrow
at the nearby temple.
-Dad, are you sure about this?
-Cut that out.
-Why exactly are you here again?
-Because you need all
the help you can get.
We're using
tournament rules here.
You'll have to use your head.
-I told you I can handle it.
-You don't even know the
rules, do you, Ranma?
-That's it.
I'm out of here.
-Oh no you don't, Saotome.
We wouldn't even be here
if it wasn't for you.
-He's right, pops.
You owe it to him.
-Oh, why did I have to
win that stupid game?
It's a sad day when
a man must hide
his light beneath a bushel.
-Like he even knows
what that phrase means.
Speaking of sad,
where's the freak?
-With Nabiki.
-And what's your
role in this again?
-You watch sports, don't you?
Baseball, sumo?
And what do these
sports have in common?
A commentator, that's what.
That's why I'm here, sweetie.
-Good for you.
-Enough with the pregame.
Let's begin.
Since you're so few,
your team moves first.
-Fine with me.
What's the matter with you?
Why so slow?
-So why do they move so slow?
-Those pieces can only
move one square at a time.
-Well, wake me
when they're here.
-You!
Attack!
-Charge!
[grunting]
-Tricked you.
Pop!
Look out!
[grunting]
-So what happens
now to Mr. Saotome?
-Well you see, now
that he's captured,
he goes to the other
side of the board
where he waits to be
used by their team.
-Cool.
-You belong to me now, so stay
there 'til I call for you.
-OK.
Now it's starting
to tick me off.
-Corner!
-Corner, corner, corner, corner!
-Hey!
I thought you were only
supposed to go straight.
[yelling]
No fair!
I thought you were
going diagonal!
-Wait a minute.
That's not right.
How is he chasing him like that?
-Corners go diagonal and
flyers go at right angles.
If somebody on our side
doesn't figure that out soon,
we're going to lose big time.
[grunting]
-Now you.
-[grunts] Tree!
-Move him over to our
side of the game board.
-Dad?
[grunting]
AKANE: Ranma, that's a gold!
Get behind him!
-Get ready, 'cause now I
know what your weakness is.
-Ranma, he--
[grunting]
-All right.
So now what's going on?
-This one's the gold.
It can't move there, and
silvers can't move here.
-That's amazing.
-Ranma, go to the
side of the silver!
[grunting]
-Ha!
Can't touch me now, can you?
-Another man down.
-You're next, so
get ready, buddy.
-Like a moth to the flame.
[grunting]
-One on one we can handle,
but together, there's
so many different moves.
-True, but there's
no rule saying
we've got to move a certain way.
-Yeah, you're right.
Hiya!
-What are you doing there?
[yelling]
-Look!
We cleared the board.
-Please tell me that now
they're gone we can go home.
-I'm not quite
out of pieces yet.
I'll be you can't
fight your own father.
-I think I might
be able to manage.
-You're not going to
fight us, Dad. are you?
-I hope someday
you'll forgive me.
-You don't really
want to do it, do you?
-We wouldn't if
we could help it.
[yelling]
-Forgive me, boy.
-You'd better forgive me.
I'm sorry, Pop, but that's it.
It's time for me to
finish what you started.
-Son, please.
You wouldn't hit an
old man, would you?
-Prepare to meet your maker,
Pop, because in a minute,
you'll be--
[yelling]
-Sometimes, the martial
arts are not pretty.
[screaming]
-Ranma, help!
Hey!
-Clarabelle, look.
It says "My beloved wife."
That piece must be so heavy.
Here.
Let me carry you.
-I'd never go with you.
[screaming]
-Let go of her now.
-How can I let her
go when Clarabelle's
the one sticking onto me?
-Oh yeah, like I did it myself.
-Using Akane like that.
That's really low.
-I call it strategy.
Speaking of which, here's
my final, final attack.
Grandmaster slam!
-Slam!
-Crush him, my pieces.
Crush!
[laughing]
-And what's that?
-That, my little cutie
pie, is one flat Saotome.
-OK.
-You there!
What are you doing over there?
-Ah, Clarabelle.
You've come back to me.
-So that's your wife.
-It's too hot for
this sort of thing.
-I can't help it.
-You're too into this hobby.
-It's not a hobby.
It's a lifestyle.
-Whatever it is, so long
as it pays the bills,
I won't complain.
Where did you find that
silly looking girl, anyway?
-She just sort of
glommed onto me.
You know you're the
only one I want.
-Oh, you charmer, you.
-Uh-huh.
-OK, everyone.
It's time to eat dinner.
-Coming!
-Time to eat, time to eat.
-Akane?
-So what if her
name's old fashioned?
OLD MAN: I see what I
eat and I eat what I see.
-So what is for dinner?
-Filet mignon, lobster.
Step it up, boy.
You're falling behind.
-How am I going to do that?
-Go faster.
-Huh?
Don't start with me, you,
-Oh, don't be such a baby.
-You can start walking
anytime, you know.
NARRATOR: Like the good ninja
he is, Kuno's manservant Sasuke
has been sent on a
reconnaissance mission.
What secrets will the
Tendo dojo reveal?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Sasuke's Mission Improbable."
We'll see you there.