NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hey, let go.
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma's
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): "Clash
of the Delivery Girls!
The Martial Arts Takeout Race."
GENMA (VOICEOVER):
There was once
a time in my mid
'20s when I walked
the earth with my
newborn son Ranma
on my back in search of
martial arts techniques.
Together, we traveled many
a strange and desolate land.
-So hungry.
So hungry.
[baby crying]
[sniffing]
[humming]
-Ah, doesn't that
smell good, Kaori?
Look at you, sleeping
like a little angel.
Your old dad's going to have
himself some nice fish, just
like your mother used to make.
Ah.
Huh?
What do you want?
-Just a little bite,
that's all I ask.
-No way.
What am I supposed to eat?
Get your own.
-Just one bite.
-I said no and I mean no.
-I can't go on.
Help me.
My boy and I are starving.
[baby crying]
There, there now, Ranma.
Quiet.
I'll do anything.
Please just tell
me what you want.
Shh, shh.
Be a good boy and stop crying.
-Anything?
Even the child on your back?
-Huh?
-The only thing I need
to die a happy man
is a male heir to
my family name.
If you give me your
son, I can bring him up
to marry my daughter.
And then he can inherit the
Daikoku School of Martial Arts.
And then-- huh?
Forget it.
Who would trade
their son for a fish?
-Throw in the rice and
pickles and he's all yours.
-That's it, little man.
Drink that milk
and grow up strong.
What an appetite.
The Daikoku School of Martial
Arts has an heir at last.
Poor man, I'll never forget
that look on his face.
Oh well.
Time to break camp.
[humming]
-I could never leave you, son.
A man's got to do what
a man's got to do.
I'll remember you
to my dying day.
GENMA (VOICEOVER): Little
did I know the true price I'd
eventually have to
pay for his help.
Oh.
-Give it back, old man.
-What do you take me for, boy?
-That's my pickle, pop.
Hand it over.
-I'd like to, but I can't.
Martial artists must rise
above their stomachs.
If this pickle causes
you to lose your focus,
it's my job to remove its
temptation from your sight.
It's for your own good.
You understand.
-Oh no.
I ain't buying that this time.
-Self-denial and
constant exercise
is the path of a
true martial artist.
Through these things
alone may a martial artist
attain enlightenment.
-Well, there's an
interesting theory.
-I'm done.
-Have a pickle, pop.
ANNOUNCER: That's right, folks.
For 10 years now,
King Kadai Restaurant
has been bringing
you 4,000 years
of delicious Chinese cuisine.
Take this flyer and get a free
appetizer with your next meal.
Here.
-Here, sir.
Have a flyer.
-Here you go.
What a car.
Have a flyer, sir.
MR. DAIKOKU: Ah, the city
seems prosperous enough.
-Huh?
You idiots!
MR. DAIKOKU: Guess
who's coming to dinner.
-Come back here.
MR. DAIKOKU: Is anyone home?
-Sounds like
someone's at the door.
KASUMI: I'll get it.
Hello?
Who's there?
-Sorry about that.
The door was open.
I let myself in.
-Oh, and who might
you be, stranger?
-I'm here for Ranma,
Ranma Saotome.
He does live here, doesn't he?
-Hey, Ranma, it looks
like you've got a visitor.
-Huh?
-Oh, Ranma!
It's me!
Your dad!
At last, I've found you, son.
-Hey, get him off of me.
-Please call me dad.
RANMA: Dad?
MR. DAIKOKU: Of course, once
you marry my little girl,
you will become my
true and legal heir.
-Married?
-What do you mean heir?
-You can come out now, Kaori.
-Greetings, future husband.
-Yeah, she sure is a
beauty now, isn't she?
-Ranma, what is the
meaning of this?
-I don't know.
I don't know.
-Don't worry, son.
Your father has already
agreed to the match.
Now, where is Genma anyhow?
-Come on.
The jig is up, Mr. Saotome.
-Explain yourself Saotome.
What's going on?
-Did you have to use
boiling water, Tendo?
-That's your least worry.
You--
-There you are, Genma.
-Yeah, there he is.
-You left so very quickly.
-Yes, well I--
-What'd you do this time?
-Ranma, my boy.
Well, you see, I, uh--
try to understand, boy.
Things were different.
-You sold me for one crummy
little stinking fish, huh?
-He also threw in the
rice and two pickles.
-What kind of father are you?
-I know that I can
never take your place
in Ranma's little heart, Genma.
But I'll try and
be a good father.
-Uh, I'm sure you would.
-Wait just a minute now.
There's something
you need to know.
Ranma has a fiancee.
-What's this?
Is it true, girl?
-No way, no.
Absolutely not.
-You know, I've been
saying that for months.
-Shut up.
-Please forgive my impertinence.
-Oh my, she's good.
-Very impressive.
[whistle]
-Meh, she's not bad.
-Well, I see.
You've got a certain
amount invested in the boy.
You must be compensated.
What would be reasonable?
-So how much you've got?
-Don't you dare.
-Put yourself in my shoes, boy.
KASUMI: Does this mean Ranma and
Akane won't be getting married?
-Why would I do that?
NABIKI: Poor Akane.
-You sold me, remember?
-I never said yes.
-Sir, your offer is refused.
After he marries my
Akane, he'll help
with the Anything Goes
School of Martial Arts.
-I've already named him
heir to the Daikoku School.
[clears throat]
What is it, Kaori dear?
Tell me, Akane,
my daughter would
like to know if
you truly love him,
or are you just being obedient?
-Love?
Hmph.
No way.
-Oh yeah?
Well, I don't like
girls like you anyway.
-Aw, who cares, pervert?
RANMA: Tomboy.
Flat-chested.
AKANE: Dope.
Dimwit.
Dummy, dummy, dummy.
You make me sick to my stomach!
[cough]
-What's that, dear?
Akane, my daughter would
like to challenge you,
and the winner of the
duel will get Ranma.
-What?
-She is of the opinion
that, despite your protests,
you have some feeling for him.
She offers you a
chance to keep him
by engaging in combat with her.
-She accepts.
I as her father
grant permission.
What will they compete in?
-Ah yes, the sport.
Ah, that's it.
How does this strike you, huh?
-Let me see.
Miss Martial Arts Takeout Race.
The winner gets a
year's supply of ramen.
She'll do it.
-I'm not giving up young Ranma.
-There's no way I'm giving up
on that ramen, or on Ranma.
-How did this happen?
-First a fish and
now it's noodles.
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
the Miss Martial Arts Takeout
Race should be getting
started at any moment now.
As explained earlier,
the first delivery girl
to safely pass through the
checkpoints and reach the goal
is the winner.
We'd tell you the rules, but
the fact is there aren't any.
-So you agree then that
the loser will willingly
give up Ranma to the winner.
-I'll gift wrap him.
-Ranma, I'm not doing this
for you, you got that?
-Yeah, sure, whatever.
Just get out there and
win that ramen, all right?
-Oh yeah, that's right.
You've got half
a right to enter.
Why aren't you
competing in this?
-Because I'm a guy and
I plan to stay that way.
Got it?
ANNOUNCER: Will all contestants
come to the starting line,
please.
That's right, girls.
Move in a little closer there.
We're just about
to-- what's this?
It seems a young girl will be
competing in her wedding dress.
Very interesting.
-Who does she think she is?
Hmph.
-I have seen that grip
before, ladies and gentlemen.
I believe we are in for a treat.
-Hiya!
ANNOUNCER: Not one
delicious drop wasted.
We're talking takeout on
a scale unheard of, ladies
and gentleman.
We're talking clash
of the delivery girls!
-I'll bet you
didn't know my girl
is a master in the ancient
art of martial arts
restaurant takeout, eh?
-Martial arts takeout?
-What's that?
-Shame.
Everyone knows the ancient art
of martial arts takeout started
in the Aizuna prefecture
during the Edo period.
They were fields and
mountains to get through,
and other kinds of perils-- wild
boars, bandits, cut-throats.
Imagine the gratitude when
that food finally arrived, safe
and still piping hot.
Thus was the art of
martial arts takeout born.
You haven't got
a chance, mister.
ANNOUNCER: Ready.
Set.
Go!
-Cheater.
-No rules, right?
-How did you?
-Observe, Daikoku
School of Martial Arts,
Special Technique--
It's Fast or it's Free.
-You can do it, Akane.
-Hey, try not to kill yourself.
-Ranma.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Hmph.
Who does that idiot think
I'm fighting for anyway?
-Ranma, hey now.
Whoa.
Loosen up your grip there, son.
OK.
Come on, hey.
Look who it is.
I'm counting on you
to win that ramen.
-My old man?
Yo, pop, I thought this
race was for women only?
-But son, this too is part
of the Anything Goes fighting
style.
Whoa--
-Stay out of my way.
KAORI (VOICEOVER):
Why won't she quit?
-Daikoku School of Martial Arts.
-Not again.
-Fishcake Blizzard.
GENMA (VOICEOVER):
Ah, it's a small price
to pay for a year's
worth of ramen.
Ugh!
What is it?
Get it off me!
No, no!
-You look good like
that down there.
Don't look so stricken
on my account, dear.
I'm sure Ranma and I shall
be perfectly happy together.
-It's not over yet.
Martial Arts
Restaurant Takeout--
who thought up this
dumb race anyway?
There's no way
I'm going to lose.
-So long, Akane Tendo.
-Ow, my leg.
It's numb.
-Guess it's just
me from here on in.
-I just can't let her beat me.
-Ramen Roundup Noodle Noose.
-Oh no!
That idiot.
-Observe the most lethal
attack of the Daikoku School
of Restaurant Takeout
Martial Arts--
the Ramen Roundup Noodle Noose!
Just like the coils
of a deadly snake,
the ramen noodles close
tighter and tighter.
The more you fight, the
tighter they become.
Surrender.
It's over.
-I'll let go if you give up.
-Ra-- Ranma--
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Don't ask me to do it.
-Ra--
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
I'll do anything,
but don't ask me to
become a girl again.
I just-- Whoa!
-Well, Akane, give up?
-Ranma, you came.
-Are you all right, Akane?
-Yes.
-Sorry, girly.
But I'm afraid I can't
let you win this race.
-Where did she come from?
-You're trying to take Ranma
away from me, aren't you?
RANMA: Wouldn't
you like to know?
-You can't have him.
-Oh no!
-There.
-Got it.
-Take a good look at that ramen.
RANMA: The fishcake,
it fell off.
-You can't serve ramen
without fishcake, dear.
You lose the fishcake,
you lose the race.
-Honestly.
Ranma, look up there.
-Huh?
OK.
-Ranma.
-No!
No!
Don't eat that.
Bad doggy.
-Oh no, you don't.
-There can only be one
winner in this race.
-Faster, faster, Kaori!
You can do it!
-For the sake of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts,
run faster, Ranma!
-We're almost at
the finish line.
Come here.
-Let go of my legs.
-No way, girl.
-Akane, go for it.
-Ranma.
-Kaori, try harder.
-Akane, do it.
-I can't.
-Akane, you can do it.
You're almost there.
SOUN: She did it.
She defended the
honor of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts,
and she defended the ramen too.
-Ranma, Akane, I hope the two
of you will be very happy.
Genma and Soun, thanks a
lot for the hospitality.
My daughter would like
to thank you as well.
-Oh, there's no
need to thank us.
At least let us offer you a
bowl of ramen for the road.
-Well, thanks for
the thought, but I
think we're a bit ramen'd out.
Perhaps we'll join
you the next time.
Farewell.
-Well, well well.
This has been a very
interesting day.
Wouldn't you say so, Saotome?
-Mm.
Well then, Tendo, shall we, ah--
-Of course, we shall.
Our favorite food is--
ALL: Takeout ramen.
-Eat up now, everyone.
There's plenty more
where that came from.
-Akane.
-Huh?
-I helped you because I
wanted the free ramen.
It's not because I
like you or nothing.
You got that?
-Don't worry.
Your secret is safe.
-The Anything Goes
School is secure.
-And we got a year of
free ramen for nothing.
MAN: Is anybody home?
-Someone's at the door.
-Hello?
Who is it?
-Sorry about that, folks.
No need for alarm.
The door was open
so I let myself in.
-And who might you be, stranger?
-I'm here for Ranma Saotome.
-Huh?
Well, I'm Ranma Saotome.
That's me.
Who are you?
-Oh, Ranma!
It's me, your dad.
Call me dad, son.
-How many more fiancees
do I have anyway?
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I
know Ranma's weak spot.
Aw, don't make such
a big deal about it.
Everybody's got a
weak spot, don't they?
Then again.
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
"You Really Do Hate Cats!"
See you there.