[opening theme]
[speaking japanese]
-Hey, how's it going?
How's about some
tea on my yacht?
-Tea, did you say?
I'd love to.
How far away is your boat?
-Ranma, what is the
matter with you?
Have you forgotten you're a guy?
-Oh no.
I haven't forgotten.
-You're a guy?
-Bingo.
-Outta here!
-Honestly.
-Come on.
I'm just playing.
-Speaking of playing, why
are you still being a girl?
-Let's just say it
saves me the trouble
of changing into a
different bathing suit.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
All It Takes is One.
The Kiss of Love is
the Kiss of Death.
-A little warm for
you, Mr. Saotome?
-I know people who'd kill
for a coat that thick.
'Course, they'd never be stupid
enough to wear it to the beach.
-Hottest day of the
summer, and look at him.
What the heck's he a panda for?
It ain't like he's going
swimming or nothing.
[scream]
-[inaudible]
-Give me back my bathing suit!
Give me my swimsuit back!
Come back here!
He stole my swimsuit!
-I knew it!
Come here.
You senile delinquant.
Can't I take my eye
off you for a second?
What are you planning to
do with this junk, huh?
Go into business selling
bathsuits or something?
Pervert.
-What-- what have you
done to my collection?
[interposing voices]
Oh youth, oh hope, oh happiness.
-Oh are you in trouble.
-Why you.
Ranma, I've got a way
of dealing with swimsuit
stealing little punks like you.
-Then whip it out, Gramps.
-I'll go steal me some new ones.
-Look at.
What's a melon doing here?
-Heya, cuties.
How's about some nice,
juicy watermelon?
Come on, cutie.
Have some melon.
Come on.
-How's about you have some
of this, you little goat.
Where the heck are you
getting all this energy?
-Where do you think?
From the blue sky, the white
clouds, and the bright sun.
I just love the sea.
-And don't forget the
bikinis, the tan-lines,
and all the exposed flesh.
-That stuff's nice, but how
can it compare with you?
-Get lost at sea, freak!
He ain't even human.
-Wo ai ni.
-It's Shampoo.
-Nihao, Ranma.
-Hey, over here.
-So happy.
You follow Shampoo
to beach, yes?
-Not on purpose.
-What are you two girls doing?
-Oh, so you're only here
for the summer then?
-Winter is snow mountain.
Summer is beach.
It great-grandmother's strategy.
-I'm impressed.
-OK, Ranma.
Say "ah."
-Give me those.
-Oh no.
Be polite.
-Me?
Polite.
Bad enough we gotta
have the freak here.
Guess this means the
ghoul's here too.
You sure this beach is big
enough for the two of 'em.
-Ranma, we go on
date after work, yes?
-No, thanks.
I'll pass.
I got it.
-What?
You'll introduce
me to a girlfriend?
You-- you really mean it?
-Sure.
Just lay off the bikini
stealing for a while, huh?
-I will.
I will.
I will be a good boy.
You just watch.
Good thing I brought my
treasure chest along.
-What's he need all that
junk for at the beach.
-How's about I give her this?
In honor of our first date.
-Just outta curiosity,
where'd you rip it off from?
-So, Ranma, what kinda
girl is she, huh?
You picked her out for me,
'cause she's my type, right?
You do know my type, right?
Big eyes, long hair?
-That's her, all right.
-Really?
Oh, it's so good to be alive.
-Oh, Ranma.
Come on.
You don't mean Shampoo.
You know she'll never say yes.
-Yo, Shampoo.
-Ranma, you come
take Shampoo to date?
-Woohoo!
Shampoo will do nicely.
Thank you.
Ranma, you still here?
Go now.
I'm fine on my own, you know?
-Sorry, Gramps.
No can do.
There's someone I want
you to meet first.
-Oh.
OK.
Whe-- where is she?
-There you go, Gramps.
Just what you asked for.
-He say he want date with
you, great-grandmother.
-What about why I want?
-You do know my type right?
Big eyes, long hair.
-Gee, why didn't I think of it?
They're so close in age too.
-Is good couple.
-We'll leave you
two lovebirds alone.
-We kids no want interfere.
-Don't go.
Don't go.
-Oh yeah.
Is beautiful bracelet.
-I want you to have it.
Think of it as a dowry.
Now, come on.
Don't take it personally.
I'm sure you'll make
someone a fine wife.
But-- but for me, the only
one I want to marry is--
-Don't be ridiculous.
I'm sure we'd all
much rather hear
how you got your hands
on that bracelet.
Why, even the ancestress of our
3,000 year old Amazon tribes
would've wept to
have possessed it.
How on Earth did you
get a hold of it?
-That's for me to know
and you to find out.
-I knew it must've
been ripped off.
-All night.
You hand that over this instant.
-I don't wanna.
-Hand it over!
-Now that I know it's so
valuable, I don't think so.
[laughter]
-Why, that monster
stole our treasure.
-But why is it so special?
-Shampoo?
You simply must get
that bracelet back
before he learns its secret.
-Secret?
-If you fail, he'll make
this world a living hell.
-What?
A love potion?
-Whoa.
You mean like in that old song?
-Yes.
Only this love potion
is so terrifying,
it frightens even me.
Swallow one of the three
pills in that bracelet,
and you'll fall
instantly in love
with the first person you
see of the opposite sex.
-That really is terrifying.
-Whoa.
Creepy.
-Oh, Ranma.
You swallow pill
for Shampoo, yes?
-That's not funny.
Let go.
-Oh, be polite now.
-I ain't.
So let go!
-This is no time for
eating snow cones.
We've gotta stop him.
-If he discovers the
secret of those pills--
-It'll be hell, all right.
-I heard it.
I heard it!
Shampoo, baby!
Let's start us up a heat
wave of the heart, baby.
Hey!
-Stay still, you little freak.
Hand over that bracelet.
Hah.
Now I've gotcha.
-Take that, you ingrate.
Nya, nya.
You can't catch me.
You can't have this
bracelet, neither.
Never, never, you hear?
-He got away.
-But he leave one pill behind.
-Hey, it's that love potion.
-Think it work?
Ranma!
What you think you're doing?
-Oh, I'm sorry.
Am I in the way?
-So what are you doing?
You're so cute.
-Uh--
-You're so cute.
-Ra-- Ranma, wait a minute.
-So cute.
-Stop it.
No.
Not like this.
Say it to me without
the love potion.
-Sucker.
Oh, yeah.
Like I'd really swallow it.
I swallowed it.
Oh my god, I swallowed it.
-Ranma!
-Ranma, look at Shampoo, yes?
-Hey!
-OK, ghoul.
Hand over the antidote.
How come I-- how
come I never realized
just how beautiful a mature
woman in full bloom could be?
-You're just teasing
me, aren't you?
-Is no fair, great-grandmother!
-Forgive me, child.
But I too am a woman.
-My darling, you know I won't be
happy until we're man and wife.
-Yes, my love.
-Great-grandmother,
you stay away from him!
-Sorry, but I ain't handing
this cutie over to anyone.
-If we no do something, Ranma
and great-grandmother will--
-They can't.
No, they can't.
I won't let them.
Ranma, don't do it!
-Cut that out!
I'm sorry, son, but I
must oppose this marriage!
-Huh?
What?
-Before you enter into holy
wedlock with that woman,
first, you must
defeat me in battle.
-Wedlock?
Who the heck do you
think I'm marrying?
-Me, of course.
-Is-- is he all right?
-Ah, well.
Guess the pill
couldn't last forever.
-You mean?
-No is permanent?
-What the sap here just
swallowed was the instant pill.
-Ah, too bad.
Imagine what t have happened
if only it had lasted.
-Bad great-grandma.
-I still don't understand.
If what Ranma took
was the instant pill,
how long will the
other two pills last?
-Each of the three
pills on the bracelet
is effective at
different duration.
The two remaining
love potion pills
are effective one day and
a lifetime respectively.
AKANE: OK, the instant
lasts an instant,
the one day lasts a day, and
the lifetime lasts forever?
GREAT-GRANDMOTHER:
Yes, if the son-in-law
had swallowed that pill.
I'd already be sending
out wedding invitations.
-That one too close for comfort.
-Ranma?
I don't think he hears us.
-Oh.
Hm.
Which girl do I pick?
-Ah-hah.
So there you are.
-Shampoo, baby.
-Oh, you want go on
exciting date with Shampoo?
-Do I?
Do I?
Oh boy, oh boy, oh
boy, oh boy, oh boy!
-But what is it?
Is it an oompa-loompa?
-It's crying and
wiggling and stuff.
-Quit trying to get it down.
Just keep poking it.
-I am not an octopus.
I am not an oompa-loompa.
Shampoo lied to me.
Get me down!
Come on.
I'll buy you some ice cream.
I'll buy you some candy.
I'll buy you whatever you want.
Just get me down!
[moaning]
-Oh, honestly, Ranma.
Just get over it, will you?
-Shampoo no mind.
-Hey, what do you want?
Huh?
The bracelet.
-He take this one
while he sleeping.
-Oh no you don't!
-Say, "ah," and fall
in love with Shampoo.
-Gha?
Wha-- wha?
-How's about this?
Still wanna give Ranma
that love potion?
-It no matter, stupid.
Once Ranma swallow pill,
Shampoo change him back to boy.
then he love her whole life.
-Hey!
-You missed.
-She what?
Akane swallowed a
love potion pill?
So in other words,
the first man she sees
is the one she'll love?
-Something like that, yeah.
-Ranma.
-Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
-Take a good long
look, sweetheart.
-Did it have to be so hot?
-Shampoo no think so.
-Dad, cut it out, will you?
I'll be the one who
decides who I look at.
-Hey, there, Akane!
-You can't take your eyes
off of him for a second.
Oh yeah.
Tell me quick, Akane.
Which one did you take?
The one day pill or
the lifetime pill?
-Hey, what happens if she
took the lifetime pill, huh?
-So this is the last one.
You can relax, Akane.
The love potion pill you
took was the one day only.
-Oh good.
-Is that all?
-What do you mean, is that all?
-If it's only a one day
pill, what's the big deal?
-Just because it
isn't your problem--
-Little freak springs
up from outta nowhere!
Before looking at some other
freak, why not look at me?
-Uh-- are you sure
you're ready to?
-Don't tell me you
thought I was serious.
-All I have to do is not
look at any guys, right?
Some stupid love potion
isn't gonna beat me.
-Akane.
-Ow.
-Jeez.
Why does she gotta
be so stubborn?
-And why's she gotta ignore a
sweet, harmless, little old man
who only wants to help her.
-Maybe it's because you make
her feel sick to her stomach!
-What did you say?
Is that any way for you
to address your master?
-Whoops.
My mistake.
I got it wrong.
The one Akane swallowed was the
lifetime pill, not the one day.
-Lifetime?
-Ranma, you wait.
-Come on.
Let go of me.
-Shampoo no care if last
pill is only one day type.
Just hurry up, swallow,
and fall in love with her.
Who care what Akane look at?
-Maybe it's not important
to you who she looks at.
But she's sure the
heck gonna care.
Let go!
-Shampoo won't.
Ranma, come back!
-Where the heck have I come now?
I can't go on.
Oh, Akane.
If only you were-- Huh?
Hello, Akane.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Ranma, you idiot.
Can't you care?
Just a little?
-Akane?
Akane?
Akane!
-Ryo--
-Hiya!
Huh?
-What was that for?
-This little pig was drowning.
-Hi-chan.
What's he--
-It's important
you listen, Akane.
About that pill--
-Poor wittle baby.
You must've been so lonely in
that house all by yourself.
-Akane, I'm trying to
tell you something.
That pill you took, it-- hey!
Wait.
Where are you doing?
Akane, that pill you took
was the lifetime one.
Put your blindfold back on.
What if some strange
guy shows up?
-What do you care, Ranma?
Who knows?
Maybe my prince on a white
horse may come along.
-Akane, have you
gone crazy or what?
What the?
-Look at me.
Look at me!
I'm a prince on a white horse.
-Why you little!
-Akane!
-Oh no you don't!
Akane!
Forgive me!
-I'll save you, Akane.
-I said no!
Akane, I--
-Ranma!
Be good.
Take pill!
You drop pill!
-Huh?
-I'm sorry, Akane,
but I gotta do it.
What if you fall in
love with some freak?
I'm gonna become a
guy just for you.
-Ranma.
-So have you fallen for me yet?
-I dunno.
Have you fallen for this?
-Ow!
But you-- but you swallowed
the-- what about the--
-The pill?
Thanks to your drowning
me, here it is!
Who needs it?
-What're you doing?
You're wasting it!
Look what she's done.
The love potion's gone.
-All's well that ends well.
Isn't that what Daddy says?
-I already told you.
I was just trying to warn
you about the lifetime pill.
-It was day only.
-Ranma.
-What the-- what
the heck are you--
-Are you absolutely sure
she took the lifetime pill.
-Yeah, that pill went
back into the water.
-I knew it.
-Oh no.
You don't think
it swallowed the--
-Run for it!
-I didn't wanna get
married to an octopus.
[ending theme]
[speaking japanese]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
That stupid moose.
What's he up to with
poor, good-hearted Ryoga?
What?
The two of them are
teaming up against Ranma?
Next time on Ranma
1/2, The Ultimate
Team-up-- The Ryoga
Moose Alliance.
We'll see you there.