THEME SONG: (SINGING IN
JAPANESE) Smile again!
MAN: Now please, Dr. Tofu,
just try it for a month.
Yes, but I already have
four different subscriptions.
So why not make
it five newspapers?
I'm really not interested.
Well, what if I gave
you an offer you simply
couldn't refuse, huh?
How about these two tickets
to the amusement park
absolutely free?
Interested?
Oh, good morning.
Oh, hi Kasumi.
How are you doing?
[clipping]
It looks much better now.
Uh, thanks.
I see you're a
friend of Dr. Tofu.
Maybe you're
interested in these?
They're free.
Yes.
The amusement park
looks like fun.
Yes, I go there
all the time myself.
[giggling]
In that case, I'll take them.
They're all yours if you could
just sign on the dotted line.
Oh, sure.
Uh, sign.
Yes, uh, well there you go.
MAN: You might want
to sign the contract.
Huh?
MAN: I just hope you never
have to operate on me.
KASUMI (VOICEOVER): Tendo family
goes to the amusement park.
Amusement park?
For free?
Oh please, the amusement park?
I am much too old for that.
But Nabiki--
BOTH: Hm?
I thought it might be
fun for the whole family.
NABIKI: Well, it is free.
I thought Dr. Tofu
wanted to take you there
on a date, Kasumi.
He wouldn't want
us tagging along.
I think it would be more fun
if all of us went together.
RANMA: Hm, it says here each
ticket is good for six people.
One, two, three, four, five,
and with me it makes six.
Oh, and in the fine print,
it says pets are not allowed.
Sorry, P-chan.
[clears throat]
You know, maybe a
family outing together
is just what we all
need, not that I'm
really interested in going.
Mhm.
I have to agree with Tendo.
I mean, how often
do we get a chance
to do things with the kids?
Good, then it's settled.
How about we all go on Sunday?
BOTH: Yes, we're going!
What's all the hubbub?
It sounds like a party.
Uh, well, we were just
talking about-- hey!
What are you doing
with my underwear?
Ah!
Come back here!
Oh!
Why, you little worm!
HAPPOSAI: What'd I do?
AKANE: Worm!
HAPPOSAI: What'd I--
AKANE: Give those back!
HAPPOSAI: Come and get them!
So we don't tell him.
All agreed?
ALL: All agreed.
It's going to be
a beautiful day.
Oh, Kasumi.
Hm?
Ah, what happened here?
I wonder who could
have done this.
Come on, Kasumi.
We gotta go.
Yeah, we should hurry because
Happosai hasn't come home yet.
Although the fact that he's
not around does bother me.
Come on, boy.
We haven't got all day.
And besides, don't
you think making
Dr. Tofu wait for us is rude?
Hm.
Mm.
Hm?
Hm.
Mm-mm.
I guess I'll wear these again.
KASUMI: Is anyone home?
Huh?
Oh!
Ah!
[crash]
[chuckling]
We'd like to thank
you for inviting us.
[chuckling]
[screaming]
Those three are so immature.
Would you like a little tea?
Uh, yeah sure.
I-- I'd love some.
Thank you.
Are you all right, Dr. Tofu?
DR. TOFU: I'm fine.
Why?
He's such a smooth operator.
Nabiki!
[grunting]
[sniffing]
My turn, boy.
Let me show you.
Wait a second, Saotome.
It's my turn.
GENMA: Excuse me, Tendo, but
I think I was here first.
SOUN: Hey, that's not fair!
Tell me, Akane, are
you having a good time?
Yeah, sure.
It's just-- it's just--
Hm?
Well I hope that, you
know, with my family
here that we're not
getting in your way.
Don't worry about that.
I-- I just want to make
sure you're having fun.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure, but I
appreciate your concern, Akane.
Hey, when we get off of here,
let's go get something to eat?
Yeah, sure, OK.
DR. TOFU: You're a shy
one like me, aren't you?
Yeah I guess a little bit.
Oh, I wish there was
something I could do to get
poor Dr. Tofu over his shyness.
Ah, good.
I'm starving.
I'd like seven peach
dumplings please.
SHAMPOO: Seven peach
dumplings coming up.
It's you, Shampoo.
Hello, Dr. Tofu.
What bring you to
the amusement park?
Well, I came here with
everyone from the Tendo Dojo.
Does that mean Ranma
come with you too?
DR. TOFU: Uh, mm,
well-- what the?
SHAMPOO: What is matter?
Ugh, I think I dropped
my wallet somewhere.
I must have.
Shampoo make you deal.
You no have to pay Shampoo
if you take me to Ranma.
Yeah, sure.
Huh?
[quacking]
I can't believe she's here.
I mean, who would
have ever thought
Shampoo would be working here?
I had feeling Ranma would come.
It must have been
fate that led you here
to be with your Shampoo.
Well, they finally
decided to show.
[laughter]
You didn't even come close
to my high score, Tendo.
Oh yeah?
At least I wasn't the
one who was hogging
the game the whole time.
Yes, but practice makes
perfect, my friend.
Look at you, Saotome,
talking like a big shot
just because you beat
me at whacking moles.
Oh yeah?
Well I still beat you.
Isn't it a beautiful day?
And I think now is the
perfect time for a picnic.
Nabiki, why don't you
bring out the lunch?
You got it.
Ugh!
KASUMI: What is it, Nabiki?
Ah!
RANMA: It's the freak.
KASUMI: How did he get here?
I hope he didn't ruin lunch.
It's gone.
ALL: Ah!
You-- you forgot all about me.
[crying]
When I came home,
I saw you were all
packed up and ready to leave.
At first I thought you'd come
and ask me to join you, but no.
That's why I hid in
the picnic basket.
By the way, I have a feeling
the mayonnaise was a little off.
Please don't cry.
We were in such a
hurry this morning
I guess no one
remembered to tell you.
Are you saying
that you're sorry?
KASUMI: Yes.
So who wants to go
on the whirl-a-wheel?
ALL: Here's your whirl-a-wheel.
Oh man, I am so hungry.
Now I'll have to buy something.
Hey, what's wrong, pops?
Nothing.
You sure?
Ah, I admit it.
I spent every last yen we
had playing that stupid mole
game back there.
What?
Are you serious?
That's right, Akane.
Every last yen is long gone.
[gasp]
Now what do we do?
Don't look at me, Akane.
I'm almost tapped out myself.
I think I have just enough
left for the train home.
How dare you waste everything
we had on an idiotic mole game.
Well, come to think
of it, it was easy.
[arguing]
[sigh]
Oh man, I'm starving.
[grumbling]
GIRL 1: Wow, you see they're
giving away a full course
dinner?
GIRL 2: Yeah, for two.
GIRL 1: All you gotta do
is win the go kart race.
Huh?
Dinner?
And full course?
Did she say it was free?
ALL: Count me in.
Win the race, win a dinner.
Where's the track?
NABIKI: Let's see.
Here it is.
Go kart race circuit.
Boy, the motor's powerful,
but the body is pretty small.
It seems sized more
for women than for men.
And that means--
That means we've got
a good shot at winning.
Come on, girls!
We've got a go kart race to win!
Yeah, let's show them
what girls can do!
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER):
Full course dinner--
that prize made for
Ranma and Shampoo.
Well, you can count me out.
I'm not much suited
for the cars.
Dr. Tofu?
Huh?
I was thinking maybe you
could teach me to drive.
[gasp]
Kasumi?
You're not serious,
are you, Kasumi?
Yes.
ANNOUNCER: Good
afternoon, everyone,
and welcome to go
kart circuit one.
There's only five
minutes left to sign up
for the hyper kart grand prix.
And remember, the
winner gets 10,000 yen
plus a course dinner for two.
Oh, somebody please pinch me.
Every prayer I've ever
made just came true!
Saotome, after I win this,
I'll have my revenge on you
for defeating me
in the mole game.
Ha ha ha!
I'd like to see you
try and beat me.
O-- OK, Kasumi, when you
turn the wheel to the right,
the car will go right, and
when you turn it to the left,
it will go left?
You understand?
Actually, Kasumi's
over there, Dr. Tofu.
All right.
I think I found the
brake and the gas pedal.
This is easier than I
thought it would be.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I'm going
to win this for Kasumi and Dr.
Tofu, and they can
have the dinner.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
My sweet Akane,
I will do whatever it
takes to let you win.
Hey, Ryoga.
Ryoga, are you here to try and
win that full course dinner
too?
Yeah, and don't get in my way.
Well, I don't know how
to break it to you, pal,
but that big old dinner has
my name written all over it.
You seem pretty
sure of yourself,
but I guess talk is cheap.
We'll see who the better driver
is when they drop the flag.
Well, enough chit chat.
I gotta get myself ready.
It's almost time to start.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Good luck.
Ranma!
Ah!
Who is that girl?
Her name's Rinko, and she's the
best darn go kart driver ever
to run circuit one.
Really?
Yeah, she even
holds the lap record.
She'll race anybody, and so far
nobody's been able to beat her,
including the boys.
Ranma.
This is going to
be interesting.
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER): Ranma
Saotome, you're going down.
ANNOUNCER: It's time to start
the hyper kart grand prix,
ladies and gentlemen.
The rules are simple.
The first to cross the finish
line of this three kilometer
circuit is the winner.
10 seconds to green.
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4,
3, 2, 1-- green!
[engines revving]
Ah!
[crash]
Akane!
ANNOUNCER: There's a crash
on the starting grid!
I-- I guess I must have left
the silly thing in reverse.
ANNOUNCER: Good news.
She looks OK, and she's
about to rejoin the race.
Outta my way, Saotome!
Quit cutting me off!
See you at the finish line!
Pardon me.
I wonder where those two
ever got their license.
ANNOUNCER: The leaders are
coming up to the hairpin!
RINKO (VOICEOVER): If big
red thinks she can beat me,
she's got another thing coming.
Whoa, she's fast!
But there ain't no way
I'm losing to a girl.
See that?
Where'd they come from?
There goes our dinner.
Wait up, girls, 'cause your
big daddy's coming on home!
Who is that creep?
Come on, we better step on it!
Coming through!
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER): And that
goes for anyone in Shampoo way,
because the dinner is
all mine and Ranma.
That's odd.
I wonder why so many cars
have retired from the race.
That gives me a
better chance to win!
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Oh no!
I can't see Akane anywhere!
Hey, buddy.
You're sitting in the pit.
Ah!
I can't believe she's
catching up so fast!
You're mine.
Hey!
Watch it!
ANNOUNCER: Wait a
second, it looks
like we have a new leader!
Ah!
No on has ever beaten me.
I have had enough!
Shifting to overdrive and
coming through, slowpoke!
Ah!
Come on!
You better move it
or lose it, sister!
Ah!
Man, this chick's gotta be
certifiably off her rocker.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Huh?
Shampoo?
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER): The
time has come for Shampoo
to take Akane out for good and
make it look like accident.
[crash]
Shampoo!
Watch where you're going!
What wrong?
You no like to race
against Shampoo?
So, you want to
play rough, do you?
Well two can play that game!
[crash]
Where you learn to drive?
ANNOUNCER: It's shaping
up to be a real dog
fight for first place!
Ah!
I can't believe how
good my car handles.
How about you, Saotome?
What's it like
driving in my fumes?
Dad!
Mr. Saotome!
Get out of the way!
Ah!
Careful, Akane,
I think you might
be driving a bit too fast.
Look out, ladies, 'cause
I'm right behind you!
Yahoo!
It's about time I step on it
and get back into this race.
Banzai!
Ha ha!
That's what you
get for passing me.
Not to finish you off.
Huh?
Make way!
Care to join me for a lovely
full course dinner for two?
There's no way I'm ever
gonna let you win, you freak.
Ah!
I'm getting sick
of being passed.
[crash]
Ah!
Watch it!
You better get of road,
old lady, or Shampoo
be forced to give
you a little help.
Who does she thinks she is?
Calling me an old lady!
ANNOUNCER: They're really
dicing it out for the lead.
Oh, it looks like I'm pretty
far back, so I've gotta hustle.
But I already have the gas pedal
pushed right down to the metal.
Huh?
Hey Mousse, hurry!
Time to fire her up.
Yeah!
Hm?
[crash]
Ah!
Hey!
MOUSSE: No one can stop me now!
Have you lost your mind?
Ah!
Saotome, you've got to
let me win at something.
You can suck on
my tailpipe, Tendo.
Mr. Saotome, I think
you're driving too fast.
Slow down.
Would you get lost
and let me race?
Hey, why don't you mind own
business and quit bothering me!
What is he doing?
Look out!
[crash]
Ah!
What's going on here?
Everyone's gone nuts!
HAPPOSAI: Hey, how about
a little room here?
What are you talking about?
You're in my way!
[crash]
Huh?
OK, that's it.
I've had it playing games
with these two bit smart aleck
punks.
I didn't want to
have to do this,
but now it's time to take
out the heavy artillery.
Happo-fire!
What are you doing?
Unhand me, you cad.
I gotta stop you from
blowing everything up.
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Take your hands off me.
Hey, that's my line!
Huh?
[boom]
[all screaming]
ANNOUNCER: There's been a crash!
AKANE: Ranma, are you all right?
Huh?
Mm.
Oh.
Look what you did to my car.
[growling]
Oh!
[quacking]
KASUMI: Akane, Ranma!
Are you two, OK?
Yeah, we're just fine.
Come on, you two.
Yeah!
Go for it!
ANNOUNCER: And here they come!
K-- Kasumi!
Whoa!
[crash]
ANNOUNCER: They cross the finish
line with the red car winning.
I wonder who it was who
said nice guys finish last,
huh Nabiki?
Way to go, Kasumi.
[chuckling]
Oh, Kasumi.
I'm really glad that you
won the dinner, Kasumi.
And thanks for
inviting all of us.
I just hope you don't mind
that we're eating all of it.
That's all right, Akane.
I'm just happy we're all
together as a family.
Well, thanks.
That's nice of you.
Another chicken leg, Dr. Tofu?
Oh, sure.
[nervous laughter]
Honestly.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): The
girls of Furinkan High
are being attacked by a
mysterious stalker with pig
tails.
Could Ranma be behind it?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
case of the Furinkan stalker.
We'll see you there.