[music playing]
Ranma, I'm attending
training camp in Hokkaido.
I'll be back in three days.
I challenge you to a match
at the usual vacant lot.
Don't be late.
Ryoga.
Yeah right, don't
be late he says.
Meanwhile, it's 10 days later.
Huh?
What?
Is it an earthquake?
What's going on?
From the Depth of
Despair, Part one.
Now where am I?
Trust somebody with your
lousy sense of direction
to come popping
out of the ground.
It's been a long
time, hasn't it, Ranma?
I hope you brought
your crying towel
because you won't stand a chance
against the new move I picked
up.
Well then, this
sounds interesting.
Now let's just see you try it.
What's that all about?
Here I come!
Shishi hokodan.
Huh?
This technique's more
powerful then I imagined.
Lucky shot huh?
But the match is just starting.
Come on.
Fine with me Ranma.
I'll let you be my punching bag.
I don't think so!
I'll get you this time!
Now you're making me mad!
This is incredible.
But it should be even more
powerful then it is now.
OK, I'll try it again.
Shishi hoko-- Hello?
Hi Ryoga.
Haven't seen you for a while.
Ranma?
Ranma wasn't in any
state to be walking.
So I decided to pack him home.
How'd he get like this?
Oh my, what in the
world happened to Ranma?
Ranma was letting
me practice on him.
But I guess I must have gotten
carried away on the little guy.
Really sorry about that Ranma.
Oh my, that was nice of you to
let him practice on you Ranma.
Ryoga, we're not done.
The match isn't-- oh!
Shishi hokodan?
The lion roar shot?
Never heard of that
martial arts move.
Impressive, being
able to defeat Ranma.
It is impressive.
But I think Ranma lost the match
on purpose, for my benefit.
How admirably modest.
Young people these days
are so arrogant they
could use your modesty.
You've shown some
dramatic improvement Ryoga.
If you'll excuse me,
I'd like to take a bath.
Huh?
Hmm.
Finally, I beat Ranma,
for the first time ever.
I beat Ranma for
the first time ever!
Why is Ryoga in
such a good mood?
He was just skipping all
the way down the hall.
Hmm.
Cheer up, will you Ranma?
It wasn't as if
you lost a match.
It was just a
practice after all.
Maybe it was a practice,
but I was serious.
I went after Ryoga.
But I couldn't even
lay a finger on him.
That lion roar shot.
I'm going to find out more
about that new move of his.
Hmm?
Did you want something Ranma?
What's that?
Why the mystery?
It's a scroll.
And beyond that it's
none of your business,
Come on, let me see.
Well then, just tell me where
you learned that lion roar
thing.
Look at you.
You're desperate to find
out about this new move I
picked up.
OK, I'll tell you.
It all started one
day about a week ago.
I was walking deep
in the mountains.
You mean you were lost again.
One night I was camping out
in a cave I'd come across.
Oh no!
A landslide.
All right, there's
one thing to use
and that's my bakusai tenketsu.
Bakusai tenketsu is
martial art technique
used for breaking rock.
This technique strike that
breaking point of the rock
and shatter it.
It didn't work.
The landslide just keeps
barreling down the mountain.
The ground is too brittle It's
useless to break it all up.
Huh?
You'll have to blast it
with something more powerful.
He was a civil engineer
from the town nearby.
The shishi hokodan?
I got the scroll right here.
You want to try it?
I'm sure you'll
be able to do it.
You look like a
talented young man.
I don't believe my eyes.
So it only took you one
night to get the move down?
It seems the engineer
was right about my talent.
Not much of a move if it
only took one night to get.
As it turns out, this move
is unlike my other technique
bakusai tenketsu.
It can be used on
people as well as rocks.
Huh, this is getting good.
You just wait.
And I'll beat that new
lion roar shot of yours.
Oh, I forgot to
tell you one thing.
Huh?
I still haven't
completely mastered it yet.
Huh?
You mean it'll
get more powerful?
Now you've got something
to look forward to Ranma.
I'll master this lion
roar shot move of mine
and defeat you once and for all.
[laughter]
What's that?
The shishi hokodan technique?
You must know about it.
Like the secret of the move.
Of course I know.
But why are you asking about it?
So I can beat Ryoga!
So Ryoga's involved?
All right.
But first you'll
have to practice.
Ready?
Cross both your fists
in front of your chest.
You mean like this?
No, much tighter.
Now you must focus your ki.
There it is.
That concentration
wouldn't stand
a chance against an alley cat.
I'll just give it another go.
Shishi hokodan!
Huh?
I figured as much.
I don't think you're ready
for this move quite yet.
If Ryoga can handle
it then so can I!
You and Ryoga are different.
He has a hidden source to tap.
He has a hidden source?
Don't take this wrong,
but you don't have
what it takes to handle it.
So don't waste your time.
Wait!
Granny!
Just give it up!
If Ryoga can handle this move
but I can't then that would
mean--
[laughter]
Then that would mean
Ryoga's going to beat me!
Help!
We've got a problem.
The school's future is at stake.
I don't need a weakling
like you Ranma.
Huh?
Ryoga, you're the
strong one here.
Defend our school
against this brute.
Coming.
Shishi hokodan.
Oh my a home run.
You are so strong Ryoga.
Oh, I can't believe
my good fortune
in having Ryoga as
my future son-in-law.
Huh?
Hey pop--
Ranma, it's all your fault
for letting Ryoga beat you.
Now all my dreams are
completely shattered.
It's not all that bad.
How miserable Ranma.
Huh?
It seems the only talent you
have is eating free meals.
Ryoga's right.
All you do is sit around
eating up our food every day.
We can't afford to let you
people keep sponging off us
like this anymore.
We don't have much rice left
to last us the rest of the month
either.
And we do have a
son-in-law lined up already.
Leave us alone!
Come on you guys!
Wait a minute!
I've made up my mind.
Now I have the confidence
to propose do Akane.
Ryoga, is it true
you defeated Ranma?
Yes, I finally became
worthy of your love.
And I did it all for you.
Oh, you're so strong and brave.
Ryoga.
Akane!
Hey, what you doing Ryoga?
Huh?
Akane.
Are you OK Ryoga?
Sure, stuff like that
happens all the time.
Well, that was perfect timing
because there's something
I want to talk to you about.
Akane, I wanted to talk
to you about something too.
Yeah?
Um--
Akane, I'd like to ask you--
Ranma seems so
depressed these days.
And I don't know why .
He's been like that since
that practice with you.
Did something happen?
Um, kind of.
Speaking of which Akane,
now that you know I'm
stronger than Ranma, will you--
Ryoga!
Yes?
Hey Ryoga, could you try
to cheer up Ranma for me?
Huh?
You've known Ranma for
longer than anyone else.
And I think that in
a situation like this
there's only one thing
that'll cheer him up,
kind words from a
friend like you.
Ryoga!
I've been looking for you Ryoga!
Let me see that new lion roar
shot of yours one more time.
Leave me alone.
I'm not in the mood for this.
What do you mean,
not in the mood?
Show me!
You're getting on my nerves.
Why you-- shishi hokodan!
That'll teach Ranma for
not leaving me alone.
He seems to have gotten
more powerful than before.
Yes, but just wait till
I fully mastered it.
He's almost mastered
the lion roar shot?
I better act fast.
Ryoga!
Huh?
Hi sweetie.
Hi sweetie?
What you got there?
Secret fighting moves?
Have we met before?
I've been admiring
you from a distance.
I'm your number one fan.
My number one fan?
I've never even noticed you.
No duh, Sherlock.
Ryoga!
I heard that you defeated
that strong guy Ranma Saotome.
Is it true?
Yeah, I guess.
Too cool!
And the secrets of your
power are written in there?
You're pretty clever.
Show me.
Pretty please.
I want to see.
OK, I'll answer your request
and show you my new lion roar
shot.
Uh, I want to see the writings
not the actual maneuver.
Stand back.
I don't want you to get hurt.
But--
Shishi hokodan.
What was that?
That's strange.
It's never happened
to me before.
No big deal.
It happens to everyone.
Shishi hokodan.
huh?
Come on, concentrate harder.
Let's see you do it.
If I screw this up
again she's going
to think I'm a total loser.
Uh-oh.
I did it.
Huh?
This isn't good.
Ranma!
why you-- How dare you trick me?
You'll pay!
No not again!
Sweet potatoes for sale.
They're hot.
Come and get them.
Oh, this can't be happening.
Ryoga's going to beat
me again and there's
nothing I can do to stop him.
Ranma!
What's wrong?
You have Akane here all worried.
Look alive Ranma.
Come on.
Will you people
just leave me alone?
I don't know.
He seems pretty normal.
Yeah, I'd have to agree.
I just did Ryoga's
lion roar shot.
Why did I suddenly get it?
What's with this move?
Shishi--
Why don't you take a
break for awhile Ranma?
Hoko--
Ugh, you haven't slept yet.
Dan!
What am I'm doing wrong?
The only time I could
do it was last night
and that was just
by total fluke.
I don't know how he expects
to be able to concentrate
for so long.
How can I get back that
heavy ki I felt last night?
Not getting
anywhere, huh Ranma?
Huh?
What are you doing here?
Ranma, your days of
defeating me are over.
And I mean forever.
Ranma, does this mean--
did Ryoga beat you?
Yes Ranma lost to me two times.
I didn't lose in
a formal match!
Uh--
Hey, I did it again.
But how?
Oh, wait a second.
Last night my ki felt so
heavy because I didn't
want to lose Ryoga's match.
Heavy ki, heavy ki, heavy ki,
heavy ki, heavy, heavy, heavy--
heavy heart.
Heavy heart, heavy heart.
That means the
shishi hokodan, it
uses the depressive
power of a heavy art
to project a heavy
ki on the opponent.
Doesn't it?
You figured it out!
Now what have I done?
I just gave him the key to the
only move I have to defeat him.
Thanks for your help.
Now the move is mine.
But I still haven't
mastered it myself.
Here goes!
Shishi hokodan!
I'm so depressed!
I got confident and
my ki evaporated.
What a fool.
I'm still not good enough.
Oh!
Yes, it worked.
OK Ranma, you got me.
Shishi hokodan.
Ah!
Shishi hokodan!
Isn't it a little early in the
morning for all this racket?
Ranma and Ryoga, I
understand that young men
want to stay up
all night fighting
to prove their strength.
I know all too well
because it's Saotome
and I used to be just the same.
But on the other hand,
you've destroyed my wall.
Take your fighting
somewhere else.
Ryoga, I'm getting balled
out here because of you.
That wasn't my intention.
But I must say that
you're the one who
started this whole thing.
My ki is so heavy.
Wait.
guys, let's talk huh?
Hmm?
Come on.
Let's talk.
Shishi hokodan!
It's a homer.
I hope he'll be
home for breakfast.
Shishi hokodan!
How foolish, fighting
with the lion roar shot.
Granny.
That move is accompanied
by unhappiness.
Whoever masters the technique
of the lion roar shot
will have his
happiness shattered.
Surely as a lion being
tossed down a cliff
suffers the tragic loss
of its entire kingdom.
Which brings us back to Ranma.
He doesn't seem to
be faring too well.
I've always been
defeated by you Ranma.
Shishi hokodan!
What's worse, I have
no sense of direction!
Shishi hokodan!
To top it off, I don't
have a girlfriend!
Shishi hokodan!
You call that a problem?
Well get a load of the
troubles that I have.
When I'm doused with
water I turn into a girl.
Now that's what I call misery.
You've got to stop Ranma.
Call that misery?
So what if you turn into a girl?
Do have any idea
what happens to me?
I turn into-- I turn
into-- that's what.
Ranma!
You're mine!
Victory is mine.
Proving that when it
comes to misery you
don't stand a chance against me.
Ryoga, you trying to run away?
What?
This match isn't over yet.
I'll fight you
again in one week.
Oh no you don't Ranma.
This has gone on too long.
It's ridiculous!
Just you wait.
I'll prove that I'm the
all time king of misery.
I'll take you on.
I want to see how well you can
do without the secret writings.
Just as I feared, they've
learned the secret.
Now they're consumed with
tapping into their misery
to make the move work.
Let's hope they don't
completely master the move
or they'll live to regret it.
What?
They haven't mastered it?
It's powerful enough as it is.
What'll happen when they
completely master it?
A move where the more miserable
you are the more powerful
it gets.
Can Ranma beat Ryoga's
lion roar shot?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," From
the Depth of Despair part two.
We'll see you there.