[music playing]
ANNOUNCER: The Egg Catcher Man.
-Oh, it's snowing again.
-I almost missed one of them.
Huh?
-Oh, my.
I am so sorry.
-No, no.
You weren't hurt, were you?
-Oh, no.
-Well that's good.
I'd really hate for this
little guy to miss out.
From the size of him, I'd
have to guess 68 grams.
Yes, sir.
He's a good egg all right.
Here.
So what you going
to make with it?
oden, custard, an omelette?
-I, uh--
-Ah, well.
Take care of yourself.
RANMA: Woo-hoo!
It's snowing!
All right!
-You'd think he'd
never seen snow before.
I
-Nah nah!
Gotcha!
-Huh?
Hey--hey!
Kasume!
Are you done shopping?
-Hey, did you get a load
of that guy back there?
-Hey, what's wrong?
-An egg?
-What?
-Huh?
-We're home.
-Hey, so you all
went together then?
-We kind of ran into her.
-Guess I better start dinner.
Huh?
Well I certainly hope
you've built up an appetite.
[humming]
-What the?
NABIKI: An egg?
Yeah, he caught a whole dozen
without even breaking one.
-Oh, wowza.
-Heh, whoopty-freaking-do.
-Fine, then let's
see you do it then.
-Sure thing.
You just watch me.
NABIKI: Here's the thing though.
maybe she was just
being nice, but why
would meeting a stranger
make her so happy?
-That's a good point, Nabiki.
You know, she's always
kind to strangers,
but she's never started singing
to herself after someone
complements the eggs
that she's bought.
-Hmm-- a quiet
snow-covered alley.
A man of too few words who
carries a paper umbrella
then vanishes.
I know exactly who he is.
-Who?
-Yeah?
Who?
-A new boyfriend!
-Oh, please.
-You asked me what I thought.
-But what about the
boyfriend she's already--
-Is it my fault
Doctor Tofu can't
tell Kasumi what
he feels about her.
I mean, it's not
like they're engaged.
AKANE: But-- but Nabiki.
-Hm?
[humming]
-You're kidding.
-It's true.
[music playing]
YASUKICHI (VOICEOVER):
The road not taken.
-All right, I felt that.
Drop a load on me, will ya?
Picking on some poor slob
just trying to catch a break,
and you gotta go
and start something.
ANGRY MAN: Hey, what
the-- go on, boy.
Get him!
-Oh, hey.
Look, a real tough guy, huh?
You-- you gonna try to scare me?
Is that it?
Woof!
[up-tempo music]
-Coming through!
Pardon me.
Coming through.
Hey, you lousy flea bag!
Who do you think you are anyway?
Ain't you supposed to be
man's best friend, huh?
Coming through, excuse me.
Pardon me!
Coming through!
What's a matter?
Too smart for you, huh?
Ah!
[growling]
-Fine.
Well, OK.
If you think you're
tough enough to take me,
pooch, then let's
just get it on.
DR. TOFU: I'll be right there.
Just give me a minute.
I'll undo the door.
What is it?
What's wrong?
-They-- they-- got me, pal.
[whimpering]
-Well, if you'll excuse me,
I'll be going to Dr. Tofu's now.
-What?
What are you going
over there for, Kasumi?
KASUME: Just returning a book.
-If that doesn't prove she
hasn't forgotten Dr. Tofu,
then--
-Uh-huh.
-What?
-Well maybe she's
going over there
to see how she feels about him.
-What?
-Akane, are you
familiar with the saying
it's a woman's prerogative
to change her mind?
-Well yeah, but--
-Excuse me.
Would I lie to you?
-Do you mind if I come along?
-Uh, no.
-Hm.
-Kay.
-Uh, Nabiki, you'd
tell me if there
was anything I needed
to know, wouldn't you?
-Of course I would, Daddy.
SOUN: She what!
Love at first sight?
You can't be serious.
-I'm just reporting
what I saw, OK?
Don't have a--
-I don't care what you saw!
I won't allow it.
Do you hear?
I won't, I won't, I won't!
-Now, now, Tendo.
No need to be upset.
It's just rumor at this point.
-But Saotome, we do know.
My little Kasume is
a complete innocent.
She's completely vulnerable to--
-To mad men.
-Yes.
Yes.
[grunts]
-Oh, woe-- woe is me.
If only her poor
mother were here.
What-- what if he
should actually--
[evil laughter]
YASUKICHI: Your little
girl is coming with me!
[evil laughter]
-I made a mistake.
Help me.
-Just a minute.
Why not take this one instead!
RANMA: Help!
I'm so sorry about that, son.
-Why don't I believe you?
-Say, boy.
Didn't Kasume say it
was a chance encounter?
-He's not from
around here, I guess.
-Then I suppose we're worrying
for nothing, aren't we?
After all there's a good chance
she'll never see him again.
-Maybe she will.
Maybe she won't.
-Akane?
Do you remember
the hatchery that
used to be right over here?
-Huh?
-Their eggs were always fresh.
-Kasume.
-Hm?
-Tell me what kind
of guy do you like?
-Me?
Well, weird ones, I guess.
-Hm?
-It's snowing again.
Let's hurry home.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Weird ones, huh?
Dr. Tofu is pretty
weird, but again,
compared to that
egg-catcher guy.
-You coming or what?
-Oh, uh-- uh-huh!
-Look, I figure two
or three days from now
and you'll be fine.
-Thanks, doc.
I guess I owe you my life.
-Actually, it was just
a slight dislocation.
-You mean that was all?
-Now exactly who was it you
said did this to you again?
Do you remember?
[stuttering]
-I guess I'll be off then.
-Say, unless I missed my guess,
you're from out of town, right?
So why not stay here
tonight and leave tomorrow?
Some hot-egg brandy
will warm you right up.
-I-- I'm sure I don't
deserve such kindness.
-Now, now.
AKANE: Can we come in?
-Hm?
-Uh, company, Doc.
-Well, hello there.
-Akane!
What a pleasure
to see you again.
Have a seat.
KASUME: May I come in?
-Huh?
-K-K-Kasume?
-Here, Dr. tofu.
And thank you so much.
I must say, I really
enjoyed it quite a bit.
-No problem.
How are you?
I'm fine, thanks.
-Hello.
-So then, I guess we meet again.
-Oh, so you're the--
-My name is Yasukichi.
Samurai egg-catcher at large.
At your service.
-For real?
-So have you known
Dr. Tofu long?
-Just met him tonight actually
in his medical capacity.
Looks like I'll be
spending the night here.
-I see.
-He's quite a guy.
-Thank you again.
See you soon.
Goodnight!
-Don't go!
-Excuse me?
-Should he, uh,
be left like this?
Maybe we should stay
with him for awhile.
-Buh-bye!
See you later.
-Oh, well he's always
like that with Kasume.
Don't you worry.
-Oh, yeah?
-Well, I'm off.
-Wait, wait, wait.
There's just one more thing.
Please take this, OK?
-Thank you.
We will.
Shall we?
-OK.
-Be careful.
-We will.
[grunts]
-Tell me.
Are you a man or aren't you?
Hey, if you like her,
you better tell her.
It's a crime to do otherwise.
I know, pal.
I know.
It's hard being a guy.
-Good morning.
I made some-- where'd he go?
Hm-- dear Dr. Tofu, sometimes
it's what a man doesn't say.
Leave everything to me.
You won't regret it.
Signed, your friend.
What the--
SAOTOME: Ready, boy?
And a one, and a two.
Oh.
-Ha, see?
I told you I could
do it, didn't I?
-Frankly, boy,
it's the least I'd
expect from a practitioner of
anything goes martial arts.
-Catch!
-All right now, son.
If anything should
happen to me, will you
promise to look after things?
-You going somewhere?
[chuckling]
YASUKICHI: Anyone home?
-What-- what are you--
-I'm really sorry.
But I just had to come.
Is Kasume here?
-Well, yeah.
But she, uh--
-Now he won't get
her without a fight.
-Now, now, Tendo.
Let's calm down, shall we?
We don't even know what he's--
-And who's going
to pay the piper
if he is here to take her?
Eh, Saotome?
-Hey, boy.
Think you could
take him in a fight?
-Not a chance.
-First off, I must
sincerely apologize
for showing up
without prior notice.
-Dad, at least hear him out.
-Yeah, yeah.
Get to the point.
What do you want.
-Yes, sir.
[clears throat]
-As you may know, I'm only
a wandering egg-catcher--
-You can't have Kasume,
and that's that.
-Huh?
-Per-- perhaps we could
discuss this first.
-Hm.
House fly.
Strange.
One doesn't normally see
them this time of year.
-Would you like some?
YASUKICHI (VOICEOVER): Ah, nuts.
I had a big speech prepared,
but now I forgot it.
-K-K-Kasume?
I, uh--
-Son, let me tell you
something about my Kasume here.
She's touched in the head,
plus she's selfish to boot.
It's practically
guaranteed she'll
make any man foolish enough
to marry her miserable.
-Why, Father!
-Sir, I'm sorry, but I
must say you're wrong.
She'd make a fine bride.
She certainly knows
her eggs for one thing.
-That's it!
-Huh?
-Again?
-Yeah, so what about it, Kasume?
-Yesterday when I went
out to do some shopping,
I thought to myself that
I'd make an omelette.
But then--
-B-- but that's when you
ran into him, isn't it?
-That's right.
Here knew somehow
just by looking
at the egg I bought which
dish would suit it best.
And it did.
-And that's why you made oden.
-Exactly.
I'd have made it
yesterday, but I
didn't have all the
ingredients I needed.
-I thought we were
short on groceries.
-And that's why I decided
to make this dish in order
that things be at their
most fresh and tasty.
AKANE: But why?
-Oh, and you know, it's always
easier to make a day's dinner
when you have a
clear menu in mind.
-I don't suppose that's
why you were so happy?
-Oh, dear.
Was it that obvious?
-Honestly.
YASUKICHI (VOICEOVER):
I missed something.
-Well, since you're
here, you might as well
tell Kasume what
you came to say.
-Oh, well-- that is--
I-- uh-- oh, yeah!
Oden!
Kasume, if it's not
too much trouble,
do you think you could
bring out some of that oden
over to Dr. Tofu?
-You came all the
way here for that?
-Well, you know,
I kind of thought
that being a single guy and
all, Dr. Tofu would, you know,
appreciate some home cooking.
I know I would.
I mean it's kind of hard not
having a wife and-- well--
-Don't I know it.
My sentiments exactly.
-You know what I mean?
-I know exactly what you mean.
Which is why you
should spend the night.
So we can talk it over.
-Thanks a lot for the new book.
Careful with the hot dish.
-I-- I will.
-Way to go, Doc.
-Excuse me, but I've got to ask.
You didn't really
come over for--
-Really?
I don't think that
hardly matters, does it?
Good deeds speak for
themselves, don't they?
If Kasume and the Doc needed
a little push, what of it?
Am I taking credit?
No.
Of course not.
In fact--
-Gee, you could've fooled me.
[humming]
-Thank you for all
your hospitality.
-Listen, next time
you're in the area,
we'll expect you to come back.
-Just a moment.
-What?
-Before you go, you
mustn't forget this.
-Oh, I-- Kasume,
take care of the doc.
-Of course.
-Goodbye.
RANMA: Not so fast.
Souvenir!
One to grow on.
-Well, if that's
it, I'll be off.
-Oof, caught a
whole baker's dozen.
-I didn't spend my entire
life around eggs for nothing.
-What a freak.
-Hey, Kasume.
Is something wrong?
-It's him.
It's got to be.
From back then.
[chickens crowing]
-You see, now this here
is a very good egg.
Hey, back off, mutt!
I ain't afraid of you!
YASUKICHI'S MOTHER: Come
on, we've got to go.
-I really wish you
didn't have to go,
but here's a present you
can have from my grandma.
-Hey, that's really nice.
You see, I really like--
YASUKICHI'S MOTHER:
We're leaving!
-I, uh-- Goodbye!
-So, is it him?
The one you remember?
-He's, um--
AKANE: Well, is he?
Well?
[music playing]
NARRATOR: Can Kuno
really grant wishes?
I can see why he'd want
one, but isn't a kiss
too high of price even for you?
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
"Ranma and Kuno's First Kiss."
We'll see you there!