[music playing]
-Blow, wind!
To Be Young is to Go Gung-ho.
-Aloha, everybody.
And once again, me have very
exciting news for you all.
[sighs]
-You just watch it be another
one of those dumb rules of his.
-Well actually,
Ranma, I hear it's
supposed to be some
kind of new teacher.
-Oh, so you mean in other
words, the big loser's
calling in the
reinforcements on us.
Is that the deal?
-Shut up!
Big exciting news is that
starting today, Furinkan High
School has new teacher.
Boys and girls,
little cake is all.
Me now introduce,
Higuma Torajirou!
-Higuma Torajirou?
Isn't that Japanese for bear?
Give me a break.
-Did you hear, the word's that
wherever this Higuma transfers,
the students end
up having a riot.
-Well that could be
good or bad, I guess.
-Anything to wake 'em up, right?
-You said it.
-Of course unless
he come soon, me
have to find new, new teacher.
What?
[screams]
-What does youth mean to you?
-That's closer, closer, clos--
-I was born with the
name Higuma Torajirou,
but I'd rather
you call me coach.
-What's he take us for?
-Like we'd really
fall for his dumb act.
-Well I figure, any enemy of the
principal, is no enemy of mine.
-I don't think so.
No fair.
Do over.
Time out.
-Are ya with me?
-Yeah!
-One, two, one, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two.
-He plenty bad coach.
Why he go and want to
do that to headmaster.
Teaching in the island if
not for the Big Kahuna.
Bad coach.
-OK, what does
youth mean to you?
It comes but once in your life.
You must make the most
of each and every moment.
Romance, friendship, in
sports, scholarship, reading,
amateur theatrics,
what is not important?
[sighs]
Whatever it is that moves
you to passion, go for it!
Akane Tendo, what does
youth mean to you?
-I guess I'd have
to say martial arts.
[laughs]
-That's enough!
Is it funny to you that a
girl believes in something?
To a Japanese, fitting
in is everything.
But you must never
let peer pressure
get in the way of
any of your dreams.
That my friends is youth.
And that's why I salute
you, Akane Tendo,
for having a dream.
-Thanks.
-Ukyo Kuonji?
-Sir!
-What warms your heart?
Please, tell the class.
-Hmm.
One youth special, ready to go.
-Yes!
Excellent.
May such feelings burn
always to keep you warm.
-Oh, great.
Now she's falling for it too.
-Ranma Saotome, what
feelings burn in your heart?
-Gee, I don't know,
guess I'd have
to say anything
goes martial arts.
-No, no, no!
That's not youth
I hear speaking.
Say it with feeling.
I'll ask again, Ranma
Saotome, the feelings that
burn in your heart,
what are they?
-I told ya.
Anything goes, school
of martial arts.
Yada, yada.
-No, no, no!
No!
Try saying it like this.
I, Ranma Saotome, believe
in the anything goes school
with all my heart and soul.
Please, have that ready
for tomorrow morning.
-Uh, OK.
[laughing]
-Cool, huh?
-Are we enjoying our youth?
-Uh, yeah?
-No riots yet, I guess.
-Yeah, it won't
be the first time
the headmaster's misjudged.
-His students seem to like him.
Guess I can't blame him for
wanting to be his friend.
-The kids can use
someone like him around.
-I'm guessing no
girlfriends, right?
-What makes you say that?
-Boys, boys, there's
nothing to be ashamed about.
-But, what if we--
-Yeah, what if we get dumped?
-All right.
What is youth if
not taking chances?
How can you learn from
mistakes unless you make them?
So you get dumped?
Learn from it.
Study it.
Next time, do better.
-We'll try it, some day.
-Pardon?
Don't you someday me!
The time to act
is now, not later.
So this girl that you
like, tell me her name.
Don't you trust me boys?
After all, I suppose
I can't blame you.
-That's not it.
-It's not?
Then you do trust me.
The key is confidence,
boys, remember that.
You just leave the rest to me.
There's nothing to
be ashamed about, OK?
-OK.
-Excellent, let's run.
-Boy, what a great teacher.
-If you say so.
-So you gonna practice?
-I, uh, what?
-You know, I believe, et cetera.
-Sure.
-Fine, don't practice.
But don't blame me though
when you get detention.
-Failure of youth.
-Hmm, well I'll be.
Perhaps there hope for him yet.
-I, Ranma Saotome,
love the anything
goes school heart and soul!
-Encore.
Encore, my boy.
-Enough of that.
-OK, everyone, listen up.
Hiroshi and Daisuke have an
important declaration to make.
-You wouldn't?
-In front of everyone?
-Come on, no
embarrassment, remember?
Stand up for your dreams.
-All right.
Guess this means
I'm off the hook.
-Well, let's have it boys.
-But, I--
-Does it have to be now?
-Come now, what is it that's
so hard about saying, Akane,
I love you?
-What?
-But we never--
Akane, I'm sorry.
We never meant--
-You see.
That wasn't so bad.
Now Akane are you ready
to give them an answer?
-Are you stupid or what?
-You're absolutely right.
I am stupid.
However, you're even stupider.
-Huh?
I what--
-Give your teacher credit
for doing his homework, huh?
You and Akane Tendo are engaged
to be married, are you not?
-So what's that
got to do anything?
-Everything, because
you stubbornly
refuse to make your feelings
for your fiancee known,
those two boys are in agony.
-You make us sound like--
-Like we're losers.
-Allow me to put in plain.
You, Akane, I love!
While you, Saotome, I detest.
Shoo, I stay.
Out of the way.
-Take it out on me if you must.
Young emotions are
strong, but don't
make the mistake of thinking
that just because your thwarted
in your goals now, that you
won't someday achieve them.
Because you will,
you will, I promise.
Strong emotions in the
young are a sign health.
And yet no emotion is so
strong that a good hard run
can't put it all right.
What say you?
Will you run?
-Sadly, I regret
that I must decline.
-Hmm, another time, perhaps.
It's decided.
A parent teacher
conference it is then.
May I have your
attention please.
I'd like to share with you
an important announcement.
-Gee, I can hardly
wait to hear it.
-Ranma Saotome, because
you have refused
to be honest with your feelings,
many of your fellow students,
including your
fiancee, Akane Tendo,
have been made to suffer.
Truly, the situation
is regrettable.
-I'll kill him!
-Are you listening,
Ranma Saotome?
Until you can--
-Shut up already, will ya?
It's got nothing to do with you.
-You're absolutely right.
It doesn't.
-Then why are you--
-It has to do with
your youth, my boy.
Your youth.
Seize the day, lad, carpe diem.
-Ah, man, what
planet are you from?
-What have I done?
You're right, it has
nothing to do with me.
I just don't care.
These are the things
I hear every day.
Not that I'm blaming you
or your fellow students.
In fact, if I had
to blame anyone,
it would be we, faculty.
I Coach Higuma, do hereby
affirm my most solemn vow.
Away with the
textbooks, what meaning
have they to the
healthy and active body?
-Like theme of big
island sportsman who
take the fish out of net only
to catch later on the hook,
Big Kahuna see his plan
for ungrateful [inaudible]
finally start to reel
them students in.
-One, two, one, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two, one, two,
one--
-Not good enough.
Now what do you want from me?
-Ask not what I want from you
but what you want from me.
Trust your youthful
feelings, let your anger go.
-My dear sir, I assure that
that is the least of my worries.
-No excuses.
Don't you see?
It's because we
bottle up our feelings
that we're so miserable.
-Welcome to Ucha--
-Uyko?
-You really came.
I thought the conference
thing was just a joke.
-Poor thing.
I can't believe you're being
forced to work like this.
-Nobody forces
me, I own my own--
-Don't shield them.
What sort of a parent
allows a daughter
to put herself through high
school by cooking okonomiyaki.
Your father died at an early
age and your stepmother,
not thinking you're good enough
for her three daughters, sent
you to Tokyo to the slave
away in some hell hole--
-Whoa, whoa, slow down.
You don't understand.
-Don't speak!
I know the pain you're
going through all too well.
I just want you to
know that no matter
what, you can count on me.
I'm here for you.
-Thank you, please come again.
Well, there goes this
afternoon's profits.
-Poor girl, is all life is?
Profits?
Would it help if I
spoke to your guardian?
-Welcome to-- huh?
Hey, what do you
know, there he is now.
-He's here?
Where?
Mr. Kuonji, I'm Coach Higuma
from Ukyo's school. [laughing]
Sir, I don't presume to tell
you how to raise your ward.
But, might it be best if
you hired someone else
to do the cooking?
Don't play dumb.
Sir, if you promise
to let her go free,
I swear I'll do anything
you ask, anything.
-Well there sure ain't
no flies on that panda.
-Going somewhere?
-I was just, uh--
-Uh huh.
More like you were sneaking away
before the coach comes over.
-Do you blame me?
Can you give me a reason
why I should stay?
-Scaredy cat.
-What?
-I shouldn't have to say
it but where does leave me
if you take off?
-Hey, you're the one who
thinks he's so great, remember?
-We're talking
about you, not me.
-Well then I say that you should
be the one to talk to him,
Akane, seeing as how you're
such great pals and all.
-You're such a jerk!
-Never said I wasn't.
See ya.
-Ranma, wait up.
-Oh, man.
-It's coach Higuma.
I know how you two must feel.
Still, you mustn't.
You mustn't elope.
-Elope?
-But we're not--
-Don't explain.
I must confess, even I
was unaware of how far
your feelings have come.
If only I'd listened
more carefully
to what you were telling me.
Forgive me.
However, elopement
is not the answer.
Perhaps if I were to come
inside and talk to your parents?
Sir, please!
I don't presume to tell you
what's best for your children,
but might you allow
young Ranma and Akane
to go on with the marriage?
-What?
-Yes, I realize they're young.
Yes, I realize that
up until this moment,
you've probably never given
a thought to your daughter
getting married someday.
-Actually, uh, we, uh--
-Sir, I know.
I'm not so old myself
that I've forgotten
what it's like to be young.
Please sir, please
allow them to marry.
-That's right, daddy, why not?
-Nabiki!
Say something.
-Who me?
-So that's all it is. [laughing]
Why didn't you say so earlier?
-Dad?
-Sir, I wish I could
be so light hearted.
I'm just worried for
their future, that's all.
They are such good kids.
-Here you go.
So father, what did I miss?
-I'm not sure we would.
-I'm not saying
it has to be now.
They're young, they've
still got plenty of time.
I know you're opposed to their
marriage, but can't you just--
-But I'm telling-- I--
-Think it over.
That's all I ask you.
-But, I--
-Think, that's all I ask.
-I, just--
-I'm afraid that you
have lost me, daddy.
-Don't argue with your father.
-Akane's all grown
up now, father.
Might she be allowed to
make up our own mind?
-I know that you're
right, but still--
-Just say yes, daddy,
and get it over with.
-Very well then.
I consent.
-You do?
You hear that kids,
your father just
gave his OK to the marriage.
Aren't you happy?
With this, my work here at
Furinkan high school is over.
-What?
-So you're going to go
bother someone else?
-Wherever there's a Japanese
high school student in distress
I'll be there.
In the East, I'll be
running with those
who suffered the pangs
of unrequited love.
In the West, I'll be running
with those studying hard
to get into a good college.
In the South, I'll
be running with those
who've taken to vandalism.
Most of all, in
the North, I'll be
running with those who know
the heartbreak of psoriasis.
-That sounds like
a lot of running.
-What is youth, if not to run?
-OK, students, listen up.
Today me have a very,
very news for you all.
Sadly, new teacher
just tell me he no
when be teaching here
at Furinkan no more.
Now, Big Kahuna present to you,
one last time, Coach Higuma!
-Students, faculty-- I
haven't been here long,
but I feel we've come
to know each other well.
I know you'll
continue the fight.
Remember, youth comes but once.
If you stop running,
you stop living.
And so for that reason
I propose to you
a final faculty
student rugby game!
Let's here it for the
spirit of Furinkan!
-Aloha!
-Here goes.
-Maybe Big Kahuna get self
caught in own fish net
this time.
-Farewell, youthful students!
-Goodbye!
-I give you, youth!
-Oh, no.
[music playing]
-Come on!
You don't really want to
study under my dad, do you?
I'd think twice If I were you.
You may live to regret it.
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
a formidable new disciple
appears.
We'll see ya there.