[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): And the
Challenger is-- a Girl?
-I wonder where I am now.
Hm?
-That's the problem with
you kids these days.
No imagination.
Lucky for you, card games
got something even better.
You just watch.
Attack!
Super-duper mid-air
lightning strike!
Attack!
Ultra high-speed whirlwind!
[fawning]
[laughing]
-Wow.
[gasping]
KIDS: Hey, come back!
Come back here!
RED-FACED GUY: You there!
Are you a martial
artist or what?
-Hm?
WHITE-FACED GUY:
All right, kids.
Let the Lord of Marbles
show you how it's done.
Bet you never saw a
marble do this before.
Here it goes!
Attack super spinner juggernaut!
-Wow.
KIDS: Whoa!
-Uh-oh, it's almost time
for "Pokemon" to come on.
Come on, guys.
We gotta go!
-Yeah.
I heard It was a good episode.
-Come on!
-W-- wait!
-Ah, nuts.
A show about a rat?
What's this world coming to?
-And if it's not cartoons,
it's ultra-violent video games.
Whatever happened to the
way kids used to play?
VOICEOVER: Man, you're dead!
VOICEOVER: And then
Bluebeard said--
VOICEOVER: I want a jawbreaker.
VOICEOVER: Olly olly oxen free!
[laughing]
-Nope, it sure aint' the
Japan I used to know.
Why, when I was a boy, my
Dad and me-- we used to.
-You don't think crying's
going to solve anything, do ya?
-Huh?
You made it!
WHITE-FACED GUY: You made it.
-Never fear.
Ultraman's here!
Seriously, though.
I'm telling you.
It's going to be OK.
-It is?
-Huh?
Hey, you there!
-Me?
-From the way you've
been watching us,
I'm guessing you're a
martial artist yourself.
-Anything Goes School of
Martial Arts, Ranma Saotome.
-Anything goes, huh?
Sounds impressive.
Care to test your skills?
What do you say, boys?
-But I-- fine.
If it's a fight you
want, you got it.
[music playing]
AKANE: I'm home!
Sorry I'm late.
I was-- where'd everyone go?
Hop, skip, jump!
[panda murmuring]
-Huh?
-Mr. Saotome, are you--
I mean, aren't you
going to introduce me to
your little friend here?
-Well there was nobody
home, so I asked the Panda
if he'd play with me.
Hey, are you the one
who owns this dojo?
-No.
My dad owns it, but
he's not home right now.
My name's Akane
Tendo, his daughter.
-Good.
You'll work out perfectly then.
I want to challenge
you for your dojo.
-You what?
[panda murmuring]
I don't know, Mr. Saotome.
Maybe we'd better not.
I know you want to
humor her, but--
-Just think of it as a chance
to test your skills, Akane.
At least that's what I'd do.
AKANE: Why don't you then?
GENMA: Ma-- ma-- me?
Oh, no.
I-- I--
-I know I look little,
but I'm real strong.
I promise.
-Of course you are,
but wouldn't it
be more fun to play video games?
If you don't like that, we
could watch "Pokemon" or--
-You're afraid that you're
going to lose to me, aren't you?
-OK, but don't you
cry if you get hurt.
Well, I'm ready
whenever you are.
-My martial arts style
is 12 generations.
-That many?
But that would mean that
she's-- Akane, look out!
My name is Temari Kaminarimon.
I'm from the Good Old Days
School of Martial Arts.
Attack!
Cats cradle a hundred thread!
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
What did she--
-Since when is cat's cradle a--
-Hi-ya!
-I've been trapped
by her threads.
-London bridge is falling down,
falling down, falling down.
London bridge is falling
down, my fair lady.
Take the key and lock her
up, lock her up, lock her up.
Take the key and lock
her up, my fair lady.
Tokyo Tower's falling down,
falling down, falling down.
Tokyo Tower's falling
down, my fair lady.
Hide the key at Mount Fuji,
Mount Fuji, Mount Fuji.
Hide the key at Mount
Fuji, m fair lady.
-Watch out!
She's trying to--
-Good Old Days School of
Martial Arts final attack!
Fire flower bean bag
endless downpour!
[screaming]
-The time of day, it's
mostly just Akane.
-Look to yourself,
Ranma Saotome.
Even as we speak, your dojo is--
-I'm almost there.
Hang on.
Huh?
-Oh, Akane!
How can this have
happened to you?
[sobbing]
-But, Father, I've
already told you.
It's mostly just shock.
SOUN: I only stepped out for a
moment, and then-- at the dojo!
Ranma.
-I saw her.
That girl that did this to you.
-Was she-- terrible?
-She must have been
to have done this.
[groans]
-She's a member of some
so-called Good Old Days Martial
Arts, wasn't she?
-Yeah, but how did you--
-I ran into some friends
of hers on the way home
who fought me in the same style.
[gasping]
-That's exactly what I said.
What the heck kind
of style is it?
-Hmm, if I remember my history--
during Japan's Edo period,
only samurais were
allowed to carry swords.
Lacking other weapons,
those resourceful,
if short-tempered
residents of downtown,
turned every day toys into
the deadliest of object.
Even famed swordsman,
Miyamoto Musashi
himself has said to
have shopped elsewhere.
Still, if you'd
asked me earlier,
I would have told you their
particular school was extinct.
Speaking of which, you
did win, didn't you?
-Oh, me?
Of course I did.
Yeah, no prob.
-There, you see, Saotome.
No prob.
That's our Tendo dojo
next in line for you.
After you avenge Akane, you
can get our dojo sign back.
-Our what?
-Jeez, Daddy.
Do it yourself, OK?
-Habiki's right, Father.
Even you can beat a little girl.
SOUN: But, but, why do
I-- listen, you two.
Ranma is Akane's fiance.
Let him do it.
It's his job.
-Well that's true.
I suppose I gotta--
-Ugh.
Look, just stay out of this, OK?
-Akane.
-I'm the one who--
who lost, all right?
So I'll be the one who's
going to handle it.
Understand?
-But, Akane, it's too soon.
-Yeah, but what about-- Akane?
-Hey, don't sweat it.
I said I'd do it, didn't I?
-Don't touch me!
-Fine.
Suit yourself.
-Yes, sadly, once
her mind is made up,
there's no stopping her.
It's just how she is.
Speaking of which,
Saotome, why was it
Akane who fought and not you?
[panda murmuring]
SOUN: Saotome, you!
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): If
they picked on Akane,
they made their last
mistake, those jerks.
It's one thing to do it to me.
But when they hurt her,
they're going to be sorry.
-Huh?
-And where do you
think you're going?
-To get that mystery
gang who hurt Akane
at the dojo, of course.
Where else?
-So you know about it, huh?
How'd you find out?
Where are they?
-I have no idea.
How am I going to find them?
-You should have told us
Temari was going to help out,
that's all.
If you don't tell us
these things, who will?
-The important thing's
that she did help.
We ought be thankful.
-How's your bathwater?
Not too hot?
ULTRAMAN: Ha!
You kidding?
If I can take this much,
they'd run me out of Tokyo.
Bring it on.
-That's our leader!
-The one and only.
Temari, here!
Throw this on.
-OK.
-Huh?
RED-FACED GUY: Who's there?
-We've come to get the
sign to our dojo back.
-I remember you two.
You're the strong one.
The other's the wimp.
-Come on.
Don't tell me those
guys beat you.
-I got a little careless, OK?
But that was then.
Like I said, I want that sign.
You're welcome to
stop me if you can.
-We beat you once.
-We can beat you again.
[growling]
-Back up, man.
-Hey!
Get out of my way, you jerk!
-Akane wouldn't like it
and you know it, Ryoga.
You know what I'm here for.
-You're here for
that girl's sake.
She wants a rematch with Temari,
and you're here to arrange it.
Am I right?
-Basically, yeah.
So can I take this to mean
you're up for it then?
-But Akane's not
in any shape to--
-Will it be fun
like it was before?
-Huh?
-Then it's settled.
Temari's old style martial
arts versus whatever
it is that girl of
yours practices.
Time and place of our choosing.
We'll let you know the details.
-Where are you going?
-Akane needs time to prepare!
-Hey, you hear me?
-Don't we get a vote?
[music playing]
[akane screaming]
-So what makes you think
this time will be different?
Akane's still recovering.
We can't expect her to fight.
-Where's we come from?
You're the one who started it.
-I started it?
You're the one who
asked for the rematch.
[screaming]
-Why do I bother?
I'm not going to win.
Might as well give up.
-Oh, Akane.
-Kasume?
-I wish I'd known
about this earlier.
Then I would have been
able to help you out.
Take these.
You don't remember?
They were Mother's
when she was little.
She used to sing us a little
song while catching them.
Remember how she
changed the lyrics?
London bridge is falling down,
falling down, falling down.
London bridge is falling
down, my fair lady.
Take the key and lock her
up, lock her up, lock her up.
Take the key and lock
her up, my fair lady.
[gasping]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I was so
surprised that I didn't notice.
It has to do with the
speed of the hands.
KASUME (SINGING): Falling
down, my fair lady.
Hide the key at Mount Fuji,
Mount Fuji, Mount Fuji.
Hide the key at Mount
Fuji, my fair lady.
Osaka Castle's falling down,
falling down, falling down.
Osaka Castle's falling
down, my fair lady.
[ball bouncing]
TEMARI: They're here.
[giggles]
-Hmm, we were hoping you'd show.
As agreed, if you
can defeat Temari,
we'll return your dojo sign.
If she defeats you, however,
you admit to your inferiority
by letting us keep it.
-Ryoga, I know you
want to help Akane,
but you got to stay out of it.
Understand?
-I know that.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Actually, it's
them that I'm worried about.
GENMA: Go, go, Akane!
Go, go, Akane!
BOTH: Go, go, Temari!
Go, go, Temari!
-Begin!
-Are you ready?
Hi-ya!
[music playing]
-I was expecting that!
So much for your
cat's cradle attack.
[groaning]
-How brilliant!
Were you watching that, Ranma?
-It's not over yet, though!
-Take this!
Old Days Martial Arts
special attack-- iron top!
[screaming]
-This time I won't miss.
I was expecting this too!
-Isn't she the greatest?
-Oh, no.
Now what?
-London bridge is falling down,
falling down, falling down.
London bridge is falling
down, my fair lady.
-Don't take your eyes off!
-Take the key and lock her
up, lock her up, lock her up.
Take the key and lock
her up, my fair lady.
Tokyo Tower's falling
down, falling down--
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Now that I know
what I'm looking
for, it's easier.
By varying her
speed, she creates
the illusion of a solid wall.
If I could stop staring long
enough for a pattern to emerge,
maybe I can--
-Now!
-Old Days School of
Martial Arts final attack.
Fire flower bean bag
endless downpour!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Not
yet, not yet, not yet.
Now!
I see them!
-I did it!
I deflected them.
-Huh?
-Are you all right?
[sobbing]
-I'm so sorry.
All I wanted was--
I never meant to--
-Now that's the daughter
I know and love.
-Are you mad at me
for losing, Grandpa?
-Grandpa?
-You're related?
-We certainly are.
I'm Temari's grandfather,
Kumajiro Kaminarimon.
Keeping alive our distinctly
old fashioned martial arts style
has been my lifelong work.
-It's our past.
We don't want to forget it.
-Because there's so few
of us left as it is.
-Now were the masks
really necessary?
-We're not mad.
We just want to know.
-To you, we must
seem like old fools
who think time
should stand still.
But really, all
we've ever wanted
was to share with the kids of
today a part of our own youth
that we feel is worth keeping.
Maybe it's time
we let it die out.
-That's not true!
-Don't say that!
-And as for the masks,
we knew the kids
would laugh at us without them.
Speaking of kids,
I realize now you
deserve your own life, Temari.
-But I don't--
-If you think we don't
need you, you're wrong.
We shouldn't ever
forget the past.
Right, Saotome?
-Right as usual, Tendo.
-You know, there's
always a place
for martial artists
in the world.
Besides you're like
a living treasure.
-Yeah, and if he's a
living treasure, that
makes you the next generation.
-I am?
-You have all been so kind.
You give me faith in the future.
Not just for Temari, but
for everyone's children.
-I'm going to train hard and
be in the Tokyo Olympics.
-What?
-Now wait a second.
I thought that the next
time was in Australia.
-If there's any justice in this
world, it'll be held in Tokyo.
Why hold it anywhere else?
-OK, now listen.
Local pride is one thing,
but I gotta draw the line.
[interposing voices]
[laughing]
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
An all expense
paid trip to any hot
springs resort in the world?
Ranma, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Hot Springs Battle Royale.
We'll see you there.