[theme music]
-Hi-ya!
-Ha!
-Martial arts
calligraphy final attack!
The mark of the god!
[straining]
-It's, it's--
-Well, are you going
to just stand there,
or are you going to attack me?
-Oh, yeah?
[yells]
How'd you do that?
[squeals]
-P-chan!
Huh?
Hm.
Where'd those marks come from?
[squealing]
NARRATOR: Close call--
P-chan's secret.
[grunts while whacking post]
-Ah!
[exhales]
[grunts]
[footsteps]
Huh?
-So, um, uh, Ranma?
-Uh!
-Why won't you answer me?
-Why should I?
-OK, let me try again.
What do you know about
P-chan and Ryoga?
You're hiding
something, aren't you?
-Cut it out, will ya?
-Well, tell me what
you're hiding and I will!
Ooh!
[grunting]
[pop]
Ranma, I'm serious!
-So am I.
-(THINKING) Has she realized
that, that P-chan and I are--
-Those tattoos, I'm sure
of it-- it's the same.
It's the same person,
I'm sure of it, right?
The same person who
drew both tattoos.
-Hm?
-Maybe-- huh?
-You've said too much,
Akane-- way more than enough.
I should've known that
you'd see right through me.
-Hm?
-Here.
Obviously I'm the
one who drew them.
Humph.
-(THINKING) All
right, he did it!
-(THINKING) Ha, am I the
man, or am I the man?
He owes me big
time for this one.
-The other drawing
was drawn much better.
-It what?
-Hey, thanks for nothing!
-Ry, Ryoga?
[groaning]
-Akane?
-(THINKING) Face it, it's just
a matter of time before my shame
is exposed.
Farewell all.
-What?
-Ryoga!
-Wait!
Wait!
What's wrong with him?
Ranma, what'd you
do to-- uh, Ranma?
-Man, stupid Ryoga.
-So this is it.
-Crying and stuff.
Jerk.
Boy, I gotta think of something.
If he's got the mark,
then he can't be beat.
And if he can't be beat,
I can't win, no matter
what kind of plan
I come up with.
My only hope is some
kind of opening.
Hey, that's it!
There's just got to be
an opening somewhere.
And if there's an
opening, I'm going
to be the one that finds it.
-Goodbye, my sweet Akane.
I swear I'll never
forget you-- not ever.
-Hm.
[birds chirping]
-Well, time to make camp.
So tired.
I don't know exactly
where I am, but I
guess I can rest, for a while.
[grunting]
-Huh?
[grunting][PAINFUL YELP
Don't tell me!
I haven't even left town yet!
Oh, of all the times
for me to get lost!
-I knew he wouldn't get far.
Uh!
Here goes!
-Huh?
-Ah!
Return it, mister!
-Uh!
-Score one for the good guys!
[painful yelp]
[thud]
-Hey!
Ah!
[whimpering]
-Are you hurt?
-What's this world coming to?
[gasps]
-Ah!
When a girl can't even practice
volleyball in a vacant lot?
-Uh, I'm, uh, I'm sorry.
I, I couldn't help it.
My, my body is just--
[crying]
-Oh, never mind.
-(THINKING) He doesn't
even know it's me.
OK, sucker.
Time to drop the elbow!
Hi-ya!
[painful yelp]
[gasps]
[screams]
-What did I just do to that,
that cute volleyball girl?
[screaming]
[thud]
[groaning]
Hey!
Where'd you run off to anyway?
[whack]
Ah!
Ow!
[splashing]
[angry squeal]
[breathing heavily]
-There's something
going on here!
First Ryoga leaves,
next P-chan disappears.
[breathing heavily]
Which leads me to
believe that maybe-- huh?
P-chan!
[terrified squeals]
[laughs]
Oh, thank goodness
that I found you!
-Of all the stupid pig headed
little-- what kind of a jerk
hits an unarmed
volleyball player?
Not even for a girl did
he let his guard down.
Wait a sec.
I know I managed to get
at least one good hit in.
And where there can be one hit,
ah, there can sure be another.
[laughs]
-P-chan, stay still, OK?
Don't you want me
to get the mark off?
Still, I can't help
wondering-- how'd
Ryoga get the same mark on him?
Do you know, P-chan?
[small squeak]
[laughs]
It's almost like you and Ryoga
are like the same person.
[frightened squealing]
No way.
It can't be.
I mean, Ryoga's away
on a trip, remember?
[frustrated squeals]
What am I thinking?
You'll catch a cold.
I'll just warn you right up.
[terrified squealing]
You stay still.
[grunting]
-(THINKING) If my theory is
right, the mark will disappear.
Don't worry, Ryoga, I'm coming.
[gasps]
-P-chan!
I didn't know you were--
-Ryoga, where are you?
I know how to get it off now!
Ryoga!
-Akane!
[gasps]
A kettle!
[grunts]
And this is Ryoga's bandana.
Akane, be honest-- did you
pour hot water on P-chan?
-Well, uh, those marks, I, I was
only trying to wash them off!
-So you did, didn't you?
You saw.
Ryoga, sure, you've become
the world's strongest man,
but look what it got ya.
Akane, listen to me.
Try not to be too
hard on the poor jerk.
It ain't his fault, OK?
-Hm?
Not his fault?
I don't get it.
He just--
Here we go.
Let's get that soap off of you.
[squealing]
[gulping]
-Ah!
What are you doing?
[squealing]
P-chan?
For P-chan to have
swallowed all that water,
he must really
have been thirsty.
Poor thing!
Which reminds me, what were
you talking about before, hm?
What?
-It was, uh, nothing, OK?
Ha, ha, see ya!
-Ranma!
Hey!
What was that about?
[squeaking]
[squealing]
-Ha!
I knew I'd find ya.
-Ranma?
-And so it seems our hero
cheats certain death once more.
-You're darn right.
If Akane had found
out, I really would
have been better off dead.
Can you imagine?
-Well, if you do
what I tell you,
you never will have to imagine.
-Meaning what?
-Oh, here you are.
Akane--
-Yes?
-Would you mind
helping me a little?
You see, what I'd like is--
-Can you really get rid of it?
-Well, yeah, if
my hunch is right.
[grunts]
Good.
The drapes are
closed, that'll help.
We don't want
nobody spying on us.
Ryoga, do you remember
how mean and you
were fighting just
a little while back?
-Hm.
-Well, I noticed something.
When you were standing straight,
you beat me right away.
But then, once you
bent down to catch
the volleyball I threw at
you, I, I hit it, right?
In other words--
[gasps]
[grunts]
-So that so-called girl was you?
-Oh, come on!
What the heck's that
got to do with anything?
-Not a thing, it just felt good!
-Humph.
Like I was saying, it
was after our fight
that I noticed
your mark, winking.
IE, when it winks, you're weak!
-(THINKING) He has a point.
If, if I can change its shape.
-And so, with chances it
disappear and be good, really
good, you're
practically half way
to be a non
invulnerable already.
[whimpering]
Here it goes!
OK, so that didn't work.
Would it kill you to move the
mark a little more next time?
-Fine.
I'll try it again.
How's about this then?
-Not yet.
Keep trying.
[peeling apples]
It ain't like Ryoga can help
it, so don't be too hard on him.
-(THOUGHTS) Ryoga?
How could Ryoga possibly
be mixed up in all of this?
[gasps]
-Look what you--
-Ah!
Oh no!
What's the matter with you?
There, like that!
Do that some more.
[grunting]
Would you do it harder,
stupid, or do you
want to keep that
stupid mark for the rest
of your whole life?
-My, my whole life?
[laughing]
At the public baths?
At the beach?
At the doctors'
or the hospitals?
To, to go on being a laughing
stock for the rest of my life?
No way, not if I can help it!
[grunts]
-(THINKING) Grr.
I've known him forever, but
he never been this bad off.
Poor jerk.
Come to think of it, I
guess turning into a girl
ain't much better.
Man, We're both so pathetic.
-OK, look, how's this?
-Harder, stupid!
Harder!
-Akane?
We're just about ready
for them, so would you
mind helping me carry them in?
-Sure.
OK, Kasumi.
I'm almost done.
[straining]
-Come on, harder!
[laughing]
-Stop laughing!
-Sorry, man.
You know I don't
mean anything by it.
What's important is that
you did it, man, you won!
You can finally lose now.
I gotta ask though, are you
sure it's what you want?
[scoffs]
-Of course it is.
-Ranma, what you don't
understand is, I got my wish.
But it didn't mean a thing
once I finally had it.
-Beating you fair and square
is the one thing I care about.
It it's because of a
trick, I'd rather lose!
I want to beat you myself,
with my own strength!
-That's cool.
That's what makes
as rivals, Ryoga.
-Well, let's do it then!
[inhales]
-OK, ready?
[straining]
There!
You're not--
[nervous laughter]
-Huh?
Ah, mommy!
[everyone talking at once]
-Ryoga, Ryoga, wha,
what, what are you?
Ranma?
-Were'd they come from?
-We, uh, loaned them
the dojo for their club.
[chuckles]
-Oh man, it figures.
[cheering]
-(THINKING) Somebody shoot me.
[crying]
[whack]
-You lose.
[gasps]
-Look, the mark faded away.
-Like magic.
-What a performance.
-Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[applause]
-(THINKING) So that's it!
Ryoga's been in training
for this club meeting.
-Akane?
Thanks to your friend Ryoga,
the party's a huge success.
I guess you must be
very fond of him.
-Oh, I've never seen
anything like it.
Oh, bravo.
Bravo!
-I still don't get it though.
Why did Ryoga and P-chan
have the same mark?
-Uh, gee, Akane, I don't know.
Maybe to practice his
drawing or something?
-Uh, I guess so.
Maybe.
-(THINKING) Poor jerk.
I wonder if he's OK.
-How, how could I?
I, I flashed my stomach
to all those people!
[sobbing]
-Well, uh, look at
the bright side.
You got rid of the mark, right?
Plus, in the end
you got a big laugh.
[laughs]
-You don't know what
you're talking about!
That kind of a
laugh I don't need!
[sobbing]
I'll never be able
to face Akane again!
[sobbing]
Ah!
-Ryoga!
(THINKING) I can't blame
him for being hurt.
He might be gone
a while this time.
[laughing]
-P-chan!
-Huh?
-Come here!
[squealing]
[laughing]
Oh, welcome back!
The mark, it's gone!
It's better this way.
[giggles]
-I take it back.
Looks like he's still plenty
invulnerable after all.
[happy squealing]
[squealing]
[theme music]
-Oh, Kasumi, you're right.
He really is good
at catching eggs.
NARRATOR: Ranma, can't you
see you're not as good?
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
the Egg Catcher Man.
We'll see you there.