[music playing]
[theme music]
Pandas chomping at bamboo.
Raccoons chomping at your shoe.
Lizard leaping--
Father, that's a nice piece
of bamboo you've found.
Thanks, Kasumi.
You like it?
The bamboo gods have outdone
themselves this year.
KASUMI: And just in time for
the Tanabata Festival of Lovers.
Hm?
You know better than that.
Lips off.
[groan]
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER): Meet
You in the Milky Way.
AKANE: Wow.
This is incredible.
This is the one
time every year when
the star known as Princess Ori
meets her starry lover, Kengyu.
It's so beautiful.
How romantic.
Lay off the mushy stuff, Akane.
You're giving me the creeps.
You're the creep here!
Anyway, this is a
festival of lovers,
so it definitely has
nothing to do with you!
Right.
You really are made out of
steel, aren't you, Ranma?
Steely is as steely does.
What did you say?
KASUMI: Akane!
Huh?
Kasumi, what is it?
Be careful up there.
The balcony railing is
getting kind of loose.
I will.
RANMA: Hey, weird.
The star disappeared.
What?
Take a closer look.
OK.
Not there.
[groan]
You need glasses.
That's funny.
Huh?
[gasp]
What?
Orion moved just now.
Look!
Over that way.
Whereabouts?
[explosion]
[gasp]
[scream]
Akane!
Akane?
Huh?
Come on!
Wait!
Alane, where do you
think you're going?
Are you nuts?
You just fell off a balcony!
I'm sure it landed
right around here.
It couldn't have been a star.
It must've been a
weather balloon.
Otherwise, there'd
be cops everywhere.
I know what I saw!
It's your head injury!
There's nothing wrong with my
head or my eyesight, either!
[gasp]
You-- you wouldn't be--
[scream]
Excuse me.
You wouldn't be
Princess Ori, would you?
Hey!
Knock it off.
[groan]
You are.
I'm almost positive.
You must be a star.
You can tell?
You know I'm a star?
Mhm.
SOUN: Oh.
Oh!
Princess Ori?
Princess Ori of the
famous Japanese fairy tale?
Princess, how did
you end up on Earth?
I'm so busy during
the lovers' festival.
I thought I'd take some time
off while I had the chance.
So what's the deal
with your love, Kengyu?
[gasp]
He's a very nice man.
Who'd have thought
the Princess herself
would make an appearance right
before the Festival of Lovers?
This rundown old house isn't
fit for royalty like yourself,
but I hope you'll try to
make yourself at home.
Saotome, a simple word of
welcome would have been enough.
[grumble]
[giggling]
With those clothes on, you
look like an ordinary girl.
Our place is pretty
simple, but I
hope you'll make
yourself comfortable.
Huh?
Thank you.
I'm very grateful.
Uh, the pleasure's
mine, Princess.
[laughter]
[sigh]
AKANE: Breakfast, everyone!
Princess Ori helped to make it.
I wanted to do something in
return for all your kindness.
I really hope you like it.
Well, you can
probably rest assured
that it won't be as bad
as somebody's cooking.
Who would that be?
No sense getting cold.
[slurping]
[scream]
Wow.
This is interesting.
Yeah, it is.
Wonderful, Princess.
God awful.
I mean, offerings are
a rare treat for us.
Huh?
[groan]
It's disgusting!
[gasp]
[scream]
Aw.
She could be your twin, Akane.
Huh.
Tendo, in the fairytale,
isn't Princess Ori
supposed to grant three
wishes or something?
Huh.
Saotome, she's not a genie.
The princess is
just doing chores
until her prince
comes looking for her
with a pair of glass slippers.
Ah.
You know, Tendo, I don't think
that's the right fairytale,
either.
We have no idea.
I'm sorry for causing
all that trouble.
Hey, it's nothing
to apologize about.
In fact, it made us happy
to know you have flaws
just like us earthlings do.
[laughter]
[scream]
[gasp]
Huh?
Look out!
[chatter]
[sigh]
Wow.
How'd she move so fast?
GENMA: Why, you!
Huh?
That's Pop!
[groan]
Pop!
What happened?
[groan]
Come on.
Talk to me.
Be on your guard, Ranma.
The man who did this to
us has martial arts moves
that are unbeatable.
[groan]
Hang in there, Pop.
KENGYU: I'll challenge
anyone simply
for the thrill of victory.
What?
You're the guy who goes around
destroying training halls!
Correct.
[mooing]
And that's your sidekick?
I'll take you on, farm boy.
But first, get that cow
out of my training hall!
Watch it!
She's Moochan.
[mooing]
[groan]
Yeah, whatever.
Come on!
[yelling]
[groans]
Let's see you dodge
this, you little cowpoke.
[groan]
(VOICEOVER) This guy's
not so strong after all.
[laughter]
Huh?
I'll wipe that
smile off your face!
Kengyu Superstar Maneuver!
[groan]
What?
What happened?
[laughter]
Let's go, [inaudible].
[mooing]
[groan]
Hey.
Not so fast.
[groan]
How do you feel, Ranma?
Are you OK?
[groan]
Now I know!
I should have been cautious!
Who were you fighting?
I don't know.
Some freak with a cow.
A cow?
What exactly did
the man look like?
I've just figured out who
the young man is, Ranma.
Huh?
He's known as the
Training Hall Destroyer,
and he roams the countryside
with his menacing cow.
He's considered
extremely dangerous
and should be
approached with caution.
Huh?
[gasp]
Sorry.
I had a feeling it might be him.
You know him?
It's my boyfriend, Kengyu.
Kengyu?
You mean your boyfriend
from the fairytale?
Yes.
The real reason that
I descended to Earth
was so that I
could look for him.
I owe you all an apology.
It's all my fault that he's
come here to your training hall
and roughed you up.
[gasp]
[animal sounds]
The Milky Way style of
martial arts, you say?
And you used to be a member?
Now it makes sense.
My parents arranged for Kengyu
and I to marry one another.
Huh?
[gasp]
This story seems
vaguely familiar somehow.
That's the funny thing
with folk stories.
Don't you think?
ORI (VOICEOVER): Kengyu
was like a different man
when we were first engaged.
Even though my parents
had arranged our marriage,
we were deeply in
love with each other.
There was only
one small problem.
Yah!
[groan]
Kengyu, you're such a klutz.
[laughter]
Sorry about that.
You're pathetic.
And you expect to inherit the
martial arts training hall?
I don't know.
Thanks again, Moochan.
[mooing]
Don't rely on her.
You've got to stand
on your own feet.
Well, I don't have
any talent of my own.
I'd be happy just to live my
life without all this pressure.
You're the princess.
So I don't have to work so hard.
[laughter]
Quit that, Moochan.
Stop being such a wimp
hanging around in the cow pods
and swapping spit
with that bovine,
and start making an effort
to be strong, will you?
Uh.
Oh.
Sorry for raising my voice.
After that, he left on a long
term training expedition.
An arranged marriage
to someone else?
But Father, Kengyu
hasn't run away.
He's vowed to
become strong, and I
know he's out there
somewhere training.
The wedding's July 7?
All right, Father.
If Kengyu hasn't returned by
then, you'll have your way.
No prob.
We'll help you find
him before then.
It's not exactly that
simple, I'm afraid, chuckles.
Sure, it is, Akane.
All we have to do is get
Kengyu back by the seventh.
What makes you think he'll go?
I've got my ways
of making it happen.
Yeah, right.
Except for one thing-- you lost.
Yes.
But if Kengyu's travelling
the countryside training
as intensely as it sounds, then
I suspect that marriage might
be the last thing on his mind.
[gasp]
Huh?
How could you say that?
A woman's hopes should
never be crushed.
[groan]
AKANE: Princess Ori.
Sorry I ran out like that.
I've been nothing but a
terrible burden to you all.
Don't be ridiculous.
You haven't been a
burden to any of us.
And we've still got two
days to find Kengyu.
That's right.
So there's still hope.
Come on.
Why don't we work out a bit?
I'm not very good, but I'd love
to be your sparring partner.
Huh?
[fighting sounds]
[groan]
You're good!
So are you.
Thanks, Akane.
I feel so much better.
My pleasure.
I'd love to work out with
you anytime, Prince Ori.
Hey, don't you think
we have a lot in common?
I've been thinking
the same thing.
Except for the fame and stuff.
Your fiancee sure
seems really nice.
Ranma?
No way!
That guy is so frustrating,
I could just dropkick him.
Akane, I used to think Kengyu
was like that before, too.
[gasp]
Hm.
Kengyu keeps moving
from place to place,
busting up all the
training halls.
So if I look around long enough,
I should be able to find him.
Hi!
Huh?
[laughter]
Sensei, I guess that just
leaves you now, doesn't it?
Why, you!
Huh?
(VOICEOVER) This'll
be a perfect chance
to watch him and find
out his weaknesses.
[laughter]
[gasp]
Kengyu Super Star!
[meowing]
[scream]
[purring]
[groan]
A kitty cat.
Huh?
Kengyu?
What are you doing here?
Kengyu, come home with me.
I heard about your marriage.
All the stars are
talking about it.
Congratulations.
It won't happen if
we go back together.
No chance!
[gasp]
I'm staying here
to get stronger.
Forget about that, Kengyu.
I was far too harsh on you.
Please, come back home with me.
Huh?
You were right about me
needing to be strong.
One day, I hope to have my very
own martial arts training hall.
Oh, Kengyu.
Don't you get anything?
We'll have to make him go.
You again.
Yeah, and last time you
had a couple lucky shots.
But now it's payback time.
Another match?
Sure thing.
I'll take you on.
Here's the deal.
If I win, you have to
return to the Milky Way.
Hm.
Pretty high stakes, but
I'll accept your challenge.
You don't stand a chance, fool.
And if you lose, you have to be
my beloved [inaudible] servant.
[groan]
(VOICEOVER) What can
I do to defeat Kengyu?
Ranma?
Wouldn't you be better off
getting a good night's sleep?
I'm trying to figure
out how to win the match.
Over the Kengyu Superstar move?
Yeah.
I don't know how I can
counter that move of his.
Kengyu is one strong
opponent, Akane.
I know.
Why don't you practice on me?
Right.
Like defeating a
weakling like you
is going to help me against
someone like Kengyu.
[scream]
What's the matter?
Can't take a punch from a
little weakling like me?
[drums]
We shall now commence a one set
match between Ranma and Kengyu.
No holds barred.
So do what it takes, and
may the best man win.
Start.
[yelling]
[fight sounds]
(VOICEOVER) As long as
my back's to the wall,
I can't take Kengyu's
kick in the head.
What?
You call this fighting?
[groan]
My arm's stuck.
I-- I can't get it
out of the wall.
[laughter]
[groan]
Kengyu Superstar Maneuver!
This is too easy.
[groan]
Kengyu Superstar!
[scream]
Running is all Ranma
can do to avoid getting
kicked in the back of the head.
Kengyu knows that, and
he's playing to him.
He's wearing Ranma down.
But it's not until Ranma's
completely exhausted
that he'll use the full force of
his Kengyu Superstar Maneuver.
Ranma.
[sigh]
[laughter]
(VOICEOVER) Kengyu,
why are you doing this?
Where did this
confidence come from?
[gasp]
(VOICEOVER) I don't stand a
chance at this rate, Akane.
I've got to win!
[groan]
Now!
Kengyu Superstar Maneuver!
[scream]
Huh?
[groan]
Ha.
So this is what the real Kengyu
Superstar kick is all about.
He catches
everyone's attention,
and then he gets his cow
the kick his opponent
in the back of the head.
That's the Kengyu
Superstar Maneuver.
That's ridiculous.
What's the matter?
Did you just figure it out?
Why, you dirty-- I'm going
to get you good, Kengyu.
[laughter]
Get a load of my
exploding roundhouse kick!
KENGYU: I'm sorry!
Today's the Tanabata
Festival of Lovers.
We made it just in time.
Thank goodness for that.
Thanks so much
for all your help.
I've learned not to rely on
Moochan's strength anymore.
[mooing]
Kengyu, you might be stronger
than before, but being kind
is what really counts.
You better treat her good now.
Yeah, I know.
Akane, I hope we meet again.
Me, too.
Huh?
What's this?
Next, it's your return, Akane.
I really hope you'll work
things out with your boyfriend.
What?
No!
You don't understand!
Come on, [inaudible].
[mooing]
[laughter]
Goodbye, Princess Ori!
Please, come back again!
RANMA: Akane.
Akane?
Hey, Akane!
Huh?
Ah, you finally came to.
Thank goodness my
daughter's all right.
I told you to be careful.
Lucky thing you've
got such a hard head.
What are you doing?
Let go!
[groan]
Just relax.
Don't you remember falling
off the balcony a second ago?
What?
Then where's the
princess and Kengyu?
Right where they're
supposed to be.
Take a look in the
sky, and you'll
see they're right
where you left them.
Huh?
[sigh]
(VOICEOVER) Was it a dream?
The whole thing?
But it all seemed so real.
Huh?
It's here.
So it wasn't a dream.
Get on.
I'll piggyback you inside.
Huh?
Mhm.
Hey, Ranma.
Yeah?
Nothing.
Forget it.
Come on, tell me.
Just drop it, would you?
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER): Odd
or even, left or right,
high or low, up or down,
cherry blossom mark
or an X. Next time on
Ranma 1/2-- Wretched Rice
Cakes of Love.
We'll see you there.