NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hng Go!
-Ha ya!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering.
[water splashing]
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma is
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
[gong]
[singing]
FEMALE NARRATOR: "Assault
on the Girls' Locker Room"
[clock chiming]
STORE CLERK (ANNOUNCING): One
of the many special bargains
available to you today as one
of our very valued customers, be
sure to use the coupons included
in your "smart shoppers" guide.
RYOGA: I'm back Akane.
At last we're together
in the same town.
Too bad I have to leave on
another journey right away.
No, no, please don't ask why.
Just know that I have
my reasons for leaving.
Akane, there's something
that I have to tell you.
I promise you I'll be a
whole man next time we meet.
So would you go on
a date w-with me?
[sigh] I can't!
A date?
Am I crazy?
She'd never agree to that!
-He doesn't look so bad.
-Oh, the poor kid!
-And at such a young age.
-What a haul!
What a haul!
Panties, bras, you name it!
I've got it!
What a haul!
-What was that?
Uh, uh.
Somebody stall him!
-All right.
Where did the pervert
run off to now?
-Honestly, I don't see any
point in going after him now.
-But Akane, we can't let
him get away with it!
-Don't worry.
He's not getting
away with anything.
First, we lure him in.
RYOGA: Excuse me, Akane?
Uh.
-Oh, hello Ryoga.
-Hi there.
-Hey, what're you
doing down there?
Oh, just laying around.
[music playing]
-Leave on another
journey right away, huh?
-Yep.
Can't be helped.
-Hey.
Don't you want to
say hello to Ranma?
Well, Ryoga?
-Well it's not really
high on my list.
There's something
I have to tell you!
-Oh?
-Akane, could you ever-- I
mean-- would you-- I mean--
-Go on.
-D date- go on a d date-- uh.
To take this parting gift.
-Hey!
Buckwheat noodles?
Oh, I love these!
Ryoga, you really
shouldn't have.
-Have a safe trip Ryoga!
Bye bye!
[nervous laughter]
[sigh]
-I'm such an idiot!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Yoo hoo!
Ryoga!
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Akane?
AKANE (VOICEOVER): In
thanks for the gift,
let me give you a
big juicy smooch!
-Oh!
[heart beating]
-Let's not rush things.
I mean, we're still
young and all.
[heart beating]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Come here, baby.
Come to mama.
-Huh?
What?
OK, just let me
get ready, my love.
-Forget it.
Changed my mind. [laughing]
-Ahhhhhhh!
Ranma, you are dead!
RANMA: Ahhh!
It was a joke!
Can't you take a joke?
RYOGA: Do I look like
I'm laughing to you?
-You big baby.
Is violence your
answer to everything?
-Shut up!
You're on thin ice, Ranma!
Plus, you're a pervert!
-Don't take it
out on me, P-Chan!
-Watch it, Ranma.
'cause pretty soon,
you may not have
P-Chan to kick around anymore.
-Say that again?
-It's because I have this!
Huh?
-Ah.
Looks like one of
your dumb maps.
-Hey!
You give that back!
[music playing]
-What is it?
-Give it back, I said!
-Oops!
[gasp]
-The map to Japan's Nannichuan!
[splash]
-Did you say Nannichuan?
[squealing]
NARRATOR: Once upon a time,
in the age of the samurai,
there were many
naughty foxes who
troubled the lands
hard-working people.
They stole food, killed
chickens, and generally
made a nuisance of themselves.
These foxes were very
clever and the villagers
didn't know what to do.
Until one day, a distinguished
priest arrived from China.
-Be gone naughty foxes and
trouble these good people
no more.
NARRATOR: He struck
once with his staff
and before their eyes--
-Lo, a spring has sprung!
NARRATOR: It was true.
All the foxes which
fell in the spring
took the bodies of young men.
And so, thanks to the
priest, the naughty foxes,
which had troubled the
people, were no more.
Of course, there was
now the small matter
of the naughty young
men to deal with.
RYOGA: That's the story anyway.
-Another Nannichuan?
You really think it exists?
-That's right.
Another spring of drowned
man here in Japan.
And that map shows
its exact location.
So next time we meet,
I'll be a whole man.
Well, I'm off.
-Hey, don't leave so soon.
I mean, it's already
pitch black outside
and you can get a
fresh start tomorrow.
That spring's waited
this long, right?
RYOGA: Sure.
Why not?
[music playing]
-I can get there fine on my own.
You don't need to walk me there.
-Come on, Ryoga.
You know you'd get lost
in your own backyard.
-Well, leave me alone!
That's why I've got this map!
OK, the arrow's
pointing this way.
Let's see, the arrow's pointing
east, so it's this way.
-East is this way, moron.
Give you a choice of directions
and you pick the wrong one
every time.
-Hey!
Gimme back my map!
-Giving you a map is like
giving a pig a pearl necklace.
That spring will dry up
before you ever find it.
-It's gym class next, you know.
-I bet that dirty old
man will come again.
What'll we do?
-Don't worry.
I think I figured out
a way to stop him.
Just leave everything to me.
-So what are you
going to do, Akane?
AKANE: Oh, you'll
find soon enough.
Just wait and see.
-I can hardly wait.
[humming]
-Oh my!
Where did you get
all of panties?
-They're a gift
from the heavens.
-Hey, are you sure you're
reading that right?
Isn't this the field in the
back of your high school?
-This is it, all right.
Look.
Here's the stone fox.
According to the
map, the spring's
exactly 100 steps away.
We made it Ryoga.
Japan's Nannichuan.
-I don't need you anymore.
A mere 100 steps to
complete manhood!
Ha ha ha!
-That's no fair Ryoga!
-Don't follow me!
-Then stop running!
-87, 88, 89, it's
under that building!
-92, 93-
[crash]
-We got 'em!
-Where'd he go?
I don't see him.
-I'll bet he ran away.
-Which can only mean--
-That he'll be back.
Everyone!
To their battle stations!
We won't let that pervert into
our locker rooms now, will we?
-No!
-It's under the
girl's locker room.
(VOICEOVER): I don't care if
it's under the Imperial Palace.
There ain't nothing I won't
do to get into that spring.
INSTRUCTOR (ON TV): And one,
and two, and one and two.
Nothing like leg-lifts to
promote the bottom, ladies.
-Master, isn't it passed
time for your morning visit
to the high school today?
-In a minute.
-So, how do I look?
-Ranma!
I No!
You don't mean to go in
through the front door, do you?
-Well, duh.
-No, I won't allow it!
Akane's probably half naked now!
-The next time I see you, Ryoga,
I'll be a whole man again.
-Do you really
think he's coming?
-He'll come.
Like the sun comes up in
the morning, he'll come.
-I don't want to be mean, but
the only way to get rid of him
is to teach him a lesson.
-Don't mind me,
girls, I just forgot--
[splash]
-It's Ranma.
[screaming]
-Uh!
-Hey, isn't that Ranma Saotome?
-Ew, he's wearing
girl's gym shorts!
RANMA: Why does this
always happen to me?
Kill me now!
-I told you not to do it.
-I don't need you to rub it in!
I ain't beat yet.
All I gotta do is move
on to plan B, that's all.
[music playing]
-You got it, Mr. P?
Get the underwear and
create a diversion.
And while Akane and her
henchmen are chasing you,
I'll go and scope
out the spring.
You got it?
[squealing]
-Don't you chicken
out on me now, man.
Go!
Look!
It's P-Chan.
-Akane, P-Chan's here.
-P-Chan?
Where is he?
Come here, baby.
Come to Mama.
[squealing]
[laughing]
-What is wrong with his nose?
-P-Chan!
Snap out of it!
-You heard her Mr.
P, snap out of it!
Huh?
AKANE (YELLING): Ranma!
-It's not half bad being a pig.
-Ryoga!
You little-- what the heck
is wrong with you, huh?
What's more important, the
future and the spring or today
and Akane?
-Today and Akane.
-Aaah!
-He's fast, but he
couldn't have gotten far.
When I get my hands on
him, he'll be sorry.
Ranma!
-Oh no!
It's Akane!
Run for it!
-Ryoga?
What're you doing here?
-Uh, hi Akane.
-Gee, I would've thought
you'd left already.
-I uh, well I uh--
[nervous laughter]
-Hey, have you seen Ranma?
He must have come through
here a few minutes ago.
He just tried to get into
the girl's locker room
wearing some girl's gym shorts.
I can't believe it.
(VOICEOVER): Even if it
is all for the spring,
I can't be a part of
this sick little scheme.
Akane shouldn't have to
suffer just because Ranma
is insecure about his manhood.
-Akane!
-Huh?
-You don't need to
worry about Ranma!
He may have his reasons,
but he's gone too far.
Please Akane, allow me
to be your body guard.
-Uh, OK.
(VOICEOVER): Huh, I've
just begun to fight.
-Hey, all right!
It's clear!
[scream] Huh, jeez,
they're so small.
-Caught you red handed.
Panties, Ranma?
You should be ashamed!
-Yo, how's it going Ryoga?
You trader!
What about the spring?
-Akane is more
important, you pervert!
You're nothing
but a peeping tom!
How dare you!
-Heeya!
He won't be bothering
us for a while.
-What the--
-You watch the door while I
pack up these pretties, huh?
-Hello, boys.
Am I interrupting?
-Huh?
-Don't even think about
running away, Ranma.
-Huh?
-Teaming up with Happosai?
I don't believe it!
You make me sick!
-Hey, hey!
Akane, you've got it all wrong.
It's just a coincidence.
Ask him.
That's not why I'm here.
-Ranma, They won't listen.
They never do.
Founding school of
Anything Goes Martial Arts,
final attack, silky storm!
Now's our chance, Ranma.
Let's run for it!
-But they'll never
believe me anyway!
(VOICEOVER): You can run,
Ranma, but you can't hide!
-Are we gonna let those
perverts get away with this?
-No!
-This goes from bad to worse.
This don't mean I'm ready
to give up just yet.
I'll get into that girls'
locker room any way I can.
Get ready Akane.
-Ranma, I'm touched.
You do care about underwear.
I'm so proud.
-I ain't like you, old freak.
I'm doing this for the spring.
Yeah, that's gross
enough, I guess.
-Ribbit.
Ribbit.
-Sometimes you got to
fight fire with fire.
And this ought to burn them!
[screaming]
-Come on!
They're more afraid of
you then you are of them!
-Snakes!
Frogs!
Creepy crawlies! [screams]
-Hey, fight fair!
-Ribbit!
Ribbit!
[screaming]
-Ew.
You pervert!
Where is he?
[screaming]
-Ha!
I knew it!
[scream]
(VOICEOVER): Uh oh.
What's he doing in here?
-Are you OK, Miss?
Sorry.
I thought you were some
pervert named Ranma.
(VOICEOVER): Dumb
as a box of rocks.
Sucker.
-Huh?
-Hold me!
-Hey!
I mean-- I've never seen
you before in my life!
You can't just--
-I've been so in love with
you for months now, Ryoga.
Don't tell me you hate
girls with glasses.
-Yeah.
I mean no!
I, I mean I don't
mind your classes,
but I've already
got somebody I like.
I'm really sorry.
-Oh well.
Never mind.
-Uh, well uh, do you really--
(VOICEOVER): Time for
beddy-bye, [inaudible].
-Ranma?
What do you two
think you're doing?
-Oh, hi Akane.
-Hey, hey cut it out!
No!
Don't do--
-Uh uh.
Akane, it's not
what it looks like!
You know I would never do--
-Akane, why do you
always have to but in?
-Ranma.
You really want that underwear.
Now I understand.
-Hey!
You-- I ain't a pervert.
I'm just a-- huh?
-Here you go.
I know I can't stop you.
-Come on!
-Please.
I beg you.
Just let this be
your last perversion.
I didn't mind it when
it was just your body,
but your mind's sick too.
Even if it's just
for a while, I don't
regret the time
we spent together.
[crying] Farewell.
-Wait!
I only did it because
of that dumb Nannichuan.
What kind of sicko
do you think I am?
-Nannichuan?
-Yeah, like the one
in China, but it's
underneath this locker room.
-Is that true?
-Would these baby
blues lie to you?
-Then you're not a pervert.
-Nah. [laughing]
-You're just a liar, then.
How dumb do you think I am?
-That was quite a
touching performance
you gave back there.
What a fool I am.
I started to believe someone
actually cared about me.
OK, so no one said
they liked me before.
But why must I become the butt
of your cruel jokes, Ranma?
-Hey, did you hear what he said?
-Nobody likes him, huh?
-That poor guy.
-Hey man, I'm sorry.
-For one brief moment,
that girl with the glasses
found a place in this empty,
unconquered heart of mine.
Tell me one thing, Ranma!
Why did you toy with
my emotions like that!?
-Duh, Ryoga.
I did it for the
spring, of course.
-For your own pride, you ruined
an unsullied relationship.
Why you-- you [inaudible]!
-Yo, man!
Get a grip!
I didn't even know there was
such a place as that spring
till you showed up with the map!
-[gasp] Ryoga!
Tell me, is that true?
But why would you have
a map to the spring
of the drowned-- No, Ryoga!
Don't tell me that you--
(VOICEOVER): She knows!
The dark secret that I've
kept from her all this time.
At last!
She knows!
[squealing]
-[groaning]
-Oh no!
-Akane, I meant to
tell you some day.
-You didn't do it all for
that pervert, Ranma's, sake,
did you?
Ryoga, I could kiss you!
-Huh?
-Good thing she's dumb
as a brick, hey P-Chan?
-Who are you calling P-Chan?
-Whoa!
Struck a nerve, huh?
AKANE: Cut it out, you two!
RYOGA: Too late for that, Akane!
-You're dead!
-Quit it!
-Hey, I think I did it.
All right!
[screaming]
-There was a spring.
So he was telling me the truth.
-Ryoga.
That map of yours
was for Nannichuan.
Isn't that right?
-[squealing]
-Then why haven't I changed
back into a guy, yet, huh, huh?
Tell me, rodent!
What's going on?
Take a good look
at me, you moron!
Speak up!
You know I can't understand
you when you're like this!
Well, tell-- [groan] Hey,
what the heck is this?
-All right.
Which one of you
broke the water main.
-Uh, Ranma did it.
-The water main?
JANITOR: That little
punk again, huh?
(VOICEOVER): I
should've known there'd
be no such thing as a
Japanese Nannichuan.
Honestly, what does
Ranma take me for?
-Huh.
Weird looking pot to be
under the girls' locker room.
[gasp] Maybe that's
got something
to do with that Japanese spring
of drowned man, or something.
[theme music]
FEMALE NARRATOR:
What is this place?
Ranma and the others went
into it willingly enough,
but will they ever come out?
What are they gathering
all those urns for?
Next time on Ranma One
Half, "House of Gadgets".
Guests check in, but
they don't check out.
See you there.