[music playing]
NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hey, let go!
-Hai-yah!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
The two have been engaged to
marry by their loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma is
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
-He wouldn't dare!
Oh, no.
Akane!
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER):
Hurry, Ranma Saotome.
If you don't rescue
her soon, Akane Tendo
will spend the rest
of her life as a duck.
RANMA: [panting] You think I'm
gonna let you do that to Akane,
you got another
think coming, pal.
[cheering and applause]
[laughing to self]
EMCEE: Lady and gentlemen.
Now for show you
all waiting for.
After magic water
poured into tank-- oh,
so incredible--
beautiful young girl
become duck before very eye!
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER):
Ranma Saotome,
the minute you
dive into the tank
to save the woman,
it's all over.
[panting]
-(SHOUTING) Akane!
RANMA: Ranma versus Mousse.
To lose is to win!
[gong]
-Hai! Hai! Hai!
And now, event you've
been waiting for.
All too incredible-- magic
water turn girl into duck
before very eye.
Is nice assistant ready?
[drum roll]
[crowd murmurs with wonder]
[cymbal clash]
-Mmm, mm, mm!
-Stay still, you!
[handle squeaking]
[muffled scream]
-You cut that out!
Hyah!
Oh no!
That water's gonna
splash all over her!
Auuuuughhh!
[screams]
Phew.
Whooaaa!
-I fooled you, Ranma Saotome.
That one's plain tap water.
The real Yahzuniichuan
is right here!
Curse you!
Stay still and turn into a duck!
[muffled scream]
-Ranma, look out!
RANMA: Shampoo!
-Mousse, what you doing?
[quacking]
MAN: I thought the
girl was supposed
to be the duck, not the tiger.
WOMAN: What?
-Shampoo?
You're helping him?
How could you, Shampoo?
-Ask her yourself, bird-brain.
-Do you hate me, Shampoo?
-Sure do.
-Huh?
Uh-- y-you're
joking, aren't you?
-Me hate you.
-Aaaaughhhh!
SHAMPOO: Hate big-time.
Hate more than [inaudible].
H-A-T-E hate you!
-Aaaaughhhh!
Wh-- why, Shampoo?
How can you hate me so much?
All I've ever done is love you.
Why, I can't remember the number
of times I've proposed to you.
Oh, Shampoo.
-Shampoo over here!
-Marry me, Shampoo.
Why don't you love me?
Tell me!
[weeping]
WOMAN: That's the most romantic
thing I've heard in my life!
[weeping]
-Come on, it's not so bad.
-What'd you say?
-You say that you're in
love, but if you really are,
you would get rid of
whatever is in your way.
-Ranma!
I can't believe you're
being so nice to me
after all I've done to you.
You're a good man,
Ranma Saotome.
I'm going to take your advice.
-Hm?
-And get rid of you!
Hyyyaaahhhh!
Where are you going?
I just got my second wind!
-He's nuts!
-Oh, Mousse, you really
love Shampoo that much?
-I'm an innocent bystander.
How'd I get into this mess?
Huh?
[screams]
What are you doing?
-Shampoo feel sorry
for Mousse, so she
help him meet new girlfriend.
New duck girlfriend!
[screams]
-Hai-yahhhh!
Hyah, hyah, hyah!
[gasps]
-D'oh!
-Saotome, surrender!
-Find yourself
another girlfriend!
RANMA: It's out of control!
Look out!
[screams]
-Akane!
Akane!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Akane.
[quack]
-Huh?
[gasp]
[quack]
RANMA: Akane?
Oh, no.
No!
Akane, it's all my fault.
[quack]
[sobs]
-Akane, don't worry.
I'll help you change back.
[dog barking]
Akane, don't worry, OK?
No one else needs
to know our secret.
Here, I'll look away
for a minute, all right?
-Ahoy there.
-Uh-- uh--
-I mean, it's still my
turn to use the scuba gear.
Wait your turn.
-Gah--
-Now, son, what's
this about Akane?
I heard something
about a secret.
(STAMMERING) What secret?
-You are hiding something.
-[laughs nervously] Uh--
-Who's hiding a secret?
What a cute duck.
KASUMI: It's adorable!
-Duh-- duh-- duck?
You're kidding!
[splashing]
[indignant quacking]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): She--
she didn't change back.
Oh.
Oh!
Akane!
-Ow-- ow!
Huh?
How did I-- what am
I doing under here?
SHAMPOO: So you only splash
Akane with plain water?
-The water from the
Yahzuniichuan is precious.
I can't go wasting it on her.
This water's for Ranma.
It mustn't be used
on anyone but him.
AKANE: Whoops!
-Gah!
[quacking]
-Oh, great.
Now there no more
Yahzuniichuan left.
MOUSSE: [quacking]
-Not Akane?
-My sister's a waterfowl.
RANMA: I don't understand.
She-- she should've
turned back by now.
She's a living bath toy!
It's all my fault.
-Don't worry, son.
It's not that bad.
I know you'll take
responsibility for this.
-Responsibility?
-This is a happy occasion.
We'll hold the ceremony
right here in the dojo.
-Ooh, I just adore weddings!
-I'll be your real
sister at last!
-OK, Mousse.
Be real man for once and
give up Shampoo forever.
-I won't!
-Mousse, no matter how hard
you try, you won't beat Ranma!
Give up and go back home.
(LIGHTLY) Goodbye.
-OK, then.
Fine.
Who needs an icy-cold
Amazon like you, anyway?
[gasp]
MOUSSE: [groaning]
-I hear that, you stupid Mousse!
-I-- I was only kidding.
-Nyah!
-Sh-- Shampoo!
[sobbing]
-Oh, how pathetic.
-What did I do wrong?
[weeping]
-Stop crying, Mousse.
Come on, I'll help you.
-How would you help me?
-Fight Ranma one more time.
This time, you'll be the winner.
-I'll what?
SOUN: [laughs] Here-- here's
to the soon-to-be happy couple.
Look, girls.
Isn't your sister a--
a beautiful bride?
[sobbing] You'll take
care of my little girl?
-Sure.
-Say, are you sure
that just isn't a duck?
I mean, that's not
really her, is it?
-Well, Father thinks so.
-Ahhhh, let's have a
toast now, shall we?
Akane, be a good girl now.
Come on.
[quacking]
-Hey! Hey!
-It doesn't want a drink, Daddy.
-Akane!
-Ugh.
Akane, I don't like this whole
mess any more than you do.
And even if you
weren't a duck, I still
wouldn't marry an
uncute girl like you.
Grr!
Hey, quit it!
I'm the one making
the sacrifice here.
-Huh?
-You might try showing a
little gratitude, you know.
Your legs are too thick,
you're built like a brick-- ow!
-I heard that, Ranma!
Besides, why would I
ever be grateful to you?
-Oh, you're not
a duck after all!
-I just knew it was
to good to be true.
Things would have
been very interesting
if you'd come 10 minutes later.
-Hm?
Akane?
Hm?
Huh?
[quacks]
OK
[sizzling]
RANMA: Mousse is challenging me?
He wants a fight?
-I've got the challenge
letter right here.
-Huh, so now he sends it.
-Many time he attack you,
but Ranma always win!
-She's right, son-in-law,
you're a tough one.
Here you go, two orders up.
-Two chow mein.
Enjoy.
-Shampoo, what if
Mousse is the winner?
[gasp]
-Hey, what are
you trying to say?
-Oooh!
-If by one in million
chance Mousse win,
then Shampoo sacrifice
herself and date with him.
[slurp]
[muffled shout]
-Shampoo, you're lucky
I was passing by!
I'll beat you into a bloody
pulp in front of Shampoo, Ranma.
See ya later.
[laughs maniacally]
-Oh, yeah?
-(QUIETLY) Let him win, Ranma.
-How come?
-Put him out of his misery.
Besides, if you let him win,
Shampoo'll have to give you up.
-Hm?
-Hm.
[gong]
-Remember now, Ranma,
you just pretend to lose.
-Do I gotta?
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER):
They obvious as wonton
on wedding cake.
Shampoo no fooled.
They no get away with it.
-Hey, Mousse!
-Huh?
Uh, what's this?
-Shampoo make it just for
you, to bring good luck.
-What?
It's for me?
Are you sure I'm worthy
of this fine weapon?
-Mhm.
-I'm-- I'm invincible!
Ranma, prepare to die!
-Don't be too obvious, OK?
-(MUTTERING) There's a
first time for everything.
-Die, They Ranma!
-Gotcha.
-You're supposed to let him win!
MOUSSE: You haven't beat me yet!
-Quit it!
Using this magnificent
weapon lovingly crafted
for me by Shampoo, I will win!
[ululating holler]
You're mine!
-Hm?
-Are those eggs?
[clattering]
BOTH: Huh?
[massive explosion]
-Aagghh!
-What the?
Aaaughhh!
-Gee, how'd that happen?
Hey!
You did that on
purpose, didn't you?
-Shampoo have no intention
to date with Mousse.
So sorry, but I
make sure he no win.
Mousse!
-Hey!
--[laughs] With Shampoo on my
side, how can I lose the fight?
Hyaaaah!
[bang]
-Mousse!
[boom]
-See?
Now he no more fight today.
-I can't believe you
would be so heartless.
-Oh, brother, I'd hate to
be in your shoes right now.
[grunting with pain]
-Huh?
You haven't beaten me yet.
[panting]
[gasp]
-Mousse, give up.
-Shampoo is not yours.
She's mine.
Rraaaah!
-Hey, you're really
going for it, aren't ya?
Well, I'm ready when you are.
-Ranma, stop picking on him!
Don't you think the
poor guy has had enough?
[wind whistling]
-Hunh!
How would you like it
if I lost on purpose?
-Wha-- what did you say?
You wouldn't like
that, would you?
-[gasp] Oh, that's right.
He's almost as proud as Ranma.
-Ranma, if you were to lose
on purpose, I would be happy.
[clang]
-Nnnngh!
-If pride stands in the way
of winning Shampoo, then
who needs it?
Hyaaaahh!
[gasp]
-Oh, Mousse!
-Take this, Ranma.
A final attack so
terrible, it's immortalized
in an old Chinese
ballad, [chinese]!
-Ah!
[panting]
-Stop running, you coward!
Take your punishment like a man!
I thought you were going
to lose on purpose!
-Aaaaaauuuuuughhhh!
[metal clashing]
-Hmf.
I'm not beaten.
Come on!
Feel the power of my
love, Ranma Saotome!
-Aaaaaauuuuuughhhh!
[yelling]
-Cut it out!
-The more I wear an opponent
down, the stronger I become.
That's how I fight,
so get used to it.
Hurry up and lose
on purpose already!
Hyah!
[both shouting]
-Uh?
Uh-oh.
Uh, heh.
No ammo.
-Huaahhh!
Gaaaaahhh!
[both shouting]
-I didn't think that
idiot was ever gonna stop.
I better bury him pretty deep.
-Ranma!
But where's Mousse?
-That Mousse, he
fought the good fight.
-Mousse no could beat
you, right, Ranma?
-Oh, he didn't have a chance.
Yep, sure did give me a
run for my money, though.
Guh?
Aaaghh!
-You won't beat me!
[gasp]
-(WEAKLY) Sh-- Shampoo!
[whimpers]
-Look, he's fainted!
[splash]
Shampoo?
-Oh, Mousse, you stubborn duck.
-Maybe he got through
to her after all.
SHAMPOO: Oh!
Look what Shampoo have for you!
MOUSSE: [quacking]
-Guess he works cheap.
[insistent quacking]
-Get it!
Get it!
Jump!
Oops.
[quacking]
-Look at him, Akane.
He's living the good life.
-Hm.
To each his own, I guess.
[quacking]
-Nyah!
[MUSIC - ETSUKO NISHIO, "DON'T
MIND CHINA BOY"]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
[screams] It's a monster!
What kind of old man is he?
What?
He's the sum of
all evil in Japan?
What do you mean, he's the
guy who trained our fathers?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," enter
Happosai, the lustful lecher!
See you there!