[music playing]
NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hey, let go!
-Hai-ya!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma is
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
[theme music]
-Huh?
Aaaaahhhh!
-What the heck is that?
-Maybe it's a UFO or something.
-Dumbest-looking UFO I ever saw.
[wings flapping]
-Son-in-law.
Where's that son-in-law of mine?
Come now, tell me where he is.
[clanking]
[alarm buzzes]
-Whhaaa!
-Look out!
-Get out of the way!
WORKER: Hey, get out
of the way, lady!
Watch out!
Come on, move!
[clang]
[rubble clattering]
[shocked gasps]
-Did you see that?
-Whoa!
[interposing voices]
Where's my son-in-law?
-Mm-mm-mm-mm.
-Son-in-law?
Where are you?
NARRATOR: "This Old Gal's the
Leader of the Amazon Tribe."
-Saotome, prepare to die!
-Hyuh!
I told you before, I-- I--
didn't do nothing with her,
all right?
Hey!
-If the rumors I've
heard are true,
you've done something
horrible to Akane, something
my poor heart of
glass can't bear
to hear without
shattering into pieces!
-Come on, Ryoga, chill out!
You know how people talk.
They make stuff up all
the time, you know that.
RYOGA: Shut up!
No more excuses!
There's not much time before I
have to leave on a short trip.
-Well, don't let me stop you.
There's one thing I've got to
do first-- beat the hell out
of you, Ranma!
[both shouting]
-Die!
[crash]
[squealing]
-Have a nice trip, Ryoga.
See you next fall.
Don't forget to write, OK?
Don't take any wooden
nickels, and all that.
Bye!
[squealing]
That stupid jerk Ryoga.
Don't he got nothing better
to do than chase after me
with that dumb umbrella all day?
Man, I'm starving.
I hope there's something
good to eat at the house.
-Meow! [hissing]
-Aaaaaahhh!
Get away from me!
--[cackles] Big enough to
eat you with, my dear.
You can't hide from me.
A ninja sees all, knows all.
-Why, you don't
know-- or do you?
Mm?
-Saotome.
How dare you touch the
lips of Akane Tendo?
-Come on, man, you gotta
be confused or something.
-He's lying, master.
-Hm?
-I saw it with my own eyes.
She begged him not to do it,
but he was like an animal.
That poor child!
-Hey, shut up!
That never happened,
and you know it.
-I can't bear to hear anymore!
Cad.
Lothario.
Casanova.
Don Juan!
Your days of lechery are over!
-Calm down, Kuno!
Aaah!
-Got you.
KUNO: No, my good Sasuke.
He's mine.
Aaaah!
Stay still!
[dazed humming]
Brave Sasuke.
Saotome, you--
-How many times do
I got to tell you?
I don't remember kissing
nobody, all right?
KUNO: Did too!
-Did not!
-Did too.
Did too, did too, did too, did
too, did too, did too, did--
[squealing]
[screaming]
-Did too!
-Hyah!
[sighs]
Hyah!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Oh, man.
They didn't have
to hit me so hard.
I didn't really kiss her, did I?
Oh, no, I can't remember
if I really did kiss her.
She's gonna rip my head off.
Hm?
[meow] [purr] [meow]
[grunting with pain]
SOUN: VO: I didn't know
he had a weak spot.
For Shampoo to know and
still send a cat in the mail
must mean something.
-Mmmm.
Gotcha.
Look!
-Hm?
What?
I don't see anything.
Ah, another one gone?
-Hyah!
Yah!
Hyah!
-Hm?
-Muh-- y-yo.
-R-ranma.
-I'm, uh, sorry.
-You mean you remember?
-Well, uh, not really.
I never remember
when I'm like that.
You know, when-- when I'm a cat.
-I see.
It could been anyone.
Is that what you mean?
-Uh?
Hey, what-- what do you mean,
it could've been anyone?
AKANE: It's true, though.
RANMA: Oh, man, do you really
think I'm that kind of guy?
AKANE: If you're not that kind
of guy, what'd you kiss me for,
then?
RANMA: Well, I, uh--
-You're such a jerk!
-Oh yeah?
-Yeah!
Jerk!
-Oh, is that so?
-Didn't you Here's me?
-Duh.
[smack]
AKANE: Stay away from me, Ranma.
[footsteps running]
-Owww!
[water splashing]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Aw, man, stupid girl.
I was trying to apologize.
So I kissed her, big deal.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I see.
It could've been anyone.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Or maybe it's not
the kiss she's mad about at all.
[meow]
-Mmmm.
[purr] [meow]
-Aaaahhhhh!
[splash]
-Gah!
Aaah!
-Ni hao!
-Sh-- Shampoo!
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
That jerk Ranma.
Didn't have to be me at all.
Could have been anyone.
-H-how did you get in here?
-Ranma, Shampoo so happy!
You know real girl.
You real man after all,
Ranma. [inaudible] me.
-Aw, come on!
-Oh, Ranma.
Shampoo love you, Ranma!
-Aaah!
Stop-- uhhh?
-Huh?
[gasp]
RANMA: That's enough.
I told you, I'm innocent.
I Hanh!
It just looked bad, that's all.
But I'm telling you,
nothing happened.
Hunh!
And that's all I've
got to say about that.
Haah!
Yeah, that's what I'll say.
No bowing and scraping
for me, no way.
I'm a guy.
She's just going to have to
get used to it, that's all.
Yo, Akane.
Hey.
-Huh?
Hi, Ranma.
-Uh-- uh.
Yo, about last
night, you know, I--
-Yes?
What about it?
-Uh, yeah.
You know, Shampoo in
the bath, and, uh--
-Oh, that.
[splash]
-Don't you worry.
I couldn't care less!
-Aaaaahh!
-Yep, she's still uncute.
[gasp]
-Yaaaahhh!
-Aaaaaahhhh!
Now, who are you?
What do you want?
-Well, son-in-law,
you're not half bad.
-Son-in-law?
-We'll meet again. [laughs]
-Where'd she come from?
-Ranma is home?
-Hello, Shampoo.
It's been a long time.
Did you just get in?
-Ni hao.
-They left China
and moved to Japan?
-Yes.
They've opened up a ramen
shop just around the corner.
-Ranma, eat this one!
It's so good!
-Come on, Akane, why
don't you have some?
-No, thanks.
-There's one left.
And we can't just
let it go to waste.
[slurp]
-I'll eat it, dear.
Oh, my.
Please, make yourself at home.
[slurping]
-Hey, it's her, that ghoul!
-Ranma, meet Shampoo
great-grandma!
-Shampoo's told me
the whole story.
Why are you so stubborn
about the marriage?
-About what?
-I'm sorry, about Ranma
is already spoken for.
Ranma will marry my
Akane, and then the two
will carry on the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
It's already been decided.
I'm very sorry.
-3,000 years of Chinese Amazon
history are on the line here.
You'll just have to
break the engagement,
and that's all there is to it.
[frustrated growl]
[smooch]
-Aaahh!
-You speak so well for
someone who just left China.
-Well, I haven't lived 300
years for nothing, you know.
-Wow, and here I wouldn't
have guessed a day over 200.
[laughs]
Yeah, OK.
Whatever, Grandma.
But I ain't marrying Shampoo.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
-Ranma, you come here now!
-Huh?
What are you doing?
Put your clothes back on!
I told you, I'm not interested!
-Stop stupid talking, Ranma!
Aaah!
What you can do
with body like this.
-Huh?
Aaaahhh!
[thud]
[meow]
-Guh.
SHAMPOO: After Shampoo
leave from Japan,
Shampoo come home to China.
-Shampoo, you've broken our
laws by coming home in defeat.
You've brought disgrace
to our Amazon tribe.
It looks like we must
train you all over again.
Prepare yourself.
Haaaah!
-Hyah!
-So many people visit Jusenkyo
this time of the year.
Why do they want to do that?
-Hyaaahhh!
-Hyaaaahh!
SHAMPOO: Aaaaah!
-Oh, too bad.
She fall in Maoniichuan,
spring of drowned cat.
There very tragic legend
of cat what drowned
there 1,800 years ago.
Now whatever fall in
spring take body of cat.
It is very cursed spring!
Such a waste of
beautiful young girl.
[meowing frantically]
-Now you know truth, Ranma.
This is all your fault!
You pay for what you've done.
-Hey, I didn't do
nothing to you!
[clang]
-I hold you responsible
for all of this.
You made her do it.
-I've heard just about
enough outta you!
Uhh?
GRANDMOTHER: Hyah!
-OK, ha--
-Ranma!
-Don't teach Grandma to
suck eggs, sonny boy.
-I'm gonna get her.
GRANDMOTHER: Come on, you can
do better than that. [laughs]
-Get back here!
Now I gotcha-- oof!
-You can't beat 3,000
years of Amazon tradition
just like that, boy.
Now come on, put
some back into it.
Let's go, give me
your best shot!
-Hah!
[grunting and growling]
-Oh, that was very good.
[grunting]
-Hai!
-She's very skilled, isn't she?
-Well, now, future son-in-law,
you can fight after all.
But you won't defeat me.
RANMA: We'll see about that.
Haah!
[both shouting]
[huge splash]
-Son, are you all right?
-[panting] You old ghoul!
-Here's some hot water!
-Here is hot water.
Shampoo here first!
Go ahead, be my guest.
-I'll do it myself.
Where were we?
-Right about here.
-Hey!
-Come and get me, sonny boy!
-Where are you going?
Get back here!
Don't you run away from me!
You fight me fair and square!
-[cackles] Come on, son.
Come on, son,
you're almost there.
Come on!
[cackles]
-Now I gotcha you-- hyaaaah!
Aaaah!
Wh-what's going on?
[cackles]
-How the heck's she doing that?
-Behold, the Amazon Splitting
Cat Hairs technique.
-Aaah!
She split herself into
18 separate illusions!
The legendary Amazon
Splitting Cat Hairs technique,
right before our very eyes.
Oh, to think that I should
live long enough to see it.
[laughs]
-Go, Ranma! [inaudible],
Ranma Go, fight!
Say whose side are
you on, anyway?
-Well, Shampoo love Ranma best.
Ranma!
Beat up Grandmother!
--[chuckles] How
about it, sonny boy?
Do you know which
one's the real me?
[cackles]
-Haah!
Hey!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Which one's real?
[clang]
-Aha!
-Ranma, listen to me, boy.
You can't look at
her with your eyes.
Look at her with your gut.
-OK.
There!
Guess I saw through that one.
-I knew I shouldn't have
fought on an empty stomach.
RANMA: Wait up, you!
Pluhh!
Bleghh!
I'll get you.
[birds calling]
That smart-aleck little punk.
He's about 100 years
too early to defeat me.
RANMA: Yo.
-Huh?
RANMA: Well, Granny, it looks
like the 100 years are up now.
-Oh, I didn't even hear you.
That great-grandchild
knew what she
was doing when she picked
you for her husband.
-I told you, I ain't
marrying nobody.
Now leave me alone.
-Oh, you're adorable when
you're angry, sonny boy.
If you're not
interested in Shampoo,
why not marry me instead?
-Uh-- oh-- I'm sorry, but I--
-Come on, it was
a joke, sonny boy.
No need to look so pale.
[thunderclap]
-What--
-[chuckles] Just wait.
In two or three
days' time, you'll
be begging me for the chance
to become Shampoo's husband.
[laughs]
-Uh-- nnh--
[splashing]
Ow, that's hot!
It's hot!
[splash]
-It's hot!
-Now what are you yelling about?
Wha-- what's wrong?
-The water is boiling!
KASUMI: Did you run
the bath too hot?
That's odd.
It's lukewarm.
-No it's not.
I can't even put
my hand in there!
-Are you sure you're
feeling OK, Ranma?
[laughs]
-Oh, hello.
Come in.
-Aaah, you old ghoul!
--[chuckles] What's
the matter, sonny boy?
Water a little too
hot for you, maybe?
-Uhh.
GRANDMOTHER: The
pressure point I touched
makes your whole body
sensitive as a cat's tongue--
and you know how
sensitive that is.
Listen carefully,
future son-in-law.
From now on even, the most tepid
water will seem boiling to you.
-If that water's too hot--
-Then Ranma can't
change back into a guy.
-Can't change back to a guy?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Can't
change back to a guy?
Can't change back to a guy?
(FRANTICALLY) Can't
change back to a guy?
[groans]
--[laughs] Agree to marry
my great-granddaughter,
and I'll show you
how to change back.
How about it, future son-in-law?
[laughs]
-I'll get you, you old ghoul!
[MUSIC - ETSUKO NISHIO, DON'T
MIND CHINA BOY"]
NARRATOR: What are you
gonna do now, Ranma?
What do you mean, you can't
change back into a boy?
Shampoo's great-grandmother
has the cure?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
behold, the Chestnuts Roasting
on an Open Fire technique.
See you there."