[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
The road to mastering
the secret of the Saotome
School of Anything Goes
Martial Arts seems endless,
and the journey is a lonely one.
But one day, I shall
master all of them.
For this is my destiny!
Ahh!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Legend
of the Lucky Panda.
Ranma, don't you
think it's strange
that no one has seen
your dad in days?
Yeah.
I guess pops disappearing
like that is kind of weird.
It appears there's
been a sighting
of a mysterious village deep
inside the Japanese Alps.
And according to
reports from locals,
the area is almost inaccessible.
But hopefully we will have
a live report from the site
shortly.
Well, well.
What have we here?
An interesting
specimen, for sure.
And once we skin him, he
will make a nice throw rug
for my bedroom floor.
Do not let him get away!
Huh?
Ahh!
If it isn't my sweet
Kana, beautiful as always!
What-- what is it
that you want, Hyato?
My men and I were hunting the
panda that came down the river.
Hey, what would
you say if I were
to give you a tailor-made panda
coat as a birthday present
this year?
The panda came down the river?
Now, if you would be kind
enough to hand him over to me.
I can't do that.
I am the one who found him.
Besides, what are you going
to do with a panda, anyway?
Take him home and
keep him as a pet?
Hm?
Wait.
I have a better idea.
I shall give him to
you as a wedding gift.
What do you think?
Doesn't my brilliance
impress you?
I know it's a silly
question, but-- I just
love it when you tell
me how smart I am.
Hooray!
Please, no!
Hey, Hyato, would
you stop being a jerk?
What the--
Kotaro.
You're interrupting.
If you had a brain in
your head, you buffoon,
you would realize I was just
about to propose to Kana.
Whatever are you talking about?
Attack, faceless minions!
Take him down!
All right!
Bring it on!
This is gonna be fun.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Huh?
You really should
shave your arms.
Excuse me.
I said let's go.
Out of my way, you
overgrown furball!
Ahh!
Ha.
Weakling.
I will let you get
away with it this time.
Kana, soon I will return
to make you my bride.
Haha!
You really should be
a little more careful.
It's dangerous.
Aw.
I didn't know you were
that worried about me.
Hey, cut it out, would ya!
I just saved your
life from that creep.
I didn't come all the way out
here to marry you, you know.
Yeah?
Well, fine!
Because I don't remember
asking you to help me, either!
[grumbling]
Oh, man.
I give up.
I don't care, either,
because it was our parents who
arranged our marriage.
So go ahead and leave.
[thud]
Huh?
Oh, are you all right?
Well, I'd say you made
the right decision coming
straight home, Kana.
I was afraid Hyato and his
men might hurt the panda.
Don't you worry.
That will panda will be
safe and sound here with us.
It's OK.
But aren't you worried
they'll come here looking
for him, honorable father?
You're right.
That is a distinct possibility.
There's an old
saying in our village
that goes something like
this-- should a panda come down
the river to the
village, welcome him,
as he will bring happiness
to the land and its people.
This you have done.
And now we should all
thank him for coming.
And hopefully he will
bring us much happiness.
Come on, Kana.
Snap to it.
What are you waiting for?
Can't you see our honored
guest just ran out of food.
Yes.
Right away.
Well, here you go.
I-- I made it
especially for you.
I guess I used too much salt.
Can I make a suggestion?
I vote we don't let Kana
cook for the family anymore.
Hey, you thief!
Huh?
It's a panda.
What in the world do you
think you're doing, calling
the lucky panda a thief?
You're right.
Ever since the lucky
panda came to the village,
there's been ample rain
after that long drought.
There's going to be a good
crop this yeah, for sure.
Oh, great and wise
panda, please forgive me!
And, if you could
find it in you,
could you give us
a healthy baby boy?
Thank you, Mr. Panda.
You just watch.
KANA: Oh, Mr. Panda!
[laughter]
Here.
Mm-hmm.
What the heck is that
stupid thing supposed to be?
Get lost.
I still don't see
how anyone could
believe that this panda is
gonna bring us good luck.
Just look at him.
Hey!
Back off, fuzzball.
Would you smarten up?
You're scaring Mr. Panda.
I think you're starting
to get a little jealous.
Huh?
Me, jealous?
Yeah, right.
Give me a break, would you?
You are jealous,
and you know it.
RANMA: All I know
is that you need
to get some professional help.
KANA: Oh, Mr. Panda,
your bath is ready.
Oh, there's nothing
to worry about.
Our bath tub's plenty
big enough for you.
Come on.
[grunting]
Here you go.
MAN: Oh my god!
Please come!
The elder!
Huh?
What about him?
[chanting]
Please, you must
tell us how he is.
We figure he won't make it.
No.
I don't believe this.
One minute the picture
of health, and the next,
as helpless as a baby.
Is there anything that
I can do or get him
to make him well again?
You must tell me.
I'll do anything you ask.
I'm begging you to help him.
There is one way to cure him.
Well, tell us.
He must consume the
heart of a living panda.
That is his only
hope of survival.
What?
Have you two lost your minds?
Huh?
Now where did that panda go?
WOMAN: And Kana's gone, too.
After them!
[music playing]
[crowd mumbling]
MAN: What's this?
A reward for a panda?
It says that the owner needs
the panda's heart to live.
We gotta find it.
Oh, this should be interesting.
MAN: You see him?
MAN: Nothing.
How about you?
MAN: Where can it be?
All right.
Let's get 'em, minions.
But sire, how can we find them
this deep in the mountains?
If only there was something
to help us track it.
Hm.
Huh?
Haha!
So, we meet again.
But how did you find us?
Run for it!
Come on, you guys!
Hurry up!
Kotaro!
You go first, Mr. Panda.
Curses!
Hurry up, minions!
Go!
RANMA: Have a nice trip.
Don't forget to write!
Why-- you--
Kana, you realize you can't
stay on the run forever trying
to protect him.
It'll only be a matter of
time until they find you.
But what should I do?
You know.
Huh?
Hey, he took off!
KANA: Mr. Panda, where are you?
Huh?
Oh, no.
Mr. Panda.
Hyato, you hand him
over right now, or else!
Sorry, peasant.
But the heart of
this panda is needed
to cure the elder
of his sickness.
Correct?
So, Kana, how is that
for a wedding gift?
Well, I'm really looking
forward to our wedding.
What about you?
Why, you-- you're just
using the panda to get Kana.
Not if I can help it.
You untie him right
now, you hear?
KANA: Kotaro, don't!
Lay a finger on me,
and the panda perishes.
Not to mention that
Kana's father will die.
Do you want that to happen?
Kataro?
All right.
You win.
I'll marry you.
But you must let him go.
Huh?
Allow me to sacrifice
my heart for yours.
And somehow, when all this
craziness is said and done,
we can find a cure
for my father.
Kana!
I agree.
KANA: Mr. Panda,
you're free to go.
Now, Kana, I expect you to
go home and prepare yourself
for the wedding ceremony.
I must go make
preparations for myself!
Congratulations, master.
Not only are you going to marry
the most beautiful woman in all
the land, but you're also
become the head of the village.
Ha!
My little plan worked
with flawless precision.
Guess again, you jerk.
There ain't gonna be any wedding
bells until you beat me first.
You got it?
Ha!
No matter how crude your
challenge, I accept.
I could use a light
workout before the wedding.
Yaah!
[laugh]
If that's all you can
muster, I'd reconsider.
Why, that little
creep's wearing
armor underneath his clothes.
Kotaro.
Kana!
Ah, I see my bride
has finally arrived.
Oh, she is beautiful.
Isn't she, Kotaro?
Excuse me, my dear,
but I must attend
to your feeble ex-boyfriend's
chivalrous challenge.
Front and center!
Prepare to die!
Huh?
Ahh!
Kotaro!
Stay back, Kana!
You're finished!
What the-- huh?
Mr. Panda.
Ha!
Only a fool would
return to fight me.
Feel the wrath of Hyato!
Come back here, you cretin!
Mr. Panda!
It's time to be rid of
you, once and for all!
[screaming]
You're my hero!
Thank goodness you're OK!
Look, it's Father!
I can't believe my eyes.
You're alive!
Yes.
The doctor figures it
must've been something I ate.
I must admit, I was
a little worried.
But right now I feel like
I'm 20 years younger.
They said you were incurable.
And to think, we went through
all of this for nothing.
I'm sorry.
So don't mind me
asking, but why are
you wearing a wedding dress?
And how come you're
holding hands?
Huh?
Oh, I get it now.
My prayers have
finally been answered.
You two crazy kids have
decided to tie the knot
without telling anyone.
I should have known!
I've never been so happy.
No, it's not--
--like that.
Oh, don't be shy.
Hey, everyone!
This calls for a celebration!
[cheering]
Yeah, congratulations!
This is great!
Mr. Panda?
Mr. Panda!
AKANE: It's starting
to get late.
RANMA: Ah, don't worry, Akane.
He'll be back.
How can you sit there so calm?
Your dad's been
missing for days now.
Hey, for the last time,
don't sweat it, OK?
Gee.
I never never realized
you could be so cold.
Good thing I don't have
any feelings for you.
That goes double for me!
I'm glad I never fell for
such an uncute girl like you!
Well, excuse me
for being uncute!
Pop, you're home.
So when did you get back?
[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
A secret sauce
that Ukyo made 10
years ago turns out
to be a catastrophic failure.
What could this mean to Ranma?
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
Ukyo's Secret Sauce, Part One.
We'll see you there.