[theme music]
THEME SONG: [sung in japanese]
ANNOUNCER (VOICEOVER):
"Gosunkugi's Paper Dolls of Love."
GOSUNKUGI (VOICEOVER):
Several months
ago, I moved to this
town, yet still there is
so much I do not know about it.
But one thing I do
know for certain
is each morning
at precisely 6:30,
my classmate, Akane
Tendo from Furinkan High,
passes this spot
during her morning jog.
Oh, my name is Hikaru
Gosunkugi, and today I've
decided to reveal
the real me to her.
Ah, here she comes now.
[pants]
Good morning, Akane.
Hey!
Hey, Gosunkugi.
[pants]
You know, I run
here every morning.
You do?
Well, so do I.
What a coincidence.
GOSUNKUGI: Yeah.
When I run on a beautiful
morning like this,
I feel like something
wonderful could happen to me.
AKANE: Hey, maybe
I'll see you tomorrow.
GOSUNKUGI: Yeah, probably.
Like I said, I'm
out here every day.
AKANE: I guess
I'll see you then.
[laughing]
GOSUNKUGI: Yeah.
Oh, Akane.
[growls]
Excuse me, you've been
hunkering down in my front yard
the entire night.
How come?
Hey, Akane.
Wait up, Akane.
[pants]
Huh?
She's way too fast.
Akane!
Huh?
[groans]
Hey, pops, did we just
run over something?
Say, did you just
call out my name?
RANMA: No, wasn't me!
GENMA: [grumbles].
Huh?
So who was it?
A-- A-- Akane.
[sighs]
Aw, nuts.
SALESMAN: Uh, pardon me.
Huh?
SALESMAN: Yeah, you.
You know, I've had
my eye on you, boy,
and I feel sorry for you.
So I thought you might be
interested in something
I have that would be
just perfect for you.
Who are you?
Some kind of salesman
or something?
Bingo.
And what I offer
are products that
can solve specific
problems for my clients.
So what do you have
in there for me?
Let's see.
A matching set of
12 paper dolls.
Paper dolls?
May I?
Hm.
Just write a
command on the doll
and put it on the person's back.
And then--
That person is forced into
following that command?
Really?
You got it, kid.
But remember, it will only
work once for each doll
and that's it.
Uh huh.
Hiyah!
[grunting]
[panting]
Well, these dolls better
work or I'm out 5,000 yen.
[whistle]
OK, you're up next, Saotome.
OK.
GOSUNKUGI (VOICEOVER):
That's it.
Go for it, Ranma,
and good luck to you.
Thanks.
[chuckles]
Wow.
Look at him.
[gulps]
[grunts]
Hey, man, sorry about that.
All of sudden, that javelin
seemed to take off on its own.
Hey, be careful.
Who's next?
GOSUNKUGI (VOICEOVER):
Man, that was weird.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
I can't be sure that
those dolls work yet.
[clock chimes]
All right, lunch time.
And man, am I starving.
Hey Gosunkugi, if you don't
get you butt into gear,
there won't be anything
left in the cafeteria.
Uh, what?
Hey, is there something wrong?
No, I'm fine.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY
Well, OK, then.
I guess I'll see you around.
[giggles]
Huh?
[hums]
[pants]
[screams]
[grunts]
Ow , that hurt.
[whimpers]
[crowd chatters]
Oh no.
Is he OK?
Our class modeling
statue got broken again?
[grunts]
Today is not my day.
[laughs nervously]
They-- they really do work.
Akane Tendo, you have been
the one person who I've always
dreamed would notice me.
And today, my dreams
will finally come true.
[pants]
Akane Tendo!
[grunts]
[gulps]
[laughs nervously]
I understand how
you feel, my friend.
Huh?
You do?
En garde!
Huh?
Kuno, just what do you
think you're doing, anyway?
[grunting]
[inaudible], come back here!
How can I take you out
if you don't stand still?
What the?
He-- Hey!
Come here!
Hey, this is a library!
Take this!
And this!
Ow!
And this, and this, and this!
[screams]
[laughs]
Come here!
Hey, you two!
What is going on here?
[groans]
GOSUNKUGI (VOICEOVER):
I finally got away.
Next time, I'm going to have
to be a little more specific
with those paper dolls.
I have to make sure others
aren't around, like Ranma.
Ah!
Hello.
Uh, hi there.
You've got some
explaining to do, jerk.
I-- I do?
About what?
Oh, I think you know, pal.
Hey, just leave me alone.
So what are you hiding there?
Show me!
No.
[whimpers]
Why don't you pick on
somebody your own size?
Just butt out.
[sighs]
I can't believe Akane
came to my rescue.
Hey, this has nothing
to do with you.
Too bad, because I
won't put up with it.
How come you're being
so stupid, stupid?
Speaking of stupid,
look at a mirror!
Um, Akane?
Ranma?
Please calm down.
I have to put the doll
on, so can you not
fight until I-- hey!
You stay out of this.
This is between me and Ranma.
See you later, Akane.
See you!
[groans]
Ah!
[gasps]
Are you OK?
[laughs nervously]
Gosunkugi, I-- I was wondering
if you're free tomorrow.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
[giggles]
Would you like
to go out with me?
Yahoo!
H-- Hey!
AKANE: Where are you going?
What the?
[giggles]
Huh? Now what's
up with the freak?
Ha ha!
I'm so happy.
(SINGING) Akane's
going out with me!
Out with me, out with me!
Ha ha!
There's definitely
something fishy going on.
Akane would never go out on
a date with a certified geek
like Gosunkugi.
(SINGING) Akane's
going out with me!
Tra la la la la.
OK.
It's time to look into this.
A date with Akane?
But where should we go
and whatever should we do?
So, my dear., having fun?
Yes, I am.
GOSUNKUGI: I knew you would.
[laughing]
[GLASS SHATTERS
Akane?
I know.
I'll take her out to the
park in the afternoon.
Oh, Gosunkugi, wait for me?
Why don't you try and
catch me, my sweet?
[laughs]
[sighs]
[laughing]
Oh, look.
Aren't they the most
perfect couple in the world?
They remind me
when I was young.
Oh to be young
and in love again.
[laughing]
[groans]
My-- My Akane.
This is all so perfect.
Honey, I'm home.
[pants]
Oh!
So how was work, sweetheart?
Forget my work.
Mm--
Ooh!
Oh!
[sobs]
Huh?
Hey, what's the matter?
My widdle tummy, it hurts.
Whoa.
OK.
I'll just give you some
stomach medication.
Uh, I need water.
[sighs]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): What a loser.
Um, maybe I should
go rest in the park.
Huh?
Yeah, sure.
But first, why don't I
go get you some water?
But-- That idiot.
I wonder what could
be taking him so long.
Sorry, I couldn't
find a fountain.
Oh, my tummy hurts!
Here you go.
Why, thank you.
[groans]
[screams]
No, no!
I gave her a sleeping pill
instead of the stomach
medication.
[snores]
Huh?
I know.
[yawns]
So, now how are you feeling?
[gasps]
My stomach!
It still hurts.
Man, that was close.
Hm?
What are those?
These?
These are nothing.
Oh, you can tell little old me.
Well, sure, all right.
They're just plain
old paper dolls,
except they're kind of magical.
Magical?
How do they work?
I really shouldn't
say any more.
Please?
You can tell me.
OK.
You write a note on them, and
stick it on a person's back,
and whatever you wrote
is supposed to come true.
Hm.
Huh?
Ahh!
[pants]
Whoa!
He must have stuck one of them
on Akane so she'd ask him out.
Man, that explains it.
Would someone please take
the paper doll off my back?
Hey, what's wrong?
I can't stop my
legs from running.
[pants]
What do you mean you
can't stop running?
All you have to do is tell your
brain to tell your legs to stop
and you'll stop.
It's just that simple.
[pants]
Hey, that's it.
Ahh!
[sighs]
[screams]
Only two dolls left.
(ANGRILY) You jerk.
You bent my front wheel.
Hey, you got a minute?
AKANE: The door's open.
So, what's up?
Uh, it's nothing.
That must be it.
I hope you don't
mind, but I'm studying.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, you just, uh, go ahead
and pretend I'm not here.
Don't mind me.
Hey, Ranma!
[grunts]
Excuse, but if you don't mind,
could you just please leave?
OK, you don't have to get mad.
Geez, I was just trying
to make conversation.
AKANE: What about you?
Aren't you supposed
to be studying?
[door shuts]
What's with him?
[clock ticks]
Oh my, I'm too
nervous about tomorrow.
I've tried everything to try
and make myself fall asleep,
but nothing seems to work.
[snores]
AKANE: Come on, Akane.
Wait up!
I'm late for school.
I gotta tell you something.
There it is, the paper doll.
Slow down, Akane.
Uh, ah!
[groans]
AKANE: See you at school.
[grunts]
OK.
[bell chimes]
[students chattering]
See you later.
I wonder where
Gosunkugi is today.
After all, today
is their big date.
[snores]
Whoa!
Huh.
Huh?
Oh no!
I am so late.
Come on.
Hurry up.
They're waiting for us.
Oh, OK.
I'm coming.
Ah, Akane?
Gosunkugi.
You do realize that
school is over.
Uh, yeah.
Sure.
Hm?
But today is our
date, remember?
Silly, our date is tomorrow.
What?
Tomorrow?
But yesterday you
said it was today.
Huh?
GIRL: Akane, are
you coming or what?
Oh, right.
See you tomorrow, Gosunkugi.
GOSUNKUGI: But--
But-- But-- But Akane!
[sighs]
RANMA: You looking for this?
Huh?
You give me that back.
Come on.
Sorry.
Tell me, are you really as
dumb as you look, Gosunkugi?
What?
What do you mean?
Feast your eyes on this.
You wrote on the doll that she
would go out on a date with you
tomorrow.
You idiot.
Don't you realize
tomorrow never comes?
[whimpers]
No!
She'll never go out with me.
What a freak.
Huh?
Hey.
Wh-- Where are you going!
Ha ha ha ha!
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Yippie!
So now what's he up to?
[gasps]
He's got another
paper doll left.
No!
Wait up!
GOSUNKUGI: I've only got
one chance left with Akane.
[pants]
[gasps]
[baby laughs]
Akane.
Are you all right, dear?
I'm fine.
And look, it's a boy.
That's right.
He's our first son.
Ah, you have made
me the happiest man.
(HIGH PITCHED) I
love you, sweetheart.
Akane, I love you.
[kissing sounds]
(HIGH PITCHED) Oh Gosunkugi,
I hope this moment never ends.
Me too.
[kissing sounds]
I think he's gone
completely nuts?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Hm.
Huh?
Oh no, you can't go.
Wait, I've got
something for you!
Don't do it, Gosunkugi!
Don't do it!
Gosunkugi, don't be so silly.
You're my friend.
Why would I hate you?
Oh, thank goodness.
[laughs nervously]
Oh man, he's plain weird.
GOSUNKUGI (VOICEOVER):
And a few minutes
later, it dawned on
me that I should have
had Akane fall in love with me.
Oh, I'm such a dummy!
[sighs]
[theme music]
THEME SONG: [sung in japanese]
ANNOUNCER (VOICEOVER):
Satori, a mysterious boy
who's supposed to be
able to read minds
decides to come and see Akane.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Akane's Unfathomable Heart."
We'll see you there.