[music playing]
[theme music]
GENMA: It's one deal
you won't want to miss.
Eat as many wild
mushrooms as you want,
receive spiritual training,
and the whole thing is free.
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER): Let's
Go to the Mushroom Temple.
Nothing feels as good
as fresh country air.
Akane Tendo, I know this
is but a ploy to find time
with me in the mountains.
You little vixen.
Sure, whatever.
Akane, you can be my
zen practice partner
for a long, long, long,
long, long, long time.
Yeah.
If it works out that way.
Ranma's going to have
an unfortunate accident
with some poison mushrooms.
[growl]
Maybe you should just
keep it to yourself!
(SINGING) Going
on a mushroom hunt.
Going on a mushroom hunt.
(SINGING) We're going to
have a Mushroom Temple feast.
[humming]
Ready to hit the road?
I reckon.
Huh?
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Could you tell us if this is
the way to the Mushroom Temple?
Huh.
This way, gang.
[humming]
Thanks for your help.
Young and innocent.
Might call it bliss.
Mycologist.
Poison mushrooms.
AKANE: Kuno!
Don't fall behind!
Oh, Akane Tendo!
[inaudible] that these
feet sprout wings of love!
Wow.
Check it out.
Not too shabby.
This plan of Mr.
Saotome's might turn out
to be a good idea in the end.
Look at all these mushrooms!
I wonder if they're edible.
MAN: Some of them are
indeed, but others
are extremely poisonous.
Welcome to this temple.
Tomorrow, a mushroom expert
will bless us with his presence.
We are honored, Your Eminence.
And thank you for
allowing us to stay.
While you're here, be sure
to eat only the mushrooms
the expert has picked.
Didn't you hear what
the Head Priest told us?
[grunt]
I don't think so.
[groan]
(VOICEOVER) There's
just no hope for Ranma.
(VOICEOVER) That'll teach
him for not concentrating.
(VOICEOVER) A sheep
in sheep's clothing.
(VOICEOVER) He doesn't
deserve Shampoo's love.
(VOICEOVER) You can do
better than that, Ranma.
[grunt]
[groan]
[gasp]
[groans]
[groan]
[bell]
[grunts]
AKANE: Ranma.
Huh?
How come you're
practicing so late?
Oh.
Hi, Akane.
What's the problem?
Too quiet for you to sleep?
No.
The stars are just so beautiful,
I didn't want to miss them.
Oh, yeah?
I don't know.
It looks like the
same old sky to me.
Think so?
There you are, my
beloved Akane Tendo!
Kuno, what are you doing?
Your heart's set on seeing
the constellations with me.
[laughter]
Stubborn girl.
Where'd you get that idea?
It seems a serpent
has crossed your path.
Come.
Let's go elsewhere.
[groan]
We shall view the stars
and create memories
that poets can only dream of.
Stop it!
I never said I wanted
to be with you!
Fascinating.
Could you keep it down?
You're interrupting my training.
Go check out the Little
Dipper and leave me in peace,
would you?
Sure.
All right.
[gasp]
Who goes?
MOUSSE: It's impolite to
interfere with other people's
relationships!
Come on, Mousse.
There's nothing special
between her and me.
Yeah!
Quit jumping to stupid
conclusions like that.
It seems you've discovered
my secret relationship
with Akane Tendo.
Now what are you talking about?
Here's your chance.
Run away with Akane now, Ranma.
Then at last, I'll have the
fair Shampoo all to myself.
Nutbar.
Who's there?
Who's siding with Kuno?
Don't make assumptions.
I'm not on anyone's side here.
But Mousse, get it straight.
This is one situation
where I can't
afford to let you
have things your way.
Is that a threat?
[laughter]
Ryoga.
This is getting a
little complicated.
[grunt]
What did I do to deserve
the hardest job of all here?
Wild mushrooms are best savored
when one is tired and hungry.
Has the mushroom expert
arrived yet or what?
MAN: It's from the spirit.
There's a toadstool to be found.
Pick 100 mushrooms, and
leave a hole in the ground.
Pick some mushrooms.
Gather mushrooms.
Which ones will be poison?
They're about done.
[laughter]
Are you sure these
mushrooms aren't poison?
Nothing to worry about.
All right!
Your Eminence.
Oh.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for the food.
Ah.
Hey, get your own soup.
[groan]
Oh, my.
He must have eaten
a poisonous one.
Even expert mycologists
occasionally make mistakes.
On a positive note, we
must give thanks that it
wasn't me who was poisoned.
Why, you callous--
[groan]
Hey, what's the matter, Kuno?
Nabiki.
[groan]
Akane!
No!
Even he's poisoned.
How come we're the only ones
that nothing's happened to?
I don't know.
This isn't good.
She has a fever.
Call a doctor!
There's no time for
that, I'm afraid.
Our only hope at this point
is the large sacred mushroom
god found at the shrine
on top of the mountain.
If you eat a piece, it will
cure any kind of poisoning.
Gotcha.
Let's hurry and
get the antidote.
You must return
before sunset, though.
Otherwise, someone might
be in grave danger.
We'll be back by then.
[groan]
Oh.
How do you feel, my good man?
[laughter]
I'm a mushroom man.
Living on the wild
side's just my nature.
Oh, what am I thinking?
The antidote.
[sigh]
The remedy never fails us.
[groans]
[squawking]
Are you saying that Akane
went to the mountaintop
to get the remedy she
needed to cure me?
No.
Akane Tendo went for
the remedy to cure me.
Oh, no!
Is something the matter?
Your two friends accidentally
ate these mushrooms.
You must be mistaken, my man.
They didn't seem to be poisoned.
No.
I'm sure they ate them.
Man.
Those are good.
Give me one of those.
Hey!
Give that back.
That is good.
The variety they
ate is commonly
known as the mushroom of love.
[gasp]
The mushroom of love?
The man and the
woman who accidentally
ingest these mushrooms
with fall deep in love,
even though they might
otherwise despise one another.
Good news, eh, Saotome?
Tendo, our worries are over.
Oh, right.
Love mushrooms, huh?
It sounds so romantic.
What's the cure for
love mushroom poisoning?
Where's the remedy?
You must go to the
large sacred mushroom
at the shrine on
top of the mountain
and get them to eat
the mushrooms raw.
Otherwise, your two friends
will be deep in love forever.
Then I've got to find that
shrine on the mountain.
I must stop this madness.
Come back here!
Just leave those two alone!
We could use a
wedding around here!
Come back!
What luck.
Mushrooms of love.
Oh, what joy
befalls our family.
And the wedding.
Stop!
Come back here!
Just leave them alone, and
let love run its course!
Farewell, young interloper.
[scream]
Waste of a fine bridge.
Let's get going.
Mhm.
[gasp]
[scream]
Kuno!
[gasp]
[groan]
Ryoga!
Help me before I fall.
Sorry, Kuno, but the clock's
ticking, and I must go.
KUNO: Ryoga!
Oh, all right.
I'll take you along with me.
I don't care what happens.
I'm going to make sure Ranma
and Akane tie the knot.
[sigh]
Hey!
Hm?
Ranma!
Akane!
Wait up!
Akane Tendo!
You both ate the
love mushrooms.
You must take the antidote.
What are those
guys going on about?
I don't know, but it
looks like they all
got over that poisoning.
Hey!
How's Akane's dad and my pop?
Don't you need us to get the
mushroom antidote anymore?
We need it on the double!
Akane Tendo!
Do whatever it takes
to get the antidote!
You hear that?
They still need us to get it.
They must've been
the only ones who
recovered from the poisoning.
We'd better hurry.
Come on.
Let's go, my pretty baby.
Huh?
Sure thing, honey.
Stay out of my way!
My line exactly!
Mousse!
Get out of my-- whoa!
[scream]
No!
Look!
They're holding hands!
I must stop this.
The love mushrooms are starting
to take effect already.
Fly.
Curse the evil fungus that
hath made Akane Tendo double
cross her true love.
Now Akane and Ranma will go
off together and get married.
My wildest dreams
have been realized.
Shampoo will be mine!
Shut up!
Go away!
Just stop--
So you came up from
the Mushroom Temple,
and you're on the way to
the top of the mountain?
Yes.
My dad and sisters
have accidentally
eaten some poison mushrooms
so we need the mushroom god
antidote.
That's a crying shame.
To get to the top
of the mountain,
just turn at the big pine
tree and keep going straight.
Now you'd better hurry along.
Great.
Thanks a lot.
Look at those two lovers.
They seem close.
They certainly do.
How about some
peppermint chamomile tea?
Good idea, honey.
RANMA: Listen, babe.
AKANE: Yeah, honey?
RANMA: After we've gone
back down the mountain--
Yeah, after we've gone back?
After we've gone back
down, will you marry me?
[gasp]
Marry you?
Come on, Akane.
Let's go for it.
What do you say?
Oh, Ranma!
I'm so happy!
Come on.
Let's get back to the others
and not waste any more time.
OK.
MOUSSE: Stop right there!
Huh?
Mousse?
You'll stay here until
the sun's gone down.
What for?
You don't have to worry.
No one's life's at risk.
Now if you'll just throw that
dangerous piece of mushroom--
RANMA: Ryoga!
Hurry and eat that piece of
mushroom before the poison
spreads any further, and
the antidote won't work.
[gasp]
What are you talking about?
Why should we take the antidote?
Yeah, Ryoga.
You're not making any sense.
I can explain it all later.
Enough delay, Ranma Saotome.
I'll personally make sure
you take the mushroom remedy.
Hold on, Kuno!
Listen, Ranma!
Come with me, Akane!
You don't understand, Ranma!
Wait, Akane!
Run like the wind!
Elope if you have to, Ranma!
[groan]
How dare you, Ranma Saotome!
She's my girl!
Stop, Akane!
What has gotten
into those three?
I don't know.
But I am definitely hanging
onto this mushroom antidote.
At least until I see with my
own eyes that Pop and the others
are all right.
Good plan.
[scream]
[groan]
You've got to
listen to me, Ranma.
Hurry and swallow that antidote.
Are you still
going on about that?
This is very serious, Ranma.
I was trying to explain
it to you before.
[groan]
That was too close for comfort.
I think it's time one of you
started explaining things.
All right.
All I've ever wanted was for
you two to be happy together.
And to see you get married
as soon as possible.
Then there's nothing
for you to worry about.
We're getting married as soon as
we get back down the mountain.
Isn't that right, baby?
Oh, honey.
[gasp]
Mousse, you tricked us.
I haven't tricked anyone.
I just need you to
stay here until sunset.
That's all.
Mousse!
You won't be
needing this anymore!
No!
We still need that.
Babe.
Hon.
[groan]
Come on.
Don't!
[scream]
[groan]
Let go of my hand, babe.
I can't, honey.
If you don't, both
of us will fall.
Now take this bag and get Ryoga
to help you back up the cliff.
No way.
I can't do that to you.
We're getting married to
each other, aren't we?
A married couple should
always be together,
even when they die.
If we can't be together in
this life, then at least
we'll be together in heaven.
Baby!
Ranma!
[scream]
Oh.
Them again.
Thank you.
You saved us.
Thanks, mister.
Don't thank me.
I just happened
to be passing by.
Glad you're safe and sound.
You were magnificent, honey.
Thanks, babe!
I'll be home soon!
Huh?
I've made you something
special so you can
find your way back home to me.
Oh, darling, you're the
sweetest little thing.
[sigh]
Pop!
Dad!
Nabiki!
Kasumi!
It's been a long
time and coming.
What a blessing.
Come on, you two.
It's time for a celebration.
[gasp]
You mean, you're all OK?
Everyone here is doing well.
[laughter]
What a joyous occasion.
What a stupendous
occasion for celebration.
Fill her up.
I've got to wash
down those mushrooms.
I'm one proud papa.
Akane, are you sure you
want to go through with this?
Keep quiet, girl.
We're almost at the finish line.
What do you mean, Nabiki?
I guess I'll be calling you
sis from now on, huh, Nabiki?
Yeah, whatever.
How about a little
reality check?
They don't need any reality.
Go ahead, and tell us then.
1,000 yen first.
Hm.
Here you go.
Thank you.
The reason you two
are so deeply in love
is because you both
ate love mushrooms.
You mean, we're in love because
of some poison mushrooms?
You can't just explain
away the feelings
we have for each other
like that, right, honey?
Of course not, my baby.
It's easy to prove that
our love has nothing to do
with some poison mushrooms.
So we'll eat some of
that mushroom antidote.
You can see for yourselves
that our love won't change.
Don't be sure of anything
when it comes to love.
[groan]
[sigh]
It's all over, baby.
And we were so close
this time, honey.
[sigh]
RANMA: Akane!
Take your hands off me!
AKANE: Ditto, buster!
What do you think you're doing?
RANMA: You're the one who's
gotten all touchy feely!
AKANE: Yeah, maybe in a
parallel universe or something!
RANMA: I don't think so!
Hey, look.
The first star in the sky.
You're right, Nabiki.
MOUSSE: Akane, hurry!
Run away with Ranma!
Don't listen to him!
You must take the antidote!
The antidote,
it's our only hope.
Why don't you listen to me?
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER): Everyone knows
that day would eventually come.
The day the child
surpasses the parent.
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
The Cradle from Hell.
We'll see you there.