Meet Ranma Saotome
of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hey, let go!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
The two have been engaged to
marry by their loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause of
poor Ranma's suffering, when
Ranma is splashed with cold
water, he becomes a she.
NARRATOR 2: Close Call!
The Dance of Death on Ice
-For the first time in
my life, I'm really mad!
How about it?
Let's fight, or are you
just going to stand there?
-I don't know what your
grievance is with me,
but damaging the rink
is a serious crime.
I accept your challenge.
Come on.
-I'm going to make you sorry
you were ever born pal.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
(WORRIED) Ranma.
-Hey, Mikado!
For humiliating
me like that, I'm
going to pay you back
a thousand times over.
[screaming]
[explosion]
-Ranma!
[laughter]
-Wow, that was one
major league head-butt.
-Idiot.
Only a fool would attempt
to launch a suicide
strike against his opponents
so early in a battle.
How-- How did you get up?
Hm.
You do have some fight in you.
I regret using non-amateur, but
I see you left me no choice.
Now, behold The Dance of Death.
-Woah!
The Dance of Death, we hardly
ever get to see him do that.
-You don't impress
me you big jerk.
AKANE: 118.
119.
120.
121.
122.
123.
-No one's ever broken
free of that spin before.
AKANE: 41.
501.
-What an athlete!
-Ranma, can you stand up?
-I guess Mikado won the match.
-Nope, afraid
Ranma won that one.
-Huh?
Ah, you're right!
He's fainted!
Let's doodle on him!
Doodly-doo Doodly-doo.
-Hey, man I want to doodle too!
-Let me draw some!
RANMA: Ow!
-Oh, honestly Ranma, did you
really have to him 501 times
to win that fight?
-(ANGRILY) Quiet!
After what that jerk did to
me, why why he got off lucky!
-Oh my!
What did he do to you?
Huh?
Uh nothing.
RYOGA: Look at you Ranma.
You're a mess.
-Hm?
-Ryoga?
-You know, I would never have
let such a thing happen to me.
-Shut up man!
If it weren't for
those dumb skates,
I never would have been--
-Oh?
Never what?
Been kissed?
Hm?
-Ranma were you kissed?
-So who did the dirty deed?
-Well, at least he was
a good-looking rascal,
wasn't he Ranma?
-Why you!
-(SHOCKED) It was a guy!
-Oh, you're worrying
over nothing.
-Yeah, it doesn't even count if
you get kissed by another guy.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Aw man.
Now, they're all
making fun of me.
Nobody cares how I feel.
AKANE: You're wide open, right?
Pay attention!
Oh, honestly, aren't
you finished pouting.
And here you call
yourself a guy.
-Oh go ahead and laugh
at me if you want.
Hey, what are you laughing at?
-Oh nothing.
-Well, for one thing--
-Well, for one thing, it's your
own fault that he kissed you.
You got to realize you left
yourself wide open Ranma.
-And I suppose you think you
could have done better, huh?
-Of course I could've.
Huh?
-Well, look who's talking!
Ew!
Hey, look!
Relax Akane.
It wasn't like I was
going to try and kiss you
or anything I mean.
I wouldn't.
-Huh?
Well, I wasn't worried.
I know you don't have
the guts to do something
like that anyway.
-Oh yeah?
Well, you keep talking like
that, maybe I just might.
-Oh yeah?
You just go ahead
and try it Ranma!
-You sure?
-Well, sure.
I dare you to do it
if you think you can.
-OK.
I'll do it, but only
because you told me.
Close your eyes.
-OK.
Um, shouldn't you kind
of like save this stuff
for you know like the people
that you really like and stuff
like that you know?
-I see!
I'm not good enough
for you is that it.
-(ANGRILY) Akane,
that's not what I meant!
I I just meant that if you
don't mind, then I don't mind.
You know what I mean?
Hm?
[screaming]
-Come on!
We don't have all day.
Are you going to do
it, or aren't you?
We don't have all day.
-(SADLY) Oh Ranma, Ranma.
Ranma.
MIKADO: (BITTERLY)
Ranma Saotome,
you, you did this to me, me the
pride of the high school figure
skating world.
No one makes a fool
of me and lives.
The day of our match,
five days from now,
will be the day you die!
-Francoise, tomorrow is the
day Charlotte comes home
to live with us
forever and ever.
You're waiting for Charlotte
too, aren't you Francoise?
Good girl!
Katherine, you'll be
cheering Azusa on, won't you?
Sweet dreams Katherine!
Sweet dreams now Antoinette!
Sweet dreams Marlene!
Sweet dreams Michele!
Sweet dreams Felicia!
Sweet dreams Georgina!
Sweet dreams Rosalie!
Sweet dreams Elizabeth!
Sweet dreams Angeline!
Sweet dreams Marianne!
Sweet dreams Jeanette!
Sweet dreams Delphine!
Good morning Delphine.
Good morning Jeanette.
Good morning Marianne.
Good morning Angeline.
Good morning Elizabeth!
Good morning Rosalie!
Good morning Georgina.
Good morning Felicia.
Good morning Michele.
Good morning Marlene.
And good morning Antoinette.
ROBES-PIERRE: It's almost time
to leave for the competition
Miss Azusa.
-Good morning Robes-Piere!
[chatter]
-I made it!
Good thing I gave myself
five days to get here.
No matter what it
takes, I'm going
to be the one to
pair up with Akane.
Me!
Rama!
-Hey Charlotte, what are you
doing around this part of town?
-No you don't!
-Don't worry Charlotte, me
and Akane will be just fine.
You just sit back and
enjoy the show, OK?
-The natural look
is the real me.
[humming]
Hm?
Mr. Saotome, you
finally made it.
-Yo, MIkado the
Molester, how's it going?
-Uh!
That's Sanzenin, you idiot.
-Your boo-boo's all better now?
-I merely let my guard
down for a moment.
That's all.
The real match will
be a different story.
Your charming
partner, Akane Tendo.
Isn't that her name?
-Mhm.
-I still haven't given your
partner my special greeting.
-Greeting?
-The girl hasn't
been born that hasn't
welcomed my special greeting.
-Your greeting?
You don't mean--
-One more.
One more and I shall
have kissed 1,000 girls,
each one more gorgeous
than the last.
-No you don't!
-You will hear me out.
Sometime during today's
match, I shall surely
steal a kiss from the
lips of Akane Tendo.
-A man, don't you ever
think of anything else
than trying to kiss girls?
-Well, what else is there
worth thinking about?
-Geez, this guy's scary.
[sneezing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
I never believed
that bit about sneezing when
somebody gossiped about you,
but now.
-Ladies and gentlemen, welcome
to the first annual Charlotte
Cup, the Anything Goes martial
arts figure skating fight
to the finish to determine,
once and for all,
who owns the pig
known as Charlotte.
And now let me introduce
our competitors.
Representing Kolkhoz
High in the Charlotte Cup
is the Golden Pair, the
undefeated Emperor Senzanin
and, his lovely consort for the
light folk, Azusa Shiratori.
-Chant it!
-Azusa!
Azusa!
-Hm, look at those lousy
showoffs out there.
Well, come on Akane.
They won't forget about us.
-And here for Furinkan High is
Ranma Saotome and Akane Tendo.
-OK.
That's enough.
-You know, we
haven't even started,
and Charlotte is
practically Azusa's already.
-Oh, no.
There's now way I'm
letting Pee-chan go.
-And there's the bell.
The battle for the
pet black pig begins.
Remember this is
a no holds barred,
single match competition people.
-Come on Ranma!
Winners strike first,
and we're going to win.
-May I say you're looking
very lovely today?
-Woah, Emperor
Zensanin wastes no time
in launching his
famous kiss attack.
-Oh no you don't.
-Ranma, look!
-Huh?
-He's such a nuisance.
-So are you!
-Imagine refusing
my kiss like that.
She must be very shy.
-Maybe you just make her sick.
Come on Ranma, hang in there.
The match has just started.
-Now, Akane brace yourself.
I will have my kiss.
-Akane, get ready to fly.
-(SCARED) Look out!
The fence!
-I can't stop!
-Mickey, does him hurt here?
Huh?
Here?
-Yes, it hurts.
It hurts, I said.
I told you it hurts!
Stop hitting me there
you silly witch!
-But Azusa was only worried.
-It is rare that I'm
ever brought to my knees.
You will regret it.
-You pull that junk
with Akane again
and I'm going to do more
than bring you to your knees.
-Oh really?
Such as?
-Such as putting your
Lady Killing butt
straight into a coffin.
Got it?
Akane is my fiance.
You touch her and I'll kill you.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
I don't believe it.
In front of all these people.
-Fiance's aren't forever.
I, Mikado Sanzenin, will take
it as a personal challenge
to break those ties.
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): What can we
do to defeat the Goodbye Whirl?
Can it even be done?
Hey, what's Ryoga doing here?
Next time, on
Ranma 1/2, Pee-chan
Explodes, The Icy
Fountain of Love.
See you there.