[theme music]
-Ayeya.
Honorable grandmother
is still alive.
Even Chinese medicine
can't work miracles.
Be that as it may, what
miracles can I sell you today?
-Your last so-called
miracle gave me
arthritis for nearly a week.
You'll forgive me
if I'm suspicious.
-True, true.
It wasn't what you wanted, but
you asked for canned arthritis,
so I sold it to you.
What you needed was
canned arthritis cure.
Well, I'd like to buy
some of that then, please.
-Oh, well, why
didn't you say so?
-What's this?
-I just love a curious consumer.
That's the Red Thread of Fate.
-Red Thread of Fate?
Tie one end to
yourself, and the other
on the pinky of a loved
one, and within five hours
you'll be bound for life.
-Shampoo take this one, please.
ANNOUNCER: Shampoo's
Red Thread of Dread.
[snoring]
-You thank Shampoo later.
-Ranma, I-- well, since
you're already here,
what don't you let him
know he can borrow this?
-[inaudible].
-Akane.
-Hmm?
-Do you always
got to be throwing
the book at guys you don't like?
Huh?
-No, only at you.
-Now what'd I do?
Come here you
little-- Cut it out.
Why I'm gonna-- quit it!
-Hiya.
[inaudible]
-Hey, are you OK up there?
What's that red thread?
Shampoo.
-Nihau, Runma.
Runma, you play cat's
cradle with Shampoo?
-Uh, ain't you a little
old for that stuff?
-Shampoo let's you
have all you can
eat for free at Cat Cafe
for entire week, Runma.
-Cat's cradle?
Why didn't you say so?
-Oh, I see.
So that's what you're into.
-Uh, look, Akane, it's
not what you think.
-It's not, huh?
Then you won't mind this.
Girls are less trouble anyway.
-What'd you do that for, huh?
-Because you're making
a big scene, that's why.
-I'm making a big scene, am I?
Hey, Shampoo, why are you
tying that thread to my finger?
I said, why are you--
-Hmm?
Now we make wedding plan.
-Wedding plans?
-Well, that's true.
The sooner I'm married to you,
the sooner I'm rid of her.
-Excuse me?
At last, Ranma know what
Shampoo feel all this time.
-I'll be.
Will you finally be my
son-in-law for real?
-Yes.
And I must insist that
you move in with us
once Shampoo and I
are happily married.
-You're not so bad after all.
-Well, then, let's decide
on a day then, shall we?
-I'm for a chapel
wedding myself.
-Shampoo agree.
-Have it your way.
-He what?
Ranma engaged to marry Shampoo?
Saotome, what is
the meaning of this?
You didn't go and make
a deal for free food
the Cat Cafe again, did you?
Did you?
-Do I look like that kind
of man to you, Tendo?
-You do.
-Say it isn't so.
-It's so.
Ranma.
What is the meaning of this?
-Aho, you mean this?
It's the sign of affection.
-Sign of-- and what's your
answer to that, Saotome?
Aah.
Thanks a ton.
-Oh, and Mr. Tendo,
may I ask you a favor?
-Sure, why not?
-Please help cancel my
engagement to Akane.
-Now the last obstacle
to wedding is gone,
Shampoo's so happy.
-Well, no one asked me
if I wanted to marry her.
Besides, she's not
the one I love.
You are.
-Akane.
-But it's got nothing
to do with me, Dad.
-That's here you'd
be wrong, young lady.
Ranma is serious about this.
-Serious or not,
Dad, I'm not the one
who got him into this mess.
He is.
-I won't pressure you
if that's how you feel.
But you are still his fiancee.
-Dad, I don't want to
hurt your feelings,
but you're just not getting it.
We never asked for an
arranged marriage, OK?
That was all our
father's dumb idea.
-I want you to
talk him out of it.
Even if you have to get
on your knees and beg.
-Knees and beg?
-Strike that.
I take it back.
Use any approach
you like, so long
as you get him to break
up with that Shampoo.
One way or the
other, Daddy swears
that he will come back to you.
-I'm leaving.
-Akane.
Akane.
-You're such a cutie.
-Shampoo happiness complete.
-It's not really like
I care or anything,
but isn't he over doing it?
-Perhaps, it's inevitable.
-I can't believe you said that.
-They are bound by the Red
Thread of Fate, aren't they?
-Good grief.
You don't believe that
corny story, do you?
-Isn't there, though?
-What?
-This one nothing, OK?
-Very interesting.
So it's nothing, huh?
-It's got nothing to do with me.
Hiya!
Let's go, P-chan.
-They're what?
Since when are Ranma and Shampoo
suddenly engaged to each other?
-Make me a shrimp
one next, will you?
-I'll make you shrimp,
squid, and octopus
if you tell me how she
got her hooks into him.
-OK.
Don't quote me on it, but she
used some kind of red thread.
-The Red Thread of Fate?
Starts here and
ends on this finger?
They're supposed
to be invisible.
-Hey, I saw it with
my own eyes, OK?
Shampoo's got him under
some kind of spell,
and that's all I
have to say about it.
-Oh, that is so like
the little witch.
-When did you get here?
-I've lived on table
scraps for a year now.
Who knows how far this
information might take me.
Farewell.
-Ha!
Let's see how that red
thread holds up to this.
Ranma Saotome.
-What the--
-Ranma, darling,
surely you jest.
You should know by now
how jealous I can be.
-Better dead than wed.
That's our motto.
-Molest not the union
of Ranma and Shampoo.
-Cry baby.
-I'm not.
Oh, brother, dear, it's
so pathetically obvious.
-What is?
-By protecting their
illicit liaison,
you hope to win Akane
Tendo for yourself.
Isn't that right, brother, dear?
-Woman, enough!
-You dang, stubborn mule.
-I intend to keep you
from severing this Red
Thread of Fate, and
you can't stop me.
-Oh, you are, are you?
No.
-Child's play.
No fair, that's cheating.
-There's no time to waste.
-Come back.
-Only three more hours till
red thread lasts forever.
-Hey, can we keep
running, honey-bunny?
-As long as we stay
together, Shampoo
run with Ranma anywhere.
-Huh?
-You said it.
-Ready or not, the
thread's coming off!
-Now they're all involved.
-Akane Tendo.
What say you to a
double wedding ceremony
with your former fiance?
-What do you say to this?
Ranma will do just
fine without me.
Let him have his own wedding.
(SIGH)
It's like a bad
dream I can't wake up from.
-It's no dream.
-Dad, the next time
you want to come in,
would you please knock?
-This is an emergency, Akane.
Look at the invitation that
arrived in the mail for you
today.
-What?
In celebration of their
love, Ranma and Shampoo
invite you to their--
Ah, what a pity.
Send them my regrets.
-You do realize that
once they're married,
there's no going
back, don't you?
You're sure that's
what you want?
-Look, what I want
doesn't matter, does it?
Nobody's forcing
Ranma into marriage.
-Maybe, maybe not.
-Huh?
It looks as though
Kasumi's theory might not
be that far off after all.
-What theory?
-That Shampoo's using some
hokey red thread trick
to tie him to her.
-I knew it.
-Yeah, right.
-Fine, don't believe me.
But don't come crying to me
once it's too late to stop it.
-It is her usual kind of
trick come to think of it.
-A red thread?
Huh?
Right, that's it!
That's when she--
-Akane?
-Huh?
-That thread should be
cut by your own hand.
-Since when am I his babysitter?
-So you don't mind if
he marries her then?
-Oh, come on Akane,
give the dope a break.
Besides, it's not his fault.
It's the thread.
-Go away, will you?
I've still got my
homework to do.
P-chan?
-No one hurts Akane
when I'm around.
When I'm around, that
is, which isn't often.
-My, aren't you beautiful?
-Did you make whole new dress
for Shampoo, great Grandmother?
-Actually, I was planning
to wear it at my own,
uh, uh-- I'm glad
someone gets to use it.
-Is you happy, Ranma?
-More than I can say, Shampoo.
-Shampoo's so glad.
-Ranma, she's tricking you.
-Don't believe
his lies, Shampoo.
-You back off, Mousse.
-Why won't you two accept
that we're in love?
-Ranma, honey-- and there it is.
Then I guess there's nothing
we can say to stop you.
d can come wedding if you like.
-Thanks, I will.
-Ah, stupid witch.
-Huh?
How did you and I-- hey,
is this some kind of joke?
-Ranma, honey, you're back.
-Red thread bow, Kudo style.
-Huh?
Come on.
Let's go be alone, Shampoo.
-Brother, dear, how could you?
-I tell you this
wedding will go on.
-That's what you think.
-Go, with my blessing.
-Ranma.
-Huh?
Ryouga?
-What you doing here?
-If you think I'm going
to let you hurt Akane,
think again, jerk.
-Put it back.
-No can do.
So this is the red thread?
-Am I missing something here?
-Ryouga, give
thread and go home.
-Like I said, no can do.
-But Ryouga, if
Ranma marry Shampoo,
then you get Akane
all to ownself.
-What?
I'm so happy.
-Me, too.
-That's right.
Wait.
If I let her marry him,
Akane will never forgive me.
But if I don't, Akane and Ranma
will-- oh, what should I do?
-Hand over.
-50 more minutes.
Not that I'm watching
the clock or anything.
Hmm?
Hmph.
VOICEOVERS: Oh, yeah.
-Huh?
What do I care who he--
VOICEOVERS: Congratulations.
Congratulations.
VOICEOVERS: I wish you the best.
My son in law at last.
-Oh, that's just what you'd
like me to do, isn't it Ranma?
Just sit back and take it.
-So what do we do now, Saotome?
-We take charge of the
situation, that's what.
-You said it.
-I sure did.
-Are you sure you want to
risk ticking him off, though?
I mean, what if he decides to
abandon you in your old age?
-True.
The girl has a point.
-Saotome, help, how could you?
-Let us through.
-Don't be such a poor loser.
Why not be happy for
your former fiance?
-Because it's not me he's
marrying, that's why?
Besides, it's not
even real love.
It's fake.
-For now, maybe.
But come 5 o'clock,
it'll be a moot point.
-So what happens at 5 o'clock?
-The thread falls off, and
their love becomes real.
-Excuse me?
-Upsy daisy.
-Oh, why you.
-Have you no witness?
-Huh?
Shampoo thought she
send invitation.
Is OK, no witness, Ranma?
-You're the only one
I'll ever need, honey.
-Ranma, you Shampoo
dream come true.
-Uh-hem.
May we?
-Soon, Ranma belong
only Shampoo.
-Just a sec.
-Hmm, Akane.
Why you try stop us?
-I'm here to help
you, not stop you.
-And Akane no mind that
witness to wedding.
-Just try and stop me.
-How kind.
I insist that you come and visit
with us once we're married,
Akane.
-You bet I will.
-Just minute more.
-Your bouquet.
-You tricked me.
-Did you really think
that I wouldn't?
-Huh?
Where am I?
-Hmm.
-Ranma.
-Huh, what did I do now?
-Prepare to die.
-Come on you guys, cut it out.
Show a little respect.
Church.
So then you understand?
-Sure, Ranma, we understand.
-Well, OK then.
Come on, Akane, let's
get out of here.
-Good idea.
-Fine, then, run away.
-So tell me, what reason do
we got to run away for, huh?
-Good point.
-I don't get it.
Now what'd I do?
-Think about it.
-But-- but I--
[theme music]
-You're not really going back
to China, are you, Mousse?
You're what?
Giving up Shampoo to Ranma?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Mousse goes home to the country.
We'll see you there.