[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): "The
Killer From Jusenkyo."
CHAIRMAN: Moving on to the
next order of business,
I see Jusenkyo visitors
has gone up again.
Why, I heard the
number of those who'd
fallen into the cursed
springs is at 144 persons.
I know we've all been
under a lot of pressure.
But gentlemen, our
heaviest season
is just around the corner.
And if we're going to do
something about this problem,
we got to do it now!
-Mr. Chairman.
-Yes, Vice Chairman?
-I'm ready to make my report.
The following five
miscreants have flagrantly
violated our Jusenkyo
code of conduct.
This one has violated
the code of modesty,
abusing his ability
to transform--
VICE CHAIRMAN (VOICEOVER):
--and wantonly
exposing himself at the
slightest opportunity.
He must be punished.
VICE CHAIRMAN: This
one has violated--
VICE CHAIRMAN (VOICEOVER):
--the code of public safety,
threatening the
health and well-being
of innocent bystanders.
He, too, must be
dealt with harshly.
VICE CHAIRMAN: This
one's violated the code
of self-gratification--
VICE CHAIRMAN (VOICEOVER):
--using a Jusenkyo ability
as a means for
personal retribution.
VICE CHAIRMAN: This one's
up for duplicitous--
VICE CHAIRMAN
(VOICEOVER): --conduct,
sneaking into the bed
chambers of innocent maidens.
VICE CHAIRMAN: And
this one's violated--
VICE CHAIRMAN (VOICEOVER):
--the code of fair play with his
unsportsmanlike conduct and--
VICE CHAIRMAN:
--murderous intent.
If we don't make an
example out of them,
how will we enforce discipline?
We mustn't forget our mission.
We mustn't forget
our sacred duty.
We must never,
ever, never forget!
TOGETHER: Never forget.
If we forget,
strike us down dead.
Never forget!
Huh?
-Never forget.
Let me punish 'em.
-Heh-heh.
Actually, we were
hoping you'd say that.
The method is left
to you, Kinnii.
But you must stop them
from abusing their Jusenkyo
transformation powers.
-They'll learn to control
themselves or else.
Rrargh!
Hyah!
[chuckling]
-If it weren't for that
one weak spot of his,
he'd really be
perfect for the job.
-Uh, yeah.
Almost forgot.
Chairman, perhaps we
should also accompany him.
-[quacking and smooching]
-Shampoo too busy to
play with you now.
Go home.
Aah!
What you doing?
-Come along quietly.
-[meowing]
-Two down and three left to go.
RYOGA: Oh, great.
How am I ever going to find
my way out of this one?
Huh?
[blast]
Aah!
At least let me have
my dinner first.
-Your crime can't be
solved with hot water.
-[squealing]
VICE CHAIRMAN: Make that
three down and two left to go.
[distant howling]
-Huh?
Someone's following me.
That's funny.
-If it's so funny, then
why don't you laugh?
-Yes.
Why didn't I think of that?
[sarcastic laugh]
It's not that kind of funny!
-Those two may be a
little harder to subdue.
-What's wrong?
-I'm convinced that someone
out there is trying to kill me,
boy.
You wouldn't have
an appetite either.
-So are you going to
tell us what you've done,
or do we have to guess?
-I'm warning you, Saotome.
If you've been out deceiving
young girls again--
NABIKI: Don't worry, Daddy.
The only young
girls he could fool
are the ones who take
their teeth out at bedtime.
-That's rude, Nabiki.
-(MOCKINGLY) Sorry.
-False teeth are not
something to joke about.
-[laughing]
Good one, Kasumi.
[laughing]
-[clears throat]
Ranma, please boy.
You got to be my bodyguard.
-Grow up, Pop.
-What if someone really is
trying to kill him, Ranma?
Shouldn't you help him?
-Ha.
If you're so worried
about him, then why
don't you be his bodyguard?
-Ranma.
-(BLANDLY) That's OK.
I understand.
-Genma, behind you!
There's some lint
on your shoulder.
-[groans]
-[laughs]
-Cut it out, already.
-I'm going to bed.
Aah!
Aah, monster!
[knocking]
(PANTING) OK.
OK.
-Shampoo and Mumu
the duck are missing?
-[slurps]
Well, they went
out on the delivery
and haven't been back since.
And here I was hoping that
she and the future son-in-law
here had run off
together in elope too.
-Aah!
You wish!
-Having Genma as
your father makes
you capable of just
about anything.
-What?
What are you looking at me for?
I tell you I didn't do nothing.
[genma screaming]
-Can't be.
Pop!
Oh, Pop, are you--
there's something
blocking the other side.
Where'd he go?
-Ranma, over there!
-[laughing maniacally]
-Come back!
Come back.
-And what was that?
-Now, this is interesting.
Where have I seen
that sword before?
If I didn't know
better, I'd suspect
the Cult of the Muscle
Sword was involved.
-Wow.
Cult of the Muscle Sword, huh?
I've never heard of them.
-Are they new?
-The Cult of the
Muscle Sword is one
of China's most
ancient disciplines.
By treating their swords
as part of their bodies,
they become almost invisible.
-Huh?
And what's this?
An armband?
-[gasps]
Yes, it is.
This means the secret
Jusenkyo Preservation
Society's involved.
-Preservation Society?
-So how come we never
heard of them, then?
-Because they're a
secret society, stupid.
Nobody knows what
their true purpose is.
All I know was
that if you violate
their so-called
Jusenkyo code, they
come after you,
maybe even kill you.
-[gasps]
-Oh, poor Mr. Saotome.
I hope he's all right.
-Can't they just let him
off with the warning?
-What do you know?
Guess they old guy needed
a bodyguard after all.
-Better hope he's not
the vengeful type.
I'd hate to have a visiting
beef from the other side.
-Come on.
Cut it out.
-Oh, Saotome.
-I have a feeling Shampoo and
that bird brain, Mumu the Duck,
have fallen into
their hands as well.
-What are we gonna do?
We've got to help them.
-And I know just the
way to save them.
Ranma, you shut up
and come with me.
-Then I'm coming too.
-Yeah, right.
"You shut up and come
with me," he says.
-Here.
Let me give you a
hand with those.
-Back off!
Say you, how do I know
this isn't some plan
to get me to steal some
girl's gym short for ya, huh?
-Oh, they'll come, all right.
If there's one thing those
jerks from Jusenkyo can't stand,
it's someone who violates
their cold of decency, morals,
and ethics.
-Who, like you?
-Hey, have a little
faith, will ya?
-That getup you're
wearing doesn't exactly
inspire confidence.
-Huh?
What-- what?
You're saying you don't
like my work clothes?
-What I'm saying is
that I'm sorry I ever
listened to you in
the first place.
Ranma, come on.
We can think of some
better plan on our own.
-Yeah, no kidding.
Say, you wouldn't be
from Jusenkyo, would you?
-So there.
Maybe next time
you'll believe what
your elders are telling you.
Good luck, you two.
Got to go.
-Hey, wait a minute.
Put those gym shorts--
VICE CHAIRMAN: Don't move.
One, abusing the
ability to transform
is grounds for punishment.
Two, endangering
others with disability
is grounds for punishment.
Three, breaking either
rule number one or two
is also grounds for punishment.
-Enough with the rules.
He's broken them all anyway.
-Let me punish him.
-No, don't.
-Ranma!
-No!
No, don't do it!
Oh.
-OK, you.
Huh?
-What just happened?
KINNII: Oh, who has done
this dreadful thing?
-You did it, stupid.
-I did this?
Buildings are made
out of wood, and wood
is made out of living trees.
We must let the tree
know how much we
appreciate its sacrifice.
-What's with him?
-The one weak spot in an
otherwise perfect warrior.
-Weak spot?
-That's right.
Once while he was
training in Jusenkyo,
Kinnii slipped and fell
into a cursed spring.
VICE CHAIRMAN
(VOICEOVER): There's
a legend which
says 999 years ago,
a young priest drowned in a
spring called Fushaniichuan.
-Now anyone who falls
into that spring
takes the body of
a young priest.
Tragic story.
-Huh?
Hey, wait a minute.
Doesn't that mean he's
breaking your dumb code too?
-But priests are good for
society, not incentives
from moral turpitude.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-I'm against violent-- aah!
-Oh.
Oh, how dreadful.
Doesn't he know that buildings
come from wood and wood
comes from living trees.
Oh, we must thank the wood--
-Stop thanking the dumb trees
and help me find my father.
-Father?
-You, know, the big jerk
who turns into a panda.
-Aah!
I've done a dreadful thing.
A dreadful thing.
Oh, please let me
take you to him.
-Do you mean you'll help us?
KINNII (VOICEOVER):
Of course I will.
It's the very least I could do.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): This
place you're taking us
to-- it's not in China, is it?
KINNII (VOICEOVER): Heavens no.
It's in Japan, but it's
just a little far from here.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
I hope he's OK.
Hand in there, Pop.
Hang in there.
I'm coming for you.
-[snoring]
Whoa!
Bleh.
[snoring]
[blathering]
[groaning]
[snoring]
-Sleeping again, huh?
Gee, that's too bad.
Guess you can't have this.
-[blathering]
-Suppressing the body's
appetite is another part
of the training you must learn.
Ooh, ow!
Hey, who did that?
How did that?
-What's that you
said about training?
-(STAMMERING) I-- I've
got to use the facilities.
-Oh, you poor dumb beast.
Let me set you free.
-[blathering]
-Oh, come on, Pop.
Get off of me.
Get--
[shampoo meowing]
Huh?
That's Shampoo.
-[blathers]
-No, you don't, Pop.
Not till we save them too.
You got the key?
KINNII: Here.
-I'm coming, Shampoo!
-Be careful.
It's dark in there.
VICE CHAIRMAN: Kinnii!
-Yes?
-Kinnii, remember your duty.
Remember.
-So the ingrates escaped, huh?
-Meow.
--[yells] D-don't
come any closer.
[meowing and quacking]
Huh?
So they got you guys too.
-[blathering]
Aah.
[yelling]
-[kinnii laughing]
Thought you got away
from me, didn't you?
Payback time!
-Just a minute.
Let me do this first.
-[pants]
Hey, you turned back to
that other guy again.
-Ain't you bright?
[grunting fiercely]
[laughs]
-We'll start the
training with you.
-Put me down!
Oh, what are you doing?
-Training you not to transform
into a panda even when wet.
-But that's ridiculous.
It's a curse, not something
I can turn on and off.
-Or maybe it's all in your mind.
-Whoa!
Whah!
Bleh.
-This one's stubborn.
-I knew I'd turn into a panda.
Your so-called
training-- it's a lie.
-It's all in your
mind, I told you.
-Yah!
-I said it's all in your mind.
-Bwah!
[groaning and screaming]
Pop?
I hear something.
[yells]
-All right.
You're coming with me.
-Why?
You're treating us all to
Chinese food or something?
Gee, in the meantime,
maybe yourself
would like to eat this!
Run for it, you guys!
[grunting]
-I'll catch those
little ones later.
Do what I say or stand in the
line for the panda, got it?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): [sighs]
I've got no choice.
-What have you done to him?
-Just doing my job.
Nothing personal.
-Job?
-That's right.
Now get into that water
and turn into a girl.
-Girl?
But I don't-- aah!
Gee, Pop.
I don't know.
What's it look like to you?
VICE CHAIRMAN: You're as
stubborn as the other one.
-Well, what do you jerks expect?
VICE CHAIRMAN: Don't you know
that it's all in your mind?
-That's hot!
-Do him again.
-[yells]
[gasps]
-Why is this one
being so stubborn?
-I don't know, mean-head.
Why don't you tell me?
[snickering]
Ooh, please save me, sir.
-Oh, oh.
What a dreadful
thing I have done.
VICE CHAIRMAN: Oh, no you don't.
-No, don't let him get you wet.
-Now, what were you just saying?
-[ranma screams]
That's it.
-I'll train the two of
yous at the same time.
-Stop it.
You can't just play
with people like this.
Can't you see it's
not doing any good?
-Let me be the judge of that.
Huh?
[grunting]
-Cut it out!
-[grunting]
Help me!
-No more Mr. Nice Guy.
-I'm free.
Now, if I could just
get this knot untied.
-Stop that!
[grunting]
-[chuckles]
-Why you little--
-You ready, Pop?
-[blathers]
-Where are you--
-[chuckles]
I'll just be punishing
you by yourself then.
[crying out]
I tried to make
this easy on you,
but you just had to be stubborn.
Behold the teachings of a
cult so hidden, so secret,
it took 3,000 years
to perfect it.
Behold a technique so powerful,
even the Great Wall of China
itself can't stand
up against it.
Behold the Cult of
the Muscle Sword!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): If I can
do something about that sword,
maybe I can beat him.
-Here goes nothing!
Rarrgh!
-I'm gonna slice you to bits!
-Try it!
[both grunting]
Let go.
Let me go.
I said let go.
-Upsy-daisy!
-[screaming]
-Oh.
Oh, dear.
Have I done something
dreadful again?
-Kinnii, here.
-Stop it, stop it, stop it!
-Huh?
What?
Aw, the hot water's gone cold.
-Phew.
GENMA: And one.
And two.
And one.
And one-- come on.
Put some back into it.
[animals grunting]
And one.
And two.
-Huh?
Who has done this
dreadful thing?
GENMA: You did it.
Don't you remember?
-[sobbing]
What have I done?
Oh, what have I done?
Farewell to trees.
Farewell to stones.
Farewell to arms.
-Hm.
GENMA: Ranma.
-Could you ever forgive me, boy?
If I hadn't insisted on training
in Jusenkyo, none of this
would have ever happened.
-Pop.
I don't hold it against you.
-(TEARFULLY) Ranma.
-Then again, who am I kidding?
Yes, I hold it against you!
What do I look like?
A priest?
-You little ingrate.
Maybe this will teach
you some respect.
-Aah, you stupid old man!
GENMA: You ignorant little pup.
KINNII: Stop it, you.
No fighting.
Please, everyone.
Can't we all just get along?
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Aw, gross, Ranma!
You're acting like
you really are a girl.
Please don't laugh with
your pinkie finger stuck out
like that.
Next time on "Ranma
1/2," "Am I Pretty?
Ranma's Declaration
of Womanhood."
We'll see you there.