[theme music]
[crowd yelling]
[music playing]
[yelling]
-Wow!
-How cool.
[whistle blows]
-He really is the
coolest, isn't he?
-Not only is he good
at sports, but he's
up there in the looks
department, too.
Right, Akane?
You do know how lucky you are.
Being his fiancee
and all, I mean.
-Am I?
I mean--
UKYO: Ranma!
-Huh?
-You were wonderful.
Oh, you must be tired.
Here, let me help.
-I, uh-- heh.
Akane, are you--
[grunting]
-Stupid jerk.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Ranma, the Lady Killer.
-Today is fate day for sure.
Shampoo feel it.
Feel too much maybe.
Be still now.
It's OK.
That's it.
Be good.
UKYO: It is you.
[exclaims]
What are you up to?
-I-- I-- hi-ya!
It's none your business!
-A-ha!
You are spying on
Ranma, aren't you?
-Shampoo already say
is none your business.
-Yeah, OK.
Fine.
But you and I both know
what you're up to, don't we?
-You be quiet.
You know not first thing
what Shampoo up to.
[meowing]
-Kitty cat, come back!
-Oh, wow.
You really must
be desperate to be
using that old trick, Shampoo.
RANMA: Gah!
Ah!
Get it away from me!
Make it go away!
-If Shampoo deal
with him, you go out
on date with her today, Ranma?
RANMA: Forget about
that now, just--
[laughs]
-You promise?
-All right, I'll do it.
I swear.
I promise.
Just get it away from me.
-And who's desperate now, huh?
-You don't have to rub it in.
[meowing]
-That's Shampoo's!
-And don't forget me.
-Oh, OK.
-Now look what you've done.
-What?
Look what I do?
All hard work for nothing!
UKYO: It's not my fault!
-Ow!
AKANE: Hold still.
You're such a baby.
It's barely even a scratch.
-You could try and be a
little nicer, you know.
-You're pathetic.
Letting Shampoo and Ukyo
fight over you like that.
Please!
-They weren't fighting over me.
They were fighting each other.
Besides, what do
you care anyway?
Forget it.
-Forget what?
Tell me.
-Well, it's just-- you're
not jealous, are you?
-You wish.
Who you date is your own--
RANMA: I told you.
I'm not--
AKANE: Is your own business.
RANMA: You get mad so easy.
-Oh, and I suppose you got
nothing to do with that?
-Hey!
Why do you got to be like that?
You're always so selfish
and in a bad mood.
And worrying and--
well, thinking about me.
Which is nice, actually,
because I think you're, you
know, really nice--
-Ranma?
-And, you know, I wonder
why I never noticed before.
Sure, you're clumsy
and violent sometimes--
-Hey!
-But you're cute.
-Am I?
Really?
-Uh-huh.
-It's just-- you never--
[laughing]
GENMA: Well, well, well.
-Huh?
Dad?
-Pop?
-No, no.
Don't mind us.
-As you were, kids.
-As you were.
-To see our youngsters
getting along like that.
Well, it does the
old heart good.
Eh, Tendo?
It's like being a kid
again, eh, Saotome?
-Or, at least young at heart.
-And mind in your case, Saotome.
[laughing]
-Hm?
What the--
-Where'd they--
[nervous laughter]
-I'm just so confused.
I-- oh, Akane.
Are you serious?
And what about me?
Was I-- I think that I was.
Or maybe, I wasn't.
But I meant to be.
I mean, I meant to
mean to be serious.
I mean--
KASUMI: Ranma.
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
SOUN: So, there you are, son.
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were shy.
Silly me.
I'm just so happy you
and Akane are together.
-Ranma, is that true?
-It will be if you
say so, Kasumi.
-What?
-You what?
-I wha?
What the heck am I saying?
-Ranma!
Are you cheating
on Akane already?
-Father, please.
Calm down.
If that's the way Ranma feels,
then the least we owe him
is to.
Oh, dear.
Oh, son.
And here I believed in you two.
[panting]
-OK, I'm awake.
Why'd I do that all of a sudden?
I mean, I don't even like--
-So, then I'm all
like, you know?
And he's all like, whatever!
-Oh, my gosh.
Really?
-They're beautiful.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Am I cute?
I am, aren't I?
KASUMI: Akane.
-Ah!
Kasumi, don't scare
me like that, OK?
-Has something happened
between you and Ranma?
-Uh, heh, what
makes you say that?
-So then you didn't say
that you'd marry him?
-What?
No, marry?
Are you crazy?
No way.
Nuh-uh.
Not a chance, OK?
Absolutely not.
Forget it.
I mean as if!
-Hmm.
-Kids these days.
No respect.
I just wanted to see
what color they were.
That's all.
She didn't have to
go all in-- Bandages.
Bandages, let's see here.
Huh?
That's odd.
There ought to be a few left.
I swore there was-- my mistake.
[yelling]
-What do you say, huh?
Have you had enough?
-No one seem be winning.
-We've been at it
all day and we're
no closer than when we started.
-Maybe we should take break.
-My thoughts exactly.
[laughing]
GIRL: Oh, my gosh?
Really?
-Is that Ranma?
RANMA: So then I was like
all totally, you know?
Can I walk you home?
-Ranma!
What you mean by this?
You're not dating
those girls, are you?
-You're so cute when you're mad.
Did you know that?
-Forget about it, Ranma.
She means absolutely nothing.
Go on.
Tell me who you really love.
-I love you, of course.
-Ranma, listen.
People who tell lie
go very bad place.
-What lie is that?
-That Ranma love you, stupid.
What you think?
-It's the truth!
-So, did you want to go out?
-Which one.
-He means me, of course.
-I think he means me.
-I mean both, actually.
-Hey, you shut up!
-Quit it!
-Well, you ready?
-Anytime, you--
-Ah!
Hang in there, Ranma.
I'll take care of
her, and then we--
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER):
That's what you think!
-Hi-ya!
-Oh, no!
No fair.
I was distracted.
-Ones that get distracted
in fights lose fight.
That sounds fair to me.
[giggles]
-We go, OK, Ranma?
We leave distraction behind.
-Mm-hmm.
[giggles]
-I'll get you for this.
[growls]
[music playing]
-Shampoo so happy!
-Still, I'm a
little bit worried.
-How come?
-Huh?
I just keep thinking this
much happiness can't last.
-Shampoo no see nobody.
Ranma.
-Shampoo.
-Shampoo!
You OK?
-Ranma, let's have a date, OK?
-Huh?
Yeah, sure.
OK.
-Ha.
[meowing]
[ringing]
[laughing]
-Very, very funny, Nabiki.
-Are you saying I'm wrong?
-The master?
Maybe.
But Ranma?
Please!
-Hey, guys.
-You won't believe what
Nabiki here says she saw.
-I'm listening.
-Just your fiancee
acting like a mack daddy.
-Oh, Nabiki.
Come on.
-Look, don't believe
me if you want.
But I know what I saw.
-Hey, girls.
How's it going?
Mind if I hang out with you?
-Seriously?
Go out to the park
and see for yourself.
-I'll do that.
-Oh, now isn't it cute
how she worries about him.
-What are you gonna do?
[laughing]
-Then it's OK what
Ranma's doing?
What the heck.
This sounds way
too good to miss.
GIRL: There.
Got it?
GIRL: Got it.
-So, where should we go?
Huh?
Ranma?
GIRL: Back at ya!
-Cute girls.
Ow!
-Are you just a
complete jerk, Ranma,
or did you forget
who you're with?
-Ukyo, I'm sorry.
I did forget.
-Oh, thanks.
-Listen, those girls
mean nothing to me.
Ukyo, what I want is a woman.
-Really?
-Yes, really.
-Hey, I forgive you.
-Now that is the woman for me.
Listen, I'm kinda thirsty.
Can I get you something?
-Um, ice latte?
-You got it.
The machine's right over there.
I'll be right back, OK?
-Something's wrong,
but I'm not sure what.
Still, should I look a gift
[inaudible] in the mouth?
Maybe I should take
my chance while I can.
-I looking for you!
Give Ranma back right now!
-Whoopsie-daisy.
Huh?
-Who's that for?
-Why, it's for you, of course.
Who else would I--
-You liar!
-I'd never lie to you.
You're the only woman
in the world for me.
-I'm sorry.
Would you please get
that ball for me?
-Oh, yeah, sure thing.
-I'm telling you, boy.
If I hadn't of seen it, I
wouldn't have believed it.
-Do you think this is any
way for a man with a fiance
to behave?
-Ranma!
-Oh, hey, Shampoo.
-We finish what we start?
-And what would that be?
-I want you tell me in boat
again how happy you is.
-Boy, is she telling the truth--
-And what about
your promise, Ranma?
-Promise?
And what promise is that?
-Remember, you promised that
I'm the only one for you.
-He say that to me, too.
-Yeah, but with me, he meant it.
-You take that back!
-Go on, Ranma.
Tell her.
-Hm?
-Now, wait a sec.
-Nabiki, I--
-Ranma!
-Ugh!
-What?
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ranma,
and I believed him.
-Akane.
Akane, please!
Open the door.
He made a mistake, that's all.
Akane!
Akane, I'm talking to you.
HAPPOSAI: Don't lie.
You know he's just
showing his true colors.
SOUN: Master, please.
You're not helping.
HAPPOSAI: Oh, you
know it's true.
Where is the little
ladykiller anyway?
SOUN: He is in the
dojo being punished.
HAPPOSAI: Well, I'll
go say hello then.
Now that's nice for a change.
Maybe now you're finally ready
to hear what I've got to say.
Hey, I recognize that bandage.
So that's where the little
rascal disappeared to.
May as well leave it on.
The best part's yet to come.
UKYO: And what
part is that, huh?
-Shampoo want hear too!
-OK, girls.
You've had your fun.
Now cut me down please!
UKYO: Not 'til
you spill, gramps.
HAPPOSAI: OK, OK.
It's a magic bandage, all right?
Ranma doesn't know about it.
I bought it in China.
It's supposed to have
some kind of love potion
that activates
with human warmth.
-Warmth?
Like by wearing it, you mean?
-You say it, no matter
who he love with?
-That's right.
That's what a love potion does.
-Now are you going to cut me
down from here or aren't you?
Come on.
-Sorry, pops.
No can do.
It's your punishment for
meddling in people's lives.
-Shampoo know something
wrong with Ranma.
Now she know why.
-Does it matter who--
-He in love with?
BOTH: In other words--
-How dare you take advantage
when Ranma is so confused.
-Oh, right.
Look who's talking, Ukyo.
Like you no try to make
Ranma marry you yourself!
-Will somebody get
me down already!
-A promise is a promise.
-You snooze, you lose.
[sighs]
-Thanks, Akane.
I owe you one.
-I didn't come here to help you.
I just wanted to
ask you a question.
[groans]
-Are you in love
with someone else?
You-- you said it yourself.
You know, I'm clumsy
and violent and, well--
-Akane.
Actually, I think
you're very cute.
What?
-Ranma!
You come me.
Ranma!
-That stupid Shampoo.
Akane, you got a
shot at this too,
but not if you just
sit there waiting
for happiness to come to you.
-Wait, I don't-- I said wait!
-Shampoo, where
are you taking me?
-A place where no one
interferes, of course.
You-- you love Shampoo, right?
-Sure.
-Then it's OK you
sign marriage license?
-OK.
UKYO: A-ha!
The moment I've
been waiting for.
Ranma, honey, will
you please sign this?
-Sure.
-Oh, no, you don't!
-Seems like we're right
back where we started.
-So it seems.
-You guys, cut it out.
What are you doing?
-Ranma, you have to
do what Shampoo says.
Magic bandage means
he loves all women.
-That's right, which
is why he's going
to write his name on
my marriage license.
-I what?
-So-- so that's it.
Wait, wait, you guys.
Don't you see it's pointless?
-How so?
-Yeah, how?
-What about how Ranma feels?
-Shampoo worry that one later.
-For once, I agree with you.
-Please, don't!
-Oh, no!
-Akane!
-Ranma!
Ranma!
He no dead, is he?
-They're fine.
Look at how they landed.
-Ranma?
Ranma?
Ranma, wake up.
-Akane, you OK?
-Ranma, you're alive!
RANMA: Gosh, you're
cute when you cry.
-You dummy.
-I guess it must be
because of the bandage.
My heart is beating like crazy.
-So you guys gonna
stay like that or what?
-We see what you're doing.
-Yeah, and the bandage
came off a while ago.
-What?
-You should be
ashamed of yourself.
-That's the last time
I trust him again.
-Just like Shampoo always say.
Men is pig.
-I'm outta here.
-Shampoo go, too.
But it no mean I give up!
-It's getting kind
of late, isn't it?
-Uh-huh.
-So, you hungry?
-A little.
You?
-Huh?
-Look here, boy.
-Yeah, look here, son.
-Out all night I see.
That's not good, Akane.
-But-- but we--
GENMA: Ranma, you're
grounded for a week.
SOUN: Akane, no allowance.
Three months.
-Huh?
RANMA: I knew it.
Girls are nothing but trouble!
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): So here's
this guy, and he plays Shogi.
What I don't get is
why do we have to play?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," Battle
Chess-- the Game may be Fake,
but the Pieces are Real.
We'll see you there!