[music playing]
[theme song]
RANMA SAOTOME: Akane,
come play with me.
Don't you want to?
-Who-- who are you?
Where are you?
Ranma.
But what are you
doing in my dream?
-Goodbye.
-What?
Where-- where are you
go-- Ranma, Ranma.
Ah, ah, Ranma.
[gasping]
[liquid splashing]
FEMALE SPEAKER: "The
Frogman's Curse."
[laughing]
-Fantastic.
-Not too bad.
-I'm so glad you enjoyed it.
And now for our
next amazing trick--
[knocking]
[music playing]
-Oh boy.
-They're so cute.
-Those frogs are genius.
-I've never seen anything
like that before.
[cheering]
AKANE TENDO: Here,
you earned it.
Well, Ranma, pay
the little fella.
-Hm.
-No can do.
I'll catch him next time.
-You mean to tell me you
blew your allowance already?
Oh well, here, this is for him.
-Why, thank you my deary.
(TO HIMSELF) So this
is Ranma Saotome,
the name I can never forget.
[car horns]
-[snoring]
[grunting]
[growling]
Hm?
Tha-- that's my supper.
Come back here,
you little-- ahh.
[banging]
--[sigh] Shampoo so
tired from delivery.
Huh?
His-- his frogs.
Hi-yah.
[screaming]
RYOGA HIBIKI: [gasping]
Wh-- where the heck
did those come from?
Hm?
[screaming]
-[yawn] I slept great.
-Ranma, how can you
be in such a good mood
when your dad didn't even
come home last night?
-Hey, I told you not to worry.
He's probably just
camping out somewheres.
-But Ranma--
-Think about it, will you?
He's missed supper
and breakfast.
Does that sound like
the man you know?
Does it?
I just know something's
happened to him.
-Now that you mention it-- hm?
[bird squawking]
-It's a little early for
this, don't you think?
-He has reason to be upset.
Shampoo is missing.
-What?
-She what?
Since when?
-But what's that
got to do with it?
-She never came
back from delivery,
so I went out to check on her.
I found her bike surrounded
by frog footprints.
It's got to be the work of the
Frog Hermit, I'm sure of it.
-Frog Hermit?
What the heck is that?
[bird squawking]
COLOGNE: They call him a hermit.
But he's more like a wizard.
He transforms people into frogs.
AKANE TENDO: Be quiet.
But why is he after Mr.
Saotome and Shampoo?
-I've heard it said he wasn't
always the Frog Hermit,
but that he started
calling himself
that after falling into
one of many cursed springs
at Jusenkyo.
-In that case, Ranma, next
time he'll be coming for you.
-Ah, yeah, that could happen.
Or maybe I could just turn
him into roadkill instead.
-I knew I could count
on you, son-in-law.
You will save
Shampoo, won't you?
-[cackling] No prob.
-But Ranma, how
can you attack him
if you don't even
know where he is?
-Hey, that's the easy part.
If he really is after me,
then all I gotta do is wait.
He'll show up sooner or later.
[dog howling]
[wet footprints]
[water dripping]
-Oh, come on.
If you're going to
attack, get it over with.
I've been waiting all night,
and I still haven't had dinner.
How long am I supposed to--
[screaming]
-Huh?
Akane.
Huh?
-[quivering]
-You mean you're scared
of a couple of dumb frogs?
-Oh yeah, take a look.
-Looks like a couple
of dumb frogs to me.
Ahh.
-Ribbit, ribbit.
-It's Pop and Shampoo and Ryoga.
-Look, that meanie, he's
turned them all into frogs.
But what does Ryoga
have to do with it?
FROG HERMIT: You're
next, you know.
-Huh?
[splat]
-[quivering]
-[growling]
-So you're finally here, huh?
Hm?
Wh-- what's that, a scarecrow?
Guess he must have taken off.
FROG HERMIT: Prepare yourself.
-Huh?
-Ranma Saotome.
-Uh.
-Wrong person, dummy.
-Be serious, will you?
-Oh my goodness, so
I made a mistake.
That's odd, from the
look I got in the bath,
I could have sworn it was
a girl I saw in there.
-From the look you--
you saw me in the bath?
Bah.
-Little freak.
[screams]
-Oh, so you're Ranma.
-Yeah, and you're that
freaky little frog
catcher from
yesterday, ain't you?
-Trainer, not catcher.
-Whoever you are, change
those people back right now.
-And why did you even do
it in the first place, huh?
--[cackling] Why, because
I could, of course.
With you, though, Ranma Saotome,
it's a different situation.
-[gasps]
-You I change personally.
-Ahh.
And what was that?
-Magic frog elixir.
-If it's elixir, then why does
it look like plain water, huh?
-I would have thought
it would be obvious.
That water you saw is from
a very special spring.
According to legend,
a frog drowned there.
And now, if someone were to be
touched by that cursed water--
-And just what proof
is there that--
-Ribbit, ribbit.
-Believe it or not,
I'm here to help you.
You fell into one
spring already.
But what if this
water were also to--
-Yeah, like I don't know.
-You'd never be a girl
again, that's what.
-A-- a what?
For real?
-Ranma, he's lying.
-Let's just hear him out.
-Here's the first step.
-What's wrong with you?
-What's wrong with you, Ranma?
If you let me change
you to a frog,
then you'll never have
to be a girl again.
I can't believe
you'd fall for it.
-[cackling] Bingo.
-Oh, now you've
really done it, you
sneaky little-- come back here.
I'm not through with you.
I'm going to-- oh
what, splashing
water your only attack?
-Au contraire.
-What the?
Ah, ah.
[screaming]
Hm.
I'll ask again, is
that your only attack?
-I'll have you know that
attack's over 1,000 years old.
-You change those
frogs back into people,
or I'm going to get mad.
-Actually, now
you're making me mad.
-Ahh.
-Akane.
Mm?
-[gasping]
-Shampoo.
Oh no, are you OK?
-[cackling]
-Shampoo.
-Ribbit.
Mmm.
-I can't stand it anymore.
-Ahh, this one's even
worse than the other.
I'll change the both
of them into frogs.
But for now--
-[gasping]
[explosions]
RANMA SAOTOME: Akane.
Akane.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why?
AKANE TENDO: Thank you,
Ranma, for everything.
Whatever it is
that's happened, I
know that you did
it for my sake.
Sayonara.
RANMA SAOTOME: Akane,
wait, don't go.
Akane.
[cracking rock]
Now what?
Is it because I'm a frog?
[balling]
-Hey, are you OK?
-You wouldn't have
known what was
happening if you
hadn't come to spy.
-That's right,
Ranma, you caught me.
That and the fact that you
were crying like a little baby.
-I was?
-Uh-huh. (BABY
VOICE) Did ums have
a bad dream about the frog?
-Very funny, ha.
-I'm sorry.
I shouldn't tease you.
But seriously though, that dream
you had, what was it about?
[bird squawking]
Huh?
-Whatever you're
saying, I don't get it.
--[gasping] You didn't have
to choke me, you know.
Now I know where you
were hiding, at least.
-Oh yeah, hiding in the tub.
That's right, yeah,
you got me, all right.
-Aha.
-Ha, ha.
-Ha, ha, ha.
AKANE TENDO: Ahh.
-Hmm?
[screaming]
AKANE TENDO: You guys.
RANMA SAOTOME: You didn't
have to look, you know.
-I didn't come to
take a bath, actually.
-Oh yeah, why did you?
-I found out where they
took Shampoo and the others.
-Really?
-Uh-huh, wanna go?
-You betcha.
-Take me along, too.
Mmm-- I told you guys
to stop doing that.
-What?
-So I guess this is the place.
-Yup.
-Guess it used to be a pond
before it all dried up.
-The frogs are
still here, though.
Look.
-Hmm?
Shampoo.
What did they do to you?
Ahh.
You must be scared
and cold and slimy.
I don't blame you
for hitting me.
Ahh-- that's it, froggy.
You're dead.
Make a monkey out of
me, will you, huh, huh?
Come on.
-[squeak]
-I'm sorry.
Shampoo, I didn't mean it.
Forgive me.
-Oh, thank goodness.
I thought they
were all smooshed.
-I'm starting to wonder
about these frogs.
AKANE TENDO: Ryoga,
can you hear me?
RANMA SAOTOME: How
do we know it's him?
If only we had some
way to find out.
-Like this?
-Um, like that.
Huh?
-[screams]
-Akane.
[bird squawking]
-Huh?
-I guess the water
kind of hit him.
-Huh.
Ahh.
[cackling]
-You've discovered
my secret hideout,
and my true appearance.
-Ranma, that frog's talking.
-I've been around so long I
can talk well in either form.
-Change those
people back or else.
-Was that a threat?
-[screaming]
-Ahh.
[explosions]
--[cackling] You three
frogs are up next.
-I don't think so.
It seems your little friends
get faint at loud noises.
-They what?
AKANE TENDO:
[screaming] Stay away.
Don't come any closer
or I'll hit you.
Huh?
Where did they go?
-The only one left is you.
-Mmm, you just can't
leave me alone, can you?
It's just like that other time.
-What other time?
-You-- you really
don't remember?
-I know you're ticked off
at me for something, but--
-You really are
forgetful, aren't you?
My associates and I were
training at Jusenkyo
at the time of the
incident in question.
Good, now try jumping
to the next pole.
One, two--
-Yah.
-Remember?
-I've, uh, got no idea
what you're talking about.
-It's your fault.
I knew it.
-What?
Do you want me to take a lie
detector test or something?
-I've had about enough of you.
Hi-yah.
-Ahh.
[grunting]
-Oh no.
[screaming]
-Ranma.
-[screaming]
-Ahh.
[sighing]
-Akane.
-Oh, ah.
-Ahh.
-Akane, no.
Akane.
-[muted laughter]
-Akane.
Please don't be a frog.
-[gasping]
-Huh?
--[sighing] That's odd,
it tastes like water.
-[cackling] That's 'cause it is.
-Huh?
-I used to have some
Jusenkyo spring water, true.
But, ah, it kind of
all, well, evaporated.
-So then those three
frogs are just frogs.
-Now you got it.
I wanted to scare you a
little, and that's all.
-But why involve Shampoo
then, and the others?
-So many have fallen into
those cursed springs.
Yet I was sure none were
more miserable than I. I just
wanted to spread that
misery around a little.
-What a rotten thing to do.
-But Ryoga never fell into any--
-Oh well, that's 'cause he, ah--
[bird squawking]
-Huh?
-Don't worry, they're
only sleeping.
I just wanted to scare
you a little, and I did.
[laughing]
-What I want is
for you to shut up.
-I may be gone
but not frogotten.
[laughing]
-Dumb lying frogs.
-Are these a lie too?
Salty-- guess not.
-Ah, th-- th-- that's
just sweat or something.
-[laughing]
[theme song]
FEMALE SPEAKER: Ukyo
is losing customers.
But why?
Is it connected to that
new crepe making guy?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Raging Okonomiyaki."
We'll see you there.