-Morning!
-Hi Akane, how ya doing?
Hey where's Ranma?
You're usually together.
-Well, uh, he kinda
overslept again.
-That dumb Akane.
It wouldn't have killed
her to have woken me up
before she left the
house this morning.
But oh, no!
Oh, man am I late!
PRINCIPAL: Good morning
and aloha everybody!
Me hope that today you fight
just as hard as yesterday!
And be good little ke-ke, yeah?
Me have such big fun
yesterday, so me tell meself,
Big Kahuna, you gotta give them
ke-kes some big fun too, yeah!
So today me bring
you new big present.
-Now what is it?
Whatever it is, I'm
sure we won't like it.
-So what kind of haircut
is it going to be today?
-Oh, how you get to be
such a cynical wahine?
When kids no trust
island elders,
whole village got a
big problem, yeah?
That why we make this!
ALL: Huh?
PRINCIPAL: It's
the statute of me!
When you come to
the school, ke-ke,
me want you to show the respect
on hands and knees, yeah!
-You've gotta be kidding!
-That is totally unreasonable!
-Now ke-ke, be good!
Me is Big Kahuna, yeah?
-Ha ha!
He makes it just in time.
-Yeah, hooray!
-He deserved that.
-That's Ranma for you.
-Huh?
-Here's to the start
of a beautiful day.
-But what did I--
-Just sit back and enjoy it.
-That Ranma is one bad ke-ke.
This time he went
push me too far!
NARRATOR: Enter Kuno, the
Night-Prowling Knight.
[humming]
-Hey-a hey-a!
Welcome to the
principal's office!
-Well why is it
you've summoned me?
-Maybe you think you better
than Big Kahuna, yeah?
-Your point?
-Mr. Kuno, at this year
Furinkan High School,
there be many, many
wonderful student, yeah?
But you be the most
wonderful of all!
-Tell me something I don't know.
-Mr. Kuno, Big Kahuna
ask favor of you.
What you say to be the Big
Kahuna's the right hand man?
-And what is this?
"I, Tatewaki Kuno
do hereby affirm
myself to be the duly sworn
deputy of the school principal.
Signed, Furinkan
High School principal
on the such and such
today of--" Hmm.
-What me say wrong?
-As though I would ever
consent to sign my name
to such an ignoble
pledge as this.
-Me hear wahine go
crazy for deputy!
-They do?
You don't want a
demerit, do you?
N-- n-- no, sir.
D D-- d-- don't hurt me, sir!
-You're so righteous!
-Champions of virtue
make me so hot.
-Heh heh heh.
-Something wrong?
-Very well I shall consider it.
-Me just knew you'd say that.
-Augh, what the heck is that?
-Ugh how tacky!
-Somebody do something!
-There's one here too!
-Maybe we can transfer
to another school.
-There's not a single
work of art in the bunch.
-Yeah, kinda makes
you sick, you know?
-On your knees, worm.
-Augh!
I--
-Let me go!
Say, uh, aren't you
one of the teachers?
What about you over there?
-Yeah!
What about you?
-It's not our fault!
-Please, I got a wife
and kids at home.
I can't afford to lose this job.
So please don't tell on us.
-So please don't tell on us.
-Oh yeah, right.
We're supposed to feel
sorry for you because--
AKANE: Ranma!
-Huh?
-Come quick!
-What's wrong?
-The principal's got the entire
Kendo Club turned against us!
-He's done what?
-Look, over there!
-Yo, Kuno!
How's it going?
-How dare you speak
to me so glibly.
Listen well, Ranma Saotome.
I Tatewaki Kuno do
hereby vow to put an end
to your days of
unfettered tomfoolery.
Ha!
-Gee, what's the
matter with you?
Your underwear too tight again?
-Silence, wretch!
-So, why don't
you tell me again,
why it is you're so ticked off?
-Ha!
As if you of all people
don't already know!
For some time now not only you,
but this entire student body
has been engaged in
licentious behavior.
Starting today,
I mean to enforce
a new standard of
moral behavior.
-Say, this wouldn't
have something
to do with the principal and
his crazy ideas, now would it?
-How little you know.
As if I, Tatewaki
Kuno could ever
be motivated by anything other
than pure and abiding love
for this school!
-Pure and abiding love, huh?
-Yeah, that's the first
I've ever heard of it.
-Your disregard for school
rules is bad enough.
But to flaunt your improper
and immoral sexual union
with a young maiden who's but
scarce come into full bloom--
-Now would be a good
time to shut up.
-Fiend!
Care you nothing
for propriety, then?
Show him the error of his--
-Stupid principal, now he's
siccing Kuno and his homeboys
on me, too.
-Come on, you guys.
Fighting among
ourselves is just what
that crazy principal wants.
-Never fear my
sweet Akane Tendo,
once that pompous
idiot Kuno is gone,
you won't have to worry anymore.
Together you and I can forge
a new era of unity among the--
-That's right, once the odious
Kuno is no more you and I will
be free to have some--
-Hey if she's not
Kuno's, she's mine.
-What a sorry bunch of losers.
PRINCIPAL: Oh, this
won't do at all!
-I may be down, but
I'm far from out!
Ranma Saetome, I challenge you.
-Hey that's fine with me
Kuno, but if you're really
in charge of school
morals, well then,
there's something else you
should be checking into first.
-What?
-Ha ha ha, what a haul!
Ha ha!
-Happosai?
-Wow, Akane!
I
-Fiend!
-Take that!
HAPPOSAI: My collection!
-If you're really
in charge of morals,
Kuno, then this is the guy
you should be dealing with.
-Ranma!
How dare you!
-How dare you, you little--
-Speak for yourself!
-Ranma!
-Hmm.
Pipsqueak.
-Bravo!
Such strength!
Such style!
You a very amazing
martial artist.
-Who are you?
-Me think maybe you
want to help kids
learn good moral as
deputy Tatewaki coach?
What do you say?
-What?
-It sounds like
a bad idea to me.
-No kidding, especially
seeing as how the freak don't
care for much 'cept for
girls' underwear anyway.
Why would he want to?
-Very well, I accept.
-Huh?
-Hee hee!
Ha!
-As though I would ever consent!
-The first thing you learn is
to speak when you're spoken to!
And you'll learn that
with proper training,
even someone like this can
become your worst enemy.
-He can?
-Enough!
The very thought that I,
Tatewaki Kuno oftimes called
the Blue Thunder
of Furinkan High
should ever be trained
by the likes of you.
And as for you
Ranma Saetome, I'll
await you at the
back of the gym.
-I'll be there.
-See that you are,
or you'll be sorry.
Ha ha ha.
-You sure it's a
good idea, Ranma?
-I know it isn't.
But if I don't go,
Kuno will never
let me hear the end of it.
-Of all the night's
haul, I'd have
to say this little
pink one's my favorite.
Hey!
Who just did that?
Dear me, look at what
the cat dragged in.
Ranma beat you up again, huh?
-If you wish, you
may become my coach.
-Oh so the likes of
me are finally good
enough for you then?
Are they?
-Well will you coach
me or won't you?
-Hmm.
Well.
Eh, why not.
We'll start first
thing tomorrow.
-Oh I see.
So the master will be in charge
of this training then, will he?
-That's bad news
for you, boy, seeing
as the master will know
your moves in advance.
-But Dad, Kuno's already
refused his offer.
-And besides, I mean, why
would the old freak even
bother in the first place?
-Hey, you didn't do
anything to make him angry
again, did you Ranma?
-Come on, Akane.
You think I'd actually do
something like that on purpose?
-Actually, it does make sense.
Being perverse is the
master's joy in life.
-Truer words were never spoken.
Why, he has no morals
at all, has he.
HAPPOSAI: Traitors!
-Huh?
-Grandfather!
-How cruel can you be?
I can't believe you
would even say that!
They-- they say parents
are misunderstood
by their children.
That's how I feel!
Why I'm only doing
it for his own good.
I'm trying to make Ranma into a
stronger martial artist, that's
all.
Don't you see that?
-(in unison) Master forgive us.
We're not worthy.
We'll never be worthy!
-Hmm.
Then you should know,
Ranma, that Kuno
came asking for my
help this evening.
-He-- he what?
-You should also know that
should you lose to him,
you'll be wearing this
cute little number!
-Oh no I--
-You'd better prepare yourself.
PRINCIPAL: OK!
Time for the be training now.
You make me proud, yeah!
-I train for one thing--
to defeat Ranma Saotome.
-Same difference, yeah?
-That being said,
I await instruction
on how training might
best be achieved.
-Ranma's main gift is speed.
So until you can more or
less keep up with him,
you haven't got a chance, kid.
-In other words, if I
strike without mercy--
-I'm not talking
about attitude, fool.
All the attitude
in the world's not
going to help you if you
can't get in a couple of hits.
What you need is energy.
Can you guess what
I've got in here?
-What, protein powder?
-No you moron.
Use your brain for once.
These here are the makings
for my super secret speed
of light elixir.
-Speed of light elixir?
-What that?
-Prepared properly it makes
you not only faster than light,
but graceful as a
swallow in flight.
-Graceful as a swallow.
-Aloha!
-I'll take it!
-Hmm.
-I see.
-It's part of your
training, stupid.
To start.
-It looks like a map.
-On it you'll find the first
of several clues leading
to the necessary ingredients
for the speed of light elixir.
-Very well, I'll set
Sasuke to it immediately.
-Do it yourself, you idiot!
-"To begin, go 50
paces to the east.
Then go 15 paces due south.
Finally open the door and
look up toward the ceiling."
[women scream]
-Please stop screaming!
I-- I can explain everything!
-Deputy in charge of school
morals cannot do such thing!
-Now that he's paved
the way for me--
-Say again?
-You're supposed to
be setting an example!
-There's been a mistake!
I only came for-- ah, I got it.
-Can't say I'm surprised.
The ones who pretend to be good
are usually worse than anybody!
KUNO: Somebody help me!
-Let's hit him so hard he'll
never be able to raid us again.
-Gotta go!
KUNO: But it's not my fault!
-But you take them only
for training, yeah?
-Come to papa, baby!
-Me know nothing.
-Vengeance is mine.
How dare you use me as
an instrument of evil!
Couldn't you have found
somewhere else to put this?
-Silence.
Do you want the
elixir or don't you?
-Yes, of course.
-Then unless you're
willing to dare any danger
and endure any humiliation
in strict accordance
with the training schedule
as I've set it out for you,
you ain't got a chance
of getting your hands
on the speed of light
elixir and defeating Ranma.
KUNO (VOICEOVER):
Saotome defeated.
Just imagine.
-You're so righteous!
-Champions of virtue
make me so hot.
-Then a champion I shall become!
[women scream]
-Huh?
FEMALE SPEAKER: Jerk!
Get out of here!
-Forgive me!
I came not to peep
but to-- there it is!
Ah, coming through!
FEMALE SPEAKER: Get out of here!
-Ha ha!
I got the second one!
The things a man does for love!
-Shutup and take a beating.
FEMALE SPEAKER: Scram!
-Ah!
An underwear thief!
-Somebody catch him!
-Call the police!
-The third clue has got
to be in here somewhere.
But soft what light
through yonder--
-So would you mind telling me
what you're up to there, pal?
Is that underwear?
Better show me some ID, buddy.
-I'm in training, you see?
-Uh-huh.
Come on pal, let's go.
-Don't you patronize me.
-Then don't go
stealing underwear.
The proof's right over there.
What the-- wh-- where'd it go?
-If you'll excuse me.
Hey!
Just don't let it happen again.
KUNO: Ranma Saotome,
where are you?
-Can I, uh, help you?
-Kindly give this
letter of challenge
your immediate attention.
Meet me after school
in the usual place.
I'll be waiting.
Signed, Tatewaki
"Blue Thunder" Kuno.
-Why write it if you were
going to read it anyway?
-Yeah.
-Akane Tendo?
-Uh, yeah?
-I regret that I am
unable at this time
to fulfill my pledge to you.
Yet once I've defeated
the vile Saotome,
rest assured that I shall indeed
become your champion of virtue.
-That's okay, really.
-Until then.
-Can you take him?
-Akane, I haven't lost
to him yet, have I?
-Ready, Saotome?
-Anytime.
And since when the heck
have you been so fast?
-Ha ha ha ha.
You're no longer a match for me.
-I just wasn't paying
attention is all.
-Who would've thought that
the dirt from my fingernails
was so strong?
-The fingernail?
-At worst, I figured he'd
give himself a stomach ache.
Ha!
-Is that your best?
Compared to the
tortures I've endured
at the hands of angry maidens,
your blows barely touch me.
-Now I'm getting serious!
-Ranma!
-He's headed for
the water fountain!
-I counted on the fact that he'd
believe whatever I told him,
but he may be
believing it too much!
-And now to end your suffering.
Prepare to-- Th-- th--
the pig-tailed girl!
-Kuno darling!
Be a lamb and lend me
your sword for a sec, huh?
-But I--
-You wanna hold me, don't you?
If you don't let
go of the sword--
-What's this?
I can hold you in my arms?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): If he don't
let go of it, I'm done for.
His attacks are just too--
-Forgive me, pig-tailed girl.
-Hmm?
-Despite the pleas
of my lover's heart,
my warrior's soul forbids it.
Nevertheless, if I
were to free one hand--
AKANE: Psst!
Ranma!
-You're a lifesaver.
-Pig-tailed girl,
wherefore art thou?
Huh?
-So, you happy to see me?
-Damn your eyes!
Where have you hidden
the pig-tailed girl?
How dare you interfere in
the amores of your betters!
-I gotta think of
something quick.
I can't take much
more of those hits.
-Run!
Run like the worm you are!
-Just as I feared, my
too-efficient training
has produced an
unstoppable killing machine
whose sword-based attacks
rival those of Japan's greatest
warriors.
-And all from the dirt
under your fingernails, huh?
-Hey, is it my
fault that even the
crud that piles up
under my fingernails
is too strong for
my own good, huh?
-Me not worthy!
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Ranma lose to Kuno?
I can't believe it!
-Run, worm!
Run!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
There's gotta be some way
to block his attacks.
OK.
-Akane Tendo and the
pig-tailed girl both, with one
fell swoop I claim
my two fair maids!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
The only time he's
got any muscle is
when he's striking
something right in front of him.
Therefore, if I only pretend
to be moving in close--
-Saotome!
-Ranma!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I'm
falling right into it!
-I think I have a stomach ache.
FEMALE SPEAKER: He did it!
PRINCIPAL: Wipe out.
-Yo, Kuno are you
all right, man?
-Ranma!
You did it!
-Congratulations, Ranma.
You became strong after all
and rose to the challenge,
like I knew you would.
-Actually it wasn't
me being strong at all
it was Kuno being weak.
-Speaking of which--
-Oh my stomach.
It pains me so.
It must be that speed of
light elixer that I drank.
-Or maybe your stomach, he no
like dirt of fingernail, yeah?
Fingernail dirt!
Why you wretched
fossil of evil, how
dare you make mock of
Tatewaki Kuno, not once
but a second time.
You-- Help me!
-But Ranma, even if it wasn't
because of the medicine,
those sword blows
of Kuno's were fast.
He's never been
that fast before.
So why do you think
it is he could
move so quickly this time?
-Gee Akane, I don't know.
Maybe it's because
when he was chasing me
he kept wanting to be
your champion of virtue
or something?
-Or maybe it's because
the fingernail dirt
of such a strong martial artist
gave him the strength of 10.
-(in unison) Be quiet, you!
-Though the lover
himself may die,
his love for his maiden
fair will never--
-Oh no, wipe out!
You think you beat
me, Ranma Saotome?
But you no beat me yet,
me make new statue.
-On your knees.
-That right, now I teach him!
Hit student, not principal!
Principal is headmaster,
which mean Big Kahuna!
So no hit the big--
-On your knees, worm.
NARRATOR: Hey, no fair!
Why'd you put that stuff
on Ranma's back for?
What?
What do you mean
he'll lose his power?
Next time on Ranma
1/2, Ranma gets weak!
We'll see you there!