[theme music]
-I'm off to school, see ya.
-Already?
-I'm trying to
avoid Akane's lunch.
-Nabiki.
[sigh]
-Yes.
OK everybody, I've made a
special lunch for each of you.
[groan]
Here you go, Dad.
And one for you.
Huh?
I wonder where Nabiki is.
-She left for school
about 10 minutes ago.
-That girl.
I wonder why she
leaves so early.
[throat clearing]
-It's not that I
don't appreciate it,
but it must be very
difficult waking up early
to make our lunches, Akane.
-Tendo's right.
Mhm, and we certainly
don't want you
to feel obligated
to make them for us.
[giggles]
-Oh, that's sweat of you, but
I really don't mind, honestly.
-Ranma.
-Shh.
-Oh, Ranma, I see
that you're awake.
-And it seems your stomach
ache is gone, good news.
-Ranma, your lunch.
-I really don't
need a lunch today.
-What do you mean, Ranma.
-OK, it's because
I don't really need
to-- need to take a lunch
to school, because I haven't
got, well-- how can I-- Ahh!
-Don't you dare tell
her that her food
tastes like eating chalk.
-And if you do, you'll
have me to deal with.
-Come on, boy.
-Let go!
-How can you refuse my
daughter's generosity?
[grunting]
[thud]
-Ranma, you forgot your lunch.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I've
eaten her cruddy lunches
for three days in
a row, and I don't
think my stomach
could take another.
FEMALE SPEAKER: "Enter
Gosunkugi-- The New Rival?"
[cat screech]
-Huh?
I will make a new friend today.
I won't make a new friend today.
Ahh!
[panting loudly]
I won't make a new friend today.
I will make a new friend today.
I will make a new friend-- ahh!
-Sorry, hey, you OK?
Man, I didn't see you.
-Hey, Ranma, wait up.
-Oh no, my petal.
-Now where'd he go?
Huh?
I'm, uh, really sorry.
I better go.
-Uh, please wait.
Um, this is for you.
-Huh?
-It's a gift.
-Is that what I think it--
-Oh yes, and it
really works too.
-Oh, that's nice.
-Do you want a
tarot card instead?
-Uh-uh.
-Akane!
-Hmm?
-Hey, what's that?
-Well if you ask me, it looks
like a voodoo doll made out
of straw.
-How cute.
-Is it really?
-Please, help yourself.
I have plenty more.
There you go.
-Are you serious?
Gee, thanks!
-[stuttering]
-Thanks a lot.
-Come on, let's
see if they work.
-All right, everyone,
settle down.
I'd like to introduce
a new student.
-Woah, check him out.
-The guy's a nerd.
-Yeah, what a complete doofus.
-Class, meet Hikaru Gosunkugi.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): It's him.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): That's
the guy I ran into.
AKANE: Here's your lunch, Ranma.
-Wow.
-Eat up, Ranma.
-Like I'm so jealous.
-I told you I didn't want lunch.
-(ANGRILY) OK,
that suits me fine.
-Hey, wait Akane.
AKANE: Excuse me, Gosunkugi.
-Huh?
-Would you like this?
-You made that just for me?
-I had an extra.
-I'm the luckiest guy
in the whole world.
Oh, thank you.
-I don't think so.
-I thought you said
you didn't want it.
-That doesn't mean you
could just go and give it
to another guy.
You got to trust me
on this one, pal.
By the looks of it,
you're in no condition
to even attempt eating
this stuff and live.
-What do you mean by that?
Give it-- give it back.
-Come on, Akane, I
didn't mean it like that.
-What did you mean then?
-Just give it to me, OK?
-I said give it.
[groan]
Ranma, you idiot!
[laughter]
-There you go.
-Hey, thanks a lot.
-I hear that
Akane's cooking is--
-Really deadly.
I dare you to tell her that.
-Why would I do that?
She's my friend.
-Why don't you?
She's your fiancee.
-Hey, isn't that the
same handkerchief
your lunch was wrapped in?
-And it's even embroidered
with your name.
-Doesn't carrying it around
like that make you feel guilty?
-Yeah, I know I
would if I were you.
-Well, let me put it this way--
I'd rather feel guilty than eat
Akane's lousy cooking.
-You think it's that bad?
-It must be.
I'm glad I don't have to eat it.
-Hello.
Were you two
talking about Akane?
Something about fiancee?
GOSUNKUGI (VOICEOVER): I
could have never imagined
that you were betrothed
to such a violent man.
Don't worry, I will
save you from your Hell.
-Hey, heads up!
-Oh, man.
That doesn't look too good.
-Hey, is everybody all right?
-That will leave a mark.
-I didn't want to,
yet Akane's fiance
leaves me no choice
but to use my powers.
So be it.
It is time to pay for
what you have done!
You destroyed my flower,
you wrecked her lunch,
and stepped on my face!
For that, you vile
wretch, you will pay!
Mark my words!
[yelling]
[panting] Look, it's Gosunkugi.
-By the way, thanks
for the voodoo dolls.
-See you later, Gosunkugi.
[giggles]
-He is so weird.
-I know.
[laughter]
[yelling in pain]
-It's time to get
serious with that Ranma,
and make him pay for
his sins against Akane.
Then all will be
right with the world.
-Hey, what are you
doing this time?
-Maybe it's like a secret, and
he doesn't want us to ask him.
-We're sorry we bothered you.
-Good luck, Gosunkugi.
-You know, if this is here,
people might notice you.
I'll just move it for you.
-And I guess we'd
better cover it up too.
-I guess so.
Hey, wait, I'm still down here.
Um, I uh-- I can't see a thing.
-Hey there, Akane.
Wait!
Hey, I'm sorry I wrecked
your stupid lunch,
but I can explain.
-Hey, what did you do that for?
-Akane.
-Oh, what is it now?
-You gotta look
ahead when you run.
-A pitfall?
-Who in this day and age would
dig such an obvious trap?
-Yeah, and who'd
even fall for it?
-I appreciate all my admirers
who came to see me off.
I thank you all for
your loyal supp--
-Well, there's your answer.
-Imbecile!
I demand to know the meaning
of this little prank.
-It wasn't meant for you.
It was meant to
trap somebody else.
-I suppose in that case, I must
admit was quite the clever ploy
to even trick me this one time.
[laughter]
MALE SPEAKER: I think we
should cover it up again.
MALE SPEAKER: Yeah, I agree.
-Hey!
Someone!
Get me out of here!
Help!
-I'm home.
Huh?
-Akane, you back all ready?
Yeah, well, you
know, Saotome and I
were thinking that we hadn't
had takeout in awhile.
And, uh, well--
-It's not that we don't
love your lunches.
-I'm sorry.
I guess you guys are all
getting sick of my cooking.
-No, that's not
really it at all.
-How could you even think that?
-Nope, I've made up my mind.
I'm through with cooking.
-Maybe we shouldn't have
ordered in, Saotome.
-What are you talking about?
It was your bright idea.
-Oh, so all of a
sudden you think
this whole mess is
completely my fault?
-Well, you're the one
who picked up the phone
and made the call, Tendo.
-Yeah, well who
looked up the number?
-Don't try to pin this on me.
[yawn]
-I had the best sleep
last night, Kasumi.
-Here.
-Hey, Ranma, did you
say something to Akane?
-Not me.
-Oh.
Well, anyway, it
looks like we don't
have to worry about her
making our lunches anymore.
-Nabiki.
No breakfast?
-No, thanks.
[choking]
-Akane?
-He's here.
Well, hello, Ranma.
-Yeah, that's my name.
-What are you up to?
-(NERVOUSLY) Not much.
Got to go, see you later.
-What a weirdo.
-My plan is working.
I think I really rattled him.
[growling]
Nice doggy.
Ow, ow!
I showed him.
That's what he gets for
trying to outwit Gosunkugi.
-Huh?
He wants to meet?
-Yeah, Gosunkugi said to
meet him over in the gym.
You think he's holding a
grudge over Akane's lunch?
-You know, maybe
it's time I tell him
the truth about Akane's cooking.
-Yo, Gosunkugi.
-Oh, you're here
already, Ranma Saotome.
-For your information, I
haven't done anything to you
that you can hold a
grudge against me for.
Understand?
Do you have any idea what
Akane's lunch can do to a man?
-No.
-Here's what would have
happened to you if you do eat.
-Ah!
-I don't need to be told my
cooking isn't up to standards,
I already know that.
That is why I'm practicing.
-Well, I-- um--
-And then for you to go and
waste perfectly good food
is totally disgusting.
-I agree.
Just the thought of making
a meal for a loved one,
and then in return that person
simply pays no regard to them.
The first time I
may overlook it,
but twice and even my
patience would run out.
[laughter]
Interesting, you are
the first challenger
to trick me more than once.
But you will be the last.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
-All right, all right,
I'll buy a stupid book.
Oh, yeah.
-Hey, you're not just
going to give up, are you?
-That's none of your business!
-I brought you something.
-What is it?
-Don't worry, you'll
figure it out.
-Oh, Ranma.
[humming]
I'll meet you behind
the school at lunch.
Ranma.
How strange.
I'll meet you on
the roof at lunch.
Akane.
That's weird.
-I suspect you came
here to interfere.
I can only assume you are
here to spy on my rendezvous
with Akane Tendo.
-What are you talking about?
-(FEMALE VOICE) I'll meet
you on the roof for lunch.
Akane.
Now leave us be, or else.
-Sorry, but I'm running late.
Akane?
-I-- I will not let you alone
with my fair Akane Tendo.
-(FEMALE VOICE) I'm so glad that
the two of you could make it.
I want to give
this special lunch
to the winner of a fight between
the two of you big, strong men.
-Wait!
-Prize is all yours, Kuno.
-I told you to stay put.
-Oh, stuff it.
-Why don't you be a man and
heed my request to stay?
-Because I don't
want to interrupt you
on your stupid little date, OK?
-Oh, well.
I was hoping you'd
take each other out.
-You!
Not only do you
continue to trick me,
this time you dare
to insult Akane.
Stand up and fight like a man.
-Um, uh, that
wasn't my intention.
-Raaaah!
-Wait, sorry!
-You OK, Gosunkugi?
He nearly whooped
you pretty good.
[laughing]
-Did you see my power?
-What you mean your power?
You were lucky.
-Feast your eyes on the
power that is Gosunkugi!
-Don't mind me, but what
are you trying to prove?
I am your God.
-You're my what?
-And it is time to pass
judgment on Ranma Saotome.
Heeya!
I call upon the wind and
thunder to answer my prayer!
[maniacal laughter]
Observe the hammer of justice.
This is the end of you.
Say goodbye, Ranma.
Your time has come!
-Hey, Gosunkugi!
Wow, never seen a human
lightning rod up close before.
-Look, he's conscious.
-So, how do you feel?
-Good.
-That's good, and
this is for you.
Is that all right, Ranma.
I can't believe there's
actually somebody on this planet
willing to taste your cooking
of their own free will.
-Just ignore him.
I know my cooking's improved.
-Oh, and here's
something from me.
-What was that?
-Ah, ah, ah.
Just you never mind.
-Antacid pills?
-Gosunkugi?
Um, Gosunkugi?
Where could he be?
He just started a few days ago.
-Well, we saw yesterday.
He was fine.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Well,
I guess those antacid
pills weren't strong enough.
[moaning]
-I'll get you for this, Ranma.
Oh, my tummy.
Oh, mommy.
[theme music]
FEMALE SPEAKER: So a
martial arts master
also needs to have
good handwriting?
Hmm, Ranma, maybe you
should practice a little.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Ranma's Calligraphy
Challenge."
We'll see you there.