[music playing]
[theme music]
[shudder]
Are you cold, Ranma?
Uh-uh.
I'm OK.
Thanks.
I'm sorry, Ranma.
I know I'm still
in training, but I
feel terrible seeing
my child suffer for it.
Ranma?
Yeah?
What is it, Dad?
Can you remember back then?
This is the first
time the two of us
have had the chance to be
alone together like this
since we came to
the Tendo's house.
I worked hard to raise you
as a strong young man, Ranma.
Hey, Pop.
Is this story going somewhere?
[wind howling]
We've been stuck here in the
storm for two days already.
And the only food
we have left now
is this one cup of
instant noodles.
One?
This might be a perfect
chance to show your gratitude
to your father, Ranma.
No chance, Pop.
Hm.
Well, in that case,
prepare to fight, Ranma!
Don't come begging for
a bite after you lose!
[groan]
[slurp]
Ah.
That hit the spot.
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER):
The Cradle from Hell.
AKANE: Come here, Ranma.
Look.
RANMA: Yeah?
Did something happen between
you guys on your training trip?
Your dad's been totally zoned
out like that for ages now.
Hm.
[snoring]
[groan]
Hello.
What's going on, Pops?
Just working out a
few things in my mind.
Ranma, get ready for
some one on one with me.
I need to confirm something.
Hm?
All right, Ranma.
This is a serious
match, so don't
think of me as your father.
Give me all you've got.
Don't hold back on my account.
Start.
I'm coming for you, Ranma!
[grunt]
[groan]
[yelling]
That's the match.
Ranma wins.
[groan]
So what's the matter, Pops?
You got the flu or something?
This confirms my worst fears.
Huh?
I've become weaker
than my son, Ranma!
What?
Oh, my.
Oh, those heady days of
victory-- back then and then
and here and here and here.
I was undeniable,
undefeated champion.
Hm.
Social Services would
love those slides.
It would be a
fatal error letting
Ranma find out about this.
Must settle down.
Must act normal.
This must be a huge
blow to the poor man.
He's so worked up
now, I don't even
think he knows what
he's saying anymore.
[groan]
There's nothing to worry
about, though, Pops.
When I was five, you
scoffed my rice cakes.
At seven, you ripped
off my crackers.
And at 12, you
nicked my rice bowls.
And yes, you even
snafued my pork buns.
But despite all that, I'll
tell you something, Pops.
I don't hold any
grudges towards you.
Kudos to long term memory.
That's some grudge
against his father.
Training?
Yes, Tendo.
I've been defeated by my son.
I've let myself become slothful.
It's inevitable that
one's child will someday
surpass one's own
strengths and abilities.
But it's far too early for me
to be beaten by my son, Ranma,
yet.
I must remain a lofty
hurdle that he can't easily
clear in order to help him
become a great martial arts
fighter.
If you're that determined,
then I'll assist you, Saotome.
Oh, this is why
I've become so weak.
I can't lose again.
Why do you do it, Saotome?
It's not right.
You keep cheating on me.
[inaudible].
[groan]
Come on, Pops.
Quit lying around
and get working out.
I'll even be your
sparring partner.
I want you to be
like a lofty hurdle
that I have to clear to succeed.
[whimpering]
[groan]
Man, that feels good!
AKANE: Hey, you better go
easy on your dad, Ranma.
What for?
I deserve to give him some
payback once in a while.
You could at least wait till
he gets some more practice
under his belt.
Maybe I should show him
how weak he really is.
[footsteps]
(VOICEOVER) He's come for me.
[groan]
No!
Dad, what are you doing?
Not that position!
The Saotome Perch Position--
the stance of total submission,
indicating that the opponent can
do whatever he wants with you.
I know what you had
in mind so don't do me
the disrespect of
trying to deny it.
You want to make me give up my
position as your martial arts
trainer.
If my son wants to terminate
me as his martial arts trainer,
so be it.
I'll bow out gracefully.
What are you getting
all serious about, Pops?
You just lost a couple
times, that's all.
Besides, it wouldn't
seem right to kick you
when you're down
and out like this.
Oh, Ranma.
[snoring]
Huh?
You were going to
try and strangle me.
You were the one who was going
to deliver the coup de grace.
Thanks a lot, Pop.
I didn't get a wink
of sleep last night.
Huh?
Pop's gone.
"Don't try to find me.
Genma Saotome."
Ranma, do you realize
what this means?
Maybe he ran away from Ranma
because he was scared of him.
But the odd thing
is that our father
has disappeared, as well.
Saotome, what's that
exercise supposed to prove?
What's it for, Saotome?
Tell me, Saotome.
What's it for?
Come on.
Tell me, Saotome.
Huh?
Mr. Saotome?
What are you doing here?
[groan]
But I wasn't out
looking for you.
RANMA: Huh.
I was wondering
what you were up to.
So you've run away to join a
circus, have you, Ling Ling?
AKANE: Ranma!
Ranma, please.
[groan]
Let's hear from
his better half.
Admit it!
I scare the wits out of you.
You wish, Pop.
Huh!
I have something to say, and
I'll only say it one time.
[scream]
Ranma!
From this day on, you and I
are no longer father and son.
What?
No, wait!
Saotome, that's
going way too far.
I won't listen
to your arguments.
This will be a duel
between two men.
And there shall be no
dependence between them,
making it the ultimate
fair and true battle.
I challenge you to a
match one week from today.
Is that clear?
Loud and clear.
This should be interesting.
Prepare yourself,
kid from nowhere land.
Count on it, prune
from nowheresville.
GENMA: You must have had
some kind of upbringing.
RANMA: Well, it's a good thing
you never raised any children.
[groan]
It's true.
A man's world is harsh, indeed.
Sounds pretty
stupid, if you ask me.
Ranma, do you have to
leave home, as well?
Are you seriously
going to fight him?
I have to get
serious about this.
Pops made up his mind.
He's determined to defeat
me in next week's match.
It doesn't seem
right-- a father and son
fighting like this.
Huh?
[scream]
[groan]
He's going to regret this.
Ouch.
You're right about one thing.
I think he is serious.
[groan]
Hi.
What are you doing here?
So Ranma's left
to train, as well?
Wouldn't it be best
to just make up?
Is that what he wants to do?
No, but still.
Listen, Alane.
It's like I said this morning.
This is a serious fighting
match between two grown men.
It's different from the
kind of good natured scrap
we usually have.
AKANE: Yeah, I know,
but this whole thing
started with little
squabbles over food.
And it's probably
true that Ranma
took your last cup
of instant noodles
while you were stranded in the
mountains during the storm.
But it's also true that
when Ranma was little,
you stole his rice
cakes and his crackers
and his rice bowls and
his stew and shish kebabs
and a whole bunch of
other things, right?
Just call it even.
You're missing the
whole point, Akane.
What?
The time has finally
come for Ranma--
[gasp]
To take flight from my nest.
It's a happy occasion
and yet somehow so sad.
What a beautiful sunset.
[animal noises]
(VOICEOVER) It's nice to be
all by myself for a change.
Come to think of it, I've
never been apart for my pop,
ever since I was a little kid.
GENMA: What's the matter, Ranma?
Daddy.
What's on your mind, Ranma?
You're so warm, Daddy.
[sigh]
[growl]
[scream]
That stupid old man!
He even plagues my
dreams at night.
Huh?
A blanket?
No way.
Huh?
So it wasn't a dream.
Pop really was in the cabin.
Huh?
[groan]
I can't take it anymore!
[echo]
[grunt]
[yelling]
Huh?
Hey, you!
Look out!
[grunting]
[laughter]
Young man, so did my show
of strength impress you?
A lot of avalanches
around here, so you
have to keep on your toes.
Oh, for crying out loud.
You threw that rock,
you stupid Pop!
Stupid Pop?
Hate to disappoint
you, but you're
mistaking me for another.
My name, you ask-- let's
see, they call me--
[groans]
You just don't know
when to give it a rest.
There's only one week
to go before our match.
What are you doing?
[groan]
Figures he'd try to interrupt
my practice and throw me off.
Boo.
Huh?
It looks like your
dad misses you, Ranma.
Hey, how did you
guys find me out here?
Saotome told us where you were.
He said he was sure we
could find you up here.
Huh?
AKANE: I know your dad vents
from time to time, Ranma.
But he really misses you.
That lame excuse for a father?
He kept on saying that you're
not father and son anymore.
But a son will
always remain a son.
It's not in your father
to despise you, Ranma.
Huh?
Look!
It's a real panda!
Hey, what's going on?
Let's get him.
[chatter]
(VOICEOVER) He's been playing
with that tire for a long time.
What kind of training
is that supposed to be?
Take that, panda.
[laughter]
[groan]
SOUN (VOICEOVER):
He kept on saying
that you're not father
and son anymore,
but a son will
always remain a son.
It's not in your father
to despise you, Ranma.
[yelling]
Give me a break, will you?
Show some self respect and
take off that stupid mask!
I did this for you.
I thought it would
be easier to fight me
if I looked like someone else.
[gasp]
Huh?
Forget to pack up your razors
when you ran away from home?
Huh.
Before this match
is over, you'll
come to regret ever making
me take off that mask.
What?
Prepare yourselves, gentlemen.
The Saotome Ultimate
Martial Arts Challenge
will now commence.
Start!
[grunts]
[groan]
[gasp]
Had enough already, Pops?
Calling it quits?
[groan]
[laughter]
Huh?
Hm.
That did it.
I'm finally ready
for this match.
Now I feel like I can fight
you and resist the temptation
to hold back.
The spirit that's been
in my mind all this time
has finally started to emerge.
[growling]
Huh?
Pop's become giant.
Saotome's a Goliath.
He's summoned up all
his fighting spirit.
You can't scare me with that!
Ahh!
Huh?
(VOICEOVER) The
Cradle from Hell.
Huh?
[grunt]
(VOICEOVER) He
dodged my attack.
(VOICEOVER) What kind
of technique is that?
I felt something.
(VOICEOVER) The
Cradle from Hell.
So that's the trick
he's been practicing.
[laughter]
Huh?
Ranma's trapped.
There's no way out.
Huh.
Worried, Ranma?
There's no escaping me now.
(VOICEOVER) I don't know why,
but my gut instinct is to dodge
him for now.
At least until I find out
what that Cradle from Hell's
all about.
It's only the beginning.
This match will
last a long time.
MAN (ON TV): Is that
your final answer?
[humming]
(VOICEOVER) Three
hours have passed,
and neither of them
has moved an inch.
SOUN: To the
inexperienced viewer,
it seems that
they're not moving.
In actual fact, their
fighting spirits
are duking it out head to head.
This is indeed a silent
match, but it's very severe
and both contenders must be
on the verge of exhaustion.
Keep your eyes peeled.
Something's bound to happen.
Give it up, Dad.
Huh?
[groan]
Oh!
Ugh!
No wonder you weren't moving!
You were sleeping
with your eyes open.
I was just having a nice dream.
Those were the happy times when
you were still a young boy.
I almost forgot this match,
thinking about you when
you were young and innocent.
Ranma.
I'm glad you woke
me up for this!
(VOICEOVER) No!
The Cradle from Hell!
(VOICEOVER) You've reached
the point of no return.
[yelling]
[scream]
Look!
The Cradle from Hell!
[whimpering]
And here we have
the same position
the panda used when
playing with the tire.
But how's this technique
going to defeat Ranma?
Come to Papa.
Feel Daddy's whiskers
just like you
used to when you were little.
He's trying to get away!
Can you blame him with
the seven day growth?
Let go of me!
[groan]
No wonder I was
getting the creeps!
[groan]
[scream]
(VOICEOVER) That was disgusting.
But now I can finish him off.
(VOICEOVER) Come
to Papa, my son.
[scream]
Don't look at me like that!
Stop doing that!
[scream]
Stop it!
Over here.
Come to me, son.
Get away from me, Pops!
[scream]
Hm.
It seems as though this
match is far from over yet.
This is the most ridiculous
excuse for a fight
that I've ever seen in my life.
So this is what they mean
by a fight to the death.
Let's hit the sack.
RANMA: Let me go!
[scream]
[laughter]
If you hate this
so much, then I'm
going to be reincarnated
over and over again,
and you'll never be able to
escape my prickly love embrace.
I am never going to have
a match with you again.
Ah.
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER): Bonjour,
mademoiselle Ranma.
You're Madame St. Paul
from Chateau Chardin.
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
Madame St. Paul's Cry for Help.
We'll see you there.