[music playing]
NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes school of martial arts.
-Here we go!
-Hi-yah!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo training hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma's
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
-Watch.
-Incredible!
-Behold, the technique
preserved through 3,000 years
of Chinese Amazon history,
the Breaking Point or Bakusai
Tenketsu.
-Bakusai Tenketsu?
-Can I defeat Ranma
using the Breaking Point?
-Well, now, shall
I teach it to you?
-Oh, would you?
Oh, please, if it helps me
defeat Ranma, I'll do anything.
Please, teach it to me.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): The breaking
point, Ryoga's great revenge.
-Yo, Pop.
I don't believe this.
Stupid old man.
As soon as I turn my back on
him, he runs for the hills.
[grunts]
COLONGE: Oh, good grief.
Look at the miserable fool.
How many times do
I have to tell you?
Look for the breaking point.
Listen to me.
You must learn to find
the breaking point
using your mind and
not with your eyes.
[shouts]
-Ryoga, you fool.
If you cannot master this,
the simplest of techniques,
you haven't got a chance
of defeating Ranma.
You will lose.
-Ranma!
[shouts]
[rustling]
-Huh?
Mr. Saotome.
-Uhh?
-Hm?
RANMA: Ha!
Ha.
Ha!
Huh?
Yo, Pop.
What are you doing here?
I thought you took
off hours ago.
What?
Did you get lonely?
-I was on reconnaissance.
Know thy enemy and know thyself.
That's a prime tenet of the
Saotome school of Anything
Goes Martial Arts.
-You mean, in
other words, you've
been sneaking around
and spying on Ryoga.
Look, Pop.
Don't be putting
yourself out for me.
I'll be just fine.
Ryoga ain't got a chance.
-Well, since you seem
so confident, boy--
-Huh?
What are you doing?
-Digging your grave, boy.
It may be the last
thing I can do for you.
-Hey!
That's bad luck.
Quit it.
-Listen to me, Ranma.
Your rival is learning the
deadly Breaking Point technique
as we speak.
-Huh?
Breaking Point?
-None other.
Everything in nature has its
own breaking point-- mountains,
snakes, frogs, dogs,
birds-- even insects.
Any one of them
can be obliterated
with a touch of a finger.
Even the human body.
-Even the human body?
Where in heck's the
breaking point for that?
-Foolish boy!
If we knew that, the
technique would be ours!
I saw him practicing
it with my own eyes.
-So like, OK.
Whatever, but what about
if I stay away from him?
How's about that?
What if he can't even touch me?
It'll be-- huh?
-Let's test that theory, boy.
Ah-ow!
-Are you crazy?
[screams]
GENMA: If you can stun the
bees without being stun,
then you'll be safe
from the Breaking Point.
Otherwise--
-Ha!
Just watch me.
Ow.
Ow!
Argh.
-Those bees were
tougher than I thought.
RYOGA: [shouts]
-Ah!
[gasps] Ryoga!
[grunts] Are you OK?
You poor guy!
COLONGE: Did he faint again?
I've told him, over and over,
see with the mind and not
with the eyes.
-But don't you think he's
had quite enough for one day?
COLONGE: If you're so worried
about the poor boy's welfare,
why don't you give up on Ranma
and devote yourself to Ryoga?
-Excuse me?
RYOGA: [groaning]
-Oh, Ryoga.
-Hold, woman.
Don't interfere where
you're not wanted, got that?
As far as I'm
concerned, (SHOUTING)
defeating Ranma is the
only thing on my mind!
RANMA: [shouts]
-Come and get it.
RANMA: Ow!
[groans]
-Don't overdo it, eh, Ranma?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I
don't care what it takes,
no matter how dangerous.
Stupid, stupid, stupid, Akane,
no way I'm going to lose.
No way.
-OK, any time.
-All right, prepare yourself.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Not with
the eyes, but with the mind.
See with the mind's eye.
-Yeah.
[shouting]
-Nice try, sonny boy.
-No way!
I felt it.
-If you'd just clear your
mind like I told you,
you'd be able to do it.
-Oh, no!
Now, you listen up.
The only thing that's
on my mind right
now is how I'm going
to defeat Ranma.
My mind is absolutely clear.
-Hm?
AKANE: Hey, you two.
Dinner!
-Wha?
We'll be right down, Akane.
[laughs]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Why
is he laughing like that?
Could it be that he's-- oh, no.
Has he learned the
Breaking Point already?
Ranma!
Ryoga's been practicing so
hard, I can't hardly believe it.
It's already been six
days since I left Ranma.
Is he taking care of himself?
Is he eating properly?
-Ah, there's nothing like
catching your won dinner.
How's yours coming out?
-Huh?
Oh, fine.
[gags] That's weird.
I guess I made another
mistake somewhere.
[laughs] That's OK.
Unlike Ranma, at least Ryoga
likes the taste of my cooking.
-If things are so bad between
you, why not accept Ryoga?
Give up on Ranma, and
let Shampoo marry him.
Everyone would be much happier.
-Well, maybe it would make
you happy, but not me.
-So you intend to keep my
son-in-law for yourself then?
-Who said that?
I didn't say that!
-Shh.
Uh, I just sensed something.
-Well, what?
-Hey!
Wait!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): It's Ryoga.
-I feel it!
Bakusai Tenketsu!
-Oh, Ryoga!
-That a boy, Ryoga!
-Heh, I got you now, Ranma.
-All right!
-At last, the day is here.
-By the time this
sun sets, you'll
be begging for your life, Ranma.
[laughs]
-Ranma.
No.
-I've been waiting
for this, Ranma.
AKANE: Hey!
What's the big idea of
kidnapping me in my sleep?
This was your idea!
-Patience.
It'll be over soon.
Well, now, are we both
clear on the terms?
The winner will get Akane Tendo.
If Ryoga wins, he and
Akane will be a couple.
Then you, son-in-law,
become Shampoo's bridegroom.
That way, everyone is happy,
and we have peace at last.
-All right, look here.
-Oh, now I get it.
So that's why you went and
sided with Ryoga against me.
-You be quiet!
I've come here to do one
thing, and that's defeat you
and nothing else.
Do you understand?
All my training and my
hardship has come down to this!
-Grr.
-[shouting]
[theme music]
-So much for your
fancy training.
You can't even focus.
-Ah, shut up, Ranma!
-Oh, let me guess.
This is some kind
of smokescreen.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): It's obvious
that's Ranma's going to win.
Ryoga is always in the
center of the blast,
so he keeps getting hit
with those rock pieces.
Ranma isn't taking
any damage at all.
Why did Ryoga suffer so much
to learn that technique?
Was all his training
for nothing?
I can't believe she'd
let him lose like this.
COLONGE (VOICEOVER):
[chuckles] You'll
learn the true terror of the
Bakusai Tenketsu soon enough.
-Hey, give it up, man.
Those rocks are hurting
you more than me.
-Shut up!
-I guess I'll have to put
you out of you misery.
Heh, that was easy.
[crackling]
Huh?
What's he doing?
-[laughs]
-Ryoga!
-H-how did you do that?
-That didn't hurt at all, Ranma.
It's felt like a baby's kick!
-What did you say?
I kicked you hard enough to bust
that stupid head of yours open!
Of course it hurt!
-That's it!
Now, I get it.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): [grunting]
[grunting] [shouting]
-The training wasn't
wasted at all.
It's made you stronger.
COLONGE: [laughs]
-Huh?
-Huh
-Well, son-in-law, do you still
think it's too easy for you?
-What are you laughing at?
I got plenty of tricks left.
-No, you don't.
All you practiced
was running away.
-[grunts]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): She's right.
AKANE: Ranma, don't
you dare lose!
-Excuse me?
-Did you forget?
I'm the big prize in this
stupid little contest
of yours. -What's so
great about that, and what
makes you think I care anyway?
-If you lose the match,
Ryoga and I will have to--
-Are you sure you wouldn't
be happier that way?
-That's it.
-Enough small talk.
Ryoga's waiting.
-[gasp]
-[gasp] [shrieks]
-Hey, what'd you do that for?
-Get your hands off me!
I hate you!
-Ranma!
[shouts]
-Bakusai Tenketsu Block!
Not much good without
your hands free, are you?
[shouts]
-You just don't get
it, do you, Ranma?
You can't hurt me!
You can't defeat me, Saotome!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): His
kicks, his punches--
they have no effect.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Ugh.
I've got no choice.
I didn't want to use
this technique, but--
-Yaaaah!
-Saotome Anything Goes
martial arts final attack.
-What?
Saotome final attack?
-Ready?
Set!
Run away!
-Huh?
What?
-He ran!
-Huh?
[wind blowing]
GENMA (VOICEOVER): The
Saotome final attack
is founded on three
principals-- speed, strategy,
and separation.
-In other words,
run away until you
can think of something
better to do?
How do you call yourself
a martial artist?
-Curse you, Ranma!
Where are you hiding?
RANMA: I'm over here.
-Try again, Ranma!
-[grunts]
-[laughs]
[groans]
-Ha!
How was that?
Bet you felt that one.
-That's strange.
The rebound he got off
that tree shouldn't
have been that effective.
-What did you say?
RYOGA: Now you've done it!
[shouts]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): No
rebound this time, either.
That's it!
That's got to be it!
It looks like a single
attack, but he's
using the Chestnut fist to hit
the same spot over and over.
He could win after all!
-We'll see about that.
-Did it work?
Did I-- beat him?
-There's no chance of
Ranma winning this fight.
-Huh?
But how can you say that?
You saw what he did.
Huh?
-It's not over yet--
not by a long shot.
[chuckles]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): He's
some kind of monster.
-Those punches are good, but how
long can you keep it up, Ranma?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): He's right.
If he keeps this up, he's
going to wear me down.
Man, I got to think
of something fast.
-Surrender!
-Hey, don't just stand there.
-Eat this!
Bakusai Tenkestu!
-Oh, no!
Ranma!
-[grunts]
-Now, Ryoga!
This is the end.
Haaaaaa!
-[groans]
-[gasp]
-I won.
[shouts]
AKANE: Ranma!
Hey!
Ranma!
-Oh, well.
RANMA: [breathing heavily]
-Ryoga, you big jerk.
Just look you now.
[whirring noise]
-What a pity.
Here I went through
all that trouble
to train Ryoga so he'd take
the girl away from you.
That's my son-in-law, though.
-Why you-- how dare you teach
an unstable type like Ryoga
a dangerous trick like that?
-What dangerous
trick do you mean?
-[gasp] [shouts]
-You don't mean this little
old Bakusai Tenketsu?
-[shouts]
-Oh, relax.
The Bakusai Tenketsu
Breaking Point technique
was developed for
work in the quarries.
It has no effect
on the human body.
-[whimpering]
-Did you hear me?
No effect, I said.
-It's lucky for you
that I'm not the type
to hold a grudge, Rama.
Give my best to Akane.
Farewell.
-It's Bushido for a
defeated warrior to leave.
We won't see him
around for some time.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Ryoga.
[dog barking]
-You two should slow down.
You'll make yourself sick.
-Give me more.
-All right.
-Ah, there's nothing like a
home-cooked meal, is there?
KASUMI: Here you go.
AKANE: Oh, look!
P-chan.
Just in time.
Let's have some
dinner, OK? [giggles]
-I thought you were going to
make yourself scarce, porky.
-Quiet, I won't have
you bullying him now
that he's finally home again.
-[squeals]
-Oh, so much for not
holding a grudge.
RYOGA: W-wh-what do
you think you're doing?
You cut that out.
AKANE: Oh, get over it, Ranma.
I can't believe you're
jealous of P-chan.
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): What?
A dojo destroyer?
How can Ranma go on a date with
Shampoo at a time like this?
Well, I'll defend the Tendo
training hall all by myself
if I have to.
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
"Danger at the Tendo Dojo."
See you there.