[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
"P-- P-- P-Chan!
He's Good for Nothing."
[dog barking]
-Ryoga, you're the--
-Ranma, make sure you wash
him all over, especially
behind the ears.
-Uh, so then, you're the pig?
-You're dead.
-Wait.
Does this really mean
you did go to Jusenkyo?
-I've endured unbearable
torments chasing after you.
China is a big place,
but it's even bigger
when you're crossing it on foot.
Mile after mile after mile.
And then, one fateful day--
-Wait up, you old fool.
Hiya!
Come back here.
Come back here!
-Some crazy girl had
knocked me off the cliff
and straight into the lake.
And then, that's when I--
that's when I realized that--
[pig squealing]
I'd been cast into hell.
-Oh, sir, you find too,
too delicious piglet.
Looks very juicy.
I make famous Cantonese-style
sweet and sour pork for you.
See, here, Jusenkyo,
there are very famous,
very cursed spring
called Iton Ichiwan.
There are very tragic
legend of piglet
that drowned there
1,200 year ago.
Oh, very terrible legend, sir.
Now, whoever fall in spring,
take a body of black piglet.
I think maybe this one come
from cursed Jusenkyo spring,
drowned black piglet, no?
Ah, sir, you hear?
I make a funny joke, no?
-Ah!
Hot, hot, hot!
You human, not pig.
No can eat this one.
-My god, if I hadn't
changed back into a human,
they'd have made me
into sweet and sour pork
and eaten me for dinner.
This is all your fault.
If you'd only showed up to
take your beating like a man.
-Now wait a minute,
Ryoga, didn't you
say that it was some
strange girl who
kicked you into
the cursed spring?
And wasn't it a panda
who tried to eat you?
-So what's your point?
-So how is it possible that
it's all my fault then?
-Go on.
-It was the girl and the panda.
It wasn't-- uh- a
panda and a girl?
[door opening]
-Huh?
-A-- a panda and a girl?
[giggling]
That girl-- now I get it.
The one who ruined my
life, Ranma, it was you!
I'm going to kill you!
-Ow, hey, wait a minute.
Hey, wait.
Listen--
-Huh?
That's cold.
No fair, Ranma.
-We'll, ah, talk a
little bit later, OK?
After you've cooled
down, of course.
K Ryoga?
Ow!
[pig squealing]
-What are they doing in there?
-Come back here,
you little runt.
Do you think you're the
only one who's suffering?
Ugh, you scratched
me you little beast.
You ruined my
perfect complexion.
-Ranma, what do you
think you're doing?
-Oh, you little coward.
Look at you, hiding
behind Akane.
-Ranma!
-Little runt!
-Stop it!
-Hey!
-Are you OK?
Oh, he's scared.
Poor baby.
Come on, let's go.
-Just hold it.
Where are you going?
-We're going to bed.
-But you can't.
He's the-- that pig is a--
-Well, go on.
-He's a-- he's not really a--
-Don't worry, baby.
I won't leave you
with that nasty Ranma.
Be a good boy and
stop crying, OK?
What?
-I don't believe this.
Keep your stupid baby.
See if I care.
-Huh?
What's with him all of a sudden?
Why is he so upset?
I can't believe he's
jealous of a pig.
No, it couldn't be, no way.
Ranma's not jealous.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
You'll get yours, Ryoga.
[growling]
-Listen here, unless you
want me to blow your cover,
be quiet, pig.
[whimpering]
That's a good piggy.
Stay still.
Whoa!
-Hm?
Huh?
Ranma?
-I, uh-- I, uh-- Ah,
it's not what you think.
I-- you've got to believe me.
I, uh-- It's not
what you-- it's him.
It's Ryoga.
It's--
-Where?
Where is Ryoga?
I don't see him, only you.
You animal!
[scream]
-Ugh.
He won't get away with this.
He won't.
-It's not what it seems.
NABIKI: Ranma,
what you and Akane
do in the middle of the
night is your own business,
but try to keep it down, huh?
-No, they mustn't.
Even if they are
engaged, they should
wait until they're married.
NABIKI: You're so
old-fashioned, Kasumi.
KASUMI: There's nothing wrong
with being old-fashioned,
Nabiki.
NABIKI: My own sister, a prude.
-A little initiative goes
a long way, I always say.
Initiative, yes sir,
that's the ticket.
-I told you, it's not
what it looks like.
I'm innocent.
Innocent!
Well, Ryoga?
Why don't you say something?
-Hmph.
There he goes again.
We don't see any Ryoga
here, isn't that right,
little P-chan?
-Hm?
P-Chan.
-Oh, he's so cute.
-Right, P as in "pig,"
and Chan as in "cute."
-Aw, let me hold him, please?
-Let me hold him
next, OK, Akane?
-Where on earth did you get
such a cute little pig, Akane?
-He just showed up one day.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I
hate that little runt.
-I'm sorry, P-Chan, but
I have to leave you here
until my classes are over, OK?
I won't be long.
What a good boy you are.
I'll be back soon.
-Hello, Ryoga.
Aren't you just a
pwecious wittle piggy?
Thanks to you,
they all think I'm
some kind of pervert
or something.
Remember that fight you're
always yelling about?
Well, I'm ready if you are.
Come back here, you little runt!
Ryoga!
-Don't be too long, you guys.
-What is that?
-It's a black pig.
-Oh, wow.
-Is it ever cute.
-I said wait, Ryoga.
[screaming]
-Get out of here, you pervert!
Lecher!
Peeping Tom!
-What a creep,
like, total loser.
[running water]
[gasp]
-Get a load of these!
Any questions?
Oh, you slippery little runt.
Wait!
Oh, where'd that
little creep go?
Ryoga!
Gotcha!
Hm?
Thank you.
What's going on here, Ryoga?
You're the one who's always
wanting me to fight you.
Have you forgotten?
Or is it that you actually
like being called P-Chan?
-Shut up!
How could you ever
understand my feelings?
How could you ever know
the suffering I've seen?
It's been hell, I tell you.
Pure hell.
[music plays]
Huh?
Somehow, I managed to
make it back to Japan.
Yes, I made it back at last.
Wah!
And even though I'm
under this curse--
a curse I'll carry the
rest of my life-- somehow,
she finds it in her
heart to love me.
-You're nuts!
She don't love you!
-Yes, she does!
-That's just your
sick imagination.
-To think that she lives
under the same roof as you.
There's no justice
in this world.
You keep your hands
off her, Ranma.
-Hey, listen pal.
Don't you drag me into this.
Wishing don't make
it true, you know.
-So that's it.
You're in love with her too.
-Shut up, Ryoga.
OK?
Come on, let's fight.
That hurt.
What'd you do that for?
-I told you, stop picking
on P-Chan, you big bully.
-What do you mean P-Chan?
There's no P-Chan here.
Where do you see a--
He's-- he's not-- I mean--
-Exactly how stupid
do you think I am?
-Huh?
Oh, I give up.
[school bell]
-P-Chan.
Here, P-Chan.
P-Chan?
I wonder where he's gone.
-Look, it's a miniature pig.
-Yeah, it's a black one.
-You're right.
[whimpering]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): P-Chan.
WOMAN: Oh, honey, look.
How cute.
-Looks like he's lost.
-Come to mama, precious.
Oh, he's such a good baby.
-I think he's taking a
liking to you mother.
-Oh, honey, after
all these years,
we've been blessed with
our very own bundle of joy.
-See the grand feast we prepared
in your honor, dear Pork Chop.
Please, eat all you like.
-P-Chan.
P-Chan?
Where-- where are you?
Oh, P-Chan.
-It's not the end
of the world, Akane.
I'm sure he'll be back soon.
It's just, he's got no sense
of direction, that's all.
-I'm looking for P-Chan,
Ranma, not Ryoga.
What-- and what do
you care anyway, huh?
-Aw, that guy is
good for nothing.
-Mama's baby is such a
pampered wittle piggy.
Look how precious
our Pork Chop is.
-Yes, mother, he's
very pwecious.
Let's give him a bath, shall we?
Sasaki, prepare
the bath, will you?
SASAKI: At once, sir.
-Oh, won't that
be fun, Pork Chop?
-Do enjoy your bath, sir.
-Oh, Pork Chop, isn't this nice?
Here we go.
-P-Chan.
Oh, P-Chan.
-How's the water,
my little mugwump.
Oh!
-This is nice.
Are you happy now?
-Why Pork Chop, what happened?
-I'm a human being, not a pig!
-Why, even better.
I'll make you my heir.
How's that, Pork Chop?
-You'll what?
-But what if he
was in an accident?
-He's fine, I tell you.
Even he's not that stupid.
-Don't start acting
like you care, Ranma.
All you've ever done
is been mean to him.
-Well, I-- well,
hey, what do we know?
He could be home already?
He's pretty smart
for a pig, right?
AKANE: Oh, I hope you're right.
SERVANTS: Master Pork Chop.
SERVANTS: Master
Pork Chop, come here!
SERVANTS: Master Pork
Chop, please come back.
Please!
Master Pork Chop.
-Hey, wasn't that--
-Yeah.
-P-Chan!
P-Chan!
-Please come back with
us, Master Pork Chop.
-Forget it.
There's just no way I'm handing
over P-Chan to these guys.
No way.
-Oh well, guess
I've come this far.
I can't believe I'm saying
this, but fellas, there's
no way I can let
you have that pig.
-So you intend to prevent
us from doing our duty?
-He can try.
-You'll have to fight us first.
-What?
-Get him.
-Hey, that hurt.
-Have you had enough, sir?
-I can't believe this.
-Ranma, are you all right?
Just hang in there, OK?
-Huh?
Leave it to me.
-Why you little--
-Here we go.
Phew.
Akane, thank you.
-Wh-- I-- I was just
protecting P-Chan.
-Jeez, how uncute of you.
WOMAN: Oh, dear Pork Chop.
-Huh?
-And here we've
grown so fond of him.
-I'm sure he would have
been a credit to the family.
Aw, how cruel fate is.
Guess we'll have to find another
heir for the family, mother.
-Oh.
-Don't worry, mother.
We'll find one who looks just
like our long lost Chiro Chiro.
-What is the matter
with you, pop?
Aw, jeez.
I don't know why I was sticking
up for Ryoga like that.
That was really stupid of me.
What was I thinking?
I mean, if I'd been
smart, I would of
let that rich couple keep
him, and then everybody
would have been happy.
That's what I should have done.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): OK, then.
Hm?
-Hm.
-Uh.
AKANE: You're
unbelievable, Ranma!
[scream]
NABIKI: You're kidding.
He tried to sneak
into your room again?
You're quite the Romeo,
aren't you, Ranma?
KASUMI: But it isn't right.
He can't keep doing this.
SUON: Initiative,
son, that's the way.
[panda grunting]
KASUMI: Father, don't
encourage him like that.
Yes, sir, a little initiative
will go a long way.
KASUMI: It doesn't matter
that they're engaged.
They're still too young to.
-Oh, what have I
done to deserve this?
-We're not listening, are we?
[theme music]
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Looks like they
want me to compete in the
upcoming rhythmic gymnastics
competition.
Get a load of my
opponent-- Kodachi
the Black Rose is
something else.
Hey, what do you mean she
fell in love with Ranma
at first sight?
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
"Ranma Meets Love Head-On!
Enter the Delinquent
Juvenile Gymnast!"
See you there.