[music playing]
[gong]
-[speaking japanese]
NARRATOR: The last
days of Happosai.
-I'm serious.
She hasn't been
wrong yet, not once.
-But how can you be sure
it's not a coincidence?
I mean, come on.
The future isn't something you
can predict with tarot cards,
now is it?
-So Miyo, can you, like,
do this for a career?
-[laughing] I don't see why not.
After all, I have been
blessed with a second sight.
Other women in my family
have been successful.
I don't see why I wouldn't be.
Better get your cards read
now before I'm too famous.
So who wants to go next?
-Let's see.
Who else hasn't had
their future read.
Oh, yeah, Akane!
Well, you haven't had
them done yet, have you?
-Well, no.
But there's nothing I
really want to know. so--
-Oh, come on.
Don't be like that.
I mean, what about Ranma?
I'm sure you'd like
to know about him.
-N-not really.
I would like to know
about the dojo, though.
So maybe I should get my
future read after all.
-The cards have spoken.
Ah, yes, of course.
Within one week's time,
you and your fiance
are destined to be married.
-What?!
-Me, married?
You sure?
No way!
It's a lie!
There's got to be a mistake!
You must have read them
wrong or something.
-Ah, but the cards
never lie, you see?
If they see something
will happen, it'll happen.
-Oh, my gosh, Akane.
I had no idea you and
Ranma had gone so far.
-Yeah, no kidding.
I mean, I thought
best friends were
supposed to tell each
other everything.
What do you want for
a wedding present?
-Yeah, what do you want?
-Who's your maid of honor?
[interposing voices]
RANMA: Wait up, you old freak!
-What do you know.
Here comes the bridegroom.
-Return that underwear!
I told you the
school's off limits.
-I see you've got some
underwear here yourself, my boy.
Who would have known?
Ha-ha.
RANMA: That's cause
I took it from you.
HAPPOSAI: [laughing]
[glass breaking]
-Did I just see an old man?
[gasps] The tower!
[gasps]
-Slippery little freak.
I'll take care of him
once we get home, though.
Just you wait.
You know, for such an old
guy, he ain't half bad.
He ought to last at
least another 100 years.
-Uh, Ranma?
-Yeah?
-Do you believe in destiny?
-Destiny?
Oh, I get it.
Everyone's talking about that
whacked-out chick at school.
I'll bet you had
your cards read, huh?
Nah.
You make your own fate,
as far as I'm concerned.
So, uh, why do you ask?
Is there something about
me in your future, or what?
-Uh, none of your beeswax.
You don't believe in it, anyway.
RANMA: Ha!
I knew it!
AKANE: She did say something
else that worries me, though.
She said it right after you and
Happosai left the classroom.
MIYO (VOICEOVER):
That old man who
just ran though has
been marked by fate.
I fer the misfortune
of a coming illness
may somehow involve you, Akane.
Please be careful.
-Huh!
-Jeez, don't scare me like that.
-L-look!
AKANE: Huh?
RANMA: It's the
freak's collection.
AKANE: It's leading
up to our house.
RANMA: Yo, pops!
AKANE: Dad?
RANMA: Pops, what is it?
SOUN: Master, what's wrong?
GENMA: What is it, Master?
-Huh?
GENMA: Tell us!
RANMA: Gramps?
Gramps!
-Hmm?
What is it, Ranma?
-Well, you left your
collection laying all over.
-Keep it.
It's all yours.
-What?
But-- but you worked
really hard to build it.
You can't just throw it away!
-Sure I can.
-Here, Master.
We've brought you
something to eat.
-We can't have you wasting
away in your room now, can we?
It's your favorite snack.
-Take it away.
I don't want it.
All I want now is
to go to sleep.
Shut the door on your way out.
SOUN: [sighs] He's been
like that since he got home.
GENMA: Since when does
the master turn down food?
AKANE: He's definitely
acting strange.
The poor dear must be ill.
GIRL: The old lech starts acting
human and we call him sick?
RANMA: Hey, so long as
he's not bothering us,
he can stay in there
all day for all I care.
-Speaking of which, boy!
-Hey, that tea's cold, pop!
What are you doing?
Let me go.
-Master, catch!
-That you, Ranma?
Cover up.
You'll catch cold.
It is a far, far
better rest that I
go to than I have ever known.
-Master, don't go!
-Master, are you
saying you're leaving?
HAPPOSAI: I must.
-Master, you mustn't
talk like this.
Why, you're still in
the prime of life.
There's no reason
to believe you won't
be with us for another
hundred years at least.
SOUN: Saotome, look.
-What?
What is it?
What do you want?
-Look.
-Th-- th-- th-- that's snow
in the middle of summer.
SOUN: It's an evil omen.
[cawing]
-Soun, Genma.
-Go on.
We're listening.
-I'm not long for this world.
When that time comes,
you'll know what to do.
It's all written
down in my will.
SOUND AND GENMA: Master!
No!
HAPPOSAI: [gasping for air]
-If anything ever happened to
him, I don't know what I'd do.
-However, there's
a good possibility
that this time the
master may not recover.
-True.
Snow in the middle of summer,
ravens on the rooftop--
all signs are
pointing to the worst.
-Can the Anything Goes
School of Martial Arts
survive the loss
of the master who
founded its techniques
in the first place?
Is this the end?
-No!
Not so long as we're alive!
The Anything Goes School is
something for which we've
shed blood, sweat, and tears.
Are you ready to
throw it all away?
We have to do
something, whatever
it takes to make
sure it goes on.
-For our school, no
sacrifice can be too great.
-Whatever it takes, Tendo.
That's what we've got to do.
SOUND AND GENMA: Hmm!
[wind howling]
-[gasps] That has to be it.
Tarot cards, crystal
ball, Ouija board.
No matter what fortune-telling
method I use to try and predict
the future, the result
always comes out the same.
Something awful is about to
happen at the Tendo residence.
And it's probably
already started.
It's the old man,
just as I've foreseen.
He's destined to bring disaster.
-I think Pop and your dad were
up with the old man all night.
-Too bad it took something
like this for them
to finally be nice
to him, huh, Ranma?
-Yeah, I guess you're right.
-He is their master, after all.
It's only natural
that they're worried.
-Something was wrong
with him, though.
That's for sure.
I don't think we should
be too worried about him.
He'll be back to his
obnoxious self in no time.
-I hope you're right.
RANMA: Huh?
AKANE: Huh?
RANMA: What the heck is that?
Gee, what's the celebration for?
AKANE: It's in here too.
Nabiki, what's--
-Your future is about to
be decided in the dojo.
So you lovebirds had best
hurry up and get over there.
RANMA: OK.
We're here.
What do you want?
-I'm sure you both are aware
that the master's condition has
only gotten worse,
and that the master
himself seems to have somehow
lost the will to live.
Ranma, while the master
is still alive to see it,
I want you and Akane to wed,
to carry on the Anything Goes
School.
-What?!
-Marriage?
-Ranma, my boy,
it is your destiny
to sire enough children
to carry on the Anything
Goes School for
generations to come.
-Akane, it may be
asking a lot of you.
But you've known for a long
time now that it's your destiny
to be a good wife to Ranma.
-The ceremony will be held five
days from now in this dojo.
-As your future father-in-law,
son, I thank you.
-Thank you, Akane.
-Five days from now?
-I know it's an emergency.
But they're still
in high school.
Isn't it too soon?
-Seeing as it's not
a real marriage,
and there's no sense in
spending more than we have to,
how would you feel about
cold cuts and a no-host bar?
[thunder]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Akane, please be patient.
I'll be showering you with
souvenirs before you know it.
The strange feeling in the
air worries me, though.
Shouldn't it be the
middle of summer?
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
[rain]
RANMA: Oh, great.
This is all I need!
[rain]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I
can hardly believe it.
But if Master Happosai
doesn't get better soon,
five days from now Ranma
and I will be married!
-Stop worrying, Akane.
I'm telling you, this marriage
ain't never gonna happen.
It's gonna take a lot more than
this to stop the old freak.
I'll bet you money it's just
an act to try and scare us.
-You really think so?
[window rattling]
-Who's there?
[pig squealing]
-If it isn't P-Chan!
Ah!
[laughing] Look at you.
You're soaking wet.
You poor baby.
You must be so cold.
Let Mommy warm
you up in her bed.
AKANE: Honey!
-Huh?
-Honey, look.
RANMA: Hello, darling.
-Look what the storm brought--
our little bundle of you.
He looks just like you.
Ah!
-Oh, let me see.
[screams] [panting] Oh,
it was just a dream.
Oh, that's all it was.
[squealing]
After that, I don't think
I'll ever dare sleep again.
Huh?
Guess I'm not the
only one who's awake.
Akane.
What the heck's the
matter with you, Akane?
What, are you
sleepwalking or something?
-Ranma.
What are you doing here?
RANMA: Well, I, uh-- let's
just say I had a bad dream,
thought I'd come in
and work out a bit.
-What kind of a bad dream?
-J-- just, uh, you know, bad.
-Uh-huh.
-I'd rather not talk about it.
Um, Akane.
-Y-- yes?
RANMA: I'm, uh, you know,
still trying to get used to it.
It's not that I mind doing what
they're asking but, you know,
looking after the
dojo and stuff.
It might not be that bad.
[screams]
[pig squealing]
Aggh!
Ow, that hurt, you little-- uh!
So now what did I do
to tick you off, huh?
What are you suddenly
attacking me for, huh?
[pig growling]
Uh, c-- calm down now.
No need to, uh-- ah!
Mr. P!
That's enough!
That's enough, I said!
-Wh- why is P-Chan so
upset all of a sudden?
RANMA: OK!
OK!
Now cut it out!
Ow!
What did you do that for?
Hey!
That hurt!
What's the matter
with you, P-Chan?
-Ah, look what time it is?
Hey, why didn't you guys and
wake me up for school, huh?
-Relax, Akane.
There's a flood
warning at school
because of the heavy rain.
So we're off the hook
for a couple of days.
-Ah, what a relief.
That's great.
Hey where's Dad and--
-We think it's
nervous exhaustion.
-Huh?
-The both of them have
taken to their beds.
-Oh, Master, no.
D-- d-- don't-- don't leave us.
No.
-Oh, Master.
School.
We must protect--
-Hello, Akane.
Come in.
I've been expecting you.
I know it looks a little
strange, but trust me.
I know what I'm doing.
So what is it you wish to know?
-So it's Happosai's
illness that's
causing all this trouble?
-His illness?
Oh, no.
I'm afraid you misunderstood me.
The cause of his problem
isn't his illness.
It's his exhausted lifespan.
-His lifespan?
-I've been doing some research.
Although the old man was born
under an extremely lucky star,
once every 100 years the
alignment of the stars
becomes extremely unlucky.
AKANE: But, well,
I don't understand.
MIYO : Four days from now
will be the critical point.
That's when it will all
end one way or the other.
The scary thing is, since his
luck has been so good so far,
when it turns bad, it's
going to be really bad.
There could be a
terrible whiplash effect.
-But what should I--
-Don't look so gloomy.
I think I may have
a way to help you.
See?
It's all in here.
Every folk remedy of its type
collected everywhere from China
to Europe.
All the ingredients are
clearly written out.
AKANE: But-- but
where would I get--
MIYO : I said don't worry.
With all these jars I have, I'll
make you a little care package.
-Oh, Miyo.
Thank you.
-You'll need to boil
it for three days.
It's all up to you now, Akane.
Remember, we're dealing with
some powerful forces here.
There's always a chance
things could backfire.
So be extra careful.
-Ugh.
Like Miyo said, it's
all up to me now.
The future depends on it.
I've got to give it my best.
Mm.
-What is that girl doing?
-She said something
about a fold remedy.
Whatever it is, she
seems determined.
--[grunting] Stupid P-C. He
wasn't holding back at all.
What could I have done
to tick him off so much?
Come on, P-Chan!
Cut it out!
What are you so mad about?
[pig squealing]
How can I know what I
did unless you tell me!
[pig squealing]
Fine, then.
If that's the way you want it--
[screaming]
[gurgling]
Ryoga!
Little jerk's probably
washed out to sea by now.
Who knows when he'll
come back. [grunting]
AKANE: OK.
Let's see now.
What am I forgetting?
Eye of newt, check.
Toe of frog, check.
Hmm.
-Oh my-- what is she making?
-She must be making
her folk remedy.
-Talk about the cure being
worse than the disease.
-Hey, everyone.
I'm home!
[gasps] What is that smell?
-I've always loved you, Kasumi.
-Nabiki, we're not dead yet.
Akane's still up and about.
-I know.
That's precisely what
I'm worried about.
Ugh.
She must be getting closer.
-Hey, how are you guys feeling?
Here.
I brought you some nice gruel.
-We'll eat it!
We'll eat it already!
Just close the door!
-Good job, Akane.
I'll take it from here.
You just run along now.
-Hmm?
The whole family is depending
on me finishing this medicine.
If it'll work for Happosai,
it should work for them, too.
It's done!
Ah, there's still time.
-Uhhh.
[gulps] [screams]
-Don't die!
Don't die!
Oh, no!
Wake up!
-Seems he didn't make it.
Ah, well, there's no
flying in the face of
Huh?
wh-- wh-- what?
AKANE: I killed Happosai!
[sobbing]
-I feel I've been granted
a new lease on life.
-Wh-- what-- what's happening?
What's going on?
-The medicine must be working.
-Akane, you saved me!
AKANE: Glad you're
feeling better.
-[groaning]
GENMA: What is it, my boy?
-I-- I feel like a goose
just stepped on my grave.
AKANE: Ranma!
-[gasps]
-I've brought you some medicine.
I made it by myself.
Drink up and you'll
feel all better.
-I'm-- I'm feeling much better.
I-- why don't you
make Pop drink it.
-Oh, don't worry.
There's plenty to go around.
-I don't wanna!
GENMA: I, uh I'm feeling
better too, actually.
SOUN: Akane, listen
to your father now.
I-- I-- I don't need-- [gagging]
HAPPOSAI: Hey, babe.
How about a drink?
GIRL: Get off of me!
HAPPOSAI: How about you?
GIRL: Go away!
HAPPOSAI: Wanna go somewhere?
Huh?
You?
MIYO (VOICEOVER): Looks
like the old goat's
up to his old tricks.
He's got more energy
than men half his age.
AKANE: Hey, good
morning, you guys.
-Huh?
-Hey, Akane.
How are you?
-Akane.
Um, um, hi.
-Oh, Miyo.
Thanks to you, Grandfather's
back to his old self.
-You don't say.
That's, uh, great.
Yeah, uh-huh.
-I' don't get it.
-Akane, where's Ranma?
-Huh?
He, uh, he's kind of
got an upset stomach.
-Oh, so you mean
you're not married yet.
-Guess the tarot
cards were wrong, huh?
-But that's only because
of Grandfather's illness.
-Akane!
Ha!
The fortune lady's here, too.
-Oh, it's a monster!
[crash]
HAPPOSAI: Oh, no fair.
Ow.
-Go back to bed
already, will you?
[music playing]
-What?
Big sister Shampoo?
You're from the same
Chinese Amazon tribe as her?
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
"Two Too-Violent Girls,
Ling-Ling and Lung-Lung."
See you there.