[music playing]
[theme music]
[chatter]
[gasp]
The ocean!
The battle for Ms. Beachside.
Skin melting-- must find water.
Ah!
[grumbling]
Maybe I wouldn't be
so hot and bothered
if I didn't have your fur
coat stuck to my back!
[humming]
[grumbling]
Hm.
Huh?
BOTH: [gasping]
[chatter]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Uh-oh.
I wonder if this bathing suit's
too loud-- how embarrassing.
Hm?
Huh?
[chatter]
Hm?
--[sigh] Kasumi's so
popular with all the guys.
They haven't even left her side
from the second we stepped out
of the changing room.
Yeah.
So what's the big surprise?
Guys prefer to
take their chances
going after pretty women
rather than wasting
their time with tomboys.
Yeah, I guess.
Hm?
Hey, tomboy?
Who do you mean by that?
I'm just saying.
I don't understand why
all these boys I don't know
are asking me to
go out with them.
They're obviously
after you because of how
you look in that swimsuit.
How do you know
they didn't hear
about my cooking or something?
That's probably it.
Uh.
Oh, why didn't I think of that?
You're right.
It's probably your cooking.
By the way, you didn't see
where Nabiki got to, did you?
Well, I saw her, but that
was quite a while ago.
[chatter]
What's going on?
Hi, everyone.
Hey, you over there, no
stepping over the line now.
There's room for everyone.
There she is.
Let's get in closer.
GIRL: Look at that.
GIRL: That's so strange.
He's gonna cut them.
[evil laughter]
GIRL: Wow.
GIRL: Oh, hey.
[chatter]
[crowd cheering]
Step up, folks, and get
your nice, fresh watermelon
at 150 yen a slice.
MAN: Oh, I'll take a slice.
Yes, sir, coming right up.
BOTH: Uh.
[giggling]
GIRL: So good!
GIRL: Yeah!
What's Kuno doing here?
Why are you asking me?
How should I know?
Hm?
Uh.
[trumpet music playing]
I must be hallucinating
from all this intense heat.
There's a mailbox
hoping this way, Akane.
Don't be silly.
Honestly.
Charge!
That mailbox-- you
don't think it's--
Uh-oh, this seems
strangely familiar.
It's got to be him.
AKANE: Yeah.
Tsubasa is at your service
once again, ladies and gents.
It's been a long time.
Your order of veggie and
seafood okonomiyaki is up, boys.
That'll be 500 yen.
BOTH: [groaning]
TSUBASA: Phew,
it's hot out here.
Wait a second, if it
isn't Akane and Ranma.
This is some coincidence,
meeting up like this.
So, dressing as a boy today?
I am a guy!
--[awkward laugh] So, uh, what
are you doing here, Tsubasa?
Actually, I'm working
at Ukyo's beach stand.
Uh-oh.
I better get a move on!
No time to dawdle!
See you later!
Come by the shop
for a bit sometime.
So Ukyo's got a stand now, too?
Weird.
TSUBASA: Charge!
Huh?
Forget it, pops.
That's a guy, not a girl.
Bingo.
You don't say.
That's quite the figure.
[grumble]
TSUBASA: There you are, sweetie.
AKANE: Ooh, it looks yummy.
SOUN: Let's eat it
up while it's hot.
Mhm.
Sounds good to me.
Hey, Ukyo, how come
you hired Tsubasa
to work the stand with you?
Isn't it obvious, Ranma, honey?
'Cause it doesn't
cost me much money.
You southern gals sure know
how to stretch your yens,
don't you?
GENMA: Mhm.
Huh?
SHAMPOO: Hiya!
Ranma, you here.
Hello, everybody.
Sh-- Shampoo.
Ranma, Shampoo so happy
to see you here at beach.
What are you doing round here?
Setting up Shampoo's
store near here.
Ranma, you come eat
Shampoo's noodles?
Huh?
Ranma's just filled up on my
delicious veggie and seafood
okonomiyaki, so he
doesn't have any room left
for some greasy
roadside noodles.
Shampoo no talking to you.
What did you say?
Uh.
No!
What-- what's he doing here?
It's the ghost cat!
My bride.
I mean, who ordered some cold,
refreshing noodles, noodles
from my wifey, yeah?
Cat a little creepy, but
good worker and cheap labor.
MAOMOLIN: I'm back.
Yeah.
That was fast.
Well, good, because I've got
another delivery for you!
Nah, isn't it break time?
You'd better hurry, or
Shampoo will get mad.
Oh, you don't know how to
treat a kitty good-- despicable.
Yeah?
Mm.
Yeah, that girl is heaven-sent.
She'd make me the perfect bride.
You take care of this delivery.
Where do you
think you're going?
[eating noises]
Huh?
Well, I guess it is
close to lunchtime.
For today's lunch, Ranma
eat what Shampoo cook up.
Hold your horses.
Let's hear what Ranma
says about this.
Ranma no can live
on okonomiyaki alone.
My okonomiyaki is for
morning, noon, and dinnertime.
People eat it as a meal or as
a snack all around the clock
and never get tired of it.
Come on, you too.
Akane, give me a hand here.
Which one are you gonna choose?
RANMA: Oh.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
My dearest Akane.
I hope you are well.
The smell of autumn
is already in the air
here in the Japanese Alps.
[squealing]
MOUSSE: Well, well.
If it isn't Ryoga.
[squealing]
Sad little pig-- you're looking
pathetic as ever. [laughs] Ooh!
[quacking]
[squeal]
[quack]
What's all the racket?
Hey, look, it's a duck.
Get it.
[eating noises]
Excuse me, ladies.
If you're going to compete,
I have a good idea that
just might solve your problems.
What do you mean?
What is good idea?
Come here, and I'll
give you the details.
Man, this is just great.
Have you made up your mind what
you're having for lunch yet?
I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
Quit rushing me.
Sure.
'Cause either way, it
makes no difference to me.
[squealing]
AKANE: P-chan!
Hi, baby.
What are you doing down
here all on your own?
What?
What's this thing?
Ms. Beachside contest?
NABIKI: Looks like
fun, don't you think?
Huh?
Akane, you should
enter the contest.
Ukyo and Shampoo
are going in it.
And they're betting
Ranma's lunch.
Whichever one of us
stays in the contest
the longest is the one who gets
to cook Ranma his lunch today.
Well, it sounds like you two
have things all figured out.
It won't be much of a
contest with just two.
The more people who enter
it, the better it'll
be for business.
AKANE: Business?
What's the point of a
swimsuit contest if you
don't sell tickets to the guys?
Think of the profit margin.
KASUMI: Oh, here you are.
What are you all up to?
Oh, Kasumi, you've got to
enter the swimsuit contest.
That kind of
thing's not for me.
Why don't you enter, Akane?
Don't you start in
on me now, Kasumi.
Make no difference whether
Akane enter contest or not.
Pardon?
What's that supposed to mean?
SHAMPOO: Just what Shampoo say.
I'm entering, too!
Then it's all settled.
Let's go sell tickets!
TSUBASA: Charge!
I'm entering the contest!
You scrawny girls don't stand
a chance against Tsubasa!
What's this?
Can boys enter the
Ms. Beachside contest?
[grumbling]
Would you mind getting
away from me, Saotome?
You're making me hot.
[grumble]
Let's see.
That makes it four contestants.
[animal noises]
[chatter]
That's a whole mess of
people you got gathered there.
It's like I told you, old man--
location, location, location.
Don't say I never
told you nothing.
So this is where
the contest will be?
KODACHI: Yes, brother dear.
Kodachi, you're wearing
a lot of clothes.
Don't you find it hot?
I thought this
white outfit would
be perfect for a summer day.
Well, if you're
OK, then let's go.
Yes, dear.
Kodachi, you're not
going to the contest?
KODACHI: [giggle]
Of course I'm going.
I'll wave to you from up
on the stage, brother dear.
[grunt]
KODACHI: [laughs]
Voila, Ms. Beachside!
That's what I'll be called
from now on, brother dear.
She's mad.
KODACHI: [giggling]
Hello.
Sorry to keep you
waiting, folks.
The moment you've been waiting
for-- the Ms. Beachside contest
will now begin!
Huh?
What is that thing?
SOUN: The winner will receive
this succulent pig and duck!
[audience oohing and aahing]
So without further delay,
ladies and gentlemen,
let's begin the contest
you've all been waiting for!
Contestant number
one, Akane Tendo.
Akane Tendo!
Get going, girl.
You're up.
Oh!
[crowd oohing and aahing]
ALL: Wow, what a babe!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Oh, what
have I gotten myself into?
SOUN: Contestant
number two, Shampoo!
Contestant number
three, Ukyo Kuonji!
four, Kodachi Kuno!
[giggle]
SOUN: Contestant number
five, Tsubasa Kurenai!
Mwah, thank you, fans!
MAOMOLIN: Good luck, Tsubasa!
You're so cute!
Yeah!
[gasp] [grunt]
Whoa!
[yelling]
[grunt]
What a performance.
SOUN: And now for
the last contestant--
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Huh?
There's another contestant?
SOUN: Contestant number
six, Ranma Saotome.
[crowd oohing and ahhing]
Heh.
Figured she'd show up.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ranma?
What's he doing?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I've
got to win this thing,
otherwise those two will
never get off my back.
First is the swimsuit category.
Now if the audience would
please cast their votes.
TATEWAKI (VOICEOVER): Akane
Tendo or the pig-tailed girl--
both of them deserve my vote.
Akane Tendo or the
pig-tailed girl?
The pig-tailed girl
or Akane Tendo?
Akane Tendo or the
pig-tailed? (ANGRILY)
The pig-tailed girl
or Akane Tendo?
I-- [stutter] I just don't know!
I can't!
How is a man supposed to
decide between the two
loves of his life?
GIRL: Just cast your darn vote!
Look at this, Mommy.
SOUN: I will now the results
of the swimsuit category.
It is with enormous regret
that I must tell you
that as a result of your votes,
one person has been eliminated
from the contest.
Kodachi Kuno, thank
you for participating.
What's the deal?
This doesn't make any sense.
Maybe your lasso performance
scared off the voters.
How could you?
[crying] How could you?
Kodachi! [grunt]
Check out your feet.
Huh? [gasp] Oh.
So without further delay,
ladies and gentleman,
I would now like to proceed
with the singing category.
And the first will be--
Me, me, me, me, me.
It seems the first
performance will
be given by Tsubasa Kurenai.
You're on.
TSUBASA (VOICEOVER): [giggle]
My beautiful voice is gonna
blow them all out of the water.
--[inhales] (SINGING DEEPLY
AND OFF-KEY) Big boy,
I know you want me, big boy.
I've never heard
such a beautiful voice
in my entire life!
(SINGING) Big boy,
you'd do anything for me!
[grumble]
TSUBASA: (SINGING)
I can't feel it.
[grumble]
TSUBASA: [sigh] I
don't understand.
It's just not fair!
You're gonna listen
to the whole song!
You're gonna kill
all the voters!
[grumble]
But my song's not finished yet!
I won't allow you to speak
to my future bride that way!
Ah!
What is that?
It's the ghost cat!
MAOMALIN: My bride, my bride!
TSUBASA: [screams]
[explosion]
MAOMALIN: Ms.
Tsubasa, wait for me!
Yeah.
TSUBASA: Ah, get away from me!
Ah!
Well, it seems two more of
our contestants have withdrawn.
And seeing as time is
running short, please
cast your vote for
one of these three
to be the new Ms. Beachside.
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER):
Shampoo win, hands down.
UKYO (VOICEOVER):
This contest is mine.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
I've lost it for sure.
Ah, ah!
Oh, that was close.
KODACHI: Ranma, darling.
Ah!
KODACHI: Oh, Ranma.
What a coincidence meeting
you here of all places.
Uh, how's it hanging, Kodachi?
Huh?
My bride!
[screaming]
Ah!
Ranma, darling!
Get away, flea bag!
Hey, my bride!
[drumroll]
NABIKI: Here.
SOUN: THANK you.
And now I will
announce the results.
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER):
Ranma be eating
Shampoo's delicious, nutritious
noodles in few minute.
UKYO (VOICEOVER): Ranma,
honey, I'll bet you're hungry.
I'll let you eat as much of
my okonomiyaki as you want.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Uh, I'd give anything
to have the last 20
minutes of my life back.
[squeal]
[quack]
[pattering]
What is that?
Huh?
[screaming]
I will now announce the winner.
UKYO (VOICEOVER): And now
for my moment of glory.
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER):
Shampoo's glowing moment.
The winner of this summer's
Ms. Beachside is-- huh?
Thank you, thank you.
Hiya!
[fighting sounds]
And now I will announce
the winning contestant.
SHAMPOO: You want
piece of Shampoo?
UKYO: You want Ukyo?
I'll give you Ukyo.
SHAMPOO: I take you on.
UKYO: I'll shake
your little noodle.
SHAMPOO: Hiya!
The new Ms. Beachside
is my daughter--
What?
--Kasumi.
[crowd cheering]
Oh, my.
Aw.
Huh?
Every vote--
that's what it says.
It's like they say.
There's no accounting for taste.
[pattering]
Hm?
Time to go.
Come back, Ms. Tsubasa!
No way!
No!
Ranma, darling!
[squeal]
[quack]
[gasp] Ranma!
I got away from them all.
SHAMPOO: Hiya!
Hiya, Shampoo's
stall fly to sky.
Well, I guess that means
Ranma will be eating his lunch
at my stand now for sure.
Shampoo no know about that.
Huh?
MAOMALIN: My bride!
TSUBASA: No!
--[scream] Get away
from my food stall!
This place is a mess.
Now I won't be able to get lunch
at Ukyo's or Shampoo's stall.
Wait a sec.
I know.
Wait right here.
Uh, hey, don't tell
me you're gonna--
Uh-oh.
Hi!
[groan]
I-- I made a bunch
of rice balls.
There's enough for everyone,
even for Ukyo and Shampoo, too.
Of all the things I
could have had for lunch,
and now I get stuck
eating Akane's rice balls.
You know what this
means, don't you, Saotome?
Mhm.
Ms. Tsubasa, sing a duet
with your future bridegroom!
[singing]
Look, if you made that kind of
lifestyle, then good for you.
But I don't go for
boys, so back off!
I don't care what you are.
You're beautiful to me.
And I'm gonna have
you for my bride!
I told you already!
[grunt] I'm a guy, numskull!
[laugh]
[rattling]
Don't beat yourself up
over it, Ms. Tsubasa.
After all, everyone has
one or two character flaws.
Blah?
This is all your fault!
You fix Shampoo's food stall!
And mine, too!
[grumble]
You owe us lunch
at the very least.
Come to me, Ranma, darling.
You deserve to be
punished, Ranma Saotome.
Where's everybody
running off to?
I told you, I have enough
food for all of you to eat.
You're gonna pay for
this, you lousy ghost cat!
[yelling]
KODACHI: Come on, get back here!
Oh, my.
What a fix.
[squeal]
[quack]
There's no telling how things
will turn out in the end, huh?
[music playing]
NARRATOR: The
heavens, the earth,
and the people call for him.
They call for him
to defeat evil.
Yes, they call for
Tatewaki Kuno, age 17.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
The Musical Instruments
of Destruction.
We'll see you there.