[theme music]
-That's odd.
So where am I now?
[rustling brush]
Hm?
Gah!
-Fooood!
[grunts]
-You there, who, who are you?
[laughs]
Why you--
[grunting and clashing swords]
I'll teach you to sneak
up on me like that!
Hiya!
[thud]
Maybe you'll think twice
before attacking next time.
So who are you, huh?
Huh?
You're, you're just an old man.
-Haven't you got
anything to eat?
-Ryoga the strong-- too strong.
[crackling fire]
-Num, num, num.
[slurps] Yum, yum, yum.
[slurps] Num, num.
[slurps] Give me another!
Num, num.
[slurps]
-Um, excuse me.
I know that you're
hungry and all,
but a mere thank you
sure wouldn't hurt.
-Num, num.
[slurps] I may be a hermit,
but I ain't no freeloader.
You'll get your thanks.
[slurps]
[gulps]
-Well, have it your way.
Ah!
You ate them!
My noodles, they're
gone, all gone!
You, you pig!
-Ah, man's gotta eat, kid-- now.
[boom]
Let's see.
Uh huh, uh huh.
-Keep your hands
off of me, you--
-Ow!
Man, where's your
respect for elders?
Keep that up and I won't
give you your reward.
-Tell me, since when does
grabbing some stranger's
stomach count as a reward?
-If'n you're too dumb to know
about martial arts calligraphy.
-Martial arts
calling-- excuse me?
-Listen up, stupid.
There's an energy center
right below the belly button
that can have an effect
on how strong you are.
Most folks don't know about it,
see, which is why it's an art.
Anyway, all martial
arts calligraphy
does is focus energy.
It can give you
what you don't got.
First off, we
gotta make the ink.
Some folks use the bottle stuff.
Me, I'm a traditionalist.
-Don't take this the wrong
way, gramps, but no thanks.
See ya.
-Where do you
think you're going?
Ain't you interested in becoming
the world's strongest man?
-The world's strongest?
-You heard what I said.
Stand still and
lift up your shirt.
It'll just take a minute.
-Hey, if I'm the strongest
man in the world,
then that means
I can beat Ranma!
-This is it, kid, the
day you've waiting for!
[yells]
[screams]
Martial arts calligraphy
final attack!
The mark of the god!
[straining]
[yells]
-It's, it's--
-It's late.
Ryoga, you stupid moron.
You're the one who
wanted to meet, not me.
It's your stupid
challenge letter.
-Ranma, meet me
in the vacant lot.
We'll start the new year right.
Ryoga Hibiki.
-Dumb jerk.
He probably got lost
again, like always.
It's here.
That vacant lot has got
to be here somewhere.
Huh, huh, huh, huh?
Like I said, he gets lost.
-Where'd you get those signs?
-These?
Oh, just a couple of souvenirs.
You know, I thought
it'd be a challenge,
but I gotta tell you, it was
too easy taking those dojos.
-What's the matter?
Disappointed they let you win?
Don't worry, I've
been here all week.
I'll make sure you
work before I beat ya.
-Hm, let's see what you say
after the fight, shall we?
I've got a feeling you'll be
singing a whole 'nother tune.
-You've sure got an
attitude, I'll give you that.
As for who beats on who,
let's let the best man win.
[yells]
[grunts]
[thud]
How'd you--
-Well, Ranma, I'm still
waiting for that beating
you were going to give me.
-You ain't gotta ask me twice!
[grunting]
-(THINKING) What in the--
how could he know my moves?
[yells]
[thud]
[screaming]
-Ugh.
Ah.
-Oh, I beat him with
only one single finger.
Well, this is goodbye then.
I've not further
use for you, Ranma.
Bye.
[grunting]
-Hey, come back here!
-You know, if it were possible
for anyone to beat me,
I would have thought
it'd had been you, Ranma.
-Wait!
Wait!
What the heck do
you mean by that?
-Hm.
I may as well tell
you my secret.
You see, it all started
10 days ago today.
[grunts]
-Martial arts calligra what?
[sighs]
-When I'm through
with you, you'll
be the strongest man on earth!
[screams]
Calligraphy final attack,
the mark of the god!
-It was then that I became
the strongest man on earth,
just like the old
hermit said I would.
However, I also became the
most tragic man on earth.
[gasps]
It's, it's like a, a-- Uh,
uh, well, that ain't so bad.
This ought to do it.
[grunting]
-Don't bother, Ranma,
it's not going to work.
It's not something you can
just scrub off with a towel.
-Huh?
OK then, how about this?
[grunts]
[screaming]
I already tried that, stupid!
Cleaners, soaps, bleaches,
brushes-- I tried it all,
but none of it worked.
That's why.
[scrubbing]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
-You just can't scrub it
off, it don't work that way.
-Ah, listen you.
I never asked for this, OK.
Now get this dumb thing
off of me right now!
-OK, OK, so I'll
tell you already!
-Ah!
You, you will?
-There's only one way to
remove the mark of the gods,
and that's to fight someone
even stronger than yourself.
Once you do--
-The mark will disappear.
-So is that why you want to
challenge all these dojos?
-They were a lot easier
than I thought they were.
Eh, no one's a
challenge to me anymore.
I'm practically invincible.
Yep, not even you can
beat me now, Ranma.
It's sad, but that's
the way it is, I guess.
-Humph.
-Well, that's that.
-Wait!
Don't go yet!
Look, you gotta let me
try to help you, Ryoga.
look, I told you-- the
only way is for me to lose.
-I know that, which is why
you've gotta let me try.
Ryoga, listen to me.
We're not just
enemies, we're rivals.
-Huh?
We are?
-Of course we are.
Why else would we be
fighting all the time, huh?
That's why you gotta wait.
You owe it to me, man.
-Ranma--
-Come on!
We practically grew up together.
-Ranma, I, I, I don't
know what to say!
I-- [sobbing] You're
too good to me.
I misjudged you.
Forgive me, please!
-Hm, now.
Hiya, take this! [grunts]
[yells]
[screams]
-Hey!
Where'd you go?
Come back!
OK, that's it.
The man's going down!
[crash]
[painful yell]
[thud]
[groaning]
[whimpering]
-Well, are you convinced yet?
So what's it going to take, huh?
-A lot more than you've
got, you arrogant jerk.
-That's enough.
[grunts]
-Yeah, that's what you think!
Hiya!
[crash]
-What are they doing?
-Gee, Akane, I wonder.
Construction maybe?
-Unable to settle their
differences outside,
the two have moved it
inside to the dojo.
-Are they having a fight?
-Oh, dear.
whole
-Oh, come now, Kasumi.
Don't sound so disapproving.
If two healthy young men
can't engage in little sparing
now and again, what's the use
of being a martial artist, huh?
Uh, boys will be boys.
-Meanwhile, those boys
are wrecking the dojo.
Boys may be boys, dad,
but personally, I'm
glad I'm a girl.
[slurps]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
-Huh?
[thud]
-Here you go, Ranma.
This ought to even
the odds a bit.
-Man, now I know that
you've gone and lost it.
-You be quiet!
I'm just doing
what I have to do--
whatever it takes
for me to lose.
You've got to beat me, remember?
If you don't, I'll never
get rid of this stupid mark.
You're the only hope
that I have left.
-Let's not drag it out then.
I'm going to make you
lose right here and now!
Aaaah!
[crash]
-OK, I'm ready!
Ranma?
Come at me at any time!
[grunting]
-All right, enough is enough.
[gasps]
-Sorry.
-Ranma, how'd the
fight with Ryoga go?
[snoring]
[grumbling]
-I just know it's going
to be in here somewhere.
Ah, this ain't it,
neither is that.
This ain't it, neither is this.
This ain't it, neither is that.
This ain't it.
This ain't it either.
Nope.
[seething]
[grumbling]
All right, now this is it.
I ask you, am I the
man, or ain't I?
Ha, ha!
Now that I've got this
scroll, I'm going to-- ugh!
Ah!
You're going down
man, you just wait.
[sighs]
-Saotome, you big jerk.
I should have know better
than to count on you.
[sighs]
-(THINKING) If I can't get
rid of this stupid work.
If Akane somehow sees it--
[screams]
[laughing]
-That is so lame!
What a loser!
[laughs]
-Then the only one I
can count on is myself!
Ranma's no help at all!
Ra, Ranma?
[chuckles]
-Get ready, Ryoga,
because I'm not
the same man that I used to be.
Because now I got a super
secret new ultra technique!
[screams]
-(THINKING) Super secret
new ultra technique?
Dare I to hope?
[seething]
-Look, up in the sky!
-(THINKING) Ha!
He fell for it, the moron.
Like the wolf who waits for
just the right moment to attack.
Strike of the wolf's fang!
-Hm.
[grunting]
-OK.
Saotome School of
Sneaky Attacks step
two-- keep things on the level,
and your enemy on the ground.
Then, like the tiger,
strike from above.
Look!
There's 100 yen!
-So how dumb do you think I am?
-Hey, uh, you know, don't
hold it against me, huh?
You're just getting too smart
for your own good, that's all.
-Grrr!
Or maybe it's just
you who's dumb!
-Encore!
-I'm sorry guys,
but do you mind?
-OK, OK.
-Super secret untrue
technique-- yeah, right.
Trying to fake me out with those
stupid techniques of yours,
you ought to be
ashamed of yourself.
[sobbing]
Huh?
-Ranma?
-I'm sorry, man.
I failed you, didn't I?
I'm just too weak, that's all.
I wanted to be the
one who'd saved you.
[crying hysterically]
-Ranma, don, don't
be hard on yourself.
It's not you who
failed, it's me.
I'm just too darn strong
for my own good, that's all.
It's not up to you to
fix my problems, that's
something I got to do on my own.
[chuckles]
[splash]
[gagging]
[laughs]
-You fell for it again!
Behold, the Anything
Goes Saotome School
of Sneaky Attacks step
three-- a stunned opponent is
a flattened opponent.
Get them belly down and you
got 'em where you want 'em.
Thus, the croak of
the croaked frog!
Remember, it's
for your own good.
So try not to hold
it against me, huh?
Payback time!
Oh oh!
[screams] How'd you do that?
[squeaking]
-P-chan!
So there you are,
you naughty boy.
[squeaks]
Huh?
(THINKING) Those
marks on his stomach--
where'd they come from?
[squealing]
What kind of jerk
would do such a thing?
It's not even good graffiti!
It makes you look stupid!
[cracking glass]
[squealing]
-P-chan?
P-chan.
[sighs]
-(THINKING) She saw me.
She looked right at me.
(REMEMBERING AKANE) It's
not even good graffiti!
It makes you look stupid!
[yells]
(THINKING) Ah, it's over!
It's all over!
-Oh, man.
Ah, it's not that bad.
You know, the way I see it, that
mark of yours could be a curse,
or you could make it a blessing.
-And how, how am I
supposed to do that?
-It all depends on
your attitude, see.
For one thing, you can--
-Uh, hi there!
My name's Ryoga, and
I'm a new employee!
-Hi, Ryoga!
[laughing]
-Hey, keep it on!
-Want to see my tattoo?
-Oh, yeah!
-Isn't it great?
Oh, and I can make
it dance, too.
[laughing]
Look, see?
-And that ain't all, neither.
You can do parties,
weddings, anniversaries,
all that kind of junk.
You'll be laughing all
the way to the bank.
Man, just think of all the
possibilities, will ya?
-I got a possibility for ya.
[whack]
[grunts]
You're insane!
You're insulting!
But most of all,
you're out of here!
[grunting]
This is all your fault!
Akane would have never
seen P-chan's stomach if it
hadn't been for--
-Huh?
Ah!
Maybe he's over there.
P-chan, is that you?
Want me to do your stomach?
-Because of you,
I'll never again dare
to show my face to
Akane as Ryoga Hibiki.
Ya!
[grunting]
-Wait, wait, wait wait!
What didn't you want
Akane to see again?
[screams]
-Huh?
-Ryoga?
-Uh, uh, Akane.
-Uh, uh, eh, hey there.
-That mark that's
drawn on your stomach.
-Uh.
-It's exactly the same as
the one I saw on P-chan.
[screaming]
[crash]
-Ranma?
Ryoga?
But what's it all
supposed to mean?
[seething]
[laughing]
-Well, well, that was, that
was kind of a close one there,
wasn't it, Ryoga?
-You are such a dead man!
-(THINKING) I'm sure of it.
That mark on P-chan
and that mark on Ryoga,
they were exactly the same!
[theme music]
-But why is it the same though?
Are they connected, or?
Ah, I get it!
NARRATOR: Next time on "Ranma
1/2," Close Call-- P-chan's
secret.
We'll see you there!