[music playing]
NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the anything
goes school of martial arts.
-Hey, let go!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo training hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma suffering--
-What did you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma is
splash with cold water,
he becomes a she.
NARRATOR: "Kissing
is such sweet sorrow!
The taking of Akane's lips."
AKANE: I said no.
Absolutely, positively not!
-Akane, please?
-C'mon, we're begging ya!
You're our only hope.
-But this is the interscholastic
drama competition.
Please, Akane.
Do it for Furinkan High.
-You know how I feel
about school plays.
Why does it have to be me?
Are you coming, Ranma?
-Ah, do the play, Akane.
It's no big deal.
-Who asked you!
-But it's the lead.
-Huh, gee.
Let me guess.
Samurai sweetheart, lady
sumo, maybe the karate queen?
-Hey, go for it, Akane.
You were born for the role.
-Shut up, Ranma!
-Maybe we have no choice.
-Me thinks we don't.
-Such a shame.
She'd be so perfect
for the role.
We'll have to find
ourselves another Juliet.
-Juliet?
-Oh, Romeo!
Romeo!
Wherefore art thou, Romeo?
I'll do it!
Please, oh please
let me have the role!
-Really?
You mean you'll do it?
[shouts]
AKANE: Upperclassman Kuno?
-Call me Romeo, my Juliet.
-Hey, who said you
could be Romeo?
No one cast you.
Permission to join.
What?
-Hmmph.
Very well, I shall
join your little troop.
Naturally, that will
mean that nothing
less than the very
finest role will do.
-No, you can't!
You haven't even auditioned.
-Come again?
I, the Noble Kuno in a cattle
call with a hoi polloi?
[laughter]
[music playing]
-Oh, and what's this, pray tell?
Permission to join.
-OK, I admit it.
Playing Romeo at my
age won't be easy.
Embarrassing?
Maybe.
Challenging?
Sure.
But if it means a love scene
with Akane, here I come!
-Lucky you, you're a hit.
Go on out there and
break a leg, Juliet.
-Thanks.
I'll give the part
everything I've got.
-Hm?
[music playing]
-Wow.
You mean she gets
Juliet this time?
-This time what?
-She means that Akane's done
"Romeo and Juliet" before
in grade school.
See?
-Whoa.
Did she look the part or what?
-How sad.
No one knew what I
was going through.
KID: Romeo should be
Akane, she's the best one.
KID: Yeah, Akane!
Yeah!
KID: Say yes, Akane!
-How could they have known?
Known that in my heart,
all I ever wanted
was to wear a pretty
dress and be Juliet.
That's all.
KID: You're great, Akane!
KID: So strong, Akane!
KID: She looks just like a boy.
KID: Akane should
always be Romeo.
-I didn't want to
disappoint them.
This time, though,
things will be different.
This time, I'll be the
one who'll play Juliet!
-The following roles
have yet to be cast.
Romeo--
KUNO: Halt!
SASUKE: Move it!
Move it!
Out of the way.
Coming through.
C'mon you slowpokes,
out of my way!
Jesus, c'mon, get
out of the way!
-Those who would be Romeo
must defeat me first.
-What do you say?
Do we give them an audition?
Remember, if we win, the prize
is an invitation to see China.
-Invitation to see China?
Are you serious about China?
-Serious in what way?
The best play gets to
see China, yes or no?
-If they win.
-Right!
That trip's as good as mine!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I can go
find that spring of drowned men
for free.
KUNO (VOICEOVER): Hmmph.
Think again.
OLD MAN (VOICEOVER): Fat chance.
-Right.
But let us first
come to an agreement
on the rules of the game.
He who stands last on stage
shall be the one true Romeo.
Agreed?
-Battle royal, huh?
Hey, you know I'm there.
-Why not?
Romeo and Juliet
with live combat!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I'm going
to get that role of win that
chance to see China!
KUNO (VOICEOVER): I
shall win the role
and steal a kiss from
Akane Tendo's lips.
OLD MAN (VOICEOVER): Those
punks ain't seen nothing yet.
-Oh, no.
If they ruin this, I'll
never forgive them.
PA SYSTEM: All
drama clubs, please
assemble at the rear
of the main gymnasium.
Thank you.
-Ah, and now for the final
entry, the Furinkan High Drama
Club with their version
of Romeo and Juliet!
[music playing]
-Romeo!
Wherefore art thou, Romeo?
AUDIENCE MEMBER:
All right, Akane!
MAN: Romeo fell in love
with Juliet at first sight,
but the families
are bitter enemies.
Romeo, while hiding
in the garden, was--
-What man art thou?
-Hey, that's not Romeo.
-No, I am Romeo!
-No, I'm Romeo!
-Which then is the question.
Which one is the real Romeo?
-My Juliet.
Me, at the basis of toads
enjoy their moment in the sun.
You see, I disguised
myself as the balcony.
Come here!
-You cut that out!
Yo, Juliet.
-Ah, Romeo!
-Seven, eight, nine, 10!
That's it, you're out of here!
-Fine.
-I lose.
-Oh, Juliet.
-Oh, my Romeo.
-Well, shouldn't they
be saying something?
-Nah, it's a dramatic pause.
-Oh, can't you just feel
their love for each other?
-Oh, my Romeo.
Say your line, stupid.
-I got lines?
SOUN: Take her in
your arms, son.
Like that.
AKANE: Huh?
-I knew you'd need
your old dad tonight.
-Dad, what are you--
-Leave it to me, son.
Do what I do and say what I say.
-Uh, OK.
-Juliet.
-Oh, Romeo.
-I pledge to marry thee and
take over thy father's dojo.
take over they fath-- Dojo?
DINOSAUR: Hey, I
don't remember any--
SOUN: Sh!
Right.
In you go.
AUDIENCE: This is it.
The moment we've all
been waiting for.
-Not for real, it's just a play.
-Will you cut that out already?
-But son, we'd give you
our parental consent.
Now do it.
It's time to kiss.
-I ain't kissing nobody.
Nobody!
No way, I don't care
if it is a play.
I ain't kissing nobody.
-I ain't kissing her.
Do you hear me?
I ain't doing it.
But I'm still Romeo.
-What do you mean you
ain't gonna kiss her?
-Stupid!
Not fair!
-Honestly.
Fine then.
-Surely, the inability
to play a love scene
is grounds for impeachment.
You're no Romeo, pigtail boy.
Hit the showers!
-You're morons as
far as I'm concerned.
-Well, would you rather I was
kissed by those two perverts,
then?
-Hm?
Like I said, there ain't nothing
I won't do to get to China.
I'll give them a love
scene they'll never forget.
-And now, my dear, as
for the love scene--
-It's not fair.
They're ruining everything.
KASUMI (VOICEOVER):
You can do it, Akane.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Kasumi?
KASUMI (VOICEOVER): You were
so excited about this role.
Don't give up on it now.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): She's right.
Playing Juliet was
my childhood dream,
no matter who my Romeo is.
-Juliet.
-Oh, Romeo.
-Oh, Juliet, how I've
waited for this day.
-I can't!
-Woo-hoo!
The wedding scene!
-Alas, poor Juliet is captured
by an evil beast, intensified--
-And who are you
calling a beast, huh?
Who do you think you are?
Do you know who you're
talking to, you rat?
Ah, my Juliet.
And now for the honeymoon.
-Suck on this.
Oh, Romeo, let's have a wedding
toast together, shall we?
-Hey, there's a new Juliet!
-Go, Romeo.
Go chug-a-lug!
Allow me to give you
a token for my love.
-Oh, a bra!
Ha, how sweet.
-Get it!
That's one down.
-Ah, my pigtailed Juliet!
-Oh, wherefore art thou, Romeo?
-Right here, dear Juliet.
-Hey!
Hey!
You!
You there!
Yes, you!
Stop!
The consumption of
alcohol is str--
-It's not Saki.
It is the dew of our love.
-Why-- why didn't you say so.
-Juliet, into my embrace, dear
Juliet, if life you value.
-Ah, Juliet is--
-Give me that.
Only pretending to be drunk.
Behold, the dreaded drunk food.
-Ya!
Feel my love's kiss.
KUNO (VOICEOVER): I
can't read her moves.
-That's right,
ladies and gentlemen.
It's the legendary
drunk fu, an anything
goes school of martial
arts special attack.
So secret, it's never been
performed in public until now.
Practiced secretly
in bars for years.
For the first time ever,
it's live on stage.
-Would you believe-- snooze fu?
-Ah, why art thou, yet so fair?
Thus with a kiss.
AKANE: I think you've
got the wrong Juliet.
Fight me, not her.
-Ah, it is the East, and
fair Juliet is the sun.
Very well.
I accept your challenge!
-Go sober up, you lush.
-Surrender, Juliet.
You're mine.
Oh!
-Romeo, you two-timer!
-Hey, no fair!
I'm Juliet, not you!
-Oh, so you want a
love scene with Kuno.
-That's not what I said.
-Then but out!
I'm going to China no
matter what it takes.
-Even with tape,
this is disgusting.
-Oh thank you, cute girl.
I'm so happy.
-That's it, I'm going home!
Good luck with the
rest of the play.
-Wait, Akane!
Don't go!
[mumbles]
-Alas, what will become
of Romeo and Juliet?
Now what?
Maybe we should have
an intermission.
-Akane, wait up.
C'mon, it's almost over.
-Why don't you go back and
kiss Kuno again, Ranma.
Pervert.
-Hey, I used tape, OK?
-So you say.
-Hey!
She is so uncute!
-No, you dummy.
[collapsing sound]
-Enter Sasuke, stage right.
Mua-ha-ha!
I'll show them all what
it means to be a star.
-What do you think you're
doing, you little--
-Wait, Juliet!
-Juno.
-Having shared a kiss with the
pigtailed girl, is it not me
I should kiss you as well.
-You liar!
It don't count if you use tape.
-Hurry, hurry.
It's scene three.
-Hey stupid, we've
got to play to finish.
MAN: Fair Juliet sleeps the
sleep of death, but wait!
There is one way to awaken her.
A kiss from her beloved Romeo.
RANMA: What is the
matter with you?
Why does everything keep coming
back to that stupid kiss?
-Please, don't you
want to see China?
-Oh, yeah.
It's-- it's-- it's a special
request from our guest judge.
-No, it's hard.
Kiss girl and win contest.
Win contest, go see China.
-C'mon, no more stalling.
Kiss her.
Well, c'mon, are you
her fiance or not?
-There are people watching, OK?
SOUN: Sounds like you've changed
your mind about seeing China
then?
RANMA: Yes!
I mean, no.
SOUN: Then, what
are you waiting for?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): If-- If I--
If I can just go through this,
I-- If I can just
get to see China,
I-- I can be a normal guy again.
Here goes nothing.
I can't do it.
-Ranma, come on.
Do it.
-You hurry.
Kiss girl.
-Oh, Romeo.
Do you really hate me that much?
-No, of course I don't.
If I did, this would be easy.
-Then do it.
Kiss me.
-Really?
-Can you just make believe?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Akane.
-The winner!
Please give big hand!
-Now that's quite a
performance, don't you think?
AKANE: What are
you so mad about?
RANMA: Oh, shut up.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): She didn't
have to trick me like that.
-Still, don't you wish we could
have done it without the tape?
You fell for it.
You're such a dope.
-You are so un-- cute.
AKANE: We're home!
-You're home so late.
Is everything OK?
-Yeah, everybody else
is already seeing China.
-Huh?
SOUN: Rawra-- er, Ranma, pleased
to meet my favorite Hong Kong
movie star.
CHINA: Please,
just call me China.
It's my stage name.
-I hope you didn't get the wrong
idea when we said the China.
-Well, son, now you can
see China all you want.
-Poor Ranma.
He must be so tired.
-Well, maybe he'll wake up if
you give him a kiss, Akane.
AKANE: I think it's
kinder to let him sleep.
[music playing]
NARRATOR: So the bathtub
is broken again, huh?
Oh, well I get
these things happen.
Good thing there's a
public bathhouse near by.
Excuse me, with [inaudible]?
Are you crazy?
Next time on Ranma
1/2, "Bathouse battle!
We're in some hot water now."
See you there.