[music playing]
[theme music]
GIRL RANMA: "I Love You, Ranma.
Please Don't Say Goodbye."
DR. TOFU: By applying rare
Chinese herbs and extracts,
combined with figure pressure
in strategic locations,
the Xai Fang Heng
Gao Shiatsu attack
can selectively erase memory.
-So that's why you
forgot about me.
-Do I know you?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Unless
I can find Shampoo.
AKANE: I'm home.
-Akane.
How could you forget
Ranma, your own fiancee?
-Ranma?
Who is that?
-Akane, he's--
-Take a look.
He's the guy standing
right behind you there.
-Hi.
-Who let you in?
Get out of my house, or
I'll call the police.
RANMA: I, uh, kind of
live here actually.
AKANE: You what?
-Oh.
-Ah.
So I guess the amnesia thing
wasn't an act after all.
-They can get to know each
other all over again so
long as daddy's little girl
hasn't forgotten who I am.
Huh, Akane.
-Do I know you?
-You don't remember him?
-Don't cry, Dad.
How could I forget
someone as special as you?
It was only a joke, Dad.
-That wasn't very funny, Akane.
-You sure fooled us.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Well,
this doesn't change anything.
I've still got to find--- hey.
How can you joke around
at a time like this?
-I fool you.
I fool you.
Hiya.
I fool.
Yes?
-Shampoo.
Shampoo, tell me where the
shampoo you used on Akane is.
-Wo da airen.
You I love.
What you do?
-Do I know you?
-Not again.
-I wonder why I did that.
-A conditioned reflex.
-Somewhere, deep in her heart,
she still remembers him.
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER): I don't
kill all memory of him.
This one strong enemy.
-Aren't you that cheer
they say at football games?
-No.
That's ra-ra.
AKANE: I know.
You're that 1985
remake of "King Lear"
directed by Akira Kurosawa.
RANMA: That's "Ran."
I'm Ranma.
-Akane, get out of the way.
AKANE: What?
-All right.
This is just what we need.
-Hey.
-Come on, Akane.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Airen.
-Hey.
Ouch.
That hurts.
Quit it.
-Quiet.
This is for your good, Akane.
-Let me go.
-Ow.
Ow.
That hurts.
You got it in my eyes.
You were a boy, and
now you're a girl.
How did you do that?
What's going on?
-Akane.
-Girl-type Ranma.
I give you kiss of death.
Now you die.
-After all that, it
still didn't work.
-I guess not.
Look.
There's a label on
it and everything.
-Come and get it.
DR. TOFU: Hello.
Anybody home.
-Good.
He's finally here.
Doctor.
-Ranma, tell me
how is Akane doing?
-She's, uh-- I tried
using the shampoo on her,
but the dumb stuff don't work.
-Of course, that shampoo
didn't work on her, Ranma.
Why don't you take a close
look at the blend number
on the bottle?
-1-1-0.
-Blend number 1-1-0
is for erasing memory,
not restoring it.
To bring her memory
back you need
the bottle labeled
blend number 1-1-9.
-Huh.
Well, where are we
going to find that one?
-Relax, Ranma.
You see, I've got the formula
for it in this book right here.
Huh?
-Oh, Dr. Tofu.
Is it true?
Can you really cure
Akane's memory?
K-k-kasumi.
Say, Kasumi, well, what
are you doing here?
-I live here, doctor.
-Oh, oh, really?
-What are you doing?
-I guess you must have
finished dinner by now.
-We were just about to start.
-Then, I won't-- uh,
what are you having?
-Would you like to join us?
-Thanks for nothing.
-Girl-type Ranma, she sneaky.
She fast.
Next time, for sure,
Shampoo kill her.
-Hey, wait a minute, Ranma.
Where do you think you're
going all of a sudden.
-Isn't it obvious?
I'm going to a
drugstore in China
to buy some of that
memory restoring shampoo.
-Wow.
In China?
-What's that?
Going to China, son?
-Have a nice trip, Ranma.
I'd love a souvenir.
Hm.
What should I ask for?
Oh, we're all out of Oolong tea.
Buy me some, would you?
-Cigarettes and rice
wine for me please.
-Oh, and I'll need a
hand-painted tea set
to serve it in.
-I would just love a pair
jade earrings, Ranma.
Ooh, and one of those
Chinese silk dresses, OK.
-Oh, and Jasmine tea.
I could use some ink and
brushes for my calligraphy.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Akane.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Why is this person
trying so hard to help me?
-Akane, someday soon,
you'll remember me again,
and I'll be waiting for you.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I wish
I could remember him.
[panting]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
The question is
how am I going to get to
China without any money?
Guess I'm going to have to
get there same as last time.
-Listen, Ranma.
A true martial artist can turn
any experience into training.
You must look upon this
journey here not as a hardship
but more as a
blessing in disguise.
-We're swimming to
China, because you're
too cheap to buy plane tickets,
so don't feed that training
junk.
It ain't a lot of fun, but
it's one way to get there.
How else am I going to get
my hands on that shampoo
and-- whoa!
1-1-9.
-Hm.
-Hand it over.
-Ranma, Ranma, why
you so nice to Akane?
-Well, let's just say
that nobody likes it
when they're forgotten
about, all right.
-Nee.
-Now, you've done it.
-Na-na.
Come catch if can.
-Give me that shampoo, Shampoo.
There it is.
All right.
SHAMPOO: That one is fake.
-Hey.
-Where is real one?
-Come on.
Give it here.
Shampoo, give it to me.
-Drop real one by mistake.
-Give it here.
-You want?
-You think you could
stop me that easy?
Well, guess again.
I'm used to women's bodies.
OK.
So you better hand it over,
or I'll get it myself.
-Hi-ya!
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I-- huh.
All right.
Let's make a deal.
If you give it to me,
I'll trade you a favor.
OK, Shampoo.
-Really?
Yeah, really.
I give you my word, but don't
go asking me to marry you
or to kill Akane or
nothing weird, OK.
-OK.
Girl-type Ranma you kill.
You kill girl-type Ranma
and get 1-1-9 shampoo.
That is deal.
-On one condition, make
that half-kill and we're
in business.
OK.
-Shampoo no understand,
but is deal.
-Hm.
So she has no idea that you
and this girl-type Ranma are--
-One and the same person.
No.
Which brings me to the point.
I don't want to have
to ask you this, Ryoga,
but will you almost kill me?
-Gee.
I'd love to, but you'll
have to find somebody else,
because I've got Akane
to think about now.
From now on, it'll be a brand
new love story between us two.
Do you remember
Ranma at all, Akane?
-Ranma, should I know that name?
-Forget I ever mentioned it.
From this day forth, I'm the
only one you'll ever need.
-Ryoga.
-Akane.
-Could you bend
a little on that?
-Forget it.
-Come on.
I'm begging you.
-No way.
-You'll be doing me a favor.
-I said no, and I mean no.
-Be a pal and beat me up.
Do it like this.
-Is this how you beg?
-So you will do it.
-No way.
-Come on, Ryoga.
I'm asking nicely.
-So this is how you
ask for a favor?
-Well, tell me how else I'm
supposed to ask you then.
-When did you ask?
-Well, I tried.
I warned you.
-I'm going to rip
your stupid head off.
-All right.
Thanks, Ryoga.
I owe you one.
Yay!
Ah, you stupid jerk.
Now, who's going to beat me up?
-You can't fool us, son.
We know why you're doing this.
Since Ryoga is in no
shape to help you,
allow us to assist you.
Almost killing you
for poor Akane's sake
is an honor I can't refuse.
Thank you.
AKANE: What are you two doing?
You shouldn't bully the weak.
-We're not bullying anyone.
Here.
We should thank him
for his sacrifice.
-[scream] It's a monster.
-Hey, who's a monster?
-What a recovery.
But just who are you anyway?
-I told you.
-Ranma, looks like we're
back where we started.
-Wha--
-From the top then.
-[gasp] Dad, stop.
If you're set on
fighting somebody,
then you can fight me.
-Hey, now, cut that out.
Would you?
-Now what?
You're too weak to fight.
-All right.
That's it.
Who do you think I'm
doing this all for anyway?
You are just so uncute.
Huh?
-That's it.
Ranma, do it again.
-You're uncute.
-Whoa.
Now she's responding.
Ranma, try making your
words even stronger.
Somewhere in her heart what
you say is having an effect.
-Now, that's
something I'm good at.
You're built like a stick.
You're face makes me sick.
Your thighs are too thick.
You can't even kick.
You're dumb as a brick.
You talk like a hick.
Your hair's a cow lick.
You itch like a tick.
-You cad.
How dare you talk
to Akane like that?
I'll make you take back
every word you said.
-I thought you were dead.
-Well, I'm alive.
RANMA (RECORDING): You're
built like a stick-- built
like a stick--
built like a stick.
Your face makes me sick--
face makes me sick--
face makes me sick.
Your thighs are
too thick-- thighs
are too thick--
thighs are too thick.
You can't even kick-- can't
even kick-- can't even kick.
You're dumb as a brick-- dumb
as a brick-- dumb as a brick.
You talk like a hick-- talk
like a hick-- talk like a hick.
Your hair's a cow lick-- hair's
a cow lick-- hair's a cow lick.
You itch like a tick-- itch
like a tick-- itch like a tick.
-Ranma, you jerk-- you jerk--
you jerk-- you jerk-- you jerk.
-Oh.
Ranma, are you all right?
-Akane, it worked.
You've remembered Ranma.
Akane.
-Dad, I--
-It's a miracle,
the miracle of love.
-Get off me.
I-- I can't breathe.
You're crushing me to death.
[pounding]
-Nihao.
-Shampoo.
-Is girl-type Ranma
almost killed now?
Shampoo come to help.
RANMA: Could somebody
help me please?
-Airen.
What you doing?
So that it.
You remember Ranma again.
You are stubborn girl.
-I wouldn't talk if I were you.
-Hm.
Too bad.
If you now remember,
you now have to die.
-Stop it, Shampoo.
-Wo ai ni.
-Ah, man.
Come on.
You gotta quit doing that.
Hey.
-Stop doing that.
-Just don't hurt Akane.
OK.
-Why not?
Is obstacle.
That is for killing.
-I guess I've got no choice.
I'll have to tell the truth.
RANMA: Ranma, are you sure
you want to do that now?
She'll only come after
you again, you know.
-OK.
Watch this, Shampoo.
-Girl-type Ranma?
-Right.
I've tried to keep it a
secret, but that boy stuff
is just a disguise.
The truth is that I've
been a girl all along.
-Saotome, is this true?
-So you see, you and me,
we could never-- uh-oh.
-I kill you.
Kill you.
I kill you.
-Huh?
Bie liao.
-Hey.
Shampoo.
NABIKI: Hm.
Bie liao.
Here it is.
It means sayonara, farewell,
we'll never meet again,
that sort of thing.
-You're not going after her?
I bet you could still catch her.
-Let me alone.
-She sure was cute, Ranma.
I bet you're sorry
you turned her down.
-She was trying to kill me.
I'm glad she's gone.
-Then why do you look like
you're going to cry, huh?
-Akane, you are so uncute.
-So I'm not cute.
Big deal.
Who cares if I'm built
like a stick, or my thighs
are too thick, or I can't kick.
-If had known that you
were going to be like this,
I never would have
got your memory back.
-I wish you didn't.
I wish I never knew
that you existed.
-Oh, oh yeah.
-Yeah.
-You are so uncute.
[theme music]
KASUMI: Now what
are we going to do?
Out of nowhere Ranma told his
dad he was going back to China,
and then the two of them
got in a really big fight.
AKANE: What?
Why should I care where he goes?
He's nobody to me.
Next time on "Ranma
One Half," "I Am a Man.
Ranma's Going Back to China!?"
See you there.