[music playing]
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): I brought
you some souvenirs, Akane.
This time I swear,
even if it kills me,
I'm finally gonna tell
you how I feel about you.
GIRL 1: Hey, did you
hear about Ranma?
GIRL 2: What?
About his other fiancee?
Sure, it's all over school.
GIRL 1: Incredible, huh?
-Don't you think
for someone who says
he's not interested
in girls, he's
sure got a lot of girlfriends.
-You can say that again.
Akane's the one
I'd feel sorry for.
GIRL 2: No kidding.
If he was my boyfriend, I
think I'd have him neutered.
ANNOUNCER: "Ryoga and
Akane: 2-Gether, 4-Ever."
-Didn't I tell you they'd
all be gossiping about us?
-Eh, sticks and
stones and all that.
-Hey, Ranma!
Ain't you the lucky one.
-Way to go!
-You don't know what
you're talking about!
-Don't blame me.
If she's got a crush,
that's her fault.
RYOGA: Ah, you're the
one who'll be crushed.
-Now what'd I do?
-Apologize to Akane!
-I didn't do nothing!
-There's lots of
people like you, Ranma!
-I can explain.
-Ryoga, please stop!
-It was the old man, I tell ya!
-No more excuses!
-C'mon.
I got enough trouble with the
uncute fiancee I all ready got.
Why would I want another--
-Go ahead and switch
to the cute one then.
Don't let me stop you.
-Come on!
-Even if your fiancee
looked like this.
Or even like this.
You'd still have no
excuse for the way you've
been treating Akane, you swine.
-Wait a minute.
Look at it from
my point of view.
I got two fiancees and I
don't want either of them.
-Don't listen to him.
Ranma's free to date the entire
student body for all I care.
-That's right.
-You still got no right to keep
stringing her along like that.
I'm going to punish
you for her own good.
Who's there?
-Sorry, sugar, but if anyone's
gonna punish my fiance.
-Ukyo?
-It's gonna be me!
-I don't know who you are,
but any friend of Ranma's is
no friend of mine!
-No, Ryoga!
Don't do it.
She's a girl!
-Good thing I'm not
so easily fooled!
-I'd take another look, stupid.
And while we're at
it, flower bomb!
-Got ya!
-Still think she's a boy?
-Why you--
-Heh.
You sucker.
Now what?
Would you have rather been hit?
-You jackass.
You didn't have to show
him my chest, you know?
-Ryoga?
Thank goodness.
I was beginning to
worry about you.
-Oh, hi there.
-You did it for me, didn't you?
-I-- I really hope that
you're not too angry at me.
-How could I ever
be angry at you?
-I-- Akane, I--
-Ryoga, I didn't know you cared!
-Honestly, why
can't he just leave
you alone Don't let
him get to you, OK?
After all, he's
not mature, is he?
I mean, not like you.
-Huh?
Yeah, well-- hm, mature, huh?
Oh, who am I kidding.
If I were really mature,
I'd just say it, and not
be such a, such a--
-And not be such
a wimp, you mean?
If you like her, just say so.
I'm on your side.
You're Ryoga, am I right?
I'm Ukyo, Ukyo Kuonji,
I'm Ranma's cute fiance.
-Oh, I can see why
he's kept you a secret.
A date with Akane,
are you crazy?
I'd do almost
anything if we could--
I know that she
would never say yes.
-Wouldn't she?
-What has she said?
Have you talked to her already?
-Watch out, that's
hot, you know.
You just leave
everything to me, OK?
Trust me sugar,
when she sees this,
she won't be able to stay away.
-I don't know if I'm ready.
I mean, a d-date
is kinda serious.
You know, I mean what--
-Hey!
Do you want to date
her or dontcha?
-Yeah.
-OK then.
-And here we go.
Akane Tendo, blah,
blah, blah, love Ryoga.
Tell me where she
lives, and I'll
deliver it to her personally.
Finally.
Leave it to that jackass Ryoga
to draw me a map that leads me
through half of Tokyo
before coming here.
And, it's almost dawn.
-Slept in Akane's bed again
last night, did you, Mr. P?
-Someone left this for me?
-I found it on the front step
first thing this morning.
-Wonder what it is?
-Wait up, you [inaudible]!
AKANE: Hey!
Hey!
What's the matter with you?
-I wish they wouldn't play
with other people's food.
-Huh?
What's this?
Akane Tendo, I'll
be waiting for you
at Ucchan's
Okonomiyaki today at 2.
A challenge letter.
[grunts]
RANMA: You what?
set Akane and
Ryoga up on a date?
UKYO: Sure did.
Delivered the invitation myself.
They're meeting this
afternoon at my restaurant.
-There's no way Akane is
going to go on some date.
UKYO (VOICEOVER):
He seems so certain.
-You don't know her like I do.
I mean, can't you just imagine
what she's up to already?
Ooh, what am I gonna wear?
Hope my workout doesn't
make me sweat too much.
Et cetera, et cetera.
Which is why this little
romantic plan of yours
is never going to work out.
UKYO (VOICEOVER): And here
they call me unfeminine.
Maybe I really am
the cute fiance.
I hope she takes
the bate anyway.
-Where's, uh--
-Who, Akane?
She left a while ago, and
she seemed very excited
about something.
-Excited?
-She also asked me to ask
you to leave her alone.
Let her handle it and stay
the heck out of her business.
-Heh.
Uh--
-What's wrong with him?
-Don't interfere, huh?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
Nah, nana, nah, nah!
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Leave us alone, Ranma.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Oh, Akane.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Oh, Ryoga.
-Oh, no not if I can help it.
-Well.
-Akane, you decided
to come after all.
-And why wouldn't I?
-Well, I guess Ranma wasn't
kidding about you being uncute
now, was he?
I at least thought you'd
shower before your date.
-My date?
What date?
-Never mind that.
You just sit yourself down--
-I-- I made it.
-Ry-- Ryoga?
RYOGA: Good thing I gave
myself plenty of time.
-What about your challenge?
-What challenge?
-I bought them on the way out.
-Thanks, I think.
-Now that you're
both here-- and so,
in honor of your very first
date, this one's on me, OK?
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Date, huh?
Now I get it, she's trying
to set me up with Ryoga
so she can have
Ranma for herself.
Think again.
And here she's got poor,
good-hearted Ryoga messed
up in this too.
-Eat up you two,
or it'll get cold.
-Mm, it's pretty good, huh?
-Uh, yeah.
-Ah, you crazy kids.
[music playing]
-What am I gonna do?
Should I tell her,
or-- here's my chance.
But, what if she doesn't--
if I don't do it now,
I may never get another
chance to tell Akane that--
that I love her.
-Ryoga--
-Akane, I--
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Where's
Ukyo when I need her?
-Hi, kids.
You two getting along?
I've got a quick errand to
run, so I'll see you two later.
-W-wait!
UKYO: You guys have fun now.
-Huh?
Hey-- hey, hold on!
You're not leaving?
-Of course I'm leaving, idiot.
I thought you wanted
to be alone with her!
-I do, I do, but
I need your help.
-It's a date in
case you forgotten!
-I know, but I--I can't.
I mean, she hasn't--
-Were you born stupid or
did you just grow that way?
-Excuse me, but if
Ryoga doesn't want to,
I don't see any reason
why we have to force him.
-He wants to!
-I want to!
-Akane, from the very
first moment I saw you,
I knew that I was in--
Hey, who did that?
-Ryoga, darling, how could you?
How could you even
look at another girl
when you've got me, two-timer!
-I've never seen you
before in my life!
You must have me confused
with someone else!
C'mon, let me go!
You can't just come out of
nowhere and that stuff like--
-Huh?
-Hmm, alright.
Who are you?
-Who am I?
You don't know?
I am Ryoga's fiancee!
-(IN UNISON): Fiancee?
-I didn't know.
How long have you--
-I'm not surprised
you don't remember.
After all, we were
but babes when
our well meaning, yet
meddlesome parents
decided that we should-- ah!
-What is the matter with you?
-Hey, we are in the middle
of a romantic moment here?
-Now I've known
you've gone crazy.
-What am I-- what am I gonna do?
-Stupid!
Snap out of it.
Are you gonna let some stranger
steal your one and only chance
for happiness?
-Yeah, that's right.
What on Earth was I thinking?
There's only one girl for me!
-Akane, I-- you're the one.
You're the only one--
-Wha?
What are you doing?
-I won't let you abandon me.
I won't, do you hear me?
-She can't just waltz in
here and do that everything
I've done to bring
them together!
C'mon, darling, let's
run away together.
-W--wait!
-No fair!
UKYO: Pretty sneaky ain't she?
But she can't have gone far.
Let's split up and
look for them, OK?
GIRL: Uh, sure.
-Hey, I didn't do nothing wrong.
Why do I have to sneak
around like some kind of--
-Sh!
-I won't!
Why should I?
I don't have to listen to you!
-Is there someone you're
in love with, P-chan?
-Wha?
Ahh--
-How do you know about the--
-Oh, but my darling, I
know everything about you.
Your likes, your dislikes,
that you turn into a pig.
-Mm, no.
And yet-- and yet
you still want me?
-I what?
-I'm so happy.
-Wait.
You didn't understand.
You don't think that I-- you
don't really think that we--
-That we were meant to be.
RANMA: Ah!
RYOGA: Ah!
What do you think you're doing?
Get off of me!
Hey, quit it!
I'm not that kind of girl!
Go away!
-Did he hurt you?
I'm so sorry you got
mixed up in all of this.
Why do you keep
torturing him like this?
-Gee, what's the matter, Akane?
Did I spoil your little date?
-Hey-- hey, you're
jealous, aren't you?
Aren't you?
-Jealous!
Who, me?
Of an alley cat like you?
-Ah, alley cat?
-One lousy love letter
driveled in sauce
and you're raring to go.
Huh?
-If you were any more rare
and to go, you'd be nude!
You pervert!
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Honestly, I thought
it was a challenge, not a date.
Fine, Ranma.
That's the way you want it,
that's the way you got it.
RANMA: Ah, man!
She didn't have
to flash me first.
If I get caught wearing some
dress, I'll never live it down.
UKYO: I'm ready.
Thanks for waiting.
-Huh?
-Ryoga?
Betcha thought I'd
never come out, huh?
-Oh, oh no, I,
uh-- well, I, uh--
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): This
has got to be a dream.
Why else would she--
that is unless she kinda,
sorta likes me too.
-Stupid, stupid, stupid,
stupid, stupid, stupid!
-What?
Ryoga, wha-- what's--
-That didn't hurt.
That means it is a dream.
That one hurt a little bit.
It really is real, then.
-Let's get out of here, Ryoga.
-Sure.
-Ain't she all gussied up?
Yeah, whatever.
-Ran-chan!
What happened to you?
-I'll tell you later.
-Hey, do you want to make
them jealous for a change?
-Sure.
-Yes!
Gee, after the way
Akane treated you,
I thought this would
be the last place
you would want to come to.
-Hm?
-What is it?
RANMA: P-P-P-P-chan!
You little pig go oink, oink!
-Huh?
P-chan?
Where is he?
-You have all of these
right in front of you.
-Mom, would you but
out, we're busy.
RANMA: Oink, oink.
Oink, oink, oink, oink.
-I'm warning you, I mean it!
-You to just pretend
we're not here.
Ranma and I are on a date, too.
-So, after all the trouble
you went through to set us up.
Finally got what you wanted!
-Ranma, honey.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Idiot.
That two-timer's got no right
to call himself Akane's fiancee.
- Who are you
calling a two-timer?
-You mean to tell you
everything you've said,
the precious moments that we've
shared have all been a lie!
-No, I mean-- uh--
-Face it, Buster.
I'm the only girl
you'll ever know
who doesn't mind that you
turn into a little black pig.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): She's
right, she's right.
This may be my only
chance for happiness.
-You've interfered with me for
the last time, whoever you are!
Darling, we were
meant to be together.
You're the only man
for me, my love.
-Do you really mean it?
-I'd get while the
getting's good, Ranma.
-Did you say Ranma?
-Ranma?
I don't see any Ranmas here.
Do you?
-I see one right here!
Ranma!
This isn't the first time
you've done this to me.
But it'll be the last.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): No
matter how I look at it,
in my heart I've betrayed Akane.
-I don't believe you!
Are you proud of
tricking Ryoga like that?
Ryoga, I'm so sorry.
I really don't know why
he keeps teasing you.
RYOGA: Akane, it's OK.
I'm leaving.
This is our last goodbye.
-Huh?
-Wait!
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): I no longer
have the right to love you.
-Ryoga!
-This is all your fault.
-Hey, I didn't know he was
going to take it this hard, OK?
-P-chan?
How in the world
did you get here?
Don't go!
Come here, baby.
-Where's Ryoga?
Gee, I hope he
hasn't gone too far.
-I sure wish we knew
where he was right now.
-Closer than you
think, as usual.
-Hey, you're not
really Ranma, are you?
-I'm not?
-My Ranma is twice the
man he ought to be.
Tell me what you've
done with him or else!
-You asked for it.
UKYO: Oh, poor baby.
You really had it rough.
But I have to admit, having
you this way is a lot more fun.
-For who?
-I mean it.
I want you to promise me that
you'll apologize to Ryoga when
he comes back from his trip.
And like other people I can
name, Ryoga is sensitive.
-You don't say.
-Your behavior was inexcusable.
-Well I don't think he's
going to hold it against me.
Do you, P-chan?
-I could keep doing
this for hours.
-I'm not a play thing!
-Don't be so selfish, Ran-chan!
Share the wealth.
-What did I do to deserve-- Hey!
You're in no position to laugh!
[music playing]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ah!
Ranma, what do you
think you're doing?
How dare you grab me
like that and then try
to pin it on Shampoo!
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
"Sneeze Me, Squeeze Me,
Please Me!
Shampoo's Recipe For Disaster!"
We'll see you there!