[theme music]
[singing in japanese]
SCHOOLGIRL: Ah, look
at the old geezer.
Don't you think he
looks half dead?
His skin's so pasty
looking and I'd
say his head's too
big for his body.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ryoga
inherits the Saotome School?
SAOTOME (VOICEOVER): It doesn't
bother me if the kids are mean.
And even if every
bone in my body aches,
I can still come
home and enjoy--
RANMA: Hey, Pops.
Hm?
You looking for something?
You stole my--
Mm, this stuff's so good.
I found it in that
cupboard over there.
Man, it is really good.
Do you even have
the slightest idea
of what you've just
done to me, boy?
You, thief-- you stole
all of my sweets.
And I need them for energy
after a hard day's work.
But I don't think that
means anything to someone
as selfish as you.
Ahh, too late now.
Why, you little imbecile,
you give them right back now,
you hear?
I'll get you for this, boy.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): Akane, as
I speak, my journey takes me
to China's Szechuan
province, a place movement
known for it's pandas.
While I'm here,
I hope to buy you
a stuffed one as a souvenir
of my undying devotion to you.
And maybe-- just maybe--
when you hug it at night,
you'll think of me.
Huh?
Excuse me, could
I have another?
I still don't understand
why you asked me here.
It can't be just
to buy me dessert.
Because I'm getting old.
Huh?
It's about time I
handpicked someone
to take over the Saotome School
of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
Huh?
But what about Ranma?
Ranma isn't the
right man for the job.
In martial arts,
there is no family.
Only the most deserving
must carry on.
As far as Ranma goes,
I think I've him
by being too protective, and
after careful consideration,
Ryoga, my boy, Ryoga, you've
got potential for the job.
Ryoga, become my disciple
and carry on the school.
No way.
This is just some
kind of trick you
and Ranma have come
up with, isn't it?
No, wait.
Please, Ryoga, I
beg you to say yes.
Please!
You're serious?
Let me think about it.
Wait.
Enough.
You forgot this.
[chatter]
SCHOOLGIRL: Look!
A real, live panda!
Be careful.
He may be wild.
I can't believe
Mr. Saotome would
ask me to do such a thing.
SAOTOME: You're an idiot!
[groaning]
Is that the best
you can do, Ranma?
At this rate, you'll never be
able to take over the Saotome
school after me.
Oh, who cares?
I never wanted any part of it.
Is this still because
I stole your sweets?
How dare you talk back
to your father like that?
You should be ashamed.
Hey, Pops, I'm not the
one with the problem here.
SAOTOME: Oh, and I see this
is the way you show respect
to your very own father.
RANMA: You've
gotta earn respect.
Besides, this whole
stupid argument is stupid!
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
Maybe he was serious.
Hey, Ryoga, so have
you decided yet?
Uh.
Well--
Oh, Ryoga.
What the--
AKANE: What?
You can't be serious, Saotome.
The Saotome School
needs someone strong,
someone who won't be burdened
with family problems.
Well, then I can only assume
you've put a lot of thought
into your decision.
You bet.
Excuse me, but if Ryoga does
in fact inherit the Saotome
school, then--
Go on.
Then what would happen
with Akane's engagement?
SAOTOME: She's right.
That's a good question.
But I don't want--
I guess she becomes
Ryoga's fiance.
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): My fiance?
SOUN: I suppose
it's only natural.
KASUMI: I'm so happy
for you, Akane.
Don't I even have
a say in this?
Akane.
[grunting]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Stupid old man.
Dragging Ryoga into this.
How could he?
Left, right, left, right.
[dog howling]
Now what
From now on, Ryoga and
myself will be inseparable.
I can't figure out
what you're thinking.
But when you come to
your senses, Pops,
would you please let me know?
Maybe it's you who should
come to his senses, boy.
When you realize
what you've done,
perhaps then you'll
admit your mistake
and ask for forgiveness.
That's all I have to say.
I can't just sit back and
let all of this happen to me.
Oh, we're out of milk.
RANMA: You can't sleep, either?
Huh?
Ranma!
You scared me.
RANMA: You want me to go
out and get you some milk?
Oh, that's OK.
It's pretty late.
Hey, I think the corner
store is still open.
It's OK, really.
CLERK: Thank you for shopping.
Have a nice night.
[laughter]
Man, I wonder if old Ryoga's
taking this whole thing
seriously.
He probably still
doesn't even have a clue.
I'm sure of it.
Thank you, master.
Oh yes, I like that
when you call me master.
Master, I personally
guarantee I can beat Ranma.
Ryoga, I must confess it pains
me a great deal that I have
disgraced my own flesh
and blood by telling you
all of his weak points,
so that you can embarrass
that boy of mine in public.
But I'm must for the
good of my school.
Then I cannot fail you.
Ryoga, look.
That star represents
my entire empire.
Your mission is
to reach up for it
and become the new shining
star of the Saotome School.
RYOGA: OK.
So has your dad moved
back into the house?
Who cares?
If he likes sleeping in a
lousy tent, I say let him.
Ranma, do you think
there's a chance that Ryoga
is going to take over
your father's school?
[grunting]
Stay on your toes, boy.
Listen carefully, Ryoga.
In order to defeat
Ranma, you must
learn his special techniques.
That's it, Ryoga.
Keep going.
Harder, harder, feel the burn.
That's it.
They seem pretty serious.
Hm.
Huh Hey, wait.
This really bugs
you, doesn't it?
Not a chance.
Please don't lie.
So what's your point?
One okonomiyaki to go.
It is so nice to see
you two getting along.
Mind your own business.
Let's go Ranma.
Oh, by the way, Akane, I just
heard Ryoga's your new fiance.
You must be really
excited about that.
Huh?
Well, you must have heard wrong.
Oh, and from the
rumors going around,
Ranma, is it true
that Ryoga is going
to take over your dad's school?
I guess.
What?
If that's the
case, then it looks
like you'll be moving out of
the Tendo house pretty soon,
hey, Ranma?
Moving out?
Yeah, I suppose
she has a point.
Hey, I got an idea.
You could move in with me.
You've got to be kidding.
Think about it.
We're already engaged,
so you can move in here
any time you wanted to.
That's a stupid idea.
Maybe not.
Akane, I'm going to
stay here a but longer.
UKYO: By the way, Akana, that
okonomiyaki is on the house.
Why, you jerk, Ranma!
Calamari as usual?
Sure.
Or maybe something in to
help me keep up my strength.
Ra-- Ranma, I mean, I know
that we've always been engaged
and all, but it's so sudden.
You know?
Not that I, you know--
I'm so embarrassed.
I bet Ryoga's going to
challenge me any day now.
[grunting]
Kick.
Good one.
[screaming]
If you want to win, Ryoga, your
moves must be more precise.
Right.
But the hour fast
approaches when
you must do battle with Ranma.
Master, what's wrong?
It is time to reveal the
last of Ranma's weaknesses.
Stop it.
I can beat him without knowing.
I've trained too long
and too hard to lose.
Don't be so sure, my boy.
Master Saotome, didn't you tell
me that I was the shining star?
Huh?
I've got a big mouth.
Hey, Akane, this wouldn't be
me takeout, would it, Akane?
Oh, and here I am starving.
This match will determine
who will inherit the Saotome
School of Martial Arts.
Begin.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Pop.
[screaming]
Wow, I didn't think
Ryoga was that good.
You're right.
[gasping]
It's turning out to be
quite the intense battle.
Ryoga and Ranma are
fighting toe-to-toe
without so much as showing
any signs of tiring.
And still the question remains
in this fight to the finish--
who will be the
last one standing
and win the honor of
being Akane's fiance?
Come on, Ryoga!
I'm cheering for you this time
for special personal reasons.
Don't you dare lose, Ryoga.
SAOTOME (VOICEOVER): It's
time to stop toying with him.
Huh?
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
Did Mr. Saotome just
signal Ryoga to block?
That means Ryoga knows when
Ranma's going to strike.
Well, after all
that, does this mean
Ryoga's our new brother-in-law.
Yes, I guess it does.
I've had it.
[screaming]
SAOTOME (VOICEOVER):
Forgive me, Ranma.
But I need someone
who won't lose focus
on his job with family problems.
Oh, sure, I remember how
hard we trained together
as I groomed you to take
over the Saotome school.
Goodbye, Ranma.
What does he think he's doing?
This announcer has no
idea what's going on here.
Huh?
[screaming] I hate cats!
I hate 'em!
Please tell me this
isn't the major weakness
of Ranma's the master was
going to tell me about.
This is so pathetic.
Here's your big chance, Ryoga.
This might be your
last opportunity, boy.
It's time to get revenge for
Ranma stealing my sweets.
Do it!
What did you say?
Your revenge for your
sweets being stolen?
This was about you
getting your revenge?
Why don't you
explain to everyone
how you could do this do your
own son over some stupid sweets
you had stashed away.
Tell us, Saotome, is what
Ranma's saying the truth?
This is all a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
Ranma, you've
got to believe me.
I was just training
Ryoga so that you
could have a more equal
partner to work out with.
You can't very well blame
you for that, now, can you?
How can you stand
there and lie like that?
OK, I admit it.
I was just trying to teach you
a lesson for stealing my sweets.
Now, back off!
RYOGA: So Ranma's right.
Huh?
You were just using
me, weren't you?
SAOTOME: No.
How can you say that?
Why, you've always been
like a son to me, Ryoga.
And besides, why would
I lie? (LAUGHING)
Help me!
AKANE: Ranma, I
brought you some tea.
There ain't no way
in a million years
I'm ever going to forgive
Pop for what he did to me.
Akane, did you happen to bring
those sweets I asked for.
No, I think we're
all out of them.
Doesn't she realize this is
how the whole mess started
in the first place?
Would somebody please tell me
why all this weird stuff always
happens to me.
Ah, Ranma, I see
you're becoming more
like your old man every day.
[theme music]
[singing in japanese]
NARRATOR: The residents
of the Tendo Dojo
go to the amusement park,
only to find that there's
no lunch, or any money.
Now, what do we do?
Next time on "Ranma
1/2," Tendo family
goes to the amusement park.
We'll see you there.