NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome, of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
And here's Akane, of
the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma is
splashed with cold water
he becomes a she.
[school bells ringing]
[music playing]
[oven timer rings]
[chattering]
-This is still a
classroom girls.
Would you please act like it?
KODACHI KUNO: Oh, teacher dear.
-Huh?
-Something wrong, Miss Kuno?
-Seeing as I've suddenly
recalled a previous engagement
I'll be leaving today's
class a little early.
[evil laughter]
-Huh?
-Kodachi Kuno, leaving early.
NARRATOR: It's a fine line
between pleasure and pain.
[school bell rings]
TEACHER 1: OK girls, that's
it for today's class.
GIRL 1: Oh, great.
GIRL 2: When she
see's I put the--
GIRL 3: That's hilarious,
I can't believe it.
They don't look half bad.
BOY 1: Hey, they've got cookies.
BOY 2: Come on, we'll
taste test them for you.
GIRL 5: You can't have any.
BOY 3: Hey, some
of those for me?
BOY 4: Come on, huh?
--[chuckling] It is
said that, for a woman,
true happiness can only be found
in cooking for her beloved.
Akane Tendo, allow
me to make you happy.
Ooh!
-I'd think again, seeing
as how her cooking probably
killed better men than you.
-Ugh.
-Maybe they won't be good.
But at least try one!
-[groaning]
-Aren't they cute?
They're animal crackers.
-These are animals?
An octopus?
-Stupid, it's a penguin.
-A hermit crab?
-It's a lion.
-It's a water flea.
-A rabbit.
RANMA: Lochness Monster.
AKANE: A swan.
RANMA: A Power Ranger.
AKANE: A racoon!
RANMA: A salimander.
AKANE: An alligator!
RANMA: I know, a platypus.
AKANE: A koala!
You'd better eat one quick
or I'm gonna get mad!
[whip cracks]
-Ha!
-Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
-Good afternoon, Ranma, darling.
-Hmm.
-So it's my twisted sister.
-A present, darling, catch.
-Huh?
-Baked with love by yours
truly, in today's home ec
class, my dearest darling.
-Hey, it's a pentagram.
-It's a starfish.
-Hey, I want my cookies back.
-Oh, is that what they are?
Uh!
They shall never touch
my darling Ranma's lips.
-Hey!
That's not fair!
-Hmm?
-You should have eaten them.
Now it's too late!
-Those things would
have made me sick!
-How can you even say that
when I worked so hard to make
them taste good?
-Mmm.
[music playing]
RANMA: Huh mm.
Ah ha.
Huh ah.
Kodachi, wait up!
-Huh?
Oh, Ranma, darling.
Oh, I just knew you'd
come for me, my love.
-Don't get any weird ideas.
I came for the
cookies, not for you.
-Ha ha ha.
You big kidder.
-Ooh.
-Head's up!
RANMA: Whoa.
SCHOOL GIRLS: Get him!
Get him!
-Ahh!
-I'll be back tomorrow!
[girls yelling]
-Uhh.
Huh?
-So bold, my love.
Make me your own.
-Uhh.
AKANE: Ranma!
MALE: I saw him go this way.
-Ranma, my love.
I feel different already.
Adieu.
-Uh.
-See, I told ya.
-Hey, my cookies.
-Hey Ranma, if you're not
gonna eat Kodachi's cookies,
is it all right if we have them?
-They're pretty good.
-Look, now you could
try one for yourself.
-No.
No, thank you.
-Now what's wrong?
-I feel like I'm gonna be sick.
(VOICEOVER) I think that
my heart just stopped.
MAN: Allow me.
-Oh!
Oh!
-Why didn't you tell me they
weren't for human consumption?
-Hey, you!
What did you say?
[snoring]
-As suspected, my twisted
sister has laced them
with sleeping potion.
-(VOICEOVER) Oh, man.
That was close.
Way too close!
[crying]
AKANE: Stop crying already.
Would you have rather
had the sleeping potion?
-He he he he he, I've got
you now, Ranma Saotome.
Your infidelity
is now on record.
-How perfectly clever of you.
Did you really?
-Yes, with my
trusty camera here.
He can deny it, but
the camera never lies.
-Then you won't
mind if I borrow it?
Uh!
Eh!
-Oh, be my guest.
But may I have my camera
back when you're through?
[music playing]
-(VOICEOVER) He embarrassed
me in front of everybody.
I'll show him, though.
I'll bake the best
cookies he's ever tasted.
KASUMI TENDO: You want me
to teach you how to bake?
AKANE: You probably would
rather not, but would you mind?
-You mean you're ready
for bridal training?
Of course I will.
-Uh, I didn't mean it
like that, actually.
-Why, silly?
There's nothing for you
to be embarrassed about.
Oh, Akane, I was beginning to
think that you would never--
well, never mind that for now.
Let's begin, shall we?
-No, no thank you.
-(VOICEOVER) Just
you watch, Ranma.
You'll be sorry you
ever doubted me.
Very sorry!
Ya!
[crashing]
-Huh?
AKANE: About this
much sugar, right?
KASUMI TENDO: Akane?
That's salt.
AKANE: And vanilla extract?
KASUMI TENDO: That's
sesame oil, dear.
-What's she making,
pot stickers?
SOUN TENDO: What's this?
She finally asked for
bridal training, did she?
And where is Akane now?
-She's still in the kitchen
working on her cookie recipe.
She's been there since
she got home from school.
-That's my girl.
Ha ha.
[oven timer rings]
-Blech!
They're no good either!
The smell of the
cinnamon and nutmeg
is overpowering everything.
The vanilla extract and garlic
I chopped into the dough
completely destroyed the hidden
notes of cherry and watermelon.
And for some mysterious
reason the corn starch
I dissolved in hot water and
blended in with the flour
is hardening to a
brick-like consistency.
Ranma will never agree
to eat them at this rate.
Uh, I won't give up!
[crashing]
AKANE: Arhh!
[oven timer rings]
AKANE: Ahh!
These taste terrible!
I'll have to start all over.
OK, then, this time I'll try
it without the jalapenos.
TEACHER 2: And so you see
the product of x and y
isn't equal to the square
root of 14 plus 8 at all.
-Huh?
[snoring]
GIRL 6: I got it!
-Wow, you stayed up
cooking all night
and he still wouldn't try one?
-I can't believe how
thoughtless he is, Akane.
I don't know why
you put up with him.
I can't figure you out.
-OK, that's it!
He's gonna eat it and like
it, even if it kills him!
-You go, girl!
Yeah!
-Huh?
[school bell rings]
GIRL 7: Good bye, Akane.
Let us know how
it turns out, OK?
-(VOICEOVER) Looks like it's
time for me to get serious.
Here we go.
Let's see.
"Cakes You Can Bake."
Here, "Easy Recipes."
Perfect.
Nothing can stop me now.
KODACHI KUNO: Sorry, to keep
you waiting, Ranma darling.
-Huh?
Ranma?
-And how were those cookies
I made for you, darling?
I trust there were no
lingering side effects.
-I wouldn't know.
-How fortunate I
made another batch.
-No, thank you.
-I see.
Then you'd prefer this?
-Ugh!
-You hand that all over!
Tisk, tisk, darling.
Now are we hungry for
cookies after all?
-OK, give me the picture
and I'll eat them.
[gnawing]
-Eat hardy, darling.
-(VOICEOVER) Oh, so
that's how it is, is it?
He'll eat Kodachi's cookies
but he won't eat mine?
Fine then.
We'll just see who's
cookies he likes better.
One way or the other.
[music playing]
-Huh.
Uh.
(VOICEOVER) Won't
eat my cookies, huh?
I've just begun to fight.
-[breathing hard] Oh, man.
This stupid thing would
have ruined me for life.
Eating them cookies was
a high price to pay,
but it was worth it.
[grunting and tearing]
-It's finally over.
Now I can live in peace.
AKANE: Uhh ahh!
-Ahh!
[music playing]
[oven timer rings]
AKANE: They're done!
-The moment of truth, Ranma.
Feed or flee.
-(VOICEOVER) Oh man, if I eat
another cookie today I'm gonna
hurl.
-I know you won't
disappoint me, son.
Please, help yourself.
-Akane worked so hard, Ranma.
And she made them just for you.
-Show some gratitude, boy.
-Mmm.
Hmm?
-Special delivery from the
mistress we dare not name.
Farewell!
(VOICEOVER) I know a loyal
ninja never questions orders.
But why must Mistress
Kodachi-- uh oh, ahh!
-Ugh, there's a black rose.
It must be from Kodachi.
-Ugh.
-(VOICEOVER) To my dearest,
darling, most adorable Ranma.
I have, this day,
with my own two hands,
prepared you a feast.
Come quickly, my love,
lest it grow cold.
-A feast?
More food?
Doesn't she know when to quit?
-Come on, you're one to talk.
Later we can paste
into our scrap book
a commemorative photo?
KODACHI KUNO: (VOICEOVER)
Such joy, darling.
Such bliss.
I'm so happy I want to share
it with the entire town, photo
by photo by glorious photo.
-Err!
I've gotta stop her
before it's too late.
-Come back and eat
your cookie like a man!
-You know, I think
I'll take a rain check.
[music playing]
-Ranma, darling.
You've claimed me at last.
[whispering]
-Oh, surely you must remember
as clearly as I, my love.
[music playing]
-Such joy, such bliss, my dear.
Oh, I cannot bear to
keep it all to myself.
Feel the love!
[murmuring]
-Ranma?
-Ranma, darling.
-I'm going to put an end to
your blackmail once and for all.
I'll eat your evidence.
-My, who knew you were
so fond of photos?
In that case, eat
your hearts content.
-Uh.
-(VOICEOVER) This
could go on forever.
I'm gonna have to
come up with a plan.
I'd much rather
eat the negative.
-All right, the
negative it is then.
But how shall I
prepare it for you?
-Uh, plain.
-Very well, my darling.
Look for it in the
collar of my dear pet,
Mr. Green Turtle, who
lives in Yonder Pond.
-Some kind of turtle, huh?
OK.
-Mm, not quite, darling.
[music playing]
-There it is.
The last one in's a rotten egg.
Huh!
OK, Mr. Turtle, come to mama.
Huh?
[music playing]
-Ahh!
Mr. Green Turtle, huh?
Stay still, you, and give
me that negative or I'm
gonna have to-- ahh!
Uh, uh.
-Oh dear, I forgot.
The high voltage security system
on Mr. Green Turtle's collar
is still on.
TATAWAKI KUNO: Ah:
that honeyed voice.
SASUKE SARUGAKURE: The cry
came from the pond, Master.
-Oh.
-Here she lies, her beauty makes
this pond of feasting presence.
Thou art yet so fair.
-Oh, Ranma.
Thy garments are still warm .
-Though the honey of thy
breath hath been sucked,
thou art not conquered.
-I think I'll throw up now.
-Leave you no friendly
drop to help me after?
-Huh, you shouldn't have.
I am a very handsome
rascal, am I not?
AKANE: Ranma, where are you?
-That sounds like Akane Tendo.
You've come to date
with me, haven't you?
Oh!
-I'm looking for
Ranma, you idiot.
Where are you hiding him?
KODACHI KUNO: Ah ha ha ha ha.
Your timing could not be
better, my dear Akane Tendo.
-Excuse me?
-Seeing as Ranma has come
to me of his own free will
he will want you to have these.
Uh.
-She's as swift as the
goddess of the wind herself.
-Uh.
-Go on, go home.
-Hm.
-Oh yeah, where did
that dumb collar go?
-It is not dumb.
-Ooh, the collar, you
give that back you.
[screaming]
-Your touch makes me
tingle all over, my love.
Ahh!
-Once it's fastened there's
no getting it off again.
-What did you say?
-There is only one
way that the lock
can be disabled-- by
dousing it with hot water.
-How's about it?
I'll scrub your back
if you scrub mine.
-You and I together!
-Uh.
-But think of your
reputation, my love.
Think of the scandal
it would cause
if we were to be seen together.
Oh, you're mad to
even suggest it.
As a gentleman I
cannot allow it.
-This way, Master.
-Mixed bathing is for
moral degenerates.
[breathing hard] Argh!
Blast!
I can't get my kimono off!
Ah!
-Well it serves you right.
-You there, yes you.
-Huh?
-I'll bet you haven't even
kissed Ranma yet, now have you?
-What?
-You haven't, have you?
Come on, you know it.
Don't try to lie to me.
-Maybe you should get some help.
-Mhm hm hm hm, have a
look at this, my dear.
-Uh.
Ugh.
Ooh!
-Are you ready yet, dear?
Hey, I'm getting cold.
Huh?
(VOICEOVER) Oh, for
crying out loud, now
what's the matter with him?
-What kind of gentleman
retains his own clothes
while a lady goes without?
Ah!
Curse you, fate!
-I don't care if you're
in the buff or not,
just get in already.
[splash] Ah ha!
I got it.
I'll never have to
be afraid again.
AKANE: Ya!
-Ahh! [splash] Hey!
Well, aren't you the playboy?
-Look, I don't know what
you think that I-- huh?
-You make a lovely couple.
Good bye!
-Wait, Akane.
-Why you Ranma Saotome!
What have you done with
the pig-tailed girl?
Admit it!
You've turned her naivete to
your own lustful ends, now,
haven't you?
You enemy of women!
Bring her back to me this
instant or you'll pay!
[music playing]
-(VOICEOVER) You dummy, Ranma.
Why did I even bother?
Maybe I'm not the
world's greatest cook,
but you didn't even
give me a chance.
I worked really
hard on those, too.
You dummy.
RANMA: Hey, Akane, I want
to show you something.
-What?
-Well take a look.
As you can see, it was
all a misunderstanding.
More like an accident.
So that means you can stop
being jealous now, OK?
-Jealous!
Who's jealous?
Of you?
You've got to be kidding.
-Then why are you so mad?
-I could care less.
-Well, can I finish
this off, then?
-Finish what off?
-Why, your cookies, of course.
-Huh?
-I'll help myself.
[gulping] Mmm.
Wow, that's pretty good.
Mmm.
Yeah, kind of spicy.
I like it.
Mmm.
This one's good too.
Yeah, kind of, different flavor.
Mmm, yeah.
-[sighing]
-[groaning] Oh man.
It hurts.
I think I'm going
to be sick again.
Oh, oh, somebody kill me.
-Poor, Ranma.
Isn't there anything
else we can do?
-Just what is it you
ate, anyway, boy?
It must really be something to
upset your cast iron stomach.
-(VOICEOVER) That's odd.
Hmm, there must be something
wrong with the recipe.
[music playing]
[singing in japanese]
NARRATOR: What are
we gonna do with him?
There's been nothing but
trouble since he showed up.
Lucky for us there's
a new Chinese remedy.
You can do it, Ranma.
Next time on Ranma 1/2, SOS!
The Wrath of Happosai.
See you there.