[theme music]
-Ranma!
You can stay a weakling for the
rest of your miserable life,
for all I care.
-Aw, come on.
You know how he is.
I'm sure he'll come around.
Ranma?
Ranma, you OK?
-Hey!
What's the matter with you?
-Stop trying to cheer me up.
-But-- I--
-Father!
They're gone!
Both Ranma and Mr.
Saotome have left!
They must have packed last
night, while we were sleeping.
And then--
-But why?
-Perhaps he felt
that being weak,
he could not take over the dojo.
-Oh, the humanity!
-I don't believe it!
-Ranma's no coward.
He would never run
from a real fight.
You believe that,
Dad, don't you?
Don't you agree?
NARRATOR: Eureka!
The Desperate Move
Of Desperation!
-Ranma Saotome absent again?
-Ukyo's absent, too.
-I wonder where she is?
-Moxabustion Rocks.
Yamogi Valley?
She's gone after him.
I just know she has.
What's with Ranma, anyway?
He doesn't even
say a word to me,
but then he invites
Ukyo along for the ride?
[grunting]
-Oh, man.
It's hot.
And heavy.
-You want to be strong
again, don't you, boy?
You're not being crushed
under just any rock, you know.
The moxa rocks of
Yamogi Valley are
known all over Japan for
their natural healing.
For example, monkey
back aches, sprained
bear ankles, birth
pains of deer.
Many fish suffer from
myopia, which they-- huh?
-Will you shut up, already?
-Yes!
Hold it.
I knew it wouldn't last.
-So I guess we
wasted a trip, huh?
If the rocks don't work, then--
-All the rocks in the world
won't do us any good unless we
can cure the strength sapping
moxabustion with that pressure
point chart of the master's.
-But we're here cause he
wouldn't give it to us.
-Precisely.
But I have a new plan.
-What is it?
Tell me.
-Come on, spit it out.
What are you waiting for?
-Ranma, my boy,
sometimes the cure
can be worse than the disease.
-To beat the old freak,
I'll try anything.
Do you hear?
-Just remember, it
was you who asked.
Saotome Anything Goes
Desperation Move,
the Crouch of the Wild Tiger.
-Crouch of the Wild Tiger?
-Assume the position.
-You mean like this?
-Place both hands on the earth.
Finally, face your
opponent and-- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
The technique itself is named
for a legendary wild tiger
which fell from a cliff, and--
-It's nothing but groveling with
a fancy name, and you know it!
-Having a hard with
the son in law?
-Hey, the old ghoul.
-You do make a powerful,
tasty okonomiyaki.
-Really?
RANMA: What do you want?
-Oh, come now.
You didn't really think that
I'd abandon my future son in law
on his most desperate
hour of need, did you?
Seriously, though, from
the look of things,
you're going to need all
the help you can get.
-Thanks but no thanks, granny.
You know, I'd just as
rather do it on my own,
if it's all the same to you.
-Not by using the Crouch of the
Wild Tiger nonsense, you won't.
Oh, that is rich.
That's not to say there isn't
a technique you can use, even
in your weakened state.
-Huh?
-That technique is
the Hiryu Shoten Ha.
-The Heaven Blast of the Dragon.
-Why, that sounds
even more powerful
than the mighty Crouch
of the Wild Tiger.
-I'm warning you, this
heaven blast technique
better not mean heaven
fart, or nothing like that.
Huh?
-Care for a demonstration?
Maybe the three of
you would like to try?
-Can't be much further.
Ranma.
Oh?
Ah!
[scream]
-What the-- Oh!
Ranma!
-The old ghoul was right!
What an incredible technique!
I can do it!
I can beat the freak!
I'll have it down
in three days, tops!
-What?
He didn't even notice me!
Oh well, no big deal.
At least he seems happy.
-I'm starving.
What have we got to eat
around here, anyway?
-Yamogi Valley, eh?
Well, if you want
the valley, you'd
best head that-a way,
past them there mountains.
-All right.
You stay here while
I go to Yamogi Valley
and look for Ranma, OK?
-Akane.
-Hm.
Admit it, boy.
Aren't you glad I asked
Ukyo to come along?
-Oh, yeah.
You did good, pop.
Just imagine Akane's nasty
food during training.
-Never mind before a match.
-Yeah.
I'd be dead for sure.
-Hm?
-I was really worried
about you, y'know?
Huh?
-Assume the position!
-I suppose it does
have its uses.
Well then, let's get
on with it, shall we?
Tell me what it was you saw.
-At the time, I thought that
we were surrounding you.
But then I realized, it was
you who was drawing us in.
And then at that point,
with a single strike--
[screaming]
-I could be wrong,
but I think the steps
went-- kind of like this.
-That's my future son
in law, all right.
All it took was a
single demonstration.
Not to oversimplify, but
yes, the Hiryu Shoten Ha
is essentially a spiral.
-I may have lost my strength,
but I haven't lost my speed.
-Listen.
It doesn't matter
how you come at me.
In fact, the stronger the
opponent, the more powerful
your attack.
The important thing is
not to lose the spiral.
Step outside even once
and you lose momentum.
Now, step into that box of ash.
This way we'll be able to see
exactly where your feet are.
Remember, concentrate on
keeping to the spiral.
-No problemo.
-Very well.
Begin the attack.
-Forgive me, son.
But a dad's gotta do
what a dad's gotta do!
-Huh?
-Ranma at age seven,
after he wet the bed.
-Ah!
Give me that!
Hand it over!
-Humiliating photo
fu number two.
A recent example.
-What are you trying to
do, embarrass me to death?
-Where's Yamogi Valley?
-What's the matter with you?
Look at your footprints, idiot.
Is this what you call
staying in the spiral?
There's no room in the
spiral for embarrassment,
no room for anger.
You've got to keep
your ego out of it.
If you're obsessed
on watching yourself,
when are you gonna
watch your opponent?
So in other words, what you need
to cultivate is a soul of ice.
-But how can a soul be ice?
-I can't tell you that.
That's something that
you'll have to figure out
for yourself, otherwise
you'll never master it.
-I can do that.
If it means mastering
the Hiryu Shoten Ha,
there's nothing too
embarrassing for me to endure.
-Ranma!
-Ranma honey!
-That's the spirit, my boy!
You're going to make me proud.
No matter what it takes.
Last night in his
sleep, Ranma said,
Akane, make me your love slave!
-Hey!
That's a lie!
I never said that,
and you know it!
-Don't lose your cool
remember, remember?
-Akane, I love you!
-Cut it out!
Admit it!
Admit you're lying!
-You're such a
jerk, you know that?
-And what about me, huh?
Huh?
-That's [inaudible], baby!
-Shut up, OK?
-Is this how you repay
me for helping you?
-Hey, what about me?
-I love you!
RANMA: I do not!
I-- I did it!
-I knew you could do it.
-This was only the first step.
Don't get too excited.
It gets worse from here on in.
-Bring it on, granny.
I'm ready.
-It's not you I'm worried about.
It's those two.
They'll have to leave.
-But-- but why?
Why can't we just stay here?
-Yeah.
Why can't we?
-Can you honestly say
you're ready to attack Ranma
without holding back?
-Huh?
-And what of you, son-in-law?
Even if you master
the technique,
will you be able to use
it against these girls?
-I-- uh--
-And so, an impasse.
Unless we can find someone
willing to go against Ranma
with all their strength,
we can't possibly--
RYOGA: That someone is me!
-Hm?
-I'd be glad to help out.
Course, I can't give
you any guarantees
that I won't kill him.
-Ryoga!
Ryoga, why-- why are you--
you've come to help me,
haven't you?
I-- I just don't
know what to say.
I-- I can't believe it.
Ryoga!
-That's not why I'm here!
-Ryoga, I don't know
how to thank you--
-Wait!
Wait a minute!
Let go of me!
-Ryoga!
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I wonder
if he got lost again?
-Ah, now this is the life.
This hot water is great.
-So what are we doing
at hot springs, anyway?
-I don't know.
What's with that silly get up?
That's what I want to know.
-You're asking me?
-Shall we start phase
two of the training?
-Oh, yeah.
-Very well.
-Ranma!
-What'd you do that for?
-That tension suit
you're wearing
reacted to the heat
of your angry attack.
Keep your cool.
Resist the urge to let go
with your fighting spirit,
and it won't resist
your movement.
Ready to try again?
-You can do it, Ranma honey!
-Attack him at
your full strength,
and don't hold anything back.
-Lady, you don't
gotta ask me twice.
-Try me, why don't you?
-Yah!
-Keep cool, son in law!
Hold back your emotions and
draw Ryoga into the spiral.
-Wow.
He's doing it.
He's drawing Ryoga
into the circle,
and the suit's not giving
him any trouble-- meaning
that he's keeping his cool!
-What's wrong with you?
-That hurt!
-Do you take me for a fool?
I told you to attack
him with full strength.
-Hey, I attacked him
with all that I--
-Did you?
The heat of battle
is the fuel that
enflames the dragon's fire.
In other words-- unless you're
willing to hurt him, really
hurt him, this training
exercise is useless.
-But I-- I thought
I was serious.
-Moron.
Jerk face.
You got no sense
of direction, huh?
How was that?
You finally ready to
be serious, pig boy?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER): When this
new Ranma hits me, or calls
me those names, it
doesn't hurt a bit.
In fact, to me his
curses sound more
like the barks of a frightened
dog from behind a fence.
-What's the matter
with you, man?
You going to come at me, or not?
-Ranma, forgive me.
-Why?
What did you do wrong?
-It seems I-- I didn't
mean to, but I-- I guess it
must be true.
I'm a nicer guy than
I myself thought.
Ranma, I'm sorry,
but I'm just too
nice a guy to hit you
when you're like this!
Go ahead and laugh
at me if you want.
-Ryo-- Hey, where are you going?
-Off for a good cry?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
I'm just too nice
a guy to hit you when
you're like this!
-Who needs you?
Run away for all I care.
I'll figure it out on my own!
Ah!
-I'm ready.
Come at me!
-Wha-- What the heck are you?
-If it's hear that
you need, try these.
Pretty smart of me, huh?
-Smart?
Try stupid.
-Shut up and fight.
Hiya!
-Akane!
See, I told you so.
-It seemed like a
good idea at the time.
What was I thinking?
-Here.
Go home, will ya?
-Why?
I was only trying to
help you, you know?
-Well, maybe I don't
need your help.
To be perfectly honest, I never
wanted you to come and follow
me here in the first place.
-You don't need me.
-What?
-I'm not good for
anything, am I?
-Are you crying?
-Wait!
You don't understand.
Akane, I-- I can explain!
Wait!
Whoa!
Akane, I-- look, it's like this.
I didn't want-- listen.
I couldn't stand for
you, of all people,
to see me so weak and pathetic.
-Oh, like you're not weak
and pathetic even when
you are strong.
-Hey, you.
I'm trying to apologize.
-Well, gee whiz.
You could have fooled me.
Huh?
How long have you been--
-Your clothes ripped to
pieces, tears in your eyes?
-Oh.
Oh, it's not like that.
Really.
-Don't say a word, Akane!
Not to me!
Now, Ranma--
-Hm?
-You animal!
You had your way
with her, didn't you?
-I what?
-Die.
-Look, you've got it all wrong.
Hm.
Akane, forgive me.
-Hm?
-Something came over me.
I-- I couldn't help myself.
-What?
-I took advantage of you.
-You what?
-Look, there's no use crying
over spilled milk, but--
-What?
What is the matter with you?
It's not true.
He's a liar.
A liar!
-Ah-ha!
Got him!
-Shut up!
-Ryoga, listen to me.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Yes!
Now to get him into the spiral.
-Die!
-OK.
Now I'm in trouble.
-Stand up, you!
-Stop!
Stop it!
You'll kill him
if you keep just--
-Back off!
I can handle it!
Do you want to ruin my training?
-Training?
Is that what you think this is?
Time for you to
think again, Ranma!
Time for you to suffer!
RANMA: That's good!
Come on!
-What will we do?
-That Ryoga boy puts
out a fine battle aura.
And what a good
friend to Ranma, too.
-You're not listening!
If we don't stop him, he'll--
-Can't you see?
-What?
-See the waves of Ryoga's anger?
Soon he'll be locked in
the coils of the dragon.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Five more steps
till the center of the spiral.
-Once Ranma is within
the center of the spiral,
the heat of his
opponent's battle aura
will awaken the sleeping dragon,
thereby claiming its power
as his own.
-Heaven Blast of the Dragon.
[clearing throat]
-What's wrong?
-I forgot to teach
him the final step.
-You what?
Ranma, run away!
-Almost there.
-Ranma!
You can't win!
-It's a twister!
-Hm?
-Huh?
It's Ryoga.
-Hiryu Shoten Ha.
-Looks like he learned
it all on his own.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Ranma?
Can you really beat Happosai?
I hate to admit
it, but sometimes I
feel more like your
babysitter than your fiance.
Next time on Ranma
1/2, Showdown!
Can Ranma Make A Comeback?
We'll see ya there!