[music playing]
[theme music]
Oh.
It's closed today.
I really had my heart set on
one of those cherry blossom rice
cakes.
Just my luck.
Huh?
This is your lucky
day, young missy.
I know a cherry
blossom rice cake
that would be perfect for
a young lady like yourself.
You don't say.
No, wait!
Young miss, I sense that
you're lost in love.
No, I'm not.
Now hold your horses!
[panting]
I know for certain that your
love life is troubling you,
and my premonitions have
never failed me yet.
AKANE: Fortune telling with
cherry blossom rice cakes?
Get the man you love to eat
your homemade cherry blossom
rice cake.
And if that man is,
in fact, destined
to fall in love with you--
Mhm?
Then just like
magic, cherry blossoms
will begin to
appear on his face.
Huh?
Come on.
NARRATOR: Wretched
Rice Cakes of Love.
(VOICEOVER) This is so stupid.
Like this is ever going to work.
[gasp]
Hey.
Wait in the living
room, and I'll
bring you some in a minute.
GIRL: Tea's ready, everyone.
Now that's tea.
I like green tea the best.
I don't know what all the
hoopla about coffee is.
[laughter]
Oh, look at this
pattern in my tea leaves.
That means something
good is going to happen,
like you'll get proposed to.
Huh?
SOUN: Uh, Kasumi, can
I have some more tea?
KASUMI: Oh, Father, don't
fill yourself up with tea.
Why don't you have one
of Akane's rice cakes?
SOUN: Well, it's just
that I'm so thirsty.
NABIKI: Yeah, I
know what you mean.
I'm totally parched.
Oh, that reminds me.
I have to take in the laundry.
Oh.
[groan]
Oh, an A cup, a B cup.
Give me a C cup.
[laughter]
Cherry blossom rice cakes.
Akane just finished making
them herself, Master.
Oh, forget it.
Not so fast.
Aren't you forgetting
something, Master?
I see you haven't
tried one yet.
Ah!
Just forget it!
I'll eat every one of
these rice cakes by myself!
No, you won't.
Master would love to have one.
Huh?
[groan]
Oh, that cherry blossom rice
cake is making my head spin.
Sure, whatever.
But how does it taste, Master?
Awful.
[gasp]
What happened to your face?
An X mark on his face?
Then just like
magic, cherry blossoms
will begin to
appear on his face.
And you'll know without
doubt that your destiny
is to be with that man.
And if you're not
destined to be with him,
an X mark will appear.
(VOICEOVER) So this
really does work.
[groan]
Well, so much for that brick.
Huh? (VOICEOVER)
Here comes trouble.
Ranma, do you want
some rice cakes?
Oh.
AKANE: Oh, no, you don't!
Bullseye.
[scream]
Here.
Help yourself.
Help myself.
Don't tell me.
You didn't make these
yourself, did you?
Yep.
Another bullseye.
What are you running away from?
Hey, if you really want
me to spell it out for you,
then no problem.
Taste isn't the only
thing that matters here!
You wish!
I'll partake of Akane's
handmade delicacies.
Bring them on!
Those aren't for you!
I wouldn't advise that.
[gasp]
Well, don't say I
didn't try to warn you.
Thanks for nothing.
Akane Tendo, your
love is a rash
that demands to be scratched.
Huh?
Another X, thank god.
Thank goodness.
What's the deal here, Akane?
Nothing.
This is some kind
of trick, right?
I told you.
It's nothing.
Let us go steady!
[gasp]
Akane Tendo, you sculpted a
mountain of cherry blossom rice
cakes to express your
monumental feelings for me.
So now that it's out in the
open, let's make it official
and go steady.
[scream]
Akane, quit goofing around
and spit it out already.
Fortune telling with
cherry blossom rice cakes?
Yep.
I mean, it was our parents
who decided we'd get engaged,
after all, wasn't it?
So--
What are you getting at?
Uh, whether we
were meant to be.
That's stupid.
[groan]
What?
What what?
I'm saying that if we're not
destined to be together, then
I'm breaking off the engagement!
Yeah, well, that
would be a relief.
Then eat one, and
let's find out!
[groan]
Forget it.
Now what's your problem?
The idea of a cherry blossom
rice cake deciding my future
totally creeps me out.
Ranma.
There's only one thing
that scares me even more.
The thought of
eating your cooking!
Come back here, Ranma!
You're not getting away!
Am so!
[squeal]
AKANE: Ranma, come
here, you wimp!
Get those things away
from me, will you?
[grunting]
[squeal]
[yelling]
What do you think
you're doing, trying
to force an innocent guy to eat
those disgusting cherry blossom
rice cakes?
Ryoga.
Huh?
Ryoga, when did you
eat my rice cakes?
Did you seriously think
they tasted that bad?
Oh, don't tell
me you made them.
Well, yeah.
[gasp]
Now it's making sense.
Those cherry blossom rice cakes
were the most delicious things
I've ever eaten.
Huh?
(VOICEOVER) Cherry blossoms?
On Ryoga's face?
Oh, no, that means
he's my-- oh, no way!
That can't be.
What a taste.
[groan]
Not going to try one?
What are you afraid of?
Uh.
Come on.
I'm not afraid.
And you've got your answer.
Wait, Ranma.
Hm.
It's not easy admitting
something like this,
but Ryoga's not so bad.
Yeah, sure.
Let's see.
He's a lot nicer than you.
Hm?
And he's honest.
[groan]
Well, I'm glad we got
that out in the open.
Uh.
Huh?
Come to think of it, you two
would make an unreal couple.
What are you
talking about, Ranma?
I'm sure you heard
me the first time.
The world's ending.
Mount Fuji's gonna blow!
Run for your lives!
[scream]
I can't take this!
Are you saying Akane
actually likes me?
She's fallen head
over heels for me?
I didn't go quite that far.
[scream]
Why do I let him do it to me?
Oh.
Get the man you love to eat
your homemade cherry blossom
rice cakes.
And if that man is, in
fact, destined to fall
in love with you,
then just like magic,
cherry blossoms will begin
to appear on his face.
I can't be bothered to
make them so how about
giving me some?
[gasp]
Hm.
[purring]
Aha.
Hm.
[meowing]
How about that?
I guess the marks
wash off with water.
You idiot, Ranma.
You don't even care about me.
Anyway, what's the big deal?
All he has to do is eat a
stupid rice cake, right?
[groan]
Blah!
That's disgusting!
[gasp]
[animal sounds]
[groan]
Oh, no.
Now what am I going to you?
[gasp]
(VOICEOVER) OK.
Hang on a minute.
I'm not going to marry myself.
So I'm supposed to get an X.
[groan]
Ah!
You idiot, Akane.
How could you be so stupid?
Hm?
Huh?
Hey, it's gone.
(VOICEOVER) It's only
a stupid rice cake.
I can get one down.
I have the steely
will to do this.
I've trained for this moment.
[groan]
It's only a stupid rice cake.
Ranma!
Are you really going to eat
one of Akane's rice cakes?
[scream]
Stop sneaking up
on me like that!
(VOICEOVER) I've got to get this
over with before someone else
interrupts.
[groan]
SOUN: Ranma, my boy.
I'm the only one who knows
exactly how you feel.
[crying]
You don't have to force
yourself to choke one down.
(VOICEOVER) Ah, no one will
be able to interfere here.
Now let's see if I get
an X or a cherry blossom
when I eat this thing.
Ah.
Uh.
I can't do it.
Maybe if I drink
some more tea first.
[groan]
Nabiki, are you sure Ranma took
one of my cherry blossom rice
cakes with him?
Positive.
Well, I wonder where he
could have gone with it then.
Maybe he's under the
house as we speak.
Give me a break.
Wherever he is,
I don't think you
and Ranma should get too serious
about those cherry blossom
rice cakes.
Wait.
How do you know about it?
About what?
Nothing.
Just forget it.
Love the one you're with.
Then it won't just
seem like an eternity.
It'll be an eternity.
[sigh]
I can't believe Ranma
keeps running away.
I just want to find out the
truth about our relationship.
That's all.
You had your chance.
Now I'm really going
to fall for Ryoga.
[scream]
Uh, Ryoga.
Uh.
You didn't hear what
I said now, did you?
These are for you.
They're beautiful.
See ya!
[humming]
RANMA: Nice going, Akane.
You and your destined
one are hitting it off.
Yeah.
Now that you're
leaving us alone.
I sure had you all wrong.
Switching to Ryoga over a
stupid cherry blossom mark.
Well, that's what you
get for not eating one.
As if it can
predict the future.
AKANE: By the way, Ranma, what
you got in your hand there?
Uh.
Nasty little rice cakes.
They have a way of
sticking to you.
I see you still
haven't tried a bite.
Uh.
You're such a coward.
So you're afraid to find
out what the answer will be!
No, I'm not.
Then what's stopping
you from trying one?
All right then.
We'll do it your way.
Sure you won't
regret this, Akane?
Uh.
I might get a cherry blossom.
I might get an X.
But no hard feelings.
[gasp]
Ranma actually swallowed
one of my rice cakes.
Revolting.
Oh, the pain.
The pain of it all.
(VOICEOVER) If a
cherry blossom shows up,
he's the one I'm
destined to be with.
But if an X shows up--
Ranma, choose one of
my lovely daughters
as your own-- anyone you like.
He'll choose Akane.
Yeah, they're perfect together.
Get real.
Why do I have to go with him?
You're not really
big on guys, right?
Ranma's half female so
it's a perfect match.
He's a freak.
I'll pass.
(VOICEOVER) If an X shows
up on Ranma's face--
Ready, Akane?
I'll turn around at
the count of three.
[gasp]
One, two, three.
[scream]
I don't want to see!
(VOICEOVER) My dear Akane, at
last I understand how you feel
about me.
[scream]
[groan]
I need a mirror.
Oh!
You're going to
regret that, Ranma!
You ruined my letter to Akane!
Tell someone who cares, buddy!
I need a mirror!
Huh?
I'm black?
Why is my face all black?
It's because you did
a faceplant in my ink.
[groan]
No cherry blossoms?
No Xes?
Nothing.
The mark disappeared!
I didn't have a
chance to see it.
Now I'm going to have to
eat another rice cake!
Hey!
I don't know what
your problem is,
but you're not making sense.
Quiet, pig boy.
I need time to think things out.
[squeal]
P-chan?
Are you in here?
[gasp]
It's Akane.
P-chan?
[squeal]
Oh, how'd you get in here?
I told you not to wander
around on your own.
[groan]
Huh?
[sigh]
(VOICEOVER) What's going on?
How can I have no
mark on my face?
Wait a minute.
So the mark disappears
when you wash.
Hang on.
Then what about Ryoga's
cherry blossom mark?
Oh, P-chan.
Should I really spend the
rest of my life with Ryoga?
[squeal]
Cherry blossoms are
supposed to show up
on the guy I'm
destined to marry.
And cherry blossom marks
showed up on Ryoga's face.
[whimper]
What's the matter, P-chan?
How come you're crying?
[sigh]
Huh?
I heard about the
fortune telling.
And the rice cakes.
Oh, man.
I think I know exactly
how you feel, Ranma.
I don't know what to do, either.
What do you mean?
Once Akane and I
get married-- what
do you think I should call her?
Honey, darling, sweet
cheeks, baby doll?
Put a lid on it.
So what's a little black
eye on a day like this?
Maybe I'll just keep calling
her Akane for a while
and see how that goes.
And maybe Akane can call
me Ryoga for a while.
Or perhaps even my
beloved husband.
Nah.
That's a bit too stiff, I guess.
So how about something more
casual like darling or honey?
Ooh, that's sweet.
Or maybe something
original like pudding pie.
Akane.
Pudding pie.
Akane!
Pudding pie!
Pudding pie, anything
for my pudding pie!
[scream]
[squeal]
Ow!
[scream]
Get away from me, you crazy pig!
[squeal]
[grunts]
Ranma!
What you doing?
None of your business.
Now would you leave
me alone for once?
[gasp]
Ranma, look at the
cherry blossoms.
What?
But they weren't there
a few minutes ago.
(VOICEOVER) Hang on.
They're P-chan's hoof marks.
All right.
Now it's all starting
to make sense.
Akane's rice cakes
tasted horrible.
So painfully horrible that
P-chan was hoofing himself
in the forehead to get
the taste out of his mind.
And the hoof marks were so dark
that they stayed on his face,
even after P-chan
turned into Ryoga.
Hm.
So you've got the cherry
blossom marks on your face, too.
But it looks like you've got
a lot more than Ryoga had.
Too bad.
Just when I thought
that it was finally
all over between you and me.
You idiot.
These marks on Ryoga
and me are P-chan--
But since you've got at
least twice as many blossom
as he had, I can't
exactly call it off.
Huh?
[laughter]
[non-english singing]
RANMA: Oh, well.
I guess there's no point
in going out of my way
to tell her the truth.
[non-english singing]
AKANE: Here you go, Ranma.
My handmade potato cakes.
You're awfully chipper, Akane.
Got some good news to share?
Not really.
Ranma's very lucky
having Akane cook for him.
Wish I was so lucky.
I'll make something
for everyone tomorrow.
Zip it, Daddy.
[groan]
Come on.
Eat up, Ranma, and tell
me how you like it.
Hm.
Ow.
(VOICEOVER) I'd better
tell her the truth before
she kills me with this stuff.
Here, P-chan.
You have some, too.
Here you go.
[squeal]
[meowing]
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER): Mold?
As in, something you use
to make sculptures with?
No?
Then you mean it's--
next time on Ranma 1/2--
The Horrible Happo Mold-Burst.
We'll see you there.