[music playing]
NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hey, let go!
-Hai-yah!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
The two have been engaged to
marry by their loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma is
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
Behold, the "Chestnuts Roasting
on an Open Fire" technique.
COLOGNE (VOICEOVER): [cackles]
I didn't even hear you.
You came up behind me
without making a sound.
No wonder my great-granddaughter
chose you for her husband.
[thunderclap]
[laughs] Listen carefully,
future son-in-law.
The pressure point I touched
makes your whole body
as sensitive as a cat's tongue.
Even the most tepid water
will seem boiling to you.
In other words, the next
time you turn into a girl,
you won't be able to
endure the hot water you
need to change back.
Unless you want to spend the
rest of your life as a girl,
you'll agree to marry Shampoo.
You won't be able
to change back.
-No!
That can't be right!
[splash]
-Aaaahhhh, it's hot!
[murmuring softly]
Hm?
[gasp] Uh?
-How do you feel, Ranma?
-What the heck am I wearing?
-That old thing?
Just something I
had lying around.
You can have it if you want.
-But I'm a guy.
Right now you're a
girl, so lighten up, OK?
That color is so you.
-It is cute.
And you have been spending a
lot of time as a girl lately,
Ranma.
-It's not like I can help it.
But I'm a guy!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
They're all acting
like it's some kind of joke.
Oh, man, I don't
care what it takes.
I'm gonna change back
into a guy or else!
[gasp]
-Ranma Saotome, prepare
to defend yourself.
Pusillanimous fiend!
-Great, this is all I need.
[gasp]
-Forgive me.
I mistook you for someone else.
And you are so unlike him.
Come to me, my love!
-Jerk.
SHAMPOO: Ranma!
-Huh?
-You change mind about
wedding yet, Ranma?
-No way!
That ghoul ain't gonna
get away with this!
Huh?
-Oh, pigtailed girl!
RANMA: Aaaah!
-Ranma, are you OK?
Oh, it's Kuno.
I wouldn't have hit
him if I'd have known.
Thing for caring.
-Well, next time I'll
just leave you two alone.
-Oh, my love Akane,
I burn for you.
Oh!
-Sh-- Shampoo!
-Ranma, I have
important talking.
You come.
-OK, we're here.
What is it?
-Very happy news!
-Happy for who?
-Ranma, Shampoo discover cure
for full-body [inaudible]
you have now.
-You mean there's a cure?
-Where?
You're not lying to me, are you?
-Do these eyes lie?
-Phoenix Pill?
-Hm, Phoenix Pill?
As in the bird that's
reborn in flames.
[phoenix warbles]
SHAMPOO: Champion
of heat resistance.
-If I take this pill, I can
turn back into a guy again?
Tell me where I can get it.
-Great-Grandmother has it.
-OK, I'm outta here.
Yahoo!
Whoopee!
Woo, woo, woo!
-Out with it, Shampoo.
Why are you telling us this?
-Shampoo love boy-type Ranma.
Maybe pervert girl like
only girl-type Ranma?
Tell truth now.
-Who are you calling
a pervert girl?
SHAMPOO: Calling you.
-I am not!
RANMA: Nekohanten.
Cat Cafe.
So here's the famous
ramen shop at last!
Yo, old ghoul!
Are you home?
-Hello there, future son-in-law.
Have you changed your
mind about Shampoo?
-No, I haven't changed my mind.
-Then why are you here?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): There
it is, the Phoenix Pill.
-Hand that over!
Huh?
Hai-yah!
-Is that the best you can do?
You still don't get
it, do you, sonny boy?
I You haven't got a
chance of defeating me.
You're 100 years too early.
Gotcha.
-Wwaaaaahhhhh!
-Hai-yah!
-Oh, Ranma!
-Oh, yeah?
[crashing]
Whoa!
Oof!
Now you've done it!
[crashing and banging]
[screams]
[crash]
-Silly Ranma.
He no beat Great-Grandmother.
-Come on, that's enough for
one day, don't you think?
Ranma?
-OK, now I'm really mad.
That's it!
Yo, old ghoul!
Hey, can anyone apply
for this job, or what?
-Consider yourself hired.
[laughs]
[chatter]
CUSTOMER: Wow, she is cute.
-Uh, come again--
I mean, welcome.
-One five-flavor
ramen, ready to go.
-OK.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I'll get that
Phoenix Pill while I'm at it.
-You spill, and it comes
out of your salary.
-Whoa, check it out.
-Whoa!
That bowl's floating in mid-air!
[grunting]
-That's the way, sonny boy.
Here you go.
Three more orders up.
-Whoa!
[cheering and hooting]
-Come on, they're not
getting any hotter, you know.
Get a move on.
-Shut up, you old ghoul.
I'm off to work again.
Have a nice day.
Do you think he's overdoing it?
-I hear the place
is standing room
only since the boy
started working there.
-I can't help feeling
sorry for the poor sap.
That old lady's really
running him into the ground.
-With her as his boss, the boy
must be working for every yen.
However, this too
is part of training.
KASUMI: Akane, aren't you
worried just a little bit?
Ranma being forced to work
in that restaurant and all?
-What he does has
nothing to do with me.
Let him move in
there, for all I care.
-Thank you.
Come again.
Bye-bye.
[gasp]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
The Phoenix Pill.
It's mine!
-Catch!
A side of spring rolls and
two orders of potstickers.
[cheering and hooting]
[frustrated growl]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales slowly]
-Uh, hello.
COLOGNE: Order up.
Roast pork ramen, wonton soup,
seven bowls total-- catch!
-What's she doing?
[cheering and hooting]
-Please, no applause!
AKANE: What are you do--
-That's my future son-in-law.
He's made great progress.
-Haven't you had enough?
Look what she's got
you doing, Ranma.
--[laughs] You ain't
seen nothing-- [laughs]
[moans]
-Ranma!
Uh, Ranma, could you-- aaah!
Snap out of it!
-Aaahh!
[cheering and hooting]
-Why are you here?
-Call it research, if you like.
-Come on, you guys,
take it outside.
Let me work.
COLOGNE: Son-in-law,
come over here.
-Huh?
Let me guess.
We're gonna roast
marshmallows, right?
-Something else.
Shampoo, give that to me.
Here I have a bag
of sweet chestnuts.
Watch very carefully.
[gasp]
-Hm.
-Your turn.
-Legendary technique.
Kachu Tenshin Amaguriken.
-Mm, what you just
witnessed was a technique
developed over 3,000 years
of Chinese Amazon history.
Even the last emperor of
China lived in terror of it.
-To pluck the chestnuts from
the flames without being burned.
That must take some
really incredible speed.
-If you can master this,
taking the Phoenix Pill from me
will be child's play.
[laughs]
--[giggle] To be told
secret is good honor.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Chestnuts
Roasting on an Open Fire, eh?
-OK!
I'll master that technique,
even if it kills me.
[fire crackling]
[groans weakly]
-Come on, Ramna, be a man.
If you can't pluck a few
chestnuts from a fire,
how will you carry on
the Saotome School?
All right then, fine.
I'll show you how it's done.
Hyaaaa-aah!
Hah!
Haah!
Huah!
Yah!
Haah!
[shouting with pain]
[splash]
-He still hasn't got it, has he?
So where'd he learn
that dumb trick, anyway?
I don't suppose you know.
-Well, I, uh--
NABIKI: Oh, yeah,
I almost forgot.
There's a fair in
the park today.
You want to come
with me, Kasumi?
-I'll show you how
it's done, he says.
Good one, Pop.
If he couldn't do it, he shoulda
said so in the first place.
COLOGNE: Son-in-law.
-[gasp] Oh!
Now what do you want?
-Have you learned
the technique yet?
Lookie, Ranma.
Here's the Phoenix Pill
that can change you back.
-Don't To patronize me,
you old-- gimme that!
Ooh!
What-- what'd you do?
-[laughs] You're still too slow.
Don't ask again, because
this is the last time.
-I didn't ask you
the first time.
[gasp]
-Wow, that was incredible.
-Not bad, eh?
Excuse me, I left
some noodles boiling.
I'll a back again
later, son-in-law.
[laughs]
-Aw, you old ghoul!
SOUN: Hm, I've been
thinking, Ranma.
I think you may have bitten
off more than you can chew.
RANMA: I've come too
far to turn back now.
If I can't figure out this
Roasting Chestnuts thing,
I'll never get my hands
on that Phoenix Pill.
-Stop!
You've still got that
full-body cat tongue thing.
You'll hurt yourself.
(WHINING) It's hot.
It's hot!
It's so hot!
[sobs] I can't spend my
whole life as a girl.
But the other thing
is even worse!
Oh, what am I gonna do?
-There, there, son.
No need for that.
-There isn't?
-The fair, son.
The fair's just the thing.
The answer to all your problems.
-Huh?
-Have some squid-on-a-stick,
win a few prizes.
What better way to
forget your sorrows?
It always works for
me when I'm blue.
-You really believe that?
-Ranma, why why
not go with Akane?
You two will have some fun.
And then who knows?
Maybe you'll find some
inspiration or something.
AKANE: I don't want
to babysit him.
RANMA: Hold your horses.
I didn't say I'd go yet.
SOUN: Calm down, son.
You know what they say.
All's fair at the fair.
[chuckles] [clears throat]
[music playing]
[mumbles]
-Oh, come on, loosen up.
RANMA: Haven't got time
to loosen up, Akane.
[laughter]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): You're having
fun despite yourself, Ranma.
-[laughter]
AKANE (VOICEOVER): I'm
really glad we came.
[sobbing]
-Hm?
[weeping]
-Hey, don't cry, little boy.
I'll help you catch one of
those little fishies, OK?
-You-- you will?
-300 yen a pop, babe.
-You nuts?
I'm not paying that.
-Catch 'em alls, and you
get 'em all for free.
AKANE: Oh, really?
300, was it?
BYSTANDER: Make room
for the little lady.
-OK, here I go.
Oh, great.
How did that happen?
Hey, I want a new one.
-Oh, here you go.
-OK, this time for sure.
Give me another.
BOOTH WORKER: You got it.
AKANE: Another.
BOOTH WORKER: There you go.
AKANE: Another!
BOOTH WORKER: Uh-oh.
Do it again.
AKANE: Another!
BOOTH WORKER: Try one more.
BOOTH WORKER: Yep.
AKANE: Another!
BOOTH WORKER: Do it again.
AKANE: Another.
BOOTH WORKER: Have another shot.
BOOTH WORKER: There you go.
AKANE: Another.
BOOTH WORKER: Got it.
BOOTH WORKER: Awww--
-Hey!
Wait a minute.
Are you sure these
aren't defective?
-You think so?
Gee.
[wails]
-Don't cry, kid.
Let me handle this.
You couldn't strain
tea leaves with these.
BOOTH WORKER: Ain't
that the truth?
-Hmph.
-OK.
-Wow, lady, you're great!
-Call me mister.
AKANE: Ranma, catch 'em
all, and they're free.
-That's easy!
Ta-dah!
[plop]
-You did it!
BOOTH WORKER (VOICEOVER):
At this rate,
the broad's gonna put
me out of business!
Gotta think of something.
-Yah!
Not so fast there, sister.
I got another game.
From the depths of
the Amazon comes
the piranha, the world's
most dangerous fish.
Old Bossy the cow wouldn't have
a chance against these babies.
Catch 'em with your bare hands
or give me the goldfish back.
-Hey, that's not fair!
-That's life.
Aah!
[crunch]
-I'll take that challenge.
-Lady, I really want one.
-Hey, I'm a Mister!
-But they'll eat you alive!
-No they won't, not
if I catch them first.
It's no different
than the goldfish.
I'm fast!
That's it.
It's the same idea as the
Roasting Chestnuts thingamajig.
-Ranma?
RANMA: I can get
enough speed to catch
those piranhas before they bite.
OK, just watch!
-She's gone nuts.
-Aaaaaah!
[yelling]
[sounds of traffic]
-OK, you old ghoul,
hand it over!
Gimme that Phoenix Pill!
[customers murmur]
-Ghoul, where are you hiding?
Whoa!
CUSTOMERS: Oooooh!
CUSTOMER: Do you see now
why I love this place?
[applause]
-Ah.
Ow, ah.
COLOGNE: I've been waiting
for you, son-in-law.
-Where are you?
Come out!
Fight me.
[gong]
What the heck is this?
Hey!
These flames aren't real.
A-ha!
I knew it!
It's just another one of
your tricks, isn't it?
-Well, you've managed to
see through yet another
of my illusions, eh, sonny boy?
I'll have you know even the
emperor of the So Dynasty
was afraid of that one.
-Hai-yah!
COLOGNE: [laughs] Come
and get me! [cackles]
-Come back here!
[hooting]
-Oh, now I get it.
You really are a
monkey, ain'tcha?
Take that!
Don't you run away
from me, you old ghoul!
COLOGNE: Here I am.
RANMA: Ah.
-If you want the Phoenix
Pill, son-in-law,
cross this boiling lake.
-You want it that way,
that's fine with me.
OK!
Hyah!
-Ho, ho, ho, it's
hot, sonny boy.
-Scared you, didn't I?
You old ghoul!
Aaaaahhhh!
COLOGNE: Keep it up, son-in-law.
The game is over!
[laughs]
-What kind of an idiot
would build a bath this big?
Whoa!
-Lost at sea.
What a sad way to lose
a future son-in-law.
RANMA: I'm not lost yet!
I'm gonna change
back into a guy.
You watch!
-[gasp]
-Kachu Tenshin Amaguriken!
-Is that it?
Well I am impressed.
Not bad.
[giggles] Look what I got.
-Well, well.
Looks like you managed to get
through my defenses after all.
-And now I can touch
hot water, no problem.
It looks like candy.
-It is candy.
[splash]
-[panting] He this way!
-Ranma!
[sploosh]
-I took out the real
Phoenix Pill, just in case.
Well, you've mastered
the Chestnuts Roasting
on an Open Fire technique.
I'm impressed.
-You catch all
these fishes, Ranma?
You clever.
-It's a good thing that
tank was there, right?
Ranma, you OK?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): That's it.
I'm gonna get you
for this, old ghoul.
[MUSIC - ETSUKO NISHIO, "DON'T
MIND CHINA BOY"]
NARRATOR: A man who came from
China after Shampoo challenging
Ranma?
Where do all these strange
people come from, anyway?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Enter Mousse, the Fist of the White Swan.
See you there.