[theme music]
[church bells ringing]
-Exactly.
It was-- hmm?
-Why, in all the years I've been
with the St. Hebereke School
for Girls Martial
Arts Gymnastics team,
I've never heard
of such a thing.
[laughing]
AKANE: A leotard
is a girl's burden.
-Oh, come on,
Akane, help me out.
-Look, I've got my own homework.
-It'll just be this once.
I'll never ask again.
Pretty please?
-Don't you "pretty please" me.
-Doo-doo doo-doo.
Hmm?
-You stop that this instant!
-I'm sorry, but I
can't take it anymore.
I just can't take it anymore.
-All I gotta say
is, whoever it is
that did that, they must
have been pretty good.
-I think you'll feel better
with some dry clothes.
-I appreciate it, but all
the hot air in the world
won't dry these tears of mine.
At least, not until we can
get the Sphere of Fury back.
-You are going to
explain that, right?
-The St. Hebereke School for
Girls Martial Arts Gymnastic
Club has in its position one
of three sacred treasures.
By stealing our
Sphere of Fury, it's
as though the spirit of our
club itself has been stolen.
-Without it, we
may as well be one
of those sad little
public school clubs.
I swear that we'll never
go sphere-less again!
-Let me know how it
turns out, eh, Scarlet?
-Laugh all you want, but
I still need your help.
Part of being a couple is
being there for each other.
Not just when times are
good, but when they're bad.
And oh, this one's
very, very bad.
-Uh, far as that being there
for each other stuff goes,
we're not a couple, OK?
Besides, you're going
to an all girls school,
which means I don't fit in.
So, whoops.
My bad.
Well, I gotta go
study, so see ya.
Ugh.
-Obviously you
would be in costume.
-Been there, done that.
No thanks, all right?
-Excuse me?
-Oh, nothing.
Forget I said it.
-Look, do you mind?
I've still got homework to do.
-Oh, but of course you
do, dear. [inaudible].
-Ugh.
[cackling]
-I do not have time for this.
-Why don't you help her, Ranma?
I mean, maybe you don't
think you're a couple,
but she sure seems to.
-She can think
whatever she wants.
It takes two to tango, you know.
-Really?
-Akane, please!
You gotta come quick.
There's this guy at school
saying that he-- that he--
-Huh?
-We can do this the easy way.
RANMA: Hold it right there.
-Huh?
-So you're a guy after all, huh?
You must be the one who stole
that sacred whatchamacallit
from St. Hebereke.
-Who is he, anyway?
-Huh?
-Martial Men's Gymnastic
Team Captain at your service.
The name's Dido Kuji.
But that's not
important right now.
Once we acquire the
Club of Inscrutability
from Furinkan High,
we'll possess all
three sacred treasures.
And with that, martial
arts gymnastics
shall once again become
the sole province
of men, which is
how it should be.
-Why don't you just
let the girls--
-Ha.
You don't know, do ya?
True women may think they
own martial arts gymnastics,
but once we show the world
how well-suited men are to it,
they'll know better.
See what I mean?
-Now I've positive that
you're better off leaving it
to the girls.
-Shut up!
You only say that because
you're jealous and don't
know how hard it's been.
I'm telling ya, it's
pure discrimination.
(GIRLS BULLYING): Ha-ha-ha!
Gymnastics is for
girls, [inaudible].
Go find your own sport.
Get outta here!
-But now we've sworn to prove
that Martial Men's Gymnastics
is a manly sport, with manly
grace for manly men-like men.
[sobbing]
-You poor deluded fool.
Real men don't wear tights.
That's just for girls.
The only true sport
for manly men is kendo.
-Ha!
Sure it is, if you
count grown men
hitting each other
with sticks manly.
-You have spirit.
Good.
But can you hold your
own in a fair fight?
-If you call three to one fair.
-So now are you convinced?
Hand it over.
-Akane, do something.
-If they get their
hands on this,
Girl's Martial Arts
Gymnastics will be over.
-Look, maybe you'd
better let me--
-How far do we have to go
before you take us seriously?
-How's this for serious?
-Hmm?
I've been doing
hasty judging you.
Perhaps you're worthy of
joining Martial Men's Gymnastics
after all.
-Lucky me.
-Suit yourself.
Either way, we'll--
-Perhaps this will.
-Good thinking.
This ought to get the job
done in no time at all.
-So this is it?
Your so-called special attack?
-Watch out!
It's called the Sphere of
Fury for a reason, you know.
-Oh yeah?
And what would that be?
Ah!
-It explodes, obviously.
-Ranma!
Can you hear me?
-You see, Akane,
it's got to be you.
And if you get that
pigtailed girl from last time
to be your partner,
the entire future
of Furinkan High gymnastics
is in your hands.
-But why does it have to?
-Because you must, that's why.
I Only you can combat the
menace of the boys in tights.
And if it means seeing
a pigtailed girls
tights, as well--
-It's settled, then.
If you lose, you hand over the
final treasure without a fight.
As a sign of good faith, we
will leave you to your training.
Farewell.
-Look, Ranma.
I don't want you to
take this the wrong way,
but I think it's probably better
if you let me handle this.
After all, it's not
like I need you to-- uh.
Er-- uh.
Oh.
-Tell me again how
you don't need--
-Ranma!
Shame on you!
How dare you abandon Akane
in her greatest hour of need?
-When I want your opinion,
I'll beat it out of you, OK?
-Is that any way to
treat your elders?
Here I'm trying to make
you do the right thing
and maybe catch a little
scenery along the way.
Especially if you were to wear
this cute little number that I
just happen to have right here.
I just--
-OK, that does it!
-Cut it out, you guys.
Happosai!
Ranma!
If you're not gonna help,
I'll just do it myself.
-Whatever you say.
-[grumbles]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Stupid Akane.
It was a bad idea the first
time, and it's even dumber now.
Still, I can't leave her to
fight those guys on her own,
even if I do have to
wear another leot--
KODACHI: Ranma.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Huh?
Kodachi?
-Hey, about that ball
thing, me and Akane--
I mean, her and
the pigtailed girl,
they're gonna get
it back for sure.
So don't worry, OK?
Bye.
Ugh!
Hey, what are you
doing this for?
-This is a fight that
neither you nor I
have any business
interfering with.
Let the pigtailed girl
and Akane handle it.
We've better ways
to spend our time.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
That's not true.
If I don't get out there and
help her, Akane will be--
-Par-- a-- ly-- sis.
-I knew you'd see it my way.
[cackling]
ANNOUNCER: Welcome,
ladies and gentlemen,
to the Martial Arts Gymnastics
Sacred Treasure Challenge.
In this corner, captain
of the Martial Arts Men's
Team, [inaudible].
And in this corner, Furinkan
High School's Akane Tendo!
-The pigtailed girl.
Where oh where can she be?
If she fails to appear, to
Akane Tendo go the spoils.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): It's OK.
I can do this.
Even if Ranma doesn't show.
-(VOICEOVER) This is it.
The moment we've
been waiting for.
Soon the treasure will be ours.
ANNOUNCER: The battle for
the third and final treasure
is about to begin.
RANMA: OK, that's enough.
Get me down!
You've proved your point.
What are you trying
to do, kill me?
Uh-oh.
Ah!
I-- I-- I get it.
It's a joke, right?
Ha-ha-ha!
It's funny.
You're gonna get me
down though, right?
-Just look at how happy Mr.
Scaly Green is, darling.
Why, he could
practically eat you up.
[laughing]
[crowd cheering]
-He-he-he.
Is this the best that
you girls can do?
This is way too easy.
-It seems challenger
Tendo is having
a really tough time out there.
As explained
earlier, the winner's
the one who holds
out the longest.
Leaving the ring calls for
automatic disqualification.
-What kind of a coward picks on
a girl and calls himself a man?
Is that what you call
chivalry where you come from?
-Huh?
Upperclassman Kuno, no!
Akane's our only help.
If you help her
and she forfeits,
girls gymnastics is finished.
-But you can't just
stand here and--
-What she needs
right now is support.
Akane, you can do it!
-Ah!
Ugh.
-But what about getting
your treasure back?
-I'm working on that, darling.
Why should I trouble myself with
the pigtailed girl and Akane
Tendo when the burly
boy will do it for me?
Amusing as this is,
you didn't think
it was for Mr. Scaly
Green's sake, did you?
[cackling]
-You do know you're
crazy, don't you?
[screaming]
-Oh dear, I can't look.
-Sorry, but I ain't
giving up nearly so easy.
See ya!
-But Ranma, darling!
-Time to finish this.
Martial Men's super special
attack-- Ring of no Return!
[screaming]
ANNOUNCER: Is this her one-way
ticket to being disqualified?
-Akane!
Let's take turns.
-Ranma, you're here!
-Did you think I wouldn't come?
[inaudible]
-I knew it!
Here comes the pigtailed girl.
-No fair!
I object.
-Refusing the substitution,
challenger Dido Kuji
calls for a ruling in the ring.
-I'll allow it.
CROWD: He allows it!
ANNOUNCER: And the
crowd goes wild.
It's obvious who
their favorite is.
Meanwhile, the pigtailed
girl takes over.
-Sucks, don't it?
-It's just as well.
Our victory will be
that much the sweeter
for the extra effort.
This attack I'm about to unleash
may not look like very much.
But I assure you, you're
about to be bowled over.
Hi-ya!
Sphere of Fury holds all
the anger and frustration
that come from being in a club
that's such a joke, that's
so uncool that all the
girls think you're a dweeb.
-That is pretty mad, all right.
-Boy, I'll say.
Even the Debate Team's
cooler than them.
-Treasure Two,
Ribbon of Solitude!
Ribbon of Solitude
holds all the sadness
that comes from not having
a date on Friday night.
So powerful a weapon
is it, a single strike
brings forth the bitter tears
of four years of high school.
Or six, depending on if you're
counting junior higher or not.
-What the-- ugh.
Ah!
Do I get the dumb
treasure now or what?
-Oh yeah, that's right.
I forgot.
Furinkan High has still got a
treasure of its own we can use.
-Now this is more like it.
Payback's hell, ain't it?
-Ah!
No, not--
-And what kind of power
do those things have?
-Club of Inscrutability.
Comes from trying to use a
really, really cool weapon,
but failing and having to
cause a distraction instead.
-Sorry I asked.
-Ah!
What the heck are those?
-The distraction.
-I hope you don't
take this wrong way,
but couldn't you have
been more creative?
-I know you're doing
us a favor, Akane,
but you don't have
to be so critical!
-Oh, don't be so sensitive!
-Time to finish it for good!
Think of this as a
token of my affection.
-Ah!
Now what do I do?
Ranma!
Ah!
[screaming]
ANNOUNCER:
[inaudible] challenger
Dido Kuji left the ring.
Either way, it's been an
exciting match, hasn't it?
-I-- I've got you.
ANNOUNCER: Uh-oh.
Uh-oh!
The pigtailed girl
is on the ropes.
-Pigtailed girl, over here!
Jump into my arms.
-Thanks, I'd rather
kiss a-- whoa.
If it's gonna take a
mid-air battle to beat you,
well then so be it!
I've got some chestnuts and
a fire I'd like you to meet.
-Yeah, Upward Spiral
Ribbon Defense!
ANNOUNCER: Hello, what's this?
The pigtailed girl's
attempting a breakthrough
of what seems an
impenetrable defense.
RANMA: Come out, come
out wherever you are.
-What an incredible fight.
It's also an incredible
mess if you ask me, but--
[crowd screaming]
-Come on!
Come on, open up!
Gotcha!
-Don't do it!
You can't.
ANNOUNCER: That's it.
That's all she wrote.
The pigtailed girl wins.
-Woo-hoo, yeah!
-Ranma!
-So, uh, what?
You're expecting anything less?
-Oh, no you don't!
-Kodachi?
-Ranma!
-All that's left for
me to do is step down
and collect the Sphere of Fury.
Then, all three
treasures will be mine,
making me the queen of
martial arts gymnastics!
A-ha-ha!
-At last, the three
treasures are ours!
-Hey now, I object.
ANNOUNCER: Is this it?
Have the Martial Arts Men
Team triumphed after all?
With all three treasures
now in their possession,
it would seem to be so!
-Now, wait a sec.
I remember reading
something about this.
It says it's very
important for neither boys
nor girls to own all three.
-But why not?
What's supposed to happen?
-Hey, look up there.
-Martial Arts Men's
Gymnastics rules!
Wha-- wha-- what
are those things?
Hey!
-The Spirits of Girls
Upset because they've
wasted their entire youth
on nothing but martial arts
gymnastics.
-Oh, well now I know
that you're making it up.
-But I'm not.
-That's it, I'm
quitting the club
and getting myself a boyfriend.
-Hey, me too.
-Somebody help me!
-Don't you see?
It's their way of telling
us that life without romance
is hardly worth living!
And that it's our
duty, Ranma-- yours
and mine-- to be happy for them.
[sighing]
-What?
-I dunno.
[ribbit]
[theme music]
What was thought
to be a relaxing
trip to the hot springs turns
into some kind of crazy scheme
to get men and women together
in the-- oh, wait, wait.
Let me try that again.
Next time, on Ranma--