[theme music]
-A women's love is war,
the Martial Arts Rhythmic
Gymnastics Challenge.
-Morning.
-Good morning Akane.
-Good morning.
-Akane, is it true
you're filling in
for our gymnastics team?
-Uh-huh.
-Good luck.
-Leave it to me.
-Oh, right Akane.
You can't even
use the tools yet.
-Shut up!
Nobody asked you.
-Hey hey hey.
-Akane Tendo prepare to die.
-Kodachi, the Black Rose.
-You again.
You've got a lot of nerve
springing a surprise attack
first thing in the morning.
-Surprise attack?
I merely came to visit
my darling Ranma.
-S0 Why don't you go
visit with him then?
-Oh, Ranma.
Shall we pick up where
we left off last night?
-No!
I mean, I gotta go.
Yeah that's it.
I got to go.
See you later.
-Ranma, darling!
Wait.
-So tell me what grudge
do you bear against me?
-Aw man, Kuno.
I ain't got the time for this.
-Ranma.
Darling.
-Hm.
Hm.
Very well.
You may date with her.
-Hm?
-Ranma, darling, did you hear?
This means we're
officially a couple.
-Hey wait a minute.
Not so fast.
Going out with you is
the last thing I want.
Get it?
Hm?
-You hate me, then.
Is that it?
-No, no.
I just-- I.
-You do hate me I can tell.
Don't lie to save my feelings.
-I told you already,
that's not it.
I've got a fiancee, see?
That's why you gotta--
-Hey.
-Come on Akane, back me up.
-You are pathetic.
-Fiance?
-Akane Tendo, is my
darling Ranma your fiance?
-More or less.
-Well, well, well.
How about it?
Winner of the tournament
gets to take Ranma Saotome.
-What?
-What did you say?
That's crazy.
-But Akane, it's perfect.
You need but lose and
you're rid of him forever.
-No need for that dear.
The beating that
I plan to give you
will be more than sufficient.
Ranma my darling, when the match
is over you'll be all mine.
Until then, ado.
[laughter]
-That woman is totally insane.
Saotome, I'm counting on
you to look after my sister.
-Hm?
Wait a minute here.
Your what?
-My sister.
What are you deaf?
-Sister?
-Bear with her
weakness, which I think
proceeds from wayward sickness
and no grounded mouth.
I love her well.
Yes.
Be wary of her at
the tournament Akane.
Already a vision of you in your
leotard drives me to madness.
Some innocence escape
not the thunderbolt.
That's what the
ancients used to say.
My sister is not the type
to give up on something
once she's set her sights on it.
She may even fight unfairly.
-Kuno's sister, huh?
Why doesn't that surprise me?
-There's no way I'm
going to lose to her.
[dog barking]
-Ranma, you said that
you would help me.
-Oh, I think you can take
her now Akane, right?
-Don't make fun of me.
Ugh!
In case you've forgotten
the match is tomorrow.
If I don't practice
I'm going to lose.
Let's get one thing straight,
I am not doing this for you,
you know.
-I know that, OK?
-I wonder where Ryoga's
been for the last few days.
I was really counting on her.
P-chan.
[whimpering]
-And where have you been P-chan?
It's been days.
Huh?
What's this?
[squealing]
-Maple leaf manju and
red bean triangles.
That would mean
Hiroshima and Kyoto.
Where were you trying
to go there P-chan?
Poor little piggy gets
washed all the time.
-He does not Ranma.
He's not Ryoga, you know.
[squealing]
-Don't you pick on him.
Come on Ranma, I've
got to practice.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Here goes.
-Whoa!
-Oh!
Ah!
-Are you OK?
-Oh, it hurts.
-There you go.
All done.
-Akane, you are such a klutz.
-You'll have to drop
out of tomorrow's match.
-No way.
I'm going.
I've got to.
I can't let her beat me.
-Akane, no.
-Oh.
Ah.
-See?
You'll have to
find a substitute.
-Well it's not that simple.
Where are we going
to find someone
who's good at martial arts,
knows gymnastics, and looks
good in a leotard?
And on such short notice too.
Huh?
Oh.
-Huh?
What are you looking at me for?
Hey cut that out,
that's not funny.
You ain't getting me in
to no stupid leotard.
No way!
-Ryoga.
-Looks like it's going
to be an all-nighter.
Huh, Ranma?
-The thing about Martial
Arts Rhythmic Gymnastics
is that hand to hand
attacks are forbidden.
The match is in
less than 24 hours.
You need to practice as though
your life depends on it.
Are you ready, Ranma?
-I'm ready whenever you are.
-Come on, then.
Let me show you a thing or-- Ah!
-Ah!
That was too easy.
Whoa!
-Use the tools you idiot.
Are you some kind of animal?
-Hm.
At least I'm not a pig.
-What did you say?
-What a waste of time.
OK.
Let's go.
-La oh la.
-Hiya!
-Ah!
-Ya!
-Wow.
Ranma you're really good.
-Hey, I haven't been watching
you a week for nothing,
you know.
-You don't even
need to practice.
-Maybe a little more.
Akane, you go to bed.
-I can't do that.
-Hey, I think you're
worried about me.
Is that it?
-Of course not Ranma.
-Please go to bed.
We're fine.
We'll be OK by ourselves.
-You sure?
-We'll be just fine.
-I'm sure Ranma will
be just fine tomorrow.
-Hey I was there, you know.
I heard you promise that if
you lost the match tomorrow,
you'd go out with Kodachi.
Which means that it's over
between you and Akane.
Isn't that right?
I came here to make
sure that you lose.
-Huh.
I knew your sudden change of
heart was too good to be true.
You're wrong about
one thing, though.
I've got absolutely no intention
of going out with Kodachi.
-You don't have any
choice in the matter.
I'm going to make sure you lose.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'll kill you if I have to.
-Go ahead and try it you jerk!
[crashing]
[dog barking]
Ranma: Why you--
-Hm?
-Take that!
Ranma: Come here I said!
-They didn't.
[fighting]
-There!
Take that.
-Ah!
-Do you give up?
Or don't you?
-Ah!
I can't believe you two
were fighting all night?
-Huh?
It's morning already?
-But the match is today.
-It's OK.
It's OK.
This cake's awfully
tough, Kasumi.
-That's a dish rag.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): That's it!
We're doomed.
-Don't forget, girls.
The martial arts rhythmic
gymnastics tournament against
the visiting team from Furinkan
high will take place this
afternoon at 1:00PM in
the second gymnasium.
-A last minute substitute?
-I hurt myself
practicing last night,
so she's going to
fill in for me.
-I know you.
Yes, you're that pigtailed
girl from the other day.
I do hope you'll be fighting
fair today, won't you?
-Wait just a minute.
What do you call this?
-Good heavens.
How ever did those tacks
get between my fingers?
-Is this really St.
Hebereke's School for Girls?
-Uh-huh.
-You're absolutely
sure about that?
-Yes.
-I made it here safely.
Here I am with the world's
worst sense of direction
and yet I made it straight
here without getting lost once.
It's the power of love, Akane.
Oh, Ranma!
One way or the other, I'm going
to make sure that you lose.
-I don't believe that girl!
You can't take your eye
off of her for a minute!
Huh?
-Hello.
-Mr. Saotome.
-Hey Pop.
You made it.
-Look at this.
Black roses.
Huh?
[coughing]
-Sleeping gas.
-Sure woke me up.
-Well that's strange, I should
have reached the gym by now.
-Be careful, somebody
could be down there.
-It's just a pit,
there's no harm done.
[squealing]
-Oh, a little piggy.
-Look, it's so cute.
-Hello Kodachi.
-Oh I know just
what to do with you.
-Good afternoon everyone and
welcome to the St. Hebereke
versus Furinkan High Martial Art
Rhythmic Gymnastics Tournament!
[cheering]
-Ladies and Gentlemen, if we
may have you attention, please.
The rhythmic gymnastics match
will begin at any moment.
-And the contestants are ready.
-Wha-?
What the what?
-The Furinkan High challenger
is entering the ring.
-Hiya!
-It's the pigtailed girl.
-She's certainly
showing a lot of spirit.
Will she be this confident
once the fight begins?
Only time will tell.
And here comes the champion.
-Watch out!
-Ah!
-Oh my goodness.
However did that
bomb get in there?
I do hope you're all right.
-Why you little!
-As usual Kodachi makes
a dramatic entrance.
And isn't her
outfit just lovely?
KODACHI (VOICEOVER): There's
no real contest here.
Once I've defeated the little
hussy, Ranma will be all mine.
I shall wed you in
this very dress.
Oh yes, my love, yes
I dare it all for you.
-If Kodachi wins then Ranma
Saotome becomes my stepbrother.
Which means that Akane
and the pigtailed girl
shall both be mine by default.
Smite her, my sister.
For the first time in
my life I cheer for you!
-Why brother dear.
-Did you hear?
Her brother.
-I'm in love.
-Hear that?
-In this m ignorance is bliss.
-And here they are,
ladies and gentlemen.
In the red corner from St.
Hebereke's School for Girls,
Kodachi Kuno.
[cheering]
In this corner uh, hm.
Excuse me, miss.
What did you say your name was?
-Ranma Saotome.
-Hey.
Should you use your
real name in this?
From Furinkan High
School, Ranma Saotome.
-Ranma Saotome?
-Ra-- Ranma Saotome?
-Did she just say Ranma?
-Ranma?
-Yeah!
Yeah!
-That brazen hussy
is Ranma Saotome?
The same name as my beloved?
How is that the same
name, given to a girl,
can be so utterly disgusting?
-Ah!
At last!
The pigtailed one has a name.
I must prepare the ink
quickly, lest I forget.
[gasp]
-It's funny but she does
kind of look like him.
-Who knows?
Maybe they're twins.
-Oh, good one!
Haha.
-You see Akane?
What did I tell you?
-OK girls, to the
center of the ring.
All right, shake hands.
-Ranma, look out!
-Huh?
-Oh.
Hey, what's this?
-How very careless of you.
-Ah.
[squealing]
Ryoga?
Oh, you just live to
mess me up, don't ya?
-Hehehe.
[growls]
[music playing]
-What do you mean so as long
as you use tools anything goes?
And Kodachi keeps using
all those dirty trucks.
And here's Ranma using
P-chan like a tool, too.
Next time on Ranma 1/2, the
tear in a girl delinquent's eye,
the end of the Martial Arts
Rhythmic Gymnastics Challenge.
See ya there!