[music playing]
NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hey, let go!
-Hai-yah!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
-The two have been engaged to
marry by their loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma is
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
GIRL: Cool Runnings!
The Race of the Snowmen.
-Yahoo!
-Yeah!
-[laughs] Huh?
Ranma!
-Hmph.
-Hey, why aren't you skiing?
-Come on, Ranma.
Don't pout.
You'll miss all the fun.
-Fun?
Where?
I must have missed it.
-Oh, don't be such a baby.
Akane isn't embarrassed to be
seen skiing with you as a girl,
so it shouldn't
bother you either.
-It doesn't bother me.
-You're not helping.
-Hey, well maybe I just don't
feel like skiing right now, OK?
[screaming]
SOUN: Come on, Miss.
Let me show you how to snowplow.
Look, Akane!
Look, Daddy's skiing!
-I'm so embarrassed.
-Pretend we don't know him.
Come on, Akane,
let's hit the slopes.
Ranma, are you coming?
-Hm.
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Yeah,
right, like I got time
for skiing right now.
I gotta get my hands on that
old ghoul's Phoenix Pill.
But how?
-Hand that over!
-Is that the best you can do?
I still don't get it,
do you, sonny boy?
You haven't got a
chance of defeating me.
You're 100 years too early.
-Aaaaahhhh!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
It's hopeless.
COLOGNE: Here you go.
You ordered ramen, right?
Leave the bowl under the tree.
I'll come back for it later.
MAN: Thank you.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
How'd she get here?
Is she following me?
[screaming]
SOUN: Ah, this is the life.
GENMA: Yahooooo!
-[humming] Ah-- ah-- ah!
[both grunting and yelling]
[splash]
[shivering]
-You come back here!
-Huh?
Fancy meeting you here.
-Big mistake, ghoul!
Today I'm gonna get
that pill for sure.
-What exactly do you mean?
-Hey, don't play dumb.
-What?
RANMA: [screams]
Oh, now you've done it.
Uh?
Cat Cafe, Snow-Mountain Branch?
What the--
COLOGNE: It's a seasonal thing.
You wouldn't believe how well
the stuff sells out here.
Would you like your
job back, son-in-law?
-No way!
Come on, gimme the pill!
-What?
That silly thing?
Wouldn't you rather compete
in that contest, son-in-law?
-Hm?
[crowd murmurs]
-Martial Arts Carry
the Snowman Race?
-Aaah!
Coming through!
[splash]
-Wait for me, Tendo!
EMCEE (ON PA): And
here it is, ski bums!
The event you've all
been waiting for,
sponsored by our own local
branch of Furinkan's famous Cat
Cafe comes Snow-Mountain's
Snowman Snow Off.
Break your opponent's snowman
with your wooden sword,
and they're right out of luck.
But watch out,
because they'll be
trying to do the
same thing to you.
Now remember,
protect that snowman,
because the one to reach the
finish with their snowman
intact wins!
As for the prize,
how about a ski tour
for two with this
beautiful girl?
-As an added bonus.
-There it is!
The pill!
-If you win the race, it's
all yours, future son-in-law.
-You got it, ghoul.
But listen up.
There's only one thing I
want from you, and that's a--
Ranma!
Hai-yah!
Only one thing you
want is Shampoo?
Yes!
Oh so happy!
RANMA: No, no, no!
That's not what I meant!
-Akane, you're not going to
let him get away with this,
are you?
-Get away with what?
EMCEE (ON PA): On your marks!
Get set!
Go!
[shouting and laughter]
RANMA: I can do it.
I can do it!
I-- I-- whoa!
KASUMI: Ranma, what's wrong?
NABIKI: Don't tell me
you've never skied before.
-Snowshoes?
-The rules don't say
anything about having
to wear skis, now do they?
And with those on
you, you should
be able to keep up just fine.
Aren't you always saying
if it's martial arts in it,
you can do anything?
-Thanks, Akane.
-So I hope you enjoy your
little rendezvous with Shampoo.
-Aw, jeez, I already told
you, it's not like that.
[soun and genma shouting]
RANMA: [inaudible].
All right!
[shouting]
SOUN: Out of the way.
Out of the way!
-OK, coming through.
[inaudible].
Hyah!
Get a move on, little dogie!
Out of the way!
The pill is mine!
Hyah!
Come on!
Aaah!
I
COLOGNE: Whoops.
I didn't mean to
hit you, Mr. Bear.
-Out of the way, ghoul!
-Ah, this brings
back the memories.
I remember playing in the snow
like this as a young girl.
-Oh!
You mean in the Ice Age?
SOUN: Ranma!
GENMA: Are you nuts, boy?
How can you throw aside poor
Akane for that Shampoo girl?
-Son, do you really
want Shampoo that much?
-Hey, that's not it!
-Come on, Dad, that's enough.
I couldn't care less who
that idiot chases after.
-Watch how much
she doesn't care.
-Aaaaahhhh!
NABIKI: I rest my case.
-OK, now you snow
bunnies, check it out!
They're dropping off like flies!
Who's left?
A pigtailed girl
and two old men!
A mysterious mummy!
-Who are you calling a mummy?
EMCEE (ON PA): Plus one more!
The pretty girl with short hair.
And she's taking the lead!
-No one get by Ranma!
EMCEE (ON PA): What's this?
The prize has joined the fight.
-[laughs] Oh, yeah?
Here I come!
-Ranma!
-It ain't ladylike
to play with swords!
-Ranma!
-Huh?
Aaaah!
-It's time for you to
decide-- Akane or Shampoo.
It's time for you to kiss
the one you want the most.
-Huh?
-Well?
Well?
-Ranma, be a man.
Pick a girl and kiss her now!
EMCEE (ON PA): What an
unexpected turn of events!
Which of these two girls
will receive the kiss?
--[laughs nervously]
Uh-- [stammering]
SHAMPOO: Vo: You no kiss
Shampoo, you kiss pill goodbye.
You want stay girl
whole life, Ranma?
[gasp]
-Huh?
You can't!
-Ranma!
-Uh, wait, Ranma.
People are watching, you know!
And we're both girls!
You can't!
-You got a dirty mind!
-Hm, just kidding.
-Dirty mind?
-Just kidding?
-Aahh!
[yelling] Hey!
It's the finish line!
I can still win!
-Oh, no you don't!
Son-in-law, you're
not getting past me
until you promise
to marry my Shampoo.
-Ha!
OK, then.
Why don't we settle
this once and for all?
-[chuckles] You're talking to an
Amazon backed up by 3,000 years
of history.
Are you sure you're up to it?
-We'll know soon enough.
-Son-in-law, you're
not getting past me
until you promise
to marry my Shampoo.
-Ha!
OK, then.
Why don't we settle
this once and for all?
-[chuckles] You're talking to an
Amazon backed up by 3,000 years
of history.
Are you sure you're up to it?
We'll know soon enough.
[shouting]
[all gasp]
-You can't win without
a snowman, son-in-law.
Why not give up?
-I'll show you!
-Oh, temper, temper!
-Give up?
No way!
This is where I pay you back
for everything you did to me,
you old ghoul!
[all gasp]
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Huh.
Finally got the old ghoul
to give up the stick.
My win for sure.
I've won for sure!
RANMA: Looks like your old age
finally caught up with you.
SOUN: Something's
not right here.
The boy's not that good.
-Give it up, ghoul.
It ain't good for old
folks to strain themselves.
COLOGNE: You haven't
beat me yet, sonny boy.
This old girl's got
some life in her yet.
-Is that so?
All right, I'll make you a deal.
Snowman or no snowman, if I
win, you give me the pill.
OK?
-I-- I've got no choice.
But if I should win, you
agree to marry my Shampoo?
That a deal?
-Sure.
I'd marry you to be a guy again.
-I'm glad you agree.
-Uh-oh.
COLOGNE: 'Cause
I'll hold you to it.
-Aaaaahhh!
-I knew it was too
good to be true.
-That fool!
I can't believe he let
himself be tricked like that!
-Did you give up
yet, son-in-law?
-No way, ghoul!
[all gasp]
[screams]
-You broke my snowshoes!
-[laughs]
-That's a dirty trick!
-Looks like it's your turn
to give it up, son-in-law.
-Not a chance!
-Oh, come on, son-in-law.
The Amazons of China have
been at this sort of thing
for 4,000 years.
[grunting with effort]
-Like this, for example.
[shouting]
ONLOOKER: What's she doing now?
[yelling]
ONLOOKER: That poor girl!
ONLOOKER: Hey, look, her
hair's standing straight up!
ONLOOKER: This is gonna be good!
[ranma yelling]
-Ranma!
--[laughs] Now what do
you say, son-in-law?
Now do you give up?
[yelling]
-No way!
-What are you doing?
How dare you grab me like that?
Let go of me this instant!
Let go!
Let go, I said!
[yelling]
-Now I feel sick. let
go of me, you go of me,
you stubborn fool.
[ranma yelling]
-Hey, you ghoul,
come on, fight fair!
-Putting your hands on
me like that-- I've never
been so insulted
in my whole life.
Why, in 5,000 years of
Chinese Amazon history,
I've never been--
-Shaddup, wouldja?
Who cares about
your stupid history?
3,000, 4,000-- it all
means the same thing to me.
Nothing, that's what it means!
[shouting indistinctly]
-Oh, no you don't!
I'm the one who taught you that
trick, or have you forgotten?
Hyah!
The match is mine.
-No!
Not yet, it ain't!
-Uh?
What'd you do that for?
-Looks like your lack of age has
caught up with you, son-in-law.
RANMA: Shut up, you!
--[laughs] You're persistent,
I'll give you that.
But you're about 300
years too early for me.
AKANE: Ranma!
-Haaaaaa-- hah!
-Aaaaaaahhhhh!
Now where'd she go?
[rumbling]
COLOGNE: Fist of the Ice Bear!
-Huh?
Aaaaaghhh!
-Ranma!
Ahh!
You OK?
You give up now, OK?
You now can win
Great-Grandmother
when she serious.
GENMA: She's right, boy.
You've done all you could do.
Give up for now, and we'll
train together for your rematch.
Knowing when you're beat is part
of martial arts too, you know.
RANMA: Shut up, you!
This fight's far from over.
COLOGNE: [laughs]
Silly son-in-law,
you can't keep this
up much longer.
-Just watch me.
-Ranma, give up now.
Shampoo no want you hurt.
-Hey, that's it!
Shampoo, with your
help, I'll win!
You'll help me,
won't you, Shampoo?
Right?
-Ranma!
You need Shampoo?
-I'm nothing without you.
-Oh, I so happy!
-Ranma!
Well, it looks like
I've underestimated you.
Huh?
Hey!
[growls]
-Shampoo do anything
to help you.
-You hear that?
COLOGNE: [laughs]
Even with her help,
it won't make any
difference, you know.
-Come on, let's do it!
[splash]
-Hm?
AKANE: Vo: Don't tell
me he's planning to--
[screams] Get it off of me!
Help!
Somebody help!
Get it off of me!
-What is it, son-in-law?
Wha-- what's wrong?
GENMA: Vo: So that's it.
The boy's planning
to use the Cat Fist.
When he's in that state,
he's practically invincible.
-Get it offa me or I'm gonna
go crazy, I swear I will!
-Akane!
RANMA: Aaaahh!
[cat meowing]
-There, Ranma, just
like you wanted!
A nice kitty-cat in the face!
[cat meowing]
-This is for Akane.
-Feel the terror, boy.
This is also for Akane.
Go, Ranma!
Show the old bag the terrifying
power of the Cat Fist.
[growling]
-Beat me if you can!
[howling]
-Aaaaaahh!
[screeching meows]
-Impossible!
[thud]
[screeching meows]
-Haaaaaaaa-- ah!
[screams]
[screeching meows]
-Ranma, that's enough!
-Mrowr?
-Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
-Mrowr!
AKANE: Here, kitty, kitty.
Good kitty.
-He won!
The boy finally defeated her.
[meow]
-You still want to fight?
[growls and hisses]
-Don't worry.
Hm, it's been a good
150 years since I
had a workout like that.
Well now, I wasn't
expecting the Cat Fist.
It's my own fault for
underestimating him.
I guess the round goes
to him, and so does this.
Here.
-The Phoenix Pill!
COLOGNE: Son-in-law, I'll be
back again before you know it.
Farewell!
[laughs]
[purring]
[giggles softly]
[laughs delightedly] Waaaahh!
I'm back.
I'm a guy again.
Just check me out!
I ain't never turning
into a girl again.
Never again!
It's great to be a guy!
Ha-haaaa!
[wind whistling]
-Huh?
I, uh-- [laughs nervously]
[women screaming]
BATHER: Get him out of here.
What's he doing?
BATHER: Oh my god,
there's a guy in here!
-Heh.
Who cares?
It's still great to be a guy.
[MUSIC - ETSUKO NISHIO, "DON'T
MIND CHINA BOY"]
NARRATOR: Dad always
says the road to getting
the secrets of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts
is terribly difficult, so
Ranma goes to the mountains
to begin some
terror-filled training.
Next time on "Ranma 1/2,"
Ranma trains on Mount Terror.
See you there.