[music playing]
[theme music]
[non-english speech]
NARRATOR 1: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
And here's Akane of the
Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR 1: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR 1: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR 1: When Ranma is
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
NARRATOR 2: Ranma Trains on Mt. Terror.
RYOGA: My dear
friend Ranma, I hope
this letter finds you well.
That's no good.
Hello Ranma, long time no see!
That's no good either.
Hey Ranma, how are ya?
[laughter]
-Now I've got it!
Ranma, I am training very
hard in the lowly mountains
of Japan.
This Friday--
-I will come to the Tendo Dojo.
Be ready, or else.
Ryoga.
-Hey!
That's a formal
letter of challenge.
-That's one way of putting it.
-Let me see that!
-That boy has a very
weird sense of humor.
-Yeah.
A sense of direction ain't
the only thing he's missing.
-Ranma, Friday is today!
-So what?
What does that
have to do with it?
I'd give him another
week at least.
He could be practically
anywhere right now.
-One, two, one, two, one, two!
-Furinkan High
School, which means,
which means that somehow,
against all odds,
I finally made it!
This is the town
where Akane lives.
At last!
Just you wait, Ranma
Saotome, today, for sure,
without a doubt, is
the day we settle
the score once and for all!
-Hey, Mister!
-Huh?
-Hahah.
[squeal]
-Welcome to-- oh!
Hello great-grandmother.
-Shampoo, look at this tasty pig
I found on my way home today.
-It look juicy!
-Hush, now.
It'll be over
before you know it.
-Now where Shampoo see
that little pig before?
[squeal]
-Hmm.
Oh, Shampoo remember.
Wait!
No can eat that one!
No eat!
No!
-Hm?
[screaming]
-Ah!
-Pig turn into man!
-How dare you try and
cook me, you-- ahh!
-Who are you?
-I'm just a guy who made
the mistake of following
Ranma Saotome to
Jusenkyo, China.
Ahh!
-Wait up, you old fool!
Hi-yah!
Come back here!
-Ahh!
[gurgling]
[squealing]
-China, eh?
Hm, you don't say.
RYOGA: If he'd only met me
when he was supposed to,
this never would've happened!
-So, you're a friend
of my son-in-law?
-You've gotta be kidding!
Your son-in-law is the cause
for all my suffering, you know?
Son-in-law?
-Well, well, well.
-How did she do that?
-What do you say, kid?
Want to join forces with me?
-In what way?
-I'm offering to train
you, you blockhead.
-Hah, no, I don't think so.
-Hey!
Where you going?
-Hey, don't take
it the wrong way,
but I don't think there's very
much I could learn from you.
See you, granny.
-Oh, is that how it is?
Well, I'll be here if you
should change your mind.
-Hehe, not likely granny,
but thanks anyway.
-Heh, one more time?
-You still here?
-If you've changed your mind,
why don't you just say so?
-I haven't!
I just can't find
the door, that's all.
-For last time, stupid
boy, go that way!
-Oh, yeah.
-Ah!
Even cabbage more
sense than you!
(FEMALE VOICE): Would
you run to the market
and pick up some of those
noodles Father likes?
AKANE: Right now?
I was just getting
ready to go practice!
SOUN: Akane, do what
your sister tells you.
It's not every day
we have sukiyaki,
and it's just not sukiyaki
without the noodles.
SAOTOME: Yes, sukiyaki
without noodles
is a day without sunshine.
[inaudible] is Akane.
SOUN: That's it exactly.
Saotome, well said!
AKANE: OK, don't overdo it.
You've made your point.
I'll go already.
Honestly!
-Whoa!
Oh, that was close!
Bring it to Kasumi, he says.
What's with Dr. Tofu?
What's she supposed
to do with it anyway?
-Ranma, today for sure I'm
going to knock you to the ground
and make you beg for mercy!
-Huh?
Ranma!
-Hey!
-Ugh!
-Whoa!
-Hey, Ryoga.
You're a week late, man.
It's OK though.
I guess it's pretty
early for you.
-It means you had another
week to live, Ranma.
I'd be thanking my lucky
stars if I were you!
Ugh!
-Hey!
Wait a minute!
-Ugh!
Ugg.
-Hey, I've got a delivery here.
-Oh, excuse me.
Maybe you'll be able
to concentrate better
once I get rid of
it for you then.
Yah!
Ugh.
This can't be happening to me!
-Ranma!
-Hm?
-Ahh!
-Don't you guys
ever stop fighting?
-Hey!
Don't look at me!
He started it.
-What am I going to do?
Ranma beating me is bad
enough, but in front of Akane?
-Gee, Akane, I bet
you miss P-chan.
Want to see him?
-Huh?
Yes, of course.
Do you know where he is?
-He's closer than you think.
-Ahh!
-Hah, scared you, didn't I?
-Turn to the right.
-Huh?
-Turn right!
You shouldn't bully the weak!
Honestly, he's such
a jerk sometimes.
I can't believe he was
picking on you like that!
Ryoga, I think it
would be better
to stay out of Ranma's way.
He's been fighting with
Shampoo's great-grandmother
while you were gone.
He's gotten a lot better.
Next time he challenges
you, just ignore him, OK?
You promise?
Ryoga?
-Mhm?
-OK?
-Oh no, Akane, please
don't look at me like that!
Please don't pity me!
-Ryoga, wait!
-I can't figure it out.
He said he was hard
at work, training
in the mountains of Japan.
There's no way I should've
beat him that easy.
Not unless, hey, maybe
it's not Ryoga at all.
Maybe it's me.
-Foolish boy!
Your arrogance is beyond belief!
-Keep your voice down, will you?
I know it sounds stupid, but
that's why I asked you, Pop.
-If you're set on proving
yourself, why not try me?
RANMA: Maybe I will!
GENMA: Anytime, boy.
You've got to know
your limitations, boy.
Nobody likes a martial
artist with a bad attitude.
You need some
spiritual training.
But first our stomachs are
in need of some sukiyaki.
-Sorry, too late!
-What?
You mean, you didn't save some?
-Girls, wasn't that good?
-Yeah, it was great.
-Stop that, you
saved some, right?
-Hey, what about me, huh?
-Look, Saotome, we left
you plenty of noodles.
Weren't you just saying
they're your favorite?
Hm?
-Ugh.
[screaming]
-Curse you, Ranma!
-Looks like you've had a
rough time of it, sonny boy.
Still think this old gal's
got nothing to teach you?
-I was just hoping you'd show
up again sooner or later.
-Haha.
-Hi-yah!
How'd I end up here doing
something like this anyway?
It's your duty to
accompany Ranma and do
all of the cooking.
-It's also good bridal
training, Akane.
-After all, you're
going to be his wife.
-Duty, he says.
Bridal training, she says.
Honestly!
Hi-yah!
-Why didn't you say
something, old man?
You know I can't concentrate
with some girl around.
Why you stupid-- huh?
-Yeah, right.
Look who's talking.
Hm.
I'd like to know
who's training who.
Uh!
-Son-in-law, are you
in training as well?
-How long have you
been here, you ghoul!
-Calm down, sonny boy.
I'm not here to interfere
with you, you know.
-Huh?
-Believe it or not, I'm
hoping you'll succeed.
Because you're going to need
all the help you can get.
-Now what?
-I'll be looking forward
to it, son-in-law.
-Hey!
-See you soon!
-So you're sure that I'll
be able to defeat Ranma
with this special
technique of yours?
-Of course.
Although whether you'll be
able to master it or not
is another story.
-I'll master it!
If it means I'll be
able to defeat Ranma,
I'll master any technique,
no matter how difficult!
-Then watch this, sonny boy!
-She's catching fish without
getting her hands wet.
Incredible!
-What you just saw was
my son-in-law's chestnuts
roasting on an open
fire technique.
If you want a chance
at Ranma, you'll
have to master this
technique as well.
-What's the big deal?
If Ranma can do it,
then I can do it.
Watch.
[squeal]
-Now, try again.
RANMA: Hey, she's making curry?
Great!
GENMA: Now, aren't you
glad we brought her, boy?
RANMA: Hurry it up, Akane!
-Slow down!
What's the hurry?
You don't want to eat it all
before the full flavor emerges,
now do you?
-No, he wouldn't want that.
And besides, we
trained so hard today,
I feel faint with hunger.
-Me too, I'm starving!
-OK, OK!
Well, I hope that it tastes OK.
Here you go!
-Ah, Mother nature's food
made with mother nature's
ingredients served in mother
nature's own backyard.
And what a rare
and unusual aroma
tickles at my nose,
my dear Akane.
-Mr. Saotome, you smelled
the white wine I used.
-White wine?
Are you supposed to
put that junk in here?
-It sure is a good thing we
brought Akane along, isn't it,
boy?
-Maybe you should taste
it first, Mr. Saotome.
-Ah, don't worry
about it, Akane.
We're so hungry, we could
eat pig slop if we had to.
Haha.
-Excuse me?
-Oh, nothing.
-Well, then, dig in!
-Well, here goes nothing.
-You like it?
-All right, boy.
Enough time wasted, we
must continue to train!
-Right!
-Uh, thanks for the meal!
-Uh, thanks!
-Now, what'd I do?
Now that's strange.
I wonder if I put
too much wine in it?
Vinegar?
-I told you, we shouldn't
have brought her!
-Who could've known she'd
be that poor a cook.
It's inhumane, I tell you!
-You'll have to fend
for yourself in the food
department.
Think of it as
building discipline.
-She forgot I'm used to
training in the mountains.
Catching my own dinner's
a piece of cake!
-So I confused vinegar
and white wine.
They didn't have to make
such a big deal about it.
I did them a favor
by cooking, didn't I?
Ranma, you're such a jerk!
Ryoga!
-Oh man, I'm starving to death!
You're lucky, Pop!
I wish I could turn into a panda
and stuff myself with bamboo.
Ah, shut up, I can't eat that!
Yeah, yeah, right.
I'm probably the only
person in the world
who could eat that
disgusting junk.
How pathetic.
-I see, so you're out
here training also.
Is that it, Ryoga?
-Well, I have to.
You saw what happened
to me back there.
-Now, this might be
a little bit better.
I've added some things
which might help its flavor.
Here you go.
I hope it's good!
-Bet it is.
Oh, it's good to be alive.
Imagine me, eating a
home-cooked meal by Akane!
I'm the happiest
guy in the world!
OK, here I go!
-It's still bad, right?
-It's delicious!
I, I, I've never had
such delicious food
in my entire life!
-Great!
Then, the mayonnaise, sugar,
and horseradish did help then!
Huh?
-Uh, Ryoga, is your sense
of taste messed up too?
-Hey!
I didn't ask for
your opinion, Ranma!
-Ugh, Akane, have you
tried tasting it yet?
-No, not yet.
-Then you try some of it.
Go on!
-Are you trying to say it's bad?
-Uh-huh.
-I won't allow you to
talk to her that way.
-What are you going
to do about it?
-I'm going to shut that
rude mouth of your for good!
-It's OK, Ryoga.
I'm glad that you like my
cooking and everything,
but you don't have to defend me.
-I'd listen to her
if I were you, Ryoga.
Besides, you know I
hate bullying the weak.
-So I'm weak, huh?
-Hey, what the?
Old ghoul?
-Ryoga!
Ryoga, you OK?
-Akane?
Ugh.
-Haha.
One week from now, we'll
continue the match.
You got that?
You have just one week
to prepare, son-in-law.
Haha.
He'll be much stronger
when you next see him.
Hahah.
-Please, wait!
-Uh, Akane?
-Why should I stay?
You can't eat my
cooking, remember?
-Oh, that's right.
Nobody human could
eat that stuff.
Ryoga, maybe, but he don't
count as human, now does he?
-You won't miss me
when I'm gone then!
-Geez.
Have it your way.
-Listen, old woman.
I don't need your fancy tricks.
I could beat Ranma
just with my fists!
-I admire your attitude,
but it's not enough.
I want you to do
something for me.
Can you shatter this boulder?
-Hah.
That's easy.
-Aren't you listening to me?
I said shatter, not
split, you fool!
Watch!
-Incredible!
-Behold a technique
preserved through 3,000 years
of Chinese Amazon history,
the Breaking Point,
or Bakusai Tenketsu.
-Bakusai Tenketsu?
-Can I defeat Ranma
using the Breaking Point?
-Well, now, shall
I teach it to you?
-Oh, would you?
Oh, please.
If it helps me defeat
Ranma, I'll do anything!
Please, teach it to me.
-What a powerful technique!
If Ryoga does
manage to master it,
what does that mean for Ranma?
[theme music]
[non-english speech]
AKANE: Ranma and Ryoga
in hand-to-hand combat?
That's fine, but why do
I have to be the prize?
Just leave me out
of it, will you?
Next time, on Ranma 1/2,
the Breaking Point, Ryoga's great revenge.
See you there!