[theme music]
NARRATOR: A Sudden
Storm of Love.
-Never, Ranma Saotome, [skids]
-Huh?
KENO: [yells] I
shall never accept
this travesty of justice.
-Wha-- what travesty?
-Kuno, what is it?
-It's about your
engagement to Akane Tendo.
[crowd excitement]
Never, Ranma Saotome.
I Tatewaki Kuno
shall never allow it.
[yells]
-This is definitely no
place to fight, Kuno.
Follow me.
-That I shall.
[crowd excitment]
-Hey, run quietly in the halls.
[crowd ascents]
-Hey here's a nice shortcut.
-I follow.
So high!
[yells]
-Hey, this is the third floor.
-Lucky for them there's
a pool down there.
-[yells]
-Ah!
Oh no!
[splash]
-Oh my--
-Look, Kuno's floating
to the surface.
SECOND STUDENT: Yeah,
but where's Saotome?
--[gurgling] Got to
get out of here.
I got to get out of here.
-[gurgling] Saotome!
-[yells]
-[gurgling] I fight on!
-[gurgling] Why you pervert!
Hiya!
-Ow.
-Is it just me, or did it
look like Saotome just shrunk?
-Nah, it's just you.
-That was weird.
-Somebody go check on Kuno.
-Gee, I hope he's not drowned.
KUNO (VOICEOVER): I'm
almost positive that person
was a female.
Which could only mean one thing.
Saotome you wretch!
Do you think you can leave
someone else in your place
and escape that easily?
-Geez, Kuno didn't have
to squeeze me so hard.
That ticks me right off.
Well, I guess the jig is up.
He must know my secret by now.
AKANE: Hey, dummy.
Just how stupid
can you be, Ranma?
You talking to me, Akane?
-Throwing yourself into
the pool like that?
-What do you know?
Blah.
-Hm. guess you don't want this.
-[gasp] Ah, no wait, don't!
-Uh-oh.
Kuno's coming.
Catch.
-[grunts]
-All right, Kuno.
I challenge you.
-Akane Tendo.
Lest too light winning make
the prize light, I accept.
If you defeat me, I shall
allow you to date me.
But beware, I am
prepared to lose.
-You say it like I want
to date you or something.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Ranma,
change back into a boy
while I buy you some time.
[fight sounds]
-You're mine.
[screams]
-Whoa.
OK, first thing to do is
to get my balance back.
Then I can use this to
turn back into a guy.
-Ugh.
-We meet again.
-[nervous laughter]
-What's wrong with you?
You're still a girl.
-It's not like it's my fault.
-Tell me, have you seen a
strange man with a pig tail?
Cowards die so many times
before their deaths,
no doubt he feared my prowess.
That man no man!
He is not a man!
Ah!
That hurt, you know.
-I'm not going to hang
around and listen to this.
I'm ready to take
you on anytime, Kuno.
-Very well, my fiery one.
Beauty itself doth persuade.
If you can defeat me, I
shall allow you to date me.
-Ah!
-Ah.
Uh--
-Who asked for a date, anyway?
-Guess what, Kuno?
Ranma Saotome's
even better than me.
Come on, Akane, let's go home.
AKANE: But it's
not even lunch yet.
-She is formidable.
But who is she?
Uh.
-[humming]
-Gave your fiance the
grand tour today, huh?
-Stop calling him my fiance,
I never asked for this.
-From what I understand, Akane
really looked out for you
in school today, boy.
-It's not like I asked her to.
-[growl] Foolish boy!
Have you learned nothing?
[grunting]
-Here we go again.
-You wound me Ranma.
I taught you better manners
than to ignore a debt of honor.
Ah, 16 years I tried to give
you the benefit of my wisdom.
Ranma-- I-- your
father has-- Oh.
What good are these hands
of mine if they cannot teach
my only heir how to walk the
path of martial righteousness.
Oh, my son!
My only son!
Son, your father has failed!
-Hiya.
-[growls]
-Sorry.
-[laughs]
-I'm so sorry.
We're getting that fixed soon.
-Saotome, let's go
to the public baths.
[dog barking]
-Hm.
Guess you don't want this.
[chuckles] Catch!
-Lest too light winning make
the prize light, I accept.
-All right, Kuno,
I challenge you.
-Guess I should go thank her.
NABIKI: [grunting] What's
the big deal, Akane?
I think it's cool he
can change into a girl.
[pencil snaps] Huh?
-Cool?
That's easy for
you to say, Nabiki.
My life may as well
be over if I have
to marry a stupid jerk like him.
Why don't you marry
him if he's so cool?
Think about it, I'm engaged
to my worst nightmare.
-And the old man calls me rude.
-Oh.
-Ah!
-Ah, ah!
-Huh?
-Mister Saotome, did you
spend the night like that?
-Not worth the effort of
changing back, he said.
-Uh, you want me to help
you with those guys, Akane?
-Excuse me, we don't know
each other, remember?
-But you know that they're
all waiting for you.
-I'm fine on my own, thanks.
-Hm.
[school bells]
-Here.
-It's your serve, Akane,
and the game is love.
[fight sounds]
-It's the 100 meter
dash of the heart.
-Push me out of the
ring with your love.
Oh.
She is immovable.
I'm in love.
-This happens every morning?
-Allow me this dance,
oh graceful one.
Uh.
-I wish these guys for once
would just give it a rest.
-Hey, I wonder where
that Kuno guy is today.
-Wither the pigtailed
treeborn kettle girl?
-Are you looking for her?
-Hm.
You know her?
-Yeah.
She's like a sister.
She has a pigtail and wears
Chinese clothes, right?
-Trifle not with me, Nabiki.
-Moi?
-Am I not Blue Thunder?
The rising new star of
Furinkan High School?
If the pigtailed one thinks she
can humiliate Kuno and simply
walk away, methinks she
thinks wrongly indeed.
[maniacal laughter]
-[yawn]
-Akane, don't you get sick
of fighting those guys
every morning?
-Uh, uh, I sure do.
-When you're cranky, you don't
look that cute, you know.
-[growl]
-Hey.
Is training, OK?
-Here you go.
RANMA: For me?
From Kuno?
NABIKI: To your girl half.
He hasn't a clue that
you're one and the same.
-Hurry up and read it.
-To the treeborn kettle girl.
Please come to the second
field of Furinkan High School
this evening at 5:36 PM.
-Sounds like a duel.
-You know, Kuno's
a real sore loser.
He's out for blood.
-Maybe it's best you didn't go.
-Hm.
I think not.
-He's late.
And he's the one that picked
the time and everything.
What a loser.
KUNO: For it so
falls out, that what
we have we prize not the
worth whiles we enjoy it.
But being lacked and lost,
why then we rack the value.
Then we find the virtue
that possession would not
show us whiles it was ours.
-Hm.
-It is now exactly 536 PM.
The moment when the sunset
is at its most beautiful.
For it is the rising young star
of the high school kendo world
who shines before you.
They call me the Blue
Thunder of Furinkan High.
It is I, Tatewaki Kuno who
has beckoned you to me.
-You still don't
get it, do you pal?
Hey, where's that stick
you're always waving around.
-I have no need of it.
-RANMA: Ha, pretty
confident, ain't ya?
-Confident enough
to give you this.
-Ha.
Huh?
-Pigtailed girl, I love you.
I love you.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Kuno still
hasn't figured out
that that pigtailed
girl of his dreams
is actually that bossy Ranma.
And then Nabiki just
has to go and get
Kuno all riled up
all over again.
Next time on Ranma 1/2,
Ranma versus Ranma?
If it's not one
thing, it's another.
See you there.