[theme music]
-It's a twister!
-Hm?
-Huh?
-Whoa.
-Hm.
-It's Ryoga.
-Hiryu Shoten Ha.
-Looks like he learned
it all on his own.
NARRATOR: Showdown.
Can Ranma Make a Comeback?
-So cold-- that
energy coming at me.
So cold!
[scream]
-Must be a nightmare.
Poor guy.
Only one thing to do.
Rest in peace, my friend.
-How's your patient
doing in there?
-Quiet.
How's Ranma?
-I guess he's still unconscious.
-That Heaven Blast of
the Dragon trick of yours
is really something else.
-The forces of nature are
nothing to be trifled with.
-What's nature
got to do with it?
-Look, you are not thinking
about this in the right way.
The Hiryu Shoten Ha isn't magic.
It's the natural convection
of a battle aura's heat
mixed in with the cold of the
two martial artists' heart.
The resulting
dragon, or tornado,
is what gives the move
its incredible power.
Unless the opponent, in this
case Ryoga, is truly angry,
the dragon won't form.
And that's why when Ranma
landed that final punch--
-That's right.
His final punch wasn't
a punch at all, was it?
What he was really doing
was mixing his cold air
with Ryoga's hot air, thereby
forming the Hiryu Shoten Ha,
or Flying Dragon
Heavenly Ascenstion Wave.
-Which is how he managed
to complete the technique.
Very good.
-When you were talking about
all that body of ice stuff,
then you were really
training him to--
-Exactly.
I was leading up to
showing him the final blow.
But I was too late.
He figured it out on his own.
-I thought I was gonna die, OK?
My brain must have
been working overtime.
-Ranma!
-Finally awake, huh?
-Man, I gotta tell you, though,
once that big blast of heat
from Ryoga started
coming in, I-- I--
if I hadn't thought
I was going to die,
I couldn't have done it.
I probably wouldn't have
mastered the Hiryu Shoten Ha
at all if it hadn't
been for Ryoga.
Man, I guess this time
I really owe him one.
-In other words, you needed
the energy of my ki to do it.
Which is why you forced
yourself on Akane!
Ranma, you die!
-Can we go now?
-Guess we'd better.
We've still got to get that
moxie map from the master.
Ranma may have a new technique,
but without that pressure point
chart, he's still
weak as a baby.
-What are we all waiting
around for, then?
Let's hurry and get a move on.
-The sooner the better.
-Ranma, will you grow
up and act your age?
-We're gonna go without
you if you don't hurry.
-Wait up, will ya?
-You're leaving already?
[shouting]
-Somehow it's just not
as fun as it used to be.
Of course!
How could I have missed it?
Ever since Ranma went away, the
old pilfering's lost its punch.
Oh, you dear, dear child.
Whyfore hath thou
gone and forsaken me?
-Forsake this, ya
stinky little goat!
-Dear me, now I think
I'm hearing voices.
-Loud enough for ya?
-Ranma!
Oh, my boy, you're alive!
-Yeah.
Back from the dead to put you
in your grave, you old freak.
-Well then, in that case, let
me welcome you with open arms!
-What have you done
to my collection?
Now you've done it!
-I'm mad!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
That's it, gramps.
Get good and mad.
It'll be the end of you.
-That didn't take long, did it?
-Look at the master.
-The heat of his anger is
warming the air around him.
-Everything's in place
for Ranma's final blow.
-Not quite yet.
-Look!
They're at the
center of the spiral.
-Do it now!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): Keep
my cool, keep my cool.
Now!
Hiryu Shoten Ha!
-The master!
He's run away!
-Hey!
Hey!
-Get lost, will ya, kid?
You bother me.
-Bother you, huh?
Why can't you just
be serious for once?
-Listen, sonny, when it comes
to peepin', I'm the most serious
man in Japan.
-Hello, nurse.
[screaming]
-I'm warning you.
Interfere with me
just one more time,
and I'm going to make you sorry.
-Well, why don't you do
something about it, then?
-I can't.
If I were to hurt you
in your weakened state,
my conscious would
never forgive me.
-Where are you--
hey, come back here!
-Yeah, right.
What a joke.
Like the master's
really got a conscious.
-He knows more
than he's telling.
-Come on.
Fight me for real, will ya?
-I had my suspicions,
but now I'm sure.
How dare you use
the Hiryu Shoten Ha
on a poor little
old man like me.
-Ah-ha.
He knew about the Heaven
Blast of the Dragon all along.
-But-- but how?
-That technique is one of the
most closely guarded secrets
of our Amazon tribe.
The only way he could
know is-- ah-ha!
-At the time I was but a
handsome youth of a mere 18
summers.
Oh, Cologne!
You may as well get
it over with you know!
You've gotta say yes
to me sooner or later.
-Oh, Happy.
Why you never listen what I say?
You only learn hard way.
-Heya, baby!
Come to--
-Hiryu Shoten Ha!
-Course, we were
both younger then.
-It's not funny!
-Without my battle aura, the
Hiryu Shoten Ha is worthless.
You're not gonna get
any anger out of me.
-Yeah?
That's only because I've been
going about it the wrong way.
Well?
-Nice handwriting.
-OK, then.
How's about a mouthful
of firecrackers?
Well?
-Nice and spicy.
-Fine.
Be that way.
I'll just have to go and
bring out the big guns.
That's all.
How do like this?
-Hey!
That's my life's work
you've got there.
What do you intend to do?
-Gonna do this.
-No!
No, no!
Why, you--
-Keep it up, gramps.
Huh?
-That's OK, Ranma.
I'll just collect
myself a new batch.
I do feel a little sad, though.
-I-- I-- I've lost!
-Don't let it get to ya.
True, you're still
only an amateur,
but everyone's got to
start somewhere, right?
-I'm just better
than you, that's all.
Nothing to feel bad about.
-I can't stand it anymore!
Pick on someone your own size!
He makes me so mad sometimes.
Huh?
Uh, Ranma?
And here he trained
so hard, too.
-I'm starting to wonder if he'll
ever get his strength back.
-If burning his
precious collection
wasn't enough to
make him get mad,
why did I bother training so
hard, if all I was going to do
was-- that's it!
Training!
Of course!
Why didn't I think
of it earlier?
-You know, I'm not
looking forward to it,
but I guess somebody's
gotta cheer him amount.
Hey.
What's that sound?
-I've got it.
I've finally got a
plan to make him mad.
I'm going to bring out 100--
no, make that 120% of his anger,
whether he likes it or not.
-Whether he likes it or not?
Is there some way to do that?
Then again, he may
be on to something.
-What?
Ranma's back?
-Yeah.
Fighting a duel
with the old guy.
-Is he still weak, or what?
-Aw, man.
This oughta be good.
-Hey.
-Uh-huh?
-Give me two of those, will ya?
-Comin' right up.
-Ranma.
-If I win the fight,
you hand over the chart.
You got that?
-Yeah, yeah.
Heard you the first time.
You can come at me whenever
you feel like it it.
-Will you look at him?
He hasn't a care in the world.
-If he doesn't hurry
up and lose his cool,
Ranma hasn't got a chance.
-Ranma said something
about raising
120% of his battle aura.
I wonder if that sound I heard
has anything to do with it?
-Come on, Ranma.
What are you waiting for?
-I'd never have done this if
it could have been helped,
but with this goes
the last of my pride.
Then again, if it means
getting my strength back,
there ain't nothing I
ain't willing to do.
-Check 'em out, freak!
Get a load of these, will ya?
Well?
[gasping]
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
I've been working
on the heat of his anger, but
the heat of his perversion
is even worse.
Burn, you old pervert.
-That's it!
That sound I heard was a camera.
-That was his secret plan?
-It's the same old stuff
he's always pulling.
-You're wrong.
It's true that Ranma
pulls the skirt thing,
but it's also true that he
always wears boy's underwear.
Look at him!
This time he's wearing
girl's underwear!
-She's right!
This time, Ranma's
risking it all!
-And without the
training, he'd never
have had the nerve to do it.
-What's the matter with you?
Do you want 'em, or--
-Yes!
-Those pictures are mine!
-It's the heat of
his perversity!
-OK.
And now for the spiral.
-If you're gonna be
hittin' Ranma, I want in!
-Mousse!
-If you're gonna
have fun at school,
you need to have my permission.
-Hand over those photos!
-Stay still and let me hit ya!
-Let me cut in here!
-Gimme!
-The chart with the
pressure points!
-Whoa!
-Quickly!
Why are you waiting?
Use the Dragon's
Heaven Blast, already!
-But if I do it now, they're
all gonna get caught in it, too.
They've done nothing
to deserve-- uh-huh.
You shouldn't have
oughta ganged up on me!
Hiryu Shotenha!
-Ranma!
-Way to go!
-How'd you like that?
[scream]
-Akane!
How did you-- Akane!
Akane!
-Ranma.
Ranma!
-Akane!
Don't move!
I'm almost there!
Akane!
-Whoa, check it out.
-Someone's in there.
-Whoever it is, they're
coming this way!
-Whoa, check that out.
-Jeez, what are the odds?
Every jerk in this school's
in the same place at once.
-Only one thing to do.
-Bury 'em!
-It's become even more powerful
since he hit me with it.
-That's because there was
plenty more battle aura in it
this time than just yours.
-With Ranma honey
still caught up in it,
how are we ever going
to get him down?
-Good question.
-We can't just stand here!
-Akane!
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
I can't breathe!
-Ranma!
Here!
Take the pressure point chart.
I got it for you when I noticed
Grandfather Happosai dropped
it.
-Akane-- is that why you let
yourself get caught up in this?
You idiot!
How dare you risk
yourself like that?
-Ranma-- hurry.
Take it.
-Akane!
There it is!
The map!
Akane risked her life for it.
I can't just-- No!
There it goes!
The single last surviving copy
of the pressure point chart.
-Now what?
-I dunno.
Confetti?
-Oh, no!
-Quickly, gather it up!
Don't let a single
piece blow away!
-All of it?
You gotta be kidding.
-Listen to me.
Unless we find all the
pieces of that chart,
Ranma will be weak for
the rest of his life.
-That's it.
It's over.
I'll never be strong again.
Akane, I'm sorry.
Akane!
That's right!
How could I-- it's not over!
Not until I save you!
Not until you're safe!
-Oh, no!
They're gonna crash!
-Akane!
-Curse you, Ranma!
Founding School of Anything Goes
Martial Arts final technique!
Get ready for the--
-What's he got, a cherry bomb?
-Happo Fire Burst!
-Wait a sec.
That just bought us some time!
Huh?
-Now hand over the
pictures, or else.
-If it's pictures
you want, take 'em!
-How sweet!
-Gotcha!
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
Least this way,
I can prevent Akane
hitting the ground.
Wha?
-He's gonna hit the fence!
-The fence!
We're gonna hit the--
-Ladies, come back.
Oh, yeah.
-Look.
Akane didn't get a scratch.
-Yeah, not even from the fence.
-The pressure point chart.
Where is it?
Ranma, the chart!
Where did it go?
-Hm?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): That's right.
Akane doesn't know yet.
She still thinks it's safe.
-Here you go.
We picked up the chart,
just like you told us to.
RANMA (VOICEOVER):
What the-- all right!
There's still hope!
-There's a piece missing.
Wouldn't you know it?
It's the only part
we really need
to cure your weakness, too.
-Does this mean
that Ranma will be
weak for the rest of his life?
-Afraid so.
-Dude, keep your
voice down, huh?
He's right in front of us.
-Granny, Ryoga, Ukyo.
All of you.
I want to thank
you for helping me.
You've all been great.
-Huh?
Ranma?
Come back!
Aw, jeez.
That poor guy.
-I hope he doesn't
do anything stupid.
-This is all your fault,
you disgusting little turd!
Take that, and that!
And that!
And--
-Wait!
Hang on a sec.
-This better be good.
-Say, granny, what's this?
-Well, what do you know?
RANMA (VOICEOVER): I'm
gonna miss all of you.
Especially you, Akane.
Wha?
-Planning to sneak
off again, huh?
-Huh?
Akane, I--
-You make me sick.
But I still want to go with you.
-Uh-- Akane-- it'll never work.
You know a girl's got no
business on a training journey.
-I'm not coming
to train, stupid.
I'm coming to
carry your luggage.
Ranma?
Who says you have to go
off training, anyway?
So you're not big and strong.
Well, big deal.
-Without my strength,
what else is left?
-Huh?
What kind of question is that?
You've got a lot of things!
-Go on.
I'm listening.
-Well, um, for one thing,
you, uh-- well, that
is to say, you
kind of-- um, look,
you just have to be strong.
You satisfied?
-Gee, what's the matter, Akane?
Couldn't think of
nothing else, could ya?
[scream] Haven't you
tortured me enough?
My strength!
-Guess that means the
moxie bustion worked.
-What's this?
Ranma Saotome back
from the dead?
-Lie at your own peril.
-We're gonna have the
big fun now, yeah!
-I'm cured!
Akane, I'm cured!
-Oh, Ranma!
Oh, Ranma, I can't tell
you how happy I am for you!
-I'm cured!
Cured, I tell ya!
Ha ha ha!
I'm 100% back to normal!
Cured!
Good as new!
Better than new!
Oh, yeah!
All right!
Way to go!
Outta my way, tree!
Who dam an?
Who da man?
Come on, pop.
You want to take me on again?
-What do you know, Saotome?
Looks like the
Anything Goes school
has no shortage of
power, at least.
-I'm just so glad
everything's turned out well.
-Hey, you want that I should
give him another dose?
-Look at me!
I'm strong!
[theme music]
NARRATOR: So what's with
the skirt, huh, Ukyo?
And Ranma?
What's the big idea?
You two going out on a date?
Next time on Ranma 1/2, Ukyo's
Skirt, The Great Girly Girl
Gambit.
We'll see ya there.