[theme music]
[music playing]
[yawns]
I have a good nap.
Ah!
I don't have nap!
I have robbery!
Ahh!
Someone steal
Jusenkyo Guestbook!
[music playing]
[laughs]
NARRATOR: NARRATOR: "The Demon
From Jusenkyo, Part One."
AKANE TENDO: Jusenkyo Guestbook?
Yeah.
According to the old
ghoul, dude goes over
to the Cursed Springs,
attacks the guide
with some pantyhose
or something,
and makes off with a list of
everyone who's been there.
But still, why would
someone do that?
I can't imagine it would
have monetary value.
It's probably got
nothing to do with money.
It's maybe revenge or
something like that.
Well, attacking with
pantyhose, though?
That's just weird.
If it were your
pantyhose, Akane,
you could attack me any time.
That's disgusting!
Oh, come on, Akane.
Don't be selfish.
Share the wealth.
Give me your pantyhose!
Come on!
At last, I've found you.
What's a guy gotta do, huh?
I'll give 'em back.
You're getting on my
nerves, now, freak.
Oh, well, can I
have yours, then?
Enough, I said!
But I want 'em!
I want 'em!
[cries]
Ranma, why you so mean?
Wah!
You little--
SOUN TENDO: Finish him, son.
Ahhh!
[music playing]
How selfish.
You'd think they'd be a little
nicer being family and all.
Still, like I say, heaven helps
those who help themselves.
So--
Hah!
OK, off to work!
He's fast.
[music playing]
[women screaming]
[laughs]
What a haul!
See you tomorrow!
Ahh!
He's more formidable
than I thought.
Still, he will be brought to
justice one way or another.
[thunker]
AKANE TENDO: Looks
like rain, huh?
And we got no umbrella.
Man, this change
when wet thing sucks.
Who's there?
[music playing]
Hey, I know you.
You're that pantyhose jerk
who went to Jusenkyo, right?
What I don't get, though,
is why are you after me?
It's not you I'm after.
It's your woman.
You want Akane?
Hah.
Well, you're not gonna get her,
so you might as well give up!
Well, what's the matter?
Don't you give up yet?
I wouldn't make me
angry if I were you.
Huh?
AKANE TENDO (VOICEOVER):
Meaning this might not
be his real form?
Why are you doing this?
What is it that you want?
[laughs]
I'm warning you.
AKANE TENDO: Ranma, the rain!
Be careful!
Maybe you'll be more talkative
once I kick your sorry little--
[music playing]
Ranma!
What the--
AKANE TENDO: He's--
he's a demon!
RANMA SAOTOME
(VOICEOVER): Wait a sec.
Changes when wet,
different body.
Could he have
drowned at Jusenkyo?
[music playing]
Ranma, look out!
[laughs]
Better leave this one to me.
It's the freak!
I can't believe it.
You're actually
helping Ranma out?
[laughs]
If you value your life,
you'll let this one go.
And while you're at it,
gimme your pantyhose!
[roars]
Ah!
I'm on fire!
Burrrrn!
[roars]
And now the finish!
What?
Akane!
[music playing]
You demon!
Wait!
Akane!
The stinking coward ran away.
Damn him.
SOUN TENDO: She what?
Got kidnapped!
And you allowed it?
You come here and
tell me my daughter's
been kidnapped by a
demon, and you expect--
Yelling about it
won't help anyone.
Try this clue instead.
He dropped it.
By accident, of course.
Hey, it's the
Guestbook from Jusenkyo!
It's just like you said, Ranma.
He must be on a quest for
revenge against someone,
meaning that the name of his
victim's in this Guestbook.
That's right.
And once you find
the victim, you're
a half step away from
the demon himself.
RANMA SAOTOME:
Way to go, gramps!
No need to thank me.
Hmm.
Interesting.
Most of the names
have been crossed out.
Ah-ha!
Look at that.
He's the one the demon wants.
The fiend!
Involving my innocent Akane!
RANMA SAOTOME: Yeah, but
what language is this?
Is it even Japanese?
You illiterate boobs!
Here, let me-- hmm?
[music playing]
Hmm.
I think it says "Happosai."
You jerk!
What did you do at Jusenkyo?
Mm-hmm.
Well, actually,
10-odd years ago I--
GUIDE: Here, sir we come
Jusenkyo, famous Cursed
Springs.
Oh-ohh--
Ah!
Oh.
Oh-ohhh--
GUIDE: Ah!
She pregnant!
HAPPOSAI: And about
to give birth.
[baby crying]
HAPPOSAI (VOICEOVER): In time,
a bouncing baby boy was born.
Sir!
What you doing?
Well, duh.
I'm washing the newborn.
Ah!
Oh, sir!
In entire 2,000 years Jusenkyo
history, that Cursed Spring
is most cursed of all!
Yeti who drown riding Ox
carrying Crane in one hand
and slippery Eel in other!
RANMA SAOTOME: Yeti
who drowned riding
Ox carrying Crane and Eel?
Then he's the demon
who kidnapped Akane.
My, how he's grown.
It's you he was
after all along!
What's worse is I
can't say I blame him.
Looks like pantyhose.
Hey, there's a message.
"If you want back your
woman, bring Happosai
to Crow's Nest Peak."
Ah!
Old--
---man.
Oh, I, uh-- hmm.
AKANE TENDO
(VOICEOVER): Where am I?
[laughs]
You're awake.
What's the big idea, you jerk!
Ahh!
Don't expect any mercy
because you're a girl.
AKANE TENDO (VOICEOVER): Ranma!
Help me!
RANMA SAOTOME: Take
your punishment, freak!
HAPPOSAI: I don't wanna!
I don't wanna!
Ahhh!
Don't you think
for a minute that
to save my little girl
I won't turn you in!
RANMA SAOTOME: Heck,
we'll even gift wrap you.
Look, I'm sorry!
[inaudible] OK?
[yelling]
Thanks a lot.
Now I can't help her
even if I wanted to.
Akane!
[music playing]
[crow cawing]
AKANE TENDO (VOICEOVER):
Ranma will come.
I know he will.
Only this guy's so strong.
And I'm not sure Ranma will do
any better when he fights him
the next time.
Oh, it's no time
to play hostage.
[laughs]
It's about time.
AKANE TENDO (VOICEOVER):
Gotta hurry!
Help me, please!
No worry.
You leave everything Shampoo.
While Ranma fight big, nasty
demon monster, that when
Shampoo strike.
And I'll help you, Shampoo.
Mousse!
As a man, I can't
just sit idly by.
Mousse, Shampoo, thank you.
Of course, you realize you
may not live through it.
Hang on, Akane.
Almost there.
Ranma!
Like you should be
trusted to save her!
No thanks.
I'll do it myself.
Don't get in the way, man.
You're the one
who's in the way!
Like I said, you're in the
way, and I ain't got time.
So where is he?
You best not be empty handed.
I want the old man.
He told me what happened.
I don't want to hear it!
I said I know what he did.
Huh?
Getting turned into
some freaky monster
like that because of him.
Man, that has got
to be pathetic.
Yeah, but not as bad as
being a cross dresser.
Girlie man.
You know, I was
feeling sorry for you,
but now-- now you're
making me mad!
You jerk!
Have you even looked
at yourself lately?
Go take a look in
the mirror, then
tell me who's more pathetic!
[music playing]
Ahhh!
Why sit around when I
can rescue myself, right?
Better go check on Ranma.
Here goes!
[coughs]
Whoops.
I forgot I can't swim.
[music playing]
[laughs]
Think you can shake me?
Think again!
Whoopsie!
Thought you got me, huh?
Ahh!
Ryoga!
Let go of me!
[squeaks]
What the--
Ranma!
P-chan!
[squeaks]
OK, turkey!
Try this on for size!
[roars]
Oh, no!
Waterfall!
Wa-waterfall!
Ranma!
Ranma?
[roars]
Ahhh!
[squeaks]
[whimpers]
[branches cracking]
[growls]
Why he so upset?
If that's the way he wants to
be, then he can save himself.
Ranma.
So, I see you are
worried about him.
I wouldn't.
I'm sure he's fine.
Yeah, that's true.
Ah!
Curse that cross dresser.
He won't get away with it.
[music playing]
Here, let me do it.
You're still my
hostage, though.
Hm.
Would you at least tell me why?
Why are you doing this?
[crows cawing]
AKANE TENDO: OK, so
you change because
of Grandfather Happosai.
Well, if so, I understand
how you feel, but--
Don't get me wrong.
The super strong body part
I actually quite like.
What?
No, what I'm upset about
isn't nearly so trifling.
AKANE TENDO (VOICEOVER):
Something worse than changing?
Just what did Happosai do?
Even so, once the
old man's dealt with,
then the cross dresser gets it.
Why are you so angry?
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Could you maybe--
Hm!
Ranma?
You wake up.
Shampoo!
Mousse!
Why are you here?
With an enemy so strong,
we may as well join forces.
Shampoo come help
Akane in hour of need.
I wonder if that's really true.
You're planning
something, aren't you?
Hm!
Shows what you know.
Haven't you any
friends of your own?
Friends of my--
We've known each
other longer than that.
It's too, too sad
have no friends.
I-- I'm sorry.
Forgive me for being a cynic.
There nothing to forgive.
MOUSSE (VOICEOVER):
Once Ranma's weakened
by fighting with that
monster, I'll take my chance
and steal Shampoo right
from under his nose!
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER):
Once Shampoo forgotten
in all the fighting,
she take her chance
and make Akane a goner.
AKANE TENDO: It's
such a big bonfire.
Won't it just lead
them right to us?
Exactly.
Excuse me.
Have you forgotten
our conversation?
I don't think you'd like
Ranma when he's really angry.
I'm serious!
Ranma is a lot more than strong.
He's persistent, which
is actually even better.
Is he?
I suppose we'll see, won't we?
He's taunting us.
He wants to make sure we
know right where he is.
And he acts like he
beat us no problem.
That's where he's wrong.
That confidence will cost him.
RANMA SAOTOME (VOICEOVER):
Hang on, Akane.
We're coming for you.
Let's do it!
Yeah!
[music playing]
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Everyone's got
something in their past,
but what could this
pantyhose guy be hiding?
Next time on "Ranma 1/2," "The
Demon From Jusenkyo, Part Two."
We'll see you there!