[theme music]
WEATHERMAN: And as you can see,
with this large low pressure
front building off
the coast, it looks
like we just might be in
store for a White Christmas
after all.
And I'm sure all the kids
watching would love that.
And now a word from--
I sure hope it
snows, don't you?
Check.
Oh, I didn't see that.
Way back when I was a boy,
Nabiki, no one in Japan
even celebrated Christmas.
Back at you, Saotome.
I didn't see that
move coming, Tendo.
Yes.
Back in the good
old days everyone
around here was a Buddhist.
Say, Nabiki, have
you seen Akane?
They're not home yet.
Oh, well, I hope
everyone is hungry
because I'm preparing the
biggest Christmas dinner ever.
BOTH: Hooray!
Hooray for Christmas!
Hooray!
Ugh.
BOTH: Hooray!
Hmm?
Oh, my.
It looks like it's
going to snow.
[chatter]
[gasp] That's so pretty!
Uh, we don't have time
to window shop, Akane,
and I didn't tag along with you
because I wanted to, you know.
Don't forget, we lost the
bet and had to do the family
Christmas shopping, remember?
And besides, why don't
you relax and try
to get into the
spirit of the season?
(GRUMPILY) Oh, man.
Hey, you never told
me what you wanted
to get for Christmas yet.
Hmm?
Well, I don't remember
you telling me what
you were wishing for either.
Oh, that's easy.
I'd like that stuffed
animal, a new blouse
with a skirt to match,
a handbag, a music box,
maybe a few handkerchiefs,
a sweater, some cards-- oh,
that new hat.
That's all?
If I had to buy half
the stuff on your list
I'd be flat broke, so
just keep dreaming girl.
Then you should look for a job.
A Christmas Without Ranma.
SHOP ATTENDANT: Thank
you, and Merry Christmas.
Ugh.
BOTH: Ah!
[nervous groans]
ALL: Huh?
Uh.
That--
--Uh.
--was for Shampoo, right?
--[nervous laugh] Well, I
guess it isn't anymore.
It's your fault.
Huh?
How in the heck can you say
it was my fault when you're
the doofus who ran into me!
Mousse, what are you--
You know it's your fault, Ranma
Saotome, and you'll pay for it!
[crowd gasps]
What do you think
you're doing, Mousse?
No!
This time you're going
to have to make me stop!
I think Mousse might be
getting a little loopy here.
You head home.
I'll catch up.
Well, you better hurry because
we still have to decorate.
All right, I'll try.
Let's do it!
Hyuh!
Mommy, look!
Those boys will get
a lump of coal, dear.
Hey, you better remember what
I told you or you're in trouble!
SHAMPOO: Shampoo no think so.
(SURPRISED) Shampoo.
For your Information,
Akane, Ranma
is going to be spending
Christmas Eve with me
at my house.
Well, for your
information Ranma
is staying at home with
his family and friends.
Is your family going to be
singing carols and eating
Christmas cake?
Yeah, of course.
Oh, only little
children still do that,
but couples who
are truly in love
spend it together in
front of warm fire.
Did Ranma say he was
coming over to your house?
No, not yet.
Ranma, wait for me!
Ah!
Yah!
What an air head.
AKANE: I'm home!
Where's Ranma?
Who knows.
Uh oh, another fight.
You two ready to
start decorating?
MALE SPEAKER: Oh,
Akane, [snorts]
could I have your bra as my
Christmas gift, huh? [crash]
Oh.
Akane, isn't Ranma
supposed to be
home by now, or
is there something
that happened between you two?
Um, what are you asking me for?
Well, I'm starting to get
a little worried about him.
I'm sure Ranma will
be home at any minute.
Tendo's right.
Don't worry.
Ah!
[yells]
Let's see you get out
of that one, Saotome.
Oh, yeah?
Take that!
Ah!
Wait a minute.
Oh.
SHAMPOO (VOICEOVER):
Ranma is going
to be spending Christmas
Eve with me at my house.
[sighs]
Shampoo planning to cook
most delicious turkey dinner
for you, Ranma.
Sounds great.
But first-- oh,
you must promise
you'll spend all
Christmas Eve at my house.
You know, I've always
had this crazy dream
about eating a whole
turkey all by myself.
Oh, how dare you!
You-- you pig!
Ugh!
I've had it!
No, sorry.
Shampoo hasn't come home yet.
In fact, I've been sitting
here waiting for her all day.
Well, thank you.
Do you want to leave
a message for her?
No, that's all right.
Hiya!
Shampoo is home.
Shampoo!
Oh, Akane!
I was just wondering
where's Ranma?
[laughs]
Huh?
Akane, you mean Ranma
no come home yet?
Here Shampoo thinking of
going Akane house to get him.
Shampoo go look.
Ah!
Shampoo!
No, I'm coming too!
Ah, it's Christmas Eve today.
Now aren't they cute?
If only I was 100 years younger.
[laughs]
Come on, Shampoo, wait up!
Why should me wait for you?
Ugh.
Grr.
Oh!
Hey, what's the big deal if
we look for Ranma together?
You're right.
We both want my Ranma
for the same thing.
Uh, I guess so.
Maybe if we find-- oh!
[gasp] Mousse!
So were you chasing
Ranma when this happened?
That's correct.
Tell Shampoo what happen you.
I was right behind him when
I ran into a little problem.
Problem?
Huh!
Hyuh!
You'll pay for ruining
Shampoo's Christmas present!
Hey, I'm too busy to fight you
right now, so just back off,
buddy.
You owe me Ran-- ugh!
Huh?
Ugh!
[girls yelling]
[mousse yelling]
Oh, the pain!
Just before you crashed, do
you know where he was headed?
Oh, my Ranma headed
straight my place.
In your dreams.
Oh, but he isn't
the type that would
come running straight
home to decorate either.
In your story, Mousse, you
said something about thief?
The answer to that is Happosai.
Huh?
Akane!
Hmm?
There are red-nosed
reindeer behind you!
BOTH: Huh?
Oh, well.
Reindeer now gone.
[pigeon coos]
[groans]
If I was using my head, I
would've just stayed at home.
Oh, I can't believe my luck.
Not that it's any different
than it's been all year.
Cheer up.
It can't be all that bad.
You don't understand, Akane.
I spend every last cent I had
buying that present for Shampoo
and now it's ruined,
and so is my Christmas.
But you can't give up.
You know, if you really
like her there's other ways
you can show her.
You've got to get out
there and-- and let
her know you want to spend
Christmas Eve with her.
[sighs] Remember,
you can't give up.
You're right.
I've got to climb the highest
mountain, ford the widest
ocean, I have got to be a man!
OK, but I don't think that
you have to go quite that far,
if you know what I mean.
(SINGING) We're hanging
the socks by the fire bright
and drinking sake
'til I'm really tight.
(SINGING) Hoping Santa
will come tonight.
The turkey's on the
table ready to be carved,
and everybody's hungry,
everybody's starved.
What's this?
Ranma wants a girl's bike and
a boy's bike for Christmas?
You made this up.
BOTH: [laughs]
[door opening]
Ready or not, I'm coming in!
Ugh!
Oh, hello, Akane.
So, can I help you?
Huh?
What's wrong?
I want you to tell me exactly
where Ranma is right now,
just like you told Shampoo.
Oh, sure, and why are
you looking for Ranma?
Huh?
I just told him to
come straight home
and help us get the house ready
for Christmas, that's all.
And after we're
done decorating he
can spend the rest of the night
with Shampoo for all I care.
Sorry, if that's the extent
of your reasons to find Ranma,
I'm afraid I can't tell you.
Huh?
Huh.
Happosai.
Yes, dear.
Oh, now I get it!
Shampoo came here and
bribed you with the ramen.
So what'd she give you
to keep your mouth shut?
No--nothing!
Honestly, she didn't
give me a single thing.
Uh.
Hey, what's that on the floor?
I, uh--
You better hand
it over or else.
Hmm?
Now spill.
All right.
I was just walking through
the park this afternoon--
No, you were on the run after
stealing girls' underwear.
OK, I was running.
[girls yelling]
Hey, Ranma, catch!
Hmm?
What the-- Huh?
No!
It wasn't me!
[laughs] Oh?
Why you little--
Why are you yelling at me for?
Don't you know you're supposed
to respect your elders?
Oh, yeah, like I'm
going to respectable
an old freak who goes
around collecting underwear.
You want to take me on?
Hey, I don't have
time for this.
I've had just about
enough of your insolence.
Here, take this!
Ahh!
And the last time I saw
him, he was flying directly
towards Kuno's house.
[footsteps running away]
Hey, come back here!
Where do you think you're going?
Hmm.
Kids today.
--[laughs] This Christmas,
Ranma is all mine!
Shampoo no think so.
Hyah!
Oh, no!
I better put a stop to this.
Hyah!
Ha!
Hey, you two quit it!
Ah!
Ugh.
Akane?
Well, it seems
another rat has come
into my house to steal my Ranma
darling away for Christmas Eve.
Oh, I-- Who are you
calling a rat, and what
are you two thinking?
It's so stupid to fight.
It's pointless!
What's it matter where
Ranma spends Christmas?
But that doesn't explain
what you're doing here.
Oh.
Well, um--
TATEWAKI: Ah, Akane--
Ah!
-- --Tendo.
This is your personal invitation
to spend Christmas with me.
Kuno?
What happened?
I'm so glad you
asked, Akane Tendo.
Huh?
It was only hours ago that
scoundrel, Ranma Saotome,
dared set foot in the
house of Tatewaki Kuno.
So Ranma did come here.
Forget him.
For now you are all
mine, and that is how
it shall be for an eternity.
[yells in pain]
--[exhales] OK. first you tell
me where I might find Ranma,
then you and Akane can spend
quiet Christmas Eve together.
(WEAKLY) OK.
Oh, boy.
[yelling] Ugh!
Oh, Ranma, darling.
How wonderful of you to drop
in unannounced like this.
What a nice Christmas
Eve this is going to be.
Ranma Saotome, how dare you
barge into the house of Kuno
on Christmas Eve,
you unsociable rube!
Oh, that's going
to leave a mark.
Huh?
What the heck?
Stand up and defend yourself!
Not again.
Come back here!
Ranma, darling, don't leave.
Don't you remember you
were going to spend
a quiet Christmas Eve with me?
You coward!
[breathing quickly]
You cannot escape my wrath!
Hey, isn't that the
shop where-- huh?
Ah!
Ugh!
So, Ranma with Ukyo?
I'd say we did a
pretty good job.
I'd say you're right.
Now all I have to do is get
dinner ready for everyone.
You want to help, Nabiki?
You kind of make
it sound like we're
expecting a full house tonight.
Don't ask me why, but I have
a funny feeling that we are.
Oh.
--[exhales] I am
so tired of this.
That's so pretty.
--[groans] We don't have
time to window shop, Akane.
You better hurry home because
we still have to decorate.
All right.
I'll try.
And for your
information, Akane,
my Ranma going to be spending
Christmas Eve with Shampoo
tonight.
If that's the extent of
your reasons to find Ranma,
I'm afraid I can't
tell you, Akane.
Well, it seems
another rat has come
into my house to steal my Ranma
darling away for Christmas Eve.
That's it.
I'm so tired of everyone
trying to ruin everything.
MALE SPEAKER: Akane Tendo.
Huh?
Ugh.
Tonight shall be the most
memorable night of our lives.
[bang] What did I say?
How many times do
I have to tell you?
Ranma [? honeys ?] not here.
As a matter of fact,
I haven't seen him
for almost a whole week.
That is lie.
--[laughs] If you were smart you
would tell us before we force
it out of you.
Why don't you try?
On second thought, I've
got a lot better things
to do with my time,
like find Ranma.
You're not going anywhere.
OK, what about if we do this?
We have battle, and whoever
wins spends Christmas Eve
alone much Ranma.
That is an excellent
idea for a commoner.
Yeah, do you have your
moments of brilliance,
don't you Shampoo?
Huh?
BOTH: Huh?
What are you doing here?
SHAMPOO: Akane want
to join fight too?
It would make no
difference to me. [laughs]
Ranma belong Shampoo.
Ranma darling and I are going
to spend Christmas Eve together.
[sarcastic laugh] Ranma
honey is mine, you hear?
I'm sick and tired of listening
to the three of you. [growls]
Do you understand me?
Unfortunately for
all of you, Ranma
isn't going to spend
Christmas Eve with any of you!
What?
Huh?
Maybe you coming down
with something, Akane.
I feel fine, Shampoo.
Ranma is-- Ranma
is-- Ranma's going
to spend Christmas Eve
with me, you understand?
[exhales]
Hmm?
Akane!
Huh.
Ranma.
What took you so long?
I've been waiting hours for ya.
Hmm?
Oh, and wait a sec.
I even stopped and got you a
little something for Christmas.
I didn't have time
to wrap it though.
Here, you like it?
Huh?
Also a music box, and a--
and I saw these cool cards
that I thought you'd like.
What do you think?
Ranma, you remembered.
Oh, that's easy.
I'd like that stuffed animal,
a new blouse with a skirt
to match, a handbag,
a music box--
[crying]
And they're some
other stuff here.
Hey, look, it's snowing.
Huh?
Hey, are you crying?
[sniffs] No.
Huh?
Oh, man, and I thought all this
stuff would make you happy.
[door opening]
We're home!
FEMALE SPEAKER:
Where have you been?
You were supposed
to help decorate.
BOTH: Huh?
What took so long, boy.
Well, we've been
waiting for you two.
[dog whimpers in agreement]
Season's Greetings,
Akane Tendo.
Look at all you're
friends who came over
to celebrate Christmas
Eve with you.
Hurry and sit down.
I'm starving.
[duck quacks]
Don't just stand there.
Dig in before it gets cold.
I can't believe my eyes.
Neither can I.
Isn't it great we can all
spend the evening together?
And remember, Ranma promised
he'd be with me all day
tomorrow.
What you mean?
Ranma said he's
spending Christmas day
with only Shampoo.
Now, now girls.
It's not healthy to argue
like that on an empty stomach.
[gasp]
OK, Tendo, can you
stop the lecture
and just start
carving up the turkey?
Oh, and save me a big
slice of white meat.
Hey, I'm the one who
bought the bird, so I
get dibs on the white meat.
So now it's
suddenly your turkey
because you sprung for it.
What about the cranberry sauce?
I bought that too, Saotome.
[end theme music]
AKANE: Snow begins
to fall in Furinkan.
And continues to fall,
and fall, and fall!
Hey, when is it going
to stop snowing?
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
A Cold Day in Furinkan.
We'll see you there.