[theme music]
[music playing]
-And here we are,
just like I said.
Next stop- outdoor hot springs.
NARRATOR: The mixed bath horror!
-Hey, look!
Check it out!
The sun's back!
-Thank goodness!
-I wonder what
happened to Ryoga!
He said he'd go ahead
but- where is he?
-Gee, I don't know.
Think he's lost?
-Haha, don't be absurd.
The hotel's just
around the corner.
Hmm.
Should I say it ought to have
been just around the corner.
-But dad, we are deep
in the mountains!
-And we might not make it out.
-Oh, come on now girls.
What's the matter?
Don't you trust your own dad?
[music playing]
-All right.
It's just possible we may
have taken a wrong turn.
-Tell us something
we don't know!
-So what you're saying
is were lost, then?
-Gee, what do you think?
-You sure?
Cos', maybe- um.
-Will you just admit it?
-Ryoga!
-Hey!
How's it going?
This guy here almost
stepped on me-- I mean,
he stopped to help me.
Yeah that's it.
-As a pig, you mean.
-Does that mean you're
from around here?
Do you know where we can
find the Royal Prince Resort?
-This guy runs the place.
-How do you do?
-Good!
Then you can tell us where it
is, this Royal Prince-- this
is so-called Royal Prince Resot.
[music playing]
-What a dump!
Akane, we should have known.
-Well, that's dad.
I mean honestly,
how cheap can he be?
-I am glad it stopped
raining, though.
-Oh, Kasumi.
You always stick up for me.
Come in.
-Good afternoon.
I'm wondering if you
girls might enjoy
a dip in our outdoor
bathing facilities.
-Outdoor.
-We'd love to!
-They do say our waters
have therapeutic benefit.
Many martial
artists, for example,
have been known to visit
us in hopes of increasing
their skills-
[voice fades]
-Wow!
Can it really help
your martial arts?
-Matrial arts?
Mixed bath?
Sounds good enough to me.
I, uh, just remembered-
-Oh no you don't!
-How dare you treat
your elders like that?
Lemme' go!
-I bet you think you're
going off to have a peak.
Good thing we're
here to stop you.
-That water's got magical
martial arts powers.
If you're too dumb to know what
that means, then I'm sure not--
-Magic?
Magical spring-
-With magical powers
-Could mean one thing only.
-I'll cure the pain!
-I'll cure the girl!
-Hey!
It could happen!
Last one in's a rotten egg!
-Huh?
-Ready or not, here we come!
-Will you be joining
us in the outdoor bath?
-Oh, well, uh.
-We heard about the
springs so we, uh.
-Thought we'd, uh, try them out.
-You'd have to be pretty
dumb to come here and not
go in the water.
I mean it's so-
-My thoughts exactly, my sweet.
Why don't you and I just go and-
-Forget it!
And keep to your own side.
-Girl?
Boy?
They're separate!
Then why did I even
bother to do any of this
if they're not mixed baths?
-Too bad, huh?
-And no peeking!
-And who says I'm gonna?
I've just got to warm
my bones, that's all.
-Ranma is right.
That guy is a freak!
-You're telling me.
-Bit what if I were to say
I haven't much time left.
Then would you reconsider?
But Ranma!
If you won't be
a girl willingly,
then perhaps you'll
do it by force!
-Think again, freak!
-Have it your way pigtail boy!
You can think whatever you want!
-Hiyaah!
-Ahh!
-Haha!
-Alright grandpa!
Time for your beatdown!
Stop running and take your
medicine you grumpy little-
-It's not just me who
heard that, right?
-Do you think
something's out there?
Like someone watching?
-Or maybe the baths
are joined after all.
-But the enterances
are separate.
I'm sure it's an animal, or-
-This far out it
could be wild monkeys.
-Or a bear, maybe.
-A bear?
-Nice thought, sister dear.
Akane, use this.
-Huh?
-I said come here
you little freak!
Or you'll be sorry you ever-
-Nice connect.
-I'm not sure, but
I think I got them.
-Let's see.
-There's someone over there.
-Or maybe the girl's side is
connected to the- This deserves
further-
-Wait a minute!
Maybe other people let you
get away with that stuff,
but I'm not gonna let you-
-There's a good chance
Akane's there, you know.
-Ah!
Akane?
T- t- taking a b- b- bath?
Wait a second.
I can't do that.
That would be wrong.
Where are you going?
Wait!
Stop.
-There's nobody there.
-But I was sure that I-
-Maybe we're both wrong.
-Aw, it's not fair!
There's no one there!
Boring!
-I tell you, I'm sure that I.
-Huh?
Ranma!
What is it?
-I don't know, but-
-Hey Ranma!
Is something wrong?
-I...
Don't know.
[music playing]
-You're kidding!
Inside the bath?
-I'm not sure what, but I did.
-Come, now.
Be serious.
Perhaps this so-called
monster of yours really
is nothing but a monkey.
-For the last time,
it wasn't a monkey!
That thing is real, alright?
Whatever it is.
-Kasumi, be honest with me.
Ranma's just making all
this stuff up, right?
-What do you think?
It could be true.
-Nabiki!
Not you too!
-It probably is haunted Akane.
Didn't you read The Shining?
-You know I hate that
Stephen King stuff-
[screaming]
-There.
Are you happy now?
It turns out the
ghost was just a goat.
-I wanna go to Akane!
Come on!
Let go!
[inaudible]
-I, uh- I knew it all along.
-Guess what?
I know this really scary story.
Want to hear it?
On a night like this, when
the warm wind was blowing
at this kind of resort,
a murder was committed.
And the corpse abandoned
in the hot spring.
From that day on, in
the middle of the night,
in that lonely place, a
certain sound could be heard,
[ominous noise]
-Bravo, DeNiro.
-Don't knock the
method, my dear.
It's late.
Lights out everyone.
ALL: Kay.
[music playing]
-In that room, a certain
sound could be heard.
-There was something there.
I felt it.
-What?
Who's there?
-Is there something
the matter, miss?
-Uh, the water, I-
-Yes?
-Nevermind.
-Hmmm.
-Dad, please.
Can't we leave early?
-But Akane.
It's a two night,
three day package.
If we leave early,
we waste money.
-Oh, who cares about the money?
-Hey you two, what's the ruckus?
-Akane seems to think there's
a monster in the hot springs.
-But there is, I tell you!
-You know, you're really
starting to remind me of Ranma.
It's perfectly safe, Akane.
Trust me.
Speaking of which, Tendo, how
about a dip in the hot spring?
-Don't mind if I do, Saotome.
-Oh, honestly.
-Now this is the life.
-I'll say.
-Boogieman in the hot springs.
Ridiculous.
What's the matter with
kids today, anyway?
-I guess they'd rather
play video games.
-You said it, Tendo.
BOTH: Woah!
Ahhh!
-What a couple of wimps.
Passing out from the heat.
-Listen, it wasn't the
heat that did this to them.
They were attacked!
-Hmm.
Attacked by what?
-Ranma's up there right now,
and he's taking a look around.
-I've got to go and help him!
-You find something yet?
-No, nothing.
-What about the manager?
We oughta interrogate him.
-Good idea.
-Ranma!
Ryoga!
Are you here?
Come on, where are you?
Answer me!
Is- is that you?
I- I guess not.
-Ah!
What do you want with me?
-Actually, we've got a
couple questions for you.
-Yeah, and we want
the truth, too.
-The one who sent out this
invite was you, wasn't it?
-What is it, some kind of scam
to lure martial artists to you
resort so they can
practice with whoever
you got out in that water.
-Who do you got
out there, anyway?
-Well, whatever the kid
is, he's not a monster.
-He's a kid?
What kind of irresponsible-
-Wait.
Save your judgments until
after I tell you the story.
We haven't always been
this run down, you know.
We used to be a
top-rated resort.
But then the master died,
leaving the young master
in charge and in heavy debt.
-Wow.
We didn't know.
-His father's last wish
was for a grandchild.
But what girls come
to a place like this?
Seems he'd be forever alone.
Because of our reputation,
the only ones who did come
were martial artists.
By engaging them in
combat, the young master
was able to forget
his loneliness,
and improve his fighting skills.
Thus the art of
Bathhouse-Fu was born.
BOTH: What?
-Yes I admit it.
I'm the one who sent
the invitations to you.
I swear, I never
meant to hurt anyone.
All I wanted was
for the young master
to meet some young ladies.
-Hm?
So, how are we
going to save Akane?
-Don't worry.
I got a plan.
-Like what?
-Like this!
-I'm sorry Ryoga, but
for what I got in mind,
you'd just drag me down.
-Wow!
What beautiful how waters.
First, I have to wash off.
Oh, it feels good!
Now that I'm clean I
can go into the spring.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): That's it.
Closer.
-Hah!
Gotchya!
-OK, where'd he go now?
Come back here you jerk!
And gimme back Akane!
It's so steamy in here,
I can't see a thing.
I'm gonna find you
sooner or later!
RANMA (VOICEOVER): How can I
fight him if I can't see him?
He's gotta be here somewhere.
-So there you are!
Can't hide forever, you know.
Ahh, I feel dizzy.
-Stupid Ranma.
Ditches me the first
chance he gets.
Akane!
-Ah!
-Ranma!
-Good news, Ronma!
I've rescued Akane!
-Whoopie.
-What?
Come on, get up!
What's wrong with you?
-I would if I could.
-Ranma, look out!
-Ranma!
-A girl?
-Saotome school final
attack-- bathrobe wrap.
Take that.
And that!
-Hit the showers, jerk.
-Let's find out
who he really is.
Huh?!
Who the heck is he?
-He's totally gorgeous!
-Well, I'll be.
-Wow, not bad.
-They have improved.
-Haha.
We certainly do look
better, don't we?
[inaudible] someone to see you!
-He there, remember me?
-Heh, not really.
-I mean honestly, if
it hadn't been for me,
he'd still be alone.
Not hanging out with
all those girls.
-Poor Akane, you'll get over it.
-Mind your own business.
I'll just [inaudible].
-Oh, yeah.
Sure.
We believe you.
-Why can't you be normal?
-Hiya, baby.
Would you like to jump
in the tub with me?
In our hot springs,
is what I mean.
[music playing]