[music playing]
[theme music]
[thunder]
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER): Madame
St. Paul's Cry for Help.
And she say, yeah,
but that [inaudible]
used to be electric.
[laughter]
Oh, well, I am--
Wow.
There.
Hold your horses.
What's the problem?
It was my turn, and I moved.
[groan]
Well, in that case,
how about this?
[neighing]
Horses?
A stage coach?
Hey, yeah.
Gee.
What is it?
I don't know.
My.
Are we expecting company?
[groan]
[music playing]
Huh?
Oh.
Is that Mary Poppins?
It wouldn't mean that
woman from the [inaudible]?
AKANE: Madame St. Paul!
Bonjour, everyone.
I've brought some tea.
I've just made these cookies.
I hope you'll try one.
Help yourself.
Hm?
Huh?
Thank you.
ALL: That was fast.
Fairly impressive
confectioneries,
considering the poor quality
of the baking ingredients
people such as
yourselves generally use.
Sure.
Typical.
Always find something
to criticize.
So, Madame St. Paul, there
must be some urgent reason
why a person of your greatness
would come into a commoner's
house like this.
Why don't you share it with us?
Very well.
For the past few
days, Monsieur Picolet
has been behaving
rather strangely.
What do you mean by strangely?
MADAME ST. PAUL:
For instance, he
leaves the curtains closed,
even in the daytime,
refusing to see
the light of day.
When he is served dinner, it
remains on the table untouched.
It's as if I'm living with a
completely different person.
Good food has always been
important to Monsieur Picolet.
I can't imagine him
not having an appetite.
In addition to that,
there is one other thing.
Recently, the
neighboring countryside
seems plagued with a
mysterious sickness.
What kind of sickness?
The young ladies
collapse with high fevers
in the middle of the night.
After which, they
inexplicably go missing.
And the numbers are increasing
with every passing day.
My, how dreadful.
MADAME ST. PAUL: There's one
aspect I haven't yet mentioned.
Every night, Monsieur Picolet
steals away from the mansion,
and he's gone until sunrise.
Blood sucking monster.
Blood sucking?
Say what?
Hang on.
You mean, the kind of
monster that sucks blood
from young women to stay alive?
In other words, the
legendary vampire
from medieval European times.
[scream]
Hey.
You're starting to give
us the creeps, Tendo.
I don't suppose
any of the girls
have weird marks on their necks,
like fang marks, would they?
Come on.
Get real, Nabiki.
You shouldn't joke like that.
Suggesting that Monsieur
Picolet has become a vampire
and is terrorizing
the countryside.
It's an insult to
poor Madame St. Paul.
I never suggested Monsieur
had turned into a vampire.
Get real, guys.
We're getting carried away.
MADAME ST. PAUL: No.
Huh?
Perhaps not.
Now that I think
of it, the victims
did have strange
marks on their necks.
[gasp]
In any case, a curse has
befallen the Chardin family.
Monsieur Picolet's behavior
is very suspicious,
and we must do something
to spare the young ladies.
You're the only ones
I could turn to.
I beg you.
Please help Monsieur Picolet.
[neighing]
Huh?
[gasp]
Come.
Let's go inside, and
I'll show you your rooms.
Yeah, sure.
Ranma, do you find
it kind of cold here?
[bell]
Ranma?
Hello?
Huh?
Oh, I don't know about you,
but I'm starved, Akane.
Wait a second.
If I know you, you probably
brought along something
to eat in that backpack
of yours, right?
Uh, well, actually--
RANMA: What is this junk?
[laughter]
A cross?
Garlic?
Holy water?
A wooden stake?
Don't tell me.
Nabiki gave me this stuff
when we were leaving.
And, uh, she insisted
I bring it along.
Dinner will be served shortly.
Oh, good.
I can hardly wait!
[music playing]
[sigh]
Why, thank you.
That was delightfully
delectable.
Thanks very much.
Hm?
You two haven't changed.
Heathens!
But this time, I won't
hold it against you
since you're here at my request.
Ah, sorry.
[door opening]
Huh?
You--
Bonjour Mademoiselle Ranma
and Mademoiselle Akane.
As usual, it is a pleasure
to be in your company.
Monsieur Picolet,
these young ladies
have come all the
way here to visit us.
Tres bien, madame.
I couldn't be happier.
Monsieur Picolet, please
sit and dine with us.
Your meal is all ready.
Forgive me, Madame
St. Paul, but I
don't seem to have much of
an appetite at the moment.
You should at least
have a little something.
Force yourself to
eat a little dinner,
even if you aren't hungry.
If you both insist,
then I'll have a bite.
[gasp]
Well, I've never seen anyone
lick your dishes so clean.
So much for table manners
of the rich and famous.
See what I mean?
I don't have any
appetite at all.
It's just as I feared.
Once again, you
hardly ate a thing.
My heart breaks for
you, Monsieur Picolet.
[crying]
20 course meal not good enough?
I'll be retiring.
Pleasant dreams.
Hm?
Monsieur Picolet has stopped
coming out in the daytime.
He just stays in the tower?
Uh, you haven't seen
Ranma, have you?
Not since breakfast
this morning, now
that I think of it.
[sigh]
[footsteps]
I really wish
Ranma would tell me
where he's going before he
just takes off like that.
Oh, it's open.
I'll check in there.
Hm?
Yo.
[scream]
Hi.
Uh.
Jeez, don't scare me like that!
I almost had a heart
attack, you jerk!
[creak]
[gasp]
Hm?
[animal sounds]
[thunder]
It's an old library.
Look at all the books.
[gasp]
And they all look
pretty ancient.
Huh?
Look, Ranma.
That's strange.
RANMA: Yeah, it looks like
someone was just here.
AKANE: It's the
translation into Japanese.
This diary belongs
to Jonathan Chardin.
Volume 13.
There you go.
He must've been studying
Japanese translation.
Sounds like a serious kid.
Let's see.
"July 10, 1892--
another sunny, hot day.
Summer is here."
Hey, this thing is
over 100 years old.
Are you serious, Ranma?
"Yet again, young ladies in
the village have fallen victim
to the beast.
Someone in the village has
sworn to the authorities
that he saw my younger brother
at the scene of the crime.
There are no real
suspects at this time.
Recently, my brother
claims to have no appetite
and has been acting
rather peculiar."
That's freaky.
This describes Picolet to a T.
And the same thing
happened 100 years ago?
"July 11-- the weather
has turned to rain.
My younger brother has
locked himself in his room
and is eating next to nothing.
July 12-- sunny again.
This morning, the
ninth victim was found.
I will clean the
basement today and search
for anything unusual."
The next page has been
torn out of the book.
I wonder what he found
down in the basement.
Hm.
[footsteps]
[gasp]
Someone's coming.
Madame--
[gasp]
[door closing]
What'd you do that for?
Doesn't that strike you
as weird-- Madame St. Paul
sneaking the book
away like that?
Huh?
Akane, tonight we're
going to check out
the basement ourselves.
Uh, we are?
Hey, wait for me!
[thunder]
[shivering]
Oh, no!
Here.
I made some tea.
Hey, uh, Kasumi?
What is it, Nabiki?
[scream]
Look at those two chickens.
You'd better tell them about
the tea before they drink it.
Good idea.
[shivering]
Before you drink that tea,
I better tell you that it's--
That it's extremely--
[scream]
Hot!
[dog barking]
A full moon.
That's kind of creepy.
[knocking]
[sigh]
It's you.
[gasp]
Huh?
Who's over there?
Monsieur Picolet?
Mademoiselle Akane.
I'm always delighted
to be in your company.
No!
Stay away from me!
Don't come any closer!
Fear not.
Come with me.
[gasp]
[scream]
Huh?
Ranma!
[gasp]
[scream]
[sigh]
It was just a dream.
I guess I must
have fallen asleep.
Ranma, it's me.
Are you in there?
I'm coming in.
Ranma?
Wonder where he went.
He wouldn't have
gone to the basement.
Ran-- no, it's not him.
It wouldn't be like Ranma to
come down here by himself.
Huh?
Oh!
Madame St. Paul!
Why are you here?
A beautiful full
moon out tonight.
The full moon
reminds me of times
gone by when I made my
formal debut into society.
(VOICEOVER) That window's
too high to jump out of.
My only chance is by the tree.
Witness how the full moon
brings wings to my heart.
Beautiful, like
Paris at midnight.
This will be a night to be
cherished for an eternity
by both of us.
Hm.
We read that old diary.
Now explain something.
What's inside this wine cellar?
Mademoiselle Akane, it may
have been a mistake bringing you
here to help us.
Madame St. Paul, I know you've
got something behind your back.
Now show it to me.
I should never have
brought in outsiders.
This should have been kept
within our family walls.
Show me what you're hiding.
Oh!
Huh?
Blue wine?
It must be the light.
There's no such
thing as blue wine.
MADAME ST. PAUL:
It's Chardin blue--
handed down for generations.
I've never actually
seen it until now.
PICOLET: Sugar,
Mademoiselle Ranma?
Uh, one teaspoon, thanks.
PICOLET: Something
troubling you?
Huh?
Have your tea
before it gets cold.
Yeah, sure thing.
(VOICEOVER) I hope
it's not poisoned.
Obviously, Picolet
has drunken the wine.
I read the next
entry in the diary.
Everyone who drinks the blue
wine becomes poisoned and evil.
We must stop him before
he takes his next victim.
Ranma.
Ranma's in trouble.
Picolet, you poisoned my tea.
I should've known better.
There's absolutely nothing
to worry about, my pretty.
Simply do as I tell you, and
everything will work out fine.
Mademoiselle Ranma.
You dirty--
[groan]
[gasp]
You'll pay for this.
This way.
This shortcut is
the fastest way.
Monsieur Picolet probably
drank the blue wine
without knowing
the consequences.
We must find a way to shock
him back to his senses.
(VOICEOVER) Ranma!
[scream]
[gasp]
No.
This poison's really
starting to kick in.
Resign yourself
and put your trust
in me, Mademoiselle Ranma.
Come.
[groan]
[scream]
Huh?
Ranma!
[groan]
Hm.
Hold it!
Take this, fang!
Care to explain
why you are holding
a cross, Mademoiselle Akane?
Huh?
OK.
Yah!
How about this?
Huh?
Mm.
Your garlic is tres bien.
Even under the effects
of the blue wine,
he has such grace and speed.
Excuse me.
This is no time to admire
his frog impersonation.
Now I believe it is time
to move on to the main dish.
Oh, no!
Please, don't!
[gasp]
Don't do it!
Bon appetit!
[scream]
[slurping]
We are the first ones to
ever witness this display.
The Chardin blue
wine has claimed
yet another tragic victim.
I've seen Picolet kiss before,
and it was nothing like that.
And this is all supposed
to have happened just
because he drank a little wine?
That's pretty far-fetched,
even for a creep like you!
Suck on this!
[groan]
[gasp]
Uh, Mademoiselle Ranma?
That's Monsieur to you.
Uh.
Amazing.
[scream]
Madame St. Paul, I can't
seem to remember anything
about the last few days.
Would you be kind enough to
tell me what happened recently?
I'd rather not go
into it at this point,
but I will tell you one
thing, Monsieur Picolet.
Never again drink any blue wine.
It carries a very bad bite.
Oh, Madame St. Paul!
How can you ever
forgive me for this?
Come on.
Tell me what happened
after I passed out.
Believe me, you
wouldn't want to know.
Hm. you know, something
reeks of garlic inside here.
[laughter]
I don't smell it.
RANMA: Come on!
Tell me what happened, Akane.
AKANE: Maybe some day.
RANMA: Akane!
AKANE: Just drop it.
RANMA: No!
[music playing]
GIRL (VOICEOVER):
The princess that
fell from the stars is a
daughter of a martial arts dojo
who's betrothed to someone.
Now where have I
heard that before?
Next time on Ranma 1/2--
Meet You in the Milky Way.
We'll see you there.