[theme music]
NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hey, let go.
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma's
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
AKANE (VOICEOVER):
"P-Chan Explodes!
The Icy Fountain of Love!"
-Got it?
Akane is my fiancee.
You touch her and I'll kill you.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Did
you mean that, Ranma?
Would you really do that?
-Hmph, a fiance isn't forever.
I'll take it as a personal
challenge to break those ties.
RANMA: You can try.
-I'll do better than that.
She won't be yours
for much longer.
We-- the world famous Golden
Pair-- have another name.
BOTH: The Anti-Matchmakers.
-Anti-Matchmakers?
ANNOUNCER: Ladies
and gentlemen, here's
the moment we've all been
waiting for-- the Golden Pair's
ultimate technique,
The Couple Cleaver!
-There's not a single couple
we've ever faced on the ice--
-That has stayed together
after we split them up.
-Ready, Akane?
-Mhm.
-Come on.
AKANE (VOICEOVER): Think
about the other stuff later.
For now, concentrate on winning.
-Hey, Ranma!
What are you two doing?
-Huh?
-You're wide open.
See?
MIKADO: The Good Bye Whirl.
-Ranma.
-Ho ho, take a good look,
ladies and gentlemen.
At last, the Golden Pair's
dreaded final technique--
the infamous Good Bye Whirl.
-Listen to me, Ranma Saotome,
release the girl's hand
and I'll stop spinning.
-Hah!
No way.
-Go on, let her go.
You can't hang on
much longer anyway.
-Ranma, let go.
-No way!
You'll go flying
head-first into the ice.
-Here's where the Good
Bye Whirl gets its name.
If one partner
betrays the other,
then he or she will be
spared, but what then?
Oh, what a terrible way
to end a relationship.
-Akane.
-Ranma, come on.
Do it!
-No!
How can you even ask
something like that?
-The more you trust
each other, the greater
the shock when you're betrayed.
A couple caught in the Good Bye
Whirl is doomed to disaster.
-Ignore him.
I'll be fine.
Let me go!
Please!
-No way!
How can I?
You're too stupid to
know what's good for you.
-What-- what'd you say?
-Little Azusa is all worn out.
ANNOUNCER: Look at
that, Challenger Saotome
never let go of his partner.
The Good Bye Whirl
was a failure.
But faithfulness has its price.
Ranma Saotome seems to have
sustained serious injury.
-Oh, no.
Ranma, Ranma.
-Little Azusa is so dizzy.
-I'm sure that every bone
in his body must be crushed.
Nothing human could
have withstood that.
-You dummy Ranma.
I didn't ask you to do that.
Dummy.
You dummy.
Dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy.
You dummy!
-Quiet.
-Ranma?
-Is that how you thank me?
Calling me names?
-You were faking?
-Is that all you really
think of me, Akane?
[moaning]
-Are you sure you're OK?
-I couldn't be better.
-Why, you've made
it to your feet.
-Come on, I'm
ready anytime, man.
-Huh, you're very stubborn.
Let's see how long you can last.
ANNOUNCER: And we're
back where we started.
Who will be the winner
of the Charlotte Cup?
Who will be the one to
take home the bacon?
-Oh!
-Don't be ridiculous.
You can't fight like this.
-Don't tell me what I can't do.
This fight's not over yet.
-That's right.
Those are my thoughts precisely.
I have no intention of
letting you withdraw.
Not until I, as promised, exact
a kiss from Akane Tendo's lips.
-No way.
Are you crazy?
-Here I-- oh!
-My Charlotte has disappeared.
-What are you doing, you fool?
-You help find Charlotte!
-This is where I come in.
-Come on, Akane.
-Wait a sec.
-Hrrg.
What'd you do that for, Akane?
-Don't do this.
Not for me.
-Huh?
-Really, it's not necessary.
-Akane.
RYOGA: Ranma, turn quietly into
a girl and let me handle this.
AKANE: Hey!
RYOGA: Pair up with
me, Akane, and we'll
take them on together.
RANMA: Oh, wouldn't
that be convenient?
RYOGA: Quiet, you.
Be a good girl and-- there.
That's it.
Now, Akane, you and I can-- ah!
-Moron.
-All right, where's Akane?
-Hey, stupid, that's my line.
What are you doing here anyway?
ANNOUNCER: Oh, wait a minute.
What's going on here?
Furinkan High has slipped
in a substitute pair
in the middle of the match.
-I'm here to pair up with
Akane, that's what I'm doing.
-Go home.
We're fine without you.
-My pigtailed princess.
-Find Charlotte.
Find Charlotte.
-Cut that out.
Come to me, my pigtailed pretty.
-Huh?
Oh, Mr. Sanzenin,
please put me down.
-I can't do that.
You owe me.
Now aren't you going to
thank me for saving you?
-Course.
What do you want?
OK.
-You cut that out right now.
You sure got a lot of
nerve, you know that, buddy?
-I see you're being shy again.
Come on, give me your hand.
-You want it?
Here, take it.
OK, enough stalling.
Let's fight.
-Wait, Ranma.
-Ow, quit it.
-Hey, Ranma, how can you fight
in your weakened condition?
You're not feeling
well, remember?
Why don't you go take it easy,
and let Akane and I take it
from here, all right?
-Hey, what's the
deal with these two?
ANNOUNCER: The crowd is
getting really restless.
There seems to be some objection
about Furinkan's last minute
pair substitution
into the competition.
-No, that's not what
we're mad about.
-Where's your sexy costume?
We can't see your body.
-That boy's costume
is really pathetic.
-Leave everything to us.
We can solve all
your fashion needs.
ANNOUNCER: What?
It seems the Kolhotz fashion
club is entering the arena.
-Go, girls.
-Hey.
Our job here is done.
Farewell.
ANNOUNCER: A brand new
look for a brand new pair.
Let the match resume.
-Hey there, Ryoga.
You have learned how to
skate by now, haven't you?
-Yeah right, Ranma.
It took me more
than five days just
to find this stupid school.
You think I had time
to practice my skating?
Hey, so long as I can
stand up, it's OK, right?
-No, it's not OK.
This is martial arts ska-- huh?
Can I please accept
my apologies.
I'm sorry I was unable to you
during the competition I know
you must be terribly
disappointed.
Do you have a fever?
Are you feeling OK?
-How about after the match,
I'll take you on a date?
-Right.
Here I come.
-Hello, miss.
Are you all right?
-Oh, Ranma, just look at you.
Go rest and let me handle this.
-I agree, Akane.
I'll skate with you, OK?
-K.
-No way.
Ryoga's with me.
-Now what?
-You said you could
stand up, you jerk.
-I can, just not
for very long, OK?
-Here we go again.
ANNOUNCER: Here we go
again, ladies and gentlemen.
How will this couple fare
against the dreaded Good Bye
Whirl?
-Let go of her hand
and I'll stop spinning.
-Come on, let me go already.
-Let you go?
Think again.
-I'll make you.
-Now the grand finale.
You might've been hurt.
Are you all right?
ANNOUNCER: There it is.
The devastating Good Bye Whirl.
Yet another loving
couple is cruelly
separated before its time.
-Hear that?
-I guess they were never
meant to be together.
-How awful to be betrayed
by a man you trusted.
Your heart must be breaking.
Don't you fret, princess.
I'll take good care of you.
-Only in your dreams, pal.
-Does it hurt?
Does it hurt?
My Charlotte.
-Huh?
-You're Azusa's
little Charlotte.
-What?
Don't be ridiculous.
And don't distract me in
the middle of the match.
-Oh, no.
Azusa knows her
little Charlotte.
Look, that's her little collar.
-Ah, there must be some sort
of a horrible misunderstanding
or something.
-No, no, no.
There's no mistake.
Look at this.
Azusa knows because she
locked it with her little key.
That makes you my little
Charlotte for sure.
-I am now Charlotte.
You're confused, that's all.
I'll tell you my real name.
-It's P-Chan.
-That's right.
Who are you calling P-Chan?
-You like Charlotte better then?
Ranma, how dare you
embarrass me like this?
I won't allow it.
-You there, what are you
doing to my girlfriend?
-I ain't your
girlfriend, you jerk.
-My dear, you're as
innocent and naive as ever.
Huh?
-You've made a fool
of me in public
for the last time, Saotome.
-Hey, I just help you
do it to yourself.
-OK then.
Let's settle it once and for
all-- a skate to the death.
-You there, stop bullying
her and fight me.
-Oh, my Charlotte.
-Gotcha.
-Why'd you do that, you-- ah!
-Don't you hurt Azusa's
little Charlotte!
ANNOUNCER: Ladies
and gentleman, what
a startling turn of events.
Mikado Emperor
Sanzenin has just been
felled by his delightful
partner, Azusa Shiratori.
Will he be able to
recover in time?
-Cold water.
-I'm doomed.
-I'm a girl already
so I don't care.
But I guess you're
in trouble, huh?
RYOGA (VOICEOVER):
If I turn into a pig
while Akane's watching, I'm
going to end it right now.
ANNOUNCER: Th-- the
rink is destroyed.
-Don't look at Azusa.
-Mikado Sanzenin is now
being carried off the ice
by paramedics.
What does this mean for
the rest of the match?
His partner Azusa goes
to his side in concern.
-Cute blanket.
-You give that back to me.
I need it.
-You give Azusa back
her little Marteen now.
Marteen, Marteen, Marteen.
-Hm, what do you think?
-I'd say he's a goner.
Look it.
ANNOUNCER: That's it,
ladies and gentlemen.
That's all she wrote.
Kolhotz High's Golden Pair
has forfeited the match
to Furinkan High.
[rumbling]
-Uh oh.
-Ranma, it's not over yet.
Fight me.
-You mean right here?
-Yeah, right here.
-Any more bright ideas?
-Shut up.
-Come back here, Ryoga.
-Ranma?
That's enough, you guys.
-Huh?
-Oh, hi, Akane.
-We're busy.
Get lost.
-What is wrong with you two?
-I thought I told you
to butt out, Akane.
-Hey, wh-- what'd
I-- oh, never mind.
I want you to tell me why you
two hate each other so much.
-Oh, that's easy.
-I'll tell you everything,
Akane, after I defeat Ranma.
-What do you mean
after you beat me?
-Akane, no!
-Ah jeez, I told
her to butt out.
But she never listens.
Huh?
-You mean--
-She doesn't know how to swim?
Hey.
-Now what?
-You sure you want to do this?
[scream]
-Oh, Akane.
-Charlotte!
Charlotte, where are you?
Come to Azusa, Charlotte.
Come out.
Where are you?
Oh, Charlotte.
Oh, Oscar!
GIRL: Look, she's awake.
-Akane, are you OK?
-Catch.
-What happened to P-Chan?
Why he's soaking wet.
GIRL: He saved your life, Akane.
He pulled you from the pool.
-Nobody knows where
he came from though.
-Is that right?
Thanks a lot, P-Chan.
-Save some thanks for
Ryoga while you're at it.
-What?
-Hey, he helped drag you from
the pool too, you know, Akane.
-Oh.
-Speaking of which,
where is Ryoga now?
-I think he went
home, didn't he?
[whimper]
-Well, that's where we
should be going too.
AZUSA: Sweet dreams, Francoise.
Sweet dreams, Catherine.
Sweet dreams, Antoinette.
Sweet dreams, Marlene.
Sweet dreams, Michelle.
Sweet dreams, Felicia.
Sweet dreams, Georgina.
Sweet dreams, Rosalie.
Sweet dreams, Elizabeth.
Sweet dreams, Angeline.
Sweet dreams, Maryanne.
Sweet dreams, Janette.
Sweet dreams, Delphine.
Sweet dreams, Juliette.
And sweet dreams,
my little Oscar.
[grumble]
Oh, you're so cute!
[theme music]