[music playing]
[music - ribbon, "little date"]
NARRATOR: Meet Ranma
Saotome of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-Hey, let go!
-Hai-yah!
NARRATOR: And here's Akane
of the Tendo Training Hall.
-What are you doing?
NARRATOR: The two
have been engaged
to marry by their
loving parents.
-I didn't ask for this.
-Who asked you?
NARRATOR: As for the cause
of poor Ranma's suffering--
-What'd you do that for?
NARRATOR: When Ranma is
splashed with cold water,
he becomes a she.
All right, that's enough.
GENMA: This dojo is for
training, not brawling.
Show it some respect.
SOUN: Ranma, Akane, you're
both under a lot of pressure.
We know that.
Carrying on the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts
is not an easy thing.
Both of you have trained
hard, and it's only natural
that passion should run
high while training.
But you're not to use this
dojo as a boxing ring.
-Ranma, I'm concerned.
We've talked about this before.
Akane is your fiancee.
You should look out for her.
Martial arts is in the
fist, boy, it's in your gut.
Your gut, boy.
-She ain't my fiancee.
-So who'd want to be?
-You may have your little
misunderstandings now and then,
but someday, you'll come
to appreciate each other.
-Right.
The future of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts
depends on you.
Ranma, Akane, only
the two of you-- huh?
Ranma?
SOUN: Akane!
-Wait.
Please listen.
-Wait, please, listen.
-Sorry, Dad, but
I never asked you
to arrange an
engagement to Ranma.
-She's right.
[sobbing loudly]
-Ranma, I just want
what's best for you.
-Then why don't you listen
to me once in a while?
-But I listening!
Really, I am!
Please, boy, you must listen.
Believe me, please!
Oh, please!
-Gee, don't cry about it.
KASUMI: Father, come quickly!
-Huh?
NARRATOR: Danger
at the Tendo Dojo.
SOUN: "Saturday night,
I, the Dojo Destroyer,
shall come to
challenge your dojo."
That's tomorrow.
-Oh, that must be a joke!
Gee, I thought those kind of
guys were only in the movies.
-What did he look like, Kasumi?
-Oh, Father, I don't know.
Only the letter was here when
I got back from my shopping.
SOUN: "A wise man once said the
path of a true martial artist
is fraught with dangers.
The training is
nothing unless you're
prepared to lay your life on the
line to defend what is yours.
If you cannot meet my challenge,
then you were never meant to be
a martial artist in
the first place."
-Right.
The Anything Goes
School of Martial Arts
must accept any
challenge at any time.
SOUN: Right.
I, Soun Tendo, am a
true martial artist.
I would gladly lay
my life on the line.
Ahem, uhm, uh-- although
the Tendo Dojo now
belongs to Ranma and Akane,
so they must defend it.
GENMA: And that's
the way it must be.
You two must join forces
and defend our dojo.
-Me?
Work with Ranma?
RANMA: Yeah, I'd be
better off on my own.
-What's that mean, huh?
-Duh, Akane.
I can take him on myself.
You'd only slow me down.
-Well, is that so?
-Yeah, you're a slowpoke!
AKANE: So what if I'm
not as fast as you?
What's important is
defending the dojo,
and I can do that all by myself.
RANMA: Yeah?
You and what army?
-Excuse me?
-There's no excuse for you.
[angry sigh]
RANMA: Aw, face it, Akane.
The only thing you've
got working for you
is brute strength.
AKANE: Oh, you mean this
brute strength, Ranma?
-That's the spirit.
You must tap into
that energy when
you're fighting
the Dojo Destroyer.
Just remember, kids, two
heads are better than one.
I'm confident that
together you'll
come up with a plan to
defend your inheritance.
Akane, are you listening to me?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Hmph.
-I don't know.
Do you think those two
will cooperate, Saotome?
-You'll see, Tendo.
I'm sure they'll work it out.
All we can do now is
have a little faith.
They're not bad
kids, just stubborn.
SOUN: Oh, Saotome,
I hope you're right.
This outside threat may be
the only chance for the two
to join together.
GYM TEACHER: OK, next?
-Aaaaagghh!
-Huh?
STUDENT: Where'd she come from?
[kids chattering]
-Ni hao, Ranma!
-Can we help you?
-Hey, what are you doing here?
-Hmm.
You sure you want talk
to Shampoo like that?
-Huh?
-This one just normal water.
Watching careful now.
This one just normal dog, right?
[splashing]
[gasps]
STUDENT: Oh my!
STUDENT: The dog!
It turned into a guy!
-It-- it can't be!
SHAMPOO: Ta-dah!
Instant Nanniichuan.
Huh?
-Whatever fall in spring
take body of young boy.
Very tragic story.
This powder make
Instant Nanniichuan.
Ranma, you be normal man again.
STUDENT: You think
it's for real?
STUDENT: Well, why
wouldn't it be?
STUDENT: You mean
it's like bath salts?
RANMA: Vo: It's-- it's
too good to be true.
If she's telling
the truth, I can
be rid of this curse for good!
-So what's he got to
do for it, Shampoo.
-You smart girl.
Ranma, you date Shampoo?
-Huh?
-Take Shampoo to
date, you get powder.
You want go date?
-Sure!
-Hai-yah!
Then Shampoo meet
you today at park.
Two o'clock sharp.
Nyah!
-Aren't you forgetting
something, Ranma?
-Oh!
RANMA: Vo: That dojo
guy's coming today.
-Oh yeah.
Heh, you understand, don't you?
-Sure I do.
-Hey, thanks a lot.
And don't worry, you got that
brute strength, remember?
That dojo guy
ain't got a chance.
Silly me.
I forgot.
Hai-yah!
[thud]
-Hey, you two, there's
no need to play rough.
[panting]
-Oh, she always like that.
Hey, Ranma, is you OK?
Meet two o'clock
sharp in park, yes?
AKANE: Vo: I wouldn't
ask for his help
now if my life depended on it.
[singing] Never gonna
be a girl again.
Never gonna be a girl again.
SOUN: Ranma!
-Huh?
-Traitor.
Have you forgotten
what day today is?
Have you?
[laughs nervously]
AKANE: It's OK, Ranma.
Enjoy your date with
Shampoo, all right?
-Akane!
-Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
I'll take him with one hand.
You just watch me!
[smash]
-Well, I guess it's
time for me to go then.
I'll be rootin' for you.
[groans] Ah!
Ow!
-Akane, can you do
it all by yourself?
-[laughs] Of course I can.
Dad, like I said, I'll
take him with my left hand.
-I'd use both hands
if I were you.
-You're sure you can do it?
-Uh-- I can do it!
-Ranma!
Ranma!
-Shampoo!
[rings bicycle bell]
-Ni hao, Ranma!
-Heh, these are, uh, for you.
-Hai-yah! [inaudible].
-Heh, yeah.
Uh, give me the
magic powder now.
-Huh?
What exactly you mean?
-Come on, you know.
-Goodbye.
-Hey, don't go so soon.
-You only date Shampoo 'cause
you want Instant Nanniichuan.
RANMA: Vo: Well, duh.
I'm Hmph.
Gee, I was really
looking forward
to going out with you and all.
I wish you could trust me,
but it's OK if you don't.
SHAMPOO: Ranma?
Instant Nanniichuan
is here for you.
I give you after, OK?
-Shampoo--
-Shampoo believe you.
-Thank you.
-Aahhh!
[coughs]
RANMA: Vo: I'm sorry, Shampoo,
but this is too important
to take a chance on.
-Ooh, Ranma!
[singing] Never gonna
be a girl again.
[meow]
-Aaaaghhh!
[thud]
-So, Ranma, Shampoo not
so stupid to tell you
where Instant Nanniichuan is.
-You tricked me!
-Now are you convinced?
I wish you'd stop worrying, Dad.
I'm telling you, I can do this!
-Well, Father?
Do you think she can do it?
-Mmm, you know how stubborn
that girl can be sometimes.
[sigh]
-Ranma, don't forget date!
Two o'clock sharp in park, yes?
-Hai-yah!
[slow footsteps approaching]
DOJO DESTROYER: Open the gate.
-Hm?
-Why you fidget so?
-Huh?
-Is it Akane?
-Hah.
Yeah, right.
[crumples can]
-Forgive me, but I am
promised to another.
-Does she make you happy?
SHAMPOO: Don't worry, Ranma.
After date, I give you
Instant Nanniichuan.
-Uh?
Heh.
You really mean it?
-If you want end
date now, then--
-End it now!
Uh-huh!
-Then you give goodbye kiss.
-Kiss you?
Are you sure about that?
-Mhm.
Mhm.
-[gulp] Uh--
DOJO DESTROYER:
[menacing chuckle]
So many dojos, so little time.
This will be 1,000th
one I've destroyed.
Are you sure this
little one is up to it?
-You must fight her or forfeit.
DOJO DESTROYER: OK, then.
You'd better say goodbye
to it, because it
won't be yours for much longer.
-Grrr.
-No mercy, girl.
-Aaaahhhhh!
Hai-yah!
AKANE: Vo: I can do it!
--[laughs] Well, let's try
that one again, shall we?
AKANE: Hyah!
Aiiiii-yah!
[grunts with pain]
RANMA: Uh-- um--
-What wrong?
You no kiss?
RANMA: Vo: I gotta
get to to the dojo,
but-- aw, man, I'm so close.
OK, then.
RANMA: Shampoo?
-Oh, Ranma.
-Sorry about this.
-Ranma!
Ranma!
Date not over till we kiss.
You sure you want to run
away without real Instant Nanniichuan?
-What?
-No kiss, no get
real magic powder.
You really worry about Akane?
-Er-- no, I-- what
makes you think that?
SHAMPOO: Ranma, you
want ride on bike?
-[cries out]
-Akane!
-Dad, just-- just
please stay there!
Protecting the dojo is something
I have to do on my own.
-[growls]
-Hai-yah!
-Give up, girl.
-Aaaahhh!
Hyah!
[growls]
[bicycle bell rings]
-Ranma, we go check on Akane,
and then we finish date, right?
-Yep.
GENMA: Ranma!
So you've come back
after all, huh?
-Yeah, he'll be sorry he
ever heard of the Tendo Dojo.
-Guess this means you got
the Instant Nanniichuan, hey?
[splash]
-Why'd you do that?
[meow]
-Huh?
[rowr]
-Gah!
Get it offa me!
[meowing]
-Then again, maybe not.
-It's over.
Farewell.
-Akane!
-Aaaaauuughhh!
-Ranma!
-Huh?
You came to see her. her.
You care!
--[groans] Yeah, and it
looks like she's losing.
-I didn't ask for your help,
so why don't you just go away?
-I didn't come back to help you.
Not exactly.
Ooof!
-Whatever.
But right now, you're
no good to us as a girl.
[hums lightly]
RANMA: OK, pal.
-Hm?
-Now fight me.
-[menacing chuckle] As you wish.
I'll take the whole dojo on
in honor of my 1,000th sign.
-Let's go!
-Hey, this is my
fight, not yours.
Butt out!
-But look at you.
You're worn out!
[gasp]
[grunts]
[cries out]
-Huah!
-Ranma!
[whooshing]
GENMA: Use the Dual Jet
Stream Raging Waters attack.
-Saotome, you don't mean--
-I do.
It's the super-secret
technique of the Anything
Goes School of Martial Arts.
-(IN UNISON) Dual Jet
Stream Raging Waters attack!
[laughs]
RANMA: Here we go, Akane.
One, two--
-(IN UNISON) Three!
Hyaaaaahh!
-What?
AKANE: Ow!
Don't yank me around like that.
You're hurting my arms!
RANMA: Hey, I'm
doing the best I can.
Hang on tight.
Hey, watch that sign!
-(IN UNISON) Hyah!
-Oof!
Unh!
[sighs weakly]
[both panting]
-You've done well, you two.
-That's how fiances
are supposed to be.
-I can see that
the Anything Goes
School is in good
hands with these two.
RANMA: Vo: Yeah, whether
we like it or not.
-Yo, Akane, you OK?
-Of course, Ranma.
Like you care!
I didn't need your help.
I could have done it
all by myself, you know!
SHAMPOO: Ranma?
Let's pick up where we left off.
-Pick up where we what?
-Where we leave off date!
Where we leave off kiss.
-Huh?
-Hey, watch it!
I didn't do nothing!
-Ranma?
What does she mean, left off?
How dare you even begin!
RANMA: I didn't do nothing?
SHAMPOO: Why you so
shy all of a sudden?
SOUN: So, what did you
two do on this date?
Tell me what happened, son!
-Uh, nothing!
-You kissed her?
-No!
-She kissed you?
-No way!
SHAMPOO: Shampoo get all
tingly when she think about
it. "I love you big-time."
He say that to me.
And then--
-Hey!
Hey, hey!
-You kiss so sweet!
-Uh--
-Here.
Instant Nanniichuan.
-Really?
I can have it?
All right!
Now I can be a guy for good!
Yeah!
AKANE: Ranma.
Thank you for your help.
I really mean it.
-Huh?
W-wait!
You know I didn't
really kiss her, right?
She only said that 'cause--
[smack]
-Ow!
[groans]
[dog barking]
[bubbling]
NABIKI: How long are you
two gonna sit in there?
KASUMI: Yes, come in.
The food's getting cold.
-Just let them be.
-I've never seen them so happy.
-I ain't a girl.
-I'm not a panda.
SHAMPOO: Thank you!
Come again.
[hums]
-Shampoo, I admire you.
You kept that idiot son-in-law's
attention for an entire day
with nothing but a
one-time-only quack remedy.
-That one day to
remember. [giggles]
-Come in, you'll catch a cold.
[sobbing]
SOUN: Just let them be.
-She tricked me.
That's what she did.
I'll get you for this, Shampoo.
Somebody's gonna pay for this!
[MUSIC - ETSUKO NISHIO, "DON'T
MIND CHINA BOY"]
NARRATOR: A
mysterious invitation
from a Chinese acrobat troupe?
Hey, that's no ordinary duck!
-Help me, Ranma!
NARRATOR: Next time on "Ranma
1/2," the abduction of Akane.
See you there.