[FARIA] Madams and Messieurs,
good evening.
My friend invited three
families to his villa,
where a forbidden
past lay dormant.
When that soul which
had been interred there
returned to life...
...I sensed clearly that a new
vengeance was about to sprout.
Somebody!
It's an emergency!
Somebody, send for a doctor!
What's the matter, Albert?
Oh, Marquise,
it's Madame Danglars!
She got sick and collapsed!
[VILLEFORT]
Enough is enough!
What the hell
are you after, Sir?!
Just what is your game?!
[MONTE CRISTO laughs]
Surely you jest.
I can assure you that
my only goal tonight is
to have all my guests enjoy
the party I've thrown for them.
You've gone too far!
I'm sure you know this
manor was originally owned
by my father-in-law.
If you're deliberately trying
to insult me, You'll regret it!
[MONTE CRISTO laughs]
Even though I was
unaware of that fact,
it seems I have
indeed been most rude.
But still this is
a most fascinating...
...not to mention a
most odd, coincidence.
Which means, that
this place must be
as familiar to you as
the back of your hand.
Isn't that right Monsieur?
In which case, my humble attempt
to entertain you all
was unfair from the start.
This just won't do.
Shall we start over
and try our game again?
[MERCEDES]
Albert.
What in the world happened
to Madame Danglars?
I'm not sure.
All of us were going along
and playing the Count's game.
I was about to give
Madame Victoria the box
with the prize in it,
and the instant I did, she--
I just don't know,
why she fainted.
I don't understand
how this can be...
Poor boy...
...forgive me...
[MONTE CRISTO] It seems
to be a case of anemia.
It's nothing serious.
[VILLEFORT]
I ask you again.
Who are you?
Where did you come from?
Precisely what do you know?
Your life depends
on your answer.
Answer me!
I am but a poor soul from the
far reaches of Eastern Space.
Other than that, I have
no past worth speaking of.
None at all.
[DANGLARS]
Victoria!
What's happened to her?!
You needn't
worry yourself.
She's merely
feeling out of sorts.
Victoria! Oh, Victoria!
Please monsieur,
I'm sure a moments' rest
will have her
feeling much better.
Don't you agree, Monsieur?
Where's Eugenie?
We gotta go find her!
[ALBERT]
Eugenie!
[FRANZ]
Eugenie! Where are you?!
Hey! Mother!
Where are you?
Eugenie answer me!
You there!
Do you know
where Eugenie is?
She's Monsieur
Danglars' daughter.
You know Sir, I've
heard quite a few stories
about you from the Count.
All sorts of things.
So, you're young Albert,
son of General Morcerf.
[ANDREA laughs]
Where's Eugenie?
I thought she was with you?!
She's already headed
towards the inner chambers,
she's walking
with your father.
Now, Albert, you need
to understand something.
Huh?
Of all the people who
live in this sorry world,
I'm the only one
capable of understanding
the inner workings
of the Count's heart.
Wha--?
Now, if you'll excuse me.
[ANDREA laughs]
Excellency!
Sir! Give me your hand!
Thank you,
Good Bertuccio...
[FRANZ thinking]
What are those markings?
I'd tell you to rest,
but I'd probably
be wasting my breath.
Are you willing
to follow me...?
Into the dark
depths of Hell?
Of course- I'll be at your side
wherever you go, Gankutsuou.
Gan... kutsu... ou?
How do you feel, Mother...
Much better, Dear.
I'm fine now.
I'm sorry if I worried you.
Valentine!
Albert!
I'm really sorry
about the other day.
I guess I got kind
of carried away.
I'm the one
who should apologize.
I said such rude things.
Well no matter what,
I... ...think it's nice
that you two can have a
normal conversation again.
I realized... that
I had misjudged him.
I'm so glad we had
this chance to talk.
I'm very grateful.
I feel the
very same way.
Well then...
Now that the excitement's
over, I'm feeling kinda--
[ALBERT grimaces]
[VALANTINE]
Albert?
[VALANTINE screams]
[MAXIMILIEN]
Monsieur Albert?
Hold on we'll get you help!
Monsieur Albert!
Well, now.
How are you feeling?
It feels like a big weight on
my chest has been lifted off.
I am glad to hear it.
I mixed this medicine
especially for you.
There is nothing better for
the treatment of chest pains.
I apologize if I made any
trouble for you, Excellency.
I don't know
what happened to me.
I just suddenly felt sick.
[FRANZ] I'm worried
about Albert.
What could be
wrong with him?
I've known him since
we were just kids,
and he's never had
so much as a mild cold.
You and Albert were
the closest of friends
even when you were young
children weren't you?
Yeah.
Mademoiselle Valentine
told me all about it.
She told me that
she's always been jealous
of how close you two are
and how she wishes she had
the same thing in her life.
It's just 'cause we've
known each other for so long.
You know I don't think it's
just because you're old friends.
Huh?
I somehow get the
distinct impression
that you share a special bond
that no one else can understand.
Speaking of
sharing special bonds
how long have you
desired Valentine?
Well, that's a rather
awkward question
to be asked by her fiancé.
Oh... Of course,
you're right. I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
I am the one who
is at fault here.
But...
...if you truly love her, then
that should be all that matters.
There you go,
saying such irresponsible
things yet again...
Irresponsible?
Well...
I suppose it is.
This is all very
strange to me, Franz.
Why is it that you can't
love Mademoiselle Valentine?
She's your fiancé.
Yeah, and what about you?
Will you stop loving her just
because you can't marry her?
Well, I, uh...
You can't, can you?
You can't simply
fall out of love...
Even if the
relationship is such that,
you can't marry the person
no matter what you desire.
Are you saying that you
harbor a hopeless love
for someone, too?
Getting married isn't
necessarily the only way
to bring
a person happiness.
Don't you think?
I hadn't thought of that...
Maybe you're right
about that, Franz
Valentine's found
herself a great guy.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Albert.
[ALBERT]
Sir?
I realize that this must
seem like an odd request,
but I'd like to know
what you've eaten today.
Actually, I've been
so busy today
I haven't eaten
anything at all.
But you know Sir,
now that you mention it,
I drank some water from the
table with the blue flowers.
The table with blue flowers
was the Villefort family's.
Yes I know.
What's that got
to do with this?
Albert, I would like you
to remain calm and listen.
The thing that's been
attacking your body is a...
...strong poison.
Poison?
That's right, a fearful
poison that comes
from Eastern Space that is
commonly know as "zhen-du."
Are you telling me that
the water was poisoned?
That would be a
safe assumption.
I think you were able to
survive because the ice melted,
thus diluting
the deadly poison.
You had a very
close call.
But who would want do
a thing like that to me?
I suspect that you
were not the target.
Oh, I see.
The poison was mixed
into the water pitcher
that was on the table,
which means that the real
target was the Villefort family.
But why would they do that?
Feelings of hatred and
jealousy towards another.
They are emotions which
silently fester and grow,
unbeknownst to the
person who feels them.
The happier that person is,
the less aware he
is of these feelings.
However, their attempt at
murder ended in utter failure.
Which means they
will try again.
They can't!
The Villeforts are good people
that I care about deeply.
Albert what are you doing?
Are you sure you
should be out of bed yet?
[ALBERT]
I feel fine now.
Sorry I made you worry.
Still, I really think
that you should try
to take it easy for
awhile.
I must agree with
Franz, Monsieur Albert.
No, we have to hurry.
I'll explain it
all to you later.
But right now we have to get
over to Valentine's house.
To Mademoiselle
Valentine's house?
Yeah.
[HELOISE] You're such
a frightening man...
At the same time you
are very, very alluring...
[VILLEFORT] Are we
clear on this, Boville?
Use every network
at your disposal
and find out everything
there is to know about him.
I believe he comes
from Marseilles.
Start the
investigation there.
[BOVILLE]
Right...
Mark my words,
I'll find out who you are.
Count of Monte Cristo, my ass.
Your honor, please
excuse my curiosity...
but what is your connection
to this mystery man?
That is nothing you need
concern yourself about.
Yes, sir.
But I suggest that you be
mindful of any household rats.
I will be I assure you!
Good.
[VALANTINE]
Look, Grandfather.
Isn't this a beautiful cross?
Pardon me, Mademoiselle...
I thought you might
want something to drink.
Thank you, Valois.
[FRANZ] Are you sure
about this Albert?
Someone's trying to
kill the Villefort family?
Don't you think the Count
is reading too much into this?
No, not at all.
He's a smart man.
And I believe him.
Franz... Listen to me...
Can I tell you something?
It sounds serious.
What the matter Albert?
See, the thing is, I think
I finally figured it out.
All right, what is it?
You just might laugh at me
for saying this to you, Franz,
but I really do think that
it's important for two people
to love each other
when they're married
What's gotten into you?
What brought this on?
Well, it's...
It's just...
It's just that I really want
Valentine and Maximilien
to be happy together.
I know it's more complicated
than that for you.
No it's not complicated.
I want the same thing
with all my heart.
If it's humanly possible,
I think two people
who love each other
should always be together.
You do?
The love those two
have is the real thing.
I want them to be happy.
No way is anyone
poisoning her!
The rain certainly seems to have
gotten stronger Mademoiselle...
Whew, it's rather
humid, isn't it?
You must be hot, Valois.
Would you
like a glass, too?
Uh... Oh no,
I couldn't possibly...
It's all right,
don't stand on ceremony.
Oh my! Valois!
Valois, what's
the matter with you?!
Speak to me!!
M-Mademoiselle...
Valois?
Valois!
Wha... What's wrong?
[VALANTINE crying]
Grandfather what's
happening to me?
Hurry!
Hurry and call the doctor!
Mademoiselle Valentine...!
How can this be happening?
Mademoiselle Valentine!
I can't believe it.
It's just like the Count said.
I don't understand what
the hell is going on here!
Just wait here.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Where else?
To go over and talk to the
Count about what's going on.
He might be able to do
something to help her!
Like he helped me!
Hey wait! Albert!
Oh, Albert...
Of course, I'll be at your side
wherever you go, Gankutsuou.
Monsieur,
His Excellency is away
on a business trip
at the moment.
Sorry.
You've got to be kidding!
When will he be back?
I am afraid that is
entirely up to His Excellency.
I'm sorry I cannot
be of more help.
Well, well, I see
that as always
you are completely helpless
when you're all by yourself.
You!
I'm looking forward to
seeing how this all turns out.
And what does that mean?
Do you have the courage to
learn what the future holds?
I don't understand.
Who are you?
Damn it! What am
I supposed to do now?!
Don't die, Please
don't die Valentine!
You child of illicit love who
has awoken from a dark dream...
...and come back to life
from the depths of death...
You beautiful child who
knows nothing of love,
nor of being loved.
Thou art anathema.
Thou art anathema!
[ALBERT] A dark
cloud spreads out
like a stain to cover our lives.
And a letter arrives
from an old friend
who was thought to be dead.
Next Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo,
Act 10: "The Letter
From Edmond."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!