[FARIA] Madams and
Messieurs, good evening.
Poison has taken
a beautiful girl
and turned her into
a sleeping beauty.
A letter from a dead
man led three men
back to dark and
loathsome memories.
I can hear it, the beautiful
melody entitled "Nightmare"
that my friend is playing...
My Papa's here.
Now you're gonna get it.
Please step aside, Madame.
No I won't.
I'm begging you!
Huh!
What's the matter? Madame?
Mama!
Mama, what's wrong?
What's the matter with me...?
I don't understand--
Renaud! Go get the car!
Huh? Right!
Heloise?
Heloise!
You! Get after those three!
They took my daughter!
I can't believe
he's shooting at us!
Faster!
All right, watch this!
Renaud?
Albert! Block the road!
Huh!
Ahhhh!!
Okay, that should do it.
Ow! Why'd you do that?!
You're really lucky.
It could have been
something serious.
Oh, I wish you
wouldn't worry me so...
Aw, come on! Quit it!
I do hope you realize that
what you guys did is usually
referred to as "kidnapping"
and is very illegal!
Like you're one to talk!
Once people know
why we did it,
I'm pretty sure
they'll understand.
But it's gonna be
Monsieur Villefort
who tries the case.
...won't it?
Yeah.
The dead man has once
again come back to us!
Edmond would never
forget what we did to him.
Even from beyond the grave.
Can't you sleep?
No. It's just that today
was a terrible day.
By the way, where did
you go this morning?
I went to a funeral.
Don't lie to me.
A letter from Edmond
came this morning, right?
How did you know that?
I want you to tell me
what this is all about.
It was just a tasteless prank.
But why would anyone
use that name for a prank?
It makes no sense!
I really have no idea!
Now, Edmond was
accused of treason
and died in the far
reaches of space, didn't he?
Isn't that what happened?
Answer me!
If you know
anything else, tell me.
Please, Fernand, tell me.
He's dead and long gone.
You're hiding something from me.
I can see it in your eyes!
I'm telling you
the man is dead!
I'm not hiding
anything from you.
He died in a
prison long time ago!
You still can't forget what
happened 20 years ago, can you?!
Can you?!
I demand you
answer me right now!
Have you been
thinking about
that man every day
of the past 20 years?!
Tell me!!
Are you still in
love with him?!
In love with a ghost?!!
It was only because I was
told that he was dead that I...
You only did what...
You were told he was dead,
so you gave up on him
and married me instead?
Is that it?!
Stop it.
Mercedes...
MERCEDES!
The crime lab has determined
that the cause
was a strong poison.
It's some sort
of botanical toxin.
We're trying to identify it.
I see.
Your Honor, I suggest that
you exercise extreme caution.
The culprit might
still be in the house.
I've already dismissed
all the servants.
You don't need
to worry about me.
But sir-- I really think...
There are two things
that you must do now.
The first is to prevent any
news of this from leaking.
The second is my daughter.
Find out where she's
been taken without delay!
The search team arrived
in Marseilles this morning
and has begun their work.
They'll find her
before today is finished.
Notify me when they do.
We have an arrest warrant
for the perpetrators
is standing by.
No, just pinpoint
where they are for now.
Leave them alone
for the time being.
Yes, sir.
Franz?
Albert, what's wrong?
I really wasn't
expecting you to be here.
So Albert, is there some reason
why you don't
want to go home?
Not really.
Want to read this letter?
Who's it from?
Maximilien?
He sure has
neat handwriting.
Yeah, as opposed
to you.
You're pushing it,
all right?
So I guess he made
it to Marseilles safely.
Yeah, and I'll bet
he's totally freaking out
over what he's
done right about now.
That's very possible.
[FRANZ and ALBERT laughing]
Hey...
Hm?
What kind of person
is Madame Heloise?
What's Valentine's
step-mother really like?
Well, She's a beautiful,
young, intelligent woman.
Yeah, she is, huh?
That's what I was
thinking, too.
Albert, can I ask
you something?
Yeah, go ahead.
You said that you
saw Madame Villefort
and the Count in the
greenhouse together...
What about it?
Ever since you told
me about it at Auteuil,
it's been nagging at me.
It means that--
Means what?
What're you getting at?
Well, why did
the Count happen
to pick her to
have an affair with?
I'm starting to think he
targeted her specifically
and made his move on her.
And how is it that he took
one look at your symptoms
and knew right
away it was poison?
Hey wait!
Are you trying to imply
that the Count is the
one behind all this?!
I don't believe that!
I don't believe
that for a minute!
Because of him, I'm alive
and standing here right now!
Just listen to me, Albert.
Even if you looked
all over Paris,
you wouldn't find very many
people who would conveniently
have antitoxins on them.
Not even doctors!
So? Were you able
to save my life, Franz?
You couldn't help, am I right?!
The only reason
I survived that night was
because the Count was there!
What could the Count
possibly hope to gain
by trying to poison everybody?
Tell me!
I don't know.
But I can sense it...
Can sense what?
A deep darkness...
Sorry to bother you.
Albert, wait! Please!
Take a good look
at the real Count!
Franz.
Whatever you say,
I have faith in him.
There's only one person
who knows the real Count...
That person's me!
So, there you are.
You've come around...
What happened?
I can't remember anything.
My memory's a jumble...
Really...
My head.
I can't seem to
shake off this feeling...
That's because of the
poison, don't you think?
Poison?
Yes.
There's a fair amount
of poison coursing through
your body right now.
Tell me.
When did you get that
ring from the Count?
What do you mean?
I hope that you're not
trying to imply anything...
Not at all.
I'll rephrase my question.
Have you ever
seen this before?
I I have no idea
what that is.
I found it in
your jewelry box.
Perhaps it's merely
a perfume bottle...
I don't know.
That bottle isn't mine!
Stupid fool!
What's wrong with you?
Are you trying to ruin me?
You realize that
what you've done
will never be able
to be made right.
If it were ever to get out
that my wife is a murderer,
what do you think
would happen to me
and everything that
I've built throughout my life?!
Your plans haven't run
their course yet, have they?
Who else did you poison?
Valentine?
Answer me!
How many more
do you plan to kill?!
Is my name on your list?
Were you planning
to kill me too?
Yes that's right!
I had intended
to kill you, too!
I only need my sweet darling
son Edouard to be happy!
Look at you, acting
so high and mighty!
I won't stand for
all these insults!
You know what,
I dare you to speak to me
with that tone
in your voice again!
I'll kill myself right here!
To the mighty Prosecutor
who values appearances
more than anything there
could be no greater scandal!
You don't mean
to suggest I--
What's the matter?
Aren't you going
to drink it?
What kind of
man are you?
Are you only capable
of killing other people?
Tomorrow morning, you
will be taken to a hospital.
I've had a private room with
barred windows prepared for you.
The quarters won't
be very spacious,
but you will spend the
rest of your days there.
Along with your poisons.
[HELOISE crying]
Albert, wait! Please!
Take a good look
at the real Count!
I know the real Count better
than anyone else on Earth.
I know it!
Excellency!
Greetings, Monsieur Albert.
Are you feeling well today?
I am, thank you.
You seem in rather high spirits.
So, I take it that Mademoiselle
Valentine was saved?
Yes.
She's recuperating
in Marseilles now
with Maximilien
watching over her.
That is wonderful news.
Yes but we got there
too late to save Valois,
he died before we arrived.
Don't forget that you
were able to save the life
of your dear friend Valentine.
You've nothing
to feel sad about.
Madame Villefort has
had a mental breakdown...
Count, why do you think
those horrible things happened
to the Villefort family?
It seems terribly unfair.
It was inevitable.
There are no coincidences
in the real world.
It all comes down to karma.
What do you mean
by that, your Excellency?
Are you saying that
the Villeforts deserved
what happened to them?
You recall that day on
Luna when you and I met?
Perhaps you feel that our
meeting was a chance encounter.
But in fate, there
are no coincidences.
Just as that setting
sun does so according
to the laws of the universe,
fate, too, is composed of the
powerful natural forces
of unyielding necessity.
There's no such thing
as coincidence in
your life, Excellency?
No. There is not.
What I have is the
power of strong will.
Even if other people accept
coincidences in their lives
and are tossed about
by them, I do not.
For you see, I have
forged my own destiny
through the power
of my own will.
Forged your destiny through
the power of your will...
That is why you and
I were brought together,
and why you and I sit here now.
Excellency, I want
to change my life.
To be a strong
man just like you.
In that case, please allow me
to offer you these
simple words of advice.
You must bide your time.
And hold out hope.
You must bide your time...
Albert!
Why do you have that idiotic
expression on your face?
Eugenie?
How's your mother doing?
It's nothing serious.
But she's been in a
bad mood ever since.
Oh.
Enough about that,
listen to this!
I've been invited
to play the piano
at the concert hall
with the orchestra!
At the opera house?
That's right! My dream
is finally coming true.
I just got the good news!
They've recognized
I have talent on the piano!
Hey that's great!
Come and hear me play, okay?
You bet.
That's so amazing!
Well, I should get back
and practice some more.
Uh, Eugenie?
Hm?
When you played for
us that night at Auteuil...
It was really...
Well, It was wonderful.
So you were paying attention?
I'm happy. Thanks a lot Albert.
Bye...
Flowers have arrived
for you, Mademoiselle.
Andrea Cavalcanti?
Hm!
Hello! I'm home!
What's the matter?
Take a look at this.
Danglars says that he has
decided it would be best
to break off your
engagement to Eugenie.
But why?
[ALBERT] I have to
know how she really feels.
So I run to the opera house.
I have to know
how I really feel.
Next Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo
Act 12: "Encore."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!