[NARRATOR] Madames and
Messieurs, good evening.
Everything lies in ruin.
What was once believed
to be solid ground
has opened up and
swallowed everything.
The young soul
wanders aimlessly,
betrayed by everything
he had believed in.
But then in the end what
he clutches tightest to is...
[ALBERT] Someone taught me
the meaning of the word hope.
Count, that someone was you!
[FRANZ]
Wait for me, Albert!
[MAID B]
Mademoiselle.
Pardon me but a
letter's arrived for you.
Thanks, I'll take it.
[ALBERT]
Why aren't you saying anything?
[ALBERT] Why are you just
standing there not answering me?
I think I understand.
My words now fall on deaf ears.
Is that... Is that what
you're trying to say?!
[MONTE CRISTO]
I once told you
that there is no such
thing as coincidence.
It's the very first
thing I told you.
Everything happens
out of necessity.
What is it you're
trying to say to me?
[MONTE CRISTO] Tell me,
Albert, if Haidee were not
a living witness to your
father's true identity...
...what value would
there be in keeping her
with me all this time?
[HAIDEE gasps]
[ALBERT gasps]
[MONTE CRISTO] Tell me, if you
were not Fernand Mondego's son,
why would it have
been necessary for me
to meet you the
way I did on Luna?
Can't be...
So From the beginning,
you were only just using me?
[MONTE CRISTO]
That's right.
I met you under a convenient
pretense of coincidence.
I took full advantage of
our so-called "friendship"
a task made easy by the
unshaking faith you had in it.
That's what I'm saying.
I even used props such as
the watch you're holding.
[ALBERT]
Can't be...
So from the beginning,
you were only just using me?
Liar! You're lying!
You're lying!
I can't believe
what you're saying.
It's been a set up
from the beginning?
It's not true!
[ALBERT] I mean, haven't you
always gone out of your way
to help me when I needed it?
Haven't you been looking out
for me and giving me advice?
I just don't believe that all
of the time we spent together
since we met was nothing
more than a big lie!
It can't be!
[MONTE CRISTO chuckles]
You poor, foolish boy.
You still wish to remain
completely immersed
in those childish and
naive delusions of yours?
[MONTE CRSITO] Is that what
you are trying to say?
Even though I
deliberately brought you
with me on that extended
pleasure cruise that day,
knowing full well
that Haidee was about
to disclose the truth
to the Assembly?
[MONTE CRISTO laughing]
I thank you...
You have been most useful
to me in the short time
that we have known each other.
I am forever... grateful to you.
I challenge you!
[MONTE CRISTO]
My, how old-fashioned.
The son of a soldier must act
in accordance with tradition...
Is that what you're doing now?
[ALBERT] The time will be
tomorrow morning at 5AM...
...in the forest of Boulogne.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Weapons?
Full armor and Long-swords.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Very well.
Bertuccio. You are my
witness in this matter.
Did you see the whole challenge
from beginning to end?
Yes, Count!
Fine Albert!
I accept your challenge.
I'll see you tomorrow
morning at five!
[ALBERT grunts]
[MONTE CRISTO]
It's a way to keep this day,
this very hour
stuck fast in time.
[MERCEDES]
I must go to see him.
Without delay.
[HAIDEE] Excellency, is
there nothing I can do
or say that will persuade
you to stop this duel
between you and Albert?
On the first day
I met you told me
that I am free to do as I wish.
That is what allowed me to live
to this day without
taking my own life.
But if you...
If you were to perish amidst
all this horrible ugliness...
I wouldn't...
...be able to go on living.
[MONTE CRISTO groaning]
[MONTE CRISTO]
Gankutsuou... Wait... Not yet!
No... It's not... yet time!
Is that Franz?
That's Albert!
[BOTH panting]
[ALBERT]
I'm sorry...
You've always been
looking out for me...
...but I'd always plunge ahead
with what I was doing,
ignoring your advice.
I'm so... sorry Franz.
I'm sorry.
Well I'm back now.
Welcome home Franz.
Just wipe off your nose.
Don't boss me, Franz
[FRANZ]
You idiot!
Don't you realize you
played right into his hands!
Albert you've got to call
off this duel right away!
[ALBERT]
Cut it out!
I know you don't
want me to do this
but I want you
to act as my second.
I don't blame you for
being angry with me.
But Franz you've got to
understand this is one thing
that I have to see through,
no matter what!
Albert listen to me.
I'm certain that the
Count has been planning
to kill you all along.
Are you saying
that you don't care
if you end up dead for
the sake of his revenge?!
Stop it Franz.
That bastard lied to me
and used dirty tricks
in order to lure me in.
He used the most despicable
means imaginable
to toy with me and turn
my life upside-down.
And I can't...
I can't let him
get away with it!
[FRANZ] Would you still
feel that way even if
that fake count used to
be your mother's fiancé?
[FRANZ]
The fact is,
your father was so in
love with your mother,
that 25 years ago,
he framed the Count
for a crime he didn't commit and
took his fiancée away by force.
Edmond Dantes?
[BERTUCCIO] Mondego's wife
is here to see you.
[MERCEDES]
Edmond!
I mean, Excellency...
But you really are
Edmond Danes, aren't you?
Oh, how I've missed you...
I was lost without you.
But you were in my heart.
These past 25 years, I haven't
forgotten you for an instant.
[MERCEDES] I know that
you can never forgive me
for what I've done.
But...
But even...
...even if it's only
one more time,
I wish that I could
speak to you as Edmond!
[MERCEDES sobbing]
[MERCEDES gasps]
[MONTE CRISTO]
Edmond... is dead.
This body retains only
his shape and appearance.
There is no longer anything of
Edmond himself left within it.
It's not true.
No! It isn't possible!
[MERCEDES] If that were
the truth, why have I had
the feeling ever since the day
we met that you are Edmond?
[MONTE CRISTO]
You refuse to be disturbed
by the coldness of my hand...
You leave me no choice, then.
I will show you absolute
proof that Edmond Dantes,
the man you once loved,
is dead and gone forever.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Until 5AM tomorrow morning
in the forest of Boulogne.
[ALBERT]
It's already too late, Franz.
[FRANZ gasps]
[ALBERT] Too late to do
anything about that!
You see whatever
happened between the Count
and my parents
belongs in the past.
I couldn't care less about
any of that stuff anymore!
But I can't forgive
what happened
with me and the Count.
And I won't just let that go.
[ALBERT]
If he hates me that much,
then he should just
go ahead and kill me
and be done with it!
Damn it!
The Count, the bastard.
He played with my feelings!
Albert! Don't do it! Don't go!
Come back!
Albert!
[FRANZ]
Please, come back...
You're still going to see him,
even though he
might kill you?
[ALBERT yelling]
[ALBERT panting]
Eugenie!
Oh you're back! That's great!
Welcome home!
So is Albert here?
Uh... No. But I was
with him a little while ago.
He said he had
something to take care of.
Oh, he did?
At least you're here.
I haven't been able to reach you
since that day you left Paris.
Well I'm sorry
that I worried you.
[EUGENIE]
Honestly, Franz.
I was just worried
sick about you.
Oh, but you timed
your return back
to Paris just perfectly.
Hm?
Oh Franz, don't you remember?
Tomorrow is
Albert's 16th birthday!
Uh... Yeah, exactly!
I knew that.
That's the reason why
I came over here to see you!
Geez, get your
act together. Okay?
By the way.
I wrote a new
song just for Albert!
[EUGENIE]
But it's not finished yet.
[piano playing]
What do you think?
Mm. It's nice.
It's very romantic.
Really not like you at all.
What do you mean?!
Don't be rude!
[FRANZ laughing]
[EUGENIE giggling]
[FRANZ]
Well, It's settled!
Tomorrow the three of us will
have a party at our usual cafe!
I can't. I'm sorry.
[FRANZ]
Just say that a friend of yours
is having a recital or
something, and sneak out.
I'm sure it'll work out.
[EUGENIE]
I'll do it.
[FRANZ] Eugenie, do you think
you can do me a little favor?
[EUGENIE]
What kind?
[FRANZ]
I wrote a personal message
in a birthday card for Albert,
but, I feel like...
...I think we're a little too
old for that kind of thing
so I feel awkward.
Idiot, who cares
how old you are?
It's just a card.
I suppose you're right.
Anyway, would you
give it to Albert for me
after I leave tomorrow?
Please? I'm begging you.
Must be a surprise. Okay, sure.
I'll do it.
I think I'm gonna keep working
on that song for a while.
[FRANZ]
You have fun.
I'll see you
tomorrow at 3, then.
At our usual cafe.
Thanks for coming to visit.
I really appreciate it.
[BERTUCCIO]
Excellency.
I uh...
[MONTE CRISTO]
What is it?
[BERTUCCIO]
Good luck, Monsieur.
[ALBERT] Let's drink to
victory with a fine red!
[FRANZ]
I'll have the white!
[ALBERT] But that guy up
there is pitch-black!
[BOTH]
To victory!
[ALBERT]
Yeaaaah!
[ALBERT] I'm gonna mop the
floor with that coward!
Just you watch me do it!
The Count is no one to fear!
[ALBERT laughing]
[BOTH laughing]
[ALBERT snoring]
[ALBERT] The clash of steel
shatters the dawn silence.
Sword of righteous
anger in hand,
I shall cut through
all deception and lies!
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 18:
"The Duel".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!