[FARIA] Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
When he goes to
visit his fiancée,
the young man sees
a young woman struggling
to fight against her destiny.
However, neither
of them is yet aware
of the cruel fate that is
silently bearing down upon them.
♪ operatic music ♪
[AUDIENCE applause]
Uh hey!
♪ operatic music ♪
Excellency!
Albert.
What happened to her?
She is not feeling well.
Haidee is
unaccustomed to crowds.
It is nothing you
should worry about.
We will meet again, later.
♪ operatic music  ♪
[FRANZ]
Let's go back in.
Okay?
I just wonder
what Haidee saw?
She looked as if
she'd seen a--
♪
[MONTE CRISTO] You saw him?
You saw that man?
♪ operatic music ♪
I've uh, heard
that you're engaged
to be married...
That's right.
[MAXIMILIEN]
Are you happy?
Huh?
I'm sorry,
but I, uh...
I don't think...
...I'll be able to
restrain myself tonight.
So Mademoiselle...
Please excuse me.
[ALBERT] I wonder
if Haidee is okay?
Oh come on, Albert,
who cares about
the Count's mistress?
It's not like that.
He cares for her.
He always treats
her with respect
and he's very kind to her.
Like a master is kind
towards his pet dog.
Don't put Excellency on the
same level as people like that!
The Count and
Haidee have... Um...
A relationship as
two independent adults.
Where they both care
for each other and--
Forget about them.
What about you
and your woman?
How do you feel
about Eugenie?
You're not one
to be asking that.
Aristocrats.
We don't marry for love,
we marry for money
and honor and... power.
Albert, is what Maximilien
said still bothering you?
I hate to admit it.
But he was right.
That's how marriages
work, you know?
I'm not getting married
because I want to, either.
[FRANZ gasps]
[ALBERT gasps]
[MAXIMILIEN] Baron Franz
d'Epinay! I'd like a word.
Monsieur why aren't you out
there with your fiancée?
How is that any
business of yours!
Don't you
love her, Baron?!
I like her. I like her
as just another girl.
[MAXIMILIEN gasps]
How can you talk
like that?!
[ALBERT] Wait a minute,
Maximilien!
You just let me
handle this, Franz. Okay?
You should love her!
She's your fiancée,
you should love her
with all your heart!
You didn't have
to say it like that.
I just said
what was on my mind.
[ALBERT] You're
too irresponsible.
But you're
always like that.
I guess I'm no different.
I've never been in
love with anyone,
at least not in the same way
that the Maximillien is.
I'm curious.
What do you think it means
to be in love with someone?
It's nothing but trouble.
I'll let you do what you
can to straighten this out.
What? Hey!
Wait!
Let's do it.
Whew.
I can't do this...
I don't believe this.
What are you
talking about?
Just do it like we planned,
and you'll have no problems.
First... you should try
paying her a compliment!
Compliment? On what?
Anything you can think of!
You know, like her
dress and her makeup!
That's Crown
Prosecutor Villefort.
He's kind of scary.
Even Petty crooks get death
when they come before him.
[ALBERT] That's
Valantine's mother.
Though, they're
not related by blood.
Edouard!
Come here this instant!
No! Lemme go!
[ALBERT] That's Edouard,
her younger brother.
He and Valantine
have different mothers.
Let go!!
Oh, look! These horses
are beautiful, aren't they?
I hate horses!
I'm so sorry.
He can be so willful
sometimes - it's embarrassing.
Is Valantine coming?
I'm afraid not.
That girl seems to prefer
staying home by herself.
I hate Valantine, too!
Humph.
They'll be coming soon.
Don't worry it's
nothing, Grandfather.
[VALOIS]
Mademoiselle...
Yes.
The Viscount Albert
de Morcerf is here
and wishes to see you.
Oh, hi.
About last night... Uh...
I think...
...he has something that
he wants to say to you.
Go on.
Um... well... I...
I'm sorry, I really have to go
and prepare my
grandfather's dinner...
Ah! Hey please! Wait!
I'm in--
I've fallen...
I've fallen in love with you!
Oh my God!
I love you!
Hey!
Geez! Way to throw
our plans out the window!
That's enough from you!
I'll talk to her first.
So you go wait over there!
I love you!
I think she knows that!
[ALBERT] I'm sorry
if we startled you.
This wasn't
what we had in mind.
[Valantine] He must have
been making fun of me.
Valantine, he meant
every word he said.
But why, would
he tell me now?
Look, Maximilien
meant what he told you.
He's just a little...
clumsy at expressing himself.
I really don't want to hear
what he has to say.
I'm already--
Franz has told me
how he feels, Valantine.
He says that... that
he only thinks of you
as the fiancée chosen
for him by his parents.
But you feel the
same way, don't you?
So you see Valantine?
That's why he says you
should do what you want.
He might not have a title,
but Maximilien is a fine
soldier and a respected
and upstanding young man.
And the most
important thing of all
is that he's deeply
in love with you.
I'm sure that he'll
make you a fine hus--
I want you to leave now.
Huh?
No one... No one ever
considers what I want.
Valantine, I...
[Valantine crying]
Just go away!
[VILLEFORT] I will
now pass judgment.
Defendant is found
guilty of larceny
and insulting the aristocracy,
the sentence is death.
But there were
mitigating issues!
You'll get no
sympathy from me!
It's human trash like this
man that ruins the kingdom...
[GUARD]
You have a visitor.
[BAPTISTIN] So, you
miss the outside world?
[VICTORIA] So, Heloise, are you
getting along with Valantine?
Eh?
I had heard that you had
taken to beating her severely.
I what? Who on
earth said that?!
It's just a rumor.
I like to think
that I'm as attentive
as I can be to that girl.
Just because she's the
daughter of his old wife
it doesn't mean that I--
Driver? Aren't we going
a little bit too fast?
[COACHMAN]
It's not me, Madame!
The horses! They...
They're refusing to obey me!
[CROWD screaming]
[ALL screaming]
[whip cracks]
[horse whinnies]
[MONTE CRISTO] You are
not harmed, I trust?
Look, it's the
Count of Monte Cristo!
We have you to thank
for our lives, sir.
It was fortunate
indeed that I had on hand
one who is skilled in
the handling of horses.
You look weird!
Are you some kind of alien?
[Heloise] Edouard,
don't be such a rascal!
Curiosity is a sure
sign of intelligence.
We still don't
know your name...
[VICTORIA] Heloise, this is
the Count of Monte Cristo.
You know, dear, he and my
husband are practically family.
I heard something
about you buying
the late Prince's
booth at the opera...
Then I am embarrassed.
It is not my custom to attract
undue attention to myself
but there were no
other seats available.
May I introduce
Madame Heloise,
wife of Crown
Prosecutor Villefort.
Madam, you are the wife
of Paris' guardian angel.
You're quite
the flatterer.
Your horses still
seem to be agitated.
Please, allow us to
escort you to your homes.
If Madame Villefort is amenable,
I shall see to it myself.
[ALBERT] It's just, I've never
seen her like that before.
[MAXIMILIEN sighs]
[COACHMAN]
Madame has returned!
Maximilien! Hurry!
[Heloise]
Valois!
Put some tea on
for our guest!
[MONTE CRISTO] Please, Madame,
that won't be necessary.
Please, call me Heloise...
Excellency...
[MONTE CRISTO chuckles]
Valantine, dear!
We have a visitor!
Mademoiselle says
that she is feeling unwell
and wishes not
to be disturbed.
Honestly, that girl...
Now Valantine!
Can't you even come out
and say hello to our guest?!
Valantine!
It's obvious that
she's utterly miserable.
Yeah, maybe...
I can see it
in her face.
Deep down, her
heart yearns for freedom.
But she is averting her eyes
away from those feelings
and hiding
beneath her sorrow.
You might be right.
She is a delicate
and fragile woman!
Can't you hear her soul
desperately crying out?!
Yeah, I can hear it.
No one considers
what she wants.
I don't. Nor you.
None of us really do.
[Heloise] Oh, that girl.
She always goes out of her way
to make trouble for me.
Perhaps she gets it
from her late mother.
She's always sickly and
stays cooped up indoors.
I've tried everything
I can think of,
to raise her to be a more
sociable person... but...
She's gonna
die young.
Isn't that what
you said, Mama?
Edouard!
You and your nonsense!
I feel sorry for
my own child, too.
Valantine stands to
inherit the fortune
of her grandfather, Monsieur
Noirtier, as well has that
of the Marquis Saint-Meran
on her mother's side.
But this boy
will receive nothing.
That saddens me.
I think siblings should
be equally fortunate,
even if they are totally
unrelated by blood.
[Heloise gasps]
[MONTE CRISTO laughs]
Ah! He's got
vampire fangs!
[Heloise] Edouard!
You're making me angry!
Vampire! Vampire!
He's a big blue-faced vampire!
I'm sorry he's
such a rude boy.
No, Not at all,
he is a darling child.
As an apology...
You must let me take you to
my very special secret place.
Oh, really?
It's a modest
little refuge I keep.
I don't know Albert.
I'm just so worried about her.
But there's absolutley
nothing that I can do for her...
[MONTE CRISTO and
HELOISE laughing]
What's going on?
Shh!
[MONTE CRISTO] So, this
greenhouse is your refuge.
It's magnificent.
[HELOISE]
Oh, you flatter me.
I know it might
sound a bit pathetic
but these flowers
might be my only friends.
Belladonna.
Mandragora. Datura.
It seems that everyone
of your favorite flowers,
share the same
fascinating trait.
Oh? What trait?
In each, their enchanting,
beautiful petals,
conceal a deadly poison...
That's interesting.
I had no idea...
[MAXIMILIEN]
Hey!
[HELOISE] My love of
horticulture eventually grew
into an interest
in botany.
It's not really a
women's subject is it?
Could it be...
...that you also have
an interest in toxicology?
Of course not.
Such a horrible thing,
Horrible?
Why horrible?
Toxicology and pharmacology
are two sides of the same coin.
Also...
...nothing is more
enticing to human beings
than the mysteries of poison.
Am I mistaken?
Poisons that steal a man's
life away in an instant.
Poisons that kill slowly
and then leave no
trace of themselves.
One starts to wonder
how many poisonings
have been consigned to the
darkness, known but to the dead.
And one more thing.
There is a beauty to
those bewitched by poisons.
[MAXIMILIEN]
Hey!
Gentlemen don't peep into
other people's windows--
[MONTE CRISTO] This enchanting
little trinket is commonly
referred to as
a Borgia Ring.
Take it. Now, press on the
stone and see what happens.
It is said that Lucrezia Borgia
used rings just like these
to dispatch countless people
throughout her diabolical life.
And foremost among her
victims was her own husband.
That ring belongs
to you, a gift Madame.
I'm so happy...
It is nothing, a mere
getting-acquainted gift
from a new friend.
Oh, Grandfather...
I want... I want to go
somewhere far away.
To some faraway place
where no one knows who I am.
[FRANZ]
It's nothing but trouble.
Benedetto! Take a look
out the left window.
That's Viscount
Albert de Morcerf.
[ALBERT] A party at
the Count's villa.
In the labyrinth, we cross paths
with a beautiful, horrible past.
Next Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo,
Act 8: "A Night in Boulogne."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!