[NARRATOR] Madames and
Messieurs. Good evening,
Wishing to express his feelings,
the young man ran
to the opera house,
where his former fiancée
anxiously awaited his arrival.
But he is not yet aware.
Not yet aware of his
father's sordid past,
which lies concealed behind
the broken engagement.
[AUDIENCE clapping]
That man is a
cold blooded murderer!
[MONTE CRISTO]
I am surprised you came
all this way, Your Honor.
Is this spectacle a
sideshow to the opera?
[VILLEFORT]
I take it you recognize this?
[MONTE CRISTO]
As I recall, that is the ring
that I gave to your lovely wife.
[VILLEFORT]
It had poison hidden inside.
[ALBERT gasps]
My, what a
fascinating contraption.
It's apparent to me
that you were attempting
to kill everyone,
including my wife.
[MONTE CRISTO] Surely you jest.
Why would I do such a thing?
[VILLEFORT]
It's obvious!
It Is a simple case...
...of that barbaric
custom from Eastern Space
commonly known
as the "thrill kill"!
No! The Count would
never do anything like that!
Sadly you're being
deceived by that man.
The Count was
the one who told us
about the threat to
Valentine's life!
[MONTE CRISTO] May I assume that
even a foreigner such as myself
can expect to receive a proper
trial in a local court of law?
[VILLEFORT]
Of course.
Under the law, you are
entitled to an impartial trial.
Hearing that sets
my mind at ease.
I have a witness
to offer in my defense.
Witness?
[MONTE CRISTO] Someone who
knows the entire truth
about what happened.
[VILLEFORT gasps]
Heloise? No!!
[MONTE CRISTO] I must tell
you that I have heard
many fascinating stories
from Madame and your son.
Including a few tales
which touch upon
certain family affairs.
You bastard!
So, your Honor, what is it
you would like to do with me?
[VILLEFORT growls]
[CROWD gasping]
[ONLOOKER A]
What's going on?
[ONLOOKER B] I thought they
were gonna arrest that guy.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Not to worry, gentlemen.
It seems that His Honor the
Crown Prosecutor made a mistake.
[ONLOOKER C]
Yeah! Way to go, Count!
Nice to see that
hanging judge get hung!
[MONTE CRISTO]
I think it would be best
for you to return
to your home now.
But Count...
Thank you Albert, but
you needn't worry about me.
[VILLEFORT] Don't think for
an instant that this is over!
[ALBERT]
Monsieur Villefort...
[VILLEFORT]
That so called "Count" of yours
has set his sights
on ruining me.
[ALBERT]
I can't believe it!
You're still saying
that nonsense?
[VILLEFORT]
I can sense it.
There is an evil presence
inside that man's soul.
[ANDREA]
I hope you're not still worrying
about your former fiancé?
[EUGENIE]
Marquis Cavalcanti.
Please call me Andrea.
[EUGENIE] I don't know what
my father said to you,
but I don't feel the
least bit grateful to you,
is that clear?
[ANDREA]
Now, now, Eugenie...
[EUGENIE]
It's always been my dream
to play a concert
at the opera house,
but using money to make
that dream come true was--
[ANDREA] But Eugenie,
it was your own merit
that won you the
right to that concert.
The reason, of course, is
that your magnificent talent
has utterly transformed me into
your loyal and humble servant.
He left you there alone.
It seems that he doesn't
even have the courage
to try to steal you away.
[FRANZ]
It's not here...
[LIBRARIAN A] Well, there
were no records matching
the requested item in any of the
volumes owned by this library.
[FRANZ]
I see.
Considering the Royal
Library's vaulted reputation,
it's hard to believe
there could be a word
that isn't registered here.
[LIBRARIAN A] It's quite
possible that the word is
on the General Security
Directorate's banned list
[FRANZ]
What are you talking about?
Regulations are in place
that prohibit general readers
from browsing classified topics.
[FERNAND]
What do you mean,
you're cutting off my
financial support?!
[DANGLARS] I'm afraid I've had
some unexpected expenses
What about the
presidential election?!
I'm sorry Fernand, but I'm
going to have to cut you loose.
[FERNAND]
You and I,
And Villefort, too...
I thought it was our dream
to climb together to the top
of Parisian power and then
bask in the wealth of riches!
[DANGLARS]
Oh, was that our dream?
We're on the verge
of making it come true.
Why now?
My, uh, investment analysts...
...are telling me to quit
gambling on you, General.
It's Edmond's letters, isn't it?
[DANGLARS]
Please...
I'm just saying that
at trying times like this
we all need to watch our step.
Oh, if you win the election...
...feel free to call.
[beep]
[STAFF OFFICER A] Excellency,
we've established a comm channel
with the Seventh
Eastern Space Fleet.
[DEBRAY] What a shameful
display last night.
[VILLEFORT]
What insolence! Who are you?!
First Secretary, Lucien Debray.
I'm hurt that you
don't remember me.
Ah, yes, the spoiled rich boy.
[DEBRAY]
The Count of Monte Cristo
is the talk of Paris
at the moment.
You won't be able to arrest
him without good cause.
He's plotting something,
I'm certain of it.
Can you prove it?
I'm the one who decides
who is guilty or innocent!
[DEBRAY] The General Security
Directorate will decide.
They suspect that you're trying
to file false
charges against him.
You've gone a little
too far this time.
It's probably only
a matter of days
before you're
suspended from the bench.
They can't!
[FRANZ]
Oh, there you are.
I need your advice
on a certain matter.
Well, it's rare for you to
be asking advice from anyone.
It seems that I need the help
of a member of
the Interior Ministry.
I noticed your best friend
isn't here with you today.
DANGLARS]
Where's Victoria?
[STEWART A] Madame is resting
comfortably in her room, sir.
[DANGLARS] I have no idea
what to do with her.
She's been acting like this ever
since she was out in the night
air at the party in Auteuil
and caught a terrible cold.
So anyway, that's why I can't
offer you a suitable welcome,
but perhaps you'd care
to join us for dinner?
Love to! Thanks!
I'm afraid I have a little
work that I must attend to.
So my daughter
will keep you company.
[EUGENIE]
Huh?
[DANGLARS] Why don't you
play another little tune?
And this time play
for Andrea here.
I would be honored if you did!
Oh wait...
[DANGLARS]
Hm?
You're inside on
Black Hole futures?!
[DANGLARS] Now, then, let's get
down to business, Michelle!
[MICHELLE] General Morcerf
called wishing to make
an appointment to see you.
[DANGLARS]
No! No! Never mind that!
I want the ultra-high density
materials market report!
Now, get to it!
[MICHELLE]
Understood, Monsieur.
[BERTUCCIO] Danglars is
accessing the market!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Excellent. It's time to sell.
Understood!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Let him gleefully eat his fill.
We'll make sure
that he's properly
fattened up for the slaughter,
wait until the time is right,
and then leak intel that there
is an impending Imperial Forces
offensive in the Central Galaxy.
Still, the thought
of helping to line
that vulture's pockets is
more than a little distasteful.
[DEBRAY]
Gankutsuou, huh?
Are you ready to start?
[FRANZ]
Mm-hm.
Here we go.
[FRANZ gasps]
Welcome to the
Repository of State Secrets.
[FRANZ]
What is this?
[DEBRAY] A Ministry
of the Interior database.
[LIBRARIAN PROGRAM A]
State search keyword.
Gankutsuou.
[LIBRARIAN PROGRAM A]
Lucien Debray,
First Secretary, class S.
Access to requested
information is granted.
Where are we?!
Please be quiet.
[SHADOW A] Gankutsuou is
the king of the shadows.
DEBRAY]
Which means?
[SHADOW B] Nobody's ever
seen what he looks like.
His name should never be spoken.
Those who break that taboo
meet a fate worse than death.
Some kind of urban legend?
[SHADOW C]
It is the truth.
He appeared on the fringes of
the galaxy a thousand years ago
and tried to gain control
of the criminal underworld.
He's an invader?
[SHADOW D]
Gankutsuou is invincible.
He controls people by
manipulating their desires.
However, he was
defeated by fate.
In June of 4002 of the
Louis Philippe calendar,
he was apprehended
and incarcerated.
[FRANZ]
Incarcerated? Where?
[SHADOW A]
We cannot answer that.
[DEBRAY]
Where was he imprisoned?
[SHADOW A]
We cannot answer that.
I hereby invoke
Imperial Edict 53!
[SHADOW A]
Gankutsuou was imprisoned
in the dungeons of Chateau d'If.
[DEBRAY]
I see. What happened after that?
[SHADOW D]
His death was confirmed
in the late afternoon
of December 23, 5043.
Ten years ago?!
He was in prison
for a thousand years?!
What name was he
imprisoned under?
[SHADOW A]
The Man in the Iron Mask.
[DEBRAY]
What was his full name?!
[LIBRARIAN PROGRAM A]
Terminate access immediately.
[DEBRAY]
But why?!
[SHADOW A]
We cannot answer that.
I invoke special
provision 3 of Edict 53!
[SHADOW A]
His name... His name was...
[LIBRARIAN PROGRAM A]
Illegal access! Illegal access!
Enacting article 6, clause 2 of
the Secrets Preservation Code.
[BOTH screaming]
That was not good!
I want to know who that
Gankutsuou really is!
No, I don't "want"
to I have to know!
Well, I wonder if
old man Noirtier might know.
Why would he?
A long time ago, he ran
the Ministry of the Interior.
But he also had
quite a few enemies,
and he was brought down.
You mean the assassination
of the Prince?
He was a very vocal proponent
of making peace with the Empire.
Apparently, that
made it quite hard
for his son,
Villefort, to advance.
Of course all that work
has been for naught.
[VILLEFORT]
Father...
You must be laughing at me,
a man who's lost both
his status and his family.
Poetic justice for a man
who's spent his career
sending innocent
men to prison
and presiding over so many
cold and merciless trials.
I know you think that this is
my punishment for defying
your wishes and supporting
war against the Empire
and for doing away
with your compatriots.
Do you know how long and
hard I worked to surpass you!
You who had the power
to sway government policy!
Do you have the slightest idea
how hard that was for me?!
Any idea of how hard
it was to be your son
in a world completely
dominated by Hawks?!
Suspended from duty, eh?
So what?!
See if I care!
I won't let it end like this!
Just you watch!
I'll come back from this
and when I do I'll
be stronger than ever!
[BERTUCCIO] She's been like
that since we arrived.
It's as if she's
regressed to childhood.
[STAFF OFFICER A]
Excellency, are you certain
that this is wise?
We can still attack after
the peace negotiations.
We should strike
while we still can!
If we are to gain the upper
hand at the negotiation table,
there can be no hesitation!
A victory here is certain
to give your poll numbers
a huge boost, Your Excellency!
[BERTUCCIO] His Excellency,
the Viscount Morcerf.
[HAIDEE]
Welcome to our humble home.
What may we do for you?
Actually, I was hoping
I could meet with the Count.
I'm afraid the Count's illness
has rendered him bedridden.
Yes, I'd heard that.
Please, let me wish
him a speedy recovery.
I ask that you allow him
to remain undisturbed.
At trying times like this,
he will see no one else
in the world but me.
Of course, Mademoiselle.
The Count has complete
faith in you, doesn't he?
Please tell him to be on guard
against Monsieur Villefort.
Villefort said that
he was gonna make
the Count pay
for whatever he did.
So he--
Monsieur Albert,
you care a great deal
for the Count, don't you?
Yes, I suppose...
I'm glad that you are
concerned for his well-being.
I'm curious Mademoiselle,
how long have you been with him?
Well, It's been a long time now.
A long time since the Count
decided he would purchase me.
He... bought you?!
[HAIDEE] Please understand,
I was born into
the royal family of a
certain frontier planet.
Our world is situated between
this kingdom and Eastern Space,
and had prospered from
the trade between them.
However...
...our excellent fortune was not
destined to last for very long.
War broke out between
the Empire and Earth,
and my home world was engulfed
in the terrible
flames of battle.
My father decided to establish
an alliance with the Earth.
He did this because he had heard
that the people of Earth
valued freedom above all else.
Soon after, reinforcements
arrived from Earth.
[ALBERT] My father told
me that ten years ago
was a time of great turmoil.
He said that he
himself had fought
in several wars of independence.
The reinforcements from
Earth broke the alliance
and betrayed my father!
[HAIDEE]
They started a rebellion,
leveling false charges
against my father,
claiming that he was working
in collusion with the Empire.
My father was eventually
killed as a traitor.
My mother and I were
stripped of our property
and position and sold into
the hands of our enemies.
My mother died soon thereafter,
and I was left
to fend for myself.
I was like a walking corpse.
Until, until the day
that I met the Count.
[ALBERT]
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to dredge
up painful memories.
I'm a fool, aren't I?
My girlfriend tells
me that all the time.
She says I don't think
about other people's feelings.
Oh, I guess she's more like
an old childhood
friend than a girlfriend.
She gave a piano recital at
the opera house the other day!
"It's wonderful to be able
to express yourself that way."
That's what I thought to myself
when I heard her performance.
Mademoiselle, you're quite
good at the harp, right?
Do my family the honor of
paying us a visit sometime.
And perhaps you
would even allow me
to introduce you
to some of my friends.
[HAIDEE]
The night we arrived in Paris...
...the Count took me aside
said the following to me:
"Haidee, this is
a land where freedom
and human rights
are appreciated."
"Therefore you
should do as you wish,
acting according to
your own free will." So...
This is the way
that I see it now.
If I remain voluntarily,
I am here because I'm free,
and I freely choose to do so.
[ANDREA] Our young Viscount
is one carefree kid.
Even though there's a fire
lit under his old man's ass.
Oh, stop it.
[ANDREA]
"It's wonderful to be able
to express yourself that way."
Ha! I'm gonna puke!
That is so damn pathetic!
But then you and I are
two of a kind, aren't we?
I can see what you
really think, plain as day.
No! Please, you're wrong!
You hate him, don't you?!
You wanna rip him
to pieces, don't you?!
Come on, let's have some fun.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Take your hands off her!
[ANDREA cackling]
It's the Count...
[MONTE CRISTO, FARIA]
Leave us!
[ANDREA]
As you wish Excellency.
Monsieur Villefort? I think.
[HAIDEE] After I met
you, I cast away all of
the horrible feelings
I had within myself.
Or so I believed.
And I thought if
I could only ease
your cruel resolve then
everything would be all right...
But I... But I just...
...I just couldn't forget
what was burned in my mind.
I couldn't forget how
I felt when I swore revenge.
[HAIDEE]
Considering how I myself feel,
it was very wrong of me to
hope to change how you feel.
I'm so sorry...
[VILLEFORT]
Ah, Count.
I'm afraid I caused
you to suffer
a great injustice by jumping
to some rather
regrettable conclusions.
Please, let me offer
you my apology!
Eat this!
Count! No!
[ALBERT] The person I
was in the past is not
the person I am today.
Who we were in the past
is not who we are today.
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 14:
"Lost Souls".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!