[NARRATOR] Madames and
Messieurs, good evening.
At long last, the time has come
for my friend to bid
farewell to things of beauty.
Sincerity. Trust. Friendship.
All of those virtues, all
of those wonderful things
that we possess
during childhood...
...is now cast into
the darkness of space,
bidding them adieu.
[RADIO] Planet Janina was
invaded by the Empire
15 years ago. But as
Space Forces deployed,
did a commissioned
officer make secret deal?
Paris has been shaken to
its foundation by this scandal
involving lead presidential
candidate General Morcerf.
Take me to
Space Forces Headquarters
[HAIDEE gasps]
Let me in.
I'm Albert de Morcerf.
[OLDER REPORTER]
Hey, that's the candidate's son!
[REPORTERS clarmoring]
Was your family aware
of what happened?
Did he ever discuss
his deeds with you?
Was the General
trying to get his hands
on the fortune belonging
to the Pasha of Janina?
[REPORTER]
Ow! Hey, watch it! Don't push!
[BEARDED REPORTER]
What do you think of your father
committing those shameful acts?
Get out of my way!
The General should apologize to
the people of Paris right away!
[REPORTER A]
Issue an apology!
[ALBERT] Look, I don't
know anything about that!
Now move aside!
[REPORTER B]
There are rumors going around
that your family isn't
really of nobility.
[BEARDED REPORTER] Yes, did they
falsify their backgrounds?
You know what? I've
had just about enough
of you filthy parasites
insulting my father!
[REPORTER C]
Insulting?!
The ones who have been insulted
all these years is us!
The citizens of Paris!
[BEARDED REPORTER] You're the
son of a traitor who colluded
with the enemy and sold
out the Pasha for greed!
[STAFF OFFICER A]
Viscount Morcerf?!
[ALBERT] Where's my father?!
Tell me where my father is!
Am I to understand
that you came in
through the front gate?
That was a foolish
thing to do.
Follow me to the back entrance.
You're not safe here.
My father! Where are
you hiding him?
Please, you gotta
let me speak to him!
Unfortunately, the general
is preoccupied trying
to deal with everything
that has come up,
so I believe that he might
not return here until tomorrow.
Oh, I see.
In that case, give my
father a message for me.
I need to ask him
something and...
...and please sir, tell
my father I believe in him.
Yes sir, I understand.
[FERNAND gasping]
[beeping]
[FERNAND]
Enter.
[STAFF OFFICER A] I have done
everything that I can, sir.
However, explaining everything
to the National Assembly
may prove to be difficult.
They're already discussing
issuing subpoenas.
[FERNAND]
I understand. You can go.
Excuse me, sir,
your son was just here.
[STAFF OFFICER A]
As per your orders,
I told him that
you were not here.
What did he say?
Your son said
that he believes...
...in you General Morcerf.
[DEBRAY]
Albert!
Hurry, get in!
[DANGLARS]
Eugenie!
What in blazes do you
think you're doing?
Why can't you do as
you're told for once?!
No! Let me go!
Let go of me!
Was I talking to myself
when I ordered you people
again and again not
to let my daughter out?
Call security!
[MAID 16A]
Y-Yes, Monsieur!
[MAID 16B]
At once!
Something terrible is happening
to my oldest friend's family...
...and you want me to ignore it?
You fool!
If you went out there those
journalists would eat you alive!
They'll write about your
relationship with Albert,
blending fact and fiction
until it becomes a farce,
and we're made
into a public joke!
Can't you see it?!
So what! I don't
care about that!
Now listen, this isn't just
about you, understand?!
I won't tolerate anything
that might lower your value,
including your behavior!
Keep a close eye on her!
Make sure she
doesn't leave the house!
[ANDREA] Eugenie, are
you truly that worried
about your friend
Viscount Morcerf?
If you desire,
I will go in your place
to inquire after Monsieur
Albert's current well-being.
But I...
[ANDREA] You should stay
here where it's safe.
I can't bear the thought of
a wonderful person like you
being disgraced by the
heartless people in the press.
[DEBRAY] You know, Albert, I've
been looking everywhere for you.
We're right in the
middle of a huge scandal,
and you go and walk right
into military headquarters,
the belly of the beast.
Pretty stupid.
[ALBERT] A Word of Advice to
General Fernand Morcerf, by...
...Robert Beauchamp.
I want you to take me to
Beauchamp's place right away.
[ALBERT]
Now!
[BEAUCHAMP]
Hey, I was on a call.
Sorry I kept you guys waiting.
Um, Albert, what are you--
[BEAUCHAMP groans]
[ALBERT]
You bastard!
All this time, you were only
pretending to be my friend!
"Watch out for enemies", my ass!
You were planning all along
to sell out my old man to get
your big scoop weren't you?
Well, isn't that right?! Well?!
Albert... listen...
I'm going tell you everything
that I uncovered
in my investigation.
The real truth.
So before you do
anything rash, hear me out.
[BEAUCHAMP]
Take a look at this.
It's a copy of a title
deed that I bought
on the black-market
in the Empire.
For 100 million Francs
I cede ownership
of Queen Vasiliki and
Princess Haidee of Janina.
The seller is, Fernand Mondego.
[ALBERT] Yeah, so what's
this supposed to prove?!
[BEAUCHAMP]
I did some digging around
and tried to follow up
on this "Mondego" fellow.
But all the information
on him had been erased.
It was almost as if
the man had never existed.
But Mondego existed, all right.
It seems that when he returned
to his home Marseilles
he immediately used
the money he had received
to purchase orders of nobility.
And that's when Mondego
changed his name.
Yeah, prove it!
Show me your proof, now!
[DEBRAY]
Albert, listen,
I was able to learn through
records at the Ministry of the
Interior that Mondego was an old
friend of Monsieur Villefort's.
They were both from Marseilles.
Upon Mondego's return.
Villefort purged all
information regarding him
from the public records.
And that's how the man known
as Mondego was
erased from existence,
and the man known
as Fernand de Morcerf
was born in his place.
Wait a minute!
What're you two
trying to say to me?!
That my father is the same
man as that monster, Mondego?!
You get your kicks by publishing
made up stories about people?
[BEAUCHAMP]
Oh please!
You seriously think I wrote
a made up story for fun?
I mean, do you have
any clue what it did
to me to have to research
and write that piece?
Do you really think that I'm
some sort of sleazy slime ball
who would sell out his
friends just for a scoop?!
That's enough.
Look. Albert...
I'm a journalist, okay?
I have a solemn duty to get
the truth out to the people,
no matter what the cost may be.
[ALBERT]
Dammit!
[FRANZ] The immortal man
from Chateau d'If...
Gankutsuou...
The strange mark that I saw
on the Count's forehead back
on that night in Auteuil was...
...was definitely
the mark of Gankutsuou.
Does that mean that the Count
has turned into Gankutsuou?
What's he doing in Paris?
[MAXIMILIEN] If you keep
pushing yourself this hard,
you're gonna
make yourself sick
You didn't stay up all
night again, did you?
You're such a worrywart,
you do know that?
Please, eat.
It's just country food,
but it'll keep you nourished.
Hey, that looks great...
Thanks a lot.
Go on, take it to him.
No can't!
I'm too embarrassed!
Aw come on, you were the one
who said that youwanted
to meet Franz, weren't you?
[GIRL] Well then, you come
in with me, big brother.
What are you two up to out here?
Hey, Maximillien!
Um... Uh...
Come on in.
[GIRL]
Here! Eat this!
[BOY] She said you looked
like you were in the dumps,
so we made these
cookies for you.
Thanks, you two.
[BOTH giggling]
[MAXIMILIEN]
You two...
[VILLEFORT] Mark my words!
You're going to be next!
Disaster will come
calling at your house!
[FRANZ]
It feels strange.
[MAXIMILIEN]
Huh?
[FRANZ] For there to be
so many family members
in the same house.
[MAXIMILIEN] But aren't there
a great many people living
in your own house, Monsieur?
[FRANZ]
Yes, years ago.
Lots of servants
lived there too.
But now, there are
just a few servants left
and my mother, of course.
[MAXIMILIEN]
Sorry, I didn't realize...
[FRANZ] There are a lot of
different kinds of aristocrats.
For instance, the engagement
between Valantine and I
was forced on us
by Monsieur Villefort,
because my family has
been known for generations
in Paris as staunch royalists.
Unlike Albert's family, mine
has not amassed a large fortune,
so we thought it
really wouldn't hurt
to have some well
connected backing
once I started to make my way
into diplomatic community.
[MAXIMILIEN]
I'm sorry.
I said all those things
without knowing the truth.
[FRANZ]
Hey, I'm not so dumb
that I need you
to worry about me.
You'd never guess
by looking at me,
but I hit the books hard.
[BOTH laughing]
[FRANZ]
Monsieur Noirtier was right.
He said that he wanted
you to make Valantine happy.
I think that maybe
you're the only one I know
who can actually do that.
[MAXIMILIEN]
I will!
[FRANZ]
Who is this?
[MAXIMILIEN] My father. He
passed away three years ago.
[FRANZ] That's quite a
beautiful ship he's got there.
[MAXIMILIEN]
She was called the Pharaon.
She was the crowning
star of our fleet.
She's changed hands now, though.
[FRANZ]
Edmond Dantes?
[MAXIMILIEN]
Oh, Edmond?
Don't tell me you
know Edmond Dantes.
[FRANZ] No, do you?
Do you know who he is?
[MAXIMILIEN]
Yes, of course.
He worked as first mate for
Morrel and Son, some time ago.
[ALBERT]
No go...
With that circus out there,
I'll never make it to the
back door let alone the front.
[ALBERT gasps]
[PEPPO]
Come on, this way!
Over here.
It's the one gate
in the mansion
that isn't hooked into
the security system.
[ALBERT] I don't get it.
How do you know all this stuff?
Hey, uh, Peppo?
[PEPPO] Get a move on.
The paparazzi'll be here soon!
[ALBERT]
I owe you one.
Goodbye, Albert.
I'm going to miss you.
[REPORTER D] Hey, there's
somebody over there!
[REPORTER E]
C'mon, let's go!
[ALBERT]
Mother! Are you here?!
Mother!
Mother, aren't you home?
There you are!
Oh, Albert...
Mother!
I'm so happy you're okay.
[MERCEDES]
Oh, thank goodness you're safe.
Thank goodness...
Mother, I, I don't...
You're looking awfully
haggard, Albert...
I bet you haven't eaten at all.
[MERCEDES]
Wait here.
I'll have someone
fix something up for you.
Stop it, Mother.
Stop pretending
that nothing's wrong.
I'm just sick and tired
of everybody treating me
like I'm some kind
of clueless kid!
[ALBERT] I just don't want
to hear any more lies.
[MERCEDES] Your father and I
are not true aristocrats.
We were both commoners
born in a small village
just outside of
Marseilles called Catalonia.
But how...
What is Father's real name?
Your father's real name is...
...Fernand Mondego.
[MERCEDES] By the time I
realized what was happening,
it was already too late.
Once I said we were
born aristocrats,
I had no choice but
to keep playing the part.
But the truth finally came out
in the middle of your
father's campaign speech.
I don't get it!
Mother why are you saying all
these terrible things, too?!
I don't understand why you
don't have any faith in Father?!
I heard the speech.
The terrible one
given by the Princess
from Janina that
day with my own ears.
If I had sensed
even for an instant
that any one of her
words were mere lies,
I would have passed
judgment over her
in Heaven's stead
then and there.
But it was all true.
[MERCEDES]
Albert...
We each must face the
inevitable consequences
of the things we have done.
We must never again avert
our eyes from the truth.
[ALBERT] Haidee wanted this to
happen from the very beginning!
Damn it! Damn it!
[MAXIMILIEN] Every year, my
father and I would go together
to place flowers on the
grave of Edmond Dantes.
Father would always
stare out at the sea,
and he would never tell me much
about Edmond or the life he led.
But then on his deathbed,
he kept calling out his name,
with tears flowing
down from his eyes.
"I want to see Edmond!
I want to see Edmond!"
"Oh why wasn't I able to
save my friend Edmond?! Why?"
Please, Maximilien, show me
Morrel &amp; Son's crew roster.
[MAXIMILIEN] I haven't seen
many of the records
that date back
to my father's time.
Edmond... Edmond...
This is him!
[FRANZ] It can't be. His face
is completely different.
But still...
[MAXIMILIEN]
What, monsieur? Tell me.
Well, the name of Edmond Dantes
was in Monsieur
Noirtier's memories.
25 years ago,
he was sent to prison
for a crime Monsieur Noitier
said he didn't commit.
[FRANZ gasps]
What the--
[FRANZ] Baron Danglars?!
Danglars was the ship's purser?
That's it! So that's
what this is all about!
[FRANZ] I have to get back
there! Albert is in danger.
[MAXIMILIEN]
I don't get it.
What in the world is the matter?
He's still alive!
Huh?
I'm sure Edmond Dantes is alive!
[ALBERT]
Haidee!
Get out here! Haidee!
Show yourself right now!
Haidee!
[ALBERT panting]
Long time, no see, little boy.
Not since back on Luna, right?
Luigi Vampa?
[ALBERT] What are you
doing in the Count's home?
What are you doing,
he says. That's rich.
[TERESA] The boy's still
as naive as ever.
Why don't you go ahead
and explain it to him.
[ALBERT] But you said that you'd
left the bandit gang, Peppo!
The truth is I've been
keeping an eye on you
on orders from
the Count, Albert.
[PEPPO] I've also been
sending detailed reports
of all your movements to
the Count since I arrived.
But Why would the
Count have you do that?
Please, you must have
a vague idea by now.
About why the Count made friends
with you up on Luna,
and then came to Paris.
Shut up! Where is Haidee?!
Hurry up and send her out!
His servants have
left the mansion.
[LUIGI] Their master is due to
arrive on Earth any time now.
[FRANZ]
General Morcerf...
The Scandal of Janina...
You're making your
move Count. Aren't you?
Oh Albert, please stay safe.
Haidee, there you are!
[ALBERT]
Count, you have to tell me.
Where can I find hope?
Where is the truth you spoke of?
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 17:
"The Confession".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!