[CROWD cheering]
[drums thumping]
[CROWD laughing and cheering]
[FRANZ and ALBERT laughing]
[ALBERT gasps]
[ALBERT chuckles]
[CROWD cheering and laughing]
[ALBERT and FRANZ giggling]
[VENDOR]
Get your moccoletti!
How 'bout a moccoletto!
Join the celebration!
[CROWD murmuring]
[MARQUISE G]
Oh, Franz!
Over here!
[FRANZ]
Ah, hello, M'Lady!
When did you
arrive on Luna?
I made a loop around
the inner planets
and arrived yesterday.
So...
You're here in time to catch
the end of the Carnival.
By the way...
Who is this?
Oh!
My traveling companion
and best friend.
Viscount Albert de Morcerf,
at your service.
I am honored to
meet you... Madame.
My...
So you're the son
of General Morcerf.
Well...
First time on Luna?
I suggest you
enjoy yourself.
In this city all your
desires can be fulfilled,
no matter what they are.
[MARQUISE G smirks]
♪ operatic music ♪
[ALBERT gasps]
♪ operatic music continues ♪
[AUDIENCE gasps]
[AUDIENCE claps]
♪ operatic music continues ♪
[ALBERT gasps]
[MARQUISE G] Apparently,
he presents himself as a count.
But I'm not so sure.
Regardless of what he is...
Luna's society circles
are abuzz with rumors.
who made his fortune
on the frontier
or that he's an
alien from outer space.
Some even say that he's
a monster in human form,
or a vampire.
[FRANZ] That might be
going a little far...
Pardon, but...
who is this person?
I mean,
what is his name?
He's called the
Count of Monte Cristo.
♪ operatic music continues ♪
[ALBERT] "Death is certain,
its hour uncertain."
♪ operatic music continues ♪
[elevator rattles]
[ALBERT pants]
[wind rustling]
whoosh, whoosh
[doors creak open]
♪
[wind blowing]
[heavy footsteps]
boom, boom, boom
♪
[air venting]
whoooooosh
[FRANZ] Are you sure you
weren't dreaming or something?
You know, daydreaming...
[ALBERT]
Get serious.
This proves it was real.
[FRANZ]
Mm-hmm.
And...?
I'm gonna use it
to try and meet him.
So what do you think?
Are you insane?
That's a huge hassle.
Look, forget about it!
You have no idea
who this guy is.
[light footsteps]
tip, tap, tip tap
You sure
you're right...?
I know I am--
[BERTUCCIO]
I beg your pardon,
but are you Viscount
Morcerf from room 405?
[ALBERT]
Um uh...
Yes. Yes, I am...
I have a message for you
from my master,
the Count of Monte Cristo.
Please accept it.
[FRANZ] Well?
What do you think?
[ALBERT] Uh, What
do I think of what?
Why would
he want to meet
two complete
strangers like us?
His note said he wants
to establish good relations
with fellow aristocrats
staying in the same hotel.
It's a coincidence...
I'm not so sure.
There you go again.
You're such a worrywart.
At least tag along while
I have dinner with him.
I have doubts about whether
he's even a real aristocrat.
This is Luna, remember?
He's almost
certainly a con man--
How do you do, messieurs.
I am the Count
of Monte Cristo,
and I'm delighted
that you're here.
You grace me
with your presence.
[FRANZ, ALBERT,
MONTE CRISTO laughing]
[MONTE CRISTO]
Come now, this won't do.
When a man has come
all the way to Luna
he simply must
try these dishes.
We thank you for
your kindness, sir,
but we seem to be the
only ones who are eating.
You haven't touched
a thing all through dinner.
Are you not feeling well?
Please, you needn't
concern yourselves about me.
Just as journeys traveled
alone are dull and unsatisfying,
meals eaten alone
have no flavor.
For me, speaking with enchanting
guests as I'm doing right now
is really the greatest
feast that I could wish for.
Please, help yourselves.
By the way,
I was wondering what you thought
of the opera we attended.
Well sir, I really don't go
to see operas very often, but...
...but for some reason this time
I found myself
drawn into the story!
Oh, I see.
So, Monsieur Albert,
are you saying to us
that you have someone in
the world for whom you pine,
just as in the opera?
No, sir, of course not!
Come on Albert,
you know that's not true.
Are you're talking
about Eugenie?
We were chosen for
each other by our parents.
I've never experienced
the same kind of intense love
like the main
character of that opera.
I want something
more in my life.
Something I can lose myself in.
Something to grab
my heart and never let go.
You see, I came on this
journey to find that something.
Really...
Why are you trying to
make it sound so noble?
I thought your goal was
focused more below your waist.
Franz! Cut it out!
[MONTE CRISTO laughs]
This is marvelous!
Youth is such
a wonderful thing.
Endless possibilities.
Hopes and dreams...
And passion unencumbered.
Your Excellency, have you
ever been in love like that?
[MONTE CRISTO]
I have.
So, what sort
of woman was she?
[FRANZ]
Albert, don't be rude!
To be perfectly honest,
I once had deep
and passionate feelings
for a certain enchanting woman.
I had dreams of a long
and happy life that
involved this woman.
However, painful,
in the end, those
feelings of passion
amounted to
absolutely nothing...
In short,
all those dreams...
were only dreams.
And in the place
where those dreams lived
stands the man that
I have become today.
Bertuccio!
Excellency.
Bring coffee
for our guests.
Gentlemen, you honor me
with your presence tonight.
Not at all, sir!
The honor is ours!
In that case...
...I want you to join me on my
balcony for luncheon tomorrow.
It'll be wonderful.
Will you come?
Oh, really sir?
We'd be honored to--
We're sorry,
Your Excellency.
We appreciate your kind offer,
but we couldn't possibly accept.
Luna's public executions are the
highlight of Carnival, you know.
The festivities reach
their peak as the blood
of heinous criminals washes
away all the crowd's sins.
One has not experienced
Luna's Carnival
without having seen this.
Is that not so,
Monsieur Albert?
Yes! You're exactly right!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Very well then.
I shall await you here
in this room again tomorrow.
Good evening.
[FRANZ]
Hey! Albert!
Yes?
What's the
matter with you?
You don't look so good.
It was so cold.
His hand was
as cold as ice...
It was like
a corpse's hand...
[MONTE CRISTO]
Who are today's condemned?
[BERTUCCIO] One is a man
who committed murder
out of his abject poverty.
The second is a man
who committed murder
over a love affair.
And finally...
...the third is a man
who slaughtered an entire family
to steal their possessions.
All three of them
are heinous criminals
who are beyond forgiveness.
[CRIMINAL 1 crying]
I did it to feed my family!
I had no choice!
My beloved wife and child,
please forgive me!
Spare my life,
I beg of you...
[AUDIENCE grumbles]
Stop that!
[PENITANT]
Stop it at once!
My Lord Cardinal, please!
You have to believe me.
I didn't murder anyone!
My rival framed me!
I could never murder anyone!
I'm innocent!
Please my Lord,
undo these chains!
[CRIMINAL 2]
I didn't do it!
I suppose they're
just saying anything
that might earn them
a reprieve, right?
[CRIMINAL 2]
I... I didn't do it!
Please believe me!!
I didn't do anything!
[CRIMINAL 3 spits]
You moron!
Shut your damn trap!
I'm sick of you and
your constant whining.
[CRIMINAL 3 snickers]
As for me,
I murdered ten people!
[AUDIENCE gasps]
[PEPPINO] Women and children,
I killed 'em all!
How's that?!
Now live it up, you bastards!
C'mon!
I wanna see some more
happy faces out there!
Aah!
[AUDIENCE yells]
It seems today's program
will be most interesting.
Don't you agree?
[MONTE CRISTO] I think we should
have a bit of sport with this.
A little sideshow to
the execution, as it were.
I have here in my
possession a single letter.
It is an official
letter of pardon
that was given to
me by the Cardinal.
How in the world did you
get something like that?
Unfortunately,
I have but this one letter
of pardon with which to play.
Now to make the
choice of which man
should get this letter
an impartial one...
I have written the initials of
a condemned man on each card.
Now, you need only to choose
one from among the three.
Come now, gentlemen...
it's nothing more
than a little game.
Just a minute, Your Excellency!
If that's the case, then...
...shouldn't we hear what
they have to say first?!
My good Monsieur Franz,
this is nothing more than
a game, we are not judges.
Regardless of what we do,
they are all going to die.
I merely suggest
that we make use
of that fact in order
to enjoy ourselves.
At this moment, we have
in our hands the power
to offer the hand of salvation
to one of these poor souls.
I wonder Monsier...
Why do you hesitate to
use that power to do good?
Yes, it almost feels as
if one has actually
become God, does it not?
[FRANZ]
What's the matter with you?!
You're using people's
lives as some sort of game?!
You're insane sir!
Come on, Albert, we're leaving!
[MONTE CRISTO]
A game...?
Yes, it is a game.
But, of course, to me our
own lives are merely pieces
that are manipulated as part
of someone else's game.
Has it ever seemed that
way to you, Monsieur Franz?
I'm afraid I wouldn't know.
Come on! Let's go!
I was truly hopeful that you
and I would become good
friends, Monsieur Albert.
I'm most disappointed.
[drum roll]
[MONTE CRISTO] You told me
you set out on your journey
in order to find something.
To seek out and grab hold
of an entirely new you...
...through the exertion
of your own will.
Come on, Albert, we're going!
[CRIMINAL 1 whimpering]
[FRANZ]
Albert!
I'll do it!
Don't!
You'll be sorry if you do!
It is just a game...
Isn't it?
[CRIMINAL 1 whimpering]
No!
Nooo!
[ALBERT panting]
Albert, please don't...
[CRIMINAL 1 yells]
Nooo!
Albert! Don't do it...!
[bell ringing]
ding, ding, ding
EXECUTIONER] A pardon has
been issued by the Cardinal!
The man who is
to be pardoned is...
...Rocca Briori.
Also known as Peppino!
Yeah!! How do ya like that?!
Thank you!
Thanks for your mercy!
Long live His Excellency
the Cardinal!
See, Monsieur Albert?
You have performed
a good deed today...
A truly good and noble deed.
Watch. The show
is about to begin.
Kill him! Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Regardless of what happens next,
you mustn't look away,
Monsieur Albert...
Not for an instant.
[AUDIENCE] Kill! Kill! Kill!
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
[neck slices off]
[swords clanking]
[MONTE CRISTO grunts]
[MONTE CRISTO panting]
[MARQUISE G gasps]
[MONTE CRISTO yells]
[sword striking facemask]
[MARQUISE G gasps]
[MONTE CRISTO] You musn't
hold anything back, Baptistin.
Forgive me,
Your Excellency.
[MONTE CRISTO]
The time has come...
My vengeance Has finally
been set into motion.
[FRANZ] Hey, let's go to
a cafe and clear our heads.
Or how about the
red light district?
Oh, right. Sorry about that.
I forgot you don't
do that sort of thing.
Well, we could
go to the casino...
Please, don't talk
to me about gambling!
Hey! What's the
matter with you?
[FRANZ sighs]
In the first place,
you were the one who
was just dying to see it.
And then you let the Count talk
you into picking that card--
I know that!
You don't have to tell
me... I know what I did!
[FRANZ] "I brought
this on my own head,
"and that's the reason
I'm so upset right now!
"I'm just angry at
myself!" That right?
You know, Franz,
I'm getting tired of you
always fussing over me!
You think that you're
my girlfriend or something?
Are you my mother?! Are you?
I 'm going back to the hotel
to get ready for the ball.
What about you?
Hmph!
You alone?
Tonight is the last night of
this year's Carnival you know.
You shouldn't be alone
on a night like this.
Yeah, but I want to be alone.
See, today was
the worst day of my life.
Oh, Albert...
[clock chimes]
ding, dong, ding, dong
[fireworks exploding]
boom, boom, boom
[WOMAN moans]
No, wait...
Don't be in such a rush...
Shall we go?
[ALBERT]
A passing fling on Luna.
It was a trap set by bandits.
Moment by moment,
the hour of death approaches.
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 2:
"Until the Sun
Rises Over the Moon."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!