[FARIA] Madams and Messieurs,
good evening.
The youth, who had
been ravaged by poison,
was restored to life
through my friend's efforts.
However, my friend
said something to me.
I will not yet let
his soul be lost.
Not until the day that he
himself snuffs out that light.
[MAXIMILIEN]
Monsieur Albert.
[ALBERT] Have you
managed to get any sleep?
If there is one thing
I have confidence in,
it's my stamina.
That may be so but
you look like hell to me.
It looks like Monsieur
Villefort has laid off
all of the maids
and butlers.
Yes, I heard.
After all that's happened
I just can't bring myself
to leave her alone
in this house.
Besides, I've
been thinking about
something that Franz said.
Getting married isn't
necessarily the only way
there is to make the person
you love happy and content.
And so, I've been
mulling it over.
Trying to figure out
the most important thing
that Mademoiselle
Valantine needs.
So I can give it to her.
And what do
you think that is?
She may be asleep now,
but I think that Mademoiselle
Valantine is lonely
to the point of crying.
So, at the very least,
I want to make sure
that I'm sitting
right by her side
when she finally
comes around.
Which is why I
made up my mind.
I'm taking her to Marseilles to
our family home to recuperate.
I don't want her to have
to endure any more
pain or suffering.
I had a feeling you'd be here.
Your Honor, I came
here today to discuss--
Mark my words, boy.
If you dare try to take
my daughter even a
foot from this house.
I'll have you hunted down
and arrested as a kidnapper.
That is not a threat.
But, Your Honor,
the things
that are happening
in this house are--
Are none of your business!
Now, get out!
You, too, Albert.
I want you out.
Begging your pardon, Your Honor,
but somebody out there
is trying very hard to
kill off your whole family!
I was almost
killed myself.
"Somebody," is
trying to kill us?
If there's
anyone close at hand
who could be described
as suspicious, it would be
that impudent fraud of a Count
whom you call your friend!
Be clear!
From now on, this is
strictly a family affair!
I forbid you from
interfering with us!
[BOVILLE whispering]
The following is a report
regarding my investigation on
the Count of Monte Cristo.
In the course of visiting
the various locations
indicated by Your Honor,
I discovered quite by accident
that a certain old priest
had been making a similar set
of inquiries all
around Marseilles.
He has visited this
area several times
during the past three months,
always asking questions.
The priest seems to
be gathering information
on an old man who
lived here some time ago
and died penniless and alone.
The old man's name
was Louis Dantes.
In order to ascertain the
priest's true objectives,
as well as to clarify the
connection between him
and the Count of Monte Cristo...
I plan to investigate the house
that Louis Dantes lived in
while he was still alive.
The old man's name
was Louis Dantes.
[VILLEFORT]
Louis Dantes? Dantes?!
[EDOUARD]
Papa!
My school play is today.
You're coming,
aren't you?
Didn't your
mother tell you?
Some urgent business
has come
up that I must attend
to--I'm sorry.
But father, you promised
that you'd come!
You said that you'd come
this time, no matter what!
Your Papa's work keeps
him very busy, Edouard.
I don't care about that!
You're a liar, Papa!
Get him out of here.
As his mother, it is your job
to explain these things to him!
But Edouard has been so excited
and looking forward to you
seeing his play this afternoon.
I don't care how
excited he was!
Stop bothering me!
[EDOUARD cries]
Tell my teacher
that the yellow dwarf
isn't gonna be in the play!
[MAID]
Monsieur.
What is it?
You're still here?
Go get your bags packed
and hurry about it.
Pardon, Monsieur...
An invitation to a
funeral just arrived.
What's the meaning
of this...?
It's all well and good that
I've been fortunate enough
to inherit such
vast land holdings,
but there's still so
much I don't understand.
The first thing is to learn
the law inside and out.
That goes doubly
when you've come
into possession of
a huge inheritance.
If we don't keep estate taxes
and what-not under control,
it can become a big problem.
I didn't know that.
Truth be told, I'm currently
looking for an experienced
and talented partner
who will be able
to effectively
manage my assets.
Oh, a partner, you say?
[knocking on door]
[door opens]
Mademoiselle Eugenie,
would it be all right
if I paid you a visit
in your room shortly?
I'm sorry, but right now
I'm in the middle
of my piano lessons.
Oh, for Heaven's sake,
please forgive my
daughter's lack of charm.
Of course.
Now this is just
between you and me,
but there's a bit of
a scandal beginning
to brew around
her fiancé's family.
What's the matter?
Uh ... nothing.
[POSTMAN]
Excuse me...
I have a letter
here for the General.
Oh. Thanks.
Edmond Dantes?
Who's that?
[knocking on door]
[FERNAND]
Yes?
I'm sorry,
are you working?
No, come in.
I was just
finishing things up.
Father, I want to talk
to you about something.
You do, eh?
Have a seat.
With the election
drawing near,
there are so many urgent
matters to be attended to.
I can imagine.
Oh, this was addressed to you.
This is a funeral
invitation...
The thing is,
I just spent the day
visiting Valantine over
at the Villefort Manor.
Father, I would
really like
to get her far away
from that place.
I was wondering if there was
anything that you could do
to persuade her father
to go along with that.
She's in great
danger every minute
she stays in that house.
You see, Monsieur
Villefort might listen
if you were to ask him.
Why do you feel
the idiotic need
to poke your nose into another
family's private affairs?
What do you mean, why?
My friend is...
Neither you nor your
friend have any right
to throw someone else's house
into turmoil on a foolish whim!
How can you say that?!
You have no idea
what's going on!
If we don't do something...
My answer is no!
I don't want you
involved any further!
What are you so angry about?!
My friend is in
terrible trouble,
and you're telling me to just
walk away and abandon her?!
Forget it.
It was stupid of me
to even ask.
What's the matter, Albert?
You look upset.
I got into a shouting
match with Father, that's all.
Oh.
Mother, do you know someone
by the name of Edmond Dantes?
Did you say
Edmond Dantes?
Yeah.
That was the name on a letter
that came in for Father today.
The instant Father
saw that name,
he started acting
strangely so I was curious.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's really nothing.
I haven't been sleeping
well lately, that's all.
I guess with the big
election almost here,
you must be
really tired, too.
Yes, I suppose
that might be it.
You should take it easy.
[ALBERT thinking]
Who is he?
Who is "Edmond Dantes"?
[MERCEDES thinking]
That man long dead...
[ALBERT] What could
possibly be worth...
...coming all the
way out here for?
Hmph, damn!
I guess this means you were
sent one of these, as well.
Who's behind this?
I don't know.
I say it's just
a stupid prank.
I think we should
all get out of here.
But why would
they send for us?
Who ever it is knows about
the connection between us.
Well, well, well
the gang's all here...
Just who
the hell are you?
[MAN laughs]
Wait I know you!
That's right.
I'm your old
friend Caderousse.
Now that you've
made it big,
have you forgotten
about me along
with all those
unpleasant memories?
I see you're all big,
powerful men now,
not at all like
in the old days!
So, you're the one who's
behind all this, Caderousse?
What kind of
stupid stunt is this?!
But don't you see I've been sent
one of these invitations too!
Just like you. Look!
Huh?
Who could've sent these?
[VILLEFORT] It would seem that
someone else must know about us.
[ALBERT thinking]
What's going on here?
I wonder...
[CADEROUSSE] You're
asking me who else knows
the connection we all have,
besides the four of us?
Only the man
who signed this.
You're talking about
Edmond Dantes?
But he was sent
to Chateau d'If...
Yes, and he died.
The dead man has once
again come back to us!
Edmond would never
forget what we did to him.
Even from beyond
the grave.
He would never forget what
we did, not in a million years.
Whose body is in here, then?
Whose body is lying
there in that coffin?!
I don't understand!
Open it right now!!
No! No please!
Please I don't want to!
Stop whimpering and open it!
Please don't make me! Please!!
Go on!
Hurry up and do it!
Oh...! Boville...!
Come on! This way! Hurry!
Do you really think it's okay
for the three of us
to be doing this?
It doesn't matter.
There's no other way!
[thump]
Mama?
Did you hear a strange
noise upstairs just now?
No. But perhaps
your grandfather fell out
of his wheelchair again.
And with Valantine asleep,
there's really no one up there
to help him get back in it, huh?
It might turn out to be a good
rehabilitation exercise for him.
[EDOUARD laughs]
Hey! Watch it!
Right, sorry...
Huh...
Monsieur Noirtier...
I promise I will keep
Mademoiselle Valantine safe.
Huh?
Is it me, or is he saying that
he wants us to go that way?
I don't...
I don't believe it!
It was really her?!
You were gone a long time.
Where have you been?
That's none of
your business.
Oh...! I am
so offended!
Gosh, and here
I was gonna tell you
some great news you
were gonna like...
Tell me what?
Maximilien decided
to put his plan
for Mademoiselle
Valantine into action.
What?
The scene of the crime,
Villefort Manor.
Maximilien brought
two accomplices.
Franz and Chateau-Renault.
They came by here to get you,
but nobody could
find you anywhere.
[gasping for breath]
What's the matter?
Commander! Commander!
This is Edouard!
We've just spotted
all three criminals sir!
Good work!
Apprehend them immediately!
And just what do you
three kidnappers think
you're doing with my daughter?
[thump]
Exactly what are you
doing in here, my son?
Uh, nothing...
You seem to be doing
an extraordinary amount
of research about me.
What is it that
you're trying to learn?
Do you wish to know
something about me?
Or something about the
Count of Monte Cristo?
Allow me to tell you
all about both of them.
It will be far faster...
...this way!
Monsieur.
Monsieur!
What is it?
There seems to be
some sort of commotion
in front of the manor.
What?
It's them!
Summon my men immediately!
[ALBERT] The lovers depart,
and new misgivings arrive.
Unexpected news
leaves me at a loss.
Next Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo,
Act 11: "An Engagement Broken".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!