[NARRATOR] Madames and
Messieurs, good evening.
Anguish. Anxiety.
Because his soul
is pure and innocent,
it is all the more susceptible
to becoming troubled
and tarnished.
The tarnish becomes
an indelible stain,
a stain that gradually spreads.
When one is no longer
able to trust others,
is that when one
truly becomes an adult?
This is so amazing!
The Earth looks
so small from here.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Yes.
In the vast cosmos,
it is nothing more than
a tiny speck of dust.
And what's more, separated
from Earth by a distance
of 25 light years as we are
now, the light of our world
you are looking at,
was reflected off the
surface 25 years ago.
25 years ago?
Indeed. A lifetime...
[ALBERT]
Thank you.
I'm glad you
brought me with you.
Looking at them across
space, all the things that
I was agonizing over seem
so small and insignificant.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Perhaps, but you must beware.
Hatred and malice are amplified
in the darkness of space.
[ALBERT]
Huh?
[EUGENIE sighs]
Everyone has gone away now...
Franz has left, so has Albert.
[EUGENIE] Thanks for coming
on such short notice.
[FRANZ]
It's fine, I wanted to see you.
I'm going to have to go
away for a little while.
So will Albert
be going with you?
No. Apparently, he went off
somewhere on a trip of his own.
Even though his father's in
the middle of a big campaign.
Can you believe him?
What do you mean somewhere?
I'm sorry.
I just don't know
anymore than you do.
[EUGENIE]
I see.
The one thing
I can say for sure is...
...is that he's gotten
himself mixed up
in something
potentially dangerous
and still hasn't managed
to figure that out.
Franz, I, you know I--
Yes I know. You're a
victim of this, too.
Listen, whatever happens
from this moment on,
don't forget who you are.
[FRANZ] Look for the truth
with your own eyes.
[MONTE CRISTO] Before I
happily made your acquaintance
I traveled about the universe,
operating this entire
ship by myself.
You flew a huge ship
like this by yourself?!
Yes.
At the time, I was quite proud
of the fact that I was able
to develop sufficient skills
to operate it single-handedly.
Come. I want you to
take a look at something.
What is that?
[MONTE CRISTO]
The Milky Way.
In the ancient Orient, it was
called the River of Heaven.
[ALBERT]
River of Heaven?
This is what I have been
wishing to show to you.
It's just so beautiful...
[MONTE CRISTO] According to
legend, two lovers live on
the opposite banks
of the galaxy separated
from one another by
the River of Heaven.
They say that once a year,
they cross the river
and are reunited.
[ALBERT] That's a romantic
story, don't you think?
[MONTE CRISTO]
Long ago, I had a friend,
a sailor who was
born in Marseilles.
I heard that story
many times from him.
Well if that's the case,
I bet that your friend
was very much in love.
This sailor of which I speak
had a beautiful fiancée.
And a best friend with
whom he felt at ease.
[MONTE CRISTO] These three
were childhood friends,
and were always keeping
an eye out for one another.
Indeed, they were
very much like you,
Monsieur Franz, and
Mademoiselle Eugenie.
Unfortunately,
over the years together,
the best friend had fallen in
love with the sailor's fiancée.
And then,
the friend, who became
obsessed with the idea
of having her and would stop at
nothing to possess the fiancée,
framed the sailor for a
crime which he did not commit.
Unbeknownst to anyone, the poor
sailor spent more than a decade,
chained up in a prison located
in the depths of space.
I can't believe it...
[MONTE CRISTO]
But a miracle occurred,
and the sailor was set free,
whereupon he returned
to Marseilles.
Oh, that's good
I'm relieved to hear that.
[MONTE CRISTO]
However...
...that beautiful fiancée,
rather than waiting
for the sailor's return...
...had become engaged
to his friend instead.
So sad...
[ALBERT]
I wonder why she didn't wait
for the sailor to come home.
[MONTE CRISTO] Also, why did
the sailor's friend steal away
his fiancée in spite
of their friendship?
The sailor, having
been betrayed by both
his best friend and his fiancée,
never returned to Earth again.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Albert, why do you cry?
[ALBERT]
I don't know...
Until just recently
I was just like you are,
I never thought I could
believe in anyone.
That's what I told myself.
But for some reason,
when I see your face...
...the very thought of living
that way seems to me like...
...like the saddest and
loneliest thing in the world.
Promise me Count.
Promise me that
we'll always make sure
that our friendship is
the exception to the rule.
At the very least,
you're the one person
in my life I can trust!
The watch that I gave you,
is it still ticking away
the time as it should?
[ticking]
[MONTE CRISTO] Albert, I shall
be departing Paris sometime
in the near future.
[ALBERT] What do you
mean you're departing?
But, your Excellency
this is so sudden!
Wait a minute, it's not
because of your illness, is it?
Not at all.
The reason I came here is
that there was a certain matter
that I had to see to in Paris,
which is why I have
kept my residence
in town on the Champs Elysees.
However, the task I came
to accomplish will soon
be coming to its
final conclusion.
[CROWD cheering, chanting]
Morcerf! Morcerf! Morcerf...
[ALBERT]
No, don't say that!
Please, stay in Paris for good!
Or if staying in
Paris isn't possible...
...then I want you to take
me with you when you go!
I don't think I could
bear being apart from you!
I'm moved Albert...
I didn't realize you
thought that highly of me.
I do!
Your youthful passion
will cool to a wiser reason.
That's not true Count!
To me you are...
I mean the way I feel is...
[MONTE CRISTO]
One day...
One day I will ask you how all
that has happened
has affected you.
I can't help but to wonder
if you'll feel the same
when that time finally comes?
[BERTUCCIO] Excellency,
there's a message from Paris.
[MONTE CRISTO]
If you will pardon me.
[FRANZ] Monsieur Noirtier...
Please, you have to tell me.
Tell me what Gankutsuou is.
[gears humming]
What's this?
Hey, wait!
[FRANZ]
In the event of an emergency,
it is possible for a
third party who knows
the password to use this pen
to make contact with its owner.
Does this mean that if
I can figure out the password,
I can access your mind directly?
[ATTENDEE A]
She's so beautiful!
[ATTENDEE B]
Hey, isn't she--
[ATTENDEE A]
Right.
[ATTENDEE B]
She's Monte Cristo's--
[HAIDEE]
I realize that I am late,
but I have come to offer my
support to you, General Morcerf.
[FERNAND]
Well, very good then.
By all means, please step up!
[FRANZ]
Valantine... I'm certain...
...that your
grandfather told you
to remember a certain password.
Do you know what it is?
[NOIRTIER] Valantine, I am now
surrounded on all sides
by enemies. If, by chance
or devious design,
anything should
happen to my body,
it is essential that
you remember this flower.
[VALANTINE]
Blue rose...
My name is Haidee.
Many circumstances
brought me here,
and I have, for some time,
eagerly awaited the day
I'd be able to meet
General Morcerf.
You're very kind.
I am most honored.
This may sound rude,
but by any chance might
we have met somewhere before.
We have, ten years ago
and I will never forget it.
I was four years old
at the time, in Janina.
Janina?
You did us the great honor of
protecting us from our enemy.
You were an officer with
the Space Defense Force.
Oh, that's how you know me.
[HAIDEE] You were a patriot
defending our country.
At least that's
what I believed...
...until that day.
[FRANZ]
Done!
[FRANZ gasping]
[NOIRTIER] I never expected that
I would be using this channel
for this purpose...
Still, I have no
further need for it now
that I have left my life
in politics behind.
I wish to thank you, Franz.
You and your friends have kept
my granddaughter safe for me.
If there are things
in my memories that
might prove useful,
you are welcome to them.
It's the least I can
do for your kindness.
Take good care of Valantine.
[FERNAND]
Who-- who in the world are you?
[HAIDEE]
I am a sad woman
who had the terrible misfortune
to lose her father at Janina,
and then, before I could
even begin to grieve for him,
I was handed over to slave
traders with my mother.
[HAIDEE] My father fell
victim to the intrigues
of a certain young officer,
and lost his life as a result.
Oh!
I don't get it. What is this?
I'm-- I'm curious as
to what this story has
to do with these proceedings?
[HAIDEE] Are trying to
say that your past has
no bearing on this,
General Morcerf?
I mean Fernand Mondego.
[ATTENDEE C]
What? What is she talking about?
[ATTENDEE D]
Who is that woman?
[ATTENDEE E]
Mondego?
[NOIRTIER]
Gankutsuou is...
The Chateau d'If.
[NOIRTIER]
Edmond Dantes.
[HAIDEE] Ladies and Gentlemen,
I am Haidee Tebelin,
the daughter of Ali Tebelin,
the Pasha of Janina,
and his wife,
my mother Vasiliki!
[FERNAND gasping]
My father was destroyed
by your conspiracy,
and my mother,
chained in slavery,
lost her life to despair!
[CROWD gasping]
[HAIDEE] Surely there's no
justification for your actions.
What is this nonsense
you're spewing?!
Listen! This is a conspiracy!
[FERNAND]
A rebellion by malcontents
who are trying to
disrupt my campaign!
He's right! Grab that
woman and throw her out!
[ATTENDEE F]
It's a conspiracy!
[ATTENDEE G]
Don't fall for her lies!
Well then, I think
it's time for you to leave.
You shut your mouth,
Fernand Mondego!
Wha-What is this?
You stop looking
at me like that!
[MERCEDES] Are you able
to prove what you say?
[MERCEDES gasps]
[CONTESSA G]
Why, isn't that...
[HAIDEE] Proof that will never
fade for as long as I live.
Proof that was branded into me
when I was turned over to
the slave traders by that man.
This brand is a record of
everything that I have endured.
[VASILIKI]
Haidee...
This dagger belonged
to your father. Take it.
If you think that you're
about to be violated use it...
...and end your life.
Fernand Mondego.
You can change your name
to whatever you want,
but the blood of my father
that splattered onto your
forehead that day will never
disappear as long as you live!
[FERNAND grunting]
[HAIDEE sobbing]
A-Ali... I...
I know it wasn't a mistake...
I did the right thing.
He is my sworn enemy, the man
who stole everything from me.
So why do I feel like this?
Ali...
[HAIDEE]
I'll tell the Count...
I have to go tell
the Count right away!
He must stop this.
I can't let him go through this.
[ALBERT]
Count...
What's the matter.
Has something happened?
[MONTE CRISTO] Why do you
seem so anxious, Albert?
I'm not sure.
It's just that I sense
the presence of a deep
and terrible darkness near me.
[ALBERT]
Count...
What should I do--
[MONTE CRISTO] Albert, you
should return to Earth.
Without delay.
Huh?
At a time like this, you
should be by your father.
My father?
Tell him to watch
out for enemies.
You should watch your back, too.
Excellency. Has something
happened to my father?!
[MONTE CRISTO]
You should return home at once.
I will lend you
my ship, the Spada.
The time has come for you
to finally learn everything.
[MONTE CRISTO] This may very
well be the last time we meet.
No, Count!
Goodbye friend...
...and fare thee well.
[ALBERT]
Count...
Why?
I thought we were gonna
trust only each other...
Wait a minute Count!
Excellency!
[ALBERT panting]
Count don't do this!
Excellency!
Please let me stay!
Let me stay!
[MONTE CRISTO sobbing]
[MONTE CRISTO laughing]
Bertuccio!
We're going back to that
city where vice flourishes!
[SPADA] Stand by for
atmospheric reentry.
[ALBERT]
Everything was a lie.
The tiny rip becomes
an enormous tear,
and everything I had believed
in falls and is swallowed up.
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 16:
"Scandal."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!