[NARRATOR] Madames and
Messieurs, good evening.
A rage that is only
permitted by youth.
A pure, unadulterated rage.
That is the most
appropriate description
for the emotion expressed
by the young soul.
How exquisite it is!
How I desire it!
More! More!
[GENTLEMAN]
C'mon, baby, why not?
[WOMAN]
Hm...
Hmph.
[GENTLEMAN]
Hm?
[BOTH yelping]
[clock chiming]
[MONTE CRISTO]
I wonder...
Is it because you are a
soldier's son that you did not
give in to fear and
simply run away?
[MONTE CRISTO]
En garde!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[MONTE CRISTO]
Edmond... is dead.
This body retains only
his shape and appearance.
There is no longer anything
of Edmond himself
left within it.
I will show you absolute
proof that Edmond Dantes,
the man you once loved,
is dead and gone forever.
[MERCEDES]
Edmond...
[piano playing]
It's done!
[EUGENIE]
I'm cutting it pretty close...
[FRANZ]
I wrote a personal message
in a birthday card for Albert,
but, I feel like...
...I think we're a little too
old for that kind of thing
so I feel awkward.
Anyway, would you
give it to Albert
for me after I leave tomorrow?
Please? I'm begging you.
I think he that
should just be a man
and give it to him himself.
[grunting]
[MERCEDES gasps]
[panting]
[MERCEDES]
I don't believe it...
Stop!
[BERTUCCIO] Not so fast,
Madame! You must stay back!
But he's only a boy! Edmond no!
I can't let you pass Madame.
But you have to let me go!
That's my son out there
and I have a solemn duty
to keep him safe!
Try to understand, this
is a formal duel, Madame.
A formal duel,
in which Monsieur Albert
challenged the Count.
What are you talking about?!
Albert is still nothing
but a child! Call it off!
I can't.
You see Madame,
Monsieur Albert holds
the rank of Viscount.
In the eyes of the law,
this duel is legitimate and
can not be interfered with.
[panting]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[gasping]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[groaning]
Stop it Edmond!
Please, Edmond...
Your feelings of hatred...
Your unbearable pain...
Your infinite loneliness...
I'll...
...I'll bear the
brunt of it all!
Take it out on me!
[grunting]
[MERCEDES]
No! Stop!
Stop it!
[yelling]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[MERCEDES gasping]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[MERCEDES whimpering]
[MONTE CRISTO]
Countess Morcerf!
Watch closely!
Watch as I prove to you once
and for all that
Edmond Dantes is dead!
[MERCEDES]
Please, stop this...
Please!
Stop!
[grunting]
[ALBERT]
Oh, crap!
Hey Franz!
Why didn't you
wake me up?! Franz!
Fran--
[ALBERT]
He wouldn't...
[MERCEDES sobbing]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[MONTE CRISTO] I wonder. Is it
because you are a soldier's son,
that you did not give into
fear, and simply run away.
[grunting]
[gasping, panting]
[FRANZ gasps]
This is the moment,
I've been waiting for...
[NOIRTIER] To become Gankutsuou
is to lose your humanity.
As the substance of his body
is being replaced
with crystal...
...the temperature of
his heart drops and drops,
until it is eventually lost.
The instant he is released
from his unbearable suffering,
he will also lose his emotions.
His anger, his sadness,
his hatred...
Mondego will lose all of them.
[NOIRTIER] That is what
he fears above all else.
That is why his heart is the
last remaining part of him.
If he still retains even
the tiniest fragments
of the human emotion, his heart
will not be indestructible.
Gankutsuou... come
a little closer...
[FRANZ] That's right...
Come straight at me.
[ALBERT]
Franz...
Franz!
I will now prove
who the victor is...
[MONTE CRISTO]
Here and now!
[MONTE CRISTO gasping]
[FRANZ gasping]
[MONTE CRISTO groans]
[FRANZ grunting]
[MONTE CRISTO grunting]
[FRANZ gasps]
[MONTE CRISTO]
You were cursed since birth,
born from the unholy union
between that vile and cowardly
traitor Fernand Mondego
and Mercedes of Marseille.
You, who have walked in the
sunlight your entire life,
could not possibly know
the tale of the innocent man
who had his youth
stolen away from him,
and the old man who fell victim
to loneliness and starvation!
Fate has now come full circle,
and the curse is about
to reach its fruition!
Curse your fate,
and curse your parents
while you're at it...
...as you die by my sword!
[ALBERT]
No, don't do it!
Don't do it, Count!
Franz, no!
[MONTE CRISTO grunts]
[inaudible]
[EUGENIE]
I sure hope he likes it...
[FRANZ]
Albert...
[ALBERT]
Stay still.
The doctor's gonna be here
soon, so hang in there.
Sorry Albert...
But, you were really out cold...
Those pills worked
pretty good, didn't they?
Why Franz?
Why did you have to do it?
I'm sorry...
...that everything turned
out the way that it did.
[FRANZ]
But...
...you taught me how
to handle a sword in
one to one combat...
...so I put up a
pretty good fight.
You'd have been proud of me--
[ALBERT]
That's enough!
Don't...
Don't try to talk.
You idiot...
You still think you can...
...boss me around...
like none of this happened
Oh no, Franz!
Franz hang on!
Albert, listen...
Last night...
I had a wonderful dream.
[FRANZ]
Maybe it was last year...
Or was it the
year before last?
The two of us and Eugenie
went to Normandy together.
Do you remember that?
No, wait, was it in
the south of France?
The three of us sprawled
out on the beach...
...and we celebrated
your birthday.
It was so windy
that when we tried
to eat a piece of cheese,
it tasted like sand...
And Eugenie's
favorite hat blew away
in the ocean breeze...
She was really depressed
about it, remember?
Happy birthday...
Congratulations
on turning 16...
Franz...
[ALBERT] Franz, hang on
just a little longer...
The doctor's gonna be
here any minute now, okay?
You're gonna be all right...
You're gonna be all right.
[ALBERT]
Hey, Franz...
It's nice and warm
out here, isn't it?
Franz?
Franz!
[ALBERT] Alone, I walk
through the darkness
of the night as
I wait for the sun.
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 19:
"Even if I Should
Stop Being Me."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!