[NARRATOR] Madames and
Messieurs, good evening.
Even when wounded
and made to suffer,
he is reborn and makes
his way onto his feet.
Youth, what a
formidable thing it is!
However, our resolve
to have vengeance
will shatter even that.
Our grip on the
reins will never loosen.
[BUTLER]
Monsieur.
This just arrived from
the Baron Danglars.
I don't believe it!
What's wrong, Renaud?
This says that the
signing ceremony
for Eugenie's wedding is
gonna be held tomorrow.
[RENAUD] He must really be
in rough financial shape.
I can't believe he's rushing
the wedding like this.
[ALBERT]
Eugenie...
No stopping!
[ANDREA cackling]
[ANDREA]
Now that's just sad.
Looks like you lost your
pride in the same instant
that you lost your status.
[ALBERT] You can say
whatever you want about me,
but you are gonna
let me through here.
[ANDREA]
The princess is in a bit
of a foul mood at the moment.
She even did this to me.
What the hell?
What did you do to Eugenie?!
Please, isn't it obvious?
After all, we're to be
man and wife very soon!
She put up some fierce
resistance, though.
You bastard!
[ANDREA] Relax, I didn't do
anything as barbaric as
to force myself on her.
After all, I reminded
her that by marrying me,
she would not only be
safeguarding the lifestyle
of her own troubled family,
but also the Morcerf,
I mean, the Mondego family.
The instant
I mentioned your name,
she began to behave herself.
I owe you a debt of gratitude.
It seems, Albert, that
you're our sacred Cupid!
[ANDREA cackling]
[MONTE CRISTO] Tomorrow will go
off without a hitch, right?
What about the
Marquis, Cavalcanti?
[BERTUCCIO] Everything is going
according to plan, Count.
There is nothing to worry about.
Please try to get some rest.
Fine. You may go now.
[BERTUCCIO]
Yes, Excellency.
[MONTE CRISTO groaning]
Your Excellency.
[ANDREA] Complete
humiliation and despair.
Those will be my gifts...
...to my dearly beloved
father and mother
as well as my
delightful little sister.
[ANDREA cackling]
[ALBERT]
Eugenie...
Mademoiselle,
this gown is stunning,
you look very lovely!
How come?
'scuse me?
How come I'm standing here,
wearing a dress like this?
Now, now...
Today's is just the signing
ceremony attended by family.
That said, I think it'd be best
for you to wear
your formal gown.
Ever since I was a little girl,
I never enjoyed
talking with you.
Oh! Well, I never!
[DANGLARS] Eugenie!
Look at you, you're beautiful!
You really do look wonderful.
Andrea will be thrilled.
I'd like to be left alone.
Of course. I understand.
After all, things are
going to get hectic.
Well, with him in the family,
we've got nothing
to worry about.
[DANGLARS] He's young, but that
boy has nerves of steel.
[DAMROSCH]
Mademoiselle, your performance
at the opera house
was most impressive.
For me, meeting fresh,
young talent
is a joy that I would not
trade for anything in the world.
I was wondering if you
might possibly be interested
in coming to study at
our conservatory?
Signed, F. Damrosch,
Head Instructor of
Keyboard Instruments.
[BEAUCHAMP] Monsieur Danglars
is a slick customer.
He's trying to show everyone
his financial situation
has been stabilized by
inviting his stockholders
and having us cover
his daughter's wedding.
When the dust settles he'll be
in effective control of
Marquis Cavalcanti's fortune.
So, the question here's Albert.
You think he'll show up?
He will. He's no longer
part of the aristocracy.
That means he's free.
[PEPPO]
Albert!
I'm so sorry...
I couldn't disobey Luigi.
He's like a father to me...
Try to understand.
I won't ever ask
you to forgive me.
But at least let me try
and do something to help you!
[ALBERT]
Give it up.
I've had it with
everybody jerking me around!
[PEPPO] Just like you want try
to save the girl that you love,
I just want to help
the boy that I love.
Hey, look everybody,
here comes the bride!
[CROWD gasping]
[cameras clicking]
Eugenie!
Wow...
[CROWD gasping]
[CROWD murmuring]
Eugenie, you have no idea
how long I've
waited for this day.
[DANGLARS coughs]
Let's begin.
Madames and Messieurs...
...we will now carry
out the official signing
of the vows between
Eugenie de Danglars
and Andrea Cavalcanti.
We will begin with
the groom-to-be.
Yes.
Marquis, do you
have any objections
to sharing all
property, and stocks
and other assets owned
as well as assets acquired in
the future with Eugenie,
your bride-to-be?
I do not.
[NOTARY]
Please place your signature
on the marriage contract.
[NOTARY]
And now, the bride-to-be.
Mademoiselle, do you
have any objections
to sharing all property, and
stocks and other assets you own
with your groom-to-be,
Andrea Cavalcanti?
[ANDREA]
Hm?
[NOTARY]
What's the matter, with you?!
Hurry up and answer the man!
Something doesn't seem right...
[NOTARY]
Quiet, please.
I will repeat the question now.
Mademoiselle, do you
have any objections
to sharing all property, and
stocks and other assets you own
with your groom-to-be,
Andrea Cavalcanti?
[DANGLARS nervous laughter]
[DANGLARS] I'm so sorry, she
seems to be extremely nervous.
Naturally, she has no objections
to these arrangements.
Danglars must be desperate.
Yeah.
Go on! Sign the
contract, Eugenie!
[EUGENIE gasps]
[DANGLARS]
Huh? What the--
[ATTENDEE B]
Hey!
[ATTENDEE C]
What's going on?
Maybe I forgot to pay
the electricity bill...
Good one!
[ALBERT]
Eugenie...
[PEPPO] You know, they say
that Marie Antoinette,
the wife of Louis XVI, who
ruled during the 18th Century,
spilled ink onto
her marriage contract
during the signing ceremony,
almost as if to hint at
the terrible misfortune
that would later befall her.
What are you doing?!
[PEPPO]
This stain's the same thing.
I'd reconsider if I were you.
[CROWD gasping]
How dare you!
Who the hell do
you think you are?!
I want to know who
put you up to this!
Come on. Follow me.
[ANDREA]
Hold it! Where are you going?!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[ANDREA yelps]
Sorry, it's too good
a scoop to pass up.
[DANGLARS] Stop that,
you bastard! Give me that!
[DEBRAY]
Monsieur Danglars.
He is the least of your worries.
[CROWD gasping]
What? What are the
police doing here?!
[POLICEMAN]
Andrea Cavalcanti!
You're under arrest on charges
of fraud, falsification
of lineage, larceny, rape,
and six other offenses!
Eh?
Let go of me, you bastards!
Let go!
Shut your mouth,
fake aristocrat!
Fake aristocrat?!
Shove it, you miser!
Son of a...
I was so damn close!
My revenge isn't over yet!
Wha... Andrea, what
are you talking about?
Let go of me!
[CROWD clamoring]
[BOTH panting]
[ALBERT]
Eugenie...
It's you and me.
[BOTH gasp]
[ALBERT]
This way!
Is that...
[YOUNG ALBERT grunting]
[YOUNG EUGENIE]
I can't believe it.
You two are sneaking in
through that hole again?
[ALL laughing]
Last night I snuck out here
and weakened the wall a bit.
Big enough for adults.
Albert, I'd completely
forgotten about this.
Let's go.
Right.
[fabric ripping]
[RENAUD]
Hey!
Your chariot awaits, Princess!
At your service!
Renaud!
Bye. And fare thee well...
[PEPPO humming]
[BERTUCCIO] Reports say that
Cavalcanti has been arrested.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Bertuccio.
[BERTUCCIO]
Yes...
[MONTE CRISTO]
Do you dream?
[BERTUCCIO]
Yes, just like anyone else.
[MONTE CRISTO]
I no longer have dreams.
For I no longer sleep, you see.
And so in its place, I had this
golden box garden constructed.
But now, this room
is the only place
in which I may remain myself.
And this single glass of water
comprises my entire fortune.
And what of you?
What do you intend
to do when it's over?
[BERTUCCIO]
What... What I dream of...
...is to serve you
forever, Your Excellency.
Even if that dream can not be...
...there is no one but Your
Excellency that I can serve.
[MONTE CRISTO] When all
of this is finally over,
all of my wealth will
belong to you and the others.
Use it in the pursuit
of your own dreams.
[DANGLARS laughing]
Bankruptcy means nothing!
I still have money!
I'll run, and run, and run
and then I'll keep on
running some more!
Hurry up!
I'll escape all of them!
[P.A.]
Attention!
Passenger boarding
for flight 747 non-stop
to New York is almost complete.
All boarding passengers,
please report
to the boarding
gate immediately.
[ALBERT] Um, I...
[EUGENIE] Um...
You should go first, Eugenie.
No, you can go first, Albert.
[ALBERT]
I was terrible...
I suppose I was only
thinking about myself.
I never gave a second thought
to how you might be feeling.
So, from now on,
no matter what happens,
or where I am you'll always
be in my thoughts, Eugenie.
Oh, Albert...
You'll always be
in my thoughts, too.
[P.A.]
Attention.
Flight 747 to New York will
be departing momentarily.
Passengers intending to board,
please proceed to
gate 4 immediately.
Albert I...
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
Whenever things get tough,
you just play the piano.
The same piano that I've
always loved to hear you play.
And I'll always think
of you when I play.
Yeah!
You go and show
all those amateurs
in New York City how it's done!
[P.A.]
This is the final call
for Flight 747 non
stop to New York.
[RENAUD] So, Eugenie's
flight took off okay?
It did.
[RENAUD]
Is that from Eugenie?
[ALBERT] Yeah. She said she
had it hidden in the bodice
of her dress the whole time.
[RENAUD]
She did, huh?
[FRANZ]
To my dearest Albert.
Happy birthday.
By the time you
read this, chances are
that I'll no longer be with you.
So instead of
giving you a present,
I'd like you to hear me out.
Albert, this is important.
I don't want you
to ever hate anyone.
Something occurred to me.
Feelings of love
and feelings of hate
both start out as caring
deeply about someone.
It's sad,
but I think that sometimes,
when those feelings
aren't returned...
...feelings of love
change quickly into hate.
If something like
that ever happens,
I want you to think
back to our childhood.
Back to a time when
we could still love openly
and honestly no matter
how often we got hurt.
Albert, I want you
to go on living.
Love people openly without
being scared of getting hurt.
I was truly lucky
to have known you.
Franz d'Epinay.
I am forever in your heart.
[ALBERT sobbing]
Turn around.
I have to see him one more time.
There's something that
I have to talk to him about.
[ALBERT]
Destiny and revenge.
The merciless
gears keep turning.
Again, I find myself
standing before him.
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 21:
"The Golden Boy's
True Identity."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!