[FARIA] Friendship, is both
fascinating and beautiful.
Thanks to this power the boy
was able to escape
the bandits' clutches.
And yet, my friend said to me,
"there is nothing so inconstant
as the human heart."
[ALBERT whimpering]
[ALBERT panting]
[car horn honking]
Hey!
Albert! Come on!!
Time to wake up!
[EUGENIE] I can't believe
you were still in bed.
I have an important
visitor arriving today
and I've been really
busy getting ready.
You didn't have to come
if you didn't want to.
[EUGENIE]
Who's the visitor?
[ALBERT] Someone who
did me a favor on Luna.
Oh, I see, now.
It's that fake Count
something-or-other, right?
You haven't even met him!
How do you know he's fake!!
Oh, Speaking of visitors,
Chateau-Renaud said
that he's bringing
someone with him.
Why are you smirking?
You know, Albert, you've got
to be the most perfect target
for a con artist in
the whole of Paris.
What?!
Wow, she's
losing her temper...
Oh...
[ALBERT] What're
you angry about?
[EUGENIE]
I'm angry?
I thought I was just
enjoying our drive.
We're not in a
rally race, you know.
Oh, that's right.
You love puttering
around at a slow crawl
with no destination in mind.
Behind the wheel and in life.
My life is none of your
business, all right?
Get out! Now!!
Sure, I'll get out.
I don't want to
ride with you, anyway!
We're already here.
You know, for
the life of me,
I can't figure out why
you and I are still engaged!
Really?
Then maybe you should ride
in Debray's car on the way--
[tires screeching]
[car crashing]
[DEBRAY]
Oh, brother...
BEAUCHAMP]
Hey!
Would you please be careful?
[FRANZ]
Are you okay?
[VALENTINE]
Yes.
Hey, Albert,
over here!
Come take
a look at this!
Hey!
Geeze...
Are women the only
thing you can handle
Mr. Big Shot, Private Secretary?
Hey, every dull drive
needs a little bit of
stimulation, doesn't it?
I mean, next to me
is a hack reporter
and in the back seat is a couple
who just got engaged!
Humph!
[ALBERT]
That was amazing!
[MAXIMILIAN]
It was nothing.
I was in a special
forces unit in the army.
[BEAUCHAMP] Muscle
reinforcement processing, huh?
I've only heard
rumors about it...
[VALENTINE]
Thank you for your help.
Um, I'll get it myself.
Thank you.
What is your name, Miss.
My name is Valentine.
Hello. My name is...
Hey!
Hi Maximilian!
I'm sorry I'm late!
[CHATEAU-RENAUD] There I was,
out on a dangerous recon,
and suddenly I stumbled
into an enemy nest.
"And then--when I dropped
my favorite grenade,
I went as white as a sheet!"
From inside the
hole, I could hear
the Eridanians making eerie
threatening clicking noises.
Anyway, I'm not
one who subscribes
to the theory that
they're a sentient race.
In termperament...
Try a piece. It's very good...
Thank you, Miss Valentine.
Hmm.
Delicious!
You're a lucky man, my friend!
Once you and
Valentine are married,
you'll be able to dine
like this every day! Huh?
Humph.
[CHATEAU-RENAUD]
Um... Where was I?
Oh, that's right!
Just then, I thought
I was done for!
And who do you
suppose showed up then?
None other than this man.
Space Cavalry Captain
Maximilian Morel...
the man I owe my very life to!
[clapping]
You're quite a man
to save a complete klutz
who managed to blindly stumble
his way onto a battlefield.
So, Captain Morel,
where do you hail from?
My family makes its
home in Marseiiles.
[DEBRAY] That's a
pretty rough place.
[MAXIMILIAN]
And you?
Paris, of course!
The old town area,
admittedly.
The town of Marseilles...
What sort of a place is it?
When I was young,
it was a beautiful
harbor town filled
with sightseers and tourists.
[DEBRAY] Well now,
it's not a place that
a lady should even
consider venturing into.
[ALBERT] We haven't climbed
up here in a long time.
[EUGENIE]
What a great breeze.
[FRANZ] Those clouds
look a bit menacing though,
don't you think?
[thunder claps]
[DEBRAY]
What's the matter?
Something interesting
catch your eye?
[EUGENIE] Why do you
suppose there's a need
to divide the world up
with city walls and boarders?
The ugliness of the
outside world exists
for the purpose of making the
beauty of our kingdom stand out.
[ALBERT] Well, that may
be so, but I assure you
there's plenty of great
things outside these walls.
Don't you think we should try
to open our eyes a little
more and see the real world?
[BEAUCHAMP] Oh, have you
grown up a little now
that you're back
from your trip?
[DEBRAY]
I suppose you're right.
So go right ahead
and take on
all the troubles that
exist outside the walls.
That should quiet
those stinging pangs
of boredom of yours,
for a little while at least.
Now, this is what
we should be looking at.
The High Court of Justice.
Danglars Bank
And the place where
your father works,
Space Forces Headquarters.
The triangle of
Parisian power.
That is the true "great thing"
that we should inherit,
don't you think?
[EUGENIE]
To me, it feels like
we're the ones who
have been sealed in.
[thunder clap]
[MONTE CRISTO]
I am no longer all alone
wallowing in abject solitude.
For I am now surrounded
by the Furies,
the goddesses of vengeance.
In the cold bosom
of the darkness...
I awaited the dawn.
And once dawn came,
I cursed my flesh until
night fell once more.
I even prayed that
I would lose my sanity.
But those prayers
went unheeded.
Nothing changed...
And when I strove for
the peacefulness of death,
the Devil's cold, pitiless hand
grabbed hold and held me back.
Well... It won't be long now...
[DEBRAY] Boy, what
a terrible drive that was...
Maybe it was punishment for
skipping the Cabinet meeting...
[BEAUCHAMP]
Have candidates for the next
President
been chosen yet?
The word on the street is
that His Excellency Morcerf
is the front runner.
You must've heard a few things
from your father,
haven't you, Albert?
You know, you should really
watch your step around
Beauchamp, Maximilian.
He's a terrible man who will use
even his friends' scandals
as fodder for articles.
That's what they call
"impartial journalism."
[MAXIMILIAN] I read your
articles all the time.
But I do not approve
of the content.
I get that all the time.
[DEBRAY]
Where are the ladies?
[ALBERT] They went home,
because their dresses
were totally soaked.
[FRANZ] Chateau Renaud's
antique, too.
If they'd said something,
I would have given
them a lift home.
That'd be just like
tossing food to a monkey.
Hm!
[DEBRAY] So, the
Count of Monte Cristo?
[BEAUCHAMP] I can't
say I've heard of him.
There's nothing on him
at the Cabinet Secretariat.
Probably an
alias. Or...
A pretender or a con man?
I'll thank you to
refrain from idle gossip
about an honored guest
of the Morcerf home.
Where'd you say
that you ran into
this "honored guest"
of yours, again?
At Luna's Carnival when
we were there last spring.
Apparently, the honored
son of the family
was abducted by bandits.
Now that's too funny.
So Albert, were you seduced
by one of Luna's wily vixens?
[ALBERT coughs]
Oh, damn it to hell...
[horses galloping]
And then the Count came in,
and rescued me before the
kidnappers could kill me.
I suppose that you really do owe
your life to the Count, then.
It's clear that
he's kind as well as
incredibly wealthy and
probably well connected.
And what about
the distinct possibility
that this millionaire's pouch
was full of forged bills?
Look at this!
If he didn't come
from noble birth,
do ya think he would have a
watch as beautiful as this one?
When con artists are setting
up a trap in order to win
people's trust, they often
use trinkets just like that.
He's not a con artist!
He commands an
enormous spaceship...
...and he travels with aliens
and a beautiful woman
from Eastern Space.
He's free from the rule of any
government, and he mingles
freely with people of all
classes and walks of life.
In everything he does, he breaks
with established tradition.
That's right, and then,
once night falls,
he wanders the darkness
in search of the
lifeblood of maidens.
Yeah, well It wouldn't
surprise me one bit if he did.
The Count has a dark
and ruthless side to him
that doesn't seem to care
at all about human life.
Shut up Franz!
Albert! Just calm down!
Hey wait, there was
a case of a sailor
who contracted a local
disease on some planet,
and went around
sucking all the blood
he could find, wasn't there?
You know, you should
be careful, Albert.
I hear they enjoy the
blood of virgin boys
almost as much as girls.
So, you think he's
a vampire or something?
It's a lot more plausible
than Lunar bandits.
Yeah, or kindhearted
rich people.
[clock chiming]
[MAID]
His Excellency,
the Count of
Monte Cristo, Monsieur.
[ALBERT]
Show him in at once--
[footsteps]
[wind whirling]
I beg your pardon.
But the door was
open so I just entered.
[ALBERT] It's an honor
to see you again.
The honor is mine...
Viscount Morcerf.
Please sir, I preferred
you called me Albert.
Surely you and I are well
beyond those formalities by now.
As promised, allow me to
introduce you to my friends.
You already know Franz.
This is Lucien Debray.
He is a shrewd civil servant,
who already holds a key position
in the Interior Ministry
This is Beauchamp.
He's a newspaper reporter.
He can tell you anything you
might want to know about Paris.
It's not a mainstream paper.
It's more of a
third rate gossip sheet.
That is most fascinating.
This is Cavalry Captain
Maximilian Morrel,
he's a big hero of
the Eridanus campaign.
Nice to meet you, sir.
Ah, the very paragon of
a faithful, brave soldier
Oh you know Captain Morrel,
Your Excellency?
Not at all.
Count, we've heard
that you've come to us
from somewhere very far away.
You're trying to
interview him already?
Don't annoy our guest.
Look, I'm just doing
my job, okay?
On many worlds,
the taking of photographs
is seen as a vile and
reprehensible custom.
I must ask you to abstain.
Oh, sorry.
I didn't know...
In the course of visiting
many foreign worlds
when I was a sailor...
...I've become
thoroughly tainted
by the diverse customs
of other cultures.
I'm afraid that I must seem like
quite the uncivilized savage
to the good people of Paris.
So, what sorts of
places have you been, sir?
I have traveled
to many, many places.
To Eastern Space.
To Northern Space.
Even to the very
core of the galaxy.
And what about the Imperium?
Of course. To a sailor, there
are no such things as borders.
But couldn't that be considered
treason against the state, sir?
I see no reason
to swear loyalty to people
who will not extend
their hands to protect me.
Would you not
agree with that, sir?
I agree that you posses
rather bold opinions.
Yes, true enough.
I suggest that you
experience being cast out
into the vast universe
all alone as I did.
You would soon see
that the only one you
can count upon is yourself.
Set the table for tea at once.
So where do you hail from, sir?
I came into this universe
from a distant land that is
far beyond your imagination.
[FRANZ] Oh a place that you'd
rather we didn't know about?
Franz! Don't be rude!
If we're going to be associating
with the Count as friends,
shouldn't we at least know
where the man comes from?
That's quite understandable.
The very reason why
distinguished gentlemen
such as yourselves
are interested
in what I do or
say is because of the air
of mystery
surrounding me, is it not?
Were that not the case,
surely a rustic aristocrat
from the frontiers of space...
would not have been
given a seat at your table.
[MONTE CRISTO laughs]
Well, you do have us there.
But that's exactly why my
friends and I want to know
more about you
and your background!
Naive as ever, I see.
Peppo!
Is something
the matter, Albert?
Huh?
Um, no. Nothing...
All right,
what are you up to?
I wound up here.
After you left
I quit the bandit gang.
So I made my way here to Paris
to see if I could find work.
Okay. But what
are you doing HERE?
Why I followed
you here, Albert.
I'm lying!
It's just a coincidence.
There happened to
be an opening, that's all.
I want you to tell
me something, Peppo...
I'm impressed.
You remembered
my name. Albert...
Are you planning
to stay here for good?
Can't I?
Well, it's, how can
I put it to you...?
Look, don't
worry about it.
Let's just agree to keep
each other's secrets, okay?
[DEBRAY] Are you
interested in learning
that man's real identity?
Don't worry about it too much.
He's nobody special.
So what shall we do?
I was thinking that we
might all go out to Le Queen?
No thanks.
I think I'm gonna pass on that.
I think I'm gonna pass too.
What the hell...?
It's the Count of
Monte Cristo's voice...
Yeah, so, what's the big deal.
It isn't on the recording.
So, what sorts of
places have you been, sir?
I ha... ...eled to
...any, ma... pla...
And what about the Imperium?
...f cou...
To... sail... ..ere are
no ...uch thin... bor...
But couldn't that...
It's probably a
small malfunction.
So is this a malfunction, too?
What an absolutely
beautiful woman.
Oh. Thanks.
That's my mother.
She's rather young
in this portrait.
This vista is that of
Marseilles, is it not?
She likes
paintings like this.
I really don't know why she
chose that place as the setting.
It's magnificent.
Actually, my father
hates this painting.
He was going to take
it down and burn it,
but we placated him
by hanging it in my room.
[ALBERT'S MOM]
Edmond...
Is something wrong with it?
Not at all.
I'm afraid it's time
I took my leave...
Oh, no please don't go!
I was hoping you'd stay
and have dinner with us!
My mother and
father have really been
looking forward
to meeting you.
And if you're interested in
paintings, my mother and father
have many interesting
pieces in their collection.
My...
...what a stirring
painting this is.
This is my father's.
The ones that my mother
has collected are over here.
[ALBERT'S MOM] Oh!
This must be your visitor.
[ALBERT] My mother's past,
which I never knew.
The men in her past.
Adults who live in the past.
Next Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo,
Act 4: "A Mother's Secrets."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!