[FARIA] Madames and Messieurs,
good evening...
At Luna's Carnival,
I encountered an immature soul.
My friend turned and said to me,
"This shall be the
prelude to my vengeance."
But this soul was too
young and beautiful.
It is that alone which
gives me cause to fear.
[clock chiming]
ding, dong, ding, dong
[gun safety clicks]
[PEPPO]
Shall we go?
[HENCHMEN] All right,
that's enough fun and games...
...for now.
♪
[MAN]
So you met him, hm?
[FRANZ sighs]
[MARQUISE G]
My, you look so bored.
[FRANZ]
No, not at all.
It's a wonderful party.
Where is your friend?
Oh, you mean Albert?
Probably trying
to pick up girls.
Of course, all of
them will turn him down.
[MARQUIS X]
But this is terrible!
This is Luna, you know!
Strolling around alone
at night is suicidal!
[FRANZ] Surely
you're exaggerating.
[MARQUISE G] On the contrary,
he's quite right.
You'll get kidnapped
by Luigi Vampa, you silly!
Luigi Vampa?
He's a new
up-and-coming bandit!
They say he drags his
victims into the catacombs,
he tortures them, and kills
them in a horrible fashion!
Really?!
Surely the police won't
stand by and do nothing.
You mean you don't know?
The police on Luna
arrange their patrols
to avoid having to
deal with the bandits.
[MARQUIS X laughing]
Even my very own
cousin was robbed
by thugs and had his
arms and legs broken...
The poor fellow was left
lying stark naked in the plaza!
All because he dared to
speak to the bandit's mistress!
[MARQUISE G]
I'm sure he's fine.
Don't worry yourself, I'll
bet he's back at your hotel.
Would you care to dance?
♪
You know what, Franz?
I despise it when a party ends.
First one guest leaves,
then two, then three.
[sultry voice]
Especially at this hour.
You won't leave, will you?
You won't abandon
me like everyone else?
[chain clangs]
[TERESA]
Take him away.
[shower water running]
[MARQUISE G singing]
[YOUNG FRANZ]
You can't!
That's mean!
Come on!
Today is my birthday!
[GEN. D'EPINAY]
I'm sorry my son.
It's time for me
to go now.
[YOUNG FRANZ]
No, no, no!
[FRANZ'S MOM] But your
father is leaving to see
to some very important
people on business.
[YOUNG FRANZ]
Fine, see if I care!
I hope you never come back!
[police sirens wail]
[indistinct chatter]
[FRANZ]
Father...
[shower water turns off]
[shower door opens and closes]
I'm sorry I kept you waiting!
I think... I should go.
[PEPPINO yells] Hey!
Are you Baron Franz d'Epinay?
[PEPPINO smirks]
Wait! I know you...
I killed em all!
As for me,
I murdered ten people!
[PEPPINO chuckles]
This is for you.
[LUIGI'S VOICE READING]
"My Lord Baron Franz d'Epinay.
"I, Luigi Vampa, have
decided to take 'custody'
"of your young friend,
the Viscount Albert Morcerf.
"Hand over the sum
of 50 million ducats
"to my messenger immediately.
"Should you fail
to comply by sunrise,
"you may consider your
friend's life as forfeit."
Where is Albert?!
Don't worry,
he's a valuable hostage,
so I'm sure he's being
treated with all due respect.
If the money is
handed over right away,
he'll be returned to you
without so much as a scratch.
You should have died. Is this
how you people do things?
Well, sir, even I have
a lifestyle to maintain.
50 million is absurd!
Hey, you're an Aristocrat.
I'm sure you won't have
any trouble getting it.
Dawn comes fast on Luna.
If you value your friend's life,
I suggest you
make arrangements
for the money as
soon as you can.
[bell dinging]
ding, ding, ding
I want to make an
immediate withdrawal
of funds from the Bank of Paris!
I'm sorry, sir, but our
connection to Europe
is currently offline
due to the solar winds
which are interfering
with communications.
There's nothing you can do?!
How much?
[FRANZ whispering indistinctly]
[FRANZ panting]
[HENCHMEN smacking while eating]
[pounding on door]
Oh, Albert... Damn!
Say, it's awfully sad to see
a young fella like yourself
all alone on the
last night of Carnival.
If you want, I know a girl,
who'll make you feel fine...
Just be quiet and drive.
[FRANZ] It was at
my father's funeral,
that I first met Albert...
[YOUNG FRANZ crying]
[YOUNG ALBERT giggles]
[YOUNG ALBERT]
Don't cry.
[YOUNG FRANZ]
I'm not crying...
Cheer up!
I'll play with you.
Get lost!
Leave me alone!
[YOUNG ALBERT crying]
Uh, hey...
[ADULT FRANZ]
Ever since that day,
Albert and I have
been... inseparable.
[doorbell buzzes]
Damn!
What do I do...?
[clock chiming]
ding, dong, ding, dong
[PEPPINO yells] It's getting
close to sunrise, you know!
You're running out of time.
Have you raised the money yet?
[FRANZ]
Not yet!
I can't transfer the money
from Paris until morning!
Gee, that's too bad.
Luigi is such a stickler
for punctuality.
If you don't have the money
ready by sunrise,
I'm afraid your friend's
life, is as good as over.
Stop messing with me!
I suggest you hurry.
I'm sure that you
don't want to see
your friend die a horrible
death, My Lord Baron.
[FRANZ growls]
You bastard...!
[PEPPINO giggles]
Violence is so unseemly...
Right, My Lord Baron?
That's better.
A gentleman really should
worry about little things
like discretion, you know.
[MONTE CRISTO] There is
no more fascinating spectacle
in the universe
than a man's death.
Yes, it almost feels as
if one has actually
become God, does it not?
[BERTUCCIO knocks] His
Excellency, Le Baron d'Epinay.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Hmm?
I'm sorry to disturb you sir
at a late hour such as this...
Is anything the matter?
You don't seem like
you're feeling entirely well.
May I get you something?
Excellency!
I need a favor!
What's the big i--Huh?
[MONTE CRISTO]
50 million ducats.
You will take us to
the hostage immediately.
[PEPPINO whimpering]
[horses stampeding]
[horse whinies]
[PEPPINO whimpering]
The Colosseum!
Heh!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Have the two of you
been friends
for a long time?
Yes.
We've been best friends
since we were young.
Friends since childhood...
I see...
To always have a friend...
It's a wonderful thing.
[YOUNG ALBERT]
Who do you like, Franz?
C'mon, tell me!
You gotta at
least give me a hint!
[YOUNG FRANZ] You wouldn't
understand, Albert.
[TERESA]
Luigi!
It's almost time to do it.
[LUIGI]
Kill him.
[TERESA] So, have you
made your peace?
C'mon!
Let me kill him
ma'am, please?
No, let me!
Give it a rest, you two!
Wait till after he's dead,
then you can carve him up!
Now, then...
Put up a brave front
while you can...
I wonder what you'll
sound like when you cry?
[TERESA laughs]
[PEPPINO yells]
Hey!
Hey, guys.
Hey, uh...
There're visitors
here to see the boss.
Oh yeah? Who are they?
[PEPPINO laughs uncomfortably]
[PEPPO]
Teresa, please, don't!
Just wait!
We can't kill him yet!
Because... because
we won't get the money!
Besides...
There's still time
before the deadline.
[TERESA]
Stand aside!
Stop it!
If you're going to
use that, use it on me!
Your stupid squabbling
is really pathetic!
Thanks for trying but
you should stand back.
Are you trying to
disgrace the boss?
Don't worry,
I'll be fine. Go.
Know what I think?
You've fallen for her.
[clothing rips]
[PEPPO gasps]
[TERESA]
That's so sweet...
But believe me,
she's way too much for you
to handle, little boy.
But perhaps...
...what you want is
to become one of us.
Hmm?
You know what?
I think I'll brand you...
[TERESA smirks]
Hey! Leave her alone!
[fighting sounds]
[explosion]
[MONTE CRISTO] I have come to
meet with Signor Luigi Vampa,
whose reputation is notorious.
[LUIGI]
Who are you?
Just call me...
...Gankutsuou.
[LUIGI stammers]
The--The King of the Cavern?!
For one such as yourself
who dwells in the darkness,
I expect that I am better
known by that name.
I have your money.
Now, hand over the hostage.
I'm sorry, but you
missed the deadline.
"Always be punctual,"
is the motto I live by.
"Punctuality is the
politeness of kings."
Louis the 18th
would be proud.
Your words honor me...
...now die!
[LUIGI laughs]
[LUIGI gasps]
Very good...
Your skill is impressive.
But I'm afraid
you cannot kill me
no matter what
your abilities.
A-A-Are you...
really...?
No! Stay away from me!
[MONTE CRISTO chuckles] I do not
work for the authorities.
[demon voice]
And now...
If you would do me the honor
of returning my friend to me...
...all will be well.
[LUIGI screams]
I take it, you're
not injured, sir?
No I'm fine.
I had a feeling that somehow
you would come and rescue me.
If you wish to thank someone,
then you should thank
the good Baron d'Epinay.
You see, He was seriously
concerned for your wellbeing.
Hey! Miss!
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Thank you.
I never asked
what your name is...
My name is Albert.
I'm Albert de Morcerf.
Albert... I'm Peppo.
Hm...
Hm?
To tell you the truth...
I was starting to consider
the idea throwing my lot
in with those bandits and
living the life of an outlaw.
You all right... Albert?
What took you so long,
Huh?
You know, Franz,
I came this close to being
killed by those thugs...
I thought... you were dead!
Why did you...?
[MONTE CRISTO]
Do not concern yourselves
unduly over the matter.
It served as a...
a pleasant diversion for me.
[ALBERT But, sir, I must
do something to repay you.
All right...
...might I ask If you'd
grant me one small favor?
Anything at all!
Whatever you want,
just name it!
At some point very soon,
I should, like to take up
residence in Paris.
Really?
That's wonderful!
However, a rustic
aristocrat such as
myself has no
connections in Paris.
As such, might I impose on you
to act as my intermediary
into Parisian society?
Yes, of course!
[FRANZ scoffs]
Good!
I shall be calling on you
in Paris on May 22nd then,
three months from this day,
When I do, we will commemorate
the events of your visit here.
Hm?
Where in the world
did you find this?
Down at the opera house.
So it's yours?
Indeed it is.
It shames to have to say it,
but I've been searching for it.
See? This shows our bond.
Viscount, please, accept
the watch with my gratitude.
Think of it as a small
token of our friendship.
Really? You mean it?
It's a way to keep this day,
this very hour
stuck fast in time.
Wow! Thank you so much!
I'll cherish it always!
Sadly Carnival has ended, so
what are your plans now, Albert?
What adventures have you
in store for your future?
[FRANZ] Albert and I are
going to cut our trip short,
take the evening
shuttle back to Paris.
Hey, hey!!
Wait a minute!
I can't go, I've already
made plans of my own!
You just never
learn, do you?
So then what
are these "plans"?
What do you mean?
That's none of
your business.
Ahh...
Perhaps...
you've a rendezvous?
Uh! Sort of...
Love is a wonderful thing.
However, perhaps
you have not yet noticed.
Or perhaps you knew,
and arranged the
rendezvous regardless.
I do hate to be the bearer
of bad tidings, but...
What? She's a boy?
She's a boy?!
[ALBERT]
Come out and say it!
You think I'm an
idiot, don't you?!
[FRANZ]
Not really.
Yeah, right.
You're always looking down
on me, always laughing at me!
I'm not laughing at you!
If I laughed at every
bonehead stunt you pulled,
I'd laugh myself to death!
Anyway, you were--
Thank you Franz...
I owe you my life.
I really appreciate it.
[MONTE CRISTO]
The bitter fruits of betrayal
must be plucked from the tree...
[NARRATOR] At long last,
the appointed day arrives.
He comes to Paris along
with a summer storm.
Next Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo,
Act 3: "5/22, Stormy."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!