[NARRATOR] Madames and
Messieurs, good evening.
Those who forge
their own destiny
and those who balk at it...
Time visits all men equally
and imposes on them
a choice for the future.
When the final letter entrusted
to the young man is read,
what future will
that bring about for us?
[ALBERT]
Count!
There's something important
I have to talk to you about!
Let me in! Count!
Could he have
already left Paris?
[REPORTER] As Danglars Bank
stocks continue to plummet,
customers swarm teller
windows in a desperate attempt
to withdraw their savings.
At this time, the whereabouts
of senior bank
management officials...
You're a bunch of idiots!
[DANGLARS] I have your
precious treasure right here.
After a fire, hold a
fire sale I always say.
He, he, he!
With this stake money
I'm as good as gold.
With five trillion francs,
I can beat any speculator.
Now, then, which stock
should I start with?
Damn it. This is so
inefficient without Michelle!
[DANGLARS gasps]
Good afternoon...
Monsieur Danglars.
Count, you startled me!
[DANGLARS]
I-I was under the impression
that I had bought out all
the seats on this flight.
I have come here from Paris.
I had to chase you.
Why would you do that?
[MONTE CRISTO]
I had hoped to have you
accommodate me with funds.
Five trillion francs
in cash, right now.
Wha--? Five trillion?!
According to our
contract there is
no upper limit to
my line of credit.
None at all.
You haven't forgotten?
Oh no, Excellency.
Believe me, I haven't
forgotten at all.
But you've caught me short.
Since I'm traveling,
I'm really not carrying any--
[MONTE CRISTO]
But you're carrying cash
in that case, aren't you?
Oh this--
[MONTE CRISTO]
Come, now. Give it to me.
I couldn't!
You see this money is--
Now...
Now.
Now!
[gun fires]
[DANGLARS laughs]
If you'd just gone home,
you wouldn't have had to die.
Stupid fool.
I'm gonna have to do
something about the body...
[DANGLARS gasping]
[DANGLARS screams]
[DANGLARS]
But... But you're--
[MONTE CRISTO] My good
Baron, as greedy as ever.
[MONTE CRISTO]
You haven't changed one bit
from the old days.
But how?
[MONTE CRISTO] Look closely
at my face, my dear Baron
and think back.
Remember the face of the man
you consigned to
oblivion 25 years ago.
Remember the
face of your friend,
whom you incriminated
with your false accusations.
With your lies!
E-Edmond Dantes?!
[LECLERE]
Edmond...
Take good care of this.
You will be the next
captain of the ship.
Yes, sir.
[DANGLARS] You called
for me, Acting Captain?
Yes, I did. Danglars
these figures you entered
in the trade ledgers
just don't add up.
Oh, um well you see...
When we were docked at Alpha
Centauri last month, there were-
[EDMOND]
Listen here!
This is embezzlement, Danglars!
[EDMOND]
I'll overlook it this one time.
But if I ever see
it happen again...
Hmph!
I guess you think you're
the Captain already, huh?
[CADEROUSSE]
All right everybody!
Three cheers for Edmond!
Young Mercedes has fallen
head over heels for that boy!
Compared to him,
all the other guys
who hit on her are
no better than garbage!
Garbage!
[DANGLARS] So, Edmond
and Mercedes are finally
having their engagement party?
To them!
I pray they'll live
happily ever after! Forever!
Congratulations...
There's really no such
thing as a perfect man.
You agree, Fernand?
[DANGLARS]
I mean let's face it, Mondego.
Every man ought to have
a flaw or two. Right?
[FERNAND]
What're you getting at?
Heh.
[DANGLARS] When Captain Leclere
was on his deathbed,
he entrusted Edmond
with a letter to protect.
What do you suppose was in it?
I heard it was a
secret document addressed
to Parisian dissidents.
[FERNAND gasps]
[DANGLARS] Eh? Pretty
interesting, isn't it?
Now, if we were
to humbly bring it
to the government's attention,
what do you suppose
would happen to Edmond?
[DANGLARS cackling]
[MERCEDES]
Edmond! Edmond!
[EDMOND] Mercedes! This is
all some kind of mistake!
Don't worry about me!
Y-You're still alive?
[DANGLARS] This sure
brings back old memories...
Those days on the ship,
when we all sailed the
sea of stars together.
And then...
What are you going to do to me?!
If you think that I was
the one who set you up,
you've got it all wrong!
I had nothing to do with it.
I-It was Fernand!
He did it to get your woman!
I only told him about the letter
because he was so
depressed about everything.
We all thought that it
would be a funny prank
if we reported the
letter was yours...
I swear I only
meant it as a joke!
[MONTE CRISTO] Out of jealousy
and unjustified resentment,
your cohorts sent an innocent
young man to rot in prison.
Is that not the case?
No!
It wasn't like that!
I hated you!
You were nothing but a constant
nagging irritation to me!
It made me sick to look at you!
I didn't have any reason!
I just wanted to get
Edmond Dantes out of my sight!
I wanted him gone forever!
[DANGLARS]
These are...
This is amazing!
[MONTE CRISTO] I appreciate
your candor, Messieur.
Now, accept my humble
way of repaying you
for the cost of your bullets.
[DANGLARS] Please!
Wait a minute! Edmond, wait!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Rejoice, Messieur.
For everything that you touch
turns to glimmering gold.
No! Wait!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Take it.
Ugh...
Humph!
Hey! Wait don't leave me here!
Please!
Wait! Come back!
[MONTE CRISTO]
And that is one.
[BAPTISTIN sighs]
[BAPTISTIN] Hey, find somewhere
else to sleep, will ya?
Where is he?
[BAPTISTIN] You've been
waiting here all this time?
Geeze, what a tenacious
young man you are.
Don't mock me! Not now--
"I simply must speak
with the Count right away!"
Is that what you're
trying to say to me?
Lay off!
You're his flunky,
it's none of your business!
Yes, you're right.
Gosh, and here I was
about to tell you exactly
where His Excellency
is right now.
[BAPTISTIN] Come on, wipe
that look off your face.
The Count's in space.
And right about now,
I bet Danglars is--
You're kidding me!
Look, kid, you
can struggle against
what's happening all you want,
but it won't do you any good.
Hey, you're the Count's
right-hand man, aren't you?!
Then why the hell don't you try
to stop him
before it's too late?
Why can't you understand
how the Count
really feels and keep him
from doing something terrible?
Don't stand there and talk
like you know everything!
Why can't you understand
that he has no choice?!
He has to get revenge
no matter what.
He can't forget the past.
He has to act in
spite of how he feels.
[ALBERT]
Yeah well, I suppose, I mean...
...maybe what you're
saying about him is true.
But there's something that I
have to tell the him right away!
Right. They say that
Villefort's first trial
is gonna be tomorrow.
What?
[BAPTISTIN] Now, it's time
for little boys to be in bed!
Go home!
[BAPTISTIN] Excellency,
this kid might turn out
to be a whole lot tougher
than you think he is.
[JUDGE A] This trial in the
case of the poisoning
in the Villefort household,
as well as the attempted murder
of the Count of Monte Cristo,
will now come to order.
[VILLEFORT] I would like to make
a statement before we begin.
My actions were
not out of self-interest.
I did what I did in order
to protect the peace
and public order of Paris.
As such, I plead not guilty
with no shame or remorse
for my actions, and will be
acting as my own attorney.
[GUARD] You can't come in if
you don't have a permit!
Go away!
[PROSECUTOR] This poisoning was
the result of the attempt
by Heloise, Monsieur
Villefort's second wife,
to poison her stepdaughter
Valentine in order
to get at her inheritance.
Monsieur Villefort
falsely accused
the Count of Monte Cristo
of these crimes
and then attempted to kill him.
Rather than being motivated
by love for his wife,
these acts were an attempt--
[VILLEFORT]
How dare you?!
Monte Cristo is a
disruptive hooligan
who is intent on
throwing Paris into turmoil!
And possibly a spy
sent here by the Empire!
[JUDGE A]
Did he say spy?
[JUDGE B]
He did.
As a long serving and faithful
officer of the court and crown,
I call for the arrest of
the Count of Monte Cristo!
[PROSECUTOR]
Is that really the case?
[VILLEFORT]
Of course!
[PROSECUTOR]
I would like to call a witness
who will help shed some
light on the defendant's past.
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
Order in the court!
The witness will state his name.
[ANDREA] My name is
Andrea Cavalcanti your honor.
Admittedly, it is an alias.
[JUDGE A] The witness will
answer the question truthfully.
In the orphanage where I grew
up I was called Benedetto.
But I don't know what
name I was born with.
[PROSECUTOR] I see here that
you were known to the public
as the head of a notable
aristocratic family, is that so?
Oh please, no,
I'm not an aristocrat.
I'm nothing of the sort.
I was abandoned as an infant,
raised in an orphanage,
and once I got out, I did
everything under the sun.
[ANDREA]
Larceny. Arson. And even murder.
And what does this have to do
with the case before this court?
[ANDREA]
A great deal.
I'm here to tell the story of
the secret behind my birth.
[VILLEFORT]
Stop joking!
[JUDGE A]
Order in the court!
Continue with your testimony.
[ANDREA] I was born in
Auteuil, in the mansion
on the estate that the
Count of Monte Cristo
has been recently
using as his villa.
[ANDREA] I was buried alive
immediately after I was born.
In a tiny little coffin.
The man who fathered me
must have been
in a complete panic.
A judge with a bright
future having a child
by his secret lover?
Even in Paris that sort
of thing is frowned upon.
So he sheltered my mother
in the mansion at
Auteuil, and took--
Your Honor!
Perhaps it would be prudent
if we adjourned for the day.
The defendant
is to remain silent!
Obviously he's nothing
more than a hired blackmailer!
Who paid you to do this?!
[ANDREA]
Is this any way to treat me?
After all, it's
been 17 years.
[PROSECUTOR] The people enter
into evidence the results
of DNA testing on the
defendant and the witness.
[VICTORIA gasping]
[JUDGE A]
What is this?
[ANDREA]
The coffin.
The coffin that my parents
gave to me instead of a crib.
[VICTORIA]
Please, stop this!
I begging you! No more!
[ANDREA]
Excellent timing.
Allow me to introduce my mother.
This is Baroness
Victoria Danglars.
Come now, isn't
that true, Mother?
Father shoved me into this box
and then buried me in the garden
behind the mansion, didn't he?
[VICTORIA screaming]
[BABY crying]
[VICTORIA]
My boy...
My baby is that really you?
[VICTORIA gasps]
[VICTORIA]
Forgive me! Please, forgive me!
[VILLEFORT]
Be quiet! Shut up this instant!
That woman's out of her mind!
[ANDREA]
Father!
Don't say such
things about Mother.
That was terrible.
It's him, isn't it?!
[VILLEFORT] He must be the
one who put you up to this!
Your Honor, the
two of them made up
this entire preposterous story!
It's the only explanation!
I mean, that baby
is dead and buried.
He's long gone.
He couldn't
possibly turn up and--
[PROSECUTOR] Your Honor,
please enter the defendant's
statement into the record.
No! I only meant that he--
[JUDGE A]
Order!
[VILLEFORT]
You have to listen to me!
This is all a trap!
You lousy con artist!
The servant who saved my
life left this scrap of cloth
with me when he sent
me to the orphanage.
He must have wrapped
me in this warm cloth
so that I wouldn't
freeze to death.
My whole life, this has been the
most important thing
in the world to me.
After all Father it's
not just a piece of cloth.
It's the thing that
connects me to you.
Then... you really
are who you say you are?
[ANDREA]
I'm sorry, Father.
But if I hadn't
resorted to this,
you would have
never accepted the fact
that I'm really your son.
[ANDREA]
I so wanted to meet you...
Father...
[VILLEFORT groans]
[ANDREA]
Goodbye Father.
[VICTORIA screaming]
But why? Why, son?
[ANDREA cackling]
You can all kiss my ass!
Every one of you!
Just looking at your faces
makes me want to puke!
In the end, all you bastards
are bloodthirsty animals
no different from us!
[ANDREA]
You hide your filthy natures
behind those respectable masks!
You do! And you! And so do you!
[ANDREA cackling]
[MERCEDES] I seem to recall
a Monsieur Dantes
living here a long time ago.
[RESIDENT] I wouldn't know
about that, Madame.
This place has stood empty
for a quite a while now.
[MERCEDES]
Edmond...
[LOUIS]
Mercedes...
[LOUIS] You're still a young
and beautiful girl...
And... And something tells me
my boy isn't coming back again.
Mercedes, you
shouldn't spend your life
looking after a
weak old man like me.
I think you should go...
Summer is almost over.
[MERCEDES]
No! I won't!
He'll come back! I know it!
[MERCEDES sobbing]
You bastard!
How are we feeling?
Better, I hope?
Who are you?
What do you want?
Why are you doing all this?
[MONTE CRISTO]
Oh, dear, have you forgotten?
What?!
Have you forgotten me,
the innocent man you
convicted 25 years ago,
when you were the district
judge for Marseilles?
[MONTE CRISTO] The instant you
discovered that your own name
was listed in that letter,
you decided to secretly
eliminate the man
from whom you had taken it.
[VILLEFORT]
Edmond Dantes?!
Is that you?!
I don't understand.
[MONTE CRISTO]
The man whom you once knew
by that humble name
died many years ago
in the prison of
the Chateau d'If
and returned to
life as Gankutsuou.
That letter you were
carrying was dangerous!
For us and for all of Paris!
If I hadn't done something,
the government would
have fallen into utter chaos!
You see, I had no choice!
[MONTE CRISTO] You are indeed
a patriot, Monsieur Villefort!
However, the real
motive for your actions
was to protect
yourself, wasn't it?
[VILLEFORT] It was to
maintain law and order.
[MONTE CRISTO]
And that meritorious deed
made you the man you are now.
Humph! All for nothing.
By the way, that needle
was dipped in poison.
Wh-What?!
[MONTE CRISTO]
That poison will be a blessing.
It will rot your brain
and send you to a place
where no decent person could
convict you of any crime.
No. No, wait!
No! No! Not that! No!
[MONTE CRISTO] Villefort, a poor
servant of the Crown...
The velvet wings of your
precious law will cradle you
until the end of your existence.
[MONTE CRISTO]
And that makes two.
[GUARD]
Start walking.
[ROBOT]
Warning!
Eastern Fleet flagship has
crossed Rubicon Line!
Be advised.
According to Article 59
of the Military Code,
this is considered an act of--
[ALBERT] In spite of everything,
the past will not let go of men.
Vengeance gives
rise to violence,
and the cycle of
sorrow continues.
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 22:
"Counterattack".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!