[NARRATOR] Madames and
Messieurs, good evening.
"Death is nothing
but a release,"
my friend once muttered
to me in a moment of candor.
"If death is a release,
what is it that you wish
to give to them for it?"
My friend answered
me succinctly.
"I will give them eternal
suffering and remorse."
All right Count.
I'm done with running away.
I want the truth. Now.
[STAFF OFFICER]
General...
I beg your pardon
but are you sure
that we're doing
the right thing?
Don't worry.
I know that you're afraid.
You see, there's
never actually been
such a thing as "the truth"!
The truth is something
that you yourself create
based on your own
personal convictions.
Even if it means setting
aside our conscience
and turning our
weapons against our own?
People never really
look at their conscience.
[FERNAND]
What they see is the truth
that is standing
there before them!
[ALBERT]
It was the day before he--
The day before Franz died.
That day, I walked
all the way here
after you confessed
your plans to me.
My world turned
totally upside down.
I clearly remember
how my tears flowed.
They wouldn't stop.
No matter how much I tried,
they just wouldn't stop.
[ALBERT]
Franz...
Franz left some
parting words to me.
He said never to hate anyone.
He said that feelings of
love and feelings of hate
both start out as a
deep caring for someone.
Excellency!
Please, you've gotta tell me!
Tell me everything!
[GUESTS laughing, murmuring]
Congratulations!
[FRIEND] A toast to Edmond's
last night of bachelorhood!
[GUESTS]
Cheers!
[POLICEMAN]
We're looking for Edmond Dantes!
[SUBORDINATE]
Madame.
We're here on direct orders
from General Morcerf
to collect you.
The General will soon
be entering Paris.
He will form an
interim government,
and we will see the
birth of President Morcerf
before the day is out.
Fine, take me with you.
Take me to see him now.
[ASSEMBLYMEN clamoring]
Isn't that...
Fernand Mondego?!
The National Assembly
is now under the control
of forces loyal to
the Eastern Fleet!
Have you lost your mind?!
This is a blatant
act of high treason!
Morcerf! We'll fight you!
How dare you do this?!
I suggest you all
hold your tongues.
You traitor!
The National Assembly
is hereby dissolved!
I declare a state
of martial law in Paris!
[MONTE CRISTO]
25 years ago,
I was a young man
named Edmond Dantes.
And I was very naive.
Indeed, before that day,
I knew nothing of
mistrusting others.
I passed the days,
working and praying
for the happiness of
my father and fiancée.
Edmond Dantes!
You are under arrest
as a prime suspect
in the assassination
of the Prince!
Oh Edmond!
Edmond!
[EDMOND] Mercedes! This is
all some kind of mistake!
Don't worry about me!
Let go of him! Edmond!
Edmond!
[VILLEFORT] You've been
charged with a crime.
But I haven't done anything!
It was an anonymous tip.
According to the accusation,
you have in your possession
a letter that contains the facts
behind the plot to
assassinate the Prince.
What in the world
are you talking about?
Before your captain
passed away I believe
he entrusted you with a letter.
That's right, the
Captain's last request was
that I deliver the
letter he gave me
to the intended
recipient upon our return.
Hm...
Paris, Rue Coq-Heron,
house number 13.
That's Monsieur Noirtier...
[MONTE CRISTO]
That letter contained the names
of all the men involved in the
planning of the assassination
plot against the Prince.
But Villefort's name
was included on the list.
And I had unwittingly
handed the letter over to him.
A man who had much to
hide and much to answer for.
[VILLEFORT]
I see.
You were simply carrying out
your duties faithfully.
Well then, Dantes.
Why don't you let me
take care of this letter
and sort things out for you?
I expect that they'll be
releasing you soon enough.
Thank you for all your
help, Monsieur Villefort!
[EDMOND]
How can I ever repay you?
My fiancée must be
anxiously waiting for me
to return from this ordeal.
[VILLEFORT]
Oh, by the way, have you spoken
of this letter to anyone else?
No, Monsieur.
I fully obeyed the Captain's
last request and kept it secret
from everyone,
including my father.
[EDMOND] No one else
knows of this letter.
Except you.
I see.
[VILLEFORT cackling]
[MONTE CRISTO]
Here in Paris, it is believed
that the Prince perished in an
assassination plot orchestrated
by alien enemies of this world.
But the plot was devised
by people here on Earth.
Those gluttons who had reaped
enormous profits from the
never ending war wished for
it to continue raging forever.
But that's...
[MONTE CRISTO]
With the assassination,
prospects for peace
became a distant memory.
And just as those men desired,
the war spread
across the frontier,
growing ever more
intense with each new day,
in the name of avenging
the assassination.
And one poor unlucky man
was consigned to oblivion.
Just so they could
keep their secrets.
Those who exploited me
and had me imprisoned
eventually became prominent
and powerful figures
in the legal and
financial circles of Paris.
And the man who had climbed to
the very top of the military,
turned his eyes
and his ambitions
to the power of the Presidency.
That is how it happened.
[EDMOND] Please! Wait!
Call Monsieur Villefort!
I don't understand!
What crime do they
think I've committed?!
I haven't done anything wrong!
I haven't broken any laws.
I'm... I'm innocent!
[MONTE CRISTO]
What I found waiting for me
when I was imprisoned within
the Chateau d'If was the very
embodiment of endless despair.
An automated fortress
constructed to defend
against enemies
along the frontier.
I became a component
of its control system.
In that place,
that never-ending Hell,
I was not even allowed
the choice of death.
[EDMOND groaning]
[EDMOND grunting]
[EDMOND] Please, kill me!
Please, kill me right now!
I don't care...
I don't care about salvation.
Even if my body should
disappear forever...
...I will find those who took
everything away from me.
Those who drove me to ruin,
who put me in this hell,
and give them the cruelest,
most diabolical
punishment imaginable!
Not even the respite of a death!
What they'll get is suffering
that will last for eternity!
[GANKUTSUOU]
My friend...
My friend!
[GANKUTSUOU]
My friend.
[GANKUSTUOU]
Hope...
Grief...
Longing... Resignation...
Rage... Terror...
Despair... And then,
hope once again.
For thousands of years,
I have waited.
Waited inside this body for
the arrival of a man like you.
I don't understand...
[EDMOND]
I don't understand!
[GANKUTSUOU]
I am one with you.
And you are one with me.
To you, I give my
knowledge and my power.
And to me, you give
your body and your soul!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Albert...
I am the Wheel of Fortune.
Indeed, it is now
only my unyielding
and merciless resolve for
vengeance which propels me
toward my final goal.
[ALBERT]
Count!
Wait a minute!
I want you to stop
all this and stay!
And give up on your
revenge. Come back!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Only one man may give an order
to the Count of Monte Cristo...
...and that is the
Count of Monte Cristo himself.
Excellency, are you
saying that there is
no one left inside your heart?
That you no longer feel?
Is that what you mean?
Are you saying to me that
the Count of Monte Cristo
that I knew no longer exists--
Excellency!
Father...
Father please, stop this...
Father!
[ANNOUNCER] The Cabinet and
National Assembly have
ceded full governing
authority to the Space Forces.
Martial law has been declared!
Citizens are asked to
surrender all weapons
and refrain from
venturing outdoors!
I repeat, the Cabinet
and National Assembly
have ceded full governing
authority to the Space Forces.
Oh no! My money! My money! Ugh!
Well, well, what have we here?
Ha! So, it's all come to this.
[ANDREA] Is this really
how the world works?
[VILLEFORT] He he he!
Guillotine! Guillotine!
Guillotine!
It's death for you!
[DANGLARS cackling, whimpering]
[ALBERT]
Baptistin!
Out of my way!
You can't stop me!
Humph!
Take this with you.
What is it?
Call us if anything happens.
Just don't turn it off.
[BAPTISTIN] Don't tell the
Count about this, okay?
[FERNAND] Underground
fortresses! Weapons depots!
There isn't a single one in
the land that isn't known to me.
I'm going to give them
all a taste of my power!
Let's get to it!
Your next target is
the Arc de Triomphe!
[FERNAND]
Humph!
Spineless cowards.
[FERNAND cackling]
Oh! Mercedes! Good!
[FERNAND]
I've been waiting for you!
Darling! All of Paris is
finally kneeling before me!
[MERCEDES]
I just can't imagine that all
of this is what you
really wanted... Fernand.
The dreams that you told me
about were all full of hope.
Dreams of a free
and peaceful world.
[FERNAND]
But there is hope, Mercedes!
Don't you see,
the pain is necessary
for good of the country!
[MERCEDES]
Fernand...
[FERNAND]
As of today,
you are the First Lady
of the land, Mercedes!
There's nothing that you
need to be afraid of now!
Edmond is alive,
and he's been right under
our noses this whole time.
He's what?!
[MERCEDES] The man who was
once your best friend...
The man who was once my fiancé
and the love of my life...
...has returned to us now
as the Count of Monte Cristo.
[MERCEDES]
He survived.
But how... How could that be?
That letter was...
That's what it was about...
So Dantes has come back?
He's come back
to get his revenge?
To take out his vengeance on us?
[MERCEDES]
Vengeance? And Revenge?!
What are you
talking about, Fernand?
I thought that you and Edmond
were the best of friends.
What do you mean, revenge?
Why in the world would
Edmond Dantes want
to get revenge against you?
[FERNAND]
He and I... were best friends?
I never once thought of that
bastard as my best friend!
How could you not
have known that?!
You've always been like this!
Do you have any idea
how much that naiveté
of yours hurts people?!
Humph!
I admit it.
The man who sent
the letter that got
Edmond arrested
was me, all right!
If I hadn't, he'd have been
made captain of his own ship...
...and I would've spent
my life as a menial laborer
at the Marseilles docks!
I had to...
I had to do it.
There was no choice.
You understand?! It was you!
It was your naiveté
that cast Edmond straight
into the depths of misery!
[FERNAND]
Oh...
I... I can't believe I said
such horrible things to you.
I'm sorry...
Forgive me!
[FERNAND] Mercedes, I love
you more than anything.
[MERCEDES]
Come, Fernand.
Let's you and I
leave Paris together.
[FERNAND] I've had it up to
here with always having
to be the pitied
underdog to him!
I'm sick and tired of living
in that bastard's shadow
You...
You are not leaving!
You're staying here right
where you belong, by my side!
In that case...
...I'll never forget
our time together.
I thank you.
[MERCEDES]
Goodbye, Fernand.
[FERNAND]
Mercedes...
Mercedes! Mercedes!
[gun fires]
No! Mother!
[ALBERT] Mother! Are you all
right?! Mother! Mother!
Father, why?
Why did you do this?!
[FERNAND] Everything I did,
I did because I loved her.
And I also loved you,
more than anything.
I really did.
Father, no...
[FERNAND]
Not yet...
I still have him to deal with.
[BAPTISTIN]
Albert!
Albert?
This isn't over yet!
Eat this!
Hey, Albert!
[BAPTISTIN]
You crazy kid...
[BERTUCCIO]
Where's Mondego?
[BAPTISTIN]
Tch! This ain't good...
Father... why...
[FERNAND]
As long as...
As long as that bastard is still
alive, I can't die, either!
[FERNAND]
Monte Cristo!
I mean, Edmond Dantes!
I'm going to take
it all away from you,
everything you hold dear
in life just as you did to me!
[ALBERT] I continue to
plead, as if praying.
To my father. To my mother.
And most of all, to your name.
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 23:
"Edmond Dantes".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!