[FARIA] Madames and
messieurs, good evening.
When he learned something
of his mother's past,
the young man saw in her
profile the figure of a woman.
However, for all his curiosity,
he is still unaware.
Still unaware of the
true identity of the man
who brought about
the look on her face.
Amazing. I can't believe
I'm seeing these sights
underneath the Champs Elysees.
It's like a dream.
Perhaps this truly
is but a dream.
At times, I do
consider that possibility.
Well, in that case, here's an
eye-opening question for you.
How much did you
sink into this place?
How much did this
dream house set you back?
We stopped bothering
with hassles like money,
about halfway
through construction.
That ought to make
a great headline.
Thanks for the tip.
[harp music playing]
Where's that coming from?
Over there!
It's the girl from the opera!
She's beautiful...
You're not gonna try and tell us
that she's artificial,
too, are you?
Don't be rude!
It's obvious that she's...
She is nothing more
than a doll named Haidee.
A poor puppet who still lives,
even though her soul has
been taken away from her.
Haidee obeys my every word,
caters to my whims
and desires and,
should I wish it, would not
hesitate to take her own life.
Really?
Hey, you shouldn't be surprised.
This is the Count of Monte
Cristo we're talking about.
I heard he renounced
his soul ages ago.
Am I wrong?
[ALBERT] That's going
too far, Beauchamp!
Why?
How else could one man
amass a huge fortune
like this in only
a single lifetime?
I am afraid... I must agree.
Why are you all
acting like this?
Listen, the Count
just isn't as cold a man
as many people think he is.
Isn't that right, Sir?
[MONTE CRISTO]
I wouldn't know.
I cannot see myself.
Welcome, all of you to our home.
My name is Haidee.
Hello.
Hi.
Who's that?
He is called Ali.
Like Haidee,
he too is a noble doll
that lives totally
in my possession.
Haidee, the Viscount seems
quite perplexed by all of this.
He's confused as
to what you are to me.
Viscount, I am a
small but humble twig,
that allows the
Count to fully bloom.
Well, how do you like that.
A graceful girl
like her is the twig,
and the big bad
Count is the flower?
Miss Haidee,
are you happy like this?
I know the joy of making
beautiful flowers bloom.
I see.
Does the music coming from
my harp seem gloomy to you?
Well, no.
The notes of a harp are
the notes of the heart.
The strings don't
respond to a timid heart,
A tense and troubled heart
can cause the strings to break.
Being here with the
Count is the only thing
that makes my heart happy.
I, uh... I assume that you two
were in love with one another
and that's why you
got together right?
In love with each other, huh?
Could you really be
as naïve as all that?
What do you mean by that?
Think about it, Albert...
Marriage among aristocrats
is a strategic alliance
with the goal of
securing an estate.
In fact, that's why Franz and
Valentine are engaged, right?
Huh? Is that really true?!
Um... Well, I guess I really
can't deny it, right, Albert?
Isn't it the same
with you and Eugenie?
Yeah I guess so...
In other words,
love is something
that just doesn't exist
in the privileged class.
But how can that be...
[BEAUCHAMP] What's the matter
with you, Maximilien?
Is what I said that
hard for you to accept?
It's not.
Well, everything
I said was true.
The only thing
that's really important
to any of them is keeping their
family fortunes from shrinking.
See, you two aren't
the product of love,
you're the product
of financial interests.
Not with me!
For my parents at least,
they say that their
marriage came out of the love
they had for each other.
That's hard to believe.
A notorious player like
General Morcerf in love?
Hey! Are you trying
to insult my father?!
You getting so mad about
it makes it even more dubious.
Is there something
about your parents
that you're maybe
feeling a bit guilty about?
Um... Of course not.
Why would I feel guilty?
[FRANZ]
Hey, Beauchamp.
I don't care if you
think you're a journalist.
You should drop this subject.
[BEAUCHAMP]
Oh, what?
You're clamping down
on freedom of speech now?[
[MONTE CRISTO]
How wretched it all is...
Is that not what
you are thinking...
...my good Captain Morrel?
To think that loveless
marriages are allowed
to go unquestioned...
[MAXIMILIEN growls]
Is something wrong, Maximilien?
The people of Paris are corrupt!
Maximilien,
you're going too far!
I demand that
you take it back!
I can't do that.
Paris has more than its
fair share of honest, people!
Take back what you said!
I won't.
Take it back!
I will not!
Stop it, Albert!
Hey, now...
Stop it, now!
Viscount Morcerf.
Do you realize
what you are risking
by pointing that blade
in my face like this?
I remind you, I am a soldier.
This will not do.
Drawing your sword like
that is ungentlemanly.
But Count...?
Regarding your opinions,
each of you is steadfast.
And given that we
are now upon the sea,
perhaps we should
act like pirates...
...and settle our
differences with a duel.
A-A duel?
On the sea, strength
counts for everything.
He with the better
sword arm makes the rules.
You can't be serious?
What is it you're
suggesting here, Count?!
Come...
Huh?
Now is the time to
demonstrate your conviction.
Time for you to prove to them
that you hold your parents'
marriage to be
honorable and sacred.
The blade in your
hand is now invincible.
And as for you, Monsieur?
All men have a blade
hidden deep within their heart.
The purer the heart,
the keener the blade.
The time is high tide,
the place a ship's bow,
the weapons bare blades!
So! Come on, gentlemen!
Let's see you go
at it, pirate style!
It's hard to believe
that there are still people
in this day and age
who'd fight a duel over love...
Hey, Those swords are real!
Is this any time to be joking?!
Yes! And the water
down there is teeming
with sharks thirsting
for human blood!
Huh? Wait a minute!
What kind of game are
you playing here, Count?
Just the entertainment
of a sea voyage.
I expect that
Monsieur Albert is thirsting
for stimulation of this sort.
Let's do it!
En guard!
Take back your words!
Take it all back!
I can't!
Why, you--!
And now?!
You poor, sad people...
The purer the heart,
the keener the blade.
I'm afraid you just aren't
capable of defeating me.
Shut up!
Understand. No matter
what you wanna say,
no matter how
other families are...
...my parents' marriage
bond is sacred!
I didn't expect you to turn
towards your unarmed side.
And I do admire the
strength of your actions.
However, the insincere will be
smitten by divine retribution!
I won't stand for it! I won't!
What is with Maximilien?
What in the world's
gotten into him?
I guess he's
the scrupulous type.
You're finished!
Why is it that you hate
the aristocracy so much?!
That's none of your business!
The hell it isn't!
You tell me why!
First, I've something
to ask you.
Is it true what I've heard?
That you don't really
love your fiancée?
Well, I--
I demand an answer!
I don't know! Okay?
Just as I thought.
I can't abide by this anymore!
You have lost, Messieurs.
Ah!
Hey, hold it!
Albert!
Don't!
There are sharks down there!
This is a nightmare...
Indeed it is.
You see, this is a dream.
A waking dream...
A twilight dream.
[ALBERT'S MOM]
Albert...
[ALBERT]
Mother...
I did it because Mother
had that look on her face...
Count...
[MONTE CRISTO] One cannot
fight against destiny.
[ALBERT]
Huh?
I'm ashamed of myself.
I can't believe
how angry I got.
[MONTE CRISTO] I know.
I can see it clearly.
Within your heart, another
side of yourself lies dormant.
Huh?
At the moment,
you are burdened
with a profound
sense of apprehension.
Just as I am.
You are?
My good Viscount Albert
I have need of you.
Who, me?
You recall that day on
Luna when you and I met?
Perhaps you feel that our
meeting was a chance encounter.
But in fate, there
are no coincidences.
Just as that setting
sun does so according
to the laws of the universe,
fate, too, is composed of
the powerful natural forces
of unyielding necessity.
But what are you
apprehensive about?
It's because a man
loves with all his heart,
that he laughs,
and loves, and hates.
What are you saying,
I guess I don't understand.
You see, Albert my life, is
much like this miniature garden.
It is a hollow,
and fragile thing.
Aw, c'mon, Albert.
Why don't you cheer up already.
Maximilien apologized for
everything he said, didn't he?
I'm not mad, Franz.
Then why--
Look, Don't hang around
the Count anymore, all right?
You've been acting funny lately.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess I have.
Something's funny.
There's something
strange about all this.
Up until yesterday,
life was one uneventful
day after another.
It almost feels
like something hidden
is at work behind all this.
Destiny...
Have you ever thought
about you know fate?
I haven't.
I really don't believe
in any that stuff.
How did your mother and I meet?
Why the sudden
interest in that Albert?
Please, I'd just like to know.
Humph.
As I've told you before,
your mother and I were married
after a storybook courtship.
Yes, that's true.
It was just as your father says.
I've never seen that look
on Mother's face before.
You look like you're delirious
with a fever, young master.
Why don't you go
out for some fresh air?
Make sure you clean in here!
Yes, sir!
[ALBERT thinking]Mother,
who are you thinking about
right now at
this very moment?
I wonder.
How far will the
ship really sail?
Well, there is
no turning back now.
I see...
You hope to expand
your business ventures
to include Paris, do you?
I can think of
no stronger backer
to have than yourself,
General Morcerf.
You do me a great
honor Monsieur,
Count of Monte Cristo.
I take it that you already
have a plan of action.
Please feel free to call on me
should you have
any needs at all.
He seems to be quite powerful.
The crest of the Danglar
family can be seen here
and there in every part of town.
He has no idea that the Count
is keeping a eye on him.
Talk about conceited...
Waving a sword around
in anger like that...
You really are hopeless,
you know that?
Tell me, what kind
of relationship
do you think
that you and I have?
So what brought that on?
It's something that
Maximilien said to me.
He asked me if it was true
that I didn't love my fiancée.
Oh. How did you answer that?
Huh, Albert?
Uh... Hm...
You and I... are childhood
friends, aren't we?
Ah!
I think that you and
Franz have changed.
It used to be the three
of us always had fun.
But now, the two
of you sneak off.
Too bad. Everybody's changing.
Do you know why
Maximilien was so angry?
You honestly don't know?
Well, if you say so.
What do you mean by that?
I guess...
...no one can do
anything to stop it...
...when two people find they
have feelings for each other.
I didn't mean to
keep you waiting.
I'm sorry, dear.
It took me a long
time to get ready.
That's all right.
Oh, my. Albert,
is something the matter?
You look so very grim.
Take care, Eugenie.
Hey, Albert! Wait a minute!
Albert!
[ALBERT] She and her father.
And her mother.
The specter of uncertainty
sneaks up on them
through their emotions.
Next Gankutsuou,
The Count of Monte Cristo,
Act 6: "Her Melancholy,
My Melancholy".
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!