[NARRATOR] Madames and
Messieurs, good evening.
The life of the boy
sacrificed to my friend
was cradled in the pure
soul's arms as it faded away.
And I rejoiced.
His soul has at
long last been tainted.
Tainted by the fires
of remorse and hatred,
which will never fade.
[EUGENIE sobbing]
Oh, Franz why did you do it?
You promised me that
you wouldn't go away
without telling me ever again.
[ALBERT]
Franz...
I couldn't bring myself
to go to your funeral
no matter how hard I tried.
How could I?
Right up until yesterday,
you were by my side.
You were always there
for me when I needed you.
But now, all I have
is this letter...
Why did it have
to be you, Franz?
Why did this happen
to you instead of me?!
C'mon, Franz you gotta
give me an answer...
Just like you always do.
Say something...
Say anything, Franz... Franz!
Move the white Queen to F3.
[CHESS MACHINE]
Pawn from C7 to C6.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Hm...
Danglars Bank stocks have posted
trading limit highs
for several days now.
Knight to E4.
[BERTUCCIO]
It's absolutely amazing,
every stock in his
investment portfolio is
on an explosive growth trend.
That Andrea kid did his
job better than I expected.
[MONTE CRISTO]
Very well.
We will start flooding
his investments
with sell-offs right away.
The Paris market
goes without saying,
but do the Eastern, Kingdom,
and Frontier markets, as well.
Flood them with sell-offs
until the markets close.
[BERTUCCIO]
Understood.
Kings Pawn to C4.
[BERTUCCIO]
Oh, Excellency...
Haidee wishes to speak with you.
Excellency...
I love you more
than I did my father
and I cannot bear to see
you change any further.
[HAIDEE]
Please, let it stop here.
White Knight, E4 to G5.
Un-needed pawns are sacrificed!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Along with everything
between me and my revenge!
Bertuccio! Take Haidee away!
Yes Your Excellency.
Excellency!
Did you only save me so
that you could eventually
use me as a tool
for your revenge?
I know that you're
not that sort of man!
Excellency! I still
have faith in you!
Excellency! Excellency!
[MONTE CRISTO]
Bishops Pawn to C5.
[CHESS MACHINE]
The game is yours.
[MONTE CRISTO]
The end is almost upon us...
[DANGLARS] Andrea! Just take a
look at today's stock prices!
It's getting so I can't wipe
the smile from my face!
[ANDREA]
I'm very glad to hear it.
[DANGLARS] I owe my success
to you. I'm in your debt.
[ANDREA]
Not at all.
More importantly, what
about the wedding ceremony...
[DANGLARS]
She's being stubborn.
Something about a friend
of her's dying suddenly,
so she's saying that she
can't get married anytime soon.
Honestly, I have no idea where
that girl gets
her stubborn streak.
It's quite understandable.
That reminds me, Baron,
how is her mother doing?
[ANDREA] She's been
bedridden for a while.
Perhaps if I went
up and visited--
An excellent idea!
If you were to keep
her company I'm sure
it would be a
pleasant distraction.
I hope that you're
right, Baron.
[DANGLARS] The big question
is how much longer
will our bank's assets continue
to multiply like this?
Right, Michelle?
[MICHELLE]
Indeed.
[DANGLARS]
Open the display!
All my stocks are
humming along smoothly.
[DANGLARS cackling]
[MERCEDES]
Albert.
Albert, please listen.
I'm thinking of
leaving Paris forever.
Come with me
to Marseille, Albert.
Of course life there
won't be as extravagant
as we're used to here, but...
...it'll be just the two of us--
I have enough saved
to at least keep us
fed for a little while.
[ALBERT]
What about Father?
You're an honest to
goodness opportunist,
aren't you, Mother?
[MERCEDES]
Albert, how dare you!
I've had just
about all I can take!
[ALBERT]
When you get right down to it,
it's you and your old friends'
fault this happened.
And me, I got
caught in the middle
of this soap opera between
you and the men who loved you
Who gives a damn
about Edmond Dantes?!
Why are my friends and I--
Why did Franz, of all people,
have to die the
way that he did?!
[MERCEDES]
Albert, where are you going?
Who knows.
Nowhere in particular.
It doesn't matter what
happens to me anymore.
Youd've been better
off if I'd died.
[smack]
If you want to blame
me for what happened,
then go right ahead and do it.
But you really shouldn't...
...you really shouldn't
think so little of yourself.
[ALBERT]
Huh?
Permit, please.
[ALBERT]
I don't have one.
They always let me pass through.
You shouldn't go around thinkin'
you're still some
sort of an aristocrat.
[GATEKEEPER B] Your ID number's
already been revoked.
You can't just come and
go as you please anymore.
What the hell's goin' on here?!
Well, what does it look like.
Like they say, a stupid father
is gonna have nothing
but stupid kids.
You'd better go and
get yourself a permit, kid.
[GATEKEEPER A] That's assuming
that they'll even give you one.
[GATEKEEPER B]
Good point.
[GATEKEEPERS laughing]
[GATEKEEPER A groans]
[GATEKEEPER C]
You punk!
[ALL grunting]
You stupid piece of crap!
[ALBERT]
Stop that! Get off my bike!
Get your hands off it!
Hey!
[GATEKEEPER A]
You're fighting me, remember?!
Now, you don't get
to boss us around
anymore ya got it?!
[VICTORIA sobbing]
This state is unbecoming a
beautiful lady such as yourself.
[VICTORIA] It doesn't matter.
I always find myself alone.
Don't say that.
Seeing you sad and feeling
so lonely tears my heat in two.
[VICTORIA]
Men always think
that saying that'll
make me feel better.
Rest assured I will
always be by your side.
My Mother.
[VICTORIA]
Andrea...
Please, just for today...
...just for now,
call me Victoria.
Victoria.
[grunting]
[FRANZ]
Albert, are you okay?
[ALBERT]
Franz? Franz, is that you?!
What's with you? Are you okay?
Oh Franz!
[FRANZ]
Hey, cut it out!
Thank goodness!
Hm?
I'm so glad that
you're all right...
Is this really the time
to be worrying
about someone else?
C'mon, Albert, let's go home.
[ALL]
Albert, Happy birthday!
Congratulations, Monsieur.
Congratulations.
What took you so long?
[PEPPO]
What have you been up to?
She's been waiting
for you for ages!
Eh?
[ALBERT]
Who do you mean?
Eugenie!
Albert...
Congratulations
on turning 16.
[CROWD laughing, whistling]
[PEPPO] Oh, they're going
at it in broad daylight!
Save that stuff for when
you're in private, will ya?!
[FRANZ]
Allow me to introduce the man
without whom this party
would not be complete!
The man who saved Albert's life,
His Excellency, the
Count of Monte Cristo!
Franz!
We can't invite
this man to Paris!
Why not?
We both insisted that he travel
here to visit us, remember?
Look. Everybody says
that they're dying
to meet the Count.
[ALBERT]
No! You can't!
He's a demon who's
come back here
to Paris to get
revenge on all of us!
[MERCEDES]
Darling, I think...
[ALBERT]
Father! Mother! Run!
Eugenie and Franz! You, too!
Get as far away
from him as you can!
[MAN]
Count!
[ALBERT]
Don't do it!
Don't do it, Franz!
Don't you see?
He's the man who took your life!
[PEPPO]
My, my, how fascinating.
[ALBERT]
Please...
Please, I'm begging you...
No! Stay away!
[ALBERT yells]
This is for Franz! Die!
[ALBERT panting]
[FRANZ]
Um, Albert?
Actually you were
the one who killed me.
[ALBERT gasps]
[FRANZ] Albert, when you really
think about it, it was you.
It was your fault.
No, all I wanted to
do was try to save you!
You always think
only of yourself,
and you damn well know it.
[FRANZ] Every time I tried to
tell you something important,
you'd blow me off
and never listen.
No! Franz, it wasn't like that!
I hate you.
I'll hate you forever.
[FRANZ moaning]
It hurts... It hurts...
Franz! No!
[FRANZ]
It hurts... It hurts...
[ALBERT]
Franz! Oh Franz...
Franz, I am so sorry!
No, Franz! Please don't die!
You can't go away!
There's something important
that I have to tell you, Franz!
So please don't leave
me alone here just yet!
No! Franz, don't die!
Franz!
[RENAUD]
Hey! Albert... are you okay?
Snap out of it! Hey!
Albert! Hey!
Franz!
Guess you're fine if you
can move around like that.
Renaud?
[ALBERT]
Where am I?
[RENAUD]
You're lucky, I just happened
to spot some
guy riding your bike.
Relax, we caught the guy.
Your bike's safe and sound.
The evildoers have
all been punished!
Sorry Renaud.
What're you talking about?
Everybody needs a tool-loving,
bike-loving friend, you know?
Admittedly, I pushed her so hard
to get here fast that she's
in pretty bad shape now.
[RENAUD]
Do you have any earthly idea
how badly I've been
waiting for today to arrive?!
I looked everywhere
for rare parts,
endured setbacks, and finally
got her in working order!
Chest swelled with anticipation,
I set out in high
spirits and what happens?
Why, that's Albert's bike!
But who's on it?!
So I pull up to him,
planning to ask him
what was going on and then--
[ALBERT]
Hey, gimme that ratchet.
Here.
Hey! My baby's showing
signs of recovery!
[ALBERT]
Aren't you being dramatic?
Dramatic, my foot!
There's no sadder sight than
a machine that can't be fixed!
I had the same problem that
night we rescued Valentine.
It was terrible...
[ALBERT]
Wait, that was your car?
Sure was!
Oh, you have no clue how
heartbreaking that was.
Renaud, how can
you talk like that?
Valentine nearly died that day!
[RENAUD]
Don't get me wrong.
I volunteered my car because
they were gonna rescue her.
Eh?
The thing is, I kinda used to
have a crush on Valentine...
Really? How come you never
said a word about it to us?
[RENAUD] Hey, Albert...
[ALBERT] Hm?
Do you remember
when we all came out
here on a warm afternoon drive?
[ALBERT]
Yeah...
[RENAUD]
It was just a little while ago,
but it feels like
a distant memory.
The quiche that Valentine shared
with us was great, wasn't it?
I could've eaten it all day.
Albert?
I'm really sorry, Renaud.
I was just remembering that day.
Franz is a really lucky guy.
You're always
thinking about him.
[RENAUD moans]
I only have my cold machines
to soothe my
troubled heart now!
[RENAUD sobbing]
[ALBERT]
Renaud...
C'mon, let's head back
and get something to eat.
Yeah, why not.
[DANGLARS gasping]
[DANGLARS]
Hey! Michelle!
We're totally
swamped with sell-offs!
What are you doing about it?
[MICHELLE]
Trying to prop up the prices,
but the volume is overwhelming.
[DANGLARS] Use every dime
we've got to stop this!
[MICHELLE] Monsieur, it
isn't just our bank stocks
or those of our business
group that are crashing.
What?
[MICHELLE] Every stock in our
portfolio is in a nosedive.
Why is this happening to me?
[MICHELLE] I am unable
to determine the cause.
Unable to determine the cause?!
[DANGLARS]
Damn it! Pull it together!
If this keeps up,
I'll go bankrupt!
[MICHELLE] Infection by
unknown virus detec... ted...
Michelle, what's
the matter with you?
[MICHELLE]
...ted...
The Eastern market
is just opening now.
Pull out our shares!
Sell off everything we've
got except our bank stocks!
Convert it all to cash!
[MICHELLE] Today's weather
in Paris is sunny-- sunny.
Current temperature
is 22 Celsius-- sunny--
with less than a 10%
chance of precipi--sunny.
[DANGLARS] Michelle!
You've got to snap out of it!
Michelle!
[DANGLARS]
The Eastern market...
[MICHELLE]
The Paris market closed today
with prices considerably lower--
[DANGLARS] Michelle,
you've got to start running
these numbers immediately!
[MICHELLE] The prevailing
opinion is that the market
[DANGLARS]
I can't keep up with it!
[MICHELLE] as a result
of the sudden sell-off--
Michelle!
[MICHELLE] Sunny, sunny,
sunny, sunny, sunny...
Michelle!
[MICHELLE] At the outbreak of
this market run-- sunny, sunny--
Michelle!
What do you want, Father?
[EUGENIE]
What's the matter?
Why are you
barging in like this?
[DANGLARS] Oh Eugenie,
dear daughter of mine...
I have something
important to tell you.
[EUGENIE]
Important?
[DANGLARS]
Yes. Something wonderful.
The thing is,
Eugenie, your wedding
with Andrea Cavalcanti
has been firmly set
for the day after tomorrow.
But why?! I made it
clear that I'm not going
to get married so soon
after Franz's death.
[DANGLARS]
That's all right.
No it's not!
Shut your mouth!
Are you saying that
you don't care if I insist?
Grr, this entire
family dies penniless
in a ditch thanks to you?!
[EUGENIE]
Father, please, calm down.
You want me to calm down?!
How do I do that?!
My stocks have taken a nosedive!
They aren't worth the
paper they're printed on now!
You should give up this
worthless piano nonsense!
You're not serious...
You're the only one who
can save this family Eugenie.
You've got to marry Andrea
as soon as humanly possible!
But what about my feelings?
[DANGLARS]
They don't matter.
The only thing
that matters to me
is that I get all
of my money back.
[DANGLARS] Thanks to this,
Andrea's fortune will be mine!
[DANGLARS]
Eugenie, at this moment,
you're the most precious
thing in the world to me.
[RENAUD] Franz is still
here with us, ya know.
Anyway, that's the way I see it.
I get the strange feeling
that he's showing us
what path we have to take.
[ALBERT]
Renaud...
[ANDREA]
And where might you be going
at this late hour, Mademoiselle?
[EUGENIE panting]
[ANDREA grunts]
[EUGENIE gasps]
[EUGENIE]
No! Stop it!
Let go of me!
[EUGENIE]
No!
[EUGENIE screaming]
[ANDREA] Even the
daughter of an aristocrat
would be ruined for life
if something like
this was done to her...
Wouldn't she?!
[ANDREA cackling]
The day after tomorrow,
you're finally going
to belong to me and me alone.
I'm afraid the main course
will have to wait until then...
[ANDREA cackling]
[EUGENIE]
Albert, save me!
Albert!
[ALBERT]
Don't give up on your future.
No matter the time, no matter
the place, you're never alone.
Next Gankutsuou, The Count
of Monte Cristo, Act 20:
"Farewell, Eugenie."
Bide your time,
and hold out hope!