School Rumble will
be starting soon,
and you don't wanna miss it!
Ah, hello there...
My name is Sano.
I'm from class 2-A...
Ha--of course you
probably know that...
Word is you're not seeing
anybody special at the moment...
So I thought you and I...
Hey...
What do you like better
for dinner, meat, and
potatoes or curry?
Huh? Well... Meat and
potatoes, I guess.
Oh really, that's what
I thought you might say.
Wait a minute, do you
mean you're planning
to make dinner for me?!
Don't be silly.
I wouldn't even dream
of such a thing.
What're you looking at?
I was wondering if
you'd go out with me...
Ha, of course not.
I totally called it!
And he gets shot down in flames!
Hey.
You shouldn't be
so hard on a guy
when he's trying to ask you out.
Think what you're doing...
In times like these,
a guy's willing to do just about
anything to get a
girl to notice him.
That's right.
I have something
I have to take care of,
so I won't need the limo.
Huh...?
Do guys like curry
or meat and potatoes?
I've always heard
meat and potatoes;
I guess it's some
kinda man thing.
Meat?!
Do you really think so...?
Honestly, I just don't know...
Well...
I haven't made it in a
while, so I'm not sure.
Okay, let me think here,
you're gonna need...
yellow onions, white potatoes,
fresh carrots, beef round...
Don't forget the stock...
Hey...! Does this mean
you've got a date?!
Here you go, young lady...
Try one of these,
you'll love it.
You mean I can just
eat it right here?
Oh, great... What do I do now?
She told me to look for red tag
items, but I don't see any.
We're gonna have
Daddy's favorite
for dinner tonight,
aren't we, Mommy?
He'll be surprised!
He sure will, honey,
he's going to love it!
So Eri's fixing
her first meal...
I don't get it, isn't Eri's
family stinking rich...?
Why doesn't she have their
cook make the meat and potatoes?
She's making this meal because
she wants it to be special,
to express how she feels.
I still don't get it...
How she feels about what?
It sounds like rain.
Yikes...! You're right...!
I've gotta get home and
get the laundry off the line!
Tenma, slow down!
You'll trip!
Huh?
Uh...? Daddy...!
What are you doing here...?!
The butler told me
I might find you here.
So you came to get me?
Listen... for dinner,
I was going to...
Listen, honey, about dinner...
I've been called out of
the country on business...
It was very sudden...
I'm afraid I can't have
dinner with you tonight.
Oh, that's all right...
Actually, I made a dinner
date with some of my classmates,
I guess it must've
slipped my mind
I mean, sometimes
I get confused,
with you jetting in and
out of the country so much,
I get our dates mixed up.
I know... and
I just got back, too...
I'm sorry...
I won't be gone long ...
Do you want a ride home?
Oh, no, I'll be fine...
You have a nice trip, okay?
Yeah. I'll see you soon.
Goodbye...
If you're not going
too far... I'll walk you.
Just a little ways...
So tell me... which
do you like better:
curry, or meat and potatoes?
Curry...
So I thought we could work
on math together later on...
Is something wrong?
Hey, Sara, good morning,
how are you...!
I thought I saw Yakumo
standing here a moment ago.
Oh, yes, she said she had
to stop at the faculty office.
Faculty office!
Got it! Thanks! Goodbye!
Okay, he's gone.
So then she says
right back at him...
What do you think about that?
You're kidding!
Seriously!
Does everyone know?!
Of course!
Almost everyone.
Where could Karasuma be going?
Man, I hate the
end of the month...
No money and Itoko
won't lend me any...
not even enough
for lunch... huh?
Well I guess you must've
skipped lunch too, huh?
And all you can do
is drink enough water
to keep your belly full.
Yep, I hear ya, the
end of the month blows.
I like you,
you're easy to talk to...
Tell you what:
Next time I get some cash,
I'll buy you lunch.
Uhhh... can you hear me?
So what do you like...
Are you a meat and potatoes
kinda guy, or a curry fan?
Curry.
Alright! I can tell you and
me are gonna get along great!
Next month the curry's on me!
Poor Karasuma.
I know... a box lunch...!
I could get closer to him
if I brought him a box lunch
and we could eat it together...!
I should've thought of this
weeks ago, it's brilliant...!
All right!
This is my chance to show
Karasuma what I can do!
Yoo-hoo!
Curry?
For school lunch?
Yeah, curry...!
With white rice on the side,
in separate containers,
and double portions!
I don't... quite... get it...
And not too spicy, okay?
Oh, Karasuma!
Uh... Hey there...
I made way too
much lunch today...
I was wondering if you'd do
me a favor and help me eat it?
Aw... right!
Guess I'll go drink some water.
Tenma sure seemed
happy when she ran outside.
Did you get a load
of her huge lunch box?
She said it was curry for two.
It's kind of unusual to
make curry for a school lunch.
You know what that means...
No, what?
Harima...!
Today we're gonna settle
things once and for all!
I'll be waiting for
you behind the gym
after school this afternoon!
You better not be late!
My darling Tenma made my
favorite dish for lunch...
and for two...?
She must have made it for me...!
This is my lucky day!
I'll give you three guesses
what I made for lunch today!
You'll never guess!
Give up...?
Okay, I'll show you,
and I bet you're gonna be
in for a really big surprise!
Two... boxes... of... rice?
I grabbed the wrong box!
Huh...? Rice balls?!
Yum.
Yummy yummy. Yummy yummy.
This is nice.
So what's the story
with you and Hanai?
It seems like you
really can't stand him.
I mean... You ducked
behind the lockers!
I've never seen you hide
from any other guy like that!
Uh... I don't...
I don't dislike him in
particular, it isn't that...
but I'm not... I'm not
really all that comfortable
around boys in general... so...
So when he comes
on like he's a bull
and you're the matador,
it completely freaks you out...
Yeah... That makes sense...
Nevertheless...!
Your sister and
Hanai are classmates,
so you've got to face your
fears and go to class 2-C...
You know why?
'Cause we've got
two curries and no rice!
Don't worry!
I'll be right there with you!
Thanks, Sara.
So far so good, now with any
luck, he won't even be here!
Hey, what is it?
What's the matter?
He's in there.
Hanai is in there.
Huh...? How can you know that?
Yes... Here I go...!
Off to see Miss Tsukamoto!
Oh my gosh! What is it?!
Hey, Hanai!
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Which gives you this.
Oh, I see.
Okay, do you get it now?
'Cause I gotta get going.
Well excuse me, where are
you going in such a hurry?
To pay a call on
Miss Tsukamoto of Class 1-D!
Miss Tsukamoto...?! I don't
blame you, that chick is so hot!
Maybe I should join you.
Hm?
I'm so there!
I'll come too! Me too!
I wanna come!
Tsukamoto's little sister!
What a dish! She's such
a babe! Count me in!
I'll just go in with you,
and then I can ask her
out when she shoots you down!
Hold it you guys, hold it!
I'll do it fast,
and it'll be okay...
Everything's going to be okay...
Yakumo!!
You okay... What happened?
Hey, sis...
Did those lunch boxes
cause any trouble for you?
What...? Are you kidding?
Come on, Kenji!
Get it in gear,
it's time for school!
Look... I really
don't want to mother you!
Okay, fine...!
I guess skipping school is
what delinquents do, but...
Okay...
So... What about school?
I'm not going.
How can a guy be so
tough on the outside
and yet so weak on the inside?
I'm not going ...
I can't trust guys and I can't
trust girls, so I'm not going.
Fine.
It's Mr. Super's Super
Fun Science Show!
Howdy do...!
Guess what, kids...?
Today on Mr. Super's
Super Fun Science show
we're going to learn
about optical illusions!
Now, look carefully at the
picture in problem one...!
Which of these two
straight lines is longer...?
Number one... or number two?
Number two... It's gotta be.
The answer is...
They're both the same length...!
No way...! Are you sure...?
That's impossible...!
Check again; number two
has got to be just a little bit
longer than number one!
This is what we mean
by an optical illusion...!
Neat, kiddies, huh?
An illusion?
Some fancy trickery.
So then... You're sure
you have to leave us...?
I'm sorry to hear that...
Oh, Mangoku...
Farewell, friends!
May heaven bless you, sir!
Tell me the truth...
You knew that girl
was in love with you,
and you were in love with her.
You only left to spare
her feelings, didn't you?
Not at all... You're way off...
There was never anything
between the two of us;
we were just good friends.
Oh please! Don't try
to fool me, tough guy.
I can tell your heart is
really breaking on the inside!
You're the man, Mangoku!
You're the man!
I feel your pain, dude.
Just calm down
and listen to me...!
I only found out recently
that you and I are siblings!
Then...
You're saying you're actually
my long... lost... brother?
Huh...? He's her brother?
Of course, that explains it!
That's why we've always
been so close to one another!
You see? It was all
a misunderstanding!
Well, I'll be a blarsnog!
Wait a sec!
What if it was all an illusion,
a misunderstanding...?
Tenma and Karasuma are really...
Mm! Isn't it good, Big Brother?!
Yup, it sure is, Little Sister.
They're siblings!
That's the reason
we've always been
so close to one
another, you goof!
Of course...! That must be it!
To tell you the truth...
It's always been you that
I've loved from the start.
Oh, crap...!
Man... Did I screw up
royally this time or what!
Hey, Kenji...
you've got company.
What do you want me to say?
Argh... who is it?
Well, it's someone you know
pretty well, actually... Ten...
I was right! It was
all a misunderstanding!
Ten--
--no... ji...
Of course... It was
too good to be true...
You piece of crap...
You got a lotta nerve standing
me up like that this afternoon!
You owe me a dance, punk.
What's wrong with me?
I'm helpless... Like I forgot...
...how to fight...
Man, I don't get it,
but you're no fun anymore!
Call me tomorrow if
you get your spine back!
Hey, sis...
Are rice balls going to be all
right for school lunch tomorrow?
Absolutely!
Harima... Harima...
Kenji Harima, are all
your tomorrows gone?
Is this the end...
for your love?
Oh, Karasuma, you mean you'd
prefer curry to rice balls...?
I should've thought of that...!
I'll cook you a
delicious curry this time!
Next time on School Rumble:
"Comic Book Blues!
Older Woman Blues!
Super Bad Water Blues!"
Oh, no...! Iori!