I've been pretending to be a
member of Harima's gang,
waiting for just the right
opening, and now I've found it!
For some weird reason,
this year he suddenly got soft!
Now's my chance to defeat
him so I can rule this school!
Uh oh ...
Whiskers, got lead?
Hmm?
Sorry to bother you again!
This is point 5.
Don't you have any point 7?
You're so useless!
Here.
Thanks Harima!
Yeah. You're welcome.
Hey, do you have a problem?
Nope.
Come on, out with it.
Act like a man and speak up.
Really, there's no problem.
The nerve.
He's even getting friendly
with Eri, the girl that I like.
Damn it.
But the bastard definitely
has his guard down.
Let's go!
I'll disrespect his ass
by calling him a dog
in front of everyone.
That'll show him who's boss!
You... You...
You, Yo, What up, dog?
How's the search
for the new bike going?
Good.
This one's pretty cool.
What the--?
All right!
I'm finally in good with Harima!
I've made the first crucial
step in my rise to the top!
And I've done it
in front of Eri too.
I am so totally cool!
Let's go see Akira.
Okay.
Did you have the Banana
Rice Cake today at lunch?
No. Was it good?
Hey, dog, what do
you say you and me
have a little man to
man talk, huh, Harima?
Yo, Tenma baby,
I'm borrowing your seat.
Call her baby again,
and you'll end up dead!
Uh-oh! I forgot something!
Nice chattin' with ya.
Am I ever gonna get to the top?
Welcome to Was Burger!
Okay, that's one Was Meal.
Coming right up!
Order in! One WAS meal, please!
How come there's such
a big line at that register
and the other one's
completely empty.
That's very weird.
Well, I guess it's my lucky day.
Let me see.
Whoa. Scary.
What's she so mad about?
What do you want?
How 'bout a smile?
A smile is free, right?
Come on, just gimme
a smile, pretty please?
She's gonna kill'im!
Lara! What are you doing!
I'm so sorry!
Just a moment, please.
Lara, stop! He's a customer!
Karen, now would be
a good time to help.
Please! Break it up!
My bones are breaking!
Look at her.
I've never seen
her so worked up.
I'm sure she's still
upset over losing
to Karen at the Athletic Meet.
Your fries are
getting cold, partner.
Don't call me that.
You think she might
move back to Mexico?
Lara? Here's your usual.
Left over hamburgers.
Hey, why don't you try
to smile a little bit tomorrow.
Don't let Karen out do you, now!
Um, please cheer up Lara.
You can't be good
at everything you try.
I think it might be good if
you smiled a little bit, though.
Give it a try.
Karen!
Kosuke! What's up?
Ah, I just came
to walk you home!
Oh! That was sweet.
But we gotta hurry it up
or we're gona miss Dozibiron.
Hey! I know you!
You're the evil empress
from Dozibiron, aren't you!
Kosuke!
You're goin' down!
Hey! Put me down!
Lara! I'm sorry!
See ya 'round!
A... Adios...
...familia.
What do you want?
You want this?
Is it good?
Then, eat up!
You must be alone, too.
Ay perrito! That tickles!
Welcome to WAS Burger!
Smile!
You're back. What do you want?
I want to see you
smile like yesterday.
Karen, please save me!
Please! Not again, Lara!
Imadori! Are you okay?!
She seems happier now.
Her punches are
livelier than yesterday.
Looks like our job here is done.
Break it up!
The time is ten
thousand years ago,
in the primitive ages of man.
It is uncertain whether or not
this is an accurate depiction
of early civilization, but we
do know that our species owes
its development to
the events of this era.
You roll the rope around like
this, and you get a pattern.
How pretty! You're so talented!
These will be really popular!
Hey, What are you doing?
I'm drawing pictures
on these leaves.
Oh awesome!
I invented it. I call it Anime.
That is amazing!
How cool!
Aww!
I'm so freakin' hungry!
Don't say that.
You're making me hungry!
That's just the way it is.
It's too bad, but our food
sources were low this year.
We can't take much more of this.
At this rate,
we'll starve to death.
Big Trouble! It's Hanai!
This is terrible.
He was loud and bossy,
but this isn't right.
Umm gotta huc. Honey but umga.
Fire!
It's hot!
Is he alive?! Holy crap!
Who pronounced him
dead in the first place?
Ooh! Hot! Eeee! Ow! Hot! So hot!
Oh. He's alive after all.
Someone get some water!
What the hell happened
out there, Hanai?
What happened?
I went to the forest
in search of food.
I found some fruit and
climbed a tree to pick it.
It was the most
gigantic mammoth.
Gigantic mammoth?
Devil Tusk.
A creature of ancient times,
feared by the people
of Yagami Village.
Looks like we have a crisis.
Devil Tusk, huh?
Someone has seen this monster?
Yes.
There's no mistake, my queen.
Well, then there's no choice.
Our village is almost
on the brink of starvation.
My people, listen to me!
We will defeat this monster!
Yeah!
Awesome. I'm drawing well today.
This black stone I
found in the mountains
is really good and hard.
The tone here should be...
Wait, what's a tone?
Oh Tenma.
I really love you, baby.
People of Yagami!
Our number one problem
is the mammoth's hide.
It's so tough that our
stone weapons can't pierce it.
Our only option is
to abandon this land.
Ladies and gentlemen, follow me!
I will lead you!
I'll pass.
I'm not leaving my home.
I love these rivers
and mountains.
Bastard.
What if we just used harder
stones for our weapons.
We don't have any stones that
could possibly be hard enough.
My stomach's eating itself!
Hungry.
Tenma!
She's so weak from
hunger, she can't move!
My darling!
Feed me, Harima! Feed me!
I'm on it baby!
Um, excuse me.
Huh?
Oh, Harima!
What the heck are you
doing back in our village?
You were banished.
Don't you remember?
You were so violent
and stupid and all,
that the queen ordered
you banished forever!
This is it!
Everyone! Listen up!
Harima!
This new black stone
I found is harder
than anystone we've
ever seen or used before.
If we make our weapons
from this stone,
we'll finally be able
to defeat Devil Tusk!
What's this guy talking about?
What are we supposed
to do with this stone?
If we could kill
Devil Tusk by stoning him,
we wouldn't be in this mess!
Hey, guys, you wanna
roast some sweet potatoes?
You know, Harima
may have a good idea.
Ah! The Wise Women!
We will use that black stone
to make our weapons stronger.
I think it just might work.
Yes! Let's do it!
Yeah!!
Great idea Harima!
Aw, come on,
it's really no big deal.
I'm Awesome!!
Let's go!
All right!
I'm going to kill that beast
and win Tenma's love!
Harima, bring us back
something good for dinner, 'kay?
I will!
Leave it to me.
Make us proud, Papa!
Now make us proud!
I promise.
I'll do it for you!
Future children!
To think that so many young men
are willing to risk
their lives for this village!
It must be because
I'm awesomely beautiful!
There is nothing
to fear, my good men!
Just follow me, Haruki Hanai,
and I will lead you safely!
So, um, did you
finish that anime yet?
For my family.
Bring it.
He's coming now!
Men! Charge!
Now fight with the
weapons I gave you!
Yeah!
Damn these weapons!
I told them to follow me,
but they were like, "No, Hanai!"
Don't you dare give up yet!
Amazing!
He actually pierced
Devil Tusks thick hide!
Way to go! Harima!
I did it!
Now Tenma's heart will be mine!
Ichijou, it's time!
Okay!
Wow! Karen and Lara
brought down Devil Tusk!
Now men!
Let's finish this
once and for all!
Yeah!
Boy, this meat sure is good!
Mm-hmm
Man, thank goodness.
That sure ended well.
Now we can last
through the winter!
And we owe it all to two
brave women--Karen and Lara!
Hey!
Let's thank the brave
women who saved us!
Yay for Karen and Lara!!
Hey, I helped too.
Aww.
Too bad, I guess
I'm just a thug, after all.
Oh well, at least Tenma
has a full belly now!
Knock knock.
Oh! Hey Tenma!
Harima, you were amazing!
Here!
This is just for you!
I don't know what to say.
Come and join us!
There's lots more left!
Oh, right!
I must record this!
A masterpiece.
When we work together,
there's nothing we can't do.
Because we're such good friends!
I have a feeling that in
our next life somewhere,
we'll all be classmates.
What's a classmate?
Heck if I know.
This ancient cave drawing dates
back to the prehistoric period.
It's called the
"Smile of Venus."
I think it kind of
looks like you, Tenma.
What? No way!
Captain!
I'm gonna do this.
You'll see.
Did you say something?
Uh, no. I'm sorry.
Would you hand me that
French Curve other there?
Oh. Of course.
Here you are.
Thanks, Yakumo.
I-I'm sorry.
The thunder scared me.
No, don't apologize.
I'll get it.
Uh, thank you again.
Oh it's--it's okay I don't mind.
Man! Great time
for a blackout, huh?
Candles, I need candles.
This is a really bad storm.
Damn!
Even touching a girl's hand
by accident makes me nervous.
Heh. If I touched
Tenma's hand right now,
I'd probably die
of a heart attack.
It's so quiet.
Should I turn on the radio?
Is this big bad storm
scaring anybody?
D.J. Yoshimo here,
and I'm diggin' it!
Come on guys!
Make the best of it!
It's a perfect time
to find a cute girl
and cuddle up with her!
You just listen to me now,
and I'll tell you how
to put the moves on!
I think I work better
when it's quiet.
Oh. I'm sorry!
Did you want to listen to it?
N-no!
Hey, I want you to know
that I appreciate you
helping me like this.
I mean it's so late.
No I-I like helping you,
and I'm anxious to see your
work as soon as it's finished.
Woah. Wait a minute!
What?
Stay right there.
Just like that.
I see!
It's the lighting!
I get it now.
This is how it's
supposed to look.
You see there's a really
important scene in the comic
where the hero and the heroine
are making a
campfire in this cave.
And for some reason
I couldn't picture it right.
That is, until I saw the
way that light hit your face.
I can't thank you enough.
I know! While
I'm thinking about it,
would you mind reading
some lines from this scene?
I think it'll help
me see it better!
Sure.
Finally, we're totally alone
on this deserted island.
That's it!
That's the feeling!
Yeah, yeah!
This is really helping me.
You're a good
little actress, there...
I-I am?
Do you think you could
read some more for me?
Uh. Oh, Sure.
I'm really glad that
it's just the two of us.
Uh huh! Uh huh!
That's really good.
Read the next line.
But, how are we
going to survive here?
Don't worry!
You're safe with me!
I will always protect you!
Ha-Harima?!
Uh, should I keep
on reading this?
I mean, the next line is...
I... love you.
All right! And, I love you too!
I promise you.
I will make you very happy!
Harima I- I think-
We will start the
perfect family together.
He's not even...
Harima.
Tenma.
He's so quiet all of a sudden.
Did I do something wrong?
Oh! I see!
Uh, hey, What's wrong?
Uh, nothing.
Sorry, I got a little
carried away there.
Come on, let's keep working.
Was I imagining things?
Do you really hate men?
Or, do you like them?
It's the Culture Festival!
And our class is
still arguing over
putting up a food stand
or doing a show!
Hey, wait a minute.
I already read this!
Tenma, this time it's for real.
School Rumble -
Second Semester is coming soon!