A... space ship...? Karasuma?
Miss Tsukamoto... the truth is
I'm not really from this planet.
Uh...
Can I ask you a
question, Harima?
Mm?
Well, I...
I was just wondering
what it means to go steady.
Everyone says it like they know,
but what does it really mean...?
To see another person?
Oh, gosh, I'm sorry, I'm way
out of line asking you this!
You know...
Uh...?! Yes?!
I'm not really
sure I know myself...
but there are these moments,
like when you're riding
your bike by the
seashore in the morning...
And suddenly the sun rising up
out of the ocean
looks so beautiful...
Or when you eat
something really delicious...
or you see a
really great movie...
You wanna share those moments...
with someone who
feels the same way...
I think... I think "going
steady" means accumulating
a series of those
moments with someone...
Uh... But what do
I know about it anyway?
I'm probably way off base!
Hey, do me a favor...
hand me that French
curve there, will you?
Huh...? Sure...
Oh my goodness...! What's that?
It's heading for
the Yagami Shrine!
Wha... What should we do?
You wait here!
But...
No buts! I'll check it out...!
I'll be right back!
Karasuma!
Incredible...
I always thought you were a
little on the strange side...
...but I had no idea you
were really an alien spy!
Talk! Why did you come to
the Earth in the first place?
Survey...
My superiors sent
me here to determine
if this planet should
be allowed to exist.
I'm going after him!
You can't mean it...
You would destroy the Earth?
Rest easy...
My analysis indicates
that this planet should
be left undisturbed.
And so it shall...
Now wait just a second!
It's not that simple!
You can't just waltz out of
here like nothing has happened!
Sis!
Come on...! Snap out of it!
Ya... Yakumo?
Karasuma...! He's going to...
Calm down! What about Karasuma?
He's going away forever...!
Karasuma...
he's not from earth,
he's from another world!
Why do you stop me... earthling?
I have to... because
Tenma is in love with you,
you alien freak!
And I want her to be happy,
even if it's with
you and not me...
so you're not going anywhere,
ya hear me, space boy?
Alas... I cannot make
Miss Tsukamoto happy.
Don't give me that...!
Are you just gonna break Tenma's
heart without a second thought?
I must... I have no choice.
All right... if that's
the way you wanna play it...
I'll just have to make you stay!
Karasuma!
Sis!
Cease your attack... I have
no wish to engage you in battle.
Too bad... now fight,
if you're a man!
Why...? Why do you do this?
Because... because...
because I'm in love with
Tenma Tsukamoto, that's why!
Harima, what...?
Tenma!
Then I must confess as well...
I am also in love the
earth girl Tsukamoto.
That makes it even worse...!
Fight, coward!
No, don't!!!
Karasuma, no!
Don't worry, I'm fine...
you'd better check
on Harima, though.
That... That scar, it--
Tenma... that one time
you thought I saved you...
it wasn't me.
You... You mean--
It was you who saved me...!
I remember it like
it was yesterday!
I know... I'm sorry
for deceiving you...
I rewrote your memory as part
of my cover story for
my mission on your world.
All this time, the feelings
of love you thought
you had for me...
were actually for Harima the
man who really rescued you.
I love you...
My assignment to this
planet was for a year,
and I was preparing
to return home...
But your letter stopped me...
so... I decided to
stay a little longer.
Because...
I had fallen in
love with you too.
If I was cold to you...
it was only because
I knew someday
I would have to return
to my home planet.
You're saying you
want me to follow her?
Go on... there's
something here I must do.
Please don't go,
I'm begging you!
It's time... I have to
leave you now, I'm sorry.
Karasuma!
When I've gone...
all your memories of me will
vanish, as if I never existed.
I'm sorry... but you
must forget all about me.
Oh no...! I don't want to!
I will miss you, Miss Tsukamoto.
Karasuma, no!!!
I won't forget...!
You hear me...?!
I'll remember you
for the rest of my life!
What am I doing here?
Tenma!
Are you okay?
Harima!
What's the matter,
Tenma, what happened?
I had a dream...
I dreamt you went far away
and I forgot about you...
Yeah right...!
Do you think I'd
ever go anywhere
in the entire
universe without you?
Oh, Harima!
Oh...! The scar you
got when... I'm sorry.
Eh... It was worth a dozen scars
to meet someone like you ...
I love you... dearest...
I love you...
That's it!
Finished!
Congratulations, Harima...!
Now all you have to do is get
it to the publisher on time!
Karasuma!
I hope you had a
nice nap, Miss Tsukamoto.
Sorry you had to carry me.
Hope I wasn't too heavy.
That's all right, it was
no trouble at all... See you.
Wait... I...!
Um, I um. See I...
I have some-something that
I want to give you for your--
Sorry.
But I... I have to go now.
Take care of yourself...
Miss Tsukamoto.
I have to go now, he says...?
Take care of
yourself, he... says...?
Does that mean the
time has finally come
for him to change schools?!
Oh man, I hope I'm on time!
Nakamura... I don't wanna
hear this song anymore.
Oh...? But I thought
this was one of your
favorites... wasn't it?
I'm just getting a
little tired of it, is all.
As you wish.
No! Not now!
I can't waste time
stopping for this guy...!
If I time it just right I can
slip by him as he goes past!
Huh... that's a long car...
Are you all right?!
Harima...!
What are you doing here?
Shall I bury him... mistress?
Call an ambulance!!
No...! We've got to deliver
this package quickly...
I'll be all right, just go.
What, are you out of your mind?
You've got to get to
a hospital right a...
I said I'm all right!!!
I've got do this thing...
even if it kills me!
All right then...
Nakamura, get him into the car.
Yes, Mistress.
Oh, an entry for the
New Faces Award...? Of course!
Would you mind telling
me your name, sir?
Nakamura, the butler,
at your service, miss.
He's bleeding...
You asleep?
The package has been delivered.
So, Whiskers...
I'm curious,
what was the big deal
with that package
of yours anyway?
I mean... was
it really so important
it was worth risking
your life to deliver it?
Yeah, it was to me.
What's in that package
is the most valuable
thing I have right now...
And I had to deliver it, even
if I got killed in the process.
Sorry for all the
trouble, Rich Girl.
Well, I guess I'll see
you around, Jeeves.
Pardon me.
Huh?
An irrelevant
question, if I may.
Excuse my curiosity...
are you, by any chance, seeing
anyone special at the moment?
If I was, I wouldn't
be goin' through all this!
See ya!
Did you hear that, mistress?
What's that got to do with me?!
Oh, Nakamura...? Could you...
play that song again?
Of course... mistress...
Huh?
Sis?
Oh, Yakumo!
Where have you been...?
It's so late!
I've been waiting and waiting!
Well, I was... that is, I...
It's Karasuma! He's leaving!
He's moving away and
I'll never see him again!
And I still haven't told
him how I feel about him...
It's over... my love is over...
This doesn't
sound like you, Sis.
Remember what you said once?
That you'd rather regret
doing something stupid...
than regret doing
absolutely nothing?
You're right...
thank you, Yakumo...
Even if we do have
to say good-bye forever,
I can at least tell him
how I really feel about him.
When you think about it,
it's funny that I've never been
to Karasuma's house before...
Let's see... the address is
around here somewhere...
Huh...? Does he
live in a rice paddy?!
Unless this is his
house right here...
even I'm not that dumb!
Or maybe they moved and
took their house with them...?!
Heavens to Betsy!!
Karasuma, where in
the world are you?
Please don't be gone,
I have to tell you!
Hello, Karasuma?!
Karasuma are you here?!
No! I won't believe
I'm not going to see him again,
I won't, I won't,
I won't, I won't!!
Captain... I gave it my all
and I'm so burned out...
I'm just white ash and cinders.
But now I can be the kind of
man who can stick out his chest
with pride and
be worthy of dating Tenma!
Huh...? Whose cat?
Oh, hey, Tenma. What's new?
Wha... Wha-wha-what
are you doing?!
For Pete's sake,
we're in a public park...!
Why are you even here?!
Woah...! Tenma, please...
What's the big idea?
Let's... play... but... that...
can only mean... that you...
...you want to go on a
date with me, is that it?
Let's... go!!!
We're goin' on a date!
Wow! Finishing that
comic is paying off already!
I've never seen
Tenma like this before!
She's so aggressive!
Okay, settle down! Stay cool...!
I gotta make sure she has
the best date she's ever had!
Look out world...! Here we come!
I... I hear the
hot milk steamers here...
are really terrific...
try it... go ahead!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
I can't apologize enough...
If I'd known you
disliked hot food,
we could've gone somewhere else.
Uh... listen... there's...
there's something I've...
I've wanted to ask
you for a long time now,
but I just couldn't...
But something's different
about you today,
so I'm gonna take
a chance... because I...
I know I can't
fight it anymore...
Uh... would you... would you...
would you like to go out
with me again sometime?
Huh?
Meow...? What's that...?
Oh, I know...!
It must be some kind of
slang expression that Tenma
and her chick friends use...!
It's probably something to say
when you feel shy and
awkward around someone...!
She's being demure...!
That is so cute!
So... is that a yes?
Karasuma?!
Karasuma!
Oh, where can he be?!
I've gotta find him!
I've looked everywhere else!
There he is!!
Karasuma...! Karasuma...
I love you...! I've always loved
you...! Please don't go away...!
I can't bear it...!
Here, I brought you
a birthday present...
What the...?!
Why, thank you,
Miss Tsukamoto...
how did you find out
this was my favorite?
Huh?
Tasty...
He liked it...
Listen to me...
I'm not going anywhere...
I'm going to
stay by your side...
Miss Tsukamoto... I love you.
It's... it's like a dream...
And that's that!
Okay, everybody,
class dismissed!
Rats...
Karasuma!
I don't understand, I thought
you changed schools already!
No... how come?
But you... you told me the
other night you had to go!
Right... I had to go
back to band practice,
it wasn't over yet.
Oh yeah... I knew that.
That was close...
Wait a minute...! Then how
much of it was a dream?
Hm?
Meow.
Uh...
"I love you"...
just three little words...
But the moment I say them...
the whole world changes...
like magic...
Today I'm going to
say them... to you...
Hey, Tenma...? We're late!
Yakumo...! Wait up!
It's Karasuma's birthday
today...! I'm gonna do it!
Good... morning!
Morning!
Wow, Tenma, you seem
really pumped this morning.
Maybe a little bit too pumped.
What's going on?
It's a secret...!
Well, I got something
to do, so see ya later!
Now wait a second...
What's she talkin' about?
Oh, yeah... was that today?
Huh...? Was what today?
There he is.
I have to give
him this present...
and tell him how I really feel.
And that dream
I had yesterday...
Miss Tsukamoto... I love you.
That dream felt so real,
it's just got to be
some kind of omen!
I won't blow it this time!
Right!
Karasuma?
Uh... hi... I've got...
I've got something
that I wanted to give you,
if you don't mind...
Here...! It's a present...
From me.
For your birthday...
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
May I open it now?
Mhm.
Uh... I made it myself,
you know... 'course...
I only thought of
it yesterday afternoon
and made it last night...
So it's only half-dried.
Why, thank you,
Miss Tsukamoto...
how did you find out
this was my favorite?
It's just like in the dream!
Tasty.
It's all coming true...!
It was an omen...!
That means next...
he's going to say...
Miss Tsukamoto... I love you.
Here it comes!
Miss Tsukamoto... I...
This is it!
It's already over.
Huh?
It's already over... my
birthday, I mean...
two days ago.
I got it wrong again!
Ka-Karasuma?
Oh, you're awake.
I hope you had a
nice nap, Miss Tsukamoto.
Oh, wow... so it...
was all a dream...
You all right?
Uh-huh...
but... do you mind if
I stay here for a bit?
Okay.
Hey, Karasuma?
Yes?
Is this a dream too?
We're all in a dream...
it's a dream
called adolescence...
someday you have to wake up
from that dream,
but even then...
the memories of it shine
forever... like the stars.
Hey... one more thing?
Yes?
There's something...
something...
I've wanted to tell you
for a long time now,
but something
has always come up...
I... I lo... I lov... lo...
It's the Culture Festival...!
And our class is
still arguing over putting
up a food stand or doing a show!
Hmph, we'll sort this
out in short order...!
And I'm really going to confess
my feelings this time...! Next
time on School Rumble...
Miss Tsukamoto,
there is no next time.