Growing up in my hometown,
I was always the kid
that got picked on.
We used to take turns
whispering to each other
about the girls we liked,
but when it came to me...
Hey, listen up!
Yoshidayama...
Has a huge crush on Aikawa!
Yoshidayama!
You're getting detention!
What the heck does
he think he's doing?
Poor guy.
Loser!!
We'd all planned to
skip class that day,
but for some reason, everyone
went back without telling me.
There's no way I could
have taken another year
in that hell of a middle school.
So I studied hard, and got
accepted to this high school.
Watch it, punk!
Oh, excuse me.
Yeah!
Here, I can be the big dog!
That's what I thought anyway.
But just my luck--
The devil goes to this school!
I mean, dammit!
If it wasn't for Harima,
I could totally be
ruling this place by now.
But no!
Instead, all my plans
for building a Juvenile
Delinquent Army,
all my plans for
Classroom Conquest,
and eventual School
Domination--all ruined!
Thanks to him!
But I'm not ready
to roll over yet...
I'll just join Harima's gang,
and wait for the right opening!
Hey, Harima, buddy.
I saw your name on the D list.
Sorry I bothered you.
I'll get there one day.
Hey there, poor little thing.
Are you all by yourself?
Come on, you can trust me.
I just moved here myself, so I
don't really know anyone either.
See!
So we're in the same boat!
Or, maybe not.
Aww. I must have scared her.
How cute!
Oh, and she's got a kitty!
She looks so peaceful,
like a spring goddess!
Is that Yakumo from 1-D?
She looks so sweet and innocent!
If I was sleeping like that,
I'd just look dumb!
In fact, I'd probably snore!
Yeah! You would!
Oh no. It's already closed.
I'm too late.
You fell asleep again?!
You're always
falling asleep, Yakumo!
I know.
I'm sorry I missed the
sale at the supermarket.
Huh?
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Hey!
Do I know my sister, or what?
I already went
shopping, just in case!
Thanks sis.
No Problem!
So, anyway, about your
habit of falling asleep
at the drop of a hat--I'm
getting a little worried.
It's becoming a big problem.
Shouldn't you do
something about it?
Don't you have a friend
who could wake you up?
Iori was supposed to wake me.
You're impossible.
So, you coming to
Karaoke tonight?
Yeah, the girls were nagging
us to ask you about it.
What do you say? It'll be fun!
I don't think Yakumo
has a boyfriend right now.
Maybe I'll get lucky.
Maybe I have a chance with her.
Um, I have to meet my
friend in the courtyard,
so maybe another time.
It's starting again, and
it's getting more powerful.
I have to be strong.
Because I'm all alone.
Hey, look!
Is that kitten gonna be okay?
That stray dog looks vicious!
It's a living thing,
you shouldn't do that!
Yeah right!
Somebody do something.
Oh no!
Iori!
I'm afraid of dogs.
Somebody!
Wow! Yakumo's brave!
How cool!
She'll kick that
dog's butt for sure!
She can do anything!
What a woman!
All right!
Did that girl just bark?
That was awesome!
Who is she?
I've never seen her before.
Isn't she a freshman?
She's cute!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Wow! That was scary!
Are you okay?
Uh, yes. Thank you!
Good.
Um, who are you?
Me? Oh, I'm sorry.
My name is Sarah Adiemus.
I just moved here.
Dream?
Oh! You finally woke up!
I think it's time
to go home now.
You ready?
I'm sorry!
You were sleeping so peacefully,
I didn't want to wake you.
Were you having a nice dream?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Tenma.
I'm gonna be late again.
After classes were assigned,
Tenma found that she and
Karasuma were in
the same class after all.
However, Tenma quickly realized
that her battle
was far from over.
So for tomorrow, your seat
assignments will be changing.
All right! I'm gonna sit next
to Karasuma no matter what!
I don't know how to do this!
Aren't seats assigned
by drawing lots?
Worrying about it
isn't gonna help any.
Why don't you just take
a bath and go to bed?
Try to have a little compassion!
I'm in love!
Man! She treats
me like I'm a child.
I'm not. I'm a full grown woman!
That's why I have to
do everything possible
to make this right.
Abra Kadabra. Make it a star!
An X?!
It didn't work at all?!
I don't understand!
Bending a spoon
is so easy for me.
Karasuma.
This isn't going to help!
I don't have any
time to be depressed.
I have to get that
seat with will power!
Okay, let's assign seats.
Possible seats are
behind, on the side,
diagonal back, to the
front, front diagonal!
There's a lot of choices,
so I should be good.
Let's see, where
is Karasuma's seat?
The last window seat!
Now I don't have
as many choices!
Now the only seat left is
the one right in front of him!
Lot number 6!
Okay, Tenma.
Time for you to pick.
Please, let me pick
number 6! Please!
Was that number 6?
But, that would be cheating.
No it wouldn't!
This is--it's gotta be...
Fate!
All right!
I got the seat in
front of Karasuma!
Ka-ra-su-ma rules!
What the-
Is this your seat?
Mmm, yeah.
I thought I picked number 6!
Ahh. Let me see.
Oh, did you see this?
See this little dot right here?
You had it upside down.
This sucks!
Where the heck is nine!
You're lucky,
this seat's special.
The front seat?
Why is this happening to me!
Not good.
Tenma's in the front row,
and I'm stuck back here!
Damn it!
This is awesome!
I get to sit next to Tenma!!
Hey!
How would you like
to switch seats with me?
You see, I have bad eyesight
and I can't see
very well from the back.
Understand?
Mr. Tani?
What is it?
I don't see very well.
Is it okay if
I sit in the front row?
Sure. Go ahead and ask someone
to switch with you, then.
Please! Let me switch with him.
I beg you, please.
Sure, please be my guest.
Oh thank you!
Thank you so much!
You've made me so happy!
Okay. You're welcome.
You have bad
eyesight too Harima?
Oh wait! I forgot.
I'm still wearing my sunglasses!
That expains it! Oh my gosh!
How silly of me!
No wonder I couldn't see!
My bad.
I'm actually farsighted.
The truth is
I can't see the board
unless I'm sittin' in the back.
By definition that is
the theory of relativity.
I can feel his eyes on me!
All right!
So then, I guess you could say
that men and women
are the same way.
So close, yet so far.
So far, but so close.
The best seat in the house.
I'm sorry for staying
so late after class.
That's okay. Don't worry.
Although I'm surprised
that someone
like you would sleep
through my lecture.
I'm really sorry.
Ms. Sasakura?
Do you think my facial
expression's a little stiff?
A little.
Good eyes though.
Well, I have
some errands to run,
but stay as long as you like.
Thank you, Ms. Sasakura.
I can't seem to get this right.
Shall I tell you why?
You're scared.
I understand. It's okay.
Everyone is always
scared in this situation.
Are you lost?
Where are you from?
I'm not from anywhere.
After all, I'm not
even a human being.
You don't believe me, do you?
That can't be helped I suppose.
See, despite my appearance,
I'm much older than you think.
Actually, I've been
wandering around the world
in this form for an eternity.
A Ghost.
Still don't believe me, do you?
Do you believe me now?
I told you, I'm not human.
It's useless. You can't escape.
I'm here, because I wanted
to ask you something.
Tell me...
Do you really hate men?
Or do you like them?
No matter how long
I exist in this world,
I can't decide.
Maybe you have to be an
adult to figure that out.
How is it for you?
Is this question hard
for you to answer?
Or is it easy?
I don't hate them.
There's just not a specific
guy that I like right now.
Even after all you see?
I know your secret.
You can read the thoughts of
those who have feelings for you.
Occasionally, in this world,
there are people who are
born with heavy burdens.
You are one of them.
Sometimes you can even see
their darkest thoughts,
and yet you still
don't hate them. Why?
It's because I understand them.
Everyone has heavy burdens,
but still they try to
be the best that they can.
I don't know if
I like them all, but I...
I see.
Goodbye, Yakumo.
Hey.
How's it coming, Yakumo?
Uh, Ms. Sasakura?
Did you happen
to see a little girl
with long black hair
when you came in?
Sorry,, I'm afraid
I didn't see anyone.
Oh...
Look at that!
There's a pleasant
expression. Well done!
I'm home.
Huh? You wanna
know if I like boys?
I love 'em!!!!
Tenma?
We've come to have lots
of fun, at the hot springs!
I'm so excited we
came to the hot springs!
Well this is the first
time I've been to one.
Are they really that great?
You have no idea what
you've been missing.
Do you think
what we did is okay?
I mean lying to Hanai
about leaving like that?
Are you telling me you
wanted to stay with him?
Uh, no!
Yes!
This is the greatest
trip of all time!
I am at the hot
springs with Yakumo!
Oh Tenma, that scavenger
hunt was so romantic...
Harima?
Who's the girl that you like?
Please tell me!
Tenma is dying to hear my
confession of love for her.
I have to tell her soon!
Wow! This place is huge!
Kow- wa- bunga!
The view is amazing!
Tenma! No jumping!
The water's perfect.
It feels so good.
Nothing beats soaking
yourself in the hot springs.
Yeah, but aren't you embarrassed
to be completely naked?
Some places do allow swim suits.
Swimsuits are totally lame...
Hot springs always equal naked!
D!
Hey!
What are you doing!
Come on, there has to be a hole
in this wall I can look though!
You perv! Cut it out!
Hey! C'mon! Stop!
Heh! They're so pathetic.
What childish idiots.
Eri! What's wrong,
are you getting sick?
I think I may have caught a
cold during the scavenger hunt.
I'm sorry.
I was the one who said we should
play it in the first place.
It was all so that I could tell
Harima something in private.
Tell me something?
Hey!
Boobies!
What did you say to him?
Yeah, tell us.
The thing is...
What did Tenma need to tell me?
No way!
Is it possible that
she was finally going
to confess her love for me?
Oh no!
I spoiled it by
getting so tongue tied.
Harima was totally
trying to hit on Yakumo?
You're kidding!
Yeah right!
Like he'd even have
a chance with her!
He's so not good enough!
I know
Is Tenma mad at me?
Just because I'm too
scared to tell her how I feel?
This is agony!
D! D!
Stop acting like a child!
Damn!
How did he get to
be so strong anyway?!
So I told him girls need to
be shown that they're special!
Every girl needs to be treated
like she's the only
one that matters!
Yeah, and then?
I think he finally got it!
I'm sorry Tenma! I let you down!
I promise that I'll find
a way to make it up to you!
I think you're
wasting your time!
He's too much like a
monkey in mating season!
You think so?
Seriously!
He should be locked up
in a cage, or euthanized!
If you want,
I'll tell Nakamura to...
I'm gonna set her straight!
And who the hell is
Nakamura, anyways!
D! D! D!
D cup!
This stops right now!
You're funny, Mikoto!
Oh! I know!!
What?
Let's sing the Hot Springs song!
What song is that?
I just sang it!
You did?
C'mon! One! Two!
♪ We've come to have lots
of fun at the hot springs. ♪
Good!
Hey! Why'd you stop?!
I don't know it!
Sing it by yourself!
♪ We've come to have lots
of fun at the hot springs ♪
What's wrong Eri?
Uh. It's nothing!
I could've sworn
I just saw a monkey.
Oh, yeah.
This is the mountains!
So seeing a monkey
wouldn't be that unusual!
♪ At the hot springs! ♪
Enough with the singing!
Here.
Meanwhile, Akira was ordered
to Italy on an important job.
Comprendo.
Comprendo?
Oh, Mr. Turtle.
Miss Turtle.
Do you like me?
I like...
I like curry.
No! Not again!
A girl can hope.