School Rumble... coming up next.
Akira has a part-time
job she had to go to.
And Yakumo came back
because Hanai was annoying.
So I can see you three
had good reasons
to cut the camping trip short...
But what happened to the others?
They decided to stop at
the Hot Springs for a while.
It's becoming less and less
of a Tea Club event every year.
That's true.
What's happening?
Is it okay to keep
a giraffe at school?
Why not? It's summer vacation.
Besides, his owner should
have never left him here
alone in the first place.
But... wait.
I thought that
he belonged to you.
I wouldn't keep
something like this.
I'm just looking after him
for a little while until
his owner gets back.
Who are these people?
I've never seen them before.
Number 6, it's time to eat.
This lady is very pretty.
But I don't think she
knows what my name is.
I'm Pyotr, but that's
not my real name.
It's a different name
someone gave to me.
I don't remember my real name.
I don't even know
where I was born.
I guess it doesn't matter.
Go ahead.
She treats me like
I'm stupid. I don't know why.
Are there any
other animals here?
Yes. I left the bigger ones in
the warehouse, for right now.
Ms. Itoko... I think
he's having trouble.
I can't seem to get him to eat.
Mr. Giraffe! Try this.
There you go.
Uh-oh. I can't get up.
Looks like his legs are
too weak to pull him up.
It's true. He needs exercise.
Haven't you been
taking him for walks?
No. Do you want to try it?
Wouldn't that be a
kind of traffic violation?
Please, that would be
the least of your worries.
But it's definitely not right
to keep him cooped up
like this all the time.
That's true.
Come on, boy. Come on...
Keep on coming... It's okay.
Be careful,
don't bump your head.
And stop!
He's kinda scary at night, huh?
Is this okay?
What if people see us?
It's just for a little bit.
He needs exercise.
I brought a volleyball
to play with.
Do giraffes play volleyball?
Want to play?
This girl seems very kind.
I think I like her.
Wow! He really
likes you, Yakumo!
I appreciate your kindness.
My memory is not very good,
but I'll try my best
not to forget you.
Oh wait. I think I might
remember something.
That's right!
I had forgotten that there is
someone who loves me very much.
My master.
But where is he?
Could I have been ...
Mr. Giraffe!
Abandoned?
I miss my master!
Wait! Please! Stop!
Mr. Giraffe!
You've been so kind to me!
I'm sorry! But I need
to find my master!
I'm glad we went camping!
Yeah, it was fun.
I'll be fine the
rest of the way!
You sure?
Yes, I'm sure...
Thanks for walking me this far.
It was my pleasure.
Oh! That's right!
I almost forgot!
You were supposed to tell me
who the girl that you like is!
Come on! Please!
I promise I won't
tell anyone else!
Oh yeah, about that.
It's just...
Tenma...
I wasn't sure whether
I should tell you this or not,
but I think it's time...
This is it! I can feel it.
Actually, the truth is...
I... I love ...
I found you, Master!
Hi, Pyotr. I'm back.
That was amazing!
Did you see that, Yakumo?
Wait, Yakumo?
What are you doing here?
Mr. Giraffe, why did
you run off like that?
Thank you for being so kind.
Well, nice meeting you.
How does it look?
Well, it's still raining.
How am I supposed
to dry this laundry?
I'm gonna have to talk to
the weatherman about this.
Huh?
What is it, Yakumo?
Poor boy, stuck in the rain.
You ran away and you
didn't pack any clothes?
We've just invited
you into our house,
and you have the nerve to
refuse to tell us your name?
How unbelievably rude!
Hey, look, it's not like I
invited myself into your house.
You should be grateful, bucko!
It's raining pretty
hard out there.
It might be a good idea
if you stayed here tonight.
Yakumo! We don't know him!
He could be dangerous!
He's an innocent boy.
How do you know that?
I just do.
You need to think
about these things!
He may be a kid but
he's still got hormones!
You're way too trusting, Yakumo!
You could at
least taste the food!
You know, Yakumo
made this and most of
the boys in school would
die for her cooking!
So what! Who cares!
At least your
big sister can cook,
which is more than
I can say for you!
I'm the older sister!
What?! You mean no-boobs
here is the older one?!
See! That's what
I'm talking about!
This just proves that
you're a stupid brat
who's never learned any manners.
And, by the way!
Yakumo's may be
bigger than mine,
but that doesn't
mean I don't have any!
Um... Tenma...
Little pervert...
You've been staring at
Yakumo's chest this whole time.
What?!
I'm declaring war!
We'll settle this with a game!
Bring it on, stupid!
Old Maid!
Chess!
Checkmate.
Othello!
You suck. I won
every single game.
What?! Ha! We're
not finished yet!
Secret weapon!
Yakumo, if you please?
"Go" time.
What the heck is that?!
That'll teach you, you pervert!
What's wrong?
I lied. I'm sorry, but I didn't
really run away from home.
It's okay.
Go to sleep.
You owe us big time!
Don't you forget that!
It's not like you did
anything for me, Yakumo did!
I'm gonna strangle
this stupid brat!
I wanted...
I, um... Ah, just forget it.
Catch ya later!
I can't say I want
to see her again!
Wait!
Come and see us again.
He was completely obnoxious...
But it was kind of fun,
wasn't it, Yakumo?
I can't believe summer
vacation is over already.
It's like the end
of a really good book.
Kinda sad in a way, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Akira!
I've been waiting for you.
Ms. Itoko is already inside.
What should I do?
I don't have
anywhere to put 'em.
We can try moving
all the animals
to the Yagami Shrine, for now.
To the shrine?
We can't leave them in the gym
when school's about to start.
People will see them.
It's only a matter of time
before someone
finds them anyway.
Um... Why can't we
send them to the zoo?
No!! There's no way I'll hand
them over to complete strangers!
We have no choice, Harima.
Now put the sheep down.
You really want to? Here?
I promise no one'll see us.
I don't know...
That fake lion
is kind of spooky.
Don't be silly, it's just
a dumb statue. See!
We are reporting live
from above Yagami Shrine.
Where a couple says they
were chased by a wild lion!
Also reported were sightings
of a zebra, tiger,
panda, ostrich, penguin,
an armadillo and
others all in this area.
Other witnesses report
seeing a beautiful young girl
walking a giraffe in
the park late last night.
A beautiful young girl, huh?
...in response to this problem,
the local hunters'
association is scheduled
to hold a hunting expedition.
This is getting
serious, isn't it?
Any ideas?
They trust me.
I have to help them.
Hey, Yakumo, I came
to visit like you said!
Hey, Shuuji?
Hey, wait... What are
you doing here, Kenji?
Were you looking
for me or something?
I wonder if there
really could be
wild animals in
a place like this?
I hope so, cause it'd be
quite a scoop. Are you ready?
What the... What's that?
A giraffe?
Get him on tape!!
There's my story!
Who are you?!
A giraffe.
That's a costume!
And what the hell are you doing?
We're not doing anything.
We were just
practicing for our play.
Play?!
No cameras allowed!
Union policy!
What are you...?
Hey! That's my camera!
You can't shoot this play
without my permission!
What's the title of this play?!
"The Tales of a Kitten".
But, you're a gorilla!
What a waste of time.
And you thought
we'd find wild animals.
Thank goodness, they're leaving.
Close one.
So what did you
guys think of my plan?
Your plan was great!
Way to go, little brother!
Well, I still needed
to thank Yakumo
for taking care of me the
other night when it rained.
I thought I finally
had my big break.
Oww... Cut it out, you guys!
Watch where the
hell you're going!
Hey. You guys can
come on out now.
We're takin' you
to a safer place.
Hold it right there, you brats!
Where do you think you're going?
Pyotr!!
What are you doing!
I'm... I'm sorry...
I think you owe
me a full explanation.
And this time, I brought help.
You have no right to do this!
These animals are
completely harmless!
Stay back. We're just
gonna put them to sleep!
Yakumo! Stop!
Get out of the way, kid!
Yakumo! You're gonna
get hurt! It's not worth it!
I understand!
Listen to me! Hurry up! Go!
Come on...! Giddyup!!
Or somethin'!
Get out of the way!
All clear!
Let go!
In your dreams!
Careful!
Kick his ass!
Hey!!
Look everyone!
Why are they dancing?
They're showing you how
much you mean to them!
And they don't want to cause
you any more trouble, Harima.
So they're trying
to fix the problem
and show everyone
they're harmless animals.
By dancing like fools.
It's over now.
What do you mean?
I've contacted the zoo and
made arrangements with them.
Oh, we're not gonna get this?
It's a fantastic shot.
Forget it.
A little while after that,
the animals were given
good homes at the local zoo.
Since they were used to people,
and knew how to do tricks,
they were a big hit
with the children there.
Once the animals were taken in,
Harima visited the
zoo pretty regularly.
Harima was known to
hate any type of routine...
but that was one
habit he never broke.
It's time for school again!
The school uniform feels great!
The atmosphere feels right!
Yes! It's a new school year!
But for some reason,
I feel sleepy.
You look like you're still
in summer vacation mode.
You totally don't get it!
Do you, Yakumo?
Nobody would dare
say it out loud!
But, inside
everyone is thrilled!
People are looking forward to
seeing their sweethearts again!
Yo! Tenma!
Hey! Good morning!
Hey!
You got a new hairdo!
It looks fantastic!
Well, it is a new school year!
Can you feel it, Yakumo?
This is the power of a brand
new school year! It's real.
Uh...
Those two are dating?!
Since when?
It's all about summer... L-U-V.
Talk about change,
look over there.
Hey! That's Karen!
Wow! She braided her
hair! She looks cute!
That's not all she's changed.
A stylishly shortened skirt,
a touch of eyeliner,
and light pink lip gloss.
She's lived every
schoolgirl's fantasy.
She's had a passionate romance
during the heat of the summer!
You have problems.
Oh, but that's great!
I think everyone should
have a summer love affair!
All I did was meet Karasuma
and go with him to
a wrestling match.
That's not much of a change.
Our relationship really sucks.
I wish I had a
summer romance, too!
Huh? If it's true that people
change when they fall in love,
then that would mean that
if Karasuma has changed...
He might have met some
other girl this summer
and fallen in love
with her! No way!
Nothing like that
would ever happen!
Would it?! Come on, Karasuma!
Come to class already!
Good morning.
Karasuma!!
He's changed. Karasuma?
What happened this summer?
I don't understand!
Wait! He's still himself,
and no matter what,
I have to accept him.
Whiskers are wonderful!
Whiskers are wonderful.
Whiskers...
Whiskers?! Is she
talking about me?
I knew it! Tenma's
madly in love with me!
I guess it's mutual now.
I'll just move a little closer.
Oops. I forgot to take this off.
Miss. The Manhattan you ordered.
Just leave it there.
Of course.
Get her!
Hold it right there.
You've wasted enough
of our time already.
Now where's the brat?!
Tell us where he is, or you die.
All right then. I'll tell you.
Those are the guys who
killed my mom and dad.
I'm sure it was them.
But I... I still don't know why.
Wait...
Akira, why are you helping me?
I have my own reasons.
Well, looks like our
little game of tag is over.
Regino, you were
like a father to me.
How could you do this?
A young godfather
should never trust anyone,
that's your first mistake.
Your dress.
Giorno, remember earlier,
when you asked me
why I'm helping you.
It's because... you remind me...
of the man that I used to love.
Get down!
Akira, please stay
here a little longer.
Come visit me in Japan,
when you're older...
I'll make you a
delicious cup of tea.
Akira, how was your
summer vacation?
Typical. Just a
little bit of trouble.
Trouble?
Hi! I'm Karen Ichijou.
I don't know if he remembers,
but Imadori and I have a date.
I've never been on a date
before. What should I do?
Next time on School Rumble...
The one who loves you
will always be with you!