School Rumble...
rocks your world!
Stay tuned to see hot girls!
Shigeo Umezu, Class 2-C,
track and field team,
seventeen years old.
His girlfriend...
Madoka Kido... also on the team.
They haven't been dating long...
They began going out
over the summer...
and things have been
going pretty well...
there's just one small problem.
I can't kiss her!
What's wrong with me...?
I've had dozens of chances
and I blew every
single one of them...!
I'm such a loser!
Well, no more!
Today at the athletic meet
I'll show off what I can do.
That's when I'll make my move!
Just wait, Madoka,
when I win this race I'll
take you in my arms and...
Oh baby!!
It's a pig! There's a pig
running wild on the track!
Umezu's been hit by a pig!
Is everything okay... Shigeo?
Madoka!
Sorry.
It's not your fault.
Blame the pig!
Oh, man...
I can't tell her
I wanted to impress her
so I could get a kiss.
Try not to be too
disappointed, okay...?
I'll make up for it in my race!
Girls are tough, too, y'know!
They will be with you there!
So... I have
something to ask you.
Huh?
If I come in first in my event,
will you give me
a kiss as a reward?
Did you swallow the wrong way?
I've been worrying
about it all this time,
and she just throws
it out there...?!
So, what do you say?
Well, think about it.
You're a shoo-in to come
in first, anyway, Madoka...
I mean, it's not a
reward if it's a sure thing.
What am I doing?!
She's handing it
to me on a platter
and I'm talking her out of it!
Hey... it was supposed
to be a reward.
Well then... I guess I have
to win the race, don't I?
Gotta go! I'm up next!
Oh...! Okay!
How do I say it?
Women are... Women are...
Yahoo!
Huh...?! Napoleon...!
What're you doin' here?!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you for seeing me!
Try to be more careful!
Oh, man, I am absolutely beat.
Think that kid was
the last injury
left from the cavalry battle.
I can finally
take a breather.
Huh?
Whoops... looks like
I spoke too soon.
Come in!
Did you get hurt?
In the cavalry battle?
Huh...? Uh... no...
Hm...? Then what seems
to be the problem?
Oh, um... well I...
I did get hurt, but...
it's not a big deal really...
So I thought I'd just slip
in here and get a compress...
I didn't want to bother
you with something so minor.
Well don't worry about that,
it's what I'm here
for, y'know...!
You can come in no matter
what the problem is.
All right then...
Let's have a look at
your injury, shall we?
You're supposed to run in the
relay next, isn't that right?
Oh... yes...
Then let's take care of this so
you'll be able to.
I have to say, you
seem different somehow
from the first time we met.
Huh...? Wait, have you
and I met before?
She doesn't remember... that...?
Not at all...?
She didn't even see me?
Oh, I bet I know!
You were there when
I was hugging Hario
in the infirmary the
other day, weren't you?
Hario?
I guess that didn't look too
good for either of us, did it?
But really, it was nothing.
It's just that I hadn't
seen him in a very long time
and I'm afraid
I got carried away.
Why do you call him "Hario?"
Huh...? Oh, right,
it's Harima.
Sorry, it's an old habit,
you might say it's
sort of a nickname.
Oh... so...
You and Harima
know each other...
you're, like,
old friends... right?
Well...
Now what would be the
best way to explain it...
our relationship, I mean.
I guess I was his landlady...
And he was my tenant, at least
in a manner of speaking.
Huh?
So you see...
You don't have to worry.
Worry about what?
Well, I thought...
I just thought you might
be jealous... was I wrong?
Heh...! Whatever gave you
that idea...? Me, jealous?
Don't be silly! I was
just curious, that's all!
I mean, if there's something
going on between the school's
most notorious delinquent and
the gorgeous young school nurse,
who wouldn't wanna know?
The gorgeous young
school nurse...?
I like that, it makes me
sound like a romance heroine.
I have to get back,
it's almost time.
But wait... what
about your injury?
I'll just go ahead and
take this with me... Thanks.
Are you sure you're okay?
You're really worried
about me, aren't you?
That's very kind...
But you don't
have to be concerned,
I think I'm gonna
be just fine now.
Okay...
Coming up next is
the girls' relay race,
second year division!
Class C still leads
with 220 points,
but Class D is breathing
down their necks with 218!
Runners on your marks!
It all comes down to these final
events, the relay races...!
They hold the key
to the championship!
Get set!
And there they go!!
Yay, Mikoto, go get 'em,
you can do it,
burn rubber on the double!
Class C has taken the lead...!
And the gap is growing wider!
Mihara!
And the second
runner is on her way!
Attaway, Mihara, go, go!
2-C's Kozue Mihara is
really putting on the steam!
Class D is falling way behind!
Oh, come on, Harima!
The only reason I got hurt was
because your stupid pig
ran out into the middle
of the hundred meter
race and tripped me!
Don't you think you owe it to me
to take my place
in the men's relay?
Did this jerk
hurt you, Napoleon...?
Show me the boo-boo!
I'm talking to you, pig boy!
I'm begging you...
No way... no how.
Come on, you've gotta do it...!
And why the hell are you
keeping that dumb pig
in school in the
first place...?!
I'll turn you in to
the health department!
Hey, shut up...!
It's none of your business
where I keep my pig or
my giraffe or my elephant,
so just butt out...!
Now get outta my face!
Oh, there you are!
Huh?
Class C's Megumi Sagano
is still in the lead...!
The fourth runner
is Eri Sawachika...!
It's Class C's to win or lose!
No one is gonna beat me,
no matter what!
Bring it!
And Sawachika is off
like a streak of light...!
And talk about great form...!
She's as beautiful
as she is fast!
Look at her go, she's amazing!
Something's wrong.
Huh?
Eri can usually run
a lot faster than this.
She hurt her leg?
Well... yes... do you
know if she twisted her leg
in any way during
the cavalry battle?
Hario... I mean,
Harima, you were
on the same team, weren't you?
Uh... I guess...
She came into the
infirmary earlier.
She told me it was
nothing really serious...
But it's been
bothering me ever since.
Could it have been...
when she...
Ugh...! This isn't
any of my concern...!
She's the one who
shaved off my whiskers...!
It serves her right!
Come... Napoleon... lunch.
You're going?
I have a pig to feed.
My ankle is killing me...!
I can't stand it...! Come on,
just a little farther...
I don't know how
much more I can take...
my legs feel like lead...
but... I will not lose!!
The baton...! Where's
the baton...?! Come on...
There you go.
It's only a minor sprain.
Thanks, I really appreciate it.
Just doing my job!
Wow, Eri, you really
had me worried...!
Does it feel all right?
Yeah...
Hey, the boys' relay
is about to start...
you wanna go watch it?
No, I don't think so...
I think I'll just
rest here for a while...
I'll be fine...
but thanks anyway, okay?
Well, okay, see you later!
Rich Girl...
This next race... is for you.
But after that
we're even... got it?!
At last, the final
event of the meet!
The boys' relay...!
In the second year division,
Class D is on top, with
Class C five points behind!
This is it, we gotta take
first place if we wanna win!
We can do it...
we've just got to!
Will we have to play a
penalty game if we lose?
And here come our heroic
gladiators onto the field!
Hey, Imadori!
Oh, Miko!
Hey, what up?
Try not to screw
this up the way you did
the cavalry battle, 'kay?
Aw, give me a break, will ya?
I didn't do it on purpose...
Please don't hold it against me.
Listen... also...
Thanks for blocking
Harry's kick for me,
that was a really
sweet thing to do.
Oh, Mikoto, will
you give me a kiss
if we win the
relay race, please?!
Had to spoil it, didn't you?!
Yoo-hoo! Asou!
Over here!
I'm rooting for you...!
Give it your best shot, okay?
Sara!
You sneaky S.O.B...!
And when did you hook up
with this one, Don Juan?
It's not like that!
Oh, sure it's not...!
Come on, what's your secret...?
You gotta give the
rest of us a chance!
Yakumo's watching!
You go get 'em, Harima!
Come on!
Do your best! Go Shadow Warrior!
Tenma's watching!
Don't screw up!
Yakumo!
Tenma!
What the heck?
What happened to those guys?
They look like they've
been hit in the side
of the head with a two-by-four!
Hey...! Are you guys all right?
Get in the game,
you drool monkeys!
Well, this is about par
for the course.
What's this?
There's some kind of
disturbance on the Class C team!
Oh. Looks like they need
to work on their focus!
That's so pathetic.
They're just suckers for women.
I thought they were gonna be a
real challenge, but I guess not.
úWhen it comes right down to it,
they're just a bunch of
weak-minded, lovesick pansies.
Okay men...! You have
to understand the relay
is different from individual
short distance races!
What I'm about to tell you
could mean the difference
between victory and defeat,
so listen up and listen good!
In a relay it's all about
how you handle the baton!
The timing of the handoff
is absolutely critical
to the outcome!
Now wait just a minute,
that's what I was going to say!
You seem to know a
lot about this, Imadori...
I'm surprised.
This race will make up
for our screw-ups
during the cavalry battle!
Aw, come on,
I was gonna say that too!
Hey... I can be serious
about things now
and then when I have to.
Think about it, if we pull
this off, we'll be heroes!
Harima... you take
the anchor position.
Who do you think
you're givin' orders to...?
Just take it easy, Mr. Big Shot.
Runners on your marks!
Get set!
And they're off!
Geez, he's fast...!
But that's what
I'd expect from 2-D...!
I've never even
seen this guy before!
Class D takes the lead!
Crap!
And now Class C
has passed the baton!
That guy's fast!
Will ya look at that?!
Runner Asou is
giving it his all!
He's overtaken the top
runner in scant seconds!
Imadori!
Leave it to me!
What's that idiot doing?!
What's this?
Imadori is in a
crouching start?!
That's is unheard of!
I should've known...!
Once a moron, always a moron!
Here!
What are you doing, ya pinhead?!
Move it!!
Game time!
Mm-kay, he's started tumbling...
in an impressive display
but the wrong event...!
He's now running!
This some kind of
strategic maneuver?
Heh, heh, heh...!
Did you see that...?
I started tumbling so
I could build up speed...!
I call it the Imadori Special!
Whatever it was, it sucked!
Class 2-D has taken the lead!
Whoopsie.
Hey! Come back!
Don't let the crowd
fool you, it's over.
With me and Harry left
against you... it's a shoo-in.
You know what...?
Your overconfidence
is your weakness.
Oh...? You think so...?
Has your class delinquent
suddenly straightened up?
Hmph!
Remember, I'm not a patient man!
And here comes
Imadori... finally!
Don't worry, Imadori, I'll do
the best I can to make up!
Imadori special!
No! Don't!
And listen to Hanai roar!
What energy!
He's running like a demon!
It's like the god of speed
has entered this race!
It can't be...!
It's impossible...!
Hanai's gaining on me!
Ugh... and what's
with that yell...
it's driving me crazy.
Can't... concentrate...
It's okay...! We can still win
this...! Stay focused, got it?!
Come on...
So hurry up and go already.
What?!
Oh, didn't you know...?
When I win it'll be
much more impressive
if I come from behind, so
please, take your head start.
Come and get me...
samurai haircut.
You can count on it...
and you can leave
my hair outta this.
Hair...
Oh, crap...! What if my hat
falls off while I'm running?!
Ahh! Here he comes!
Harima! Take the baton!
The men of 2-C
are counting on you!
Man... you don't
care who gets hurt
in your relentless pursuit
of victory, do you?
I have no choice!
Let's do this!
Oh, wow, I don't believe it!
He actually gives a crap!
Harima!
What's gotten into him?
Oh, wow, look at him go!
It's incredible!
I don't believe it...
he's really doing it!
Way to go, Harima!
Whoa! Harima is even drawing
the cheers of the other classes!
Every second counts!
I've gotta reach the goal
before my hat falls off!
Ahh! The faster I run,
the more it slips!
Dear, Lord...
I know this is the first time
I've ever prayed... but please.
Give me... a miracle!!
Impossible!
Goal!!...!
Kenji Harima is first...!
Class C wins the championship!
Now that the competition's over,
I gotta say you're
a beautiful dancer.
Argh!! I hate when there aren't
enough girls for partners!
And why does the
committee chairman have
to get stuck with this job?
I had no idea you were
so delicate and graceful.
Me...? Do you really think so?
Hello.
Where... is... he?
Looks like Karasuma's
DJing tonight too.
Everyone's acting like
they haven't noticed...
they're just dancing away
like everything's normal...
Oh, well... at least now I won't
have to hide my head anymore.
And it looks like I'm back
to being all alone again...
I suppose... that's best
for a delinquent like me.
Dance with me.
What, are you kidding
me, Rich Girl...?
You with that bum leg...
...and me with
my bald... head...
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
If you're dancing with me,
you gotta hold your head up
high, you got it...? Okay...
Rich Girl... you okay?
Don't worry about it...
I'm fine... You know what...?
Today was a good day.
Oh, man... check it out!
Hey, is that Eri?!
Y'know something, Whiskers?
What?
You're... a really lousy dancer.
Is a person's fate controlled
by money, or by chance...?
This is the perpetual mystery
that drifts over
the sea of time.
Next time on School Rumble:
"Irritation. Indecision.
Wandering."
Stormy weather is coming.