Hurry. Time is running out...
School Rumble is about
to begin. Don't miss it.
Bring it!
Here you go.
Wheel a monitor and a
player to class and set it up.
We've got a video to watch.
No problem, sir.
Thanks for being
such a good sport.
I only ask because
you seem to enjoy media.
Yes, sir...
That I do...
And especially videos.
Bless your heart,
you poor little thing...
Are you running
errands for Itoko?
Oh... Yes, ma'am...
I don't mind.
Please excuse me. I have to go.
Wow, what a sweetheart.
Yeah. She's well-mannered,
polite, and proper, too.
So everything you weren't
when you were her age, huh...?
You hellion...
Say that again and I'll cut you!
I was only teasing.
Oh...! Before I forget,
have you considered it...?
Being my model for
the art show? Well?
Yeah...! About that...
Well, I guess I'll...
do it... just 'cause it's you.
Thanks a bunch, Itoko.
Go, go! Yeah!
Come on, you can do it!
Gentlemen, I have information!
Huh?
Huh??
I don't get it.
Me, neither.
What are they doing?
A war council.
Huh?
Well, Nishimoto...
Your report, please?
At oh-nine-hundred,
I learned Ms. Sasakura
is holding an art exhibit.
And the model who's going
to pose for her paintings?
Better hold onto
your seats, men...
According to my
top secret sources,
that model is none other
than Itoko Osakabe...
And the theme?
"The Female Nude
in Form and Figure."
They might just be paintings,
but they're still a way
to see Ms. Itoko's hot bod!
Mmm, those slinky curves...!
Oh, man! We'll see the
engine and the caboose!
Nishimoto's da bomb
when it comes to sexy
pictures and movies!
Yeah, the guy rules!
He's always able to get his
hands on adult-only videos!
Do you mean
pornographic materials?
Settle down, men.
We have a mission.
Ganji Nishimoto...
Due to his gentle nature, his
influence over the male students
of Class 2-C,
and his large belly,
he's also known as
"Buddha Nishimoto."
Imadori, report...
What's our target's size?
D-cup... No doubt about it.
Kyousuke Imadori...
aka "Hummingbird."
One of Buddha Nishimoto's
most trusted lieutenants,
and a partner in the
famous "Video Store Pact."
He is also a pervert.
And Fuyuki... For your job...
Don't tell me...!
Surveillance, right? I'm on it!
I'll pass out pics of
Ms. Itoko to my sources!
Takeichi Fuyuki...
aka "White Heron."
Recruited with a video
entitled "Three Hot Babes."
He, too, is a pervert.
Hey, Nara... Pass these
out for me, will ya?
Uh...
Kentaro Nara... Ah, who cares?
Idiots.
I know, right?
We're completely surrounded
by perverts. It's pathetic.
But isn't the
body a work of art?
Maybe it's something
we should see.
Yeah, I guess that's true...
Ms. Itoko does have
a nice figure, after all.
Does Karasuma want
to gawk at her, too?
Thank goodness...!
Guess Karasuma's
just not interested.
It's nice to know he's not a
deviant like the other guys.
Huh?
So anyway.
Some of the other
guys aren't slimeballs.
Just check it out.
Asou...
Umezu...
Harima?
Wait, I thought he'd be into it.
Don't be fooled...
I bet that dirty mind of his
is chock-full of nasty thoughts.
Just look at the way
he's playing with his nuts.
These creeps are gonna
get crushed by Itoko...
They'll find out why her
nickname is "The Nutcracker."
I guess we can count
Hanai out. Good boy.
He's always so... serious.
We have a lot of
work ahead of us
if we're to reach our objective.
Good luck, men.
You're dismissed.
Fuyuki...
Can I keep some of these
pictures of Ms. Itoko?
Sure!
Woo hoo hoo...!
They're so sexy! Oh yeah!
Whoa!
I think the sleeping
giant has finally awakened!
Show me what you've got,
Imadori, right now!
No, they're mine!
But I'm the...
Class rep...! Do it!
I was wrong... He's a perv.
It's Yakumo!
Uh... Me? Are you sure?
Yes... You'll be fantastic.
I want you to take
part in my exhibit.
Did she say-?
I guess I can do it then.
Thanks so much.
You're a big help!
Then... that means...!
Yakumo, she's...
She's going to pose nude!
Her... Naked...
But that means
all the other guys
who go to the exhibit will see
nude paintings of Yakumo, too!
I can't let them see
my true love in the buff!
Hey!
Oh, what should I do...?
The exhibit...
Huh?
Nude...
What's with him?
What...?! You're gonna be part
of Ms. Sasakura's
exhibit, Yakumo?
Yes.
Wow, that is so cool...!
Maybe I should help out,
too! It'd be fun!
Really...? Thank you...
I'd be so nervous
doing it alone.
Nothing to worry about, Sis!
We'll just grin and bear it!
That means...!
Tenma's gonna pose nude!
Her... Naked... Wait!
But that means all
the other guys who go to
the exhibit will see nude
paintings of Tenma, too!
I can't let them see
my true love in the buff!
Oh, what should I do?!
...so Star B appears
as a double image
when Star A is aligned with it.
The scientific term
is microlensing.
Does everyone follow?
Any questions?
Wow, something's really
inspired a lot of you...
Wish I knew what it was.
She is so...
Pass it on. The opening
date's been announced.
When...? Where?
It's next Saturday
at the Yagami Gallery.
Roger that. Got any new info
about the featured paintings?
Rumor has it they'll be
stylish, sexy, and eye-popping.
Tenma...
I heard you were going to
be in Ms. Sasakura's exhibit.
Oh yeah!
I'm gonna show...
off... what... I've... got!
She's gonna do it...
I can't wait!
Everyone's gonna
see her goodies.
Oh, Tenma...
You know not what you do.
Hey, Sis.
Here. You forgot
your lunch again.
Thanks, you're the best!
So you're going to be in
the art exhibit, too, huh?
Yes.
Good luck pulling
it all off, Yakumo.
Wow... Just think
of all the exposure!
All the exposure?
Oh, sweet, precious Yakumo,
what am I supposed to do?!
Did you know they're going
to sell prints of
all the paintings, too?
No...! How cool!
I know. I might even
be tempted to buy one.
Why stop with just one?
That's it!
I'll get there before
all the other guys
and buy up all the prints!
What a genius plan!
I miss those days.
Getting misty-eyed
over our wayward youth?
I believe someone
is getting soft.
Maybe. Some of my students
remind me of us at that age...
Makes me realize that nothing
ever really changes, you know?
You and I. We've
been through a lot.
Yes. Yes, we have...
Good times and bad, we've
stuck together through them all.
Yes, that's affirmative.
Good work.
We strike at nine a.m...
this Saturday!
It's been said that "art is
in the eye of the beholder."
But the guys from
Class 2-C are looking
with another part of the body.
Get ready, men...! This is it!
Ms. Sasakura...
Congratulations on your exhibit.
Glad you could
make it... Thank you.
All guests need
to sign in, please!
Tenma... Hey, you guys are
workin' pretty hard, huh?
Actually, I knew it
would be pretty easy...
And to think Yakumo was
too nervous to do it alone.
Oh, excuse me,
you forgot to sign in!
I can't believe it!
We didn't see anything!
The only ass at
that exhibit was you.
I'm not sure I understand
what she meant,
but Ms. Itoko told me
this the day of the exhibit...
"Nothing ever really changes
in life, especially boys."
You want to put on
a staged wedding?
Uh-huh... It's just to
advertise the church, you see...
We'll stage a wedding,
take lots of pictures,
and use the best
photos in a brochure.
And so... you want
me to play the bride?
Of course, you'd be perfect.
Hey, are you gonna get
married, Ms. Yakumo?!
Can I be your flower girl?!
Can I? Pretty please,
can I, Ms. Yakumo?
Well?
Um... But who-
Wait, let me guess.
You want to know who's
playing the groom...?
Don't ya?
I'm a plane! Vroom!
No need to worry...!
A co-worker at my part-time
job would be perfect!
It's time, love muffin!
I-I'm sorry, Yakumo...
My co-worker couldn't
make it, so Hanai volunteered.
Do you want to just call it off?
We can, but we'll
miss the deadline
to get the brochure printed.
It's okay.
Yeah...? Really...!
Thank you...! You're the best!
Okay, here we go.
Now, Hanai, I need you
to give me a serious look.
Huh...? Serious, you say...?
How 'bout this?
Oh...! That's great...!
You'll be just perfect!
It'll be even better
if you don't talk!
Flattery will get
you everywhere!
You're a real moron, Asou!
I can't believe you didn't
want to be the groom!
What...?! Are you crazy?!
Look, I wanted to do it,
but I couldn't get off...
Your orders, please?
Man, I would have just quit!
Dude, you could have
been in a picture with that
hot Tsukamoto chick when
she's wearing a wedding dress!
Yeah, you jackass!
Are you guys ever
gonna order anything?
The oolong tea you ordered, sir.
Keep it cold.
I'll be back after
some ass-kicking.
Huh?
Now that blowhard Hanai's
gonna be the groom.
Not for long...! The nerve
of that beardless geek...!
No one's good enough
to play Tenma's husband!
No one that is... but me!
She's beautiful...
That does it!
I can't hold my
feelings in anymore!
If I do, I'm going to burst...!
Here... goes nothing!
Oh, Yakumo...
I must tell you something.
Stop the wedding! Now!
Huh?
Hail... Mary!
Let's roll.
Hold it!
Explain yourself, Harima!
Back off, Four Eyes...
Go find yourself
another girl, got it?
He's bad...!
Hope he kicks his butt!
Do it...! Beat him, Four Eyes!
Another girl? I think not...
There will never be a woman
more incredible than she is!
We agree on somethin'.
This shouldn't take long.
Now take a hike,
beardless boy...
I'm gonna be her
husband! Not you!
Wrong!
I never thought it
would end... like this...
Had enough yet?
Oh, Harima!
Harima, dear!
Tenma, no!
What...?! How...?!
But you were out cold!
I'll never stop coming back,
jerk...! Because I'm in love!
So say your prayers!
Had enough yet?
Oh, Hanai!
Hanai, dear!
My Yakumo!
What...?! I thought
I broke your face!
Never! My love makes me strong!
All right...! Do you really
love this girl that much?
Answer me!
Of course!
She can only have one guy in
her life and that's gonna be me!
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but that's a position
I'm going to be filling shortly!
Not after...
my Hurricane Dragon Punch!
Mere child's play...
compared to my Hundred
Flowers Tiger Attack!
Gentlemen, the shoot
has been completed!
No thanks to you two.
You're...?
I'm Yakumo Tsukamoto.
Stepping up to be the man
that you couldn't be
in this blessed union.
You guys were fighting for
so long that I had
to find someone,
and Akira was the
only one available.
Yakumo and I are going out
to dinner now. Take care.
Thanks for all the help today.
You guys were great.
See you in class.
Look, dude, I'm... sorry. Okay?
Forget it...
Hey, you never told me...
So why did you come
to the church anyway?
Meteor shower?
Yeah...! And it's going
to be visible in a few hours!
I'm so there... When?
According to Ms. Itoko,
tomorrow night.
Hey, we should all get
together and watch it!
Sounds like fun!
Where would be the best place?
Yagami Shrine.
Perfect! I'll get Yakumo
to make us box lunches!
Yeah! Free food, baby!
Meteor shower, huh?
Yakumo... You're the only
shooting star for me...
Better start making my list.
For what?
All the wishes I want to make...
If you see a falling star,
your wish will come true
if you repeat it three times
before the star burns out.
Oh, so that's how it works?
I better think of some wishes.
Don't just stop with some.
Think of a lot.
There'll be plenty of shooting
stars to make wishes on!
Is wishing three
times even possible...?
Stars fall pretty quickly.
Come on!
With that attitude you
won't get any wishes.
Well, I'm game if you guys are.
So speak up, what's
everybody gonna wish for?
Uh...
I hope the sky's
clear tomorrow night.
Please stay clear, skies!
Right...
Yeah, I guess
we'll have to cancel.
The weatherman said it's
going to pour all night...
Yeah, I wanted to see it, too.
It's not fair.
How are...
the wishes going to come
true if I can't see the stars?
Here, Sis. You don't
want to catch cold.
What's the fuss, Iori...?
Is there something outside?
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ I will be with you ♪
Oh, wow...
♪ Whenever you need ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ I will be with you ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
Hey, Sis...? Wake up!
Ow!
You sleep... like a log.
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Whenever you need ♪
I want my sister to have
a life full of happiness.
I want a nice, soft pillow.
I've been growing my beard
long to impress Tenma!
But when I woke up this morning,
someone had cut it
all off...! Who did it?!
They'll be takin'
a dirt nap real soon!
Next time on School Rumble:
"That's Gone! This is
Gone! Options, Gone!"...
Did you do it,
spoiled rich girl?!