Love; war or comedy?
Tragedy or farce?
Find out next on
School Rumble!
Too eager!
All right! You go boy!
Kick his butt, Mangoku!
Yeah! Wah!
Ah! What a day for a field trip!
A class field trip.
It almost makes me feel like
we're back in grade school.
Oh, you make it sound
like we're in kindergarten.
Call it an "educational outing."
It still amounts to the
same thing, doesn't it?
So, where are we headed today?
Who knows?
Look, it's Karasuma!
There's something
different about him today!
No argument here.
For some reason candy tastes
better on days like this.
I wonder what causes that?
Do we have to stay in our
assigned seats after we leave?
Let's hope not.
With everybody so relaxed, the
boys might actually talk to us
without tripping
over their tongues.
I'm not into awkward small talk.
Of course! I should have
thought of this before!
I can sit next to Karasuma!
Ah, Tenma! Even with your mouth
full of candy, you're beautiful!
Today, I'm gonna
sit next to you!
You eat just like a chipmunk.
It's so not cute.
I can't help it, I'm nervous.
It's him!
Karasuma!
Okay! I'm going for it!
Crap! Why am I sitting here
playing Old Maid with this guy?
Tenma's sitting right behind me!
Besides, this guy's
impossible to beat!
Talk about a poker face.
I can't even see Karasuma!
He's so close, yet so far!
Oh, I wish that
Harima would move!
This is ridiculous!
I gotta make a move!
Come on! Huh? Old Maid again?
Okay, guys, rest stop!
Be back on the bus in
fifteen minutes sharp!
Yes, Mr. Tani.
Dammit! All I have
to do is sit down!
Okay. I've still got a chance.
I've got a list of topics
ready to make small talk with.
I've read all
the latest magazines.
I've got it all covered.
Okay Harima.
It's go time. Be cool.
Let's go, people!
Go time! Go time!
Go time! Be cool.
Somebody just shoot me.
My what a nice
looking young man.
Watch it.
You're in for trouble if Mrs.
Suru takes a fancy to you, kid.
I can't take it!
Besides, this old guy is
beating me at cards, too!
I gotta get outta here now!
Hey you, driver!
You gotta stop this bus!
Hold on! What about our game?
Oh, please stay a little longer,
sonny, there's gonna be yogurt.
I can't stay here! Get off me!
I gotta get back
to Tenma! Stop it!
Tenma!
Oh, crap, where am I now?
Ugh! Get your snout outta there!
I gotta get back to the bus!
Somebody stop this thing!
He's alone, he's alone!
That seat's empty!
This is my big chance!
Yes!
But what should I say?
Pardon me for intruding,
but is this seat taken?
Oh, puke!
That's just too cliché!
"Hey, there, are you
having a good time?"
Oh, no, that's even worse!
Now what?
She looks like she's
having a fit over there!
I see.
Enough! Just do it!
K-K-K-K--
Hey, Karasuma! Can I sit here?
Huh?
Thanks, appreciate it!
Why you stuck up little--
You should never mess
around with a woman in love!
Hope you enjoy your ride!
Think my seat's broken.
That's weird.
Okay, pork chops,
get outta my way,
there's a beautiful
woman waiting.
I gotta get back
to that field trip!
Tenma! Huh? Oh no.
Wait for me,
Tenma! I shall return!
Oh, I don't feel good.
Mr. Tani, may
I sit up front please?
Of course.
Aren't you feeling well?
See you later.'Kay, Karasuma?
Yes, I did it!
At last! My big chance
has finally arrived!
Only now I feel sick, too.
It's true! Kharma
is a cruel mistress!
Mr. Tani?
May I sit up front, too?
You too? I hope
this isn't an epidemic.
Now what's up with those two?
Eh.
I'm not gonna let a
little bad luck stop me!
I will sit next to Tenma,
just wait and see!
Tenma! Wait for me!
Morning.
Oh! Morning, Sis.
Breakfast is ready, and your
lunch box is on the counter.
Thanks.
I can't wait for you.
I've got to leave early today.
Oh? That's unusual.
What's this? Three lunch boxes?
Her lunch box,
my lunch box--
Could it be for a boy she likes?
Go, Yakumo! Go, Yakumo!
Go, Yakumo-mo-mo!
See you later.
My precious
baby sister's in love!
There's so much
I'll have to teach her.
Of course, she's so
inexperienced compared to me.
I hope this guy isn't some creep
who'll take advantage of her.
Now I'm worried.
I'd better follow her and scope
this guy out, just to be safe.
Whoops! Almost forgot
to lock the door.
Hey, Sis.
Oh man! All this just for a cat?
I thought you had
yourself a boyfriend!
Sorry, it's a cat.
Oh, well, forget it.
So you've been taking
care of a stray cat.
How's it going?
Well, so-so.
He's pretty stand-offish.
He hasn't even
come close to me yet.
Stubborn little thing.
He's not ready to trust me.
Here's your lunch.
You can eat it
when you're ready.
Oh, for heaven's sake!
Why are you wasting
your time on this?
I'm just testing
something, that's all.
You need to forget
about that dumb cat
and find a boyfriend
like a normal girl!
Crimanetly!
We're gonna be late! Let's go!
So long. See you later.
Check it out!
Isn't that the new
freshman, Tsukamoto?
What a babe!
Yeah, she's easy on the eyes.
She's the most
popular girl in her class.
No duh!
And not only is she gorgeous,
she rocks at sports, too!
Just the other day,
the coach for the track team was
trying to sign her up!
Yeah, she's smart!
She was eighth in her class
after the midterm exam!
Wow! So the perfect
girl really does exist.
She must have a heck
of a social life.
That's what you'd think,
but she never talks to guys.
Oh, the picky type, huh?
Not at all.
She just doesn't realize
how popular she is!
What a waste.
Yeah, it's her
only flaw. Too bad.
Morning!
Sara! Morning.
What are you day dreaming about?
I thought--
I thought I saw a cat.
A cat?
Do you think it was the
same cat you've been helping?
I'm not sure.
And it followed you to
school to repay your kindness?
Come on, that sounds
like a fairy tale!
I guess you're right.
Those things don't happen.
Not in real life.
Okay.
Pay attention.
This stuff will be on the test,
so you might want
to write it down.
Hey, is this yours?
Holy crap!
I actually spoke to Tsukamoto!
This must be my lucky day!
Oh, thanks a lot.
Yes!
She almost touched me!
Excuse me, Miss Tsukamoto?
It's my understanding
that you're one of our
most gifted students.
Would you care to join the
Student Council this year?
Oh, well--
It's really a great honor.
You will join, right?
I have to get home
right after school.
Well, at least come with me
and take a look at the
student council room, okay?
Come on, come on!
Knock it off! You're
scaring her, you little perv!
I didn't mean anything! Honest!
Hmph!
Hi, I'm Haruki Hanai!
And captain of the aikido team!
I'm acquainted with your sister!
In fact, she and
I happen to be classmates!
Enough chat,
let's get to the point!
Do you want to
join the aikido team?
'Cause I think you'd look pretty
good in aikido pants!
I'm sorry. I'm not really
all that into martial arts.
No!
The martial arts allows a woman
to protect herself
from unwanted attentions!
For example.
If I do this.
How did she do that?
No problem.
I'll grab her left arm.
I don't get it!
What's the matter with me?
Why can't I get a hold of her?
Whoa! Your sister
is the clumsiest klutz
in the entire world, but you--
Oh! I'm sorry about that.
Yakumo! It's burning!
Oh no, I wonder
if I can save it?
Forget it! Let's try something
different today, an experiment!
But I was making your
favorite curry, are you sure?
So? We'll just make a
different curry, I don't mind!
All right.
So what should we make?
Here's the deal, I'm making
two lists of ingredients,
then you choose one at random.
There! Now choose!
The left one.
Here you go!
Yes! Banana and bean jam cake!
Hold on, you gave
me the wrong paper.
I said the left.
Right! Banana and bean jam,
banana and bean jam,
banana and bean jam!
Oh we're gonna make a
curry, make it in a hurry,
oh I hope it isn't furry,
really shouldn't worry!
Let's dig in!
Oh, gross!
Oh, come on,
sis, it was your idea.
I think it turned
out pretty good.
Dinner time!
You still here?
Poor little thing.
You got yourself stuck,
didn't you? Come on.
Nice and slow.
Almost there.
Oh, man.
Are you all right?
Huh?
I heard it.
Sometimes, I can read
what's in people's hearts,
so I wondered if I could read
what your heart would say,
but I guess a cat's
heart always says "meow".
Too bad.
Man, I didn't bring an umbrella!
It's too late now.
Let's make a break for it!
Wow, it was clear til
just a little while ago!
Did you bring an umbrella?
No.
No sweat.
You can share mine.
Thanks!
What about you, Akira?
I'm good.
Hey guys, do you
think we should hang out
for a little while
and wait for Tenma?
She said she had
something to take care of.
I'll betcha anything you like
she forgot to bring an umbrella.
Name your odds.
No, she's got an umbrella,
all right, you can count on it.
Therefore, we can leave
with a clear conscience.
But how do you know that?
I just know.
Hmmmm.
At last! They're gone!
You forgot something, Mikoto.
While it's true I always
forget my umbrella.
Ta-da!
My very capable sister
always leaves me a back-up,
just in case!
What a downpour!
I'm sorry everybody.
I didn't really have
something to take care of.
It's just I couldn't
miss a chance like today!
A rainy day, and a guy,
and a girl, under
an umbrella together.
There's no way it can fail!
Karasuma and
I under one umbrella!
En garde, Karasuma!
Your heart is mine!
Whoops.
Oh, no!
I just realized something!
What if Karasuma already
has his own umbrella!
I've done it again!
I'm such a total idiot!
Idiot, idiot,
idiot, idiot, idiot.
That hurts.
Huh?
Oh my gosh!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Please. I'm fine.
Uh, it's funny
I should run into you.
I wanted to ask you
if you, uh, have an--
Umbrella?
Uh, no.
Sweet!
Look! Karasuma!
I have an umbrella!
The two of us could share it!
I brought my rain costume.
His rain costume?
Most high school kids
wouldn't be caught dead
in a nerdy rain costume!
But that's why he's special!
My Karasuma can
look stylish in anything,
even a geeky rain slicker!
It's another thing
I love about him!
But wait! This sucks!
There's no point in sharing!
He's already prepared
for the rainy weather!
Oh, so what if you
have your own umbrella?
Let's share anyway!
Huh? But we have two,
we'll just get wet!
How come?
Because it'll be fun, you goof!
And I love doing
coupley stuff like this!
Who cares if
we get a little wet?
Aw.
Oh! Oh!
I hadn't thought of that!
I can use that approach!
Okay, this time I'm not
gonna take no for an answer!
Karasuma! H-hold on a minute!
We--we can still share
my umbrella, just for fun!
You--you'll enjoy it!
I promise! So why don't
we give it a try? 'Kay?
His rain costume is a water imp?
I love you, Karasuma.
So very, very much.
Softball? But I reek at sports!
But Karasuma is watching,
so I gotta give it my all!
Next time on School Rumble:
"Burning Hot First Love!
Burning Hot Tea Party!
Burning Hot Softball!"
Can too much tea
make you pass out?