School Rumble is coming up next!
Wow, it all looks so good!
Let's dig in!
I almost forgot to ask...
how far was everyone
able to swim today?
Two meters.
Zero meters.
Oh, get with it, you guys...!
I can't believe you didn't
make any progress at all...!
The class klutz here swam twenty
meters, a new personal best...!
What about you, Mikoto?
Five kilometers.
Oh my god! That's incredible.
How could you
possibly swim so far?
Imadori must be the
greatest swimming coach ever!
Hey, Imadori...!
Think you can give me
swimming lessons next?
Sure thing...!
I bet I can take
you pretty far
in a very short
time, no problem!
Oh no! How clumsy of me.
Don't get cocky, kid...
Wow... He's hardcore.
Oh my goodness,
are you all right?
It's nothing really.
Here, let me get that.
That's very kind of you, Tenma!
I really appreciate it!
Hot soup! I spilled
hot soup in my lap!
It's really hot, no kidding!
Calm down, you big baby,
I've got it.
Don't get fresh
with me, you jerk!
Mikoto, you
little devil, you...!
Pretty smooth the way you got
that guy all alone for so long!
What did you do?
Come on, tell us!
We wanna hear all the
dirty little details later!
Woah, there.
Oh, Miko, you're
such a bashful flower!
Wait a minute...!
Could this be the reason Harima
has been in such a bad mood...?
Because he's jealous
of Mikoto and Imadori...?
Of course...! She must
be the one he's sweet on!
Psst...! Hey, Harima!
Could you come outside with me?
There's something
personal I'd like
to talk to you
about... Okay?
All right...!
It took a little while...
Okay, a long while...
but Tenma's finally noticed
my irresistible charm!
This is kind of...
awkward for me...
But I understand...
there's someone
special you like...
Yes! Yes!
Have you told this
someone how you feel?
What...? Oh...! Ah, well...
I've tried more than once
but she has an odd way
of missing the point.
I can imagine...
She's pretty dense
about these things.
No, it's okay...!
It's all my fault!
Oh, you sweetie...!
Gosh...! What a guy...!
You're a real
old-fashioned gentleman!
Okay, then...!
You can count me in!
Holy crap, I'm so happy!
Tenma! I just wanna hug you!
Let me help you practice...
Say, "I love you."
I... I luh...
That is, I...
Luh...
Luh-oo!
Argh, it's no good!
Oh...! Come on, now...!
That's 23 times!
Toughen up...!
I mean, you're a big
strong guy, right...?
Three words!
How hard can it be? Geez!
I'm sorry, Tenma...
Never mind...
Well, I guess I have
no other choice
but to show you by example.
No...! Wait!
Hold on a sec...
I'll be right with you.
That was close...
Harima...
Here's the deal...
It's like this:
I love ya, beautiful.
Hey!
If you're just gonna
laugh at me, forget it!
I'm trying to help you!
Now straighten up
and get serious!
Listen, babe, how many times
do I have to spell
it out for you...?
You shoulda realized
how I felt ages ago!
That's it!
Yeah...? Really...?
Did I do a good job?
Okay...
Now you give it a try,
just like that!
Well, that's weird... huh...
You look like someone.
Wow, look at the time!
Back to work!
I, uh... I... Can't say it!
Okay, I'll do it for you again.
Hey, babe...! What do I have to
do, paint a picture for you...?
You sure can be thick!
That's it on the nose...!
You changed the words
a little from before,
but that's exactly
what I'm trying to say!
Hold on...
I think it's
coming back to me...
No, no, it isn't!
Yes, I've almost got it.
Enough!
Babe!
You're so thick...!
Now listen to me!
I...
Love...
Yuhaaa... I can't say it!
But that was perfect...!
All right, let's take
it from the top...
I'll do it for you once more.
Look, how many times do I have
to tell you that I love you...?
You must be dumber than dirt...!
Do you have any idea what
you've been putting me through?
Aw man, if she only knew!
Tenma's right over there...
Maybe I can snuggle
up next to her...
D cup, D cup, it's got to
be a D cup, D cup, D cup,
it's got to be ...
D cup, D cup, it's got
to be a D cup, D cup...
D cup, D cup, D cup, D cup...
That's the fifth
time he's gone around...
You'd think he'd
get the hint by now.
Ah! I'll just sneak in from
behind... easy does it...
Just a little farther,
and then...
I've finally got you,
Yakumo, my beloved...
Oh, no! This bastard's
gonna ruin my whole plan!
Yakumo, hold me...
Holy crap, this guy is strong!
He's breaking my ribs!
Let go! Let go, dammit!
Argh...! It's okay...!
Don't... resist me!
What's going on?
Are we having an earthquake?
Hey... Wait a minute...
Hmph!
Hey, what's wrong with
you guys...? Rough night?
Yeah, you could say that.
I had the worst nightmare.
And what happened to your faces?
You look awful!
Don't ask.
Hey, Akira, are we gonna
get to see your video later?
That's a very good question...
That's enough!
Well done, Haruki. Good job!
The old man's losing it.
Did he really think
these newcomers
had a chance against our school?
Maybe he should let his son take
over the dojo; he's terrific.
It'd be a waste of brains.
He's a straight A student, too.
That's true.
Hey, Yasaburo, how 'bout a
little praise for your kid here?
Don't worry about it.
Pretty impressive, Mikoto,
that guy was nationally ranked!
Aw, no big deal, I got lucky!
Huh?
Hey, Grumpzilla...!
You won your round too,
so let's see that
happy face...? Hiya!
Hey...! Ow...! Watch it!
Mikoto's birthday party...
And they want me to
perform something again...
But if I do another
martial arts demonstration,
Mikoto will be mad at me...
Hm...
Ah, crap...
I can't possibly think
of something that
everybody will enjoy!
But my honor as a
man is at stake...!
Haruki Hanai cannot
let anyone down!
I must have something
stashed away...
A magic set, juggling
balls, anything...
Hm?
Yes...
That was the summer
of our second year in
elementary school...
Man, you are so
pathetic, you know that?
You suck!
And your dad teaches
martial arts?!
Imagine a useless little loser
like you trying to do aikido!
You haven't got a
chance, dorkface!
They were right...
I couldn't cut it in aikido...
I only took it up
because Dad made me.
Maybe you'd be better if you
stuck to studying, four eyes!
The bullies never
left me alone...
I'm finished!
Haruki!
Get back and finish your food!
If you don't eat it all,
you know Mikoto's
going to leave you behind!
I don't know why they
always compare us...
I'm the quiet brainy type.
Mikoto is outgoing and friendly.
Everyone admires
her... but me...
You need some help up?
Everyone is going out for
noodles after practice...
So let's be sure and make
ourselves extra hungry!
There's no way I'll
ever be as good as her.
Ya want some more?
No thanks, I'm good.
You're not full already...!
Come on, have
some more noodles!
Ulp! No, really, I'm full!
Look out, you're spilling!
Oh, sorry!
One a hero, the other
a punching bag for bullies...
and it just kept
getting worse...
Now for our next class
we'll be doing duets,
so I want you to form into
pairs and start practicing!
Everyone in my class
started giving me
the silent treatment,...
pretending like I didn't exist.
I was as invisible as the air...
It was so weird,
I couldn't stand it...
Finally, I just stopped
going to school.
I didn't do anything wrong...
I just decided to leave,
all by myself...
Hanai!
Mikoto?
I'm here about the duet...!
Because I'm the class
music monitor this term...
The teacher says you
should pair up with me!
No! I'll never go
back there again...
There's no way!
What?!
You come out of there or
I'll keep blowing this thing!
I should have given up,
but I was too stubborn...
Mikoto didn't give up either.
She was there on hot days.
She was there on windy days.
She was there on rainy days.
Mikoto's running late today...
Mikoto!
I told you, you didn't
have to go to school today!
Now come on,
let's get you back home!
It's Mikoto's mom!
No, I'm staying here!
What's gotten into you?
You know you're running a fever!
I'm such a jerk.
So, you decided to
come back to school, huh?
Good, 'cause
the teacher's really
been buggin'
me about this duet...!
So let's do it, Hanai!
She never said a word...
not about being sick... or
about her mother scolding her...
Nothing...
Hey...!
Aren't you afraid you're
gonna catch loser cooties
from that geek?
What a cute couple!
Yeah, when are you
two gonna get married?
Hey... That's none
of your business...!
Now get lost!
Why'd you pair up with a
nerd like Hanai anyway?
It's not like the teacher
forced you to do it.
She wanted you to pair up
with somebody else all along!
What...? So Mikoto teamed up
with me because she wanted to?
Aren't you embarrassed
to be seen with him?!
No, I'm not!
I'm not embarrassed
by him at all!
Yeah, you better run, wimps!
Well...?! Don't just
stand there. Practice!
I think she was really
so embarrassed she
could hardly stand it.
Stop crying!
It's annoying...!
On top of that, you're
playing it all wrong...!
Now shape up, we got
a performance...! Hmph!
Right then...
I decided I was going to be
a hero, just like Mikoto...
Hooray.
Okay, Hanai,
let's see what you got!
Give it your best shot,
we're pulling for you!
I hope you'll enjoy my
performance today, Yakumo.
I can't read his mind today...
Today I, Haruki Hanai...
will play the recorder!
Man, you suck!
It's too hot!!
Hot-hot-hot-hot!
Yakumo, something's gone haywire
with the air conditioner!
I think it's from when you
were playing samurai last night,
chasing Iori with the broom,
and you hit the air conditioner
because you decided
it was a bandit.
The repairman said he'd be
here some time this evening.
I'll never make it...!
I'll... die... for... sure!
Okay, here's the deal!
Hm?
We're gonna play
"rock, paper, scissors!"...
Winner goes and cools off,
loser watches the house...
Now get your game face on!
Tell me again why
I should agree to this.
Okay, then, one, two... three!
Rock...! It's a tie!
One, two... three!
Yee... haa!
I hate to say it, but you're
really bad at this game...!
You know what...?
There's a trick to reading what
the other person is gonna do!
See...? You hold your hands
like this and peek through!
Sorry, Yakumo! I'm outta here!
Be careful!
Hello...? The electrician...?
You can't come tonight...?
I see... Goodbye.
Now what...?
I've gotta find some way to cool
things off for Tenma later...
Wait a minute... I know...
Sure...
If I can just convince her to
wear a summer kimono ...
Alright...!
I'm a princess, I'm a princess,
hm... hm-hm... hm... hm.!
Even if it isn't
actually cooler,
it'll make her feel cooler.
And a cool foot
bath should help, too...
Hello, there...
How'd you like a bath?
Iori?
You shouldn't run
off like that, kitty!
You found a nice cool
spot in the shade, huh?
Dum... plings...
dum... plings...
gonna get some dum...
plings, dum... plings...
Sis?
What is it, Yakumo?
Hey, is there
something the matter?
Did you wanna get
something special?
Mm-hm.
Well, what is it...?
You can tell me...
Right...? After all,
I'm your older sister!
Leave it to me...!
I'll take care of it,
'cause that's what sisters do!
That's it... Of course...
I'll get that out...
Yoohoo...! I'm home...!
And I brought ice cream!
A wind chime...!
That's so awesome!
For some reason just looking
at it totally takes
my mind off all the heat!
You're the best, Yakumo!
Ah, Miss Tsukamoto...
Karasuma!
But I didn't think
I'd see you here!
I'm on my way to a
pro-wrestling match...
Do you want to go?
With you? You know it!
Next time on School Rumble...
I've got a pro-wrestling date
with Karasuma...! Alright!