School Rumble...
It's not pansy-core.
My name is Tenma Tsukamoto.
Today I'm gonna confess my
feelings to the one I love...!
Well, that was the plan anyway.
But not only have I not
confessed my love,
Karasuma's hardly been
in any recent episodes!
Meanwhile, we've accepted a
challenge from Class D
and we're gonna throw down
at the athletic meet!
But don't forget,
this is still supposed
to be a romantic comedy!
...so remember, ladies
and gentlemen, a student
has a responsibility to his
physical heath as well as
to his mental excellence.
Don't carelessly injure
yourselves like, say,
the students in...
2-C... oops,
I beg your pardon...
I mean a hypothetically
careless class...
that's like 2-C...
but isn't them.
You suck, Katou!
Next, may I present
Ms. Tae Anegasaki,
the new school nurse...
If anyone gets hurt, please be
sure to have her check you out!
Hey there...! I'll be waiting!
I hope I break something!
Wow... everyone is
really worked up this year!
Yeah, but you gotta wonder
if they're "worked up"
for the right reason.
Huh... face it,
men are all idiots.
Well, we better get
this show started.
You mean you're
not participating
in any of the events?!
I can't, I've got to stay at
this station the whole meet.
I guess it can't be helped,
but it won't be the
same without you.
Oh, Miss Tsukamoto?
Huh?
Do your best, kay?
I will.
And the games are
off to a fierce start,
with 2-C and 2-D going
head to head and toe to toe!
Harry...! You're looking
good there, m'man!
Hey, what can I say,
if they can't hit ya,
they can't hurt ya!
Hey, guys... remember...
the goal is to get
the balls in the--
2-C We rock your world!
2-C We got hot girls!
Go 2-C! Yeah!
I wish I was in 2-C!
Uh... she doesn't seem
to be enjoying this.
She looks actively pissed.
I heard she didn't
want to do it ...
but I think it's like
a requirement for
chicks, or something.
If it really bugs
you that much...
you don't have to do it.
Really?!
Man, I can't stand
these athletic meets!
So what I'd like to
know is, what are you doing,
hanging out in the infirmary...?
Aren't you usually
up on the roof?
Uh... too many pigeons today...
Get lost, you idiot!
I've got rewrites to do!
You can level with me,
you're working
on that hot new
nurse, aren't ya?
Hey, Harima...!
Come on, hurry,
we need you on the field!
Scram, Tsukamoto...!
My man here doesn't have time
to waste on your
stupid athletic meet!
I got lots of time to waste.
It's 2-C!
2-C again!
Class 2-C is dominating
the competition so far!
Yeah, we're mopping up the floor
with those clowns
from 2-D...! Right...!
Now it's my turn
to take 'em down!
Look... let's get
one thing straight here...
I don't like you either,
but right now let's
focus on the event.
Huh?
Nice form.
Now it's the tug of war event
between second year
classes C and D...
and neither side
is giving an inch!
Man, are we taking those
guys to school or what?
Hey... what happened to Lara?
Uh...
She said it wasn't right
to eat lunch with the enemy.
Well, well, you're startin'
to enjoy it, aren't you?
We're one ahead.
Only the cavalry battle
and the relay left...
that'll decide it.
I sense... Evil!
Masakazu!
I, Haruki Hanai,
hereby swear that...
I will destroy you in battle!
I wanted to say that!
Two events remain to determine
this year's winner...!
Next up, a tradition at our
school, the cavalry battle...!
Three boys and one
girl form one horse team!
What are you going to do?
Are you gonna to drop out?
Well, it's just that
Harima's on your team,
and I thought it might be
awkward for you two...
Oh, not that you'd let it affect
your performance or anything
like that I'm just sayin'.
First of all,
I'm fine with it, okay...?!
And second of all,
why should I care
what that loser thinks,
that's his problem!
As long as you're not upset...
All right, each class,
mount your horses!
Ready for me to mount you?
Sure.
Oh, I'm ready!
I'm counting on you, gentlemen!
There's nothing to worry about!
Hey, would you
mind bending over?
In your dreams, Blondie.
Good luck, Harima!
Eri! I know you'll go
out there and do your best!
Whoa, easy!
Cork it, toots,
and quit draggin' your feet!
What set you on fire?
Let's play to win!
Yeah, playing
to lose'd be stupid.
Hi yo, cavalry, away!
Yay!
Take no prisoners.
Yeah, fine, whatever
you say, Your Highness.
Ichijou...
Hmph...! Hmph!
Now let's see what
you've really got.
Let's... dance.
No more fooling around,
we need to get serious...
Let's go for the win...!
You got me?
Second year class...
are you ready to begin?
Ready...
Whoa!
And it's a furious battle
right out of the gate!
A regular clash of titans!
No quarter given or asked!
Whatever the heck that means.
I've got it!
Who was that?!
The team everyone is watching
this event, Harry and Lara,
have made their move...!
And what a move...
They seem to be everywhere...
striking like lightning...
missing no opening!
Okay, I think we should
go after her first.
What do you think?
Not yet...! Let's thin
out the competition first...
Her turn'll come, don't worry!
Good thinking!
Huh?
Whoa, nelly!
Ichijou just collected her
seventh headband of the game!
Come on, you spineless
wimp, get in the game!
I'm not feelin' it
And so the cavalry
battle comes down
to just three teams competing
for the most headbands!
Between 2-D and 2-C, the rest of
us don't have a chance in hell!
Let's face it, our class sucks,
we might as well just
give up right now and go home.
No...! Sure, we may suck
but we still have our pride...!
I say we go down sucking!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Now what?
Are my eyes deceiving me?
Oh! Class A has
joined its horses!
They've formed a pyramid
with the riders all at the top!
They're virtually unassailable!
Hold on...!
That's gotta be cheating!
Heh...! the rules say
the riders' feet can't
touch the ground,
otherwise it's anything goes!
Let's see what the steering
committee chairman has to say!
Move allowed.
And it's a go...!
A very generous interpretation
by this year's chairman!
Too generous!
Tough luck, baby cakes!
The headband is at the top of
the pyramid, get it if you can!
Sweet mother of pearl!
One of the girls is climbing the
pyramid like a monkey up a tree!
And once again...
it's Karen Ichijou!
That's it, Carolyn, you rock!
Don't give up now,
you fools! Counterattack!
You ass!
Why did you step out
of the pyramid?
Oh, the humanity!
Way to go... Ichijou!
Thanks...! Look at all
of the headbands we've got!
She's the one
we have to get! Ichijou!
Uh... you're scaring me.
You won't topple us so easily!
It's class B's
three fat brothers
whose names no one can remember!
I can barely see the rider!
They look like a wedding cake
with only the bride on top!
Holy Crap! They're fat!
Let's go get 'em!
Oh, my Aunt Fanny's girdle!
Suou is facing them head on!
Whoa... That's nails!
Check it, bro...!
Enemy rider at eight o'clock!
Eight o'what?
Brace yourself!
Too bad...!
We put on another 90 pounds
apiece just for today's contest!
I'm getting seasick.
I know...! Go for their legs!
You mean like this?!
Come about ninety degrees and
then hit 'em from the right!
Ramming speed!!
And the brothers are down!
Suou and her team's
deft series of moves
have toppled this wobbling
wall of human flesh!
You 'n' me, baby!
Hey... gimme a break, will ya?
Hey, jerk, if you don't want it,
why not share it
with the rest of us?
Harima, come on, don't
just wander around the edge,
we gotta get in there
and fight! Let's move it!
Screw that! You wanna fight?
Do it yourself!
Oh, for Pete's sake,
are you still holding a grudge?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
your little bald...
You suck!
How can you be so petty?!
And over something
so insignificant!
How could you call
this insignificant,
you little blonde twit?
Do you remember
what you did to me?
Why, you...
What am I doing?
That'll just make things worse!
Chrome Dome here
is a complete jerk
and pushes every
button I've got...
but, it's up to me
to be the adult here.
Okay, here goes.
You know, Harima...
Yoo-hoo!
Hm?
Do your best, Hario...!
I'm watching!
Uh... yeah, sure...
Wow... she's so warm
for your form I'm sweatin'!
Shut up and go get
your hair harvested.
Okay, careful with that,
it could slip off, ya know...
Face front!
That means... now.
Okay, okay, you're
the boss, I get it!
Right turn, please.
Look, you've made your point...
And left...
Bet you think
this is funny, huh?
Come on, enough's enough!
Oh! I think your cap
might be slipping!
You'll pay for this!!
This is our best chance... Now!
Time for the Pincer attack!
Right!
Get lost! We're busy!
Giddy up, horsie!
Shove it, Princess!
What's that?
Oh, man... What happened here?
Akira! You okay?
Yeah, just dying.
Ha...! Looks like
that's it for 2-C.
Yeah, frickin' pansies.
Look... behind you...
It's class D's ultimate
weapon... Tennoji!!
Ugh. It's over...
We haven't got a prayer...
Don't panic! If anyone can
do this, we can...! Attack!
Damn... three teams at once!
You've gotta be kidding.
This is incredible!
With Tennoji in the game,
every other class is
being annihilated!
Only a miracle can keep 2-D
from winning this one!
Come on, you guys...
we haven't fought at all yet!
If I hide behind a strong team
and can just last
to the end, maybe...
Babies, babies, there's
enough Nara to go around!
No. Tenma's in big
trouble...! Let's go!
Right!
Oh, no... I don't think so.
I was gettin' tired of
fighting all those small fries.
Now I'm after the big fish.
Damn.
Come and get it.
Mikoto! I'll take
care of Tennoji!
Be careful!
We're coming... Tenma...
Uh... oh...
Sweep attack!
Everyone... forgive... me...
Tenma!
Oh! Sorry! Are you all right?!
Okie-dokie...
Bastard...!
How dare you hurt Tenma!
Crap...! Your Hurricane Kick
had no effect!
Ooh, Sawachika's team
is in deep doo-doo now!
The last attack did no damage-o!
You can do it...!
Go, Eri...! Go, Harima!
Damn it, I can't use
all my strength
when I'm stuck to the
team like this...! Argh!!
Okay, listen up, Rich Girl!
You gotta do just
what I tell you!
What's this?
Rider Sawachika
is going around wide!
That's your plan?!
Are you crazy?!
You really wanna try that?
Try what you like, it won't
make any difference!
Quit whining!
Can you do it or not?!
All right, let's do this!
Twin Hurricane Kick!
If I'm goin' down,
I ain't goin' down alone,
you're comin' with me!
Huh...?! No, wait...!
If he takes my cap...
I'll be humiliated in
front of the whole school...!
And in front of Tenma!
They're over; my happy
schooldays filled with romance.
Gone!
No, Sawachika!
Ouch! Rider Sawachika
has fallen off her mount!
It looks like
they collided somehow!
What could've happened?
Hey...! Rich Girl... you okay?
It's your fault we're out of
the game... you bald workhorse!
And just listen to that crowd
roar for Miss Eri Sawachika!
Thanks everyone.
You're very welcome.
Uh-oh! At the other end of the
field, Rider Suou is in a pinch!
She's surrounded by
two of Class D's best!
She's wide open
from this side...! Hah!
Oh, son of a...
Huh...? Banana boy
took the hit?!
Go... get 'em... Mikoto...
Imadori!
All I ask... is that you
remember me at this moment...
a man who fought
for your sake...
and fell in battle...
at your side...
Spare us the melodrama!
Hit 'em hard!
We're gonna kick your
collective ass, 2-D!
She did it!...!
Rider Suou crushed her opponent!
Thank you... Imadori.
Look out! Get out
of the way! Imadori...
Gotcha.
Unbelievable!...! After tripping
on their own classmate,
Team Suou is out of the game!
At this rate,
we're doomed for sure!
No... not yet.
What do you mean?
We've still got one shot.
Okay, folks, it looks like
we're the only ones left!
Let's give it
everything we've got!
Roger!
I've been waiting
for you... Ichijou!
Go!!
What an onslaught!
Ichijou and Gonzalez
are at it tooth and nail!
Lara's gonna make paste out of
that kid from 2-C!
Look again...
she's just flailing away...
Karen's blocked every
punch Lara's thrown at her.
Doin' okay up there Lara?
Don't you worry about me!
There is no way in hell I am
going to lose to that girl...!
She's going down and that's
all there is to it...! Attack!
Take this, Ichijou!
Karen Ichijou has
been unhorsed...!
Class... D... gets... the win!
No!...! Not yet!!
She hasn't fallen yet...! Rider
Ichijou is still in the game!!!
What? I don't believe it!
It didn't work?!
No.
Hanai tossed her up into
the air at the last minute
and then caught her!
Your kick barely
connected with her,
I don't even think she's
bruised, let alone hurt.
Nice move, Hanai!
This is gonna be rough.
Huh?
There's no way Hanai can fight
back carrying her like that.
Finally, victory will be ours.
Oh, mama!...! A direct hit!!
What the hell...?
So now what?
Paint my ass blue
and call me a baboon,
Hanai repelled the attack...!
Talk about abs of steel!
Damn... what is with this guy?
Ah, at last the tree
of training bears the
sweet fruit of victory!
Hey! You're the old man
from the mountaintop!
Oh! I haven't seen you
for a long time...
you're the girl with
the D cup, right?
Cut that out!
You mean you know this guy?
If you wanna score,
now's the time!
Shut up!!
Gonzalez is riding toward
Ichijou with tremendous speed,
ready to uncork
her signature move!
The whole reason I came to
this country... was to fight!
This is it...! Thor's Hammer!
She... She vanished?!
Not quite.
I haven't seen this in years!
A flawless execution of "Nymph's
Dancer!" What a performance!
Lara?
Are you all right?
Oh, dear, I did it again!
Dios mio, Ichijou,
that was a pro wrestling move!
You know what...? You should
come to my dojo some time...
I think you'd make
an interesting opponent!
Um, I think I'll pass on that.
Ichijou's the type
who reacts without
even thinking when she's up
against a tough opponent...!
I never thought I'd meet such
a natural when I came here.
The score now stands...
220 to 218...
and Class C is back in the lead!
Eh... just shake it off.
No, I can't do that.
I was just playing
around up until now,
but from here on
out it's personal...
I'm going to beat them.
You were so cool
out there, Carolyn!
Yeah, 2-C remains victorious!
Eh... none of this
really matters anyway.
Well... I gotta
go feed Napoleon...
So long... classmates.
Go out for the relay...?
Hmph...! No way...!
It's no skin off my nose
if this class wins or loses!
Next time on School Rumble:
"Women's Battle!
Men's Battle!
After the Battle!"
Rich Girl...
What happened to us
on that battlefield?