Do you ever
remember it, my love...
that day on the white bench?
What an incredible
glorious day...!
Spring has finally come!
And she must be...
the goddess of
Spring... Primavera!
But who is she?
Hey, isn't that Yakumo
Tsukamoto from Class 1-D?
Wow, I guess she's
always beautiful,
even when she's asleep.
Man, Some girls
have all the luck
Yeah.
"T" is for tea on a summers
day "Ska" is for dancing
"Mo" is for most wondrous "To"
is for toe-tappingly terrific!
"Tsukamoto" dy Haruki Hanai...
in the spring of his
sophomore year...
Ah Pool cleaning!
Why are we doing this again?
'Cause Hanai
volunteered our services.
That's our class rep for ya.
...and so today it's
your homeroom's turn
to clean the pool, okay?
Yes, sir.
Sir! My class will
clean the pool! Sir!
Huh?
Thanks...
but Class 1-D's already
been assigned to clean it...
We'll do it...!
Cleaning a pool is the dream
of all upstanding young people!
It is our passion, our
raison detre, our destiny!
I, Haruki Hanai,
have a favorite saying:
"To ignore a dirty pool shows a
lack of courage and initiative!"
Well, if you feel
that strongly...
He's always been a workaholic.
Even when he was a little kid.
You were childhood pals, right?
That's right, Haruki Hanai...
Top martial artist...
Top student... Top everything!
You and him,
childhood pals, huh?
Our class dictator and I grew up
studying martial arts
in the same temple
Oh, Yakumo...
To keep your immaculate hands
from being sullied by this task,
I have to put up with
everyone in class harassing me!
How romantic.
Hanai's having a one-sided love
affair with little Tsukamoto.
Did she just say Tsumakoto?!
Then... that explains...
Hanai is pretty
amazing, isn't he?
Tenma did seem pretty
impressed with the guy.
This can't be ignored.
Uh! Karasuma!
Smells mossy...
I wonder if this is his most
favorite scent in the world...
Could it be?
You've got to be kidding me.
I'm doing this all
for you, dear Yakumo...
Please let my scrubbing
not be in vain!
You know...
I'll always remember the two
of us under the blue sky...
A swallow! How lovely!
And speaking of...
It's Yakumo!
Yakumo, please you've
got to wake up...!
It's not safe to sleep out here!
She's still sound asleep.
What should I do...? Uh... Uh...
I know.
One sweet kiss!
Exercise!
That's how I need to think
of all this, as exercise...!
Building my muscles up for
my beautiful beloved Yakumo!
Whoa, didja see that?!
Harima totally
missed Hanai's slapshot!
He can be a real jerk at times,
but Hanai's an amazing athlete!
It appears that
you lost something,
so I was just trying to return
it to you as a courtesy...
Too fast for you, eh?
Whatever, big man...
But hey, if that's the way you
wanna play it, then fine by me.
Whoa! Check it out!
They're locked in a dead heat!
Yeah, it's anybody's game...!
Wait... but maybe not...
Would you look at that?
For all his bad-boy posturing,
Harima turned out to be a
real wuss, don't you think?
Actually, he's doing
better than I expected,
especially for a guy
who's not into sports.
And don't forget:
he's holding his own
against a Shorinji student
who has a black belt in Kenpo.
A master of martial arts
can't lose to a common thug...!
This ends now!
Hey, Sis.
Yakumo!
In your face, jerk!
Oh, dammit!
Hey, it's Yakumo, the new
girl everyone's drooling over.
Wow, she really is pretty!
My teacher sent me out
to see how the cleaning
was coming along.
What do they think we've
been doing out here today?
Goofing off?
Never fear, Miss Tsukamoto!
We're working hard...!
We took a short break to
test out our hockey skills...
and nothing more!
Oh, hey, what's up Hanai...?
I didn't know that
you knew Yakumo.
Hey, why don't we
take this competition
beyond mere child's play...?!
Let's engage in a
real battle instead...!
As you know...
The School Festival
is approaching...
And if you want a say in
what the class does this year,
get down here and join
me on the playing field!
Have you gone insane?!
I haven't been able to
decide which would be better:
putting on a play or setting up
a booth that
sells refreshments...
A friendly game will
help with our decision...
unless somebody objects!
You know, he wants to
impress Yakumo so much
that it's actually
kind of scary.
Guys always fall to
pieces when they're in love.
I'll play!
This sounds really fun!
Uh, wait, count me in, too!
Great! Who else?!
They're actually going to play?
We need some more players!
You gonna do it?
I'll do it if you do it, man!
Well, I think I'll watch a round
first and see how it turns out.
You can count me in, too,
but I'm on the school
play team, 'kay?
You're playing?
Sure. Why not?
I mean, it'll be fun.
You're going to play,
too, right, Mikoto?
Yeah, but I'll be
playing for the booth.
Does it even matter?
Super awesome booth team unite!
Super class play team unite!
You're goin' down, Akira!
We'll see about that.
Princess Aurora is here.
She pricked her finger
on an enchanted spindle
and fell into a slumber that
lasted for one hundred years.
But now... she will
finally be awakened
by a kiss from the Prince.
I know that story.
It's "Sleeping Beauty"...
Right?
Right! I'll play the Prince!
And Yakumo will make the
perfect Princess Aurora!
We are gonna put on...
the best play... ever!
You are so sad
Hey, Asou, you want in?
Take your pick, but it looks
like everone's betting on Hanai.
Then put me down for Harima.
Way to go! That's the spirit!
Akira and her friends are so
stylish, so sophisticated...
And don't forget beautiful!
They're considered the
prettiest girls in school.
Honestly, I do get
a little jealous over
all the attention they get.
Okay, you guys!
All together now!
Go!
Alright! Go, booth, go!
Again!
Go, booth, go!
What's that?!
Say it loud!
Well, I guess I'll
just tell my teacher
that everything is
going along as usual.
Yayyyy, okay, take five!
Yakumo... for you... I...
He's really gone nuts.
The match will now begin.
It's game time, folks.
Wow!
It's like a real game,
with a referee,
a stopwatch and everything!
Karasuma's the referee...?!
I've gotta make him
notice me somehow!
Ms. Tsukamoto... We...
We? We--what...? We...? We?
We're now at war?!
We'd like to start the game
now, so I hope you're ready.
Tenma my love...
Karasuma my love...
Yakumo my love...
This is all...
...for love!
Yes!
All is fair in love and war!
Let's start the game.
Well, you can taste the
excitement in the air today
as Class 2-C squares off
for the School Festival!
There's an opening!
Down the middle...!
Too easy! I'm going for it!
Harima, no, don't!
That's a... curve ball-!
What the hell?!
Great work, Eri!
A stunning move on the
part of Eri Sawachika,
not to mention a great
pass to her winger, Hanai!
Crap.
He's attempting to score!
Goalie Mikoto Suou
had better watch out!
Sh-She stopped it!
Oww!
Hey! Take it easy!
With the play
at stake? No way...
Besides, I've seen you take way
harder hits than that, Mikoto.
And just where
did he see that...?
I wanna go!
Probably at the
Shorinji Temple...
They studied Kenpo together.
I hear they're pretty good.
Huh...
Take this!
What did your grandma
teach you that?
Man, Mikoto's really on fire!
Look'it that!
It would be nice
if you kept your minds
on the game, you pervs!
Back off...!
You've got the wrong idea!
Hey, don't be so harsh.
We're just admiring
her athletic prowess.
Her prowess, huh?
Kick his butt Mikoto!
Keep it up!
We're rooting for you!
You're great, Miko!
Go for it!
Thanks, but this is
kind of embarrassing!
And I'm only one woman.
I can't do this on my own.
Harima! Tenma!
I'm counting on you!
Here you go, Karasuma.
Please enjoy!
Thank you.
You look lovely today.
Here you go, Harima.
Please enjoy it!
Thank you. You're pretty.
Don't you worry!
This game's in the bag, baby!
They're completely hopeless...
Here it comes!
You can defend all you want,
but that's not going to
score you any points...
What's that?
I guess I'm gonna
have to step in.
Huh?!
If Harima loses, we have
to put on a dumb play.
Looks like another
player's joined the game!
Harima, cover the center!
Who the hell are you?
Just do it!
Cover your own center!
Tenma's about to pass to you!
Huh?! Wha-?!
Center, right?! I'm so on it!
Tenma!
Yeah! I've got it!
It's coming your way! Block it!
Huh?!
Aw, Dammit!
It's yours, Harima!
Take the shot!
Her heart and soul gliding
across a pool of chaos.
This is more than just a puck!
So I have to pour every ounce
of energy I have into this...
Lightning flash... of love!
Kenji Harima...
That was his name before
that day, but after that shot,
he became known as
the Phantom Striker.
That's offsides... No goal.
What kind of a
stupid rule is that?!!
Stop it!
You can't argue with a referee!
So much for the
Phantom Striker...
Where's Yakumo...?
Gone, huh...? Oh, well.
Even if you're not here,
I promise you...
...a resounding victory
for your dear love!
Please, Harima,
you've got to stop this!
Uh... I think the game's over
With more players
duking it out on the field,
this game has
reached a fever pitch!
Team against team!
Friend against friend!
Oh, man...! What a fiasco!
They're really making fools
out of themselves out there!
Sure is fun to watch, though!
Hey, Fuyuki, why are
you goofing off over here
with that digital camera, huh?
Because...!
I'm capturing our golden
years in high school plus
a few other tasty shots!
Huh?
Like this super low angle!
Oww!
What are you doing, Fuyuki?
Uh... nothing!
Crap...! Missed her!
Just suck it up...
Can't get discouraged.
After all, I'm lucky to
be a great photographer
and to be in a class filled
with so many red hot babes!
He... seems to be
really dedicated, huh?
Yeah. Too bad it's not
to photography, though.
Stop it!
I'm sorry what?
You little pervert!
You're taking smutty
pictures again, aren't you?!
Smutty?! How dare you?!
I take offense to that...!
What you so foolishly call
smut, I prefer to call art.
Oh, you know exactly
what it is, sleazeball...
and my fist is gonna show you!
Oh, crap...! Uh... Hey, wait...!
Uh... I just printed up some
really great shots of Yakumo...
Can I interest you
in buying a set of ten?
You vile brute...!
You would even
dare to sell them...?!
How much are they?!
One hundred.
That's Too much!
I beg to differ.
They're a bargain
at twice the price...
She's in her summer uniform...
So, Mina... You think
Hanai will give in?
Maybe... sure looks like it.
Do you see how your Dojo-mate's
embarrassing himself?
I don't know him!
They're too expensive!
You've won this round... Fuyuki!
If I'm not taking photos,
I'm losing money...!
And with all the hot
babes in action out here,
I could make a real
bundle selling the pictures!
Yeah...! Work it!
Well, at least you
have good taste...
But do you have the talent
to capture a girl's essence
and her style in a perfect shot?
I just got the perfect shot
of you, Ms. Tsukamoto!
Me?! Are you sure?!
But... I'm not what you'd
call a very photogenic person!
A camera doesn't lie and it
sees things that others can't...
So be honest...
You're in love, aren't you?
That's just the look I want...!
You're a natural,
you know that?!
You're perfect...!
If you don't mind me
saying, you're just as
pretty as Mikoto and Akira!
That slimy creep
didn't even notice me!
Huh?
Nice of you to join us.
The booth team's full you
must be on the play team.
Hey, I'm flattered you
think so, but, uh, you see,
I'm really not
much of an athlete.
Don't worry about it
sweety I'll help you out.
I'll get your blood pumpin'!
Think it's clean enough?
Yeah, looks like
the game's over,
so why don't we
go fill the pool?
Sure!
Asou... let me try.
Huh...? Okay,
take your best shot.
Dead end, dirtbag!
Aw... Crap...!
Well, if I'm gonna die,
it might as well be worth it!
Mikoto!
Cushion my fall
with your big boobs!
You are so dead,
ya little twerp!
Get away freak!
Such wondrous booooooobs!
You're so dead!
No, this wasn't our fault...!
It was out of our control!
They're beautiful...
No! I was just trying
to stop him! Wait!
Watch the shades, okay?
We weren't able to reach a
decision today... but Yakumo...
I swear to you that
for the School Festival...
...we will put on
"Sleeping Beauty!"
Hey, remember how
Yakumo's a freshman...? Yeah.
That means that she
can't be in any play put on
by the sophomore class.
Didn't think about
that one, did ya'?
Hey, hey!
There's no reason
to shove, okay!
Get 'em while they're hot, boys!
Photos of the
gorgeous babes from 2-C!
Got any more shots of Mikoto?
Nope. All sold out! Sorry!
How about Eri Sawachika?
Got any of her?
I never had any
to begin with, dude.
G'day, chap! I'm
not from around here...
But how much for this
picture of Tenma Tsukamoto?
Three sets of the Yakumo
Tsukamoto pictures, please!
Yes, sir!
Thanks for the
business, big guy!
Hey, kid, you
don't have anything
to eat for lunch, either?
Don't worry about it,
I'll treat you!
So what do you like better:
curry or meat and potatoes...?
Next time on School Rumble:
"The First Shopping Trip!
The First Packed Lunch!
The First Heartbreak! Huh?!"
Me?!