Sit tight!
That dizzy romantic
comedy "School Rumble"
is about to start!
"I love you."
Just three little words.
But the moment
I say them,
the whole world
changes like magic.
Today, I'm going
to say them to you.
Hey, Sis? We're late!
Yakumo! I'm sorry!
Alright! School starts today!
I can't wait! Ha!
Thanks for waiting for me!
Being late's no way to start!
I know.
My name is Tenma Tsukamoto.
I guess I'm just your average
high school sophomore,
like a zillion other
girls in the world.
And like any young girl,
I've fallen in love!
Maybe the food will
be better this year!
Hey! Karasuma!
It's him! Karasuma!
Ohmigosh!
I can't believe I just
said his name out loud!
Just think, wouldn't it be cool
if you guys ended up
in the same class?
Mhm!
We are gonna end up in
the same class together!
I've prayed for it
every night for six months!
My horoscope said
I was lucky in love!
My tea leaves foretold success!
I found a four leaf clover!
I tripped and
fell down the stairs!
What was that last one?
I'm gonna go check
the class assignments!
Okay, I'll cross
my fingers for you.
Did you see the
ball game last night?
"I love you."
Just three little words.
But the moment I say them, the
whole world changes like magic.
Today, I'm going
to say them to you.
I-I'll get you for this, Harima.
Yeah! Time for the
badass to get the girl.
Let's go to school!
My name's Kenji Harima,
and everyone knows
I'm the baddest
badass in the school.
At least I was until someone
came along and changed my life!
I'm too nervous to look.
Oh, please let
Karasuma be in my class!
Tenma! Hey!
Hey, girls, what's going on?
It's her. Holy crap.
Now hold on, young man!
Button that shirt
up at once or--
I've gotta be in her class!
Huh?
Did you hear the good news?
We're all in class 2-C!
Including you.
Really?
Hurray!
My three best
friends all together!
It's wonderful!
I knew today was
gonna be my lucky day!
But--
Is there something wrong?
Oh, uh, definitely not!
No problem here!
So Tenma is in 2-C, eh?
I know!
I'll use psychic power
to make sure I'm in 2-C!
Just gotta concentrate
for ten seconds.
Ten. 2-C. Nine. 2-C. Eight. 2-C.
Seven. 2-C. Six. 2-C. Five. 2-C.
Four. 2-C. Three. 2-C.
Two. 2-C. One!
D! Just face it, Harima.
I saw you on the D list.
Ugh. What was that for?
That was just a love tap.
That's what happens
when people distract me.
2-D? It can't be!
My psychic power had to work!
Kenji Harimashi?
That's not my name.
You upset my
vibrations for nothing!
You vibe-killer!
Sorry!
I didn't know
you were vibrating!
Well, try to be a little
more sensitive from now on.
You know, like me!
Okay.
Hmph! What's he know!
My name's gotta be there!
Huh?
Dammit!
I can't find my name anywhere!
C'mon!
I gotta be in
one of these rooms!
What the--?
Man, it's like
I don't even exist!
Harima!
Hm?
Why are you checking
the level 2 list?
You were held back,
don't you remember?
Aw, crap.
How'd it go?
Is he in your class?
Can't look.
Would it be easier
if I looked for you?
No!I've got to see this
with my very own eyes!
Oji Karasuma.
We're in the same class! Yes!
Good for you.
Soon we'll be
together, Karasuma!
And our love will kindled!
So you're in 2-C?
But it doesn't matter 'cause I'm
transferring out in two days.
And we were gonna
be in the same class!
Oh, well, life goes on.
The hell it does!
I gotta think.
Maybe cleaning the
house will help me think.
Maybe doing all the
laundry will help me think.
Maybe dishes will help me think?
I couldn't think of anything.
Maybe a good
night's sleep will help.
There's no way I can sleep now!
I can't let him go
without at least trying
to tell him how I feel!
Better to risk doing something
dumb than do nothing
and kick myself
the rest of my life!
Okay! Let's do this!
I'll just write "I love you."
I mean, that should be easy!
Okay, I love y-y-y-y-y--
--your skiing, I hear you're
awesome at the giant slalom.
Agh! What's the matter
with me? What am I saying?
Once more. I love y-y-y-y--
--your skipping.
Okay, Tenma, stay cool,
you can do this.
I love yogurt!
No, no, I love yoga!
I love yurts! I love Yorkies?
I love--
Rats. I can't say it.
Now what am I supposed to do?
Okay, shake it off.
I'll just write down how
I feel, nice and simple.
It turned out to be
kind of a long letter.
Oh, wow.
I did it.
I poured out my heart to him.
He--he's reading it!
And, he's still reading it!
Ah! I think he's
finally finished!
Wait a minute.
Oh my gosh, he's reacting!
I hope this is a good thing.
That's funny, there's no name.
Oh, no!
It's all over. My first love.
It's--it's Karasuma!
But I thought he transferred
to another school!
No, for some reason he decided
to postpone the transfer.
He managed to talk his parents
into letting him finish
out the school year here.
Why would he?
How come?
No one knows for sure but the
rumor is someone asked him to.
Our heroine Tenma Tsukamoto
is hopelessly in love
with Oji Karasuma!
But her hopes are
dashed when she learns
he's about to transfer
to another school!
Desperate to make her feelings
known, she pours out her heart
to him in very long
love letter to no avail!
But in a dramatic
turn of events,
Karasuma
postpones his transfer,
restoring hope to
Tenma's storm-tossed soul!
And now she begins
the real battle,
a battle for true
love in a cruel world!
Great first page!
I hope the whole
book is this good.
Okay, no more stupid mistakes.
I'm gonna find out what the
experts say you should do.
Karasuma, you're so cool.
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid!
Do you love the
guy or not? Focus!
But reading makes my head hurt.
Wait! "Know yourself
as well as your enemy
and a hundred victories
will be yours." Who wrote this?
Sun Tzu? Huh.
I guess it must be some kind
of a secret kung fu love manual.
Know yourself.
What kind of a girl am I?
Tenma Tsukamoto.
Age: 16.
Height: 154 centimeters.
Weight: 43 kilograms.
Looks and figure: average.
Social status: nobody.
Sports poor!
Academics poor!
Cooking sucks!
Good qualities-- zilch.
Get a grip.
Let's see what
else he's got, huh?
Rabbit taking off.
Taking off what?
Can you undo me in the back?
Put it back on!
That can't be the right reading!
Excuse me, what does
this expression mean?
Oh, that--that means
"rabbit running away."
Oh, of course.
Thanks so much for your help.
Sure.
He's right here!
How'd he get there!
That's right.
Rabbit running away.
Great, now he thinks
I'm an illiterate lunatic!
But on the other hand,
he actually talked to me
for the very first time!
Now I know what
to have him read next!
Man, am I an evil
genius or what? Heh, heh.
Ow! My contact!
Uh, could your read
this phrase for me?
Sure thing.
Let me see,
it says "I love you."
Hey are you in high school?
You're really cute.
Maybe if I show him a cane
field, he'll call me sugar!
Karasuma!
What do you get from this?
Let's see.
Come on, come on.
Says it's a thresher.
I showed him the wrong picture!
Well, I guess it's
about time I get going.
See you, Miss Tsukamoto.
Yeah, sure, later, Karasuma!
He knows my name.
It wasn't that long ago
I was a total smart ass
and a hopeless moron.
And I was a god.
Nothing and nobody
could tie me down.
I belonged to no one.
But now I'm tied
by the bonds of love.
I'm in love with
Tenma Tsukamoto.
Hey, what the heck
is Harima doing here?
Oh, man.
He's sitting in my chair.
Do you think he broke
into the faculty room
and forced them to pass him?
Oh please oh please
oh please oh please
oh please oh please oh please!
So far, so good.
I made it into Tenma's class.
Now I gotta figure out a way to
tell her how I feel about her.
What?
"I challenge you to a fight"?
Come on!
Nobody does this
by letter anymore!
Wait! A letter!
I bet chicks like letters!
Ha ha!
Read this!
The greatest love letter
in the history of the world!
I asked her to meet me
behind the gym at 4 o'clock.
Oh, Tenma.
Did you read my letter?
I love you, darling.
You're the only man
in the world for me.
Almost four o'clock!
It's her! She came!
What the hell?
Oh crap! I forgot the challenge!
Set for same time and place,
what are the chances?
I can't believe this!
I can't go out there now
and let Tenma see
me fighting that gorilla!
Come on. Where is that creep?
I'm gonna miss my four-thirty.
I beg your pardon, miss.
Huh?
Sorry, but what's a
nice girl like you doing
in a place like this?
Uh, meeting someone.
That slimeball!
He's talking to her!
I'll kill him!
Ah! A letter?
Well, yes, it--
Do you mind if I--?
Hey! Gimme that!
Bastard!
Well, well, it's a love poem.
Isn't that special?
Wait a minute!
"Oh, Thank You.
An Epic Poem of Gratitude."
Oh how sweet.
Oh, thank you to the heavens
for sending you to earth.
Oh, thank you to your parents,
twas they who gave you birth.
Damn, girl,
that's just pathetic!
I swear Tennoji,
I'll end you for this!
Is this a joke?
Too bad he didn't sign it!
I think you're wrong.
Huh?
I know I'm not very smart,
but I think whoever
wrote this was very brave
to say what he
felt in his heart.
It's a beautiful,
sensitive, wonderful letter.
And I just adore it!
I'm the luckiest
guy in the world
to have fallen in love
with a girl like Tenma!
That's great, 'cause
I wrote the letter!
I love you!
What? And he called me pathetic?
Thank you, that's very sweet,
but I'm in love
with somebody else.
There, there.
These things happen to everyone.
Except me!
That's for laughing
at my masterpiece!
If there's one thing
I hate, it's criticism!
I've got to think of some way
I can spend more
time with Karasuma.
There must be something I can do
to get his attention
outside of school,
I just gotta concentrate.
Oh pretty!
If I could just find a
way to spend more time
with her, she would notice me.
I've gotta find more time.
Ah! Of course!
Riding a bicycle!
Why, good morning, Karasuma!
Good morning, Miss Tsukamoto!
Another splendid day, isn't it?
Indeed!
We could bike to
school together every day!
Ah, Tenma!
Good morning, Harima!
Lovely weather
we're having, isn't it?
Almost as lovely as you.
We could bike to
school together every day!
Sheer genius!
Tenma sure has been
acting weird lately.
I wonder what's up.
It's because they wound
up in class together.
Huh?
Don't worry about it.
You'll figure it out.
Morning, girls.
Hey! Morning, Yakumo!
So where's Tenma?
She's uh-- she's biking
to school from now on.
Here we go.
Uh, with what?
This is gonna be great!
So where is he?
Yes! Now for a casual
yet friendly greeting.
Good morning!
What a coin--
Whoa!
Has he got a freakin' jet
engine on that thing or what?
Hey, Karasuma! Wait up!
Soon I'll be riding with Tenma.
Whoa! Here she comes!
Tenma, what a coincidence!
Hey, lovely weather
we're having, isn't it?
Huh? Wait up!
What's the deal?
Is she training for
the Tour de France?
She's going way too fast!
Hey, come back!
Tenma!
Hey, slow down, will ya?
Wait for me, Tenma!
Look at him, even
on a bike he's so cool
and composed,
he's just adorable.
Huh? How does he do that?
Well, he's not gonna get
rid of me that easily! Charge!
Whoa. She's fast,
but if I can outrun the cops,
I can catch up to her.
They don't call me
"legs of steel" for nothing!
Let's kick it into overdrive!
Wait up, Karasuma!
Tenma! Wait up!
There's nothing like
having a good hair day
to make a girl feel beautiful.
Good morning.
Morning! Huh?
Amazing! He went up that
hill like it wasn't even there!
Huh?
Tenma?
My--my hair. It's ruined!
What is going on?
Whoa, Eri! Bad hair day?
Oh, yeah, you could say that!
You'll never guess
what happened!
Karasuma came by
on a bike and Tenma
was following right after him.
What does that mean?
Gee, whaddaya think?
Now I get it!
Huh? Get what? Get what?
But wait, I'm pretty
sure I saw a third person
chasing right after them.
Hey!
You don't think Tenma has
a thing for Karasuma, do you?
When you're as dumb as they are,
the last thing you need is
to fall asleep during class.
Miss Tsukamoto,
here's your eraser.
Thank you.
Gosh. That's too bad.
She just missed out on
a really good chance there.
This doesn't bode well for the
rest of the school year, huh?
I love you, Karasuma.
Oh, man!
Tomorrow's our school physical!
I don't wanna get weighed!
But I do wanna
know Karasuma's stats!
I just have to find out!
Next time on School Rumble:
"Tough Test!
Trapped in the Bathroom!
The School Physical!"
Uh, do I look fat to you?