School Rumble's coming up next!
If you know what's good
for ya, you won't miss it!
For your viewing pleasure,
three special shorts!
Short Number One:
It's Hard On Younger Sister.
Mm! Smells good, huh?!
Our noodle soup uses tofu
made from natural soybeans...
Wow! That soup really looks
yummy, doesn't it, Yakumo?
I'm home!
Oh, hey there, Sis...
I hope you're hungry.
For dinner tonight, I made
a big bowl of noodle soup.
How weird...! But how'd
you know that's exactly
what I wanted tonight?
Yakumo didn't have the
heart to tell her it was
because of the
TV commercial they'd seen.
Short Number Two: It's
Also Hard On Older Sister.
Uh, Sis? What are
you looking for?
My old water imp.
But I'm not having
any luck finding it.
Wait, did you say... water imp?
Yeah, silly!
What'd you think I said?
I want to give it to
Karasuma as a surprise gift!
Oh, I see...
Here it is,
in all its dusty glory!
Wow, it really is old, isn't it?
It says here it's the
mummy of a real water imp.
Short Number Three:
Tenma's Hair Secret.
Like all girls her age,
Tenma takes the time
to fix her hair each
and every morning.
But to keep track
of her daily schedule,
she makes subtle
changes to her hair.
Oh... morning, Tenma-
Morning!
Nine... o'clock?
That's right...!
There's a program on tonight at
nine that I don't wanna miss...
This way I won't forget it!
Okay, line up people!
Good!
Alright...! You're all in
for a very special treat today!
I made box lunches for everyone!
Miss Takano...
Thanks, Hanai.
Miss Sawachika...
Thank you!
Miss Tsukamoto...
Cool!
Miss Suou...
Oh, thank you.
Imadori, Nara, enjoy!
Okay.
Alright! Sweet!
One more...!
This particular dish was
made with extra special care,
and Yakumo Tsukamoto,
this is... for you! Huh?
This is so good!
Talk about tasty!
I'll say...!
I never knew Hanai was
such a good cook, did you?
Yeah, he is...!
And I'm sure he's gonna
have a great time even
if Yakumo didn't get
to come... Right, Hanai?
I forgot to pack my own lunch...
Harima, give that back!
No way! I didn't have any
breakfast this morning!
Gimme...! Gimme!
Does he have to be so pathetic?
Hey! Looks good!
The rooms are separated
by sliding doors.
So... there's no locks?
We're gonna change.
So that door better
stay shut, got it?!
Miko... don't worry.
It'll stay shut, I promise.
Well, men?
What say we change, too?
No prob! I've got
my trunks on under my jeans.
What are you doing...?
You promised you wouldn't!
There are naked
girls next door...
Can you blame me?
What do you think
you're doing, you pervert?!
Wow, your swimsuit
looks totally hot, Akira!
What about mine?
Pretty daring, huh?
Mikoto's suit makes
her boobs look even bigger!
Your suit's pretty
cute, too, Tenma.
Thanks! It's a different
color than Yakumo's.
My dearest Yakumo?!
For the sake of Yakumo,
I will not allow any
untoward behavior!
The beach!
There's so many people!
Tenma, she's so cute...
Crap! Missed a
peek at the goods!
Oh, dearest Yakumo!
Why! Why couldn't
you have come today?!
Tenma, can I use your sunscreen?
Oh, I forgot to
bring any. Sorry.
I've got some
right here...! Hey!
I'll get my own.
Hey, where's Harima?
Guess he's still in the room.
It figures.
That guy's always
been a loner. A rebel.
Could have sworn I took
it out of my beach bag...
The rugged spirit of the ocean
is calling to my wild side...
Just wait for me, Tenma!
Alright... I've done
enough fooling around.
'Bout time I hit the beach...
Now where are those trunks at?
Swimming trunks...
oh, swimming trunks?
Could have sworn I put
those things in here... Huh?
No!
Don't scream...!
I didn't do anything wrong!
She's the one who
walked in on me...!
If she screams, everyone's
gonna come running in
and think I'm a pervert!
Even Tenma! Oh, crap!
What am I gonna do?!
Great...! So now what?!
I didn't mean for things
to turn out like this!
Geez, I'm a real moron!
This chick squirming around
isn't making things any easier!
Better just explain it to her,
let her know this is all
just a big mistake...!
I better quiet her down first...
But how do I do that... Got it!
You keep quiet.
What was I thinking?!
Yeah, I can shut her up by being
as creepy as possible! God!!
Somebody's here!
Now I'm a goner!
Wait, don't tell me.
You took off your clothes
and went to find
your swimming trunks.
You looked all over,
couldn't find them,
and then Eri walked in.
You tried to explain
yourself, she got scared,
and your infinite wisdom
led us to where we are now.
Don't worry, Harima.
I don't think you're a pervert,
but you are a total screw-up.
What's wrong? Did you
ever find your sunscreen?
I never got the chance to look.
Why not? Did something happen?
I don't want to
talk about it, okay?
Let's cut the watermelon
open and eat it!
Miko! It's watermelon time!
Miko...! Miko...!
Mikoto's drowning!
Somebody, help...! Hanai!
Do Kenpo or something! Save her!
You thought you could
learn to swim quicker
in deep water...? Gimme a break!
Man, back off.
Hanai... you were just
like a lifeguard out there!
Oh, thanks...
Of course, I'm used
to saving her life.
Oh! Would you
just shut up already?!
That's uncalled for...
Now relax and enjoy your coffee.
Yeah, whatever...
Wow, I wish
I could swim like you...
You're really good...
None of us girls
know how to swim...
Isn't that right, Eri?
Just be quiet.
Gentlewomen!
Today, your fondest
wishes shall be granted...!
I want to see everyone
put their best foot forward...!
Let the swimming lessons begin!
Dammit, Tenma!
Look what you did now!
Come on... It'll be fun.
Let's let him teach us.
I know you'd make a
good teacher, too, Nara.
Me...? A teacher?
Very well, then!
We men shall be the teachers!
Finally, something
to get excited about!
Without Yakumo here,
I was beginning
to feel like this trip
would be a waste of my time!
Hey...! If I teach
her that gives me
an excuse to talk
to her...! And get close!
I've gotta be the one
that teaches Tenma,
so I better straighten
out those other guys!
Yo, Imadori!
I noticed you seem to
like the flashy ladies.
So you should teach
the flashy, rich chick, okay?
Sure!
Listen, Hanai, you seem to
be good friends with Mikoto,
so it would make sense
for you two to partner up.
Uh?
Yo... uh,um...
Nara...
Yeah, whatever.
Anyway, you don't
really stand out,
so you get to teach
that quiet girl, okay?
Huh?
Just draw up a chart.
It'll make it easier.
Who, me?
No, your mother.
Here, I'll do it.
Eri here,
Mikoto there, you here,
Tenma there,
and me... right here...
Hey, guys...! Time to assign
our swimming partners!
Great!
Oh, Tenma!
Right...! Now get with your
partners and begin the lessons!
Well... Let's go, Mikoto
Just don't let me sink, okay?
I don't believe it.
Harima's even
dumber than he looks.
Screwed up by one lousy line...
Wanna swim?
Thanks, I'd rather drown.
Uh... Hey...
Guess it's about time we started
those swimming lessons,
don't ya think...?
Ha, okay...
Awkward...
Okay, just give me your hand...
Huh?
Your hand...
Your hand...? Your... hand...?
Just like that, see?
Take strong and even strokes...
Show me again.
I'm gonna build you the biggest
sand castle on the beach!
We're far enough already...!
Stop...! Imadori!
Aw, come on!
You're not gonna wuss
out on me now, are ya?
I'm ready to learn...!
'Kay, Nara?
I promise I'll do
my best, Tenma.
This is your chance
to get close to her, man!
Don't screw it up!
Well, let's get started then.
Uh... Y-yeah!
Wow, it's so soft and cushiony.
You like the view down there?
Listen... I'm warning you...
Don't get any ideas... 'Kay...?
You might be
Tenma's teacher today...
but that doesn't make
you her boyfriend,
so don't get your hopes up, and
keep your filthy mitts off her!
Y-Yeah, uh, sure. Gotcha.
But I want to be more
then Tenma's teacher...
Maybe once we get out in
the water, he won't see us...
That's it!
Let her go and she's got nowhere
to swim but into your arms!
Hey... I'm gonna let go of you
for a little while, okay, Tenma?
Uh... sure... That's alright.
Hey...! What the...
Where are you going?!
Wait! Stop! Come back!
That's far enough!
I did it!
I'm like a freakin' mermaid, and
it's all because of you, Nara!
Ha-ha, yeah...
Hey...! You guys coming?!
I doubt it.
Hanai wore himself out.
Hey, twerp...!
Quit staring, unless you want
me to squash you into fish food.
Right... Sorry
Aw, man...! What am I gonna do?!
Harima's watching
me like a hawk.
He could seriously kick my butt
and do it in front of Tenma.
So much for
getting close to her.
Guess I'll just... watch.
Somebody please help!
Lost swimsuit!
Wha...?!
It's gonna be okay,
Tenma! Did it come off?
Harima's gonna beat
the crap out of me.
But if I don't do this,
what kind of a man am I?
I love you, Tenma Tsukamoto!
Where's it at?
Tenma's swimsuit... Oh!
Hope you realize
I'm doing this for one reason...
It's for you!
Nara...
Here... Take it.
Thank you, Nara...
Huh?
Boy! You're a klutz, Harima...!
Aren't you lucky Nara
was so close to me
and able to find your trunks?!
Isn't he the greatest!
Where are we?
Oh, no! We're marooned!
Geez! I told you
we were going out too far.
But you wouldn't listen.
We're never gonna
get home, are we?!
Quit crying, you pansy!
I'm trying to think!
We can see the shore.
Think anyone can see us?
No! It's further than it looks!
No one can see us
all the way out here!
Besides, we'll starve to
death before anybody finds us!
This is no time to panic.
Then again, if we don't
find a way off this rock,
who knows what might happen...
Oh, please don't say that!
C'mon, I don't
wanna die here, babe!
I don't wanna die,
either, moron...!
Oh, and being stranded
doesn't give you the right
to call me "babe," got it...?!
Wait a second...!
You can swim, right...?!
Then why don't you just swim
to the shore and get help?!
I'm... sorry, I can't!
Why not...? Is the current
too strong or something?
No...
Then...?
Let's just say I'm really
allergic to shark bites.
Oh my god!
Your wuss factor just
shot up, like, twenty points!
Hey, don't be so harsh.
Sharks can be a real threat!
I think someone's been watching
a little too much
animal discovery.
There's no point in arguing...
If we're getting out of here,
we've gotta think
of a way to get the attention
of the people on the shore.
Hey, good idea.
Thinking's what I do best,
so just leave it to me.
That might work...
Yep, that'll do it...
A signal fire.
We don't have any matches...
or anything to burn.
We'll burn our swimsuits!
And whose were you
planning to burn first?
Well, yours does have
one more piece than mine...
Maybe there's something in this
cave that could help us out...
Let's split up and
take a look around.
Okay!
Stranded in the
middle of nowhere...
Just me and "Captain Perv-o."
Mikoto...! Hey!
Look what I found!
Uh, okay?
It's a jar!
Yeah, I know what it is...
but how does it help us?
You know...! We'll do like
they do in the old movies...!
We'll put a message in it and
send it away for help, you see?!
That'll take years, you idiot!
Speaking of that message,
we don't have a pencil,
so I guess we'll have
to write it in blood.
Forget the stupid
message...! Drop it...!
We don't have time
to keep goofing off!
Let's get serious!
Hey, I am totally being serious!
We... need a plan.
Plan A...! Build a raft...
but, we don't have any rope...
Plan B...! Swim like
mad towards the shore...
but I can't really swim,
so I wouldn't get very far...
Plan C...! Human SOS...
but we're short one human...
Plan D...! Ride on
the back of that idiot!
Out of all those plans,
D's the only one that
might be feasible...
but it would put Imadori in some
danger, and I don't want that...
What else can we do?
I'm all out of ideas.
Is Imadori actually thinking
with his mind for a change?!
So, any luck...?
Have you been able to come up
with any good ideas, for us...?
I think I've got four
possibilities that might work:
Plans A, B, C, and D.
D.
What...?!
Did he actually think of
the same plans as me,
and come to the
same conclusion?!
Can he read minds
or something...?!
Even if he can't, he did
pick the most dangerous one.
Not so much of
a pansy after all.
Gotta admit... I'm impressed.
It's gotta be D...
I always get boob sizes right.
You're a D-cup for sure...! What
can I say, babe, it's a gift--
Will you be serious for once?!
Man, Mikoto is so hot.
Wonder what the best way
is to let her know I'd swim
for the shore in exchange
for a little smooch?
I wonder if I'm even her type...
Hey? What are you looking at?
Uh, so tell me.
Are there any
guys that you like?
Well, yeah... sort of...
Guess I better
forget the smooch.
Bet she's the faithful type.
So... this guy of yours...
Do I know him?
No, he's... he's a few
years older than me...
When I was a freshman...
he was a junior...
He graduated early
and now he's attending
a university in the city.
He's the brightest guy I know...
I really want to get
into the same college,
but I hear the entrance
exams are pretty tough!
Ah... there's still hope.
Long distance
relationships never last.
Hey!
Why are you asking
me about this?!
Got my reasons...
That reminds me...
If I would have stayed
home and studied,
I wouldn't be in this
stupid mess right now!
Sorry, was just trying to get
your mind off the situation...
Guess we really
should figure out
how we're gonna get ourselves
out of this mess, huh?
S'okay...
Hey, wait...
How could we forget?!
All of our friends
are back on the beach!
They'll notice we're gone
and send out a
search party, for sure!
Hey, guys, before
we go back to the room,
let's get in a picture together!
Oh! A group shot. Splendid idea.
I'll take it.
Come on, everybody, let's go!
Over here!
Okay, guys...
So, what do mice like?
Hey, wait!
What's wrong, Tenma?
I don't know,
but I have a weird feeling
we're forgetting something.
Big smiles!
Ready when you are,
Akira...! Yeah!
Cheese!
Search party, huh?
Mikoto!
Where have you and Imadori
been all this time, huh...?
Uh oh, Harima's in
a really bad mood!
Could Mikoto be the girl
that Harima's in love with?!
Is she the one...?!
Next time on School Rumble:
Find out all these
answers and more!