Sit tight!
That dizzy romantic
comedy "School Rumble"
is about to start!
So, Harima, now we'll
settle this once and for all.
Let's get him!
Even in the worst situations.
When a man's in love.
He can't afford
to lose his pride.
You bastard!
Bring it on, losers.
You can't beat me
because I'm in love.
And it's all for you, Tenma
Harima comes to school
every day now, doesn't he?
Maybe he's planning
some sort of bomb threat.
Tenma!
You took off without your lunch.
Oh! Silly me. Thanks, Sis!
Listen.
Hm?
Are you okay sitting there?
Is it safe?
Say what?
He's got kind of a weird vibe.
Huh?
Harima!
Look! Your desk
is crushing your bag!
You poor helpless little bag!
Everything I do is for you.
I never gave a
damn about school.
I came and went as I pleased.
But you turned it into a
paradise I can't live without!
Pretty hysterical.
The toughest punk in town,
and I show up on time,
every day, stay all day and
then stick around for clean up!
What a joke! On me! You get it?
Okay, that's just weird.
Yep. No doubt about it.
He's planning something evil.
Right, time to check out the old
language skills with a pop quiz!
Just fill in the blanks, people!
Okay. And start!
Too many letters. Brain hurting.
School is hard.
Oh, well. It's worth
it to be near Tenma.
I should just enjoy
this moment of bliss.
But wait! Her name!
She forgot to write in her name!
Is she crazy?
If she forgets to
write her name in,
she'll get an automatic zero!
If she gets an
automatic zero she'll fail!
Oh my god!
She's gonna fail!
Tenma's gonna fail!
Ten--!
I can't warn her out loud!
We're in the middle of a test!
What should I do?
Think Harima think.
Time to be a hero
and save the girl.
I've got it! I'll try
mouthing the words!
Aw crap! That didn't work!
This is tougher than
I thought. Okay then.
Dammit.
So far I'm dead in the water.
Come on, Harima, you gotta
come up with a better idea!
There's gotta be
another way to warn her!
Heroes always have a plan B.
Oh, well. I hate
to be so obvious,
but I guess I'll have
to take the direct route.
Holy crap!
I completely forgot
to write my name!
Even if I'd managed
to get every answer correct,
I would've failed!
Better be more careful, Harima!
Everyone's laughing at me.
Still, anything for Tenma!
She's laughing at me, too?
But I was talking about her!
Hasn't she ever
heard of learning
from other people's mistakes?
And why does she
have to be so cute?
Oh dear!
Screw you.
Sorry.
I can't give up yet.
There! It's perfect!
Wow, I got the answer to
number seven, the last question.
Man, this test is so easy,
I can't believe it!
Here we go!
Did she get it?
No, no, no!
How does this happen?
This girl is just too stupid!
And I know stupid!
Dammit!
What haven't I tried?
Amazing.
Harima really seems to be
concentrating on this test!
It's like he's actually
trying or something!
Hold on!
What if I wrote Tenma's
name on my paper,
so that her no-name paper
would be mistaken for mine?
Yes.
What's this?
Sir, this paper
has my name on it
but this isn't my handwriting!
What?
Strange.
Huh?
Harima turned in
a paper with no name.
Did Harima do
this to protect me?
What a sweetie!
It was you, wasn't it?
I just can't turn my back
on someone who needs help.
Oh, Harima.
I love you!
Ditto.
What's up with him?
It'll work!
Tenma, I'm doing this for the
sake of our future happiness!
Here are your test
papers from yesterday.
Tenma, I'm afraid
you got a zero.
What the--?
I'm sorry, Tenma!
I'm so sorry! Please forgive me.
I'm just so stupid!
What do you think?
Shall we hit the
coffee shop, or the mall?
I don't care.
Uh! I can't.
There's a sale at
the supermarket today
and I have to go.
I gotta do the dinner shopping.
Let's see,
what sounds good tonight?
Whoa!
Are trying to tell me that you
do the cooking at your house?
Come on!
Huh? Yeah, well that is I--
I thought Yakumo
did all the cooking.
You're right, she does.
I knew it!
I always thought Tenma
looked like the spoiled one.
What? Really?
Karasuma!
Wait, why did I hide
from him just now?
I guess I was embarrassed
to let the boy I love
see me coming out
of the girls' bathroom!
Oh, great!
Now that I've thought
of it, I can't go out!
I'm such a moron!
It's just the girls'
bathroom but I pee in here!
What'll I do?
Okay, I really
need to get out now.
Still there.
Come on!
Why is he being such an idiot?
Why would anyone
stand around talking for
so long in front of
the girls' bathroom?
But that's why I love the guy!
Ah! No!
This is no time to
be blinded by love!
Still at it.
Okay, now it's a
matter of endurance!
I'll show him what a
woman's will power can do!
Love isn't for wimps!
I'm being tested!
No problem! I can handle it!
Besides, he can't talk longer
than ten minutes! Heh, heh!
It oughta be safe by now.
Oh, man, is it ever good
to see daylight again!
I don't believe it,
he's reading a novel?
Plan number two!
Where the heck did she go?
Hey, Tenma? You still in here?
Okay, it doesn't matter, just as
long as he doesn't recognize me.
What are you doing now?
Ha! You're just in time!
Quick, who am I?
Uh.
Yeah, Tenma?
I'll be going home now.
Huh? Hang on!
How'd you know it was me?
Wow, little too much for me.
Plan number three!
I'll use this to
distract Karasuma
and then make my escape!
One. Two.
Go!
Okay, who's the wise guy?
Huh? You gotta lotta nerve,
sneaking up on me!
Who did it? Was it you?
Was it? Spit it out!
Come on, if I have to,
I can destroy all of you!
Sorry about that, Harima!
I'll apologize to him later.
There's nothing left I can
use and I'm all out of plans!
I'm gonna spend the rest of
my life in the girls' bathroom!
Huh? It's stuck!
Wait a sec.
Ready on the left!
Ready on the right!
All systems go!
30 meters, slow descent, begin!
I'm not giving up!
There's no way.
I'm gonna let Karasuma see me
leaving the girls' bathroom!
It's a matter of pride!
I finally made it at last!
You okay?
Yeah, fine. Huh?
Well, just be careful.
You're lucky
you didn't get hurt.
Come on, Sis.
I told you before, I'm not mad
at you for missing the sale
at the supermarket today, okay?
No! No!
That's not the problem!
Oh, please. I beg you!
I hope you'll be kind.
I haven't done this
for a long time.
Sis?
Is there somebody
in there with you?
No, no, no, it's nothing.
I mean nobody.
I was just talking to--
To what?
You mean you were
talking to the scale?
Oh right.
The school physical's tomorrow!
How can you be so calm?
You're lucky you're so skinny!
Life is hard for us
full-figured girls!
Now get out! I wanna be alone!
You fiend!
Do your worst!
You shall never beat me!
I don't wanna be unsympathetic,
but I don't think
you can blame the scale.
Okay, girl, do it!
I hope we can be friends.
It's a nightmare.
I've got to wake up, that's all.
Get off the floor
before you catch cold.
I skipped breakfast today!
I haven't eaten for three days!
I think I dropped a dress size!
You're gonna collapse!
After the weigh-in,
I'll stuff myself!
All that for only
one dress size!
It just isn't fair!
Okay, let me guess!
The look on your face
says you've gained weight.
Am I right?
Score one!
Oh, just ignore her.
You weigh about the
same as me, don't you?
So don't even worry about it!
Thank you!
On the other hand,
she's got a much
bigger bust than you do.
Let's see.
A. No, no, B, definitely.
And this one. A, I think.
Imadori!
Hey.
Are you trying to
guess blood types?
Bra sizes my friend!
Yeah, I can tell at a glance.
It's a gift.
I don't even need to measure,
though I could if I wanted to.
Smile for me!
That's it, baby,
give me more of that!
Ah, that's the ticket!
Work it, girl, work it!
The camera loves you!
Okay, I know I probably
shouldn't ask this,
but what are you doing?
I'm taking early graduation
pictures, of course,
what does it look like?
And I guess you don't think
that's asking for trouble?
Fuyuki!
I'd like to order a
complete set, please!
Are you guys nuts?
You're just begging for it!
Hey!
Gimme that!
Give it back, Hanai!
That's my dad's camera!
Sorry, but as
class rep, it's my duty
to confiscate camera equipment
used for immoral purposes!
You cannot deny
the awesome power
of their chocolate brownie!
I'm not arguing.
I'm just saying I like
their truffles better.
Word, yo.
Which makes it
two to one. I win.
Karasuma's gonna have his height
and weight measured today, too.
I wonder.
He must be about
a hundred seventy one.
No! A hundred
seventy two centimeters.
Weight. He looks light.
Limber, too. Hmph!
I'm no good at
guessing a boy's weight!
Oh no! Now I've done it!
I can't stand it!
It's gonna drive me crazy!
I gotta know! I gotta
know everything about him!
I gotta know his height,
weight, shoe size,
collar, sleeve length,
waist, hips, inseam,
glove size, hat size, chest!
His chest.
It's probably bigger than mine.
Hey, is it just me or
has anybody else noticed
that the boys are a little
more out of control than usual?
Oh, they're just getting
all hot and bothered
thinking about
today's physical exam!
I'm sorry!
Please forgive me!
Sure thing, what are
we forgiving you for?
You know, Tenma,
no one else has a knack
for killing a conversation
quite like you do.
Come on, Eri, you gotta
be used to it by now.
Enjoy the drama.
Yeah, so back to the boys.
Isn't it pathetic the
way they're wrapped up
in their lewd little fantasies?
I mean, if they're
that desperate
to satisfy their curiosity,
then they should
just become doctors!
Wow, so much for being PC!
That's right. Boys can
be doctors or nurses.
Oh, come on, you two,
it was just a "for instance",
I wasn't making
a political statement!
Become a doctor or a nurse?
Yes! I'll become a nurse!
Maybe I'm overreacting,
but doesn't that strike you as
an abrupt career decision?
Yeah, well, consider the source.
Oh, gosh, I think she's
really serious this time.
No, no, I'm not talking
about my future job!
Huh?
You sure about that?
I'll see you all later,
girls. So long!
Oh, man, I thought
she was serious.
Don't relax, I sense
a zany plan coming on.
There's just no
telling with her.
There! Talk about
the perfect disguise!
That idiot! Her hair
is a dead giveaway!
At least she didn't put
on a nose and glasses!
I don't get it.
What can she possibly be after?
This is kinda fun.
I don't think I've had to wear a
name tag since grade school!
You have to give her credit,
she can have fun doing anything.
I'll bet you ten to
one she's filling out
that card with her own name!
Gosh, what do you
think we should do?
Nothing, of course!
Huh?
Come on, don't you wanna
watch and see what happens next?
I agree, it's probably better
if we don't
interfere at this point.
So far, so good.
Soon, Oji Karasuma's
vital statistics--
--will be all mine!
Sorry if I kept you waiting!
I'm looking forward to
working with you, doctor!
No problem, I was
running late myself.
I'm subbing for
the regular doctor.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm young Doctor Harima.
Nice to meet you.
Attention please, students.
The physical
examinations scheduled
for today have been cancelled.
Once again.
The physical examinations
scheduled for today
have been cancelled.
They will be re-scheduled
at a later time.
Oh, it's so hard
to say I love you!
It's easier to bend
spoons with your mind! I know!
I'll have a sleepover
and invite my friends
to share stories about
their love troubles!
Next time on School Rumble:
"See and Sketch!
Letter on an Arrow!
Pajama Party Confessions!"
Mikoto, your breasts are so big!