Coming up after this,
it's School Rumble.
Today, we'll be learning how to
sketch each other's portraits.
Now, I want you to look
at your partner closely
and draw him, or her,
as well as you possibly can.
Damn, now why'd I have
to get stuck with you girls?
Thanks, appreciate that.
I guess we're the left-overs.
Hey, at least there's
no pressure this way.
I suppose, but
wouldn't you rather
be drawing a cute
guy or something?
Wow, this part of your
face is shaped really weird.
Uh. What are you talking about?
Which part?
Ha ha! Just kidding!
There. It's finished.
Hey, how's this for a cute guy?
You're supposed to draw me!
I can't believe this!
I have to sketch Karasuma!
H-Hi! Let's do our best!
Of course.
Good luck.
What is she doing?
Karasuma's gonna have
a hard time sketching her
if she keeps her face
covered up like that.
I can't!
If I have to keep staring
into his eyes, I'm gonna--
I'm gonna--
And she freaked.
What's the deal with her?
Heh, Karasuma shouldn't have
any trouble sketching her now!
Karasuma is looking at me.
Look! Look at me!
Look at me with all your heart!
Please look until
your heart's content!
I want you to look
at me forever and ever!
I can't believe it!
I woke up late this morning
and forgot to brush my hair!
Uh, Karasuma, please excuse me,
I uh-- I have to
go to the, uhhh--
Sure. Go ahead.
Oh, I knew it!
My head looks
like a tornado hit it!
Yakumo, why didn't
you wake me up!
Uh, I'm sorry to
keep you waiting.
Don't worry.
It's bad for you
to try and hold it in.
You've got it all wrong
Karasuma, you dummy!
That's not it at all!
That's not why I went!
Don't you understand anything?
I did it all for you! I'd do
anything for you! That's why!
No, that's not true.
Really I'm being selfish.
It's just-- I wanted you
to think I was beautiful!
That's why.
No, I need to stop
thinking about it!
Just act normal. Focus.
Oh my gosh!
When I tried to
draw him our eyes met!
I'm too nervous!
I can't do this!
I'm a wreck! What am I gonna do?
Oh! I know!
I'll try and look
really innocent,'
so he can't tell
what I'm thinking!
What's with that face?
It's really creepy.
Yeah. What's she on?
There, I'm finished!
This is terrible!
I just can't do this.
I'm too embarrassed!
You okay, Tenma?
Oh, Ms. Sasakura.
Don't worry about drawing
Karasama perfectly.
Try to draw him
from inside your heart.
The way you feel him.
Draw Karasuma the way
I see him inside my heart?
Of course! He's burned
into my memory.
I'll just close my eyes.
And draw him from my heart.
I see him perfectly!
Why did she close her eyes?
She's drawing from the heart.
Kay!
Everyone, it's time to
turn in what you have so far.
Yes, ma'am.
Tenma, how do you think
your drawing turned out?
Um, okay. I think.
Can we see it?
Unbelievable.
Amazing!
Nicely done!
Well, why are you guys
acting so surprised?
'Cause this is unusual for you.
But why does he
look like he's so mad?
Oh my gosh! No way!
Hey Eri, coming to lunch?
Karasuma, I'd love to see
how I look in your eyes!
I-- I wonder if I
look cute in his picture?
If I do then that
means he really likes me!
Well, that could be
wishful thinking on my part,
but still I can hope!
Oh, I want to see.
I have to see! Oh.
Just a quick peek!
I'm ugly!
Now a word from our sponsor.
Would you like to keep
yourself looking younger?
Start early with...
What should I do?
I need to get
Karasuma's attention!
If only I could come up
with a special way
to tell him how I feel!
Sleepy?
Do I look sleepy?
Isn't it ovbious I'm
in unbearable pain here?
Sorry.
I wanted to tell you that you're
favorite show's about to start.
Huh? It's on already?
What are these guys doing here?
I thought I told you.
No talking!
Too eager.
All right! You go boy!
Kick his butt,
Mangoku! Yeah! Wah!
A letter?
That's it!
Uh Tenma? What are
you so excited about?
It's my secret!
You didn't care
about my worries,
so I'm not gonna tell you!
Coming up next on "It's Your
Life", a beautiful reunion!
Listen, Sis?
Not that I really understand
what it is you're trying to do,
but are you sure
that's necessary?
I sense it!
Something is about
to change, I know it!
It's definite. Today my
love won't go unanswered.
What in the world
are you talking about?
Just wait and see, you'll
think I'm so brilliant!
Well, if you say so.
I'm off!
I'm a little worried.
I need some coffee!
Man like me's gotta
keep on his toes!
Hey you punks!
Don't forget the party tonight!
I--
I got--I got my coffee.
Boss!
Hey! Boss!
The only way to send
a love letter filled
with true passion is
to shoot it by arrow!
Thank you!
Dekedennn. Deke deke den.
What the--? What the hell?
What the hell was that?
Try again.
My last resort!
Trick shot!
I'll-- I'll get him this time!
Ah! Karasuma went into the bank!
He's stopped moving!
This is my chance!
Karasuma. Get ready!
Now I've got you!
A daring and
courageous young woman
thwarted a bank robbery with no
less than a bow and arrow today.
Incredible.
That's not what was
supposed to happen!
Why is it so hard
to tell him how I feel?
to tell her how I feel?
What's up?
You look spaced out.
What if she's talking about me?
That's right.
When you have a problem,
the ones you can
always count on for
advice are your girlfriends!
A slumber party? Sounds fun!
Hey! That tickles!
Tenma stop it!
Talk about overdoing it.
Now that's what I call a bath!
That felt great! I haven't
laughed so hard in ages!
I'm thirsty.
Surprise, surprise!
Here's some iced tea!
Cheers!
Ah, I needed that!
Wow, this iced
tea is simply delish!
Who says delish?
Excuse me. I've made
you some snacks.
Aww, Yakumo,
you're the greatest!
We're so hungry!
Thank you!
Oh no. Thank you for taking
such good care of my sister.
Please help yourselves.
Geez, I know I always say this,
but I wish I had a
little sister like her.
Damn, Tenma can eat.
Let's dig in!
This is nice!
I'm glad it's just us girls!
I agree, it's great to get away
from the guys
every once in a while.
Once in a while?
You spend that much time
around guys? I had no idea.
I know, especially
that fried stuff.
The tofu?
Ya! That was it!
Ya, that tofu, that was--
I should get the
recipe so I can have
my chef make it for me sometime.
Chef? Oh, that's right,
she's from a rich family.
I'll bet that makes her
really popular with the guys.
Yeah, I wonder what kind of
vinegar she used to pickle them.
Maybe I'll just
ask her nonchalantly...
Umm, Eri. Ahem.
She puts her heart and
soul into everything she makes.
Yeah, totally.
Ahem!
Um. By the way.
Um, Mikoto,
is there a boy you like?
What? Where the heck
did that come from?
You are so weird.
Oh, come on.
Huh?
You're not trying very
hard to deny it, Mikoto,
so there must be a
little something to it, huh?
Huh? What do you mean?
Stop being so modest.
Three hopeless boys confessed
their love to you this year
and you turned all
of them down flat.
What? Who told you about that?
That is absolutely
none of your business!
But that's nothing compared
to the five boys
that want to date me!
Five?
Those two are so gullible.
Well Yakumo has eight!
So, if it's ok, I'd like to
ask you a question about that.
Um, if you were in love,
how would you tell
that person how you feel?
No no! It's not for me!
See-- ha ha! No!
It's for my friend's friend! Ha!
See, she's madly
in love with this guy,
and um, she has no
clue how to tell him!
So, I thought I'd ask you girls
and see if you had any
advice I could give her.
See, um, she's
in a real dilemma,
and I just thought
I could help her out.
She's so obvious.
Tell me about it.
I've never been
in that situation,
so I don't know. Sorry.
Neither have I.
Besides, I don't think
I'd ever tell anyone.
What? Oh. Really? I see.
Hey! What about you, Akira?
Do you have any good advice?
Well, I don't know if this would
work, but--
I've heard of this weird thing
called the
"Suspension Bridge Effect".
"Suspension Bridge Effect?"
Hey, have you
heard of this thing
called the
"Suspension Bridge Effect"?
It's supposed to really work!
Ya!
It's supposed to
be the ultimate way
to confess your
feelings for someone!
"Suspension Bridge Effect"?
What is it?
And, how does it work?
It's the phenomenon
where a person falls in love
while they're crossing
a suspension bridge.
When a person is
standing on the bridge,
his heart beats fast
because he's afraid of falling.
He then mistakenly thinks
his heart is beating fast
because he's in love with you.
I see, so the person is actually
nervous because of the bridge,
but you take advantage of that
and try to make him
think he's in love with you.
Um, I guess you
could put it that way.
Arr! Be careful, you might fall!
You're gonna fall!
Karasuma, I love you!
Would that really work?
Well, theoretically, yes.
But it's not proven.
C'mon, it's not hard to make
someone fall in love with you.
Really? But how? Tell me?
You just have to be cute.
But that won't work
for clumsy girls like me.
Don't be silly, darling.
That's the very reason
that God created fashion.
Doll yourself up,
even peacocks do it.
You could learn from them!
They also do it for protection.
And only males.
Look at the
peacocks, they do it.
Peacocks?
Peacocks, huh?
Karasuma, I love you!
Are you sure?
I know that look.
You're imagining weird things
again, aren't you Tenma?
You just don't get it, do you?
What are you talking about?
It's about what's in your heart.
It's what's inside that counts.
All you have to do is just
be yourself and be confident.
Mikoto.
I think you're absolutely right!
Thank you so much!
You're the best!
Huh?
I hate you, Mikoto.
What are you? A D-cup?
That's not fair!
Of course the guys love you!
You cheater!
What? Have you
gone totally psycho?
Great. Now I'm even more
discouraged than I was before.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Oh right, I should write down
some notes before I forget.
Now, if I can remember all the
advice that the girls gave me.
Somehow none of
this seems right.
This is ridiculous!
No one in their right mind
would any of these things!
It's stupid!
Oh my gosh! I'm really late!
Yakumo's gonna kill me!
That's right, there's a
short cut through the forest.
Maybe I should
take it this time.
What did Yakumo say?
Don't take that shortcut
through the forest, okay?
Why shouldn't I?
There's a pervert in there.
Oh, I thought it was because
of a bear or something.
Tenma, a pervert is
way more dangerous!
Please be careful!
That settles it then.
I'll be careful.
I won't go through the forest!
Oh, that's Karasuma.
Don't be afraid!
I'll protect you!
Karasuma! You're my hero!
That's how it's gonna happen!
That's how we'll fall in love!
Today's my lucky day!
Sweet Tenma.
Thank goodness I followed you.
Finally, my chance!
When Tenma is attacked,
I'll rescue her!
She'll be so grateful,
she'll fall in love with me!
Heh!
Unfortunately, I'm usually the
one people think's the pervert.
Ha ha ha! I know, not
to hard to imagine, right?
But not today! See--
My police officer
disguise is foolproof.
Alright, this is it.
Today's my lucky day.
Karasuma!
Oh no. I've lost sight of him.
What am I gonna do if
someone comes after me?
Look, if it isn't another
stupid high school girl.
Aww, too bad she's all alone.
She looks delicious.
Hurricane Kick!
Molesting high school
girls is a crime!
Are you all right?
Yes sir. Thank goodness
you came in time.
I'm saved.
Oh my god! It worked!
She thinks I'm her hero and now
she's fallen in love with me!
Thank you, Mr. Police Officer!
Oh, crap! I can't
believe she's that stupid.
Yes, I look like a
police officer right now.
But surely, if I take my
hat off, she'll recognize me!
Excuse me.
I know I'm a perfect stranger,
but you saved me anyway!
I'll always be
grateful for that!
You're very noble.
Just doing my duty.
I must be on my way now.
Please be more careful in
the future, Miss Tsukamoto.
I will.
Thank you very
much Mr. Policeman.
I wonder how he knew
my name? Oh well!
Imagine a thug like me
going on a school field trip.
All for the sake of love!
But why am I playing
cards with this guy?
Next time on School Rumble:
"Pigs Go Oink!
Cats Go Meow! Frogs and
Water Imps Go Ribbit!"
And no one knows
what they're thinking!