Hey, you! Don't run away!
"School Rumble"
is hot on my heels!
Pardon me...
...but I couldn't help
but notice the time.
Shouldn't you be dressed
for school, Mistress?
I should... but I'm not
going to school today.
I... I don't feel like it.
Nakamura... um?
Hm?
Oh, never mind.
What to do...?
If I show my face at school,
I'll die of embarrassment...
Look, I'm tellin' you guys!
They're a couple!
What? Are you serious?
Well, it would
explain a few things!
Yeah! Like why those two
looked so cozy at the dance.
What two?
What do you know? It's Harima!
What are you lookin' at?
What the hell is this?!
No, no, it wasn't us!
You've gotta believe us,
dude! Please!
She's absent because
of her sprained ankle?!
Come on, she danced on it!
Sounds like a lame excuse...
You ask me? Depression.
I know...!
We should all go visit her
after school and cheer her up!
All right.
Heh!
We should take up a collection
and buy her a Get Well cake!
Poor little Eri!
Poor...?! She lives in a
mansion, for cryin' out loud!
Who the hell threw this?!
All right, who did it, huh?!
You better spit it out now!
If you don't tell me, I'm gonna
have to bleed it outta ya!
We already told you we
don't know who did it!
Don't say I didn't warn ya!
Harima...! Stop it!
Hey, why does
she look so sad...?
I didn't yell at her or nothin'.
Wait a minute.
If she saw that drawing...
Then she thinks I'm
dating that rich girl!
Did I break Tenma's heart!
Okay, well that was weird.
It was pretty awkward.
Aw, how sweet. Look,
they're sharing an umbrella.
Those two?
Well, duh! If
something's written down,
it's got to be true...
No, not necessarily.
Wish someone would
share an umbrella with me.
Crap! It was that stupid
dance, wasn't it...?!
That's why those jerks
think we're a couple!
Ugh... I was just tryin'
to be nice to that rich girl!
It didn't mean anything!
So why did some jackass
have to do that drawing,
and why did Tenma
have to see it!
I'm so stupid...!
On the camping trip...
Oh, Harima... Don't be a playa.
Ugh! I should've listened
to her, but I didn't.
There's no way I can face her!
Harima!
What do you want?
A fight? Let's get
it over with then.
Harima...
The only reason I came here
was to say, "Congratulations!"
Uhhhh...
Well...
that and apologize for
the misunderstanding we had
in the alley the other day...!
I thought you were
in love with Yakumo
when it was really
Eri all this time!
What did you say?!
You did come to pick
a fight! Didn't you?!
N-no...! I just wanted
to let you know
I'm really happy
for you and Eri!
Shut up!
Isn't love a wonderful thing?
Hey, Harima!
Tenma...! Crap.
Uh, hey there...
So how's it goin'?
Great! Nothin' like
being put on the spot!
What am I s'posed
to say to her?!
Hey, don't get stressed out.
I know what you want to say.
Huh?!
You're having trouble getting
the words out, aren't ya?
So she's knows
what I'm thinkin'!
Tenma's incredible! This
is like fate or somethin'...
If I'm dreamin',
I don't wanna wake up...
Listen... you just gotta
spit it out at some point.
Yeah... I know that, but...
Oh, Harima... It's okay.
Say how you feel...
Okay! I'm gonna do it!
What?! Great!
Get it off your chest!
Uh, sorry this
has taken so long...
but you wanna know how I feel?
Well, here goes...
Finally... finally I can tell
her she's the love of my life!
She'll be so thrilled!
Yep, she sure is
one lucky girl, huh?
Who's "she?"
Oh... you tease! Eri!
She must be so happy right now!
Eri, huh...?
Why would the rich girl
be happy right now?
Oh, come on, now!
Don't play dumb with me,
Harima! You and Eri!
You've been shot through the
heart by love...! Sha-Kaboom!
Bullseye... Partner.
Tenma, she...
really thinks I've
got somethin' goin'...
on with that rich girl.
Oh, man...
She... wasn't upset...
or nothin'.
She actually... seemed happy...
If she thinks I'm with another
girl and she isn't sad...
Then that can only
mean one thing.
Tenma was never
in love with me...
See ya around!
Let me know what happens
when you tell Eri...!
I want all the juicy details!
Uh...
Harima, is everything okay?
What was I thinking?
Dancing with him
in front of everybody?
Still though... It was sweet.
I need to thank him.
And... I think I know how.
Ow!
Harima...? Uh, what are
you doing in here alone?
My life's over here...
Got no reason to stay anymore...
Tenma's sister...
Yes?
I've... I've gotta
fix it... The name.
Name?
In the classroom...
On my desk...
It's all wrong. It--
I-I'll get it! Be right back!
I gotta write...
Put my feelings down on paper...
The tale of the girl I loved...
and how she broke my heart.
Yep. Empty.
I knew PE would be the perfect
period to slip in unseen...
Genius plan if I say so myself.
And, this saves me from having
to thank him in front
of everyone else, too.
They'll be wrapping up
out there any minute.
'Kay, let's see...
He sits next to Sis, so...
This must be it...
Huh? Wonder what he was
talking about back there?
The thing about
fixing the name...
The name tag?
This stitching
job's not the best.
That could be it... maybe?
Uh, Harima?
He's gone...
I'll fix this myself...
I just hope he doesn't
get too angry...
Akira? You here?
What have you got there?
Uh... Oh! This thing?
Well, it's... Harima's
jacket. I'm fixing it.
The stitching was loose
around the name tag...
Just a simple fix so--
Uh... Eri?
So, why are you
fixing his jacket?!
Uh, did Tenma ask you?
Well, no. You see...
I was just trying
to help him out.
Harima asked me
to go get this and...
Wait. Harima asked you?
I never knew you two
were so well acquainted.
Yes, uh, Harima, he drops
by every now and then...
Oh, really...? Why?
Why...
Promise me! Don't tell
anyone you saw this, Please!
So... You see a
nametag that needs
a better sewing job and
you fix it just like that.
Wow. That's really
terrific of you... And sweet.
Um, I like helping people...
It says a lot
about you, you know?
That you're kind, considerate,
and want to take care of people.
You know, you'd make a great
girlfriend for some lucky guy.
Thank you...
Hey, can I see that?
Uh, of course.
Wow...! This looks great.
Here...
Nice work... I sure wish
I could sew like that... See ya.
Wow, Eri's really running late.
Don't worry about it.
She'll be here. Come on.
It was her idea for us to meet.
I doubt she'd bail on us.
Yeah, you're right.
Besides, I get to watch
Yakumo work. That's always fun!
Hey... Why are you
dressed like that?
Someone asked me to...
Who?
Hey guys.
Oh, hello again.
Hey, we were about
to send out a search party!
We were starting to get worried.
Glad you could finally make it!
Hey, wait! What gives?
Why are you
wearing your uniform?
Yeah. Did you have to go
to school for something?
Well, sort of...
Can I... just order, please?
Uh, sure... Well,
what can I get you?
A Bloody Mary.
Uh... but we don't...
What? No Bloody
Mary's here? A pity.
Uh... no...
I'm sorry about that.
I could use one... Oh, well.
Just bring me a triple Espresso.
Hey, I heard the good news!
About you and Harima!
Did he do it?!
Did he tell you he loves you?!
Tenma... she's the one he loves.
Whhaaatttt?!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait a minute!
What's this all about, Sis?!
Oh, Yakumo, didn't you tell
your big sister about this?
For shame.
No, look, it's not what you...
I can't... I can't
believe it. This is crazy.
I thought Harima
was in love with Eri.
Yakumo...! Please, you've
got to tell me the truth...!
Have you and Harima
been seeing each other?!
Well... in a way... yes...
So it's true...?!
Why didn't you ever tell
me about this, huh...?!
I'm really shocked...!
My little sister getting a
boyfriend is big news...!
And... my life's over.
Cooking for
someone you love...
It's done!
Hope this tastes half
as good as it smells!
Hey, maybe I should
bring some to Karasuma!
Hey, Sis... What are you doing?
Feast your eyes
on my tuna curry!
Ta-da!
Tuna curry?
Yeah...! Smells yummy, huh?
Uh... yeah...
But what's the occasion?
It looks like you went through
a lot of trouble
just to make dinner.
Hey, it was worth it,
and don't worry about a thing.
I'll clean up this mess.
Let's celebrate!
My little sister just
got her first boyfriend!
Uh, Tenma...
About that Harima thing...
Finally ready to dish some dirt?
No, it's... it's just...
it's not what you think.
This relationship between me
and Harima's complicated...
So you're a little nervous!
Don't worry about it...!
Every relationship is
like that at the start!
No... Sis!
Don't worry
you'll work it out...!
You make a cute couple...!
Yakumo and Harima!
It's... not like that...
I'm so glad you found somebody!
I wanna fall in
love just like you!
All the excitement today has
really made me hungry!
Let's eat...! I hope
you've got an appetite, Sis!
Oh, Tenma...
After all that time,
she never loved me...
Gotta leave it all
behind. Her, school...
And... find a
new life out there...
Sagittarius,
you'll be lucky in love!
Maybe... Maybe
Karasuma's horoscope
will predict some romance,
too...! Let's see here.
He was born October 28th,
that makes him a Scorpio...
Hey, wait! It's almost the 28th!
I cannot forget
Karasuma's birthday!
There's no time to waste!
Sis, can I give you a hand?
No thanks!
If I don't do it myself
that means it didn't
come from the heart!
Ta-da!
Well... you did try...
Yeah, but not hard enough!
I can't give him that cake!
I've got to learn how to make a
better cake before his birthday!
Karasuma, he deserves
nothing but the very best!
I've gotta get it right!
Just do your best, Tenma.
Oh, Tenma...
You comfy, squid bait?
Can I get you another
pillow or an extra blankie?
This ain't no summer
camp, ya know!
Look! He's scared!
Tell us this, wussy boy.
Do ya even know the
name of this ship?
Uh, no...
Of 'course not.
Well, allow me to
do the honors, kid...
Don't wet yourself,
but you're aboard...
the fiercest ship on the seas,
The Cry of the Demon!
Ya see, this ship
plies the stormy waters
where other ships fear
to sail! Welcome to Hell!
No room for lazy
panty-waists out here...!
We gotta chain a'command,
and you're at the bottom
of it, so listen up!
The deck's covered in fish
guts...! Go clean it up! Now!
You sure 'bout this, Ootani?
You-know-who's up
there right now.
'Course. Why else do ya
think I sent that kid?
Oh, you're pretty
cold, you know that?
Last time I used one of these...
...was when we
played pool hockey.
Ugh... Can't get
hung up on the past...
Just forget it...
Uh... What the hell?!
Whoa...! What
happened to this guy?!
Hey, kid...
Since yer swabbin',
clean that trash, too.
Oh... and if ya know
what's good for ya,
you'll never question
my orders like him.
Out here, the
cap'n's word is law!
You'll live longer
if ya learn that now!
Dear Tenma: Hope you're well...
Look, I don't know if we'll ever
see each other again, but...
I've been drawin'
this comic and, well,
it's about you and me,
and how I feel and stuff...
I may never return...
so I wanted to let you know...
Hope you get this...
Right... Back to work...
Told ya he was soft!
Look at this crap...!
It's a comic book,
a girlie romance one...!
Look, he even draws like a girl!
You lousy-!
Give that back, you bastard!
Forgot to say "please"...
This is a man's ship, punk...!
We ain't got no room
for this kiddie crap!
Comics are good...
for one thing.
You bastard!
This just isn't your day,
now is it, sweetheart?!
Now I'm 'onna
teach ya some manners.
Like for starters,
how to respect your elders.
Kiss that drawin'
hand goodbye, punk...
Uh... Captain?!!
I should keel-haul ya,
but I need all hands on deck.
A storm is brewin'!
I left my old life behind
for a new one on a tuna boat...
And its captain is the toughest
guy I've ever met in my life!
For real...! Next time
on School Rumble...
Uh, those aren't words!