Hey, Happy New Year...!
School Rumble is
coming up next! Yeah!
When you watch television...
keep the lights on...
and don't sit too close!
Iori!
Bad kitty!
Behave yourself!
Iori!
What's gotten
into that cat lately?
Oh, I can't stand
it anymore, it's so hot!
Yakumo...
when is the air conditioner
gonna be fixed?!
The repairman said
they'd be here around noon,
or a little after.
Aghhhhh...! But everyone's
coming over here
to do homework today!
I'm afraid it can't be helped.
No... fair!...! I'm gonna die
in this heat, I just know it!
There are lots of people
who are out in this heat,
and they don't die.
They go to work...
They play sports...
All kinds of things...
Awwwww... Yuki...
are you sure you can't go?
Not even for a little while?
Oh, I see...
Well, maybe next time...
Damn it...
Okay, who else we got?
Hey there, Kyoko!
What are you doing...?
Eh...? I see...
Well, maybe next time...
I don't get it...
What's everyone's problem today?
Okay, moving on...
Oh my goodness,
I'm so sorry...! I didn't...
Wait, you're
Imadori, aren't you?
Yeah... and you're...
Karen Ichihuh?
Ichijou.
Oh... I'm really sorry, honest!
S'okay, no problem.
So what's up in there...?
Wrestling practice?
Uh... uh-huh.
Whew... I can't imagine...
It must be pretty rough
in this kind of weather...
Let's see, who's next?
Well, we train every
day. We're used to it.
Come on, every day...?
Are you guys crazy...?
Geez, it's summer vacation.
That means it's time to get out
and have fun dating
around, ya know?
You should really think
about getting a boyfriend.
I'm... really...
I'm not... very good
at things like that...
Do you really enjoy wrestling
every single day...?
I mean, isn't there something
else you'd rather be doing?
I'm not very good
at anything else.
In fact, I'm not even
that good at wrestling.
But I do enjoy it.
It's a whole lot of fun for me!
Huh... Wrestling... Weird.
I never thought
that was something you
could be so serious about...
Here you go, Eri! Iced tea!
Thank you.
Mikoto will be here
in just a little bit,
but Akira said she
couldn't make it until later.
Oh, man...
We won't make any
headway until Akira gets here.
You're right...
A couple of dummies like you
and me haven't got
a chance on our own.
A couple of dummies?!
Now wait just a darn minute!
The only class I have
trouble in is language skills,
so don't go lumping me in
the same category with you!
Yeah, that's great.
Do you understand
problem number seven?
Don't you even listen when
people are talking to you?!
Okay, fine, so you
don't understand it...
It's no big deal...
I'll just do it myself.
No...! The point is...
Forget it.
So, uh... Tenma...
What's up?
There's, uh, there's something
that I wanted to ask you.
Oh, yeah, what is it...?
Ask me, ask me!
I was wondering if you've
ever seen... a man's body.
Wait a sec...
I didn't mean to say...
Damn it...!
Whenever my mind wanders,
that image comes
back into my head.
There it is again!
And now I've asked
Tenma a stupid question,
all because I wasn't thinking!
This is all that
pervert Harima's fault...
He had to lose his head and do
something totally ridiculous...
And to ask Tenma
of all people...!
She's probably the most
naïve girl in our entire...
Of course I have.
What?!
I've seen men's bodies.
You've...
Wait a minute,
you can't mean that...
You what?!
Sure... Hasn't everyone our age?
What's the big deal?
That... That can't mean...
Tenma has...
gone all the way...?
I haven't even done that yet!
Ahem...!
So... I guess this must
have been with Karasuma?
Oh, gosh...! How did
you know about that...?
Yes, it was just the
other night when we...
Noooooooooooooo!!
It was the greatest
night of my life...!
Karasuma was such a gentleman.
Huh? What on
earth's the matter...?
Oh...! I hadn't thought...
Maybe you haven't seen one?
And I thought she
was into contact sports!
Of course I have.
I thought so.
I mean, it's only natural...
So, what are
your favorite moves?
How embarrassing.
Tenma's more
experienced than I am!
Hold on...! I bet she wouldn't
do something like that!
Well, how about taking
one right in the mouth?
Yeah...! That's
great for starters!
What about having
your arms held back?
Oh, yeah!
That's an amazing move!
That's it... I give up!!
Yes, sir, the guys
just can't get enough
of that stuff... Whew!
Is that true?!
Then... if Akira hadn't come in
when she did,
he really might've...
What's happening to my body!
Uh, by the way, there's, uh,
something I wanted
to talk to you about.
You mean there's more...?
Well, then spit it out!
Come on...! I can take it!
Well, it's... about...
it's about Harima.
Huh?
I'm pretty sure he's got
a major crush on Mikoto.
I'd really like it if
things worked out well
for the two of them.
But let's face it, I'm no
good at this sort of thing.
So I was wondering if
I could count on your help.
I think this could be
a good thing for Mikoto.
I was kind of surprised
Harima liked her...
But then, Mikoto is so pretty...
Well... come on...
when you think about it...
Mikoto isn't really
all that pretty.
A.C. Repair!
Thank goodness, you're here!
If you don't mind, we'll need
to check the compressor first.
Strange. He's so quiet.
Right this way.
Oh. That's gonna be tricky.
Hey... get the ladder.
Right.
Well, I'll let you get to it.
Iori...! Where have
you been...? Come here!
Oh, my gosh...
What's wrong with your leg?
Are you hurt?
Wait a minute...! Iori!
Oh, man, now what
am I gonna do...?
He's mad at me for
scolding him so much!
Come on, kitty!
Get your mousie...?
No...? How about a fishie?
You like fish...
Come on out and I'll even
let you have two, if you want.
No good...
I guess I shouldn't have
been so hard on him...
Allow me.
Come here.
Let's see... Ah, here
we go, he's got a thorn.
Look, it's right here
behind his rear left leg.
There, he'll be okay now.
Oh... I don't know
how to thank you!
Wait...! Do you...?
Huh?
Do you... like animals?
Well... to be honest,
I never really used to think
about them all that much...
Then one day, they
suddenly seemed to like me.
Hold on... Huh?
This house...
It seems familiar somehow.
So... Has anyone else
noticed how hot it is...?
Should I open the
window a little wider?
Sure... Whatever.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
The window's already
opened as far as it'll go...
This is awful...
I've got to do something
to break this silence...
I know!
Hey, Eri. Can you
help me out with this?
Hmm... You're asking
the wrong girl.
Oh, well, how about you, Mikoto?
Hm...? Oh, the classics...
Sure thing... This is
probably what they're after...
Oh, I see... Thanks a lot!
Nothing to it...
That was an easy one.
Um, Mikoto...
What do you get for this one?
Sorry, I don't know
the answer to that one...
Is that math...? Let me see...
Oh, this is nothing. Here.
Wow, that was great...
You're good!
Nah, it's simple...
But you have to be
able to do this stuff
if you're even
thinking about college!
Oh, what am I gonna do...?!
Even without the A.C.
it's freezing in here!
Okay, study questions
are a bust...
I need something
fun to break the ice...
But what...?
There must be something!
Hey, sorry I'm late, you guys,
but I picked up the
pictures from our vacation.
Oh, thank you, Akira!
Thank you...! Hey everybody!
Let's all look at
the nice pictures!
Ha ha...! We sure
had a good time!
Ooh...?! What's this?
Looks like Imadori
really likes you, Mikoto!
Tenma!
Would you shut up?!
You can't tell it from these,
but you must be pretty busy,
since you're secretly
running around
with that hairy
delinquent as well.
Huh?!
That's it! If you've
got something to say,
just spit it out.
I'm sick of playing all
these catty little games!
I don't know what the
hell your problem is,
but you seriously
need to grow up!
Just get over yourself!
Ah, that does it!
It is so on, Mikoto!
Unlike you, I don't
just cozy up to anyone
who can grow whiskers...!
First you're all
nice with Hanai,
and then you and Imadori
just disappear somewhere,
and now you're after Harima!
Whoa, whoa, whoa...!
What the hell are you
talking about, ponytails?!
You're the one who had him
on his knees in the middle
of the freaking
sidewalk the other day!
That...?! I couldn't help it,
he just suddenly popped up
out of nowhere, grabbed my hand,
and started confessing
his love to me!
I've had enough of this...!
I'm out of here!
Eri, wait!
S'all right...
See you later, Tenma.
Mikoto, is it really true?
Harima told Eri he loved her?
Yeah, it's true...
At the time I thought I should
just keep my mouth shut
and get out of there
before they could see me.
Then why... I don't get it.
I was helping him practice
how to confess his love to you!
He seemed so
serious about it, too!
And all that time, he was
chasing after both of you!
Oh, Harima, you...
you're terrible!
Come on, kid, just tell
me why you're crying.
No... forget it, it's nothing.
It's nothing.
Look, I can see
it's not nothing.
It's just that I don't know
what's going on anymore!
Oh, is this a case
of teenage heartbreak?
Is that what this is?
I'm very sorry, sir...
I'll get right back to work,
you don't have to worry.
Would you like a rice ball?
Um... I don't... I don't
really know what's going on...
but I hope you feel better.
Thank you.
I'll just help myself.
Oh, yeah, I remember those days.
It was rough.
Wow, that's tasty!
Wait, you want me to
recommend you for a job...?
Okay, so what happened?
Didn't you have a
viable form of employment?
Not anymore, I don't...
I'm through with air
conditioner repair forever...
It's personal.
Right, whatever...
If you really need a job,
I'll see what I can do,
but there's no room for
weaklings at this place!
Thank you, I won't let you down.
Okay, ladies,
it's time to get to work...!
Come on, move it, double time!
Yes, sir!
So what are you
doing here, beard boy?
I should ask you that.
It sucks, but you need money if
you wanna date the ladies.
Oh yeah, you just
figured that out...?
You're dumber than you look.
Hey! Less talk and more walk!
I don't need you
to tell me to work.
Keep it cool...
I'll just keep it cool and
concentrate on my job.
That's all that's left for
me now...! Time to kick ass!
Hey, new kid...! Attaboy!
Pretty impressive, carrying
that big sucker all by yourself!
Wow... I'm... needed?!
Why, you might even be able
to keep up with Hanai here.
Huh?
No sweat...
It's a light workout for me!
Hey... careful... newb...
When you're not used to it,
you can strain yourself.
Thanks... I'm okay... but
you should watch yourself,
you looked a little
wobbly on those stairs.
Very nice, boys...!
That's the way to hustle!
This...? It's nothing,
boss, easy as pie...
Easy, easy, easy, easy!
You guys sure
are some workers...!
The only other person
I've ever seen
lift a load like
that alone is Ichi!
I... Ichi?
Hey...! Ichi!
Yes, sir?
Oh, hey, guys!
Uh... Hey there, I'm Karen...
We go to the same school.
Heh... it's funny...
We're in the same class,
but we've never really talked.
Nooooooooo... Uhh...
It's that chick
from the wrestling team!
Oh, yeah... I remember her now.
She is in our class...
I didn't know she was
working for this company...
So you all know each other...?
In that case,
I'll let Ichi here show you
"tough guys" how
a real man works!
Huh...?! No,
I wasn't trying to...
You're like a freak of nature.
I mean, you're just so strong.
"A freak of nature?"...
But I'm a girl.
An ordinary, everyday girl.
It doesn't take any kind of
special talent to lift things...
It's just applied dynamics.
I get tired... just
like everyone else does.
Out of my way!
Wha... Imadori, I...
You shouldn't have to
strain yourself like this...
Why don't you let me
take care of it?
This is no kind
of job for a girl...
You should take it easy.
Oh, wow...!
Thank you so much, Imadori!
No problem.
Well, here I go...!
This is better!
Oh yeah!
Am I a genius or what?
Now all I have to do is
carry these lightweight boxes
one at a time, nice and slow!
And to think that girl might've
carried them all in at once...!
This way I get to skip
the heavy stuff and goof off!
Hell yeah!
I wonder if it's okay to
be paid the same as that girl?
Ah, now that was a good workout!
Money! Yeah! I rule!
It's nice, isn't it?
Nice? It's great...! I can
even ask you out if I want to!
I can do anything!
I'm king of the world!
Okay.
Um, thank you...
This is my first date... and...
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh, no...!
I wish I just knew when
to shut up! Dang it!
Yay...! We've got A.C.
and we've got snow cones.
Life is good!
Even so, you can't stay
indoors all the time, you know.
Don't worry about me!
I've got all kinds
of plans to go out!
I'm going to the fireworks
with Mikoto and Eri... Oh...
I forgot... Mikoto and Eri...
We may not be able to go to the
fireworks... or anything else...
Sara here!
When I told Yakumo I'd never
been to a fireworks display,
she invited me to come along
with her to the summer festival!
Next time on School Rumble:
"Summer, Friendship,
And Fireworks!"
I'm going to wear a kimono!