Please don't go away.
School Rumble is next.
C'mon, you guys!
Let's go swimming!
Hurry up! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!!
Gosh, what are you,
nine? Calm down!
But you just ate.
You shouldn't go swimming.
You might get cramps!
What? I never heard of that!
I'm getting in!
You guys are boring!
Wait, Tenma!
It's slippery,
you're gonna fall!
She never listens.
Whee!
Round and round I'm spinning!
Wow, she's cheerful today!
Ugh!
But seriously can we do
something about that inner tube?
Ya, I know what you mean.
Hey, guys!
Those chicks are totally hot!
Yeah!
Now you're talkin' !
Look at the blonde
with the brown eyes...
She's a hotty.
Check out the hood
on the one next to her.
Brilliant? I think so!
That one with the
short hair looks smart.
She's probably got experience,
you know what I mean?
Yay! Around the world I go!
My friends are
gonna get burned...
and turn red like watermelons!
They're being hit on!
Yay! I'm gonna join 'em!
Wait a minute.
If I went over there right now,
I might be interrupting.
I'd be the fifth wheel.
They would make nice couples.
Actually, there are
couples everywhere!
So, you wanna watch
me work out later?
It's sad, but lately
things don't seem to be going
all that great with Karasuma.
Ugh! How much stinkin' curry
does a girl have to make!
That's it!
I want to get hit on, too!
Come on! Any takers?
I'm willing and vulnerable!
Are you asking me?
Yes, I happen to be
studying here in Japan.
You see my mom's
in Sweden right now.
She's running a
company over there.
Cool.
I think I'd rather not.
Aw...
I just wanna talk so
I can get to know you a little.
Come on now, don't make me
look like a loser in
front of everyone.
So, what's your
capital-per-asset ratio like?
Okay, I've circled
around twice now.
Huh?! Seriously?!
They're still at it?!
I guess I'll have
to go around again.
Okay...
This time I'll break
my current record
for the fastest time around.
Are you okay? Hey...
Aren't you Tenma Tsukamoto?
Phew, sorry for a
second there I thought
I'd almost killed
a middle school kid.
Huh?! Middle school?
For your information,
I'm 16 years old.
Obviously, you're the one
that's in middle school,
so you should
speak more politely
to your elders, young man!
Are you kidding me...!
Have you gone mental?
I'm Kentaro Nara!
We're in the same class!
Ha-ha! I got you! Stupid.
You might as well be
a middle schooler...
I mean, that was totally lame.
I think I understand.
You just wanna get hit on
by guys like your friends,
there's nothing wrong with that.
I mean, I know I'm kinda
childish compared to them,
but I just wanna be
treated like... a woman.
I don't think that's
asking too much.
But Tenma, you come
across as a fun girl
that's easy for guys to talk to.
I don't think they think
of you as the dating type.
That's mean!
It's true that I get along
really well with guys
and have a lot of fun with them.
But I wonder why none of them
ever wanna get serious with me.
I wonder why, I wonder why...
Why don't boys
want to date me...
Why don't they want
to get serious...? Why?!
Uh,... If that's the case...
maybe I should ask you out.
Uh, like I said... maybe
I should try asking you out.
I mean, if you don't mind
That's great!
Now I can tell the
girls a guy hit on me!
Uh, so... Do you...
wanna go to Karaoke tonight?
Nara is such a nice person...
Karasuma was never
this sweet to me.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much,
but I kinda have a
crush on this other boy.
Please don't let go!
You're okay.
I promise I won't let go.
I wonder who Tenma
has a crush on.
Nara?
Hmm?
Maybe I should let go and
try to swim by myself now.
Do you think I'm ready?
You can try.
Tenma!!
That was awful!
But I was able to swim
fifteen whole meters this time!
That's a brand new record!
What's wrong?
Uh... Nothing. Nothing's wrong.
You're a weird boy!
Wow... her skin is so soft.
So, you came here with
some friends of yours?
Yeah. They're really great guys.
I think you'll like 'em.
I can't wait to meet 'em!
Maybe they'll become
my new friends, too.
Yeah! Oh...
there they are. Hey!!
There's Nara...
Where the heck have you been?
Uh, Tenma...
What are you doing with Nara?
When you said you came with
friends, you meant these guys?
Yeah.
You sly dog.
You two been hanging out?
I don't believe it,
this is perfect.
Let's all go on a date.
I don't know if we should.
Let's decide with a contest.
Contest?
Hey, that could be fun.
Wha? Are you serious?!
If the girls win,
dinner is on you guys.
And it will be expensive.
You have my word.
Hey, Akira, don't you
think that's a bit harsh?
I mean, we were planning
to go to my favorite restaurant.
I don't think a high school
student's allowance
could even cover the appetizer.
What? You're crazy.
But that is one good bluff.
Sure beats the hell
out of the noodle stand.
Hey! If these two get
serious, we could win!
All right!
We're game if you guys are.
Let's see... What kind
of contest should we have?
We'll swim for it!
So, whoever is the fastest
swimmer out of all of us
wins for their team, Okay?
I can't lose.
If I go on a date, it'll be like
I'm cheating on the guy I like.
I know I can't win...
But...
One of us will definitely win!
On your marks ... get set ...
Go!
You guys are so stupid!
Why didn't any of you tell
me that you couldn't swim?
We're sorry.
I thought at least
one of us could swim.
Oh, man, ...
I should have listened to
that weather forecast today.
Huh?
Yes!
My sanctuary
from nature's wrath!
Oh, hey. Are you
waiting out the rain?
Yeah.
This is awkward.
Things haven't been
going well with Karasuma
since the curry incident.
I've gotta make it up to him.
Maybe this rain is fate's
way of giving me that chance.
I wonder if Karasuma
is mad at me,
or if he's gotten
bored of me already.
I'd really like to be
friends with him again.
Uh... Karasuma...
A water imp costume...?
Oh yeah, that's
Karasuma's rain gear...
It may be too late
to say anything now,
but someone should really
tell him how silly that is!
No, no! I can't!
If I tell him he looks stupid,
then he'll really be mad at me.
I love Karasuma.
So, I've gotta be quiet.
No, I have to say something!
Karasuma... um...
Well, there's something that
I really have to tell you...
Um... It's just...
Here you go.
Would you like to
borrow this to keep dry?
Huh?
I'm not going to let you
get soaked and catch a cold.
But, this Water Imp costume
will only protect one person.
You were worried because
you thought I was going
to leave you
here all alone, right?
You thought I was going
to just take off and
let you get soaked...
I'm not that mean.
Did I misunderstand
you, after all?
No. You were right, Karasuma.
Tenma...! She must be
around here somewhere.
Yakumo! Did you
come to pick me up?
Tenma!
What the... Is that...?
Karasuma let me borrow
his water imp costume...!
It's a boy's size, though,
so it's a little big on me.
Karasuma said he'd be
fine with just the head piece.
Isn't he nice?!
Yes. He's very nice.
Hey, look. It's Harima.
Yeah.
They say he's back in school.
There's a rumor going
around that he had to disappear
for a while because he had a
fight with some gang members.
I'm not surprised.
I've heard rumors
like that before.
He's like a wolf that's been
living too long in a dark
and desolate world where
guys like us just don't belong.
So what are you gonna
do for summer vacation?
The beach! I've always
wanted to go to the beach.
Do you think Eri and Akira
would be up for it?
It's not like I confessed
and she rejected me.
That means
I still have a chance.
So, from now on, my main
purpose in school is to spend
every possible
moment with Tenma!
And with that said...
School's out for
summer vacation!
Yay!
Dammit!
Why does school
have to be out now?!
Like I was saying...
We'll hit the beach first.
Yeah, I mean we did
promise those guys
we would go with them!
I really don't understand why we
have to go out with a bunch
of stupid guys who are
all talk, but have no brains.
Ugh, Don't listen to her.
Mikoto is just way
too much of a prude.
Besides, you should try
to get more experience.
Otherwise, you'll
just screw it up
when you finally
go on a real date.
What?!
Did you watch
too many after-school
specials growing up?
I think it's beautiful
that Mikoto wants
to wait for true love.
You're acting
really weird, lately.
That's because it's summer.
What does that mean...?
As if summer has anything to
do with you acting like a freak!
What are they talking about?
Tenma's going to the
beach with some guy?!
Not if I can help it.
I've got to hear more.
I'll just casually
get a little bit closer.
I can't wait!
What the...?
Uh... I've gotta go.
That woman is insane!
She has no right
to still be pissed
over what happened
the other day!
It was a mistake!
Who in their right mind
could ever fall in love
with a woman like that!
I've got no choice.
I'm gonna beat the
crap out of that guy
if he doesn't
forget about Tenma!
Help.
Aw, no way!
Even if I did that,
I still wouldn't get to go
to the beach with her.
Maybe I should get some guts
and ask her to the beach myself!
Maybe she'd prefer that
over me beating up that guy.
Ah, yes. That could
be a good idea.
You know, I think
I might just do that.
Okay... I'm handing
out your report cards.
Harima!
Yeah.
I have to talk to you.
I'm a little confused about
that letter you gave
me a while ago...
Better shut up or I'll kill you.
Damn, nothin' but turtles.
Hey, you did the same as me!
Oh, uh... What was that?
I got all turtles, too!
Thank God, I was born stupid!
Okay.
So, Tenma?
I've been wanting to talk
to you about something.
If you want...
I would like to ask you...
I'd really enjoy it if you came
to see a movie with me tonight!
Right there...
That's where
we'll be going. See?
Mhm! Wow.
It looks really nice...
I'm glad we're going...
I don't think Tenma
knows this is sort of a date...
so it's kinda sneaky.
But, I really do like her.
Please, don't do this.
Don't take our daughter.
She's all we have.
Please don't!
Are you okay with this, Harima?
Yeah.
Why do I have to
go to summer school?
I should be on vacation!
Well, at least there's
one thing to look forward to.
So, x squared y
plus 43... equals 149.
I have Akira as my tutor!
Score one for me!
Ah, stupidity has
brought us together!
Oh yeah, that reminds me...
The trip we're going on is
an overnighter, right Tenma?
Have you packed yet?
Yep, I'm all ready!
Damn! I forgot
about the beach trip!
Interesting.
Crap...! That guy's
probably gonna have
his grubby little
paws all over Tenma!
And how could he not?
I mean, she is the cutest one!
Aw, dammit! Who the
hell is this guy!
I'll hunt him down!
And pound him
'til he can't walk!
No! I'm a changed man now.
I'll try a more
positive approach.
Yes!
What the hell are
you laughing at, punk?
You gotta problem with
me wearing bikini shorts?!
I look good in bikini shorts!
Oh, man. Tennoji is so stupid.
I don't act stupid
like that anymore.
Do I, guys?
What?! You mean all
three of you can't go?
No, we all got our asses
kicked by some crazy dude
with a bald head.
Man... This really sucks.
There's no way I can be
the only guy on the trip...
I guess I'll have to find
a way to let Tenma down easy.
Wait, this is so perfect!
If I'm the only guy, then
there won't be any competition.
It'll just be me and her!
Alright! She's taking
extra classes right now!
So I'll go to school
and see her tomorrow...!
Good morning!
What kinda guys can
I get to go as replacements
to be with the
other three girls?
Imadori is too much of a
ladies man; he can't be trusted.
I can't ask Hanai,
he's way too bossy.
Harima seems to like Tenma,
and he's pretty much a
psycho, so that won't work.
Whatever I do, I can't let
those three know about it.
Hey, good morning, everybody!
Hey, good morning, Nara!
What's up?
Are you here about the trip?
I heard the other
three guys had to cancel.
That's too bad.
I hope you're not planning
on calling it off now.
So, I came up with a great idea!
Why don't we just ask three
other boys to join us instead!
This isn't happening.
Don't tell me.
This is the guy who invited
Tenma to the beach?!
But I'm a delinquent.
I can't go on a trip
with a bunch of guys
without hurting anyone!
No, no, no!
Hold up! I have changed my ways!
Yes... I can be a friendly guy
I'll go to the beach!
All right! That's it! Yes!
I'll go to the...
I'll go to the beach!
Pick me! Pick me! Pick me! Yeah!
Okay! Imadori's in!
Could we discuss this, please?
Damn! I can't be the
friendly type anymore!
He stole my idea!
I think that
I should go with you.
Oh, that's good!
I think that I--
I think that
I should go with you.
Hanai, you're in too!
Now we just need one more.
In that case, we're gonna
have to invite Yakumo.
That's one extra girl,
but unfortunately,
it can't be helped.
Of course it can be helped!
What are you? Stupid?
Yakumo, huh?
I wonder if she would...?
She does tend to be really
shy around crowds, y'know?
Yeah! Summer's here!
I'm absolutely dying
to go swimming!
Harima wants to go bad!
They used to call
me Harima the Merman,
because I'm such a good swimmer.
Well, there's definitely
no one else from our class
that we can possibly invite!
And I'm sure everyone
is extremely busy.
Man... All this spare time!
Okay... Then I'll see
if Yakumo wants to go.
Yes, that would be great.
I love girls.
Oh, man...!
I'm totally left out!
That sucks.
That was my chance to go
out with the girl of my dreams!
Huh?!
Ten... ma. You came back.
I, uh... forgot something
so I had to come and get it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no. She must have heard me.
Harima. Come to
the beach with us.
Does this mean...
Tenma likes me?
Yes! Tenma...!
You are my goddess!
I will make you the
happiest woman in the world!
Hey! Good luck!
Say what?
I don't know who you like...
but, I'm really rooting for you.
So do your best. Okay, Harima!
Well, I'll see you later!
That sucks...
You totally got the
wrong idea, Tenma.
Wait a minute.
What am I thinking?
This could be the chance
I've been waiting for...
I'm actually gonna go
to the beach with Tenma.
All right!
Kenji Harima ... gets
his chance to kick ass!
A crazy spirit
awakens my wild side!
Just wait, Tenma!
I know you'll fall in
love with me at the beach!
Next time on School Rumble:
"Save Me at the Beach!"
Oops!
"Save Me, I'm Naked!
Just Save Me! For Real!"
Why do these
things happen to me?