School Rumble's starting...
...right after this.
Mountain spirits, please
bless us with lakes, pears,
and trees, instead of
snakes, bears, and bees!
Uh, is that a real camping song?
Uh, yeah.
You've never heard it?
She's pulling your leg, Eri.
Uh! You are so obnoxious!
Gotcha!
Hey...! There it is!
The campground!
Wow!
The mountains are so
beautiful this time of year!
Yeah, and smell that fresh air!
Echo!
It's too bad Sara's
not here to see this.
Hey, look...
She already had plans...
and this was a last
minute trip after all.
Oh...
So what exactly
does camping have to do
with the Tea Club anyway?
Nature calms the mind...
Besides, this really isn't an
official club outing anymore.
Right!
You and Yakumo
are the only members.
If we didn't come, you wouldn't
have had enough people!
I'm really surprised that
Hanai didn't come along.
Shouldn't he be here?
He should...
but since I gave him the wrong
date, I wouldn't count on it.
What...?!
Yakumo went camping...?!
With the Tea Club...?!
This morning?!
Akira Takano,
damn you and your trickery!
So tell me, Harima, do chicks
dig the ride?
Harima! You gotta help me!
Give me your motorcycle,
on the double!
You sure got a funny way
of askin' for a favor.
I don't have much
time to explain!
They all went camping!
I was supposed to go, but
Akira gave me the wrong date!
I need to get to the
campground quick,
so I need your motorcycle!
Holy crap!
This is my chance to find out if
what Tenma said was really true!
No time to waste!
Let's roll!
Oh, thanks!
All right!
Haul ass, man!
Huh?!
Come back...! You creeps can't
just leave me behind! Stop!
Stop! Dammit!
Madame Chairperson...
what can I do to
help out right now?
Why don't you gather firewood?
Mmmkay.
Oh, Yakumo.
What a moron!
Hey, look, guys.
Hey, Miko!
Don't worry!
We men will handle
all the chores!
The cooking and the cleaning...!
You ladies just kick back
and enjoy the beauty
of the great outdoors!
Wow! Really?!
Imadori, unpack the dishes!
Harima, go get firewood!
Whatever.
Aw, man.
It's him.
I wonder if he knows
a lot about animals?
Firewood duty...
It just ain't fair.
Uh... here's one.
Would you like some help?
Hey...
You're Tenma's little sister,
right...? Uh, thank you.
Sure.
Just my luck, ain't it?
Out here with the little
sister instead of Tenma.
Oh, Harima, you...
you're terrible!
I wonder what would make
her say something like that?
Hey, maybe if I talk to
her sister I could find out.
I guess he doesn't
remember me. Strange...
Hey, what are you making?
Come on, Hanai's a great cook.
I'm rubbing out some of
my world famous curry!
There's a convenience store
down the hill that
sells frozen curry.
We could just buy some.
Bite your tongue...!
Me deny Yakumo a fresh,
home-cooked meal made
from the heart?!
No! Never!
Okay, then.
I'll just leave you churning.
You guys know where Yakumo is?
Oh, she said she really wanted
to help Harima get wood.
Are you okay?
Uh... hey...
Look, I know this is
gonna sound kinda weird...
but has, uh, has your sister
been mad about anything lately?
Huh?
I just heard she was,
uh, angry or somethin'.
I don't know.
Well, now that you mention it,
she did say she discussed
someone with Eri and Mikoto...
Bingo!
You wouldn't happen to know
who they were
talkin' about, would ya?
Not sure... but I believe
it was some guy.
Oh, really? What kinda guy?
Uh... Well, he... had a
beard... and sunglasses...
Lotsa guys look like that.
So... what'd she say about
this guy we don't know?
Uh... Well, she...
She was really touched
when this guy shared his
feelings with her, but...
when she felt he wasn't
being honest with himself,
that made her sad.
What?!
It... It can't be...! Not being
honest with myself?!
That can only mean one thing!
When we were "practicing" our
love confessions on the trip,
Tenma saw through me and
realized it wasn't an act!
She knew that I really
felt that way about her!
So, then...
Oh, Harima, you...
you're terrible!
What she really
meant to say was...
Harima, I've been terrible...
Oh, please forgive me, my love.
Of course! That's what she
wanted to say!
Moron! Where's your head?!
That's what you get for
jumping to conclusions...!
Besides, Tenma's such a
sweetheart she'd never say
anything bad about
the man who loves her!
Um... that really hurts.
Oh... sorry about that!
Sometimes I don't
know my own strength...
I can't understand
this guy at all...
But I can tell...
he has a good heart...
Well, we should be heading back.
Oh, do me a favor
and don't tell your sister
what we talked about.
He doesn't remember, does he...?
I just wanted to
talk about animals...
Oh, well...
Oh, hey, I forgot...
Those rice balls you made
were good... Real good.
Uh... You okay...? Ready to go?
Uh...
Sure.
That slimeball's sunk even lower
than I thought he could...!
Hitting on Eri and
Miko wasn't enough?
Now you've got to
hit on Yakumo, too!
You're just a player...! You've
got no sense of decency!
None...! Harima...
You messed with
the wrong big sister!
Hey, we're back.
It's about time, Harima...!
Oh, nice firewood, Yakumo.
Finally... Hey, Beardy!
Buy me some tea, would you?
Right now...? But I just
lugged all this stuff back
from the woods
and I'm really tired.
You heard me, swine!
Yeah, but I wish I didn't,
you stuck-up little brat...!
Still mad at me, huh...?!
But then again...
if I don't do what you want,
you might tell Tenma
about what happened...
Here.
I don't like that kind.
Cut me a little slack
today, will ya...?!
There's only so much
I can take! Just drink it!
What did you say?
Yes, ma'am. I'm on it!
Splash attack!
You're gonna get it next, Akira!
Uh... Hey, there...
Whoa.
Yakumo!
Stay away from him...!
That guy is an animal!
But...
I saw him!
It's just like Harima
to get you in the woods
and start hitting on you!
No... he wasn't...
Yes, he was...! I saw that
creepy look in his eyes!
But how?
He was wearing sunglasses...
He really doesn't seem to
be a bad person at all, Sis.
Poor Yakumo!
You don't
understand guys at all...!
But you've never been on
a date, so how could you?
But neither have you, Tenma.
Don't believe me? Take a peek!
Tenma's totally checking
me out! Awesome!
See!
He's got that big,
creepy smile on his face...!
Trust me on this.
He's totally after you.
But all I wanted to do
was talk to him, so...
I know a little bit more about
guys than you do, so listen...
Harima's a player.
In fact, all guys
are the same, Sis.
They're cheating dogs
who can't be trusted...
So stay away from Harima!
Then you should stay
away from Karasuma, too.
Huh?!
When you talk to Karasuma,
you always seem happy.
But if he's a cheating
dog who can't be trusted,
you have to stop.
No! You don't understand!
Karasuma's not like that!
He's no player!
Really? But how
could that be true?
You just told me that all
guys were the same, Tenma.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Why do you always
have to be so smart?!
It's hopeless...! Yakumo
always beats me with logic!
But, I can't give up now!
It's my job as her big sister
to protect Yakumo
from creeps like Harima!
Wow. I've never
seen her like this.
She must be worried.
Uh, Tenma...
I'll do what you want, 'kay?
Big Sister Power Activate!
Just do what I say!
No ifs, ands, or buts, you got
it...?! It's for the best!
Oh, Sis, I just wanted to
talk to him about animals...
Still, it is really sweet,
your "Big Sister Power!"
Aw, it's so beautiful!
Harima!
Uh... Hey, what's up?
Come here for a minute.
We've got things to discuss!
Unresolved things!
Be my partner in
the scavenger hunt,
and we can talk
things out as we play.
Is this Tenma's way
of saying she wants
to be alone with me tonight?
Well?
Sure...
Together we're team ninja.
Yes! My famous
homemade curry's done!
Yakumo! Dinner is served!
Fill your belly
with my creation!
Oh, Hanai.
You took too long,
so we started without you.
Wow, this tastes amazing
for frozen curry, Akira.
You really went all out.
I'm pretty much awesome.
Want some, dude?
Hey, guys, we've got
after-dinner coffee!
That's really nice,
Tenma. Thank you.
I helped, too!
I ground all the beans up!
What, you want a cookie?
Mmm, it's so decadent.
This is the Tea Club.
Here ya go, Imadori.
Hey, thanks!
Some of Tenma's fresh coffee!
Man, am I lucky
to be here or what?!
Here, yours is special.
I get it...
She's trying to send me a
message with these beans...
Coffee beans are strong and
there's a whole lot of 'em,
just like her feelings for me!
All right!
Let's draw straws and get our
partners for the scavenger hunt!
Okay, everyone,
here are the rules
for the scavenger
hunt, so listen up!
There are a number of shrines
scattered throughout the forest.
Take a charm from one
and bring it back here.
Why don't we just roast s'mores?
Because we're not pansies.
Right! First team, get ready!
I'm a little scared, Eri.
How about you?
I'm fine!
Oh, Yakumo!
And go!
Please be careful!
Don't get lost!
Next!
You ready for action, partner?
Hands off, creep...!
Try that again and you won't be
coming out of the woods alive!
And go!
Hey, Miko, stop! Wait for me!
Next!
Don't worry, Yakumo!
I will catch up to you!
And go!
Well, Harima, this is it.
No turning back...
It's not gonna be
too easy, ya know?
Yeah.
Are you ready for this?
Heh... You have no
idea how ready I am.
All right, we've got a lot
to do and no time to waste.
Go!
So tonight we're gonna settle
"unresolved issues,"
huh, Tenma...?
I know what that means!
We're finally gonna be a couple!
I didn't know it
was supposed to rain!
You think everybody
else is okay?!
I'm sure they're fine.
Let's find some shelter.
I just wanted to
get him out here
so I could tell him to
stay away from Yakumo...
but now... Oh, Harima! Look out!
Thanks!
Almost lost my head there!
Well, you are pretty tall!
Tenma!
I didn't see that
hole back there
or I would have
warned you. Sorry!
It's... not your fault, Harima.
Hang on, okay.
Well, I guess
for the time being,
we'll have to call a truce.
I never knew there was an old,
abandoned school out here.
Here... Warm yourself up.
Tonight turned out to
be a real mess... Sorry.
Don't be. It's not
your fault... Okay?
Harima! Oh, no, snap out of it!
If this is a dream,
I don't wanna wake up...
Hey, Harima...
Yeah?
Now, listen up...
When you love someone,
there are rules to follow.
If you're in...
love with a girl, she's
the only one you can date.
I don't want anyone's
feelings to get hurt.
I think you're a
really sweet guy...
In fact, I know you are.
I do hope you're listening
to what I'm saying...
A girl wants her true love to
only have eyes for her.
Do you understand now, Harima?
You can't date more
than one girl at a time...
It just isn't right!
You don't have to tell me...
Don't you worry, Tenma.
You're the only girl in my eyes.
Yes... I understand...
I promise you...
I'll follow the rules.
Glad to hear it...!
We connected tonight, huh?
Is this really happening?
Could this finally be it?!
Crap! Tenma must
be catching a cold!
No wonder! She's
soaked from head to toe.
I gotta get her out
of those wet clothes fast!
But if I suggest it,
then she's gonna think
I'm a total pervert...!
Still, I can't just let
the love of my life get sick.
What kind of guy
does that make me?
But how can I get her
to strip without looking
like Mr. Pervert?!
Come on, think!
Yes.
Huh?
Get your clothes off...
right now.
You can't be serious.
Here, lemme explain...
Is... he joking?
No, he's dead serious!
Harima's nothing but
a filthy-minded,
two-timing
perverted sleaze!
I never told anyone...
but he made a pass at
me back at the beach club
and he wasn't wearing any pants!
That's awful...! I'll stop him!
Wait a sec...
Tenma's smart enough
to see through that creep.
She'll probably punch him
and then give him a
swift kick in the pants!
I've got them off, Harima.
What...?! Is she crazy?!
Okay, you can turn around now.
Uh, right.
Pretty lucky I found
these curtains, huh?
They don't smell great,
but they'll keep us warm
until our clothes dry out.
You know, we look pretty goofy
in these things,
but if they'll keep us
from getting sick...
This doesn't change anything.
He still can't be trusted.
You really think so?
Can I ask you something?
Who's the girl that you like?
Come on, don't be shy.
You can tell me.
Uh, who...?
Oh, the girl, right...
So you really wanna
know, huh? Wow!
Stop laughing
and get to the point!
Yes! Tell me, tell me, tell me!
Well, you see... kinda funny...
you asked, 'cause...
Hey! Speak up and stop
beating around the bush!
Who are you in
love with, silly-head?
They're acting
like nine-year-olds!
I'm... in... love... with...
you... Tenma.
What...? Can't hear you!
Okay, just whisper
it in my ear then!
Well... Who is it, huh?
Wait a minute... She means...
It's simple...
When a girl's in love,
she wants her guy
to be the first one
to say "I love you."...
So you say it first...
Can you do that for me, Harima?
Uh... Is everything okay?
Oh, no! Are you still cold?!
The fire's dying down... Crap!
Don't worry, Tenma!
You'll be good
and comfy in no time!
Just gimme a minute, okay!
Need some firewood fast!
Think that wall's
gonna do just fine!
All right! Somethin'
else to burn!
This'll keep us warm
for a while...! Aw, yeah!
What the...? Somethin's
got the other end of this.
Maybe it's a mouse,
a real heavy one...
If it's not a mouse,
it's gotta be a rat... Big one!
No rat's gonna get between me
and my special night!
What did you find over there?
Uh, nothing! Hey,
the rain's stopped.
I bet our clothes are pretty
dry. Wanna head back?
Sure... I'll get dressed.
You shouldn't have been
eavesdropping like that.
That was karma getting you back.
It's not fair!
You were listening, too!
Agh! This was a mistake!
I'm getting out of here!
Uh, wait for me!
We're back!
I saw Imadori.
What happened to him?
He learned a valuable
lesson... about hands...
You always keep them
to yourself... or else.
Guess you got grabby.
Nighty-night, pal.
Where's Yakumo?
Why isn't she back?!
Has anyone seen her...?
I'm so worried!
Yakumo! I'm coming!
Welcome back.
Uh, look...
We got caught in the rain...
and our clothes got drenched...!
Got any we could borrow?
Sure do.
But how did you...?
I told you I was awesome.
Oh, summer vacation's ending!
It went by so fast and
I still want to play...!
Next time on School Rumble:
"Mid-Summer Giraffe's Night Out!
End of Summer Panic Party!
Summer's Over--Back to School!"
What's gonna happen?!