Schoo--
School Rumble will be
coming up in just a moment!
He's here!
What a bastard...!
I can't believe he had
the nerve to come back!
Get him!
It looks like you've
been dumped...
Why did you come here, fool?
There's no place for you
here anymore, outcast!
Time to die!
What's the matter, Harima,
not running away, are you?
You turned into a
coward as well as a loser?
Karasuma.
Very impressive.
I guess some guys
will go to any lengths
to eat a homemade box lunch.
I waded through a sea of blood
and fought my way back
from hell itself to beat you!
You're too late.
Tsukamoto's heart belongs
to me now, for all eternity.
Te... Tenma!
I'm afraid you've
lost... Harima.
Cursed hellspawn!
There can be no mercy
for the likes of you...
a twisted obscenity who plays
with people's hearts like toys!
It's sad, really...
not too long ago you
ruled over this campus,
until I took it
all away from you...
Your precious Tsukamoto
became my plaything,
and I tortured you as
a cat does a mouse...
until I drove you screaming
to the ends of the earth...
it's such a shame...
I pity you from the
bottom of my heart.
Save your pity...!
It's time for the final battle!
I'm taking back Tenma...
and reclaiming my rightful
place on this campus!
You don't know when
to give up, do you?
Dare you accept my challenge?!
Let's do this!
Take this, fool...! Ha!
You must know you
cannot defeat me.
Are you sure about that, punk?
H... How... How did you
become... so powerful?
Suffering...
My suffering tempered me.
You have... won... uh...
Tenma!
Speak to me!
Am I dreaming?
No, no... it's really me...
Everything is
gonna be all right.
It can't be...
He said... that you...
Oh, Harima, is it really you...?
It's me... I promise...
Our torment is over...
We have our whole
future to live for now.
Oh, Harima.
I love you.
And I you.
Yum... yummy...
Yum... yummy.
Oh, Karasuma, I hope
you're enjoying the rice balls.
They're not too salty, are they?
That's awesome!
Oh, Karasuma, is the rice ball
rolled the way you like it?
That's awesome!
Oh, Karasuma,
I'm really enjoying this,
but I hope it isn't boring you.
So awesome!
Wow, this is quite
a piece of work...
Well done, it's
superb for a first effort.
Yeah...?
Tell me, what made you
decide to write a comic book?
I... I'd rather...
No, no, no, that's all right.
Forget I asked!
Can you say what made you
decide to bring your work to us?
Well, I'm a really big
fan of the artist, Nijo.
I've been reading his stuff ever
since this company
started running it.
So that's it...!
I thought so...!
There's a definite
influence here,
especially the way
you draw the eyes.
There is...? That's exactly
what I was going for!
Then I should tell you about our
Jou Nijou talent competition
for new artists
that's coming up.
Mr. Nijou himself is going
to be on the panel of judges.
Take my advice, you
oughta submit your work...
At the very least, I'll bet you
get an honorable mention.
Wow, do you really think so?
With an award like
that under your belt,
the next step would be
to get you a weekly serial.
And you're young, so you don't
have to rush into anything.
I don't know what to say!
Mr. Nijou's work has been
such an inspiration to me!
Artistically, I was totally
lost until I read his stuff.
And to think he
might read something
of mine is a real honor.
Hey, man, I know how you feel!
Nijou's "Genroku
Defense Force" is one
of the most exciting
things I've ever read!
Yeah, that was my favorite...!
It rocked...!
Did you edit that book?
No wonder you and me are
on the same wavelength!
I loved that part
where the team sneaks
into the enemy's territory.
Yeah, only no one's there,
so they sneak back.
That was great...!
Yeah, that book was
huge, it was a total hit!
Well, speak of the devil, Mr.
Nijou himself just walked in!
Morning, Mr. Nijou...
Thanks for coming by.
Tell you what, I'll
deliver this myself... huh?
No, this was a mistake.
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?!
What's the matter?
Where're you going?
Wow, it's really coming down.
Aw, it's just a shower,
it'll blow over.
Tenma's got that
dopey look on her face.
I wonder why.
Oh, it's nothing.
You're not foolin' anybody.
We already know.
You've been eating lunch with
Karasuma and getting very cozy.
But how...? Who told you...?
How could you
have figured it out?
That's easy, we're geniuses.
And you're obvious.
Of course...
Hey, you...
What are you doing out
in the rain like this?
It was the only
dream that I had left...
The only path that still
remained open to me...
Become an artist...
Get famous...
And then, maybe someday, she'd
be walking along the street...
The girl that I loved...
And she'd step into a little
bookstore on the corner,
and there would
be one of my comics,
and she'd just
happen to pick it up...
She'd smile and
say, "Interesting,"
and that would be enough.
Just the thought of
that made me so happy...
That wasn't too much
to ask for... was it?
Oh, wow.
Now that I get a look
at you... you're very young.
And very handsome as well.
You're gonna catch cold...
Why don't you come to
my place and warm up...
Uh, what's your name?
My pen name is Hario Harima...
I wanted something that would
be easy for kids to remember.
I don't now...
I think rice balls every day
might be getting a little
monotonous, don't you?
What?!
I guess that depends on how
much Karasuma likes rice balls.
Maybe he's just too polite
to say anything about it.
You're right.
He already said his
favorite dish was curry;
that's how all
this got started...
I bet the only reason
he hasn't said anything is
because he's so nice and
doesn't wanna hurt my feelings!
Oh, stupid, stupid, stupid!
How could I not have
noticed this sooner?
Dumb me...
I've been taking advantage of
his kindness this whole time...
I'm such a yutz.
Right.
Tomorrow I'm starting all over
again and having Yakumo
make curry like
I planned in the first place
You mean you make
your sister cook for him?
Huh?!
You know, Tenma, if you
really want to win his heart,
then you have to do the cooking.
But I can't even boil
water without burning it.
As long as the main
ingredient's love, you're good.
You think so?
You're right!
If all it takes is love,
then I can do it, no sweat!
Okay...! Karasuma,
next time the curry is on me!
To tell the truth...
When I first saw you...
I felt like we had
some kind of connection...
"He's like me,"
I said to myself...
I've been dumped, too...
Not all that long ago...
These are men's
clothes, all right.
Just make yourself at home.
Can I get you anything to drink?
A beer or something?
Ohhh, I'm out
of the good stuff...
And cash is a little
tight this month...
We'll just have to
make do with this...
Can't be helped...
Here.
Well, I don't think I can...
Oh, gosh...
I bet you don't
even drink yet...
Actually...
I meant, I don't think I can get
drunk on something that weak.
In the end...
I guess I was
just fooling myself...
I thought we'd live
in a cozy little house
in the country somewhere...
have ourselves
a couple of kids...
And on her birthday,
I'd bring her champagne
and flowers every year.
And every year
she'd be surprised...
But it was just a dream...
just a stupid, fleeting dream!
What's this?
Is it important?
This junk...?!
This garbage...? This trash?!
No! Stop it!
Throw that thing away...!
It belongs in the garbage dump
with the rest of
my broken dreams!
You know, it's possible to fall
in love more than just once.
For example...
Your next love...
could be right here.
Well?
I can't...
Oh... I didn't mean to...
It's all right,
don't worry about it.
Good night.
I'm so sorry.
Dear Hario Harima...
I read your story...
I may not know much,
but I think it's very good...
You have a lot of talent...
So you shouldn't give up...
I'm leaving some
money on the table.
Buy yourself a hot meal, okay...
I can't take her money...!
I'm already in her debt...
And after she said she
was short on cash... huh?
There's more...
Of course, it's not
as good as Nijou's
"Genroku Defense Force"...
I love his work!
Ya... hooo!
Okay, that's all
the ingredients!
Now, sis, are you sure you
wanna do this yourself...?
I'll be glad to help you...
Relax, I'm fine!
It won't mean anything
if I don't do it myself!
You go take it easy.
Watch TV, or take
a bath or something!
Well, okay...
Yeah...! And here we go!
I cut my finger!
I've got the bandages!
Uhhh... so what's next?
Make sure it's not wet
when it goes in the oil...
Yakumo...! Help...! It exploded!
Hey, brother, you've been
around here a lot, lately.
Yeah, well, what can I say.
I really don't have
anything else to do.
I did it!
Beef curry made with love!
Okay...
Let's see how it tastes.
Well, at least it's different.
Hey there, Iori...! Take a taste
and tell me what you think.
Oh, come on.
At least try.
Iori!
What are we having for
dinner tonight, mommy?
What would you
like to have, honey?
Pancakes!
All right, all right!
This is the third
day in a row...
Hario...? I left
some lunch money
for you on the table, okay?
No matter what I tell myself...
I keep going back to
that woman's apartment.
What am I doing, anyway?
Iori...! Where are you...?
Come back, kitty!
Tenma?!
What are the odds...? I run
into her here, of all places.
She seems to be
looking for something.
Could it be me...? But I can't
let her find me like this...
I'm not the Kenji Harima
she used to know...
I've hit rock bottom...
I've even started
going bald from sorrow...
I don't want her to see me...
It's better for us both if
we just pass each other by...
Farewell, Tenma.
Iori!
Iori...!Iori!
It's Tenma's cat...
It's being washed
away by the current...
Crap... I want to help...
but we mustn't have any
more to do with each other...
Oh please, somebody!
Somebody help me!
Please save him...!
Save my kitty!
Please! Help me!
Someone else'll help!
Iori!
Iori...
Oh, thank you, thank you!
Go ahead...
Mock the ruin of
a man I've become.
Say, you wouldn't
happen to be...
You're not...
A water imp?!
Uh, water imp, right.
Thank you again, Mr. Water Imp.
Rice balls again?!
She just doesn't get it!
But she keeps ruining the curry!
Then there's only
one thing to do!
And what's that?!
Next time on School Rumble,
I have a secret plan!
That's not what
the title card says!
Cause it's a secret!