School Rumble is
about to begin after this.
Hey, is this yours? Holy crap!
I actually spoke to Tsukamoto!
This must be my lucky day!
Itoko! Pass me the pepper!
A "please" would be nice,
and that's Ms.Itoko to you.
Come on!
You don't really expect
me to call you that, do you?
Of course I do.
And when you learn some
manners, I'll pass the pepper.
Pretty please, Ms. Itoko!
Much better.
Geez! It doesn't
matter to you, does it?
I mean, it's embarrassing
for me to call you "Ms."
Well, get used to it.
By the way Kenji,
there's something I've
been meaning to ask you.
Have you made any progress
asking out Tenma Tsukamoto yet?
What?
Why would you ask me a question
like that all of a sudden?
Well, what do you know?
This pepper shaker was empty!
Don't try to change the subject.
Since I'm acting
as your guardian,
I need to know what's
going on in your life, Kenji.
If I'm the one paying the bills,
and you're living under my roof,
and in a comfortable
apartment, I might add,
I think that alone gives me
more than enough right to know.
Damn! I move in with my cousin,
and all of a sudden she
thinks she's my mother.
I've got to give you
credit for leaving home
and trying to live on your own,
but when you found out
how hard that was--
Have you forgotten I was the
only one willing to take you in?
Well, don't you think you
owe me something for that?
I can't believe it.
You're forcing me?
You catch on quick.
But I'm sure you're so grateful
you would've told me anyway.
You've got to admit,
she's really cute.
She's got that whole
"girl-next-door" vibe about her.
A real traditional
beauty, I'd say.
Huh?
I bet that's what
you like about her, huh?
What? My wallet!
How did you--? When did you--?
You only have two
dollars to your name,
but somehow found the money
to laminate this photo. My, my.
Uh, that picture, it isn't mine!
It belongs to one of my buddies!
He asked me to keep
it for him! I swear!
I guess this fake ID in here
doesn't belong to you, either.
What's the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
Oh, never mind.
That school boy stammer
of yours says plenty.
Let's see.
The ideal date for the
typical girl-next-door
would be the
typical boy-next-door.
But a bad-boy with a goatee?
Not so much, I'm afraid.
I better eat this
before this gets cold!
Kenji, do you want
a little fried rice
with your black pepper?
Well, that looked painful.
That was nothing!
You know, I've got reasons for
the way I dress and my goatee!
So tell me.
No! You're being
really nosy, you know that?
Just stop it!
You're acting all weird.
It's freaking me out!
Normally, you don't give a
damn about what girls I date,
but now you can't stop
asking me about my love life.
What's the deal?
Don't you have
anything else better to do?
Hey, you're up to
something, aren't you?
Well, maybe.
Honestly, I'm just curious why
you're interested in this girl.
My cousin brags for years
that he's "his own man"
and not tied down to one girl
and now there's one
he can't even talk to.
Sounds like love to me.
I'm concerned about you.
Come on.
I can't believe you're
making me do this!
Alright! I'll tell you.
This is how it all
started with her.
Two orders of miso pork, please!
No pork for me,
Sis, just veggies.
Well, come on,
let's hear it. Spit it out.
Wow, you don't beat
around the bush, do you?
Why don't you
admit you're worried
about your little cousin?
Fine. I'll admit it.
I'm worried.
Hmph. I'm so touched.
I'll never forget it.
I was fifteen the
first time I saw her.
All the punks in this
neighborhood are so weak!
What I wouldn't give
for a real challenge!
Please, please don't hurt me!
Keep quiet now, sweetie!
Excuse me, Miss? Are you okay?
Didn't matter who it was.
I just wanted to
beat someone up.
Uh.
You saved my life.
Thank you so much.
And that's how I met her.
I've been hooked
ever since then.
I'm gonna carve
you like a turkey!
You say somethin'?
Uh, are you--
You're-you're bleeding!
I didn't even feel it!
Great, what now?
Can't call the police.
With my record, they'd
just haul me off to jail.
You're coming with me, 'kay?
Just taking you to a safe place.
I won't try anything
funny, I swear.
Man, she's light.
Does this kid eat anything?
You know, this is the kind
of thing I could
get into trouble for.
She looks so innocent.
Just who are you, mystery girl?
I can't eat anymore. I'm full.
Uh! She's just a kid!
Hello? Come on!
Get up and get
out of here, okay?
Can't believe I'm saying this,
but up close, this girl
is actually pretty cute.
She's cute enough to kiss.
Sorry, kid,
but can you blame me?
Your lips just look so kissable.
If another guy
was in my position,
he'd do the same thing, right?
Arggh! What the--? What is this?
Some kind of joke or something?
Pretending to be half-asleep?
Knock it off!
Believe it or not,
I'm not as dumb as I look!
I love you.
Huh?
Are--? Are you really serious?
Uh. Of course you're
not really serious!
You're still half
asleep, aren't you?
Uh, I'm sorry!
Wh-where am I?
Look, I know what
you're thinking, okay?
This looks weird.
But before you
scream or say anything,
please let me
explain a few things!
Hey, no need to get physical!
Look, you're not
making this any easier
by not saying anything,
you know that, kid?
Hey!
Just listen to me, okay?
Nothing happened.
I didn't do anything, I swear.
What the hell was that?
This--this girl.
I love her.
Um, thanks, for saving me.
I really wish I could
be more grateful,
but you tried to
take advantage of me,
so thanks for
nothing, Mr. Pervert!
I have to see her again,
but how can I?
I know.
I'll just become somebody else.
Someone she won't recognize.
Yeah, that's it.
So you started
dressing like a thug
and went with the
old goatee disguise.
How original.
I couldn't think
of anything else!
It was the best that I could do!
You know how hard
it is to live like this?
Hiding your face
from the one you love?
Try to understand!
I understand!
It's that girl's
fault if you ask me!
You know, for some reason, that
story sounds really familiar.
Itoko! You knew
she was back there!
Come on, it's reunion time.
Don't do it! No!
Huh?
One order of miso pork!
Bon appetit!
Yay!
I'm gonna eat
the whole thing!
Delish!
Damn Itoko!
She knew Tenma was there!
She just wanted to embarrass the
hell out of me in front of her!
Man, that Ms. Itoko's something.
Talk about a real woman!
Wouldn't it be great
if all female teachers
looked that sexy?
Huh?
Looks like someone left a
dirty footprint on this wall.
How thoughtless!
I'll clean it up.
Did Harima seem scared of her?
Yeah, but why
would a thug like him
be scared of a teacher like her?
Okay, now it's all clean.
Please have some.
We've brewed the
Tea Club's famous milk tea,
plus there's raspberry pie.
It's delicious.
Think so? That's great.
I thought that you might
not like your tea too sweet,
so I took a chance.
I sprinkled in a little
cinnamon to enhance the flavor.
What do you say, Yakumo?
Does this mean you're interested
in joining the Tea Club?
I know I speak for everyone when
I say we'd love to have you.
Right, Miss Itoko?
She'd make a fine
addition to the club.
Look, I'm just the advisor
and I really have no
say in its operation.
But I've got to ask.
Just what in the world is that
young man doing on the floor?
Oh please! Oh please!
Please I beg of you!
Please, Ms. Itoko,
allow me to join the Tea Club!
Having tea with
Yakumo would be wonderful!
Hanai, you're so honest.
Wait a minute.
Don't you have the
Aikido Club to go to?
What are you doing here?
Well, ma'am.
I really wanted
Yakumo to join but,
you see--She wouldn't have it!
Yakumo's been invited
to join a lot of the
school's most popular clubs,
but Hanai chases after
her like a puppy dog.
He always ends up
disrupting their activities
and embarrassing
Yakumo in the process.
Please forgive me, Yakumo!
Uh, it's okay, Hanai.
Wow, this guy is
completely hopeless.
Reminds me of someone.
As I said earlier,
I'm just the faculty advisor.
At this school, we
respect the independence
of both the students
and their clubs.
All membership decisions
are left to the
chairperson's discretion.
It's up to you, Chairperson.
Mhm.
No way.
What? That's it?
I don't understand! Why?
Hanai, tell me?
Do you even like tea?
Not at all!
I told you he was honest.
Not liking tea is
beside the point!
"Having tea" is just another
term for a social gathering,
i.e., people getting
together, like on a date,
and I want to date Yakumo!
So you see, I should be given
the chance to join the club!
Oh, I see.
Uh, you do?
Perhaps, but if
he wants to join us,
first he'll have to pass a test.
Pass a test?
A taste test.
Taste them and tell me
which one Yakumo brewed.
Are--are you nuts?
How should I know
which one she brewed?
That's impossi-
Let me make this
easier to understand.
The taste of tea
mirrors its maker's heart.
So if you truly
know Yakumo's heart,
this will be an easy test.
Say, is that true?
A real man never backs
down from a challenge!
Only a coward would turn
his back and run away!
I am a real man and
I accept your challenge!
Akira, what kind of tea is that?
It's got a pinch of
hot green pepper in it.
Oh.
My--my whole face is on fire!
This sensation comes
from only one flavor.
The flavor of sweet, sweet love!
This is it! Yakumo
brewed this one!
You're sure?
Huh?
I'll try this one, just in case.
Oh, it's--it's like
hot blood pumping
through the heart
of someone in love!
And that is the
proof of pure love!
Yakumo made this one, too!
Yakumo's heart is in only one
of the two teas, so which is it?
This--this is crazy.
How can I not know the true
nature of Yakumo's heart?
Why? Why can't I tell?
Disqualified.
You didn't show him any mercy.
He didn't deserve any.
So, Yakumo.
Now that you've seen
how we handle people
who don't take tea seriously,
welcome to the club.
Uh!
Oh good, you're finally awake!
Where's Yakumo?
Sorry. She went home already.
Here, I made you
some sweet milk tea.
It'll get rid of that bad taste.
Why, thank you.
Akira said you can come
and go as long as you abide
by the club's posted rules.
Takano said that?
Let's enjoy tea together
again sometime soon, okay?
Hm.
Guess I owe you one.
Oh, Akira.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I misjudged you.
Did you now?
In order for the class to learn
about a little something called
teamwork, our homeroom
assignment today
is to play a friendly
game of softball!
I think I'll pass.
Softball? But I'm
just so bad at sports.
Tenma, my sweet.
That sad look doesn't match
that beautiful face of yours.
It's a beautiful day,
so let's not waste it!
Let's get out there and
forge the bonds of friendship
and teamwork with sweat!
Come on, Tenma, cheer up!
Yeah, let's do it!
Harima's on fire!
Do you think he's
trying to blend in?
I had almost forgotten that
sports are a great outlet,
where delinquents can channel
their aggression productively.
Oh, awesome!
That's great! Way to go!
She certainly sent that
one flying, didn't she?
Mikoto's really good at this.
Time to defend our lead.
You think you can handle this?
How tough can it be?
Besides, I just
learned a few pointers
from someone on
the softball team.
You just learned?
A few pointers?
So stand back! Watch this!
Boy, Eri sure is a fast learner!
It's hard to believe she's
never played sports before.
Third!
Good catch, Akira!
Gotta hand it to you.
You're quick.
Your form could use a little
improvement if you ask me,
but your speed is impressive.
Those three were incredible.
Not only on the field but
in the looks department, too!
Totally hot.
Oh, man! Look at that photo op!
I can't believe
I forgot my freaking camera!
Okay, now's my chance,
so don't screw up!
Hit the ball and Karasuma
will finally notice me!
Strike three!
I got it! I got it!
Oh, Miko, why do I have to
always be so clumsy? Why?
You shouldn't get so down,
especially on my chest.
Instead of wasting time crying,
why don't you
practice a little bit?
You're mean, Eri!
Anyone ever tell you that?
That's the way I am.
Look, Tenma,
there's a lot at stake here.
The score is tied.
We can't let them gain
any points in this inning,
and that means no screw-ups!
Hey, hey, there's no reason
to get rude about this.
Before we started, you thought
this game was a waste of time.
If we have to play,
let's win at least.
Well, bases are loaded.
How 'bout letting me pitch, huh?
What are you doing here?
Thought you were going to skip?
Yeah, I was going to,
but then all my girlfriends
wanted to see me play.
Chicks always dig the pitcher.
Do they now?
We're all rooting for you!
Win the game for us, Imadori!
Sorry, our team
roster's already full.
It's not anymore.
Someone's sitting this one out.
Tenma?
Uh, yeah.
He's a much better choice
if you really want to win.
Of course, you know those
are her words, not mine.
Tenma, you pushover.
Hey, isn't it best to
cut the weakest players?
Okay. Have it your way.
This first one's
just a practice pitch--
Though some mistake
it for a fastball!
Hah! It's so slow,
it's putting me to sleep!
Dude! Oh! Man!
I think practice is over.
Just lay still now, Imadori.
Is he breathing?
Kay, so, we need a new pitcher.
It's the manager!
He's gonna pick a new pitcher!
What manager?
I didn't know we had one!
Pitcher Tsukamoto.
What?
Me? Are you sure?
But, Karasuma.
I really don't think
I've got what it takes!
Miss Tsukamoto.
There's something
I want to tell you.
You don't need to worry about
what others may think of you.
Just believe in yourself and
give it everything you've got.
At least that's what Eri
Sawachika wanted me to tell you.
Wow! You said that?
Just drop it okay!
Oh Karasuma.
I'm so moved by what you said!
I really, really am!
Karasuma, I'll do my best!
Hey you, glove boy!
If I strike out, her team's
gonna win, right?
Uh, yeah, so no
pressure or anything.
Look at that fastball!
Uh. Where's the ball?
It's a dead ball!
Runner on third walked in!
And that's the game, guys!
He's so heavy!
Just take some
deep breaths, Nara.
Has anyone checked
Harima's pulse?
What did you
think you were doing?
Didn't you hear me?
I said no screw-ups!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Well at least it's over now.
Hey, who's this guy
that Tenma's in love with?
Huh? She's looking over here.
Could it be me? Is it me?
Next time on School Rumble:
"Survival After School!
Arrival When Confessing!
Hospital For Two!"
I have to tell
you this right now!