(dramatic music)
(thunder rumbling)
(warbling electronic music)
(upbeat pop music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(ominous music)
The time has come
at last, my lord.
All of the necessary
preparations have
been completed.
(centipede squelching)
(sirens wailing)
(rocks rumbling)
(crowd shouting)
(siren wailing)
(Momiji gasps)
- [Daitetsu] Hmm.
So do you sense anything?
Oh, oh, well,
it certainly
doesn't seem to feel
like a typical Aragami to me.
No, duh!
Huh?
I could tell that
just by looking at it!
What we wanna know is what is it
and why the stupid thing's
hanging on the outside
of a skyscraper!
(Azusa laughs)
Hmm.
Well, I'm sorry.
Why do you always expect me
to know what they're thinking?
(crowd chattering)
(ominous music)
It is.
All right, but it is.
And I don't wanna be fired...
(dramatic music)
- [Momiji] Can you feel it?
I can't ignore it, an ominous
premonition of catastrophe!
(clock bell chiming)
(birds chirping)
(bird squawks)
Huh.
(girls giggling)
- [Red-Haired Girl] I think I
might get an F on that test.
Really?
I have got to
study some more.
Study boys, you mean.
(girls laughing)
Hey, she scores!
(squawks)
(girls laughing)
- [Girl] That scores an F
in coordination (laughs).
- [Girl] With the fall damage?
(Kusanagi chuckles)
Oh, Momiji!
(girls laughing)
Oh, oh!
(Momiji laughs)
Hmm.
Momiji!
(gentle music)
(girls laughing)
(Momiji laughing)
Huh? (grunts)
- [Kaede] You've
been watching over me
for a long, long
time, haven't you?
You've been watching over me,
protecting me all my life!
Thank you.
Leave me alone.
It seems that I couldn't
protect you after all,
could I, Kaede?
Huh! (grunts)
Uh!
(faint rumbling)
There's something
moving underground.
What is it?
(crowd chattering)
(rocks clattering)
(crowd screaming)
(ominous music)
(glass clatters)
- [Woman] Oh, my God!
(man shouting)
(woman screams)
Is that...
Oh, my God!
Whoa, whoa!
What is that? (screams)
Oh, no!
(centipede squelching)
I wanna go home!
Oh, no!
(rocks rumbling)
(centipede squelching)
- [Red-Haired Man] Oh,
come on, get outta here!
Oh, my God, oh, my God!
(wind whooshing)
(Murakumo laughs)
This is your work, isn't it?
Well.
So we meet again, Murakumo.
What are you up to this time?
- [Murakumo] (laughs) It's
none of your business, traitor.
I see, but I still owe
you a little payback
from the last time we met.
(skin snaps)
(shouting)
Come on!
(dramatic music)
Hmm.
(shouting)
(energy whooshes)
Haven't I told you that
I have eight mitamas?
There's no way that an
imperfect soul like you
can defeat me, Kusanagi.
Shut up and fight! (shouts)
(energy whooshing)
Mm, mm!
(Kusanagi screaming)
(Kusanagi groans)
Was that your best effort?
I would've thought that you
would do better than that.
(Kusanagi groaning)
I'm beginning to think
Princess Kushinada
thinks too highly
of you. (laughs)
(Momiji groaning weakly)
(students chattering)
(Momiji gasps)
What's wrong?
We've got to go home now.
(Momiji gasps)
(crowd chattering)
(siren wailing)
Wow, so there's this...
Oh, my gosh.
Are they ever gonna...
There's another one.
Police... I mean, I don't know.
It was on the news, are they...
Mm.
It's the same
as the other one.
Oh!
Another giant centipede skin?
This is getting
ridiculous, what's it mean?
(ominous whooshing)
I wouldn't either.
I have no idea.
Matsudaira.
Sir.
Perhaps it's just
my imagination, but doesn't
that thing look like
a huge Shimenawa, or
sacred rice straw rope
that's been hung on the
side of that building?
- [Azusa] You're right, sir.
(siren wailing)
So it appeared in Akasaka
right after the
incident in Ikebukuro,
and it wound its shell around
the building the same way.
I wonder what the Aragami
are up to this time.
I'm afraid we don't know
the answer to that yet.
- [Momiji] I can't
believe I can't
help you this time.
Check this out.
Oh, that's fascinating.
I wish I didn't have
a big test tomorrow.
It really is.
(laughs) Well, I
think you can trust us
to handle this one
without you, okay?
Okay, but if something happens,
please call me right away.
What, my test (laughs),
don't worry about that.
I'm a real whiz at
mathematics (laughs).
Okay, goodnight, sir.
(moaning)
(cheerful music)
Oh, I am such a liar.
(Kusanagi grunting)
(gasps)
(peaceful music)
Hmm (sighs).
(Kusanagi groans loudly)
(gasps)
Kusanagi, is that you, Kusanagi?
(gasping)
(gasps)
(Kusanagi groans)
- [Yoshiki] This is fascinating.
- [Azusa] I can't wait
to get back to the lab.
Hmm, mm.
(suspenseful music)
- [Ryoko] Is
something wrong, sir?
Huh, no.
(dynamic electronic music)
(peaceful music)
- [Kusanagi] Kaede, Kaede,
I, I want,
huh, oh!
Oh, thank goodness
you're finally awake.
Uh.
Eh.
Why are you staring
at my face like that?
Uh, did you bandage
my wounds, Momiji?
Of course, I was so
surprised to find you
out in the garden, I never even
thought of calling a doctor.
But I don't understand,
you're so strong.
How did you get hurt like this?
Hmm.
Oh, no,
it wasn't that nasty
Murakumo, was it?
Is this related
to what's going on
in Ikebukuro and
Akasaka somehow?
Well, hey, I was
right, wasn't I?
Wait a second,
tell me everything!
I can fight with you,
Kusanagi, you know that I can.
Please, come on, why won't
you tell me what's going on?
(Kusanagi grunts)
Huh, hey, wait a minute, you
can't go anywhere like that.
(Kusanagi grunts)
Kusanagi!
(traffic rumbling)
(horn honks)
(rocks rumbling)
(dramatic music)
(Kusanagi grunting)
- [Murakumo] I'm beginning
to think Princess Kushinada
thinks too highly of you.
- [Kusanagi] You said
Princess Kushinada.
No, there's no way that
Kaede could still be...
(centipede rumbling)
(centipede squelching)
Hmm.
(thunder rumbling)
(Kusanagi grunting)
(wind whistling)
(Kusanagi shouts)
Hmm, oh, not you again.
But that's all right.
I already finished my
latest masterpiece.
Watch closely.
Huh?
(energy warbling)
(somber music)
(laughs)
(energy beams whirring)
Hey, look at that!
Wow!
What's going on?
Sacred ropes
surrounding three buildings.
It's got to be some kind of
incantation or barrier spell.
Behold, imperfect soul, the
hidden realm of the Aragami.
These three defiled human towers
standing in perfect triangle
have been transformed
into a nexus of
incredible power.
Ask me if I care,
you freak! (grunts)
Do you really intend to fight
after what I did to
you last time? (laughs)
(rocks rumbling)
(Kusanagi exclaims)
(Kusanagi shouts)
The huge centipede
that encircled the
Shinjuku Sumitomo building
has just moved for the
first time since it cast off
the giant... (Momiji gasps)
(Kusanagi grunts)
(Kusanagi shouting)
I guess you're just a victim
of too much self-confidence.
You simply don't have
the skill to fight me
on equal terms, imperfect soul.
(Kusanagi shouting)
(centipede squelching)
(rocks rumbling)
(Kusanagi shouts)
(high-pitched whirring)
(Kusanagi shouting)
(tires screeching)
What?
Oh!
Murakumo!
It can't be!
As we feared, he's on
the Aragamis' side.
(suspenseful music)
(crowd chattering)
Oh, gee.
Kusanagi!
- [Man] Where did it come
from, where'd the light go?
Look!
It's like three buildings
like that.
I don't know.
(energy whirring)
(Momiji gasping)
I can feel it, the power
flowing in the sky.
(Kusanagi shouting)
(energy whooshing)
Huh?
(dramatic music)
I've told you before, there
is an enormous difference
in power between you and I.
(Kusanagi screaming)
(dramatic music)
Kusanagi!
(Kusanagi shouts)
(groaning)
(Kusanagi growls)
(gasps) Kusanagi!
Momiji!
(Momiji screams)
Momiji! (grunts)
Hmm.
(Kusanagi grunts)
How very reckless this
Kushinada of yours is.
Huh, this Kushinada?
Do you mean that Kaede's alive?
The Kushinada you once
protected no longer exists.
She is gone forever, gone.
Ah.
Why is it that you continue
to fight me, Kusanagi?
Huh, uh.
(somber music)
(sighs)
What's the matter?
(warm music)
Answer my question,
imperfect one.
(Kusanagi laughing)
Huh?
Huh (grunts), why I fight
is none of your business, hmm.
(thunder rumbling)
(high-pitched warbling)
(energy whooshes)
(explosion booms)
(energy warbling)
At last, the climax
has finally arrived.
(lightning crackles)
I shall be leaving your
presence for the moment.
It's been quite
enjoyable, Kusanagi.
Hold it!
(centipede rumbling)
(Kusanagi shouts)
(dramatic fanfare)
Hmm.
(Momiji moans)
(dramatic action music)
All right, fang face, maybe
I'll tell you the reason.
It's not like you're gonna
tell anyone, huh? (shouts)
Here's the answer to
your question! (shouts)
(Kusanagi shouts)
(centipede squelches)
(Kusanagi growling)
(centipede crashes)
(laughs)
(birds chirping)
(centipede squelching)
(crowd chattering)
Not unless the slow... Ew, oh.
Hey, notice how... Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
This isn't like... Oh, no!
(peaceful music)
Ah, this one here.
It's destroying... Oh!
Been a conscious feeling.
Think it...
Feeling, but...
Something's about to happen
here in Tokyo,
something terrible.
- [Man] I spent 16 years over...
(soaring music)
(birds chirping)
(moans) Huh, oh,
this is my room!
What am I doing here?
Yo!
Huh?
Kusanagi!
Mm-hmm.
I can't believe
you're really okay.
Oh, thank goodness, oh, I
was so worried about you.
Hmm, oh, really?
But you know, you were sleeping
pretty comfortably there.
Uh, oh, you were watching me
sleep, weren't you? (groans)
(Kusanagi laughs)
(gasps) You brought me
back here, didn't you?
Well, of course I did.
Didn't I say that I
would always protect you?
(gasps)
(gentle music)
It's true, I will
always protect you.
Oh.!
Hmm.
(high-pitched warbling)
(laughs) Hmm.
(upbeat music)
- [Momiji] Who's calling me?
Something powerful and alive
is being born in the darkness,
and yet at the same
time, something wonderful
is happening inside me!
I love you, Kusanagi, from
the bottom of my heart.
I want to tell you how
overpowered my feelings are at,
what, I have to tell
him by doing that?
That's too weird! (gasps)
It's the next episode
of "Blue Seed."
I love you, this is so extreme!
It's time to confess.
I'm so embarrassed but I'm
really happy, too! (laughs)
(upbeat pop music)