(thunder rumbles)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
This is an important
announcement
from the Government of Japan.
Japan is facing the most
critical danger in its history.
In two days a total
eclipse will occur
and Japan will be battered
with unprecedented disasters.
However there is one way to
prevent this from happening.
This girl, Momiji Fujimiya, is
the girl who will save Japan.
- [Narrator] The Setting
Sun, the Coming Day,
a Private Time for Each of Us.
- [Reporter] There
are only 48 hours
before the eclipse but
this girl is still missing.
What, what did the
government say?
What does this sacrifice
girl look like?
(rumbling)
It's because of those monsters
the whole town
looks like a jungle.
What kind of disasters
could be worse than this?
If we can survive by
taking that girl's life,
why don't they
hurry up and do it?
Find her and make her
a human sacrifice.
- [Reporter] The most critical
danger in its history.
In two days a total
eclipse will occur
and Japan will be battered
by unprecedented
natural disasters.
Kaede.
Is this what you really want?
(slow sorrowful music)
(crowd talking)
- [Man] Who in the hell are you?
Hello there, are you
the Prime Minister?
Who are you?
This is from Kunikida.
Ta, ta, ta.
- [Prime Minister] Hey, wait!
- [Kunikida] Prime
Minister can you hear me?
Prime Minister?
Kunikida, where
the hell are you?
I'm somewhere doing my best
to analyze the power
of the Kushinada.
I'm pleased to report that we
have some hope of succeeding.
- [Prime Minister]
Time is critical.
Can you do something right now?
Prime Minister I understand
how you must be feeling.
But you acted too rashly.
- [Prime Minister] You
mean that TV announcement?
- [Kunikida] How could you sell
a girl's life over
public television?
It wasn't us, I swear.
- [Kunikida] What?
That announcement was made
by an anonymous source
without our consent.
What did you say?
- [Prime Minister]
Someone, we don't know who,
leaked the information to
the television network.
- [Kunikida] There must be a
Aragami spy in the government.
In any case, the current
situation is beyond our control.
We only have two days
before the eclipse.
Kunikida, we've got to
have a Kushinada now.
Huh?
The Aso mountain's just erupted.
What?
- [Reporter] Breaking news.
This is a volcano update.
At 12:07 today, Mount Naka-Dake
in the Aso mountains
in Kumamoto Prefecture
erupted on a huge scale.
At 12:09 Mount Aso...
Did these eruption occur
because of Susano-Oh?
If this keeps up there'll be
nothing left to
save in two days.
- [Reporter] Mount Mihara
in the Izu Oshima Islands.
Many earthquakes,
felt all over Japan,
have accompanied the eruption.
In addition to the
eruption, tsunami warnings
have been issued for the
Pacific coastline areas.
- [Announcer] Tsunamis are
inundating the Sakai area
with Shizuoka at the
center of the damage.
The areas under water are
almost completely destroyed.
Some shelters in the
area are now under water.
- [Reporter] The
number of casualties
and missing is still
unknown, but they're huge.
- [Reporter] A tsunami has hit
the Pacific coastal
areas at Hokkaido.
Prime Minister.
Please believe me.
I'll contact you later.
Huh?
I can't get anything
from there!
Wait, Kunikida!
- [Announcer]
Possibilities of tsunamis
occurring along the coast.
- [Woman] Give instructions
to move shelters
to a new location.
- [Prime Minister]
Hurry, Kunikida.
What should I do?
Hm, Miss Matsudaira?
(gentle music)
What is that sound?
This is the pulse, sir.
The pulse?
We placed Momiji under the
artificial Kushinada pulse
and this is what happened.
This is the same as
when I touched Kaede.
(gentle music)
Is it some kind of resonance?
Look at this, sir.
The Aragami tissue which
we couldn't destroy
using only the artificial
pulse is falling apart.
Look.
It turned to dust.
This might be it, sir.
(Momiji sighs)
Momiji.
Momiji!
Not very effective is it?
She's already exhausted
just from doing this.
If she has to that 'til
all the Aragami are dead
she'll be squeezed out
like a tube of toothpaste.
That shouldn't be a problem.
I think we can augment
Momiji's pulse electronically.
Are you sure?
Yes.
That melody.
Huh?
I wonder what that
melody could be.
I felt its warmth in my heart.
The sound must be
caused by the resonance.
But that note
progression is odd.
(Yaegashi groans)
Yaegashi!
It's Matsuri!
Idiot, you're badly hurt!
Don't do this to yourself.
I'm all right.
Yaegashi.
(Yaegashi groans)
I've been going over
this in my head.
(gentle music)
Taken together, the notes
make a tetrachord melody.
The song of the Rite of Matsuri.
The Matsuri?
These notes must be the basis
for all ancient
Matsuri melodies.
Matsuri.
The Matsuri.
Yes, the Rite of Matsuri was
originally a secret ceremony
performed to create
pools of psychic power
required to control nature.
A way to pool psychic power.
(chimes jingling)
Matsuri.
I got it, the Matsuri!
Yes that's it!
Mr. Kunikida, the Matsuri!
Huh?
If Kaede was able to increase
the power of Susano-Oh
by using the Rite of Matsuri,
then that means the
power of the Kushinada
can be increased
by the ritual too!
Hm.
When Momiji began to glow red,
Susano-Oh fired energy
at both Kushinadas,
both Momiji and Kaede.
Maybe his instincts told him
that the red light
was his weak point.
So how can we utilize this?
That's the problem, all right.
Mr. Kunikida, could
you please take me
to the place where the
Ceremony of Human Sacrifice
is going to be held?
- [All] What?
She's right!
The Ceremony of Sacrifice
and the Rite of Matsuri
have got to be one and the same!
And if that's true,
then being on the site
of the Rite of Matsuri will
maximize Momiji's power!
I feel something sir.
The blood of the Kushinada
is telling me something.
Understood, it's all or nothing.
We'll try Momiji's plan.
Right.
- [Both] Hm.
(Kusanagi groans)
(somber music)
The Kushinada is
our last chance?
But how?
The Kushinada pulse is
some kind of ultrasound.
It has the power to
destroy the giant plants.
This power used to appear only
when a Kushinada was killed,
or offered up as a sacrifice.
We believe that by
making the Kushinada
and the artificial
Kushinada pulse resonate,
we can now unleash
the Kushinada's power
without having to use
her as a human sacrifice.
A method of electronically
amplifying her power
is now being calculated,
and will be completed by
tomorrow morning at the latest.
However, I do regret
that in doing this,
we will be destroying the
great work our ancestors began.
Are we right in
undoing their work?
That decision weighs
heavily upon my conscience.
- [Prime Minister]
We have a duty
to make the citizens happy.
- [Kunikida] Hm, but what
is the meaning of happiness?
I wish I knew.
Smell of air, clean air.
I'd forgotten it.
We Japanese lived with
nature for a long time.
However at some point,
we started to ignore
the part of nature
where our gods lived.
- [Prime Minister] The
Japanese government
has already asked the Americans
to use nuclear weapons on Tokyo.
Atomic bombs?
- [Prime Minister]
Missiles, actually.
This city will
become a sea of fire.
But when sir?
Two days from now, at the
same time as the eclipse.
We will do our best
to evacuate everyone
from the metropolitan
area beginning tomorrow.
But sir!
After the beginning
of the eclipse,
I'll give you one hour.
During that time,
you must execute
the Ceremony of Sacrifice,
or whatever you have in mind.
I understand, sir.
Have the sacrificial
altar ready for us.
- [Murakumo] I understand.
- [Man] Yes, our propaganda
seems to have taken effect.
- [Murakumo] How about
the special ceramics?
- [Man] We have more than enough
to form the ceramic field.
- [Murakumo] Set
the ceramic field
around the Altar
of Human Sacrifice.
- [Man] Yes sir.
Kaede Kushinada, queen
of traitors beware!
For I am Murakumo,
king of the Aragami!
(ominous music)
(ethereal music)
(eerie music)
- [Momiji] What are
you thinking about?
- [Kusanagi] Did you finish
typing all that data?
Yeah finally.
Anyway, what are
you thinking about?
Nothing.
Liar, you look
pretty serious to me.
Don't be dumb, and just
what are you thinking about?
Do you really think you can win?
You're gonna be up there
on that sacrificial altar.
You're the one who oughta be...
Worried?
(emotional music)
And you really think you'll win?
I can't honestly say,
but I won't just give up
without trying either, you know.
(helicopter whirring)
I'd like to thank you all.
Thanks to your support,
the program data
has been sent to the
Ministry of Investigation.
All of the preparations
will be completed tonight.
Yeah!
Great!
Tomorrow, everything will start,
and tomorrow everything
may end as well.
Hm?
What was that?
I want all of you to
listen to me carefully.
As of this moment, I
am dissolving the TAC.
(intense music)
(all gasping)
What do you mean
by that, dissolved?
- [Kunikida] The
government of Japan
has asked the United States
to render assistance.
In a worst case scenario, the
final option will be employed.
Now wait a second, what the
hell do you mean, A-bombs?
Yes, nuclear missiles will
be used against Susano-Oh.
If missiles are
used, Tokyo will be...
(explosion booming)
- [Ryouko] But sir...
I don't intend to force anyone
to join the mission tomorrow.
I would like you to spend
the rest of your time
enjoying the few
moments we have left
before tomorrow, making
sure you won't regret
what we have to do.
Ha, when did you become
such a pessimist, old man?
We've got a job to do,
and we're gonna see
it through to the end!
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were going soft.
Idiot!
You were all individuals before
you were members of the TAC.
You have live to lead, families!
Don't throw all that away
just because of some
misguided sense of duty.
Once you've thought about it,
if you still intend
to fight with me,
gather in front of
the Diet Building
at sunrise tomorrow morning.
Hm, good luck everybody.
Nice knowing ya, bye-bye.
You yellow belly!
You're wrong.
It can take as much
courage to withdraw
as it does to attack.
Yeah, what he said.
I've got my own sweet
assets to protect.
Goodbye, everyone.
Huh?
Sakura?
(computer beeps)
Scorpion and Pluto are aligned.
Position of death.
Oh so friggin' what?
Any more information
on the Kushinada pulse?
Uh no, nothing so far.
I see, hm.
Here, a souvenir.
Hm, the address of the
shelter where Matsu's son is?
I got it at the Ministry of
Information on my way back.
Well everybody, you're released.
Spend your time deciding
what to do today.
I'm going to
collect my thoughts.
Sorry, I'm going out as well.
Say hi to Jun for me.
Hm.
Well, I've got
nothing better to do,
so I guess I'm taking
care of Yaegashi.
(Yaegashi groans)
Koume, please.
I need a favor.
Idiot, you should be in bed.
Is your motorcycle available?
My bike?
I need to get some software.
Hey!
Hey wait a second!
Well, I guess I have no choice.
- [Yaegashi] Sorry.
Well, what shall we do?
How about the beach?
(pleasant music)
(Momiji giggles)
Hold tight!
- [Momiji] No no, you
touched the wrong place!
- [Kusanagi] Hey, you think
it would make me happy
to touch your
little baby finger?
What?
You!
Stop it, stop it, wah!
(engine roaring)
(pleasant music)
- [Yaegashi] I'm sure it's
around here somewhere.
Hey, Yoshiki.
This could be our
last day, you know?
Today could be the last
day for us to be together.
(gulls cawing)
It's so quiet isn't it?
Hm.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
- [Momiji] I feel
as if the eclipse
and everything that's gonna
happen tomorrow is just a lie.
I wonder if Kaede's
all right or not.
- [Kusanagi] Hm?
- [Momiji] Mr. Kunikida, Miss
Takeuchi, Miss Matsudaira.
All our friends in school.
All of them liked her.
I wonder if she'll
still be happy
when all of those people die.
Who knows what Kaede thinks?
I wonder what
she's thinking now.
(choral music)
- [Girl] Kaede!
Why don't you come to
Shibuya with me on Sunday?
It'll be fun!
I'm sorry, I have
something to do.
- [Girl] Okay, I'll
wait for the next time!
- [Man] What is the
power in Kushinada?
The data doesn't
show any difference.
If a Kushinada dies, the
Aragami will die too right?
I wish she would just die.
Mr. Hayashi!
You're Kaede
Kushinada aren't you?
I'm going to have to
kill you to save Japan.
(men groaning)
Father I'd like to
go back to Izumo.
But I know I can't.
I'm sorry.
(Kaede crying)
(somber music)
- [Kusanagi] Did she
ever know happiness?
I was thinking
that maybe I wasn't
the best father
Kaede could've had.
Daitetsu.
I tried to hide and protect her,
but she only got
sadder and lonelier.
I'm the one who's responsible
for the monster that she became.
Me, and nobody else.
That's not true!
Anyway, I still believe
that Kaede will come
back to us someday.
Boy, that would really
be strange wouldn't it?
For me to become her mother?
Sounds just fine to me.
(people chattering)
Jun, Jun, Jun!
Hey Jun!
Jun.
- [Jun] Mom.
Mom.
Jun, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, oh Jun.
Why are you saying sorry, Mom?
You're weird.
I don't know why, I
don't know, but...
Honey.
Mom, that human sacrifice
is Momiji, isn't she?
Hey you.
Huh?
Did I hear you say you know
that human sacrifice girl?
What, are you talking to me?
What's wrong with knowing her?
Why don't you hurry up and
turn her into the police?
This situation is intolerable!
One girl dies, and everybody
will be fine and dandy.
Be practical, why don't ya?
What's one girl, more or less?
That's a good idea.
I'll get a rope.
Yeah come on!
(crowd clamoring)
Don't worry, Mom.
We'll be okay.
You're still going to
help Momiji, aren't you?
Yes, Jun.
The chairman of
the US House of...
I, I don't know how to say this.
I never thought I
could lose before.
I always thought I could
win against anything,
but for the first time in
my life I'm having doubts!
It's all right, Koume.
It's not every day
that you fight a god.
I don't get it!
How can you be this calm?
- [Yaegashi] Well
it's just that...
You are the same
Yaegashi, aren't you?
The guy who couldn't
shoot a bazooka?
You're the one I
always made fun of?
How could you be so
calm when I'm so...
Maybe, it's because
I've known fear
and because I know
it can be endured.
Sometimes you've got
to accept your fears.
Don't be stupid,
I can't do that!
Being strong is the
only virtue I've got.
It's okay, give in and
let me be the strong one.
Let you be strong?
You don't, you can't, damn it!
You're Yaegashi, you can't
say that you're like that.
You're a wimp, and I'm an idiot.
I feel like I ought
to be able to win,
even if my power
doesn't increase,
I'm sure she'll
resonate with me.
Huh?
My sister, I mean.
I really think Kaede will
resonate with me in the end.
You're wrong, Momiji.
Kaede hates everyone
and everything.
It's just that she hates
human beings the most.
That's not true.
I share her blood, and I have
a sister's faith in her soul.
My sister loves
plants and nature.
She loves Susano-Oh.
She's not the kind of
person who abandons people.
I want to believe that the
Kushinada loves human beings.
Prove me wrong.
I will.
(emotional music)
- [Narrator] The day of
destiny has finally come,
arriving in a cloak of
deadly silence and dread.
Who knows what kind of
horrible things may happen
when the very sky is
covered with darkness?
Nobody knows.
There's only one
thing we do know.
There's no other
way for us to win,
except my fighting back.
We must believe in the
power of the Kushinada.
It's the next episode
of Blue Seed, number 25,
All or Nothing!
Decision!
My Fate!
Kaede, my twin sister,
I will not lose.
(pleasant music)
(singing in foreign language)