(thunder rumbles)
(eerie music)
(upbeat music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy,
dangerous night ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Pick me up, foxy night game ♪
(man sings in foreign language)
(woman sings in
foreign language)
(men and woman sing
in foreign language)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy,
dangerous night ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Pick me up, foxy night game ♪
(sirens wailing)
(people screaming)
(creature roars)
(crash)
(people yell indistinctly)
(rumbling)
(crash)
Use the lights!
- [Man] There it is!
(concrete crumbling)
(groans) Help us.
- [Yaegashi] Momiji, is
that data scan ready?
Mm-mm, we can't hit it
without shooting them as well!
- [Yaegashi] Just a
second, that's right.
Move it, Yagashi!
How long does it
take to collect data?
Forget that stuff and get
over here and help us!
Just a second, I'm
almost finished!
Momiji, push the shift key.
Right, the shift.
(groans) Come on!
- [Ryoko] Mm.
(gun clicks)
(rapid whipping)
Data collection completed!
(Yaegashi yelps)
Here we go!
(gun bangs)
(Ryoko grunts)
(screams) Shut up and
die, you stupid insect!
(gun booms)
(thud)
(men groan)
Are you all right!?
- [Ryoko] Hold on!
- [Yaegashi] Wait, Momiji!
We gotta them out of here!
Let's go!
Run, hurry!
(screams)
(dramatic music)
(gasps)
Kome!
(screams)
Miss Takeuchi!
Yageashi, shoot it, shoot it!
Shoot it? Right!
(gun clicks)
What the!? (grunts)
(groans)
The safety!
Unlock the safety, you idiot!
Release it!
I understand, but
I can't find it!
- [Kome] It's above the trigger,
you stupid geek, on top!
Kome, look out!
(creature growls)
(screams)
(tense music)
(creature roars)
(Momiji screams)
(gun booms)
(creature roars)
(Momiji and Yaegashi yell)
- [Momiji] (gasps) Mr.
Yaegashi, are you all right?
Ah, Momiji!
What did you do!?
(both yell)
Momiji!
(explosion)
(crowd chatters)
(gasps) Kusanagi.
When did you start
using cannons, princess?
Sheesh, there's not
much left for me.
(chuckles nervously) Sorry,
the others were in trouble.
- [Kusanagi] It's all right,
I'll just give it
the coup de grace.
- [Momiji] Huh?
What do you mean?
It's not dead.
(siren wails)
Don't take your eyes off it!
(stammers) But, what, Kusanagi?
(siren wails)
(eerie music)
(wet pop)
(light clicks)
(steady beeping)
Now, take a look at this.
The cicada Aragami shrank
down to this after it fell.
Examine its head carefully.
This is a piece of concrete.
Uh, did it land in wet
cement when it fell?
- [Azusa] No, my guess is
that the cicada was buried
in wet concrete while it
was casting off its skin.
Poor little thing.
(Yaegashi groans quietly)
- [Azusa] But
whatever the cause,
what's more important
is that we didn't find
one of those Blue Seed cores.
Huh?
No seed!?
That's right, not
a seed in sight.
Oh, and the official name
of the seed will be mitama.
Sir, Kusanagi told me that
the Aragami wasn't dead yet!
- [Azusa] Yes, and now
we have to worry about it
finding another host.
Hm. (slurps)
Looks like we'll have to
broaden the search area.
It's probably in a
seedier part of town.
(group groans)
Miss Matsudaira,
continue examining the cicada.
I'm on it, sir.
Kome...
- [Kome] Don't pair
me with Yaegashi!
Kome!
Kome, I'm really sorry
about what happened.
Shut up!
(Yaegashi yelps)
You almost got me
killed, you stupid geek!
Uh, but the TAC hired me to
be a computer specialist,
not to fire rocket launchers.
You mean you can't do
something Momiji could!?
Kome!
Kome, what!?
Hang around him and
you'll be dead, Momiji!
Work day!
You're mean!
Hey, calm down.
Why don't you go with me, Kome?
- [Kome] Let's go.
(chuckles weakly)
Right, Momiji,
you come with me.
I want Yaegashi to
start analyzing the data
he collected yesterday.
(car engine revs)
I can't go.
Huh?
Well, what's wrong, Momiji?
Um, well, I've got
a little headache,
and I was thinking I
should stay and rest.
Hm?
Oh, I see, uh, that
could be serious.
In that case, I'd better
leave you here with Yaegashi.
(gasps happily) Yes, sir!
(liquid flowing)
(Yaegashi groans)
(groans) An insect
trapped in wet cement,
boy, does that describe me.
(somber piano music)
(door lock clicks)
Hm?
Ah, Momiji?
Oh, hi!
Look what I got, the
bakery was having a sale.
(Yaegashi grunts uncertainly)
Please cheer up, Mr. Yaegashi.
You don't have to
be so depressed.
Just catch this Aragami
and no one will
remember anything else.
(chuckles weakly)
Easy for you to say.
I can't even fire
a rocket launcher.
I'm sorry I took that
gun away from you.
I feel like this
is all my fault.
Hey, why don't we catch
the Aragami together?
Huh?
It's a great idea!
Everyone will be so impressed
when we catch one by ourselves!
And if we need help,
I'm sure we can get
Kusanagi to give us a hand!
(groans) That's very kind.
Thank you, Momiji.
- [Momiji] Here, let's eat
strawberry buns and persevere.
No one can feel bad
while eating these, okay?
Yes, I'll do it.
I'll eat this bun
and I won't give up!
- [Momiji] Mm-hm!
I'll eat this and ah!
Oh?
(screams)
What!?
Floppy, floppy disk!
I forgot and left the single
most important disk of all
back at my house!
(gulps)
(tires screech)
[Yaegashi's Mother] Oh, Yoshiki,
why are you home so early?
And who's this?
I'm Momiji Fujimiya.
Oh my, this is the first time
Yoshiki's brought a girl home
since he was in
elementary school!
Has this relationship
been going on a long time?
For gosh sakes, mom,
don't be ridiculous!
Please, Ms.
Fujimiya, do come in.
Nice meeting you.
- [Yaegashi] (clears
throats) Since we're here,
I'll finish typing
up the data on my PC.
Have fun!
Wow!
It's like a library in here.
Are all of these books about
computers and programming?
- [Yaegashi] Uh-huh.
(knocking)
- [Momiji] Hm?
How about some ginseng tea?
Here you go.
- [Momiji] Oh, thank you.
How is my son?
He never talks about
his work with me.
(Yaegashi groans)
- [Momiji] Well...
My boy had such a glowing future
when he was with the
Economic Planning Agency.
- [Momiji] Oh!
We put him in the
very best schools,
from kindergarten
through college,
but then he was transferred...
- [Yaegashi] Mother, if
you're finished with the tea,
you can leave.
I wonder if he's not
aggressive enough.
He was raised in a family
made only of women, you know,
just his two sisters and
I, but he's very bright.
You're really lucky
to have caught him!
Huh?
Mother!
Yes, yes, all right.
He's all yours! (giggles)
(Momiji sighs)
(Yaegashi groans)
(door shuts)
Goodness, your mother really
thinks the world of you.
Yeah, well, I did
have a lot of promise.
At least I did, until I
was transferred to the TAC.
(gasps)
In all my life,
the TAC was the first place
I've ever failed at anything.
But you haven't.
Yes, I have.
(eerie shimmering)
(train rumbles)
(groans) Nothing here either.
- [Ryoko] Huh.
- [Yaegashi] Ever since I
first came here to the TAC,
I felt myself becoming
more and more miserable.
Miserable?
But why?
I know I was transferred here
to crunch numbers
and process data,
and I know that I'm
the best there is
when it comes to computers,
but somehow, it's
just not enough.
(sentimental strings music)
I just, I just don't
feel like I belong.
- [Momiji] That's not true!
Huh?
Mr. Yaegashi, you've got to know
that you're absolutely
vital to the TAC!
You're good at making copies,
and you clean the
office voluntarily,
and the tea you make
is really the best!
And you've got your special
anti-Aragami program.
Mo-Momiji.
Please,
please have a little faith
in yourself, Mr. Yaegashi.
Momiji!
(groans)
(fanfare music plays)
Huh? (screams)
Hi, Momiji here!
(Yaegashi groans uncomfortably)
- [Momiji] Huh?
(water trickles)
(water flows and bubbles)
(high-pitched ring)
(screams)
Uh, uh, uh. (screams)
(crash)
Um, just what is this?
- [Computer] Can you guess
what's on the underpants
I'm wearing today?
Kaba-san, the happy hippo!
(Yaegashi groans)
(Yaegashi pants)
(screams)
Just one thing.
Is that the disk we came for?
No, no, you don't understand!
Uh, I admit I play adult video
games, but this isn't one!
So, what's the difference?
This is a revolutionary program!
Once you've inputted
sufficient data,
it can produce a
reliable forecast
of what might happen next!
There's nothing else
in the world like it!
Right, so what does
this innovation
have to do with my underpants!?
It was just a test!
Just a stupid test!
It's stupid, all right!
It failed, I'm not
wearing my hippos!
I'm telling you the truth!
I designed it to
track the Aragami,
but I really thought
it would work.
What did I miss?
If we had your Aragami
detecting ability
and a working version
of this program,
but I guess I failed.
(playful music)
(screams) You sure did!
(Momiji groans)
[Yaegashi's Mother] Oh,
are you leaving so soon?
Why don't you just
stay a little longer?
Please, don't give
up on my Yoshiki!
(electricity crackles)
(energy hums)
(high-pitched ringing)
(groans)
Huh?
Momiji, what's wrong?
A-Aragami.
Aragami?
(phone rings)
(train rumbles)
No, it wasn't blue-green, sir,
it was all blue.
(yawns)
I can't get ahold of
the boss or the others.
We have to do something.
I know, let's see
if we can locate it.
(engine revs)
(car horns beep)
(tense music)
(insects skitter)
(energy hums)
Momiji, are you okay?
It's getting a lot stronger.
Keep going straight.
Okay!
(crashing)
(energy hums)
(car horns beep)
(tires screech)
What's going on?
It's bumper to bumper
as far as I can see!
(gasps) It's here!
(crash)
(creature growls)
(both yell)
(rumbling)
- [Momiji] Is that an insect?
It looks like several
kinds combined.
(creature roars)
(crash)
(both yell)
Stop it!
Why are you attacking the road!?
(gasps) Momiji, come on!
You can't talk to
that one, come on!
If that's the same Aragami
we fought last night,
it won't stop
demolishing the road,
not until every last
piece of concrete
has been completely destroyed!
We're leaving!
(Momiji gasps)
(creature growls)
(both yell)
(groans)
(yells)
(fanfare plays)
Kaba-san, the happy hippo!
I was right!
Stop it, there's
no time for that!
- [Yaegashi] Oh!
(Momiji gasps)
(both groan)
(rumbling)
(both yell)
(both scream)
Run for it!
(tires screech)
What on earth is that!?
(phone rings)
What do you want?
Huh, what was that!?
I said I'm inside a giant cocoon
on the Metropolitan Expressway!
Momiji's here too, we tried
to call you earlier, but we...
What did I tell you!?
Momiji, didn't I tell you
to stay away from him?
- [Momiji] But, Kome...
No buts! (groans)
Hey, Kome!
Don't forget there are
two people in there!
- [Kome] Oh, rats.
(creature growls)
(both scream)
(grunts)
(intense music)
Momiji!
Kusanagi!
Didn't I tell you not to
hog all the fun, princess?
(Momiji gasps)
It's not fair!
But I'm not having any fun!
(creature growls)
But you were smiling. Hi-yah!
(gasps) I was not!
Hm.
It's extermination time! (yells)
(creature growls)
Damn, where's his
Blue Seed? (yelps)
- [Both] Huh?
I'll try to find it!
(Kusanagi grunts and yells)
It's not good, I can't
locate the mitama!
What!?
But maybe I can. (grunts)
What do you think you're doing?
We've got one chance.
I'm inputting the rest of the
data we collected last night.
(creature roars)
Come on, baby.
(computer beeps)
We've got it!
It was right about
your underpants,
it must work!
(yelps)
It's hidden in the ovipositor!
The ovipositor?
Oh, that thing.
(grunts) There!
(Kusanagi yells)
(creature roars)
(grunts)
(thud)
Oh, boy.
Kusanagi.
(both yell)
(explosion)
(gasps)
Momiji!
(creature growls)
Momiji! (growls)
Momiji.
(click)
Huh?
(beeping)
(yells) Another launcher!
- [Kome] You almost got me
killed, you stupid geek!
(dramatic music)
(grunts)
(groans)
Hang around him and you'll
be dead Momiji, work day!
(groans)
- [Momiji] Mr. Yaegashi,
you've got to know
that you're absolutely
vital to the TAC!
Please, have a little faith
in yourself, Mr. Yaegashi.
(groans) Kusanagi.
(groans)
(Yaegashi exhales)
(grunts) I can do it!
I can handle a simple launcher!
(launcher booms)
(yells)
(thuds)
(grunts)
(explosion)
(creature roars)
- [Kusanagi] Hi-yah!
Huh? (screams)
(Kusanagi grunts)
(groans) I did it, I can't
believe I really did it.
(groans)
(creature roars)
Now what?
What's that monster
going to do now?
(creature roars)
Without the seed,
I guess it had no
reason to go on living.
(seed clatters)
(wind whistles)
(helicopter blades whir)
(gasps)
You're joking, right!?
I just don't believe it!
Yaegashi was the
one who killed it?
(Yaegashi grunts)
Didn't you experience
some hallucinations?
(Yaegashi grunts)
Did you really experience
hallucinations?
I'll have to run
some tests on that.
(books thud)
(Yaegashi grunts)
(laughs)
(playful music)
- [Yaegashi] Mm-hm!
All right, I'm going to
do it, I won't give up
because no matter
what some people say,
I'm absolutely vital to the TAC!
- [Kushinada] The Aragami,
which have been trying to
kill me, the Kushinada,
have launched a new offensive.
But now, a puzzling new mystery
has come up to the surface.
Mr. Kunikida, just what
is the Kushinada Project?
Because of this project,
a little girl who has nothing
to do with any of this
is in terrible danger!
I can't forgive
something like this.
The next episode of
Blue Seed, I'm Fired Up!
I'll Do it Because
I'm the Kushinada!
And let me tell you,
I'm serious this time.
(mellow music)
(woman sings in
foreign language)