(thunder clapping)
("Babel Carnival")
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy,
dangerous night ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Pick me up, foxy night game ♪
♪ Take it easy,
dangerous night ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Pick me up, foxy night game ♪
(ominous twinkling sound)
(ominous music)
What happened to me, where am I?
Susano Oh, you damned monster.
- [Kaede] So Kusanagi,
you've finally awoken.
You saved me?
This doesn't make any sense.
Why are you helping
me now, Kaede?
In three days, all
of this will be over.
What was that?
- [Kaede] From the
darkness that shall fall
three days from now, a
new world will be born.
- [Mamoru] What do you mean?
Kushinada's job is to
protect Japan, isn't it?
Or is it?
We intend to create a Japan
that is worth protecting.
You must be insane, you're going
to destroy this
country to protect it?
I must protect Japan
from itself at any cost.
You're not making
any sense at all,
do you really understand
just what you're saying?
This is the purpose
of the Kushinada.
When the time comes,
you will understand
what is right and what is wrong.
And how will I come to
realize that Princess Kaede?
We shall be reborn together.
Say what?
Susano Oh is your god,
sacrifice your seeds to him.
Kaede.
All must be returned to
the green that once was.
Soon we shall protect
your hand again, Kusanagi.
(growling)
(mysterious music)
Meeting again, starting
the journey, I won't lose!
A generator, I found
one, I found another one!
Hey Koume, is this
generator too small?
Every little bit helps.
Cool.
Let's put it on the
boat and go to the next-
Hey watch it,
don't work so hard.
You need to take a break.
Yeah,
but if we stop
finding generators,
then Matsudaira can
continue her research.
We've gotta do our best.
And if you don't
get enough rest,
you're gonna pass
out from exhaustion.
Oh, I'm fine, I'm
young and spry.
If I pass out, don't
worry about a thing.
Hey don't invite bad luck!
So, the Kushinada will destroy
the Arigami by overworking
herself to death,
is that your plan?
(laughter)
- [Momiji] Hey wait a
minute, that's not funny.
No, I guess not.
(laughing)
Hey tourist, stop
acting like an idiot
and help me get all
this heavy stuff
on the boat, then
we'll grab the beer.
- [Koume] What's wrong?
I thought I felt something.
- [Announcer] This is
the coast defense force.
Koume.
Right, take cover.
- [Announcer] An
emergency evacuation
has been ordered
for all of Tokyo.
Electricity, gas, order
and telephone services
will all be disconnected
and there is
no convenient cases of when
they may be reinstating.
All residents who
have not yet evacuated
from this area,
please proceed to
your designated
shelters immediately.
Great, I'm not
just a loser kicked
out of an elite group, I'm
also a wanted fugitive.
Oh stop griping and think about
all the benefits you're getting.
Momiji, don't let this
ding dong's complaining
make you think about
the committee of
human sacrifice again.
We've got three days left,
I'm gonna keep doing my best.
Way to go, kid, that's great.
Okay, let's get
back to the base.
Those damn Aragami
aren't gonna like
that the human race
doesn't give up so easily.
Hey Yaegashi, what
are you smiling at?
Actually, I was
just thinking about
what a strong woman
you are, Koume.
But you know, that strength is
what makes you so attractive.
(laughing)
Attractive, what the hell
are you talking about?
Koume, Yoshiki, calm down,
we've got to keep
working together.
We've only got three more days,
and I don't know what we can do.
have we located
the Kushinada yet?
I've had all of the
police department
set up roadblocks and barricades
surrounding the city, but.
But?
I'm sure that Kunikida
has anticipated that.
It makes one wonder what he's
thinking about, doesn't it?
I never would have
thought he was the
sort of man who'd take
such drastic actions
based solely on his emotions.
No, but he's not the kind of man
who ignores his
feelings, either.
That's true.
So,
what's the evacuation status?
The exit as from the
city are almost complete.
However, we've never coordinated
an evacuation this large,
not even during World War Two.
Therefore, we have
to make sure that
people have enough
food and water,
that they receive the
proper information,
otherwise there's no way
we can prevent total chaos.
We can't make people understand
the gravity of the situation
with half truths about
mutated vegetation.
There are also rumors spreading
that Japan will be completely
destroyed in three days.
Who's starting these rumors?
I believe that they began in the
group of amateur
astronomers working
in a local observatory
here in Japan.
They predicted it
after they found
out about the eclipse and the
abnormal path of the moon.
Rumors like that could
be very dangerous,
so we must make an
official announcement.
Kunikida, where are you,
and what are you doing now?
This is unbelievable.
(growling)
Now look, I may have
accidentally rescued you people,
but that doesn't
give you the right
to use my gorgeous apartment
like a garbage dump.
Now, now, now,
calm down a little.
Why don't you let
me take you out
for dinner and a
little nightcap?
No thanks.
- [Ramen Man] Hot, hot!
He's toast.
Sakura.
Is there any possibility that
the U.S. might take action?
No, the White House
wants to keep an eye
on what's happening in Japan,
but due to the terms of
the joint security treaty,
the U.S. can only intervene if
your government requests it.
And I doubt our government
will tell the U.S. the truth.
I don't think our government
knows the whole truth anyway.
How's the artificial
Kushinada pulse coming?
Well, let me show you.
(whirring and screeching)
(computer beeping)
The external layer of this
specimen has become
strengthened.
We can't destroy the
cells hidden inside.
We duplicated Momiji's
Kushinada pulse exactly,
but it's still not effective.
I wonder if we need more
power than three generators.
Or maybe the pulse
itself isn't enough.
There are so many possibilities.
Well we can always strangle
the real sacrifice girl.
It would be a lot more
convenient, you know.
Straighten out.
Ms. Matsudaira, I
think we need to
investigate my body some more.
That's some outfit.
Ms. Matsudaira,
you can do anything you
want, I won't complain.
That's the spirit Momiji.
Ever since we learned that
Kusanagi's still alive,
there's been a different
kind of fire in your eyes.
(light music)
Yeah, I've never
felt so much like
doing my best in my entire life.
Momiji.
Life is wonderful.
Have you used your matama
to tell him you're in love?
But I really wanna see him
and talk with him again.
But first, I've gotta do
the things I've gotta do,
or I won't be able
to face him again.
- [Sakura] Get over it.
Very well said.
It's coming, no!
Aragami!
(dramatic music)
(screeching)
(screaming)
Murakumo!
(mysterious music)
I don't understand,
what can possibly
be going on in the
Kushinada's little head, what?
Ah, you've got some
nerve coming in here,
you cabbage patch freak!
(screaming)
It makes no sense!
Koume, ah!
Yaegashi!
Are you all right Ms. Koume?
Don't move Murakumo,
why are you here?
I need the Kushinada.
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
- [Koume] He's got Momiji!
Momiji!
Where are you taking me?
What are you going
to do with me?
Just what is the
Kushinada doing?
The Kushinada is the wife
of our Lord, Susano Oh,
the king of the Aragami.
Tell me, just what in the
hell could she be thinking?
You're asking me?
I don't have the slightest idea.
She's still planning on
destroying Japan, isn't she?
Yes, that's right.
I thought that the
destruction of mankind
would establish the
kingdom of the Aragami,
but the Kushinada lies.
(crashing)
An Aragami.
This can't be.
The Aragami should
be under my control.
What's going on here?
I don't know, what's happening?
What did you say, Aragami
are appearing all over Japan?
(screeching)
(crashing)
Prime Minister, the
self defense force
is out of anti Aragami weapons,
we may lose everything.
Report from the
troops in a second.
They're reporting that
the Aragami that appeared
at Fumiya Station
have been absorbed
by a gigantic plant.
A gigantic plant?
We're getting similar reports
from all over Japan, sir.
(screeching)
(static screeching)
It ate it, what does this mean?
It means that the
Kushinada has betrayed me.
What in the hell is going on?
(crowd murmuring)
(static screeching)
(ringing)
What is this?
(loud pulsating ringing)
Susano-
What in the hell is going
on here Princess Kaede?
Is it your intention
to destroy the Aragami
by tempting Lord Susano Oh?
Kaede, it's you.
Answer my question or I will
slit your sister's throat right
in front of Lord Susano Oh.
I am sorry for deceiving you,
but this has always
been our lord's intent.
Impossible.
- [Momiji] I don't understand,
what's going on Kaede?
- [Kaede] We are about to
begin the rite of Matsuri,
which has been passed to
us from ancient times.
- [Momiji] Matsuri?
- [Kaede] Yes, when
I first learned of
the rite of Matsuri, I
knew what my fate would be.
(beeping)
The mission of the Kushinada
is to protect Japan,
to create a Japan filled with
living growths and foliage.
You told us before that Japan
was crying, didn't you, Kaede?
Do you believe that
we're killing the plants?
Is that why you're
saying you're gonna
create a life of vegetation
and nothing else?
Is that why you're
gonna kill everyone?
I will kill no one, we shall
simply start all over again.
This is how it all began when
the very first rite
of Matsuri was held.
The first rite of Matsuri?
In those days, Japan
was a much smaller
and more barren country
than it is today.
At that time, mankind's
greatest concerns
were simply getting
enough to eat,
thus the faith they held
as the practitioners
of the most ancient
of all sciences
came together and performed
the rite of Matsuri.
In order to guarantee
a good harvest,
a new breed of psychically
enhanced vegetation was created.
Psychically enhanced vegetation?
Yes, the rite of
Matsuri unlocked
a new source of psychic power,
and used these
plants as a strike
to control the forces of nature.
I don't understand,
what does this
have to do with Susano
Oh, or the Kushinadas?
For the rite of
Matsuri to succeed,
it requires focus, a
god, and human people
who are of willing,
impressionable faith.
This god becomes
the reservoir for
all those seeking psychic power.
- [Momiji] That's
Susano Oh, isn't it?
- [Kaede] Yes, in
order to transform
all of the unborn kingdom,
including mankind into plants,
in order to spread
the seeds which have
the power to initiate the
transformation mankind created,
Lord Susano Oh.
Liar!
Are you saying that
our god, Susano Oh
was created by human beings?
It is the truth, the
world's greatest psychics,
those who carry them, the
Kushinada created him.
But that's-
You lie, it cannot be!
Don't be a fool,
why do you think
Aragami lose their power
when a Kushinada dies?
All things born
from Lord Susano Oh
must return to Lord Susano Oh.
Now, we shall perform
the rite of Matsuri
to create a new Japan.
Betrayer!
First Kusanagi and now this?
What about Kusanagi?
All right, damn you, if the
Kushinada really is our source,
then it may be illogical that
the Aragami would disappear
with the Kushinada's death,
but why does our Lord Susano
Oh require the likes of you?
To perform the rite of
Matsuri requires a maiden.
A maiden?
You mean that the tithing
of the rite of
Matsuri is actually
under the control
of the Kushinada?
Give up your life
to Lord Susano Oh,
and you will sleep with the
other Aragami, Murakumo.
In the future,
Japan will be reborn
as a beautiful garden of
trees and vines and flowers.
But we were just tools, a means
of distributing your
seeds, weren't we?
More than that, you
served our Lord well.
Shut up, if my kingdom of
the Aragami can never be,
then I shall slay this one
now and be done with it.
Die!
(screaming)
Kusanagi, I knew
you weren't dead.
Momiji, are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine, are you okay?
(ringing)
Why Kaede, why
did you spare him?
I don't understand why
you're doing any of this,
your plan's making no sense.
Perhaps that's because you're
simply a foolish human.
That might be true,
it could be true,
but do you really
think this is necessary
even though it
caused so much pain?
Think of Mr. Kunikida and of our
mom and our grandma
and Kusanagi.
(crying)
So many people that I love,
why would you kill them all?
Why does the rite of Matsuri
have to be performed?
It is the purpose
of the Kushinada.
Says who?
I don't like it Kaede, and
even if I do make mistakes,
I'm a Kushinada too,
I won't let you do it
no matter what you say!
And what can you do to stop me?
I don't know that, I don't know,
but I'm also a Kushinada,
so maybe I'll be able-
(screaming)
You die!
No!
(electricity crackling)
(ringing)
(mysterious music)
The Kushinada pulse.
Oh my god.
It sounds like some
kind of melody.
So this is what the power
of the Kushinada feels like.
Are both of you all
right, Momiji, Kaede?
Kusanagi.
No, Susano Oh!
(ringing)
- [Murakumo] Whoa!
(rumbling)
No, Susano Oh!
Momiji!
Let's get out of here.
(screaming)
Hang on, Momiji!
(dramatic music)
- [Man] A huge, gigantic
plant has appeared,
Kairi Yuyoki, a gigantic plant!
But why did we fly,
I lost my matama.
No, it's right here.
(ringing)
This time Momiji, you're
the one who rescued me.
(panting)
Daitetsu, Daitetsu turn on
the radio or T.V. right now.
- [Daitetsu] What's wrong Ryoko?
Hurry up and turn it on.
Repeating, this is an
important announcement
from the government of Japan.
Japan is facing the most
critical danger in it's history.
In two days, a total
eclipse will occur
and Japan will be battered by
unprecedented natural disasters.
Regions all across Japan will
be devastated by these events,
however, there is one way to
prevent this from happening.
We must sacrifice this girl,
Momiji Fujimiya as
a human sacrifice.
- [Toshiki] What did they say?
This can't be happening!
(funky music)
- [Momiji] The secret
is out, the duty
of the human sacrifice.
When the time comes, I
must sacrifice my life
for all human beings,
but beyond that,
although I might not have many
other choices left in my life,
I'd like a little time,
just a little time
between now and then.
I've found the man I
love, and with this
feeling of love comes a need,
a need to keep on living.
It's the next episode
of Blue Seed, number 24.
The setting sun, the coming day,
a private time for each of us.
What am I thinking, am I
being selfish, or am I human?
("Touch and Go")