(thunder crashing)
(funky music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(growling)
(slashing)
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
(panting)
(gasping)
(growling)
So you've shown
yourselves at last!
(yelling)
They're fast!
They're different
from other Aragami.
They've got a feral
smell about them.
(dramatic music)
(growling)
(laughing)
(grunting)
Man, where in the heck
did those things go?
(screeching)
Huh?
It's one of them.
Something cut this
monster in half.
Who could have done it?
Some other kind of Aragami?
(mysterious music)
I'll set it for seven AM.
After a long hard day, it's
time for a little sleep.
Good night.
(yawning)
- [Kusanagi] You
oughta be more careful
about locking your windows.
Kusanagi!
What are you doing in my bedroom
in the middle of the night?
Don't you know how rude that is?
Say, are you free tomorrow?
Hm?
Could you spend a
little time with me?
What do you mean?
- [Kusanagi] Ah, come on,
don't you think it'd be fun?
Uh, well...
You must have some time.
- [Momiji] Well after
school is over, I have to...
Good, I'll be waiting.
Wait, Kusanagi!
Kusanagi!
(sighing)
Did he ask me out?
On a date?
(groaning)
Goodnight.
(clock ticking)
(alarm clock ringing)
(yelping)
(birds chirping)
(upbeat music)
Well, they don't look much
like the ones in the picture,
but I did cook 'em myself!
Oh, I wonder if I should have
cooked lunch without asking.
Oh, I'm sure it'll be okay.
Ah, a delicious
home cooked lunch,
one of them must be for me.
I'm so happy!
Hey, Momiji, let's go!
Right, I'll be right there.
Goodness, something
smells wonderful.
Is that a picnic?
Ah, yes, ma'am.
But it's not Saturday is it?
Is it for the boss?
Well what can I say...
No, ma'am, it's not,
I'm meeting a friend
after school today.
(groaning)
This father's heart is crushed.
You can order the same takeout
lunch you always get, sir.
What I want to know is,
who's the lucky person
who gets to eat Momiji's
hand made lunch?
(gasping)
Momiji, do you know what makes
a homemade lunch so delicious?
It's because of a
special ingredient.
The wonderful
spice of true love.
Oh, I didn't know that.
(sobbing)
- [Yaegashi] I wonder
who killed this Aragami.
It had to be that jerk Kusanagi,
he's always grabbing the
good ones out from under us.
I hate him!
Ouch!
Now, wait a second.
Mr. Sukashira told us that,
according to both the
eyewitness reports
and the forensic evidence,
there were at least
three Aragami.
Okay, so that just means
there are two more Aragami
out there hanging
around somewhere.
(laughing)
Well, we'll know the
truth soon enough.
Miss Matsudaira and
our intrepid boss
are out finding the answers now.
- [Koume] A date?
What does this mean?
(slurping)
Hmm.
I'm sorry to keep asking,
but are you sure
you didn't do it?
No, I don't know anything.
Hmm.
Then who, or what,
could have done it?
Well, that's what you get
paid the big bucks for,
isn't it?
Mm-hm.
Now that you've pumped my brain,
I guess the conversation's over.
I'll take care of it this time.
All I ask is for you to
keep your eye on Momiji.
Uh-huh, buying me tea is
a pretty cheap pay off.
- [Sawaguchi] Oh yes,
I owe you for watching
Kaede as well, don't I?
Huh?
(mysterious music)
(laughing)
Beautiful!
It's like a dream!
(yelling)
Oh, thank you.
I know you, I've seen
you before haven't I?
You've been watching me for a
long long time, haven't you?
You've been watching over me,
protecting me, all my life.
Thank you.
I need to know more
about your past.
Please, you know that
we need your help,
and I don't wanna
make another mistake,
not like I did with Kaede.
There's nobody under the
white gate, except this man,
but there's only one
grasshopper on the big column,
from which the paint has begun
to peel in several places.
- [Momiji] Kusanagi...
What am I doing?
(laughing)
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- [Azusa] Based on the food
remaining in the stomach,
it would appear that the
Aragami was merely a stray dog,
which became
possessed by a Mitama.
The Mitama, on the other
hand, is quite unique.
It's very different
from the types
we've previously encountered.
There's a new type of Aragami?
Our current investigation
will clear up the mystery.
But if the Mitama is like
the Aragami equivalent
of the human brain, then
the higher thought centers
of this one are
extremely underdeveloped.
Huh?
Hm, so learning the
origins of this Aragami
may be even more
important than usual.
Probably so.
Right, that's enough
briefing for me!
Let's go out and
catch some Aragami!
- [Yaegashi] Koume,
you don't know
where these Aragami are do you?
Huh?
Are you saying that
you can find them?
(laughing)
Of course.
When I navigate,
it's smooth sailing.
Hah, you just leave
everything to me, Koume.
(growling)
(upbeat music)
(laughing)
Well, I'm sure my strategy
is right, but yikes.
I guess I need to
work on the execution.
Well, seeing as how
your strategy is
to try and catch every
stray dog in this city,
you're damn right you'd
better work on it, navigator!
(barking)
(yelling)
Who killed those hellhounds?
I just can't figure it out.
Kusanagi!
Hmm...
And the pitcher throws to first!
- [Kusanagi] Ow!
Ah, I'm sorry, I didn't
think I'd hit you!
Don't worry about it.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
(relaxed music)
A movie would be kinda nice,
but all that's showing
now are cartoons for kids.
Well, how bout the
planetarium, I mean, huh?
He's over there already!
Hey, wait for me!
(alarm blaring)
Sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm really sorry!
Why are you always so dense?
Come on!
- [Momiji] Kusanagi's
hand is so big.
(ethereal music)
(upbeat music)
(whimpering)
I wonder if there's some
secret rendezvous around here?
(laughing)
Maybe there's some
romantic spot hidden here
that only Kusanagi knows of!
(giggling)
(cymbals crashing)
Wait a second, this
is the hotel district!
He can't be, no way!
Momiji, are you
feeling anything yet?
Well, not really.
Try!
Are you asking me to
force my feelings?
It doesn't work that way!
- [Kusanagi] I guess I must
have picked the wrong place.
I'll say you did!
I've got an idea, why don't
we just go to the park?
The park, huh?
I guess we could try it.
Hey, wait for me!
Most canines are very
territorial and seldom leave
their chosen hunting grounds,
so I don't think this
method of investigation
is the wrong way to
go about finding them.
- [Koume] Hey little
puppy come on, come here.
Good boy, good!
I got him.
Maybe I'm going out on a limb,
but I can't help but feel
that we wouldn't be
having these problems
if people wouldn't let
their pets run wild.
You're probably right.
Poor little guy.
What's the matter
puppy, what's wrong?
Huh?
(growling)
Oh, boy!
- [Momiji] Um, I
hope you like this.
Oh, thank you.
Um, it's not very beautiful,
but I'm sure it tastes
better than it looks.
(slurping)
And?
I've eaten worse.
(laughing)
Oh my gosh, I think this
is the one I made for you.
They look exactly
the same to me.
Yes, but I don't like cucumbers,
so I didn't put any
in the one for me.
You know, neither your
height nor breasts will grow
if you keep being so picky.
(groaning)
(slurping)
This is my favorite place.
There's so many trees
that I could almost feel
as if I were back in Izumo.
I was born in Izumo.
I went to school in Izumo.
I guess I figured I'd spend
the rest of my life there.
I thought I'd graduate
and fall in love.
Maybe get married
when I was around 23.
Girls think about
things like that.
Hmm?
I still find it so
hard to believe.
I mean, I've never
thought I'd move to Tokyo,
and now I've even
eating cucumber slices.
I'm sorry if I'm boring you.
To tell the truth, actually,
I don't like cucumbers either.
(laughing)
I'd say that the two of us get
along pretty well together.
Wouldn't you, Momiji?
Yeah!
Tastes nasty?
Mm-hm.
Well, I guess it's
time to get back
to looking for Aragami again.
- [Momiji] Aragami?
Come on!
What's wrong, are
you getting sleepy
after all that food?
The reason you asked me out
was because of my
Mitama tracking power.
Huh?
I got up early and
made our lunches
and my heart was pounding,
and I thought that...
I'm so dumb.
(sobbing)
Hey, wait up!
Huh?
(groaning)
(growling)
Yaegashi!
(yelling)
(screaming)
(groaning)
(yipping)
(growling)
(slashing)
(humming)
(laughing)
Well, the misunderstanding
was my fault, but...
(sighing)
Even so, how could
I ever smile again?
I've gotta try.
(screaming)
(gasping)
What?
(growling)
It's the Aragami that
Kusanagi was looking for!
Kusanagi?
(screaming)
It's dangerous, stay back!
- [Momiji] Because you
need to protect my Mitama?
- [Kusanagi] What?
What stupid thing are
you talking about now?
It's not stupid to me!
I can do anything
that I wanna do!
You know, you're always
bossing me around!
Well, I've got
news for you buddy!
It's not gonna be
like that from now on!
I have a Mitama, just like
you, and I don't know...
(shouting)
(dramatic music)
Let me go!
If I didn't like you,
I wouldn't protect you!
I've been waiting for you,
and the person who killed
your littermate should
be right behind you.
(grunting)
Come on, lead me to
our common enemy!
(yelling)
(grunting)
Damn!
Kusanagi!
(groaning)
Kusanagi! Kusanagi!
You idiot, keep yourself hidden!
(shrieking)
Momiji, get out of there!
(screaming)
(howling)
Run, Momiji!
(screaming)
Oh no!
(panting)
(yelling)
No!
(roaring)
(grunting)
(slashing)
- [Kusanagi] So the mystery
man arrives at last.
I'm sorry I couldn't
wait for you.
Turn around and show me your
face, you long-haired jerk!
- [Murakumo] So,
you're Kusanagi.
What?
(laughing)
How do you know my name?
Kusanagi?
Interesting, I didn't know
the Kushinada was with you.
Who are you?
Yeah!
- [Murakumo] I am
called Murakumo.
- [Kusanagi] Why did
you kill these Aragami?
- [Murakumo] You'll
find out soon enough.
- [Kusanagi] You jerk,
what does that mean?
Ask me that the
next time we meet?
(laughing)
(shrieking)
Well, since the Aragami
have been killed,
I guess my Mitama and
I will go home now.
Momiji!
I'm sorry that we had
a misunderstanding.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I think I understand
everything perfectly well.
You never do what
you're told, do you?
I don't follow blindly.
I can't believe how
you childish you are,
both in attitude
and breast size!
Well, excuse me!
I hate you!
(shouting)
Ha!
(soft music)
The lunch was delicious.
(tires screeching)
Here they are, late as usual.
Well, I'll let
them sort this out.
Just what are you up to?
- [Momiji] Well since
Kusanagi is my partner,
I'm guessing there's
gonna be a lot of problems
involved in our working
together from now on.
You know, an awful lot
of high school girls
have already have a
lot of experience.
At kissing, I mean.
But Kusanagi wouldn't know that,
cause his big fat potato head
doesn't have the slightest
idea what romance is anyway!
Well, it's all right with me
because everybody knows
that 15 year old girls
who kiss guys are nothing
but a bunch of tramps.
It's the next episode
of Blue Seed, number 10,
Innocence! Love! My First Kiss?!
He's gonna do what with my lips?
(funky music)
(singing in foreign language)