(exciting music)
(adventurous music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(singing in foreign language)
(chiming)
(eerie atmospheric music)
(metal clanking)
(cicadas chirping)
Please awaken, Lord Susanoo.
(crying)
This human-infested
Nara countryside
must not please him either.
(cosmic whirring)
(wind rustling)
(lightning zaps)
(roaring)
♪ 99 bottles of
beer on the wall ♪
♪ 99 bottles ♪
(crashing)
- [Man] What?
What the...
Hey, is that a deer?
That's too tall to be a deer.
Hey, are you a deer?
(screaming)
- [Momiji] A Chase
Down Yamato Highway.
- [Kusanagi] Love Under Fire.
(train engine whooshing)
- [Sugishita] Anaphylactic
shock caused by the symptoms
of acute type one
antibody-dependent anaphylaxis.
- [Kome] Hmm.
- [Sugishita] According
to the serum tests,
they found huge amounts of IGE,
or immuglobin-E, type
antibodies in the bloodstream.
- [Matsudaira] In
other words, an extreme
allergic reaction to pollen.
Based on the evidence found
in the nearby thicket,
we can surmise that
the Aragami was
about 50 meters long.
The victim must have
died almost immediately.
It really looked like it hurt.
- [Kome] Hey, I got an idea!
- [Sugishita] Oh?
Let's go get something to eat!
(sighing)
Well anyway.
Yeah?
(gobbling)
What happens next?
Well, we change trains
to Kintentsu at Kyoto,
then when we get to Nara
we have to contact the
police headquarters.
Idiot, I'm talking
about with Kusanagi.
What are you gonna do next?
I already told you.
I'm gonna wait and
see what happens.
(roaring)
You are driving me crazy!
(gobbling angrily)
(lighthearted music)
You told him you
loved him, didn't you?
(sighing)
(growls)
Well, I guess I kinda did.
(shrieks)
That was what...
The others wrote this,
but I really do feel
that way about you.
I'm in love with you, Kusanagi.
You know, when I stop
to think about it,
I really did do something
kinda dumb, didn't I?
I mean, I don't know
if Kusanagi saw it
or even heard a word I said.
(groans)
I'll never get married.
Why do you keep making all
those strange looking faces?
(whimpering)
(shrieks)
Do you think he saw my panties?
(sighing)
(shrieks)
(sighs) Still the
same old Momiji.
- [Momiji] Kusanagi!
You really gotta learn
to be more steady
on your feet in public.
Did you see them?
What?
My panties, last time,
did you see them?
See them last time?
You mean the ones with
the bears on them?
Or was it the penguin panties?
Or do you mean the
hippopotamus ones?
So I guess you didn't
see them after all.
- [Kusanagi] You came here
to chase Aragami, didn't you?
Yes!
Didn't you feel her energy?
Kaede's energy.
Don't you feel it?
No, sorry.
You really don't
need to apologize.
Kusanagi!
Kusanagi.
(all sighing)
What an awful situation.
I still can't
believe she's alive,
not only that, but she's
also helping the Aragami.
The Kushinada was
supposed to marry
with Susanoo wasn't she?
Hmm.
(phone ringing)
- [Takeuchi] Hello,
Takeuchi speaking.
- [Kunikida] Routine
communication.
Have you arrived at Nara?
- [Takeuchi] Yes sir.
We're going to visit the
local police stations
in the site of the incident.
- [Kunikida] As soon
as this meeting is over
I'll take a helicopter
and join up with you.
Until then you're in charge.
- [Takeuchi] Who is this
person sent from the US?
Did the Japanese
government even ask
the US government to send help?
- [Kunikida] I've
received no information.
However, I've been
assured that this is
a very good professional
faith healer.
Susanoo is once again
linked to the Aragami,
as is the Kushinada,
and Kusanagi.
Why do all of these
characters match
the ancient Japanese myth?
Perhaps the person in
this room will help us
answer these questions.
(water running)
(doorbell rings)
(gasping)
(upbeat pop music)
Hi.
You're that girl!
How are you?
I'm thank, fine, you.
Um, excuse me but
why are we here
when you said we'd go
straight to the site?
Nara is famous for its
shrines and temples.
If we didn't come and pray, it
would be like tempting fate.
Oh.
But I didn't think
Yaegashi would join us.
So, Kome.
What? What do you want?
How does it work?
Work?
Yeah, like will
it punish someone
who really deserves it?
Punish?
Yes, punish!
I thought that everything
was gonna be okay
for you, Momiji.
All I wanted was
for you to be happy!
Happy!
(growling)
That's why I gave you
my favorite panties,
even if they were for my rival.
How dare that bastard
treat you that way?
Who, Kusanagi?
He's such a jerk!
How can he treat you like that?
But he's...
Sawaguchi, tell me how
to make this thing work!
Well, it's easy.
First, you promise
to do something
and then you ask for
something in return.
Like, if you give up
drinking for a year
then your prayer
will be answered.
I see.
Hmm, I make a promise.
Hmm.
(beeping)
- [Takeuchi] Where are you?
The Aragami is back.
(dramatic music)
(gasping)
- [Man] Come on, let's go!
Hurry up.
It's near the intersection
of Prefectorial Road nine
and 122, near the Akushi Temple!
(explosion booms)
(gunshots firing)
(roaring)
(whooshing)
(coughing)
(crashing)
(tires squealing)
Ah, blast it I've never
had hay fever before
and I'm not about to start now,
it's pruning time!
No!
Kome come back!
This isn't regular pollen!
(sneezing)
Damn! What a pain!
(coughing)
- [Momiji] Kome, hold on!
We'll be right there!
(coughing)
- [Yaegashi] Hurry
up and put this on!
(roaring)
(shouting)
Hurry up, Yaegashi!
(gunshots firing)
Momiji!
(crashing)
(screaming)
- [Momiji] Kome!
- [Kome] I've pollen
and I can't get up.
- [Yaegashi] You're heavy, Kome.
Are you all right?
I got it!
- [Both] Huh?
- [Takeuchi] Let me do it!
No!
I have to fight it,
I have to do this!
Momiji!
(dramatic music)
- [Momiji] I won't
screw up, Kusanagi.
I made a vow.
I prayed that if I
killed the Aragami
without your help,
that you'll love me
the way I love you.
That's why...
(crashing)
(Aragami roaring)
I did it!
(dreamy music)
(roaring)
I did it!
(whooshing)
(coughing)
- [Yaegashi] Here,
let me help you.
- [Kome] Nuts, I can't see
anything with all this pollen.
Momiji!
(shrieking)
- [Momiji] Kusanagi!
Stand back.
- [Momiji] Okay.
Oh wait, no, no! You can't!
I mean...
I mean, I can't,
I mean you're not
supposed to help!
- [Kome] Momiji, I
got my bazooka back!
Let's finish it now.
Momiji, stay here.
No!
(high-pitched ringing)
Kusanagi.
Kaede?
Kaede!
- [Momiji] Kusanagi!
(crashing)
(roaring)
- [Kome] Damn, it got away!
(sighs) Kusanagi.
(atmospheric music)
(bells tinkling)
Where are you Kaede?
With the information
I've gathered
from the local fire department,
and the self-defense force,
I've plotted the areas damaged
by the pollen on this map.
Assuming that the same
Aragami has been the cause
of both incidents, I've
drawn this conclusion.
Ceder trees within a
two kilometer radius
of the sides have come into
an abnormally fecund bloom.
The Nara forests are
largely comprised of ceders.
If this continues, the
entire surrounding area
will become uninhabitable.
Please, you have to do
something to help us!
This 1000 year old resort town
is slowly being destroyed!
- [Matsudaira] Don't worry.
We have a surefire new weapon.
New weapon?
I asked to have a prototype made
of a plasma
photosynthesis laser.
Konsei Biochemical
was in the process
of developing it.
Uh, Matsu, do you think
you could put that
in layman's terms?
In other words,
it's an artificial
photosynthesis machine.
Mm, do you know
any smaller words?
Yaegashi, why don't
you run the demo?
Yaegashi!
Uh, yes.
By shooting both positive
and negative electroids
into the Aragami, we could cause
an electric photosynthesis.
However, the detonator has to be
within one kilometer
from the electrodes.
We'll have to act very quickly
and be very precise.
All right!
I can handle shooting
electrodes, no problem!
Momiji, you let me know
where that sucker is!
Huh?
Momiji?
(chuckles)
I'm sorry.
(sighs)
(growling)
(breathing heavily)
- [Momiji] Kusanagi.
Hey.
Kusanagi's going to be back.
Buck up, kiddo.
Oh, no Kome you've
got it all wrong.
I'm not depressed at all.
I mean, I haven't been dumped.
- [Kome] Uh, well...
- [Momiji] Yet.
- [Yaegashi] Forget about
that stupid plant boy.
(gasping)
Just forget all about that...
that jerk, and let me
take care of you, Momiji!
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
What are you...
- [Yaegashi] I'll treat you
well, and I'll protect you
no matter what happens, Momiji!
I swear I will!
Mr. Yaegashi, what's
gotten into you?
I made a sacred deal!
I told the gods I would
shoot the electrodes
into the Aragami all by myself,
if in return you and I
would always be together.
I'm not giving up on you yet.
(yelps)
What?
Yaegashi, this isn't a game.
It's serious!
I know this is serious,
and I wasn't joking!
Uh...
Yaegashi?
Damn, that guy's brave.
Sugishita!
(yelps)
Mr. Yaegashi...
(whirring)
(growls)
(rumbling)
(people panicking)
- [Man] Hey, the
ground's shaking!
(dramatic music)
(coughing)
(people screaming)
Take cover!
Enter the news building and
shield the entrance tightly!
(growling)
This looks good.
(screams)
Hey, come on!
Yaegashi, let's go!
I'm coming!
(roars)
(engine revving)
Yaegashi seems to be
getting into this stuff.
- [Momiji] Mr. Yaegashi, I...
If I can kill this Aragami
without getting his help
please make Kusanagi love
me the way I love him.
(crashing)
- [Kome] Ah, nuts!
I can't aim at it
under these conditions!
- [Yaegashi] We only
have one electrode each!
We can't afford to miss!
- [Kome] You're
telling me not to miss?
Yes, I've got a perfect shot!
(grunts)
I did it!
Yaegashi, you're next!
- [Yaegashi] Just
shut up and drive!
That's not good!
If it goes into the
temple, we can't attack it!
Hey Yaegashi, I'll kill you
if you harm a single hair
on that Buddha's head!
Sugishita, fire
around and cut it off!
Right!
Okay everybody, hold on tight!
(tires squealing)
- [Kome] Oh no, we're too late!
(shouting)
(laughing)
The lovely priestess Sakura
has put a holy
seal of protection
around this temple.
- [Kunikida] Takeuchi,
did she make it?
- [Takeuchi] Boss, the faith
healer you were talking about
was Sakura Yamazaki?
(giggling)
(crashing)
Mr. Yaegashi!
Don't worry, Momiji!
I know I can do it!
I swear I'll make you
happy, no matter what!
(growling)
- [Momiji] Mr. Yaegashi.
Momiji!
I'm sorry, Mr. Yaegashi.
You're nice to say
such sweet things,
but I'm sorry.
(grunts)
Bullseye!
(zapping)
(cracking)
(screaming)
(crashing)
Kusanagi!
Sorry I'm late, princess.
That's okay!
I was able to keep my promise.
Huh?
(chuckles)
Nothing, never mind.
Uh, Momiji, I...
Yamato is a wondrous place,
a hidden valley in the country
where the great mountain ranges
come together in greeting.
This place is the setting
of your favorite poem,
my dearest Kaede.
Oh, it's so beautiful!
It's like we're seeing
a real living part
of Japanese history!
You've recovered from your
broken heart pretty quickly.
- [Momiji] But he
came to rescue me,
so I don't have to
give up hope yet.
That a girl, Momiji.
(shrieking)
The wind from Masca
causes the clothes
of the cortisone to
wave in the breeze.
It should be causes
the hem of her skirt
to wave in the breeze,
right peeping tom?
(all laughing)
Kusanagi, I won't be depressed,
and I won't give up on you,
but what are you going to do
the next time you see Kaede?
What kind of person is Kaede?
(sighs)
(laughs)
Mr. Kunikida.
(giggles)
(trees crashing)
- [Kunikida] Well, we've
remedied the current situation,
but we still don't know
why Susanoo has appeared
or what he's up to.
Meanwhile, a strange
phenomenon is taking place
all over Japan.
Large areas of trees
are dying inexplicably.
Are these really
signs from Susanoo?
Everything is shrouded
in a veil of mystery.
(intense music)
- [Momiji] I wonder what
kind of person Kaede is.
What is it about her that
makes Kusanagi so upset?
Every time I think about
it, I almost get depressed.
But, no!
I won't let it get me down.
I'll just eat some
kappa cucumber rolls
and put on a happy face.
What?
You're not talking about sushi?
You're talking about
the Kappa monster
from the Tono legend?
Oh man, I don't
even like cucumber!
It's the next episode
of Blue Seed, number 15,
Lost and Trembling on
a Trip to Michinoku.
I like salmon roe
and sea urchin sushi.
(lighthearted pop music)