(thunder booming)
("Carnival Babel")
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
My name is Momiji Fujimiya
and I was born in Izumo,
the birthplace of
many Japanese myths.
Until recently, I thought I was
a normal high school student.
But then, I was attacked
by a horrible monster,
and nothing will ever be
the same for me again.
The monster was an Aragami.
Unfortunately, the target of
their latest assault was me.
The reason is that I'm a little
different from other people.
I am the Kushinada.
(gentle humming)
Huh?
(screams) I'm late, huh?
Where am I?
(Momiji yells)
(upbeat music)
(Momiji gasps)
Uh.
I'm in Tokyo!
What's going on?
Oh, my brain hurts!
(Momiji groans)
It wasn't a dream!
I really must be a sacrifice
for the Aragami!
(bird demonically crowing)
- [Crow] Kushinada!
(ethereal music)
(crow caws)
- [Ryoko] So, the
Kushinada is awake?
- [Kunikida] Yes,
I checked her out
of the hospital last night.
I've got her here
at my house for now.
- [Ryoko] And have you told her?
- [Kunikida] She's
reading the letter
from her Grandmother right now.
Dear Momiji...
Grandma, what'd you
write this with?
A chicken foot?
I can't read this!
- [Grandma] How are
you feeling, Momiji?
Huh?
- [Grandma] I'm sorry
for not warning you,
and I imagine that much of this
has come as a big surprise.
As the descendants of the
original Princess Kushinada,
our family has inherited the
power to stop the Aragami,
although the cost of that
power is our own lives.
I never told you this,
but you had a twin sister.
When you were born, we
allowed Kaede to be adopted.
We thought it would
help protect her,
but when she was
killed by the Aragami,
the power, and the
responsibilities,
of the Kushinada
now belong to you alone.
I know you're young, and
I know it's not fair,
but only you can
stand against them.
And, should the time come,
I know you'll do
what must be done.
Your Mother and I
have entrusted you
to the care of Mr. Kunikida.
His agency, the TAC, is the
only organization capable
of protecting you until
the Aragami are destroyed.
Please trust them.
(groans) Yeah, right!
I fell asleep in Izumo
and woke up in Tokyo!
I've been sold into slavery
by my own grandmother.
Someone could've at
least asked me first.
Really!
(television remote beeping)
Huh?
Wow, look at all the
channels they've got!
Well, at least
it's a nice prison.
Maybe being the Kushinada
won't be as bad as I thought.
(Momiji groans)
They don't still
sacrifice people, do they?
(gasping)
No, no, wait, no, no, no!
(men laughing)
(groans)
(playful music)
This is dumb.
Mr. Kunikida wouldn't
really sacrifice me
to the Aragami, would he?
Hi.
(Momiji yelps)
I see you survived.
Kusanagi.
What are you doing here?
You're not still trying
to kill me, are you?
(Momiji screams)
I thought so.
This blue thing?
Do you know what it is?
It's like the ones
in your hands.
I guess I was wrong about you.
Looks like you're just an A-cup.
Jerk!
Pervert!
- [Kusanagi] Woo-wee, you
must be feeling better
if you can move that quickly!
You know, I've heard
that isometrics
are good for
developing the bust!
Oh, will you shut up?
You really shouldn't
let the TAC see that.
In fact, the less the
TAC knows, the better.
- [Momiji] What do you mean?
They may have good intentions,
but knowledge is power.
Don't give them a weapon
to use against you.
See ya!
Wait!
Kusanagi!
(car rumbles)
(Momiji yelps)
Good morning.
(Momiji groans)
Nice morning, don't you think?
Sir, we've reviewed
the overnight report
from the metropolitan police.
Between last night
and this morning,
there were six abnormal
homicides reported
in greater Tokyo.
Out of the six, five were almost
certainly Aragami attacks.
Have they asked us to help?
No, neither the secretariat
nor the public
safety commissioner
has asked us to step in.
All right, keep monitoring
their investigation.
If they run into any of the
Aragami, they'll need our help.
Right, Momiji?
Huh, yeah.
(Momiji sighs)
Sir, just how will
you stop the Aragami?
(Kunikida grunts)
There are several ways.
Could you name one?
Now, now,
why worry yourself about
those sort of things now?
Is it all right for me
to ask where we're going?
Well, where would
you like to go?
You know, your Mother
and Grandmother
have legally placed
you in my custody.
(Kunikida laughs)
(Momiji yelps)
I never even had a
chance to fall in love.
I've never been on a date.
I've never gone to
an amusement park
and I still haven't been kissed!
All right, let's go!
(Momiji grunts)
(upbeat synth music)
(cheering)
- [Koume] I'm bored.
- [Ryoko] So am I.
Well...
Do you wanna join
them on the rides?
Not me.
This was all Kunikida's idea,
he can babysit the Kushinada
while we go help the others
in the pit.
Huh?
This is the excavation
where Kaede disappeared.
We've closed the site to
search for Aragami artifacts.
Hey, over here.
On the defense force, they
called me the Hurricane.
Here, I'm just a
freaking pack mule.
Oh, get over it.
Damn!
Fighting monsters is
fine, but this sucks!
I'd rather be that
pampered sacrifice.
(Momiji yells)
(Kunikida screams)
Sir, are you all right?
I'm feeling just fine.
Maybe I'd better
go get a doctor.
No, I feel fine.
Mr. Kunikida!
I think I'm the one
who needs protection.
(Kunikida and Momiji laugh)
Sir?
What?
Could you at least tell
me what the Aragami are?
Where do they come from?
It's a long story.
(crow caws)
- [Kusanagi] Not again.
Ogres, goblins,
sprites and fairies,
since the dawn of history,
mankind has invented many
strange mythological creatures,
but not all of them are just
figments of the imagination.
Oh.
- [Kunikida] Take a
look at these photos.
Can you tell what these
creatures have in common?
No.
It's a trick question.
The Aragami have no
bodies of their own.
That's how they live so
long, hopping body-to-body.
Did you notice
anything unusual about
the one you
encountered in Izumo?
It was a plant.
Right!
In that case, the Aragami
took the form of a tree.
It's our hypothesis that the
Aragami are plants themselves.
During the day, they
photosynthesize,
and store energy.
They become more
active at night.
Monsters, ghosts, demons;
they're all creatures
of the night.
Somehow, I don't think
it's a coincidence.
But, what do I?
Huh?
What am I supposed to do?
I'm sorry, so many strange
things have been happening
to me so quickly,
and I know everyone
keeps telling me
that I'm different
from everyone else,
but that doesn't tell me
what I'm supposed to do now!
Well?
Why don't you go out
and do some sightseeing?
You know, the room
you're staying in now
is yours for as
long as you like.
That's not an answer!
(phone rings)
Kunikida here.
Sir, the Aragami are back!
Location?
You won't like it.
They're in Tokyo!
The metropolitan police
have asked us to step in.
As near as we can tell,
there are two Aragami,
and they're fighting each other.
Right now, they're
moving toward Shinjuku.
All right, I'm on my way,
and tell Koume not to use
firearms inside the city.
(chuckling)
(gun fires)
(Yaegashi screams)
Too late, sorry, Sir.
Huh?
Ah, he hung up.
- [Momiji] I'm going with you.
- [Kunikida] No, you'll
be staying right here.
Why should I?
Just because.
Let me have a gun!
Hey, wait!
I said no!
Forget it!
Is this what the rest
of my life will be like?
(sad string music)
Go ahead, say it!
I'm too valuable to
be risked, right?
Momiji, I...
Can't you see?
I'd rather fight the Aragami
than spend my whole life
waiting to be sacrificed.
I said no, Momiji.
I want you to stay
here, where it's safe.
Mr. Kunikida!
No!
I knew it.
I'm not a person,
I'm just a sacrifice.
It's glowing again.
(gentle humming)
(deep bass music)
(grunting)
You're after the Kushinada,
but I won't let you have her!
(Kusanagi yells)
(growls) Where did it go?
Kushinada!
Where are you?
(gun blasts)
Hold it!
Make one false move
and I'll blow you away!
Yeah, right.
Sorry, I don't
have time to play.
All right!
Bug off!
(Koume yells)
Right, you're dead!
Nap time!
Sorry about that.
Next time, listen to me.
Don't move!
You again!
Yeah, that was
good work in Izumo.
Just whose side
are you on, anyway?
The Aragami's or ours?
This is the third time
we've run into you.
We know you helped save the
Kushinada's life in Izumo.
So, it's none of your business.
If you are on our side,
would you allow our
scientists to examine you?
We need to find out how
the Aragami function.
I promise you won't be harmed.
- [Kusanagi] Wait a
second, where's Momiji?
What?
You jerks, you
left her all alone?
(foreboding synth music)
- [Crow] Kushinada!
What's going on?
It's getting stronger.
(rumbling)
(gasping)
Who's there?
(monster caws)
(Momiji gasps)
- [Monster] Kushinada.
Kushinada!
(Momiji screams)
- [Monster] At last, Kushinada.
I can't give up, I can't!
Come on, come on!
Oh, no, it's locked!
(Momiji screams)
(monster laughs)
- [Monster] A blue seed.
I didn't know you
had Orochi's soul.
This thing's glowing again.
I get it!
It's reacting to you!
- [Monster] I'll
reclaim Orochi's seed
once I've ripped
you limb-from-limb!
(monster laughs)
(Momiji screams)
Trapped you are.
Such a pity.
It's not over, yet.
I won't let you take me alive!
- [Monster] Struggle, suffer,
it will avail you not!
(coughing)
What?
- [Monster] I've sealed
you inside a ceramic field!
Prepare to die.
A ceramic field?
- [Monster] Inside that field,
you're just another human,
no longer must we protect
your pathetic existence.
- [Monster] The time has
come for you to die at last.
Ow, ow, no!
(yelling)
(grunting)
Huh?
- [Monster] Our greatest desire,
our dream of a thousand years,
shall at last be realized.
Let me go!
- [Monster] Fool, your
little gun cannot harm me!
No, maybe not.
But I won't know
unless I try, right?
I won't go easily.
- [Monster] The end is now!
Die, Kushinada! (laughs)
(gun blasts)
(monster screams)
No, the light!
(crow caws)
Got you!
Idiot.
In order to absorb the light,
he had to stop using
his other powers.
And now you know.
The blue seeds are the
souls of the Aragami.
And this one?
A bird has no mind or soul.
The seeds can't control you,
not as long as you're able
to think for yourself.
Ugh, I can't believe
they left you here.
Kusanagi?
Thanks, I was afraid you
were still trying to kill me.
All I wanna do is to
keep killing Aragami,
and the best way to do that
is to keep hanging around you.
Thanks again, I
won't let you down.
(Momiji groans)
Momiji?
Hey...
Momiji!
Look at the walls!
Some kind of fusion melted it!
There.
Momiji!
Nuts!
Ah, what's going on?
What happened?
Momiji!
What a mess!
Oh no!
Yaegashi, call an ambulance!
Right!
This never would've happened
if I'd brought her along.
I should've listened to you.
Yes, but, Sir...
I'm sorry, Momiji.
I just couldn't bear the thought
of losing both you and Kaede.
I never even thought about
what your feelings were.
I tried to keep you locked
up like a precious jewel,
and by leaving you here,
I almost killed you.
Mr. Kunikida.
Momiji!
Are you... I'm all right.
You shouldn't exert yourself.
I'm sorry about the mess.
(Kunikida sighs)
Jeez, you mean you killed
him with a flare gun?
Please, let me help
you fight the Aragami.
Sorry we're late,
come on Momiji.
Ta-da!
Allow me to introduce you
to the Terrestrial
Administration Center's
very newest recruit,
Miss Momiji Fujimiya.
Thank you for having
me on the team.
I promise to do my best to
help the TAC fight the Aragami.
Thank you so much!
Ooh.
Huh?
That hurt.
(everyone laughs)
(soothing synth music)
Hey, it's me again.
I'm Momiji Fujimiya from Izumo.
Think you know all that.
My sign is Libra,
my blood type is O,
and I've just been
made part of the TAC,
but there's problems.
I tried to be nice, but, maybe,
now it looks like I
was a little too eager,
and, well, Miss Sawaguchi's
not happy with me at all.
Will we be able to get along?
Find out in the next
episode of Blue Seed.
More Bad Luck?
Why Does This
Always Happen To Me?
And what does any of this have
to do with fortune telling?
("Touch and Go")