(thunder cracks)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo. ♪
♪ Take it easy
dangerous night. ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo. ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game. ♪
♪ The shade of the
moon is as clear ♪
♪ As it can be,
inviting the night. ♪
♪ The sound of the
klaxon showers out, ♪
♪ The pulse of the quiet city. ♪
♪ Silence, so much
more wearisome ♪
♪ Than loneliness,
is a labyrinth. ♪
♪ Pulling the body
into pleasure. ♪
♪ The shining night is
a sea of illumination. ♪
♪ Blue, the blue time
begins to melt. ♪
♪ The future floats to
the surface ephemerally. ♪
♪ Life glitters in
the same numbers ♪
♪ As the lights,
and then is gone. ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo. ♪
♪ Take it easy
dangerous night. ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game. ♪
(water flowing)
(birds chirping)
(melancholic music)
You muse bare better fruit.
Or I'll have to cut you back.
We will bare better fruit.
Please sir, you must forgive us.
This place is filled
with evil energy.
Like all Japan.
Lord Susanoo, what
shall we do now?
(glass shattering)
(dramatic music)
(guttural growling)
I'm gonna come out
here and kick some-Ah!
- [Crowd] (confused shouting)
Oh my god, what's that?
(crowd shouting)
(monstrous roar)
(sirens wailing)
Lost and Trembling on
a trip to Michinoku!
(confused workers mumbling)
I asked you to leave
the site as it was.
Don't be ridiculous!
We had huge amounts of damage,
and if I had to stop
construction for
whatever reason,
I'd be up to my ears in debt.
Unless, maybe your
organization is going to
pay off my overruns.
But a kappa sea monster
did attack here, didn't it?
Yeah, well, finding
out what happened
is your job isn't it?
Well, that is what
one of your employees
said in his official report.
Report schmort!
Ah
But it's not worth
interrupting construction over!
Hmm...
Hey get a move on,
clean that mess up!
What a bunch of idiots!
There goes a class A jerk.
You said it, I don't think
we're gonna get any useful
information out of anyone here.
Katie, is that you?
You are Katie,
remember me? Yayoi?
Have you forgotten?
Oh I um, I... Um, here.
(shocked gasp)
(cheerful music)
Beautiful!
Yeah and I've got dibs
on the biggest bedroom.
My family was really fortunate
in finding this old
house to renovate.
That's why my dad retired.
- [Mature Woman] So
that's why you transferred
here from Katie's school, right?
- [Yayoi] Yes, I was
really surprised!
I never even knew Katie
had a twin sister!
Speaking of Katie, how is she?
Oh, well, I um...
Katie! Katie!
Kusanagi!
Katie, come back!
Kusanagi don't go!
Katie!
(collective grumbling)
Ah, Katie's just fine!
But she's sorta kinda
out of the country.
Yeah, that's it!
Wah, she's studying abroad?
Wow, she always did
get straight A's!
What, was she really that smart?
Uh-Um...
Oh, now I see!
You didn't go to the
same school as we did.
Oh yes, Katie was the top
student in every class.
And her penmanship
was beautiful!
She was calm and graceful,
and so tidy that a lot
of people mistook her
for one of the teachers!
Sometimes she just seemed
too good to be true!
(melancholic music)
Hmm...
The Japanese countryside,
bumpkins and pumpkins.
Hey, great sake! Have
another Yaegashi!
(drunken mumbling)
At least one thing is certain,
the Aragami have been
active in this area.
Yaegashi, please, could
you go and pick up
the item we discussed tomorrow?
Sure thing!
I'll go get it, sure!
Go get what?
An anti-Aragami thingy-
(drunken laughter)
Hey you can't pour anymore until
you finish what I poured for ya!
(painful moans)
Here, have mine too!
There! (drunken laughing)
there ya go!
If you're going to
the lab tomorrow
keep it within your limits.
I wanna do that but
she's pinning my arm!
How's about that?
You surrender now, do ya? Huh?
(dramatic music)
Why would an Aragami appear
in a place like this?
Is it because
Susanoo's been reborn?
Susanoo...
(gentle sigh)
High grades, neat and sensitive,
so many differences...
(surprised gasp)
- [Yayoi] Momiji, did Katie
ever tell you about her prince?
Huh?
Ah, so she hasn't even told you!
Katie told me once that she
was attracted to someone.
Someone mysterious!
Mysterious?
I guess she hadn't
talked with him
very much or anything.
But he was close to her somehow,
and he protected
her from things.
He was her prince, her
knight in shining armor.
I wonder if their
relationship went anywhere!
Oh well, that's got nothing
to do with us, does it?
Don't catch cold!
Was she talking about Kusanagi?
Hello, Momiji!
Kusanagi, why are you here?
Well wherever there are Aragami
you'll find me.
Oh...
Do you feel anything?
No...
I see.
About Katie, are you
worried about her?
(gasps) of course you are!
Sometimes I can be so stupid
and sometimes I just don't
know what I'm talking about
I mean duh, of course
you're worried about her
duh, I mean come
one-ow that hurt
but you know I, I-(shouting)
Man how could I be such a-
You're such a klutz.
Oh?
Hm...
Katie's a wonderful
person, isn't she?
Oh yes, very wonderful.
She was such a brilliant,
well behaved, and graceful
young lady and I
liked her very much.
I guess she, I mean Katie,
must have recognized Kusanagi.
Ah... hm.
I- I can't compete
against her...
Why?
Because I'm not like her,
I'm clumsy and my grades are bad
and I'm really dumb,
it's hopeless...
I suppose, from
that point of view,
you certainly can't
compete against her at all.
(confused gasp)
What are you guys
doing here in the barn?
I got you computer boy!
Go away! Your breasts!
(drunken yelling)
God help me your breasts!
Here have another drinky!
Um if you don't mind,
Kome let him breathe!
Yaegashi, take that
out of your mouth!
Come on, Yaegashi, let's
go get another round!
Even I would dump you Momiji,
if you've given up on yourself.
Oh no...
We've got to catch
up to our schedule!
Hurry up, hurry up!
(workers shouting)
Oh my god, no!
Hey Aragami! I sure
hope you're having fun!
(monsters shouting)
Ha, don't you really think
you could stand against me?
I've never been defeated!
(aragami roaring)
Hey!
Eat this!
(reciting prayer)
Great now we've got absolutely
no ideas to where
the Mitama might be.
That was real
smooth, faith healer.
What, I was planning on
capturing them alive carrot boy!
Sure you were!
It's the truth, dammit!
(confused yelling)
(nervous laughter)
(angry grumbling)
This place has been
targeted by the monsters,
but since I've sealed
it off, it'll be okay.
Oh, let's put that one there!
I don't care about
your monsters!
What are you gonna
do about my building?
Look, can't you just be
thankful no one was killed?
Jeez some people have
no sense of gratitude.
I will when you leave!
Well that's the second time
they've attacked that
construction site.
Just what are these
Kappa Aragami up to?
Momiji, can't you
sense the Mitama
that's controlling them?
Excuse me?
- [Ryoko] Hey,
what's the matter?
Momiji you've been
acting even stranger
than usual today.
I have?
I mean, no I'm fine!
(mitama whirring)
It's close... very close.
What?
(dramatic music)
Look something moved over there!
Over where, Momiji?
Over there, that way!
So, this is the killer factor
that Matsudaira
wanted us to get?
Yes, this factor is one of the
strongest we've ever discovered.
The advanced tests have
all been very promising.
But we won't really know until
it's been tested in the field.
I see, it's hard to believe
that something so small and
ugly might stop the Aragami.
Eh, I'd better pick up
some plastic explosives
on the way back in.
(grass rustling)
Look!
I see them, in the grass!
Momiji, be careful
and follow me!
This way!
Right!
Momiji!
(monsters roaring)
You're screwing up, as usual.
(guns shooting)
(monsters shouting)
This is bad!
Watch Momiji!
(dramatic music)
(surprised shouting)
(monsters shouting)
Bravo!
Hello, you're a little
late aren't you?
I don't think so...
This was a trap, and that
persimmon tree must
have been the bait.
I'm sorry, I'm stupid,
I'm totally stupid.
Huh, what?
I should have seen it,
of course it was a trap!
I'm so stupid!
I'm sorry, I'm not
smart like Katie-
Momiji!
Aye!
Just how long are you
going to torture yourself
by wallowing in Katie's shadow?
But I don't think that I can
compete with her at all...
Yes, and you're right.
But that's because
you're not the same
Momiji you've been in the past.
Sure, Katie was
smart and graceful
and well behaved and beautiful,
but you know, you've got a
lot of strong points yourself.
Some of which Katie
doesn't have, Momiji.
Or at least the girl
that you used to be does.
The girl I... Used to be?
(shocked gasp)
Come on we can escape
through this hole!
(monsters shouting)
Son of a-
Kusanagi?
And Sakura's there too?
- [Koume] Special delivery!
Sorry we're so late,
here's the killer factor
you ordered, Just in time.
Hurry up!
Hm...
Do you need any help?
Have a little confidence!
Oh, he spit on us!
I can't move!
(monster roaring)
Hmm... it's working.
Splendid I can't get up!
Well try!
Kusanagi!
Momiji don't be stupid!
Hey man, come on, this way!
Don't just stand
there, get them loose!
You idiot, I'm supposed
to be protecting you!
Oh no, end of the line!
Momiji!
(monster roaring)
(pained screaming)
Run, Momiji!
No!
It's working...
What was that?
Well during the
process of making Sake,
some useless
microbes are produced
during the fermentation stage.
This factoring agent
kills the unwanted germs
so we call it a killer factor.
- [Yaegashi] The
killer factor, and the
unwanted Aragami that
has infected the planet,
are now fighting each other!
Boy, you sure are exasperating.
But that's just
the way you are...
I- I suppose so...
That's just the way I am!
(happy laughter)
I didn't get a
chance to show off
all my powers again because
of that stupid sacrifice girl!
I may have to reconsider
the terms of my
cooperation contract
with your boss!
(upbeat music)
The construction will
continue, won't it?
I wonder if the
persimmon tree was trying
to protect this little shrine.
I don't know, but
if it was protecting
this shrine, then it
was protecting a part
of mother earth that we
ourselves have abandoned.
Perhaps this is tied into
the strange phenomenon
of dying trees which has
been going on all over Japan.
- [Koume] Do ya think that
the Aragami are behind it?
- [Yaegashi] I don't
know, but what if
all the anger the earth
must harbor against
human beings were
unleashed at once?
If the Aragami were
able to focus it?
It would be the end of life
as we know it, Armageddon.
(bulldozer plowing)
- [Momiji] A man has
committed suicide
in the village of Wakasa
in the Fukui prefecture.
And, as I understand
it, the victim was
an old friend of Mr. Kunikita's.
Now Mr. Kunikita
must make the journey
to see his friend's
widow, there's a very
sad and tragic tale
behind all of this.
The story of pale blue
tears that lasts forever.
The next episode of Blue
Seed, number sixteen,
Japan is a paradise,
tears in Wakasa.
Why do human beings exist?
(mellow music)
♪ I don't know when
and why in my dream ♪
♪ We were kissing,
just the two of us. ♪
♪ Watching each other's faces ♪
♪ Since a long time ago, ♪
♪ As if we have been
here for a long time. ♪
♪ There's something wrong
and I feel strange. ♪
♪ The red sunrise
penetrates into my eyes. ♪
♪ The blue real is born, ♪
♪ So deep inside of my heart. ♪
♪ I'm sorry for telling
you love was unneeded, ♪
♪ Making you lose your way. ♪
♪ I'm sure that I'll
be sad as you feel. ♪