(thunder rumbles)
(intense music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(crickets chirping)
(owls hooting)
(eerie music)
(wings flapping)
Whoa what was that?
Ah!
Prefectural police headquarters!
This is the Lake
Suwa Police Station.
There's a monster in the lake!
Huh?
(monster roars)
(eerie music)
Dear Mr. President,
R-E the Aragami report.
(computer beeping)
(Sakura giggles)
Now I'll finally
make some real money,
not like the pittance
they pay me at the TAC.
I mean really, a girl's
got to make ends meet.
(glass cracks)
Something is calling me.
(intense music)
(plate clatters)
What, what's happening?
(Kusanagi groans)
Damn, how long is this
going to continue?
The Nozuchi Talisman.
It's finally returned.
(eerie music)
- [Narrator] Geez!
Oh man!
Sakura's Not Good Enough?
(bell tolls)
(kids chattering)
That was the same
feeling I had in Ise.
I wonder if it's because
Susano-Oh is growing.
If I'm right...
Hi!
Good morning little
boys and girls.
I have great news today.
Sakura?
- [Teacher] Well,
this is very sudden,
but Sakura Yamazaki is
quitting school as of today.
(kids clamoring)
(Sakura giggles)
I'm saying adios
amigos to you morons.
I'm going to go to
performing arts school
to fulfill my dream of
becoming a super idol!
Excuse me, Sakura?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
well don't worry.
I promise I won't forget
all you little people
when I'm famous.
So long!
(Sakura giggles)
- [Momiji] Hey wait,
Sakura, what's going on?
Did you feel anything yesterday?
Hm, just as I thought.
You mean Susano-Oh?
Kusanagi!
Not just Susano-Oh.
There's also Nazuchi.
Nazuchi?
An Aragami that my family,
the Tsuchimikado
family had vanquished.
16 years ago when the
Fujimiya sisters were born,
Nazuchi woke up along with
all the other Aragami.
Then my mom, who inherited
the family responsibilities
tried to defeat
Nazuchi, but she failed.
She was in its mouth
in a matter of seconds.
(eerie music)
(birds chirping)
Mommy wasn't real
bright, was she?
If she had been an accomplished
faith healer like me,
she could have won.
Oh well, she was weak.
So, just what happened
to Nazuchi then?
It disappeared to the
bottom of the lake.
I think Mom did her best and
put Nazuchi to sleep somehow.
- [Momiji] But it awoke
yesterday, didn't it?
It sounds like the
growth of Susano-Oh
must have acted like an Aragami
wake up call for Nazuchi.
After I kill the monster,
I'll be able to
quit faith healing.
I'll say goodbye to
the Tsuchimikado family
and become a rockstar!
(Sakura chuckles)
But you can't... Here.
After I make my big stage debut,
I'll let you say you
used to know me, bye.
Wait, Sakura!
Hm, this one's going
to be a load of fun.
What have those
two been smoking?
What?
What is this?
Ah, from Hokkaido to
Okinawa there were 12
Aragami related
incidents last week.
Then the greenery disappeared
from 250 golf courses,
300 different forest
parks and rest stops,
and there's who knows
how many crops have died?
The whole country
looks like my backyard!
It's gotta be the Aragami again,
they've got their
leafy tendrils in this!
Calm down, Sugishita.
How can I be calm with
all that going on?
I've gone from being crown
prince of the discotech
to the king of overtime!
Stop complaining.
Huh?
We've all been working hard.
No kidding, looks like a
homeless shelter in here.
(all snoring)
Geez, do you people
live here or what?
Anyway, why are the Aragami
killing other plants
when they themselves are
basically the same thing?
A good point.
So what do you
say that you and I
go research inside a hotel?
I'm not interested in your twig.
Twig?
Hm.
What's wrong?
Foreign countries
won't keep silent
while Japan is slowly destroyed.
The day will soon
come when others
will learn about the Aragami.
What will happen to the
country of Japan after that?
Mr. Kunikida!
Is school already over?
That's not important right now!
Sakura said she's quitting
school and the TAC!
(tires squeal)
- [Man] Does that
scatterbrained psychic
think we have any
people to spare?
- [Ryouko] You sure are tough
on other people, aren't you?
- [Sugishita] Oh I'm
soft on you, Ryouko.
- [Ryouko] Moron.
- [Kunikida] I hope
she hasn't left yet.
(elevator chimes)
- [Momiji] Wow, what a view!
(Ryouko gasps)
What's the matter, Ryouko, huh?
(ominous music)
Miss Yamazaki, are you there?
Hello, Miss Sakura,
it's me Sugishita,
the handsome detective?
Looks like there isn't
anybody here, huh?
(engine roars)
Wait for me, Nazuchi.
I'll send you to hell myself
with the card of sun
stars and five souls.
Huh?
It's not there, crap!
(horn blares)
- [Sugishita] What is this?
It's the data bank
on the Aragami
that only we're
supposed to have,
and it's been
translated into English.
She's an agent for
the CIA isn't she?
So all that Nazuchi garbage
might just be a smokescreen.
If she's quitting the TAC,
she might be
fleeing the country.
Don't worry, that
whole Nazuchi story
must have at least
some truth to it,
judging by the state
of this hotel room.
Um excuse me?
She had this card
and I think, ah!
Something is coming, there!
Who are you?
Hurry.
Hurry up and use the seal.
The Nazuchi Talisman,
why is it in your hands?
Move!
(groans)
Sugi!
Ryouko!
Miss Takeuchi!
Give me the talisman.
What are you doing?
Mr. Kunikida!
(ominous music)
No!
(Momiji screams)
Kusanagi!
Who or what are you?
You'll have to do
better than that, huh?
Not again!
Kusanagi!
What's going on?
Is Susano-Oh doing this?
Please hurry Sakura, hurry.
The Nazuchi Talisman.
Run quickly!
(intense music)
- [Sakura] What?
Damn!
Where are you guys?
Get here as fast as you can!
Both Miss Takeuchi and Mr.
Sugishita have been hurt!
(all panting)
(explosion booms)
(dramatic music)
Get out of the car,
the wall's collapsing!
Yes sir, ah!
Kuniki!
No!
Hey sacrifice girl, do you
have my magic talisman?
Look out!
(eerie music)
No, I want that Mommy!
I want that one with flowers.
Mommy it isn't fair.
Mommy please.
No.
If you keep crying like that,
I'll give you a
thump on the head.
Oh no, no thump no!
If you're a good girl,
I'll buy it next time.
Really?
Sure.
Mommy.
Mommy, Mommy!
Mommy!
Oh!
Sakura stay there!
(somber music)
Mommy?
Mommy!
(people murmuring)
- [Man] The girl did
some weird incantation.
There's something
wrong with her.
- [Man] Creepy.
- [Man] Who'd adopt
a freak like her?
(Sakura crying)
- [Man] Hello, little girl.
What's wrong with me?
You're what we call a psychic.
Your ability will be quite
useful to some people I know.
Why don't you come with me
to Washington DC, young lady?
And we'll help you develop
your power, Miss Sakura.
- [Mother] Sakura.
Sakura.
Why am I dreaming about my past?
Huh, ah!
Momiji, that sacrifice girl!
Wake up sacrifice
girl, come on wake up!
Sakura?
Where am I?
Oh damn.
We ain't in Kansas anymore.
(ominous music)
What is this place?
It's Nazuchi's stomach.
All of those cars are being
melted by stomach acid.
Even if this vehicle is made
with special plated armor,
I wonder how long
before it goes too.
(ominous music)
- [Girl] Damn, if
Momiji weren't in there
that overgrown slug
would be dead by now!
We have to be careful.
We can't jeopardize the
safety of those two girls.
Damn!
Hey Yaegashi, hurry
up and do something!
The deus ex machina
stuff is your department!
I'm trying to
establish communication
with them inside the monster.
- [Momiji] Mr. Yaegashi,
please respond, Mr. Yaegashi!
Momiji!
Momiji, are you both all right?
- [Momiji] Yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry I messed up like this.
Sakura's fine too, but the
other people in here are...
Oh!
Momiji!
Can you still hear me?
Ah Kusanagi!
(ominous music)
Ew!
The acid is about to
eat through the seats.
We have no choice.
We're getting out of
the car, sacrifice girl.
But what about the...
If we get on the roof, we
can find a way to fight it,
but the risk increases.
All right then.
But I'm bringing this.
Ah!
(stomach rumbling)
(speaks foreign language)
Crap, Nazuchi's just
munching these guys down
like popcorn and candy.
Wait, here Sakura,
will this help?
My Nazuchi Talisman.
You have it.
It's too late for that now!
We'll be digested before
it starts to work.
Well then what do we do?
- [Sakura] Nothing,
this whole thing
is an exercise in futility.
We're done for.
Sakura?
(Sakura laughs)
Why are you laughing?
It's so funny that
it makes me cry.
I'll suffer the same
fate my mother did.
Both mother and daughter.
Both of us weren't good enough.
We both had the same
traditional family weakness.
(somber music)
Sakura, Sakura you can't
just give up like that!
In your hotel room there
was a picture of you
standing there with your mother!
If you love her,
then do it for her!
Don't stop now.
(emotional music)
(Sakura giggles)
Sakura.
Mom?
- [Mother] Sakura!
(stomach rumbling)
(both gasp)
Mommy!
She has a matama.
I'm sorry, Sakura.
Because I was not strong enough,
I was forced to
leave you all alone.
I melded myself with
Nazuchi's matama.
It was the only way to stop it.
For years, Nazuchi and
I have slept as one,
but now that the god
Susano-Oh has awoken,
I can no longer control Nazuchi.
This is why I have
called to you.
Sakura, use the talisman
to destroy me before
I lose control.
Hurry, please.
You must destroy me
to destroy Nazuchi.
Mommy.
No way!
It can't be!
- [Kusanagi] Momiji!
Kusanagi!
(dramatic music)
Do it now Sakura, hurry up!
I can't control
Nazuchi much longer!
Please hurry!
Sakura.
What are you waiting
for, faith healer?
(Kusanagi groans)
(all screaming)
Hurry!
The talisman, do it now Sakura!
You must seal me into
the final darkness!
Oh no!
(dramatic music)
Hurry!
(mother screams)
Sakura!
The talisman, to
me hurry, Sakura!
(Sakura groans)
- [Sakura] Mommy.
Oh no, I can't.
I have lived for so long
with no other thought
but to avenge my mother.
- [Momiji] Sakura.
I will not give up my revenge.
Even though other
people hated me,
or said I was a freak,
I trained myself
in faith healing
so I could heal Nazuchi.
That was my life's goal!
But it wasn't supposed to
happen like this, it's not fair!
I didn't come here just
to kill you, Mommy!
It isn't fair!
I'm sorry, I can't do it!
You weak little girl!
(mother screams)
(both gasping)
If you keep crying like that,
I'll give you a
thump on the head.
Mommy.
No, ah, oh!
- [Sakura] Mommy!
Kusanagi!
- [Kusanagi] Listen,
faith healer.
If you can't do it,
stand aside and I will.
Don't even think about it!
Then do it, or I'll
take care of it myself!
No, this is my responsibility.
I'll handle this!
Sakura!
(speaks foreign language)
Sakura, I'm sorry your life
was full of so much pain.
(emotional music)
Mommy.
Thank you for setting me free.
Rest in peace, Mommy.
(Nazuchi groaning)
(all sighing)
I'm back!
Hey you made it out alive!
Momiji, welcome back!
Hahaha!
(bell tolls)
(kids chattering)
(Momiji yawns)
I stayed up all night.
Good morning!
Sakura, why are you here?
I decided hanging
around you would help me
find Susano-Oh and
kill that little brat.
If Susano-Oh hadn't
awoken Nazuchi,
Mommy could have slept in peace.
I have to avenge her, so I
can't quit being a faith healer
until I've gotten even!
Ah, will you stay
at the TAC too then?
(Sakura laughs)
I'm going to earn
lots of extra money
by selling the data files
that Mr. Kunikida created.
You're not shy about
money, are you?
(Sakura laughs)
- [Sakura] Well I've
got a lot of work to do!
Sakura is number one!
I won't stop to
become a super idol
until I finish making
myself a legend!
- [Momiji] Somehow I don't
quite think she gets it.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] A fog
of seven colors,
a town of mirages,
and two flickering shadows.
Memories of the past to take
our matamas to a faraway place.
Kusanagi, are you leaving
me to go chase Katie?
The next Blue Seed
episode number 19,
Heat Haze!
Start on a Journey!
Love, I Won't be Far From You.
Because I love you,
I can't control you.
(pleasant music)
(singing in foreign language)