(thunder clapping)
(dramatic theme music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy,
dangerous night ♪
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(foreign lyrics)
(upbeat music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
- [Woman] It's 5:36
in the morning.
At long last, the
fatal sun has risen.
The eclipse will start in
six hours and 32 minutes.
And then, the rite of
Matsuri, the ritual
that the gods Susano-Oh
and my sister Katie
have plotted for so
long, will begin.
And, of course,
I have my own rite of
Matsuri to perform as well.
I don't know what will happen,
but there's one
thing I am sure of.
Today is the day,
whether we win or lose,
everything will be over
by the end of today.
That's all I can say.
(gentle orchestral music)
All or nothing.
Decision.
My fate.
(low rumbling)
(mechanical humming
(wind whistling)
- [Man] Katie, are you
sure you won't regret this?
(slow dramatic music)
(soft heart beating)
(soft dramatic music)
Finally, at long last,
the time has come for
this world to be reborn
and I am the one who will
execute the first step.
(slow dramatic music)
(soft heart beating)
(high frequency ringing)
It has begun at last.
The waves of raw energy,
I can feel them in the
very core of my being.
(water splashing)
(sighs)
(high frequency humming)
The artificial kreshinado
pulse isn't stabilizing.
Uh huh, maybe it's
the power supply.
Do you think we ought to
add another generator?
Hm.
Miss Matsudaira, is
everything ready?
- [Matsudaira] The amplifiers
we've installed across
Japan are functional,
but we still haven't
stabilized the pulse generator.
We should be ready by the time
the eclipse starts, though.
I trust you.
The digital broadcast
circuit is ready and
hooked up to the
satellite network.
It's all ready to go, sir.
Yeah, it's a go, sir.
Hm, at thirteen hundred
hours and seven minutes,
a nuclear missile will
be launched at Tokyo.
To succeed, we must complete
our mission before that time.
Are you still willing to risk
your lives to protect Japan?
(group agrees)
- [Man] Finally,
the ancient ceremony
of human sacrifice
is about to begin.
- [Man] This is the end,
the end of an ancient
battle that has lasted
for tens of thousands of years.
One hour and seven minutes
left before the eclipse,
and in another hour, a nuclear
missile ends everything.
(gentle slow music)
(rumbling)
(people panicking)
- [Man] Look at that!
(high frequency chirping)
What's going on?
Sir, the giant plants are
budding all over Japan.
At the same time?
Yes.
Prime Minister,
riots have begun to break
out all across the nation.
So, the end is beginning.
We're out of rations, and the
water supply is running out
and on top of that, the
information that we're providing
to the people is insufficient.
Information.
For the time being, you
must lie to the people.
Also, you must refute
the news broadcast
made regarding the
human sacrifice and make
an official government
announcement to calm the public.
(sighs)
(people shouting)
Hey, buddy, what's
happening here?
Yeah, all this
about the eclipse?
May I have your
attention please?
The following is an
official announcement
from the government of Japan.
We're switching you now to Tokyo
for an important message
from our prime minister.
(sighs)
- [Woman] What's going on?
He's just sitting there
(crowd chattering)
What is up?
Minister!
People of Japan,
I must first apologize to all
of you for a great deception.
(gasps)
The true cause of all
these abnormal disasters
has been a race of monsters
called the Aragami,
which have lived in Japan
since ancient times.
Minister!
But, we have kept
this secret from you.
I am also afraid
that I must tell you
that there is only one known
method of killing the Aragami.
Greetings, people of Japan.
Wait a second, is that the
one they just talked about?
It's the sacrifice chick.
My name is Momiji Fujimiya.
As you saw on the
news the other day,
I was raised as a
human sacrifice to
protect Japan from the Arigami.
My family, the Kushinadas,
have the power to
subdue the Aragami with
a sacrifice of our lives.
When I die, the Aragami
will die with me.
But, I don't want
to give up my life
just because it's
my family's fate to
die as human sacrifices.
(gasps)
So, I'm asking you, please,
give me a chance to fight.
To fight against the
Aragami in a different way.
What is this nonsense?
(grumbles)
Using my powers, the Kushinada,
I can fight the Aragami.
Susano-Oh, the leader
of the Aragami,
is currently sleeping
inside this giant plant
that has grown in the
center of downtown Tokyo.
Using a special device
designed to amplify my powers,
I'm sure I can defeat him,
but if I fail, then
I'll accept my fate
and sacrifice myself
to save Japan.
Maybe I'm being selfish,
but all I'm asking for
is a chance to live.
(crowd shouting angrily)
(baby crying)
I don't care,
just hurry up and do something!
Ridiculous.
Do you think you can make
the people understand
by saying garbage like that?
We told them the truth.
But sir.
I have more faith in
people than missiles.
People of Japan, the eclipse
will begin in 32 minutes.
Your government
has done its best
to bring the situation
under control
by requesting military aid
from our American allies.
However, to ensure your safety,
we must ask you to
please stay calm,
and continue to evacuate
the area surrounding Tokyo.
(animated conversations)
(clock chiming)
(sirens wailing)
(high frequency humming)
The pulse has stabilized.
Shall we begin?
(grunts)
Right.
(gasps)
(wind whistling)
Initiating pulse.
(high frequency humming)
(wind flute music)
(crowd murmuring excitedly)
Confirmation on disc one.
Status is green.
(electronic zapping)
(wind flute music)
- [Momiji] Katie,
please, resonate with me.
(rumbling)
(wind flute music)
It can't be, another Kushinada?
What's the amplification?
We've amplified the
Kushinada pulse over 520.7%.
Susano-Oh ought to be
feeling it right about now.
(high frequency zapping)
(wind flute music)
- [Momiji] (gasps)
This isn't right.
I feel as if something's
warping inside my body.
Something's wrong.
(low frequency rumbling)
No!
(electric crackling)
(explosion blasting)
(zapping)
Whoa, it's a wall of light!
Withdraw!
(men screaming)
This light, this isn't
the one! (screams)
(men groaning)
(electric zapping)
Momiji, oh!
(water rumbling)
(grunting)
Sir. (groaning)
(gasping)
(rumbling)
(animated chattering)
Notify the defense force.
Cordon off the downtown
area immediately.
Sir.
What else can we do right now?
- [Man] Sir, the
eclipse is starting.
(rhythmic drum music)
Damn, looks like Momiji's plan
isn't going to work, is it?
(rhythmic drum music)
(crowd gasping)
(cheery theme music)
(creature growling)
(suspenseful music)
Momiji, Momiji!
(gasps)
Momiji!
- [Momiji] My sister, Katie.
Forget about Katie.
I'm not worried about her.
I'm worried about you.
No, that's not what I meant.
It's my fault that I
wasn't able to reach her.
I'm sure Katie would
help if she knew.
Momiji.
(laughing) I thought
it might be fitting
if you were the one to
kill Lord Susano-Oh,
but I guess I expected
too much of you.
You again.
Stand aside.
I shall establish the
kingdom of the Aragami
and become its king.
However, first, both
Kushinadas must be eliminated.
I don't think so!
(high frequency humming)
(yells)
It would appear there
is at least one more
imperfect soul who
will have to die.
(electronic humming)
(roaring)
(dramatic music)
(crowd gasps)
Murakumo is Orochi?
- [Orochi] Die, Kusanagi.
(eclectic zapping)
(explosion blasting)
- [Momiji] (gasps) Kusanagi!
- [Orochi] Behold.
(evil laughter)
- [Man] What is that?
- [Woman] A ceramic field.
- [Woman] A ceramic field?
Oh, god, not again.
- [Orochi] Kushinada is
powerless within this field.
Now both of you will die.
Finally, you will be together,
united at last in death.
(rumbling)
(shouting)
(loud rumbling)
(suspenseful music)
(grunting)
Oh, no you don't.
I won't let you get away
with this, you monster.
You forgot that I've still got
the eighth seed
you gave to Momiji.
It's mine now.
(aggressive shouting)
(zapping)
(evil laughing)
- [Orochi] Come out, come
out, Katie the betrayer.
- [Man] Mister Prime Minister,
what's happening out there?
- [Prime Minister] I don't know.
Our enemy seems to be
beyond our understanding.
It would appear that
we have no other
choice except to kill the
Kushinada immediately.
Do what?
Mr. Prime Minister,
tell the U.S. to fire
the nuclear missiles now.
- [Prime Minister]
What are you saying?
No missile could hurt
Lord Murakumo now
and we must kill the Kushinada
while she's still
within our grasp.
Oh my god, they're Aragami.
(shot blasts)
(screams)
If the Kushinada is killed,
won't the Aragami
all perish as well?
(laughs) Do you see that?
It's a ceramic field.
- [Man] A ceramic field?
The Kushinada's life
is hanging by a thread
and we are here to cut it.
- [Prime Minister] Go
ahead and shoot me, then.
I'll never do your
bidding, you evil monsters.
Then we'll just have to take
over your body, won't we?
(laughing)
(growling)
God!
(maniacal laughter)
Are you all right,
Mr. Prime Minister?
Who are you?
Inspector Sugashina,
Metro Police, section 24.
I've been investigating
Aragami infiltrators
inside our government.
Filthy cow, I'm
gonna kill you first.
(shouting)
Okay, giant pink turtles.
(laughing) It's amazing how
boring being safe can be.
Of course, this rescue's
still gonna cost you a bundle,
Mr. Prime Minister.
Warn Kunikida.
Kushinada is in danger.
(dramatic music)
(rumbling)
(whimpers)
- [Orochi] Come out, betrayer.
Come out, Katie Kushinada.
Your sister, the
father who raised you
and your former coworkers
are all in my hands.
- [Crowd] Momiji!
- [Orochi] Even Lord Susano-Oh
cannot kill the Kushinada.
(laughing evilly)
I won't let you interrupt
us, you stupid monster.
This fight is between
my sister Katie and me,
so just make like a
plant and buzz off!
My, what a feisty
little princess you are.
(panicking)
- [Together] Momiji.
Let her go, Orochi,
let her go or else!
(gun blasts)
(explosion blasts)
- [Orochi] I should have
known she wouldn't come out.
Therefore, I'll begin
by killing this one.
(screaming)
You die, Kushinada.
- [Katie] Orochi!
(screeching)
I, I knew that you'd
come, my sister.
- [Orochi] (laughing)
After all is said and done,
you're still a human being,
unable to give up your
stupid, foolish emotions.
Hello, Katie.
Be gone, Orochi,
you're in the way.
The hell you say?
(electronic zapping)
(grunts)
(siren wailing)
This is it, this feeling.
(growling)
- [Orochi] Die, Kushinada!
(aggressive shouting)
(roaring)
(crashing rumble)
(humming frequency)
Thank you, Katie.
- [Man] Are you all right?
(roaring)
(crashing)
- [Oroshi] Kusanagi,
having failed to die once,
you're desperate enough
to face me again?
- [Kusanagi] You'll see
whether I'm desperate or not.
I won't let you kill Momiji.
- [Orochi] Even though
you have eight seeds now,
you can't do anything with
that tiny little body.
Killing the Kushinada is
still child's play for me.
(explosion blasting)
Lift ceramic field!
Hi, there.
Looks like you can't kill
that silly sacrifice
girl now, can you?
Camera crew,
did you get a good shot of
me destroying the field?
You betcha.
- [Orochi] If I can't
have the Kushinadas,
then I'll absorb Susano-Oh.
No, you won't!
Momiji, I'll handle him.
You've still got to take
care of your sister.
Make her believe, Momiji!
Make Katie believe
in your power!
I will.
Murakumo, this is our final
battle. (aggressive shouting)
(roaring)
(loud crashing)
Kusanagi.
Your fault.
Our plan won't work.
I now know that we
won't be able to kill
Susano-Oh only using the
amplified Kushinada pulse.
The two pulses, the
resonance from the machine
and the resonance from
my reaction with Katie
were too different in
strength and in feeling.
Momiji, are you saying that
using the pulse generator
to amplify your power
was just a waste of time?
I was afraid this might happen.
That can't be true!
Are you telling me we
don't have any chance
of winning this battle?
Katie, as your sister, I
beg you, please help us.
Can't you trust me, Katie?
Mankind may have polluted
Japan for a long time,
but I know the two of
us working together
could change things.
If all of the people living
in Japan really tried,
I'm sure we can
change everything.
The people who live in
Japan now don't have
the faith to do such a thing.
We cannot trust them with
the future of this land.
Then tell me, why did you
help me just now, Katie?
To simplify the battle.
I would have had to
dispose of Orochi anyway.
I don't want to fight you.
I want to change this land
into a garden of purest green
and you want to cover
it with filthy humans.
It's inevitable.
No, you're wrong.
The polluters of this
blighted land must not win.
It is the mission
of the Kushinada
to prevent such a thing
from ever happening again,
no matter what the cost may be.
You were wrong, Katie.
Maybe I'm a human being
before I'm a Kushinada,
but I know you're wrong!
I believe in mankind and
no matter what you say,
I will save them all!
(laughs) You're already
too late, Momiji.
The cave of the sun
has been sealed.
(electronic ringing)
- [man] Katie!
- [Woman] Katie!
(dramatic orchestral music)
- [Katie] Yes, it
is already too late.
(rumbling)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- [Man] This is the fourth
division in Yokohama.
Something is happening to the
front of the gigantic plants.
- [Man] Captain, the bud
is turning towards us.
- [Man] Let's attack.
- [Man] Wait, we need to
wait until we get the orders.
But sir, we've got
to do something now!
I'm gonna shoot anyway.
(canon blasting)
(growling)
(crowd murmuring confusedly)
(screaming)
Run, all personnel, evacuate!
Too late indeed.
It's not true.
I'll fight, even if I'm
the last one. (crying)
- [Group] Momiji!
(shocked gasps)
(labored breathing)
Turn the artificial
pulse on me again.
That last time,
I felt something.
- [Man] Momiji.
♪ La, la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la la ♪
♪ La la, la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la ♪
What is that?
(aggressive yelling)
(roaring)
- [Orochi] Is it time to
say goodbye, Kusanagi?
Damn you.
♪ La la, la la la ♪
(rustling leaves)
♪ La la la, la la ♪
Prime Minister, the pollen
of that gigantic plant
is spread over a
dozen locations,
at the same time as that
blue light flashed out.
Prime Minister, the US
government wants to make
the final confirmation
on the nuclear missiles.
Shall I say yes or no, sir?
(gentle calming music)
♪ La, la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la ♪
That's the Kushinada.
♪ La la la la la, ♪
♪ La la la ♪
- [Narrator] Sealed
in the darkness,
beyond the rays of
the light of hope,
will the power of
Momiji Kushanada
be able to control Susano-Oh?
All the world can do
is stand by and watch,
as the final battle unfolds.
- [Momiji] Mom,
Grandma,
Mr. Kunikida,
Miss Matsudaira,
Miss Takeuchi,
Yaegashi,
Koame,
Mr. Sukashida,
Sakura,
and Kusanagi.
Please, let me say
thank you for everything
and I hope we can work
things out in the future,
if there is a future.
It's the final episode
of Blue Seed, New Soul.
I won't say goodbye,
just see you again.
(cheerful upbeat music)
(upbeat foreign lyrics)