(thunder crashing)
(energetic rock music)
(singing in foreign language)
(birds chirping)
(bell tinkling)
(sniffing)
(yowling)
Chiko?
Where are you?
Stop hiding from
me, you silly cat!
Chiko?
(bell tinkling)
Huh?
Chiko?
Is this where you've
gotten to, Chiko?
(ominous music)
(screaming)
(gasping)
(tires squealing)
Hey, are you all right?
Hmm?
Man, I'm lucky!
- [Momiji] Irritating!
Jealous!
Unbelievable!
(humming)
Hm?
(sentimental music)
My first kiss.
(sighing)
- [Kusanagi] Hey, have you
been sick or something?
- [Momiji] Kusanagi!
You've been hard to find.
What gives?
I gotta go!
What?
What's wrong, Momiji?
Now, what's her
problem this time?
(sighing)
(bell chiming)
- [Momiji] I am so
dumb, dumb, dumb!
Why did I have to
run away again?
That wasn't my first kiss,
it was just mouth-to-mouth
resuscitation.
I don't even think
he enjoyed it.
Attention, class!
We have a new student
starting today.
Come on in, you little.
(class gasping)
- [Student] Is that outfit
covered by the dress code?
- [Student] Oh
look, it's Madonna!
Not Yamazaki?
Momiji?
Unbelievable, what the heck do
you think you're doing here?
Son of a bitch, you're
trying to submarine me again,
aren't you, you
stupid sacrifice?
You've got some nerve!
You're the one that
transferred into my school,
you oversexed fortune-telling
little trollop!
It's only temporary.
Once my mission's
finished, I'm outta here.
Huh?
Um, yes, due to
her father's work,
Miss Yamazaki has been
living in the U.S.
for quite a while,
and I'm afraid she
hasn't gotten used to how
we do things here in Japan.
I think you all
oughta get together
and give her some advice.
Oh yeah, I'll teach
her a thing or two!
Howdy, fellas.
(male students cheering)
Um, yes, well, for right now,
you better sit next
to Miss Kanbayashi.
She's our class leader,
and she's very responsible.
Wow, next to the class leader?
Golly!
My pleasure.
Hmm.
(sighing)
Sakura, that chair
is not appropriate.
Oh, but this is how we
do it back in the U.S.
Huh, really?
- [Sakura] All right, Momiji.
I won't let you get
under my skin this time.
Here, take a look at these.
Each of these shows the
body of a young girl.
- [Ryoko] Every ounce of blood
has been sucked
from their bodies.
- [Yaegashi] And five
girls at the same time.
That's scary.
That's right, these
girls were all seen
walking around in
a trance-like state
prior to their collapse,
but autopsy shows
the blood had been
drained from their bodies.
Then something must have
manipulated their dead bodies
like puppets to
get them away from
where they were actually killed.
It sure sounds
like aragami to me.
Yeah, that's about
what I figured.
Aragami.
As soon as I heard
about these incidents,
I just knew they would fall
under your area of jurisdiction.
And that's why you ran all
the way over here, huh,
not to see Takeuchi, eh?
(laughing nervously)
Nitwit.
Huh?
By the way, where's your boss?
We're really not allowed to say.
Mr. Kunikida has
something important to do.
Huh?
Mr. Kunikida.
We'll have
considerable difficulty
if you can't come up
with some sort of answer.
As you know, we
can't afford to make
the very existence of the
aragami public knowledge,
let alone that they
intend to destroy Japan.
However, the government
intends to issue
some kind of statement to
dispel the public concern.
We've received inquiries
from all over the world
about the recent series of
incidents, and let's face it,
we can't keep on
pretending that monsters
haven't invaded our
cities when just last week
there was a giant
frog walking through
the Foreign Exchange Building.
This problem is about to
reach epidemic proportions,
and we must be prepared to
deal with it, Mr. Kunikida.
Well, this is not the first time
that Japan has been faced
with such a problem.
I would think our
state department
would be rather
used to it by now.
(chuckling)
Well, first of all, we obviously
can't tell other countries
that our nation kept
the aragami a secret.
But if what you
tell me is correct,
we'll have to come
up with something
that at least sounds plausible.
Maybe something to do
with mass hallucinations
induced by a drug
in the water supply,
or on the subways.
- [Secretary] That sounds
like a promising start.
Not really.
After all, our police
organizations have a reputation
for being among the best
in the world, don't they?
Hmm.
I understand.
We wouldn't want
to propose anything
that might relect poorly
on our police forces,
would we, Mr. Secretary?
(yawning)
I really can't
believe how boring
all of these stupid Japanese
high school classes are.
Huh?
Hi!
(sighing)
And the boys are even more
boring than the classes.
Aren't there any real
studs in this school?
Somebody like that
hunk Kusanagi.
(laughing)
Oh my, Kusanagi's not
your boyfriend, is he?
My, my boyfriend?
N-no, it's nothing like that.
I see.
Not that you'd be
any competition.
Wh-what did you say?
Oh, nothing.
Hm?
There she goes.
Hey, wait just a second!
(suspenseful music)
Huh?
Kusanagi.
- [Sakura] Okay,
what are you up to?
Thanks.
- [Sakura] Nuts, she just went
into the teachers' lounge.
- [Kusanagi] I thought so.
You're that
schizophrenic psychic.
- [Sakura] Kusanagi,
what are you doing here?
I could ask the same
question of you.
Ah, Kusanagi!
Oh, Yamazaki.
I see.
Not that you'd be
any competition.
It can't be.
(clanging)
Huh?
Momiji?
I'm sorry, excuse me.
What, wait!
Momiji!
What is wrong with her today?
(laughing) You're cute,
but you're as dense
as a bag of bricks.
We've got more important
things to discuss.
Just what are you doing here?
Hunting for aragami?
Well.
(laughing nervously)
(crying)
- [Momiji] Why did I have
to run away like that?
So what if Kusanagi and
Sakura do have a relationship?
I feel like such an idiot.
I first ran into Reiko
about a week ago.
- [Woman] Reiko!
Reiko, what happened?
Don't worry, there's nothing
physically wrong with her.
However, it's my
professional opinion
that she's been possessed.
Just who are you?
Oh, look at this!
What does it mean?
It can't be.
You look like
you've got some idea
of what might be behind this.
I think you'd better
tell me everything.
What, who are you?
I'm the world's
greatest exorcist.
My success rate is 100%.
I'm from Kusamikado
Faith Healers,
and boy, are you
guys ever lucky.
So anyway, after a
little negotiating,
I've set myself up to
watch Reiko 24 hours a day,
and since I have to stay as
close to her as possible...
So that's why you transferred
into Momiji's school.
But are you sure it was an
aragami that possessed her?
I think so, but there
are alternatives
that I can't ignore.
Alternatives?
- [Matsudaira] The entire
body is completely desiccated,
but look at the neck.
- [Yaegashi] Ugh, a spider!
- [Ryoko] I believe
this might have been
the control mechanism.
So it is aragami.
I knew it!
- [Matsudaira] It would
be wiser to assume that.
Right, we'll make a map of
where the bodies were found
and conduct a search of
all those neighborhoods.
Hmm.
Hey, look, Momiji's school is
almost in the center
of the pattern.
So anyway, it turned out
that the English teacher,
Mr. Takahara, was only
teaching us dirty words.
What a perverted teacher.
Reiko, what are you doing here?
Our class has gym class
next, not yours, right?
I have made no mistakes.
(laughing)
I know exactly what I'm doing.
(bell chiming)
(sighing)
I guess I'd better
get back to class.
(crashing)
Huh?
(screaming)
(laughing)
At last, it is
time to be reborn!
(screaming)
(laughing)
The blood of these virgins
will give me power.
(groaning)
Hey, did you hear...
Who's back there?
Oh, not again!
(eerie music)
(birds chirping)
(ominous music)
Is this it?
The stone that you were
just telling us about?
Yes, it is.
I've been told that under that
stone is a bottomless pit.
In the olden days, whenever
there was a drought
or a famine, they
would throw young women
into that pit as a sacrifice.
- [Kusanagi] Wonderful.
So why did they put
the seal on the rock?
Legend has it that a huge spider
which craved the taste of blood
began to emerge from the hole,
attacking the
villagers no matter
how many sacrifices
it was given.
I heard the tale from my father,
who learned it from
his father before him.
But I always thought
it was just a story.
I don't know if the creature was
originally an aragami,
or if the aragami
took over its body afterwards.
But it would seem to me
it must have been revived
when the holy seals were broken.
I've gone ahead and
resealed the rock
with a new seal, but.
But even so, Reiko
hasn't come back.
Miss Kanbayashi!
(groaning)
(laughing)
That's really what's
been bothering me.
Even though I resealed the
rock, Reiko hasn't returned.
Maybe someone who
works for the aragami
is working against us.
They've been known to
have collaborators.
Someone who works
for the aragami?
I got it!
Huh?
So tell me already!
Is that all you've got
to contribute, Kusanagi?
This operation is my
baby, remember that.
I've got a 100%
kill ratio so far,
so don't screw up my reputation.
You've got quite an
attitude, cherry blossom.
- [Sakura] So do
you, carrot boy.
Lots of negative
energy, isn't there.
Yeah, there is.
(screaming)
Momiji!
(ominous music)
Are you gonna run away again?
Kusanagi!
- [Sakura] What
happened, Momiji?
It was Reiko Kanbayashi!
Uh, huh?
That was in the back
of the building!
Sakura, take Momiji!
(glass breaking)
Damn.
It was so gross.
Little spiders came
out of her clothes.
Little spiders?
That's the answer!
My seal didn't work
because its servants
had already escaped.
(engine revving)
I'm coming with you!
(screaming)
Be careful!
This is unbelievable.
Oh, great master, please
revive and be reborn.
Revive and take revenge upon
the miserable humans who
sealed you beneath the stone.
(chanting in foreign language)
Wait a minute, that chanting.
That's the spell used to release
the spider from the stone.
The spell for
releasing the seal?
We have to stop them!
- [Kusanagi] No, they wanna
release it, let 'em do it.
- [Momiji] Kusanagi?
If we don't destroy the mitama,
the soul of the aragami,
this won't mean anything.
Isn't that right,
fortune-teller?
You got it.
But are you sure?
Look there.
Huh?
(rumbling)
(laughing)
(ominous music)
It's so big!
I got dibs on this one!
Wait, you idiot!
Shikigami appear, do my bidding!
(roaring)
Ha, you weren't as
strong as you looked.
(laughing nervously)
Get outta the way!
What are you doing?
Do you wanna be splattered,
you stupid bimbo?
Come on, come on out and fight!
Come on, baby.
How about if we attack the
spider from both sides?
Of course, I'll handle
most of the damage.
Heh, whatever.
(shouting)
Kusanagi!
(speaking foreign language)
(shrieking)
Eat this!
Ah!
Kusanagi!
- [Kusanagi] Don't come any
closer, stay away from here!
(shouting in foreign language)
(shrieking)
Not bad, better than I expected.
Well, of course.
Your techniques might even
be worth considering, maybe.
I just hope you'll be
able to keep up the pace.
(laughing) Trust me!
Shikigami, attack on my cue!
- [Momiji] I, I wanna
fight with them.
(gasping)
Please!
Please let me fly
like I did before.
Let me, let me fly.
(shouting)
Sakura!
(chanting in foreign language)
(shouting)
Kusanagi!
Mo, Momiji, you've
got to stop her!
Stop her, how?
- [Kusanagi]
Interrupt the spell.
Break it somehow.
Understood.
It's useless!
Just what do you
think Momiji can do?
Don't you know
that she's useless
except as a human sacrifice?
Be quiet, shut your mouth!
Listen, Momiji.
(dramatic music)
- [Momiji] Even if I can't fly.
Momiji!
(screaming)
Even if I can't fly!
There, there it is!
I hate spiders!
Way to go, Momiji!
(shrieking)
(shouting)
It's my turn now!
(shrieking)
(sighing)
Huh?
That was great work, Momiji.
You really did it.
Kusanagi.
(sirens blaring)
(tires squealing)
Well, I guess I'll let
these jokers finish the job.
See ya.
Kusanagi!
- [Momiji] I've decided.
That was my first kiss.
(gentle music)
- [Kanbayashi] I'll guard
that stone carefully
to keep something like this
from ever happening again.
I hope you'll be up to the task.
I'm glad you're back.
By the way, Momiji.
Did you forget that
you're supposed to
report to us first, no
matter what happens?
- [Momiji] But this all
happened so suddenly!
Even so, do it!
Yes, sir.
As long as you understand,
I'm just glad that
you're alive and well.
Right.
Hey, hey!
Ooh, how I hate that
Momiji and Kusanagi!
Okay, if that's the
way you want it,
I'll just stay right here and
make life miserable
for both of you!
Somebody get me down!
- [Momiji] What is this
strange feeling of uneasiness?
Something's coming,
I can feel it.
And somehow, I
can also feel that
Kusanagi's going to be going
somewhere far, far away.
This can't be happening, can it?
Kusanagi isn't going
anywhere, is he?
Oh, please say it's
not gonna happen!
It's the next episode
of "Blue Seed."
Can you feel it?
I can't ignore it!
An ominous premonition
of catastrophe!
Oh, I love him so much, I'm
afraid I'm gonna lose him!
(mellow music)
(singing in foreign language)