(thunder rumbles)
(intense music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
- [Narrator] The final
moment is drawing near.
The moon has swallowed the sun
and a total eclipse
has sealed all of Japan
in a shroud of darkness.
The Cave of the Sun has
been sealed at last,
and Susano-Oh's ceremony
to destroy the people
of Japan has begun.
What light can the power
of the Kushinada bring
to a land that has been
sealed in eternal darkness?
(creature roaring)
The gates of night have fallen
and only one girl
may hold the key
to mankind's salvation.
Her name is Momiji Fujimiya,
and she is the Kushinada.
Miss Matsudaira,
go ahead, do it!
Right.
(laser whining)
(Momiji screaming)
- [Momiji] Kaede!
- [Kaede] No, it's too late.
It's much too late.
(dramatic music)
(creature roars)
Kaede!
(characters gasping)
(ominous choral music)
(soldiers grunting)
(crowd gasping)
(baby crying)
- [Soldier] What in
the hell is that?
- [Soldier] The whole
country is glowing blue!
- [Soldier] What in the
hell is going on over there?
Captain, what the?
Relay the launch
command sequence
to the submarines.
Standby for missile deployment.
Aye-aye sir.
- [Officer] What's
happening over there?
What's happening to Japan?
(eerie music)
Prime Minister,
we don't have any other
options left open.
We've got to
evacuate immediately
and let the US Navy handle this.
(man screaming)
Prime Minister, it's
too dangerous now.
We've got to get out of here!
Let us pray.
(Momiji singing)
Sir, Momiji's heart rhythm
is getting weaker and weaker!
Huh?
All the data on her
vital signs show
that she's in extremely
dangerous condition!
Matsudaira, stop the
artificial pulse irradiation!
We have, Sir!
The machine's overheated!
The artificial pulse isn't
irradiating her anymore!
- [Kunikida] What?
- [Woman] But Momiji
is still, she can't!
- [Woman] You mean she's
sacrificing herself
to stop Susana-Oh?
(Momiji singing)
- [Momiji] My arms
feel so heavy,
but my blood, the blood
of a Christian goddess
is screaming in my veins.
Matsuri.
What's wrong?
- [Boy] What was that?
Can you hear that?
Listen.
I heard it.
It's some sort of music.
Matsuri.
(chime dings)
- [Kaede] Momiji.
(creature roars)
(ominous music)
Kaede!
(creature roars)
Whatever your plans are,
I'm going to stop you.
(creature roars)
(Kusanagi groans)
Kusanagi.
Kusanagi!
Stay out of this, lizard breath!
Momiji and Kaede
are in the middle
of an all or nothing battle
as the Kushinada for
the future of the earth!
Don't you get it yet?
You've already lost, all right!
(creature groans)
An all or nothing battle
to be the Kushinada?
You don't understand
anything, rah!
(Kusanagi yelling)
Look at me, I'm taking
all of the power
of Susana-Oh into my body.
You stupid fool.
When you selfishly
struck out on your own
without knowing
what you really are,
you started down
a path that leads
to your own complete
destruction.
You're no better
than the humans!
That's a lie!
Behold!
(creature roaring)
(all gasping)
(creature laughing)
Jesus!
My god, it's huge!
What is this?
Look Kusanagi, Susana-Oh,
I am the king of Aragami.
- [Kaede] You are a fool.
(creature groaning)
I am, I am!
No I am!
(creature groaning)
I am the king!
The king of Aragami!
(explosions booming)
(all yelling)
It's too dangerous to
stay here, hurry up!
Sakura!
Sir!
Momiji, Momiji's vital signs!
Her pulse, respiration, and EKG
are dropping to nearly zero!
(all gasping)
(emotional music)
- [Momiji] Sister.
M-Momiji?
- [Momiji] Kaede.
Momiji.
Hunger, war.
Hatred.
In order to swallow
all the despair
and change it into hope,
Susana-Oh was born.
- [Momiji] But Kaede...
- [Kaede] For the
sake of tomorrow,
we change despair into hope.
But Kaede.
My sister, did you
give up on hope?
What?
Why Kaede?
(emotional music)
- [Kaede] Does any hope
still exist in this country?
In this ugly, filthy
planet we've made?
In the hearts of man,
kindness and gentleness
have been forgotten.
Does hope even exist?
Momiji, Momiji!
- [Both] Momiji, Momiji!
Momiji, idiot, you wanna die?
Momiji!
- [Both] Momiji, Momiji!
- [Kunikida] Momiji!
- [Momiji] Don't you understand?
I must do this for you.
I want to protect you,
because I love you.
That's all.
That's why.
I love you.
I love you all.
(boy singing)
What are you singing, Karu?
(children singing)
(adults murmuring)
Listen sir, our
time is running out.
We have to hurry and evacuate
or that missile
will kill us all.
Prime minister, prime minister!
What is that sound, can
you hear that singing?
What's going on out there?
All across the land.
(eerie music)
(children singing)
What's that?
Momiji!
Momiji.
(gentle music)
(flames roar)
In your chest, can you feel it?
It's warm.
Same here, what is this?
Yes, I'm feeling hot too.
But it doesn't feel painful.
More than that,
it's like emotions
wrapping around my heart.
I can't describe it,
but it makes me
wanna do something!
Matsuri, that's it!
This heat and the
feeling of excitement
are from the Rite of Matsuri.
This is what the
Matsuri really is!
Matsuri, the
Kushinada's Matsuri?
(children singing)
(children clamoring)
Stay inside everybody!
Come on Dad, why
don't we go with them?
What are you talking about?
I've got to!
I can't stop myself from going!
Hey!
(children singing)
(children gasping)
- [Boy] Look at 'em all!
What's going on?
Come on, let's go out there!
I don't know what's going on,
but I can't hold my
body back anymore!
(all laughing, clamoring)
- [Momiji] I love
you, all of you.
(children singing)
(people cheering)
I love you.
I love you all.
(intense music)
Momiji!
(all shouting "Momiji")
(wood snaps)
Kusanagi.
Momiji.
Momiji!
- [Announcer] T-minus
30 seconds and counting.
29, 28, 27,
26, 25, 24,
23, 22, 21,
20, 19... God help us.
We're really gonna do it.
- [Announcer] 17, 16, 15,
14, 13, 12... (alarm blares)
11... Captain!
There's an urgent message
from the president!
- [Announcer] Nine, eight...
- [Man] Mission aborted!
All stations stand down!
At the request of the
Japanese government,
the missile launch
has been canceled.
Repeat, the launch
(emotional music)
(flames crackling)
(people chanting)
(children singing)
(people cheering)
Cut it out, stop!
If you touch the pollen
you'll be turned into a plant!
Who cares about that?
Can't you feel the
heat in your heart?
He's right, this heat's
springing from my body!
I have to do something about it,
don't you feel it?
Don't you feel the heat?
Yes I feel it.
I've been feeling
the same way myself.
Tell me what to do.
(children singing)
(fireworks popping)
Who's afraid of
those monster plants?
Let's Matsuri, Matsuri,
the greatest Matsuri ever!
(children singing)
- [Momiji] I love you.
I love you all.
(children singing)
What is this?
Can the Kushinada do this?
Is this, is this the real
power of the Kushinada?
Kaede!
Do you still think there's
nothing left except despair?
She was the real Kushinada!
The power of the Kushinada
is causing the seeds of hope
to grow where
there's only despair!
Do you see?
(dramatic music)
- [Kaede] My part in
this play is over.
Kaede.
- [Kaede] Farewell, Kusanagi.
- [Kusanagi] Kaede?
- [Kaede] I think I know now,
why the Kushinada
was born as twins.
Kaede.
Help us, Lord Susana-Oh.
(baby coos)
What is this?
Momiji, Momiji!
Kusanagi.
Thank you both.
It is time for me to rest now,
until the time when
Lord Susana-Oh and
I are needed again.
Farewell, my sister.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] The Cave of
the Sun has been opened.
The Kushinada's Rite
of Matsuri is over.
Now, a new era is
about to start.
A new life full of
hope for all of Japan.
(pleasant music)
(birds chirping)
- [Momiji] A lot of things
have happened to
us, haven't they?
But did we do the right thing?
- [Kusanagi] Kaede said, she
told me that she understood now
why the Kushinada
was born as twins.
- [Momiji] The reason why
we were born as twins?
- [Kusanagi] We did
the right thing.
When we need her, she'll
come back to us again.
Yeah.
Hey, here we are again!
Geez, this is the
place where I met you
for the first time, remember?
Is it really?
I don't remember anything
except the funny panties
you were wearing.
You jerk, you jerk!
You're an idiot, a jerk,
and a pervert Kusanagi!
- [Kusanagi] Okay, I remember,
I remember this place!
- [Momiji] Girls hate bullies
and perverts, you know that?
- [Kusanagi] I was only kidding.
But I love you.
What?
You're just suddenly
realizing that?
You!
Yeah.
- [Momiji] Why don't we
start over from here?
From here?
Yeah, from here.
But what is that?
Mm.
(bell dings)