(thunder)
(Blue Seed Theme song)
(helicopter whirring)
- [Yaegashi] The
Aragami's deployment
is quite strategic sir.
The capital city
of each prefector,
receives the most
virulent infestation,
with the damage
expanding outwards.
I see.
Sir, how is Momiji
doing since...?
I can't believe that
Kusanagi is really...
Shh!
Not yet, Momiji believes
that he could still be alive.
(sad music)
(sigh and gasps)
(yells)
Momiji, once we've
killed them all,
why don't we go to the beach?
What?
I'm not after your
Mitama this time,
I mean a real date.
Kusanagi.
Huh?
(yells and screams)
Kusanagi don't go.
Kusanagi please don't leave me!
Don't go without me!
Kusanagi!
No!
(gasps)
Kusanagi.
(helicopter engine)
(gasps)
(dramatic music)
Is this really Tokyo?
Kusanagi, please say that
you'll come back to me soon.
(sighs)
The moon looks too red.
- [Ryouko] What?
- [Scientist] What?
The moon's orbit has changed?
- [Assistant 1] Yes sir,
it sounds crazy, but look.
- [Scientist] I
don't understand.
What could it mean?
- [Assistant 1] It's way
out of its normal orbit.
As near as I can tell, this
is its new projected path.
- [Assistant 2] A
sudden change like this,
is it even possible sir?
No, it's against
the laws of physics.
But it is, sir.
It is really happening.
How will this affect the earth?
Right.
Well, before the eclipse
that was to occur
over Indonesia, will
instead happen over Japan,
in 156 hours and 12 minutes.
It's almost impossible to
predict all of the unnatural
phenomenon that could result
from such a sudden change
of the moon's
gravitational pull, sir.
There'll be volcanic
eruptions and magma shifts.
(crashing noise)
There could be earthquakes,
and there will be tidal waves.
Sir, those abnormal plants
appearing all over Japan
are probably a result
of this change.
(electricity crackling)
Then the darkness will come.
What is going to
happen to all of us?
Take a look at this,
the Slagget Boulevard
which runs through
the center of Magoya
and on through the Marunouchi
area looks like a jungle.
There are hundreds
of reports of damage,
coming from residents in
every part of the city.
The Self Defense
Force is cooperating
with the water authorities
of each community,
in order to ensure drinking
water for the people.
And water tankers
have been dispatched
to deal with this emergency,
live here on channel 16.
- [News Announcer] Stay tuned
and wait for the instructions
from each autonomous station.
Mayor, we're ready to
move our headquarters
to the Madoriku
federal building.
It doesn't appear to be as
badly damaged as this one.
Please get on the
helicopter immediately.
I heard you.
Mayor!
More damage from the huge
plants has been reported
from Chekusa, Matou, Moriyama,
Otsuta, and Nakagawa.
The suspension of water supplies
and the closing of roads,
is being updated continuously,
but the current total
is 120 neighborhoods and
the damage to homes is...
[Government Official]
That's enough.
- [Analyst] What?
(sirens)
What is the Self
Defense Force doing?
(glass cracking)
- [Rescue Worker] Hurry
up and search the building
under the root.
Hurry up, get a move on!
(general chatter)
Connection of electrodes
and tubes completed
- [Soldier] Organic
reaction, okay.
Start injection of TI plasmids.
- [Soldier] Plasmids away!
(explosive sounds)
That's good.
What?
(dramatic music)
(explosions and shouts)
The Self Defense Force
in Agrio has withdrawn?
Yes ma'am, they
fought the plants
using your vector weapons,
but the report
states that there was
an unexpected organic reaction.
Hm, I don't understand it,
in Sapporro, Osaka, Nagasaki,
Kochi, and now Nagoya.
None of the systems we've
developed are working at all.
How could the Aragami
have managed to develop
such a sudden resistance
to all of our weapons?
[Soldier On Radio] This is
the Self Defense Force troop
in Hiroshima, the
organic (mumbles) I get
is beyond recognition, and our...
[Soldier 2 On Radio] It
doesn't have any effect
on them at all.
Please, check these materials
and give us new gunners.
Tell me,
the report from the observatory.
Hm?
How many days did they give us?
Six?
Five?
- [Newscaster] In
the city of Osaka,
90 percent of the citizens
have begun a mass exodus
into the mountains
around the city.
Mass exodus.
What an ugly sounding phrase.
It's Kunikida, you called sir?
Hm.
One week?
And then all of Japan will
be plunged into darkness.
The staff at the observatory,
thinks that all of these
strange occurrences
are the result
of the change in the moon.
Of course, they don't
know about Susano-Oh.
Do you really believe
Susano-Oh actually changed
the orbit of the moon.
Well, darkness is the best
condition for certain plants
to become active and we
know the Aragami prefer it.
Maybe they created the
darkness with the intent
of doing something
under it's cover.
I'll get Miss Matsudaira
working on it.
She's still analyzing the
data on the Kushinada.
Don't worry about it.
What?
It won't be necessary anymore.
But Mr. Prime minister...
I'm sorry.
(electrical crackling)
Unbelievable, the power
of the Kushinada's blood
has jumped to more than five
times what it was before
all this.
It's probably
because of Susano-Oh,
just like the Aragami's
Mitama's, your personal Mitama's
becoming more active, Momiji,
at a level of five times
greater than it has ever
been measured before.
Then I should feel Kusanagi's
presence even more strongly.
(chime)
I feel him.
Kusanagi?
Mm-hm!
Momiji, wait.
I need somebody to
take me someplace.
(car engine roaring)
Kusanagi, you're
in the same place
this energy is coming
from, aren't you?
You're alive, you've got to be!
And I'll be there to rescue you!
(beep)
This is Kunikida,
Takeuchi get out of there!
(gasps)
(tires screeching)
Damn!
Let's not get violent, shall we.
The Prime Minister's
given us orders
to take the Kushinada
into protective custody,
for the good of the
nation of Japan.
Say what!
(tires squealing)
(yells and crashes)
Is everybody all right in there?
Yes.
We're fine.
Momiji's a member of our team
and protecting the
Kushinada's the TACs job.
You aren't going to
lay a finger on her.
(gunfire)
(gasps in pain)
Sir!
(shout)
Mr. Kunikida!
Make one false move, and
we'll splatter the street
with your blood.
Get back, damn you!
The Kushinada plan has already
been put into operation.
The ritual of human
sacrifice must be held
in exactly 149 hours.
Human sacrifice?
You fools don't even know
what Susano-Oh's up to.
Be careful sir.
Do you intend to sacrifice
her based on a guess.
You cannot escape, and
you're all public servants.
Don't make us shoot
you as traitors.
Now, turn the
Kushinada over to us.
(sounds of attack)
(yells and groans)
What on earth?
(laughter)
- [Momiji] Murakumo!
Don't over exert yourself,
princess Kushinada.
Where is Kusanagi?
What have you done with him?
Kusanagi?
Hm.
Give him back to me!
Kusanagi is dead.
No!
(sad music)
He was such a fool.
We made him an
Aragami, but even so,
he fought against us.
Liar!
I know you already knew.
You don't feel Kusanagi's
energy anymore, do you?
It's a lie, it's a lie!
(gunfire)
If you don't kill
yourself pointlessly,
we'll let you be
born again as plants
in our glorious new world.
What?
In the darkness which will
come, seven days from now,
Japan will be reborn.
Is that so.
Members of the TAC, please
protect the Kushinada.
If the Kushinada were to die,
we'd be quite inconvenienced.
(evil laughter)
(crying)
It's not true, it's not true!
Kusanagi!
(gunfire and breaking glass)
Cut it out!
No, let me go!
Idiot, we've got
to get out of here!
(tires screeching)
(sad music)
They're following us.
- [Ryouko] I'll lose them!
Kusanagi is dead!
He was such a fool.
He tried to fight against us.
(gunfire)
(whimpering)
Momiji!
(yells)
- [Ryouko] Momiji!
Momiji, what the hell do
you think you're doing?!
I must sacrifice myself.
- [Koume] What!
Momiji.
Good girl, the key
to Japan's future is
in your hands Kushinada.
Momiji.
Momiji!
(tires screeching)
(crumbling rocks)
(dramatic music)
(water splashing)
(transformation sounds)
Oh!
Lord Susano-Oh.
(splashing water)
Yes,
yes,
I understand, yes.
(soft music)
Dammit, what the hell
are we gonna do now boss?
Don't panic Koume, I
know where they plan
to take her.
- [Group] What?
Yes, I know where she is.
(car door opening)
(sigh)
(walking noises)
(door creaks)
(dramatic music)
- [Assistant] Wow, I
didn't expect this place
to be so enormous.
- [Govt. Official] Actually,
I was surprised too,
this temple was built
over 400 years ago.
It's hard to believe, a
hidden underground temple,
built and maintained for
government sanctioned
human sacrifices.
- [Govt. Official] Yes,
your tax dollars at work
for the protection
of the nation.
(door squeaks)
(footsteps)
Miss Momiji Fujimiya,
I'm glad you finally made
up your mind.
130 million, that's how many
men, women, and children
will be saved by your sacrifice,
and yet, I've never
made a harder decision.
We have one week until the time.
If there's anything you want,
anything I can do for you,
between now and then,
just let me know.
(footsteps)
(door slamming)
All of Japan in exchange
for one girl's life,
I'm sorry.
Kusanagi.
(cries)
Please help me.
Help me like you always do.
You'll always be there
for me won't you?
You'll show up any minute now,
with that big dumb
grin on your face.
I know you will.
(crying)
- [Azusa] Yaegashi,
take a look at this.
- [Yaegashi] It looks like
there's a regular rhythm,
doesn't it.
- [Azusa] It's the pulse
of the Kushinada effect.
What?
By using the special
ceramic as a filter
over 30,000 times, I've
isolated the mysterious
common datum between
the files I've collected
on both Momiji and Kaede.
This is what makes
the Kushinada unique.
- [Yaegashi] Then
we might be able
to stop the Aragami using this.
- [Azusa] Yes, this is the
power of the Kushinada.
What we're doing is
treason you know?
No, it's our job to
kill the Aragami,
and Susano-Oh, right sir?
You're both right.
Either way, we can't just
sit back and let them
sacrifice Momiji.
Right!
(explosion)
(dramatic music)
- [Kunikida] Are you ready?
We'll begin the operation
in five minutes.
Right.
Koume are you there?
Five minutes.
Got it, we do it in five.
(dramatic music)
Done.
(grunts)
Right, let's get this
show on the road.
(truck engine)
(tires squealing)
(explosion sounds)
(shouts)
(grunts)
(metal clanging)
(running steps)
Got it!
Yikes!
- [Guards] Hey freeze!
Hold it right there!
(spraying sound)
Just 12 seconds left.
Ten, nine...
Eight.
Seven, six (groans)
(sounds of battle)
Five, four...
Three!
Two!
One.
Zero!
Perfect!
(explosion)
Miss Takeuchi, Koume!
We came to rescue you, Momiji.
Yeah, why'd you
turn yourself in...
(Koume mumbles into hand)
Come on Momiji.
I can't go with you.
What!
Just what is your problem?
It's all right.
By sacrificing myself,
I'll be avenging the death
of Kusanagi.
Hm?
Momiji.
Mr. Kunikida's been
shot because of me
and when I die, it will save
all of the people in Japan.
(slaps)
We didn't fight all this way
just to keep the government
from sacrificing you
as the Kushinada.
We fought so that we
could fight beside you,
so that we could kill
Susano-Oh together.
So that we could finish
this once and for all
and destroy the Aragami forever.
What was the point of
everything we've done
if you're just going
to throw it away?
What did Kusanagi spend his
entire life protecting you for?
Momiji are you just going
to let them kill you
or will you fight!?
Miss Takeuchi,
I don't...
(mysterious music)
He's alive.
Kusanagi.
Kusanagi!
Are you sure?
Yes.
That's enough.
What have we here.
Is the TAC staging a Coup detat?
Get out of our way.
You know damn well that you
can't shoot the Kushinada.
Shut your mouth.
I don't think I'll have to shoot
the Kushinada, you traitor.
(gasps)
Sakura!
(upbeat music)
(lauaghter)
You can't do anything
without me can you?
Thanks for the help.
Oh, I can't believe that I'm
in dept to that fruitcake.
(loud breathing)
Hiya!
(explosion)
(metal clanking)
We outta be able to
squeeze through here.
(growl)
Mr. Shikigami please
don't kill them,
just stop them for
a little while okay.
(fast pace music)
This way!
Mr. Kunikida!
(car engine roaring)
The Prime Minister told me
that he's shutting down the TAC.
Huh?
I'm not giving up.
How about you?
You know we won't sir.
In for a penny, in for a pound.
I'll do my best, I won't
let you down, Mr. Kunikida.
Well, I don't know.
Japan's been pretty lousy to me,
and I still haven't gotten paid
for my last three TAC jobs.
(growls)
Well, but on reflection,
I'll guess I'll do whatever
you guys are doing, I guess.
I'm afraid we won't
have much time to plan.
I'm sure the government
will do something about us.
All right Yaegashi,
turn on the switch.
Right.
(laser humming)
The Kushinada pulse
isn't stable yet.
Have you finished copying
all of the Kushinada data?
Just a little longer.
- [Kunikida] Miss Matsudaira,
grab the necessary data
and get out of there now.
We'll rendezvous later.
We need more time.
We've almost figured out
how to kill the Aragami.
(electricity shorts out)
Huh, what?
Ah!
Somebody's cut off the power!
(gasps)
What's wrong Momiji?
It's Kusanagi, his
energy is getting weaker.
(sad music)
- [Momiji] I can hear
Kusanagi's voice.
I can see Kusanagi's smile.
I can still be
close to Kusanagi.
It's just a simple thing,
but I'm happy, so very happy.
(gasp)
Now I'm going to do
my very best work,
better than anything
I've ever done before.
It's the next episode
of Blue Seed, number 23.
Meeting Again, Starting the
Journey, I Won't Give Up!
I won't let them
extinguish the passion
that burns in my heart.
(Blue Seed Theme song)