(thunder crashing)
(energetic rock music)
(singing in foreign language)
(crickets chirping)
(romantic music)
(screaming)
(engine revving)
(tires squealing)
(screaming)
(horn beeping)
- [Momiji] The incident occurred
beside a small pond
at the edge of Tokyo.
It would be the first in a
new series of engagements.
(mysterious music)
(horns beeping)
My name is Momiji Fujimiya.
I was born in Izumo,
where I was just
another high school student.
Or anyway, that's what
I'd always thought.
Then I learned that a
mysterious race of beings,
the aragami, had been reborn,
and well, to make
a long story short,
I guess a lot of strange
things have happened to me.
I'm now a member of a special
organization known as the TAC.
Ew!
- [Momiji] I'm
also the Kushinada,
the only human with the
power to stop the aragami.
Don't ask me how, I don't
like to think about it.
What's going on?
Huh?
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning?
Momiji Fujimiya reporting
everything cleaned and secured.
- [Momiji] This is Mr. Kunikida.
He's a native of Tokyo,
his sign is Virgo, and
his blood type is B.
He seems to be in
charge of the TAC,
but I'm not completely
sure of that.
Next in command is
Ms. Ryoko Takeuchi.
A maple roll?
- [Momiji] She was
born in Hokkaido,
her sign is Leo, and
her blood type is AB.
She used to be with
the police department.
She's cool, calm,
and a crack shot too.
- [Ryoko] Aren't
these from Hiroshima?
Aren't you from Izumo, Momiji?
- [Momiji] Mr. Yoshiki
Yaegashi, born in Miyagi,
sign, Pisces, blood type O.
I don't know much about him yet,
but he used to be a
computer specialist
at the economic planning agency.
Well, Momiji means
maple, so I thought
these rolls were appropriate.
(phone ringing)
Hi!
- [Azusa] There's a
sweet bun on my computer.
- [Momiji] Yeah, I put it there,
it's my first day you know?
Oh, I see.
Thank you, Momiji.
- [Momiji] Ms. Azusa Matsudaira,
she's a Capricorn and
her blood type is A.
She has degrees in biotechnology
and a bunch of stuff I
can't even pronounce.
And last of all, the
person who just came in
five minutes late is
Miss Kome Sawaguchi.
(yawning)
She's from lower Tokyo,
an Aries and type B.
She was in the
Self Defense Force,
and I think she
was happier there.
Her motto is if you still
have bullets, keep shooting.
Huh, huh?
What?
My guns!
(screaming)
(growling)
It's just a little
present from a coworker.
We'll be working together, and...
How dare you, you
touched my favorite guns.
Don't you know how delicate
they are, you idiot?
Oh, I'm sorry.
My baby!
Little jinx.
- [Momiji] Miss Sawaguchi?
Not now, hm.
Uh, ma'am, are you sure
we're supposed to be here?
What's that?
Well, I thought Mr.
Kunikida told us
to go to the Metropolitan
Police Department
and start cross-checking.
So what?
Well, I just thought that maybe
he wanted us to make a
list of the incidents
which could be related
to the aragami.
(screaming)
Don't you think I know that?
(playful music)
Maybe I've got plans of my own.
I'd rather fight monsters than
do boring research any day.
Come on Lady Luck,
gimme a good one, yeah!
Here we go, come on.
Aw, more bad luck.
Hey look, a good one!
Mine says a stranger
will cause you trouble.
(growling)
Wow, mine says a new
acquaintance will be fun, lucky!
My get up and go
got up and went.
Hey look, Miss Sawaguchi?
Could lie down in the street.
Ma'am, Miss Sawaguchi,
where are you going?
(women chattering)
How embarrassing.
- [Kusanagi] I'll say, where
do you buy those things anyway?
Mr. Kusanagi?
Aren't you just a little old
to be wearing funny animals
on your unmentionables?
You pervert!
Have you been feeling
anything odd lately?
Odd, aragami?
Yeah.
- [Momiji] Will they
attack me again?
No, probably not.
This one seems a
little different.
What do you mean by different?
Well, I guess we'll both
be finding out soon enough.
Bye.
Kusanagi, wait!
A new kind of aragami?
- [Kunikida] A living gel?
- [Ryoko] It was still
attached to the car.
The police have it locked
up in their lab right now,
but if you could
pull some strings
to get us inside, we could.
Sounds sticky.
I didn't hear that.
There's something else, sir.
Write a report, I've
gotta get Matsudaira
into that crime lab before
your bogeyman melts.
But Mr. Kunikida,
there's a pattern here.
Just south of where the
car was found is a pond.
To the east is the river,
a road to the west,
and a hill to the north.
That means...
When I say follow me, I
mean stay right on my tail.
You'll never survive in Tokyo
if you can't follow
instructions.
- [Momiji] I'm sorry.
Look, princess,
don't you think it's
about time you got
your act together?
What, why do you keep
calling me princess?
I want you wait here.
What?
Stay right here, you got that?
Don't move.
(honking)
- [Man] Move it, get
outta the street!
Miss Sawaguchi.
Well, I can't stay in
the middle of the street.
Hm?
(lighthearted music)
Ooh, how cute!
I love it.
Too bad it's just a model,
I'd love to own one of these.
Hey, you wouldn't happen
to have any connections?
Well, maybe for my birthday.
Momiji, Momiji, didn't I
tell you to stay right here?
- [Sugishita] Hey
Ryoko, rumor's got it
you've got an aragami in there.
- [Ryoko] Sorry Sugi,
it's classified.
Transferring to the TAC
didn't improve your
attitude one bit.
Come on Ryoko, you and I used
to be friends, didn't we?
Even if we were, which
we weren't, I couldn't.
Of course, if you did,
I'd have to shoot you.
It's been quite a while
since the police found it.
I know, its
resilience is amazing.
What could the aragami
be up to this time, what?
(crowd chattering)
Damn it all, why couldn't
she just stay put?
Can't follow orders, no
discipline, stupid little, what?
Momiji, all right.
(shouting)
Gotcha.
Uh-oh.
Sex fiend!
Don't be stupid, you're
not the girl I wanted.
Hey, lady, what do you
think you're doing?
Hey, what's going on here?
Um, well, uh.
Bye!
Halt in the name of the law!
(screaming)
This is ridiculous!
(sighing)
Where did she go?
Move it, get out
of the way, move!
Get out of my way.
There she is.
Momiji, where were you?
(weak fanfare)
(groaning)
The Defense Force
was never this tough.
- [Momiji] I'm sorry.
You know, we must
have missed each other
while I was buying this.
- [Kome] What did you say?
Well you know, I did
touch your favorite weapon
without asking permission,
so I bought you this.
- [Kome] You bought this for me?
Mm-hm, isn't it cute?
I thought it would
look so pretty on you.
Gimme a break.
I said gimme a break!
How could you even think I'd
wear something so juvenile?
But...
- [Kome] Let's get
one thing straight.
I hang around you
because it's my job.
I'm not your friend and
I'm not your babysitter.
But I thought...
Find your own way home.
(sad music)
Sawaguchi!
(sighing)
Why am I such a loser?
(rumbling)
Oh, earthquake!
(shouting)
(crowd shouting)
(growling)
What's that?
Aragami!
(phone ringing)
Ah, more trouble.
Kome, where are you?
I'm at the police
department, of course.
- [Yaegashi] Then I
guess the boss must be
at another police
department, huh,
'cause he says you're not there.
Look, we've got reports of
abnormal water
behavior all over town.
There must be an aragami
in the underground streams.
All right, something
to shoot at.
It seems to be heading for
the Koishikawa Plateau.
The others are on their way.
All right, just
leave them to me.
- [Yaegashi] Wait, Kome!
Now what?
- [Yaegashi] Don't forget,
you have to protect Momiji.
Right, I know that.
More bad luck.
- [Momiji] I can
feel it inside me.
It's getting stronger
every minute.
- [Driver] Hey ma'am,
where do you wanna go?
The railway station
or the Tokyo Dome?
I don't know yet, can
you just keep driving?
(gasping)
Right here is fine.
- [Driver] You got it.
(crowd screaming)
- [Momiji] It's over there.
(roaring)
- [Aragami] I sense
the light of a soul.
Are you one of us?
You're hurting innocent people!
Why are you doing this?
- [Aragami] I am not the first.
Always humans are first.
I must find my first place.
Your first place?
- [Aragami] You have a
soul, you understand.
(roaring)
I don't understand.
Are you sure that's
what he said?
Yes, but I don't
know what he meant.
- [Yaegashi] I knew it!
Let me check, yes,
I was right, Fusui!
Fusui, what does that mean?
It's like phrenology, you know,
like how they read the
bumps on your head.
Fusui takes it a bit further,
and uses natural landmarks
to chart flows of power.
In the place this
creature used to live,
there will be a
plateau to the north,
a street to the west,
a pond to the south,
and a river to the east
with a high buildup
of natural energy.
- [Momiji] Oh, you mean
it's trying to go home?
But what if it...
- [Yaegashi] I'm one
step ahead of you.
A plateau that matches
that description
was just leveled
for the construction
of a waste disposal facility.
Then where is the
aragami going now?
Hmm.
To the north, we have
the Kojimachi Plateau.
To the west is the Koshi Road.
South is Tokyo Bay, and to
the east is the Sumida River.
It's the center of Tokyo,
the energy levels
will be off the scale.
Oh no.
- [Yaegashi] Momiji,
I want you to come
back to the office
with Kome right now.
I don't want you in danger.
(gasping)
Miss Sawaguchi!
- [Yaegashi] Momiji,
are you there?
Hello, Momiji, Momiji?
- [Momiji] Oh no!
- [Yaegashi] Where'd she go?
Doesn't anyone listen to me?
(ominous music)
- [Announcer] The next
station is Ichigaya,
Ichigaya Station.
At least I got rid of
the excess baggage.
(roaring)
(groaning)
Did we hit something?
- [Announcer] Attention
all passengers.
There's something on the tracks!
Evacuate the train,
evacuate the train!
Now that's what I call timing.
(roaring)
(yelling)
(crowd shouting)
- [Security] Hey,
what are you doing?
You can't just come in here and
take a Jeep without
authorization.
Let me see your I.D.
Time for a little stress
relief, I pity this monster.
(horns honking)
- [Kunikida] What, you
can't find Kome or Momiji?
- [Yaegashi] Well,
I did tell Momiji
to come back to the office.
Where's the aragami now?
- [Yaegashi] It's
moving southeast towards
Ichigaya Station.
Would Kome do
something that stupid?
(roaring)
Pull over!
You're in big
trouble now, buddy.
(roaring)
Huh?
You've gotta have a weak spot.
(shouting)
We're teaching for free, whoa!
(screaming)
(breathing heavily)
(rumbling)
All right, where are you
coming from this time?
Miss Sawaguchi, look up!
To your right!
Look up, look above you!
Above me?
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
Thank goodness I could make it.
- [Kome] What are
you doing here?
I can tell where
the aragami are.
Somehow I can sense them.
You're kidding,
that's incredible.
Uh-huh!
- [Kome] Well, where
is it hiding now?
Straight ahead!
What?
(screaming)
All right!
Bullseye!
Ah, no way!
(screaming)
Kusanagi.
Didn't the TAC teach you
how to shoot that thing?
- [Kome] What did you say?
(roaring)
Momiji, where's its center?
Find out where the blue seed is.
What?
Go on, do it!
I see it, it's at the center of
the body, right
beneath the head!
In the throat, huh?
(roaring)
(gasping)
I knew it, the blue seeds
are the real aragami.
It's just like the
one on Momiji's chest.
(groaning)
Yahoo!
(laughing)
- [Azusa] As soon as the
main body ceased to function,
this piece died as well.
Ew.
I see.
What did the autopsy indicate?
It appears to be plant-based.
The creature's genetic structure
was exactly the same
as that of green algae.
So our hypothesis was correct.
Uh-huh, but we still don't know
how they mutate living
organisms to suit their needs,
or how the actual
blue seeds function.
(growling)
(gasping)
(playful music)
Miss Sawaguchi,
you're wearing it!
Well, we turned out to
be a pretty good team,
and I just thought, (laughing)
like, if you find the monsters
for me, I'll handle the rest.
Wow, yes ma'am.
- [Kome] And you
don't have to call me
Miss Sawaguchi
anymore, Kome's fine.
- [Momiji] Sure, Kome.
(laughing)
Well, I said it before,
this just ain't me.
Hey, just what do you think
you're looking at, buster?
(gun firing)
(haunting music)
- [Momiji] Suddenly, the
focus is on Ms. Matsudaira.
Who is she really,
and who is this
man she keeps mumbling
about, or is it even a man?
There are lots of
secrets to be revealed
in the next episode
of "Blue Seed."
"Surprise, She's the Mother
of Science," coming soon.
(mellow music)
(singing in foreign language)