(thunder crackles)
(intense music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night fame ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(waves crashing)
(emotional music)
Yamatone.
- [Narrator] Japan
is a Paradise!
Tears in Wakasa.
(horns honking)
Mm!
Wow!
What a spread!
Mm!
- [Man] Give me another!
- [Woman] Hey, I can't
eat with one chopstick.
Hey, here's what it
says about Wakasa.
Turbot, tilefish,
and Echizen crab.
I sure envy the boss.
I don't think he went
there to eat seafood.
- [Both] Mine!
(both giggle)
(girl shrieks)
(pleasant music)
(man humming)
Yello!
Hello Mr. Sugishita.
- [Sugishita] Hello
Momiji, how's it hanging?
Good I guess.
Oh wow, snacks!
Mm, so where's Kunikida hiding?
In Wakasa, his best friend
from college passed away.
That's right.
His friend was one of the
founding members of the TAC.
Mikyo Yamatone.
He's an ethnologist,
been missing about
three years I think.
That's him!
- [Girl] It was a
pretty freaky death too!
You wouldn't know anything
about it, would ya?
Me?
Ah, thank you.
Speaking of strange occurrences,
I understand that
all of the trees
in Wakasa have mysteriously
started to die.
And none of the local fishermen
have been able to
catch a single fish.
Is that right?
It must be, it's on TV.
Man, Japan's becoming
a hard place to live.
Ah... Hold it!
Tell us why you came here first.
Free snacks.
(slurps)
(girl shrieks)
Cooties, cooties, cooties!
(somber music)
(water splashing)
Hm.
(birds chirping)
(soothing music)
Oh.
Excuse me, my name is mister...
Kunikida.
I've been expecting
you for a while.
What?
But how?
Hm.
- [Woman] My husband talked
about you constantly.
I see.
I'm afraid that he
must not have had
many flattering stories
to tell about me though.
When we were both young,
we did a lot of foolish
things together.
He said that you
and he were always
drinking together, and arguing.
(Kunikida chuckles)
Yes, we spent more
than a few evenings
consuming enormous
quantities of sake together,
and talking about
the future of Japan.
I envy you for all those
evenings you shared.
He was a good friend,
and yet I never knew
that he had married
until I arrived here today.
When did you?
We weren't, not
officially, legally.
Oh.
It will take a few
days to complete the
autopsy on Yamatone.
I mean, your husband's body.
If I discover any
new information,
I'll be sure to let you know.
(twig snaps)
- [Woman] Mr. Kunikida?
Yes ma'am?
I just remembered that my
husband left a letter for you.
A letter?
Yes, he told me that if
something ever happened to him,
to give it to you, Mr. Kunikida.
I don't know, but I
guess that my husband
may have had some
kind of premonition
about what was going
to happen to him.
(men screaming)
Hm.
(waves crashing)
- [Yamatone] To my dear
friend, Daitetsu Kunikida.
By the time you read this,
I will no longer be
a part of this world.
I can imagine that
you're angry at me,
especially after I
disappeared so suddenly
without giving notice to anyone,
not even you, my best friend.
But I wish to talk
to you about Japan.
Japan.
The Japan of today is a
dead and soulless creation.
Worse, it has turned cannibal,
devouring its own
history and culture
as its citizens
sacrifice the land itself
on the altars of
profit and progress
in a way that would shame the
ancestors we once held sacred.
Have you seen the trees?
Is it possible that
the abnormal phenomenon
now occurring across Japan
is a ritual of purification
performed by the
ancient gods of Japan?
Do you understand?
Japan of today has
become so defiled
that not even a
god would claim it.
Kunikida, where has the
Japan which we dreamed about
when we were young gone?
Why don't we return
such a Japan to our god?
Japan must be
returned to god's ways
and be under god's control.
Am I wrong, Kunikida?
(man humming drunkenly)
(bushes rustle)
(creature growls)
(man screams)
(waves crashing)
(man screaming)
(creature snarling)
(people chattering)
(intense music)
A local sailor.
Believe it or not,
he's only 28 years old.
28?
Yeah and we found another
stiffy up the beach,
friend of his age 20.
Looks just the same.
Hm.
(eerie music)
So what would make these men
display the symptoms
of extreme old age?
It's like something out of
an old fairy tale, isn't it?
Hm?
Huh?
(girl giggles)
Here!
Here.
Here you go.
Catch!
You ready?
Hey, huh?
Huh?
What's the matter,
sense an Aragami?
Rats, I'm major disappointed.
(ethereal music)
Cave of the holy
fast of Yabakune.
Kushinada.
Ah?
- [Woman] I have
something to tell you.
Just who are you,
where are you hiding?
- [Woman] Kushinada, the
humans are using you.
Huh?
- [Woman] They will
sacrifice you, you know?
No they won't!
Mr. Kunikida promised me
that he would never let
something like that happen!
- [Woman] The history of humans
is the repetition of mistakes.
Anger, hate, killing each other.
They repeat this ugly
history in an endless cycle.
They're foolish
creatures, after all.
That's not true!
Mr. Kunikida is very kind to me,
and Mr. Yaegashi sometimes
helps me finish my homework,
and Ms. Kame sometimes takes
me to the arcade with her.
Not only that, but everyone
else is so very nice.
- [Woman] Aren't
you afraid of dying?
Kushinada, have
you ever wondered
whether it's worth throwing
your life away to save humanity?
Who are you?
Are you Aragami?
Or are you a human?
- [Woman] Neither one.
Neither one.
(girl humming)
What's wrong, Momiji?
Kame, where's the cave?
Excuse me?
I followed that nun
and went into a cave,
and then I heard
a woman's voice...
Chill out!
Geez have you been
smokin' something?
No ma'am, not me.
Oh for gosh sake, you
were just daydreaming.
[Kushinada Voiceover]
But it seemed so real.
(eerie music)
Yaobikuni?
An old superstition, but
some of the villagers
call Mrs. Yamatone that,
and the parallels between
them are intriguing.
Yaobikuni, the nun
Yao is the story
of a fisherman's daughter who
ate the flesh of a mermaid
and gained eternal
life and youth.
Supposedly she became a nun
and went on a pilgrimage.
I think I met her earlier today.
I think Momiji needs a nap,
if you know what I mean!
The stories began when
an old man in the village
first saw Mrs. Yamatone.
He almost died of fright,
because she looks exactly
like the woman who lived
there 80 years ago.
Did you say 80 years?
Here, this is a
picture of the woman.
(eerie music)
She certainly
looks like Awakaba.
It's only natural
that the old man
was surprised, but even so.
The villagers all laughed
at him in the beginning,
but then the strange
occurrences began to happen.
Trees died, and they were no
longer able to catch any fish.
The people began to
think it might be a curse
from the nun Yao, so
they began to shun her.
Ridiculous!
I'm here.
Huh?
Matsu!
I thought you were staying
in Tokyo.
Well the prototype's
been completed
and I thought it might
come in useful here.
What is that?
Oh you'll like this.
This is a corona shot,
a kind of gas gun.
It reacts to the carbonic acid
that forms inside
an Aragami's body,
generating a tremendous heat
that will destroy their
cellular structure.
It's a vegetable steamer.
That's a neat trick.
So even if that
woman is Yaobikuni,
this lil baby will make her
go up in a puff of smoke!
Shut up!
Huh?
What's been going on here?
(tone chimes)
- [Man] Mr. Kunikida,
Mr. Kunikida.
You have a phone call
from Mr. Sugishita.
Witnesses say that
three days ago,
this man was seen along
with the two fishermen
whose bodies we found entering
the house of Mr. Yamatone.
Right, I'm asking you again.
Why did you go to
the house that night?
What were the
three of you up to?
No, I'll be killed!
Who's gonna kill ya, tell me!
No, no I don't wanna die!
Help me!
I saw the way you and
the others ran away
when you saw Awakaba.
Will you care to explain
to me what that was about?
What?
I know there are some
bad rumors about her
going around the village,
but running away like
that wasn't normal was it?
I don't know, I
don't know anything!
Enough, tell me the
truth or so help me I...
You're hurting me!
Then talk!
The woman was
dead, she was dead!
What?
We killed her!
(birds chirping)
I will tell you the
truth, Mr. Kunikida.
I am indeed Yaobikuni.
800 years.
For 800 years I have walked
these lands, never aging.
I've avoided being seen,
running from the rumors,
moving from place to place,
a cycle that never ends.
But then I met Mr. Yamatone,
and my life changed.
Perhaps he saw a bit of
his lost Japan in me,
but I didn't care about that.
All I knew was that for
the first time in my life,
I was no longer alone.
Yamatone loved me.
He loved me even though he knew
what it was that I had become.
He loved me even knowing
that I was no longer human.
- [Kunikida] I see,
that's why he disappeared
three years ago then.
It was his desire for us
to come here to Wakasa,
and I could not deny him that.
People talked about
us behind our backs,
and as usual the rumors
continued to spread,
but for me each of those
days was a happy one.
Until that night.
(people screaming)
- [Man] We can't catch even
a single fish because of you!
- [Man] It'll be over
for us if this continues!
- [Man] You damn Yaobikuni!
(people screaming)
(somber music)
She's not moving!
She's dead!
(men screaming)
Awakaba!
Don't worry, my love.
I won't die.
No.
Everything will be...
I hate them, Awakaba.
I hate the entire human race.
They no longer deserve to live.
No my love, no!
No, it can't be!
(creature roaring)
(man screaming)
- [Man] Shoot it, shoot it!
Stop!
It's exactly like
the boss predicted.
Yamatone's corpse
has disappeared!
Then that means... Uh-huh!
That the monster
really is Yamatone.
(creature roaring)
We're in pursuit
of the Aragami now!
If it keeps going
straight, it'll pass
right in front of the
Wakasa Hiko Shrine.
Uh-oh, it just turned!
Now it's headed for
the Mantoku Temple.
I see, he's avoiding
historic sites on purpose.
He doesn't want
them to be involved.
(waves crashing)
(creature roaring)
(guns firing)
Get him!
(men shouting)
Shoot, shoot!
(man groans)
Fall back, retreat
but keep firing!
Come on.
Here!
(creature roars)
Don't shoot!
Please don't kill him!
What's wrong?
That Aragami is Mr.
Kunikida's best friend!
What?
(creature roaring)
So what do we do now?
What should we do, sir?
Give it to me, I'll
handle this myself.
Yes sir.
(creature roaring)
- [Kunikida] Yamatone!
(man yelps, coughs)
(creature roars)
Sir!
(creature groaning)
Yamatone?
(emotional music)
(creature roars)
(wind whistling)
(rain pattering)
(eerie music)
(chimes jingling)
- [Narrator] From a
love that lasts forever
to casual flirtation.
Love is so mysterious, isn't it?
You start thinking about things
like what kind of a man is he?
Then after a while, you just
find yourself falling
in love with him.
But once you've fallen
in love with someone,
it might still be hard to
let him know you love him.
Maybe you might
even begin to think
you shouldn't have fallen
in love with him at all.
Isn't that right, Miss Takeuchi?
It's the next episode of
Blue Seed, episode number 17.
Let it Bloom Japan!
A Blizzard of One-Sided Love!
Are you always in the process
of falling in love with someone?
(pleasant music)
(singing in foreign language)