(thunder)
(mysterious music)
(lively music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(foreign language)
(birds chirping)
(panting)
Ooh, I'm gonna be late!
Huh?
Kusanagi?
I've been waiting.
(romantic music)
Ah!
Oh!
Momiji,
I'm in love with you.
What, but this is so sudden!
I don't think that uh, woh!
- [Kusanagi] Momiji!
(sighs)
Ah!
Momiji!
(screaming)
(sheet flaps)
(panting)
(thuds)
Why do I have dreams like that?
- [Kunikida] Momiji, I said
there's a phone call for you!
Right!
Don't they make a
lovely couple, Ryouko?
It must've been caused by
what Mr. Sugishita said.
(footsteps)
Hmm, hello, this is Momiji.
- [Man On Phone]
Congratulations, you've passed
the primary selection
process for the Kanto area.
Passed what?
Sir, just what are
you talking about?
- [Man On Phone]
I'm taking about
the Junior Miss Idol Singer
Talent Scout Caravan!
Miss Idol Singer,
you mean me?
(mystical music)
What?
How strange!
A rival appears.
(airplane roars)
(door clicks)
Mm.
(groans) (chuckles)
- [Sakura] Hey bud, you wanna
take me to the Empire Hotel?
Sure, so, are you here to
do a little sight-seeing?
(engine drones)
No, I'm here to do
a little business.
Hm, I don't suppose you're
possessed by any demons?
Say what?
- [Sakura] Oh don't
worry about it.
(panting) (footsteps)
Oh no, thanks to that weird guy
on the phone I'm gonna
be really, really la...
Oh, oh there she is!
(reporters yelling)
What on earth?
- [Female Reporter] You're Miss
Momiji Fujimiya, aren't you?
- [Male Reporter] I've
heard that you played
a big part in solving
that kidnapping incident.
I'm, I'm sorry, but who are you?
A super heroine who
rescued a six year old girl
and uncovered a dark corner
of the political arena.
Do I have to answer that?
- [Male Reporter] How
is it possible for
a simple high school
student like yourself
to work so closely
with the police?
Um, excuse me but I'm gonna
be really late, sorry!
(panting) (running footsteps)
(soft sad music)
What kind of day
is this gonna be?
So many strange
things have happened.
Ahhh!
Hey!
(screams)
Uh, what's wrong, you're
more spastic than normal?
I am not, you just snuck
up on me, that's all!
(romantic music)
Oh!
Your face looks a little red.
Are you running a fever?
No?
Ah, I guess not.
It's nothing, I'm
perfectly fine.
And it's really got nothing
to do with you anyway.
I'm late, gotta go bye!
Huh?
(footsteps)
What's her problem?
When you tell me you love me.
(humming)
(dreamy music)
(towel ruffles)
Look out, finally
my first assignment
since my triumphant
return to Japan!
Ho!
Hoo!
Ready or not
Aragami, here I come!
This is awesome, awesome!
This is such a great
opportunity Momiji!
But I'm not sure that
I wanna be famous!
I didn't even apply
for this contest!
(gasps)
What if this is just
some kind of prank!
Ah, I wouldn't worry about that.
Maybe a friend of yours signed
you up without asking you.
That's beside the point.
I don't think it's a good idea,
the media are already
following her.
And an Idol contest, really?
But you've got it all wrong.
Don't you see?
Huh?
It's the other way around?
If we have to go
public with the truth
about the existence
of the Aragami,
and if Momiji
becomes a teen idol,
she could help us get
our message across!
If you say so.
You're acting
pretty enthusiastic.
Well, it's really
not such a bad idea.
She is cute, as a matter of
fact, I rather like the idea.
(confused sounds)
And Momiji wants to become
a beautiful idol singer too,
don't you, right?
Well, I uh.
- [Yoshiki] Okay,
then it's decided!
I'll take you to the TV station!
Hm, an idol singer.
(leaves rustling)
(engine roars)
(door clicks)
Hmm.
(motorbike roars)
(chuckling)
(footsteps)
(door creaking)
(lights click)
- [Man] This studio has a
history of strange incidents.
- [Sakura] Mm-hm.
Because of all
the strange things
that keep happening here,
we've had to close the studio
under the false
pretext of renovations.
Mm.
(footsteps)
(wind blowing)
Hm?
(glass shattering)
My god, are you all right?
- [Sakura] Just stand by
with that camera, okay?
What?
This was supposed to
be just an inspection,
but someone doesn't wanna wait.
- [Man] Contestant
14, thank you so much
for taking the
time to come down.
- [Momiji] I feel so
awkward and strange!
Why is this happening to me?
I'm not prepared for
this, and no one except
the participants
are allowed in here.
And next, number 36,
Miss Momiji Fujimiya.
Ah, here!
(chair crashes)
Uh!
(awkward music)
Oh boy, what do I do now?
(clears throat)
Well now, are we ready to begin?
(light music)
Ban boom karak kirik ak.
(mysterious sounds)
Come on Aragami, you
don't have to wait for me
to reveal you, do you?
(explosion)
Um well, excuse me, but
I really don't have any...
You've got no talent?
Ah-uh.
Well, why don't you
perform a skit for us?
You're waiting
for your boyfriend
to go on a date, but
he hasn't shown up yet.
You're getting really
worried, Momiji,
what do you do, huh?
Um, well...
(chanting)
(rattling)
(glass breaks)
Waiting for my
boyfriend on a date,
but he hasn't shown up?
(chanting)
(gurgling)
(mysterious sounds)
(gasps) oh no, not now!
What?
Ah!
Very believable!
Oh!
(panting)
Momiji?
What am I feeling,
where is it coming from?
(heart beating)
It's not the one I usually feel.
I haven't felt this before!
Huh!
Ah, Kusanagi!
Another Aragami?
Yeah!
Right, let's go partner!
Right!
(rocks crashing)
(monster roaring)
Oh, what a nice monster!
- [Kusanagi] Is that it?
- [Momiji] Uh-huh!
- [Sakura] More mitamas, are
you friends of this Aragami?
We came here to kill
it, you ditzy broad!
And who the heck are you anyway?
You're my competition? (laughs)
But if you don't know who
I am you must be amateurs.
I won the total
incantation consultant
office's amulet seal
and prayer award from
the Kusamikado School
of Faith Healers.
I'm Sakura Yamazaki
Aragami buster!
Interesting, Momiji why
don't you step back?
What?
Okay, Miss fortune
teller, let's see which
of us can kill it first, yeah!
- [Sakura] You're on!
But, I thought we were partners!
Yah!
You're pretty good,
what's your name?
I'm Kusanagi.
Ah!
Ya!
My turn, ya!
(monster grumbles)
Ha!
Ya!
(screaming)
(gargling)
(sighs)
(gasps)
Nice fight Kusanagi, come here!
(kisses)
Ah!
(screaming)
You're kind of
impulsive, aren't you?
You know I've been
looking to put some muscle
into this operation.
I'd pay you well, how about it?
- [Kusanagi] Well, I'll
think about it, ha!
Ooh, that's what
I call prime beef.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm Kusanagi's partner!
Oh, here she is!
We thought she'd be here.
Hey hey, camera crew,
yoohoo, over here,
over here, I, Sakura
Yamazaki, Aragami buster
have cleansed this studio
so it's perfectly safe.
- [Male Reporter] You're
quite a young lady.
Huh?
- [Female Reporter] Tell us.
- [Sakura] What?
What happened here?
- [Sakura] Why are
they interviewing her?
Did you do yet
another fantastic job?
- [Male Reporter] So,
what kind of monster
did you kill this time?
No, look see, I really, I
um, uh, I didn't really.
Momiji, are you all right?
(footsteps)
Ah!
Momiji?
That's right! I
read the CIA file.
She's that human sacrifice
girl I can't believe it!
Why should a little
wimpy human sacrifice
get more attention than an
attractive Aragami buster
like me, it's too much!
I'm not gonna let her
steal my spotlight!
(mysterious music)
(radio buzzing)
- [Male Reporter] I guess
you were pretty surprised
by what happened
today, weren't you?
Well, yes, I was, but
I'm also very relieved
because I know that it could
have been so much worse.
I wonder if we're
indebted to this tree,
which has been here
for over 600 years.
(dripping)
(sighs)
Mamoru Kusanagi is
a jerk, an idiot!
Well, I just won't have
anything to do with him.
(splashes)
(bubbling)
Kusangi's too
insensitive anyway,
doesn't he realize
what an important part
of the TAC I've become?
If he doesn't respect
me, he can just go-
- [Voice] Hear me, please.
Huh?
(gasping)
What was that?
- [Kunikida] Momiji!
Yeah?
- [Kunikida] You're going
to the finals tomorrow,
you want to get to bed early!
Kay!
Do I really want to do this?
(mysterious music)
(crackling)
(sticks clunk)
(vibrating)
(leaves rustling)
(crowd talking)
Are you really sure this
is all right, really sure?
Yes, I'm sure Momiji will
make a great idol singer.
But sir!
And if that happens,
she'll become a celebrity.
Don't you see?
That means that if
the government tries
to make us use Momiji
as a sacrifice,
we can use the tie to public
opinion to our advantage.
Huh?
(bangs)
- [Kunikida] You must know
that I have no intention
of sacrificing either Kaede
or Momiji for this country.
- [Ryouko] I see.
(door creaks)
Sorry we took so long.
(gasps)
Mm.
(dreamy music)
(sighs)
It's great, you look great!
I just know you'll
win the finals!
I'm so glad I sent
in that application!
What, what did you say?
Um, oh um, oh um, oh
we'd better be getting
to our seats now!
Momiji, do your best!
(sighs)
(crowd chattering)
Oh, this place is packed!
I can't do this, I'm going home.
(laughing)
Huh?
So, are we finding out
that the spotlight's just
a little too hot for you?
Silly sacrifice.
My name is Momiji, you tramp!
- [Sakura] Ha, your name is Mud.
(gasps)
Now watch closely,
and you'll see how
a real superstar
handles an audience!
Take notes.
(upbeat music)
(running)
What is that girl doing?
Hi everyone, Momiji's cut out
but I, Sakura
Yamazaki will thrill
and bewilder you
with my ample charms.
I can't believe how much
nerve this woman has.
I'm riding on the wind,
as I spread my silver wings.
Like a great eagle I will fly
into the blue sky.
Lovely angels lead me there
as they circle in the air.
Please show me how
you feel about me.
It's like walking in a dream!
When you tell me you love me,
it's a rainbow against
the dark gloom.
Don't be scared to tell me.
I'll be waiting for you.
Huh?
[Sakura And Momiji] Flying
past the gate to heaven.
I'll meet you on a shining star.
A special place that's meant
just for the two of us.
I'm giving my heart
and soul to you.
I promise to always be true.
What are you doing here,
you were so full of fear?
I've just come to
fight for what is mine.
(giggles)
I guess she just might
be competition after all.
Love flowing from your heart.
- [Sakura] Warms
up my secret part.
[Momiji and Sakura] And
sets me on fire deep inside,
you make me so happy.
If you need a place to rest.
[Momiji and Sakura] Place
your head upon my breast.
Let my love sooth
your weary rays.
Kushinada?
(gasps)
(singing)
Listen to me, please,
please listen to me.
That voice, that's the
one I heard last night!
Who are you?
- [Sakura] I've been
waiting for you.
Ha, oh!
(crashing)
(screaming)
Momiji, ah!
Oh good grief!
Are you all right, Momiji?
Um, I think I am!
(crowd shouting)
- [Kusanagi] That
Aragami is still alive.
(monster gurgling)
Everyone keep calm!
Walk to the nearest exit!
Get out of my way, move it!
(crashing)
Real ladies despise having
guests drop in unannounced.
- [Koume] Get out of my
way, this Aragami's mine!
Freeze!
(mystical sounds)
Bye bye, time to
go meet your maker.
(chanting)
Catch!
Yah!
(crashing)
What do you think
of that, freak?
(monster grunting)
What?
What is she doing?
Momiji, stay here, yah!
(yells)
(screams)
Kusanagi!
(monster gurgles)
(heavy breathing)
Shikigami, ha, yah!
(mysterious sounds)
It didn't work,
Kusanagi, I'll attack
the Aragami from behind,
try to break free!
- [Momiji] Hold it right there!
- [Sakura] Don't interrupt
me you sacrifice girl!
If you try and attack
it you don't know
what it might do to Kusanagi!
Killing the Aragami is
the most important thing!
- [Momiji] Leave it alone!
Are you telling me to let
this Aragami monster
get away unpunished?
Let me handle this, understand?
I promise I won't let
them hurt you anymore.
(monster grumbling)
You're the one who
called me, weren't you?
She's talking to it?
Why are you so sad?
(rustling)
Huh?
Ah.
- [Monster] Once I
was a willow tree,
one of a pair, planted
closely, side by side.
Then the men came,
and I was cut down.
My body was gone, but
my roots remained,
buried under the stone and mud.
At the TV station!
- [Monster] We had been
together for such a long time.
And you wanted us to know that.
- [Monster] Yes.
I understand your sorrow,
but a lot of people
were hurt by the way
you expressed it.
- [Monster] I won't
cause any more trouble.
Please, please enshrine my
spirit next to the other tree.
I understand, I promise.
- [Monster] Thank
you, Kushinada.
(whooshing)
(yelling)
(thuds)
- [Momiji] Kusanagi!
(groaning)
Are you hurt, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
- [Momiji] Please,
tell me one thing,
why did you contact me?
Because I'm the Kusahinada?
- [Monster] Yes, but
there is one more reason.
I sensed that you have
feelings much the same as I.
What?
- [Monster] Yearning after
the one you love, suffering.
It was because my feelings
overlapped with yours.
(mystical sound)
(pings)
(sighs)
- [Kusanagi] Momiji,
thanks for what you did.
You're the one all right.
What does that mean?
Why that you're a great
Kushinada of course!
Oh, that.
Hm, what's wrong?
(laughs)
Nothing, really.
(giggling) (romantic music)
No, freaking way!
She made me look
like an amateur!
Arg, yah!
Just you wait sacrifice girl!
The next time we meet,
I'll be the victor!
The rank of top idol and
number one Aragami buster
will belong to me!
I won't lose!
Because of all the
damage to the studio,
this year's idol contest
has been canceled!
And I was so sure that
Momiji would have won!
(crying)
(sad comical music)
(light music)
Ah, I see, I don't know
why I love Kusanagi,
but I wonder what part
of Kusanagi do I like?
I mean he's perverted, indecent,
and he says mean things
to me all the time
and he won't take me out to
have fun either and, what?
Tomorrow?
I don't have any
plans for tomorrow.
Are you asking me?
It's the next
episode of Blue Seed,
number nine, are you serious?
Is this a dream?
An exciting date!
A girl's heart is
pretty complicated.
(relaxed music)
(foreign language)