(thunder crashing)
(energetic rock music)
(singing in foreign language)
(thunder rumbling)
(mechanical whirring)
- [Workman] Ah
jeez, what a mess.
Well, if all those crazy
monsters keep attacking
this structure's
gonna crumble faster
than a piece of
year-old coffee cake.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Huh, what is that?
I sure hope it ain't
one of them monsters.
(rumbling)
You shouldn't have come here.
Inferior humans aren't allowed
to wander about in
places like these.
(suspenseful music)
(screaming)
(chuckling)
(gasping)
Who's there?
(breathing heavily)
Somebody's calling me.
(thunder crashing)
(screaming)
I hate thunderstorms!
- [Kusanagi] (laughing)
You hide your head
but not your butt?
No wonder the storm
won't go away.
Kusanagi!
You came in without asking!
Again!
Nice pose there, Princess.
I'm never gonna
forgive you, you jerk!
I'm an innocent young girl,
in the flower of my youth
and you sneak into my
bedroom and you look at my,
you see me in my pajamas!
Kusanagi, you pervert, you
creep, you rotten, huh?
This is definitely
a Kodak moment.
What, you mean now?
Wait, I just woke up
and my hair's all.
What the heck are you doing?
Ready?
Hey, wait a minute, I...
(thunder crashing)
(screaming)
(whimpering)
I love you!
This is so extreme!
Time to confess?
This is KTV Lunchtime News.
First, news of another
monster attack.
The Metro Police announced today
that the 26th Department
of Public Safety,
the Bureau for Countermeasures,
and Management of
Special Incidents
has been established
to handle incidents
which are related to
unidentified organisms.
Kora Uzaki is
reporting from live
from the downtown
Metro Police office.
Mr. Uzaki?
Yes, I'm standing in front of
the Metropolitan Police
Department Office.
This is Mr. Sugishita,
Director of the 26th
Department of Public Safety,
and he has just
finished speaking
to newspaper reporters.
Director, what exactly are
these mysterious organisms?
Well, I'm Director Sugishita.
Currently we suspect
the mysterious organisms
are chromosomal mutations.
However, the
information gathered
from current samples
is inconclusive.
So it's difficult to determine
just exactly what that means.
We are working closely
with a team of specialists,
so we ask everyone to stay calm.
I'm afraid to say, however,
that similar incidents
may occur in the future.
If you're involved in
one of these incidents,
or if you have any information
that you feel will
aid our research,
please contact me, Sugishita,
Director of the 26th
Department of Public Safety,
here at this station.
(clicking)
Director this, director that.
What a loud-mouth jerk!
But now we can
announce information
about the aragami to the public,
and still keep the existence
of the TAC a secret.
Boy, is that ever true.
It would a serious
problem if people find out
that our government
knew about the aragami
but kept it a secret.
Yes, it would be very sticky.
Like a bag of gummy bears.
Or should I say,
like ara-gummy bears.
(chuckling) Ara-gummy!
(groaning)
Ara-gummy bears!
(laughing)
(quirky music)
I'm late for target practice.
- [Yaegashi] Let's see, that
disc I put that thing on is,
uh, up in the warehouse
somewhere, yeah.
- [Ryoko] We haven't
finished that, uh,
thing yet, have we?
Ara, ara, ara-gummy bears!
(laughing)
Oh, that's rich.
(humming)
Ah, you certainly
look happy today.
What put you in
such a good mood?
Oh, nothing.
It's just a nice day
today, that's all.
Really, then why is your smile
about to split
your face in half?
I'm not smiling that much.
(giggling)
Let's see, same old thing.
No big changes in the
testing numbers today.
What?
It's odd.
The Kushinada
electromagnetic wave shows
some unusual movement.
Has anything strange
happened to you lately?
Well, not that I
know of, really.
I've never seen such an unusual
amount of movement before.
There must be some reason.
I don't know if it has
anything to do with this,
but I've had some
weird dreams lately.
(ominous music)
Somebody's calling me, but
I can't tell who it is.
I see, a dream.
(gasping)
Now I get it.
Huh?
So that's why you're
in such a good mood.
No really, this is nothing.
I was just...
- [Kome] Let me see.
(chuckling)
Huh?
Hey!
Let me see!
Nice picture!
Cut it out, give that back!
Give it back to me!
- [Kome] I knew it, you
guys did it, didn't you?
No, we don't have that
kind of relationship.
Of course you don't,
but you're in love with
Kusanagi, aren't you?
No, I'm not really in
love with him or anything.
We're just friends.
Oh, you don't care, huh?
Well then, we'll just
throw this picture away.
No, don't!
So you are in love with him.
Well, I just,
I don't really know.
I'm just kind of confused.
- [Takeuchi] Well, love is
often confusing, isn't it?
And you know plenty
about that, don't you?
Matsu, what are
you talking about?
Mr. Sugishita?
Sugishita?
Don't be ridiculous.
He's just a young pup.
I like my men to be a
little more experienced.
Well, I like the
big muscular guys.
You know, the caveman type.
Well, I'll ask the gorilla
from the zoo if he's taken!
(screaming)
Shut it, Yaegashi!
So Momiji, have
you told Kusanagi
that you're in
love with him yet?
What?
No, I couldn't.
Idiot!
In order to catch a man,
you've got to spring your
love on him like a trap!
I don't know, isn't
Kome talking about love
one of the signs
of the apocalypse?
(screaming)
Yeah, and here come
the four horsemen.
Clippity clop, clippity
clop, clippity clop!
Well anyway, Kusanagi
isn't a mind reader.
After all, Momiji, if
you don't talk to him
he'll never know how
you feel about him.
But he doesn't care about me.
He probably thinks I'm
just a stupid, klutzy kid
with a dumpy figure.
That's not true, Momiji!
You're a very pretty young lady.
Besides, he's always with you.
Who else would he
fall in love with?
Well, if Kaede ever
reappeared they might.
Then again, maybe not.
Just go ahead and tell the guy
that you're in love with him.
But he always creeps up
on me so unexpectedly
that it makes me all flustered.
What about a love letter?
But we don't know
where he lives.
(sighing)
Well, I think I
have the solution.
- [Momiji] Really?
(chuckling)
- [Yaegashi] Kinda
says it all, don't it?
What, you want me to wear those?
- [Yaegashi] It's something
he checks regularly, isn't it?
(chuckling)
But, um, see, I really
don't think that, um.
You know.
- [All] Hmmm.
You mean, you guys actually
all think I should
really do this?
- [All] Mm-hm.
(phone ringing)
Hello, TAC.
Oh, Sugishita, it's you.
What's the matter?
You think what?
Two days ago, two workmen
were reported missing
from the cave-in
site at the subway.
According to the other
construction workers,
a brilliant flash of light
came from the manhole
just prior to their
disappearance.
I can't send someone
over on a lead
as flimsy as that.
I realize that, but just
look at the location
of the accident.
The subway site is this
red point on the map,
and these three white points
are where the centipede skins
were hung on the buildings.
Hmmm?
- [Sugishita] The
incident occurred
at the center of
these three points.
Now is it worth your time?
Now you're talking, my friend.
The team and I are on our way.
Last one here's a rotten egg.
All right everyone,
let's move out.
Huh?
(quirky music)
Hey, where'd everybody go?
- [Momiji] Oh, I still think
this is a really bad idea.
- [Kome] Hold
still, this stuff is
hard to get off as it is.
- [Momiji] Oh, this
is too embarrassing.
- [Ryoko] Calm down
and put these on!
Hurry up, somebody
might come in here
any minute now.
(sighing)
Hey, Yaegashi.
Why are you sitting
on the floor?
Uh, well, I was...
Is everyone else inside?
Okay everyone, we have to go...
Investigate.
We were, uh.
Well, sir, we were just.
I'm so embarrassed.
What the hell are you all doing?
Right sir, let's move out!
(humming)
Hold it.
If you do tell him, good luck.
Thank you.
Halcyon days of youth.
(giggling)
- [Momiji] Now what do I do?
(eerie music)
He loves me, he loves me not.
He loves me, oh!
Kusanagi!
(screaming)
I'm so embarrassed.
I didn't write that,
the others did it
without my permission.
I really had nothing
to do with that.
- [Kusanagi] I love you too.
- [Momiji] What?
- [Kusanagi] I love
you too, Momiji.
- [Momiji] But I'm a klutz,
and I have a dumpy figure,
and I'm really not very...
- [Kusanagi] No you don't.
- [Momiji] But Kusanagi,
there's somebody else
you love more than me, right?
- [Kusanagi] There is no
way I would love someone
more than I love you.
- [Momiji] Oh Kusanagi,
this is my first real kiss.
(tires squealing)
That hurt.
Are you all right, Momiji?
(giggling)
Yeah, just bumped my head.
- [Kusanagi] I love
you too, Momiji.
He said he loved me.
Now if only it were real.
- [Ryoko] I understand
the basic story.
Is there any other
evidence to suggest that
the aragami are involved
in this incident?
Not really, nothing
else has happened yet.
But I wanted to try
and nip it in the bud.
Don't call on us for
stupid things like this.
We were getting to the bottom
of a problem when you called.
Why?
What's going on over there?
Is it anything I can help with?
It was nothing!
Nothing, don't worry
about it, nothing.
Momiji, concentrate.
Do you sense anything strange?
Uh, no, I don't feel
anything right now.
(ominous music)
(gasping)
Kusanagi!
Hey Kusi boy, nice timing!
Come on, Momiji.
Don't you get chummy with me,
you psychotic gun freak.
My apologies, Kus, old boy.
But it was nice
timing, you know.
(laughing)
What are you talking about
when you say "nice timing"?
It's about Momiji.
(playful music)
Is something wrong, Momiji?
Go for the gusto.
Um.
(giggling)
I just, um.
I wanted to, um.
Tell you, I, um, want.
Are you mentally
ill or something?
I'll do it.
Kusanagi, are you
currently seeing anyone
on a regular basis?
I asked you if you were
currently dating someone.
God, you're as dumb as she is.
Anyway, what do ya think
about ol' Momiji here?
Kome, what are you doing?
(whooshing)
(gasping)
It's close.
Over here!
- [Momiji] You're the
one from my dream.
What is it, Momiji?
Is it aragami?
Where is it?
Who are you?
(gasping)
Momiji!
(shouting)
Matsu!
What?
Hurry up and get in the car!
Is this a dream?
I guess not.
(crowd shouting indistinctly)
- [Momiji] Who are you?
I'm coming.
(whooshing)
(crackling)
(rumbling)
Is this the place?
Are you in here?
It was very foolish of you to
come here, young Kushinada.
- [Momiji] Wait for
me, I'm almost there.
(crackling)
(groaning)
(whooshing)
It's you, you're the one
who's been calling me.
Why did you bring me here?
What do you want from me?
What delicious irony.
The guardian deity of the
aragami is about to be reborn,
and his incredible
uncontrollable power
has summoned none other
than the Kushinada.
(suspenseful music)
Out of my way, you
worthless insects.
Three beacons will appear,
and at their center an
incredible force will gather.
Is this Tomaroshi, the
ceremony of resurrection?
And if it is the sacred rite,
just what exactly do
they intend to do?
- [Momiji] What happens next?
Hmmm.
(heart beating)
(baby crying)
Finally, he has returned.
Where am I?
(laughing)
After thousands of years
of darkened slumber,
our god finally has
awoken and been reborn.
Hey wait, you're that guy!
Have you come back to us?
Then the god must
have gained control
over his awesome powers.
That baby's a god?
The great god Susano-O.
Susano-O?
Susano-O!
Momiji!
Momiji, are you all right?
Yes!
Murakumo!
I'm not going to fight
you, imperfect soul.
Because I can't risk
having anything happen
to young Lord Susano-O.
(rumbling)
Just what exactly are
you up to, Murakumo?
We are finally going to rid
this puny world of
its vile humans.
And we will create the
kingdom Ne no Kuni.
The kingdom of darkness.
We?
Speak for yourself, you
aragami puppet scum!
Princess Kushinada, come
tend to lord Susano-O.
(dramatic music)
(gasping)
Kaede!
It's really you.
Kusanagi!
Kaede, come back!
Kusanagi, no!
Kaede!
(rumbling)
No, this subway
accident wasn't caused
by any of those so-called
chromosomal mutations.
What happened here
was just a simple case
of concrete exhaustion.
He really said he'd rid the
world of us vile humans?
Ha, I'd like to see him try it.
Susano-O.
- [Ryoko] But why
was Kaede there?
- [Kunikida] Kaede.
(melancholy music)
Kaede.
Kusanagi.
Hey, come on,
cheer up, Kusanagi.
Try and think of it this way.
Since my sister's
alive, well then,
you'll probably see
her again someday.
(wind whooshing)
But that was...
The others wrote this,
but I really do feel
that way about you.
I'm in love with you, Kusanagi.
Kusanagi?
(lively music)
Well, I guess my
twin sister Kaede's
alive after all.
Kusanagi, are you still
chasing after her shadow?
I don't know what to do.
And to make matters worse,
all sorts of unexpected
things are popping up.
It's just one problem
after another.
But hopefully everything
will blow over soon.
It's the next episode
of Blue Seed, number 14,
"A Chase Down the Yamato
Highway, Love Under Fire!"
What's eating Mr. Yaegashi?
(mellow music)
(singing in foreign language)