("Carnival Babel"
by Takada Band)
(Heavy thud)
(Kunikida grumbles)
- [Takeuchi] How's
the boss doing?
- [Momiji] What do you mean?
He seems a little
stressed out lately.
You think so?
I thought he was
doing really well
(gun shot)
after what happened.
I mean, he lost his best friend,
but he seems to be
handling everything okay.
Hmmm.
I mean, well,
he still prepares my breakfast
for me every morning,
even if it is instant curry.
- [Takeuchi] Men at his age
(Kunikida grumbles)
tend to work
themselves too hard.
Even when there's
something wrong.
(water splashes)
(bell jingles)
(roots crack)
(boulders crash)
(bell jingles)
(train rumbles)
My insides are on fire.
(Kusanagi groans)
(brakes screech)
Well, home safe and sound.
Huh? Momiji? Are you all right?
Yes.
Momiji?
(melancholy music)
I suppose this looks
pretty fishy, doesn't it?
But, I just can't stop
thinking about him.
(Kunikida grumbles)
Huh?
Takeuchi.
I thought you went home
after you dropped off Momiji.
There's something I
need to tell you about.
(Momiji sighs)
What did that dream mean?
(baby cries)
(Momiji gasps)
(bell rings)
(gong rings)
(baby cries)
Huh. And how was
Momiji after that?
She seemed all right to me.
Hmm.
Well, it was just
a dream, I suppose.
Still, you know,
you could've just told
me that over the radio.
(nervous laughter)
Well, I made too
much by accident.
Is that for me?
Well, I didn't
think you'd eaten.
But you shouldn't have
gone to all this trouble.
Everybody will be in
trouble if you get sick.
So, why don't you try a
bite of the grilled beef?
After all, you are
the meat of the TAC.
Is that a joke?
Well, you've been too busy
to make any of your puns lately.
Thank heavens for
small favors, right?
Actually, I kind of
miss hearing them.
You really miss my puns?
- [Takeuchi] Sir, you've been
working overtime ever since
you came back from Wakasa.
You're gonna ruin
your health, sir.
I'm fine.
Besides, you should worry more
about yourself than about me.
Huh?
You should make dinners like
this for some nice young guy,
not a crusty old man like me.
Remember the old
saying, "Life is short,
fall in love, woman."
You shouldn't focus your energy
on an old fossil like me.
But thank you for
your thoughtfulness.
You're welcome.
Stupid.
The inexplicable phenomenon
of the dying trees
has increased,
centering around the areas
where the Aragami
have been sighted.
Did the Aragami suck the
nutrition from the trees?
No, this phenomenon has
continued at the site
even after we
killed the Aragami.
But why?
Is it possible that
the abnormal phenomenon
now occurring all across Japan
is a ritual of purification?
Performed by ancient
gods of Japan.
Do you understand?
The Japan of today
has become so defiled
that not even a
god would claim it.
Father, tell me the
nature of the Japan
I must protect
with my sacrifice.
If it is my destiny,
then tell me, I beg you.
(TV chatter)
(Kunikida sighs)
Huh?
(fax machine prints)
(phone rings)
Hello, Takeuchi speaking.
- [Kunikida] It's me.
I have to go Ise to
run some errands.
Ise?
Do you mean the city of
Ise where the shrine is?
Mhm.
There's something I
need to investigate.
I'll be back sometime tomorrow.
(bullet train rumbles)
- [Takeuchi] May I sit here?
Oh, excuse me.
Please, have a seat, I'm, uh...
Takeuchi?
What are you doing here?
I need to check
on something, too.
Mind if I sit down?
(bullet train rumbles)
So what's going on?
(Kunikida grunts)
A landslide occurred in
the mountains near Ise.
Is there anything that
points to Aragami?
No, nothing in particular.
Then why go there?
Hmm.
It's just intuition.
Intuition?
But Boss.
The landslide occurred
when Momiji had that dream.
Is that the only reason?
Yes, it is.
I'm just following a hunch.
(bullet train rumbles)
(soft thud)
(snoring)
He pushes himself
too much, really.
(Takeuchi sighs)
Please, keep sleeping
until we get to Ise.
(truck rumbles)
Susano-Oh,
you're plotting something
big, aren't you?
I feel it in my pajamas.
A meddler is approaching.
Imarogi, come.
(Imarogi roars)
(brakes screech)
(Kunikida grunts)
Huh?
Well, ma'am, like I
told you on the phone,
I think this is just an
ordinary every day landslide.
Has the team found
any sinkholes,
or was this the only area
that was affected
by the landslide?
Negatory, ma'am.
A slight tremor reached Oirase.
(Kunikida grunts)
Sir?
Please stop, sir.
There are things
you amateurs would overlook!
Calm down.
I would be satisfied
even if I get
just a piece of tree root.
Sir, it's too dangerous.
Let us handle this.
You call yourself
a member of the
Japanese Self-Defense Force?
You think it's okay
to blow this off?
(soldiers agrue)
Leave me alone.
Please, make yourself at home.
Yes, thank you.
I overplayed my hand, didn't I?
We can go back and
try again tomorrow.
And we'll hit the earthquake
epicenter in Isobe.
Should I ask Matsu to come?
Oh no, it was only
a foolish intuition.
You've just been
working much too hard
for your own good, sir.
(sighs)
Huh?
Oh, how cute, and it
looks just like you.
Huh?
I'll give it a shot.
One more time.
(chuckles) Wait a second.
You need to use a
little strategy.
Have you ever done this?
They had these back in
the ancient days, too.
Which one do you want?
The lion, there.
The one with the
big bushy beard.
Hmm.
So that one resembles
me, does it?
Well, maybe a little.
All right, then.
Right there, sir,
that's perfect.
(sighs heavily) This
is a lot more stressful
than I thought it would be.
Be careful now, sir,
easy does it.
Okay, okay.
There, That's it, that's it.
(Both groan)
This one still looks like you.
(gorilla snort)
(chuckling)
(phone ringing)
Kunikida speaking.
- [Man 1] The Mie
Perfecter Police Department
has just contacted us and
told us that the Aragami
have appeared near
the Ise Jingu shrine.
What was that?
(bumper music)
(Imarogi roars)
(people scream)
- [Man 1] The Aragami
is heading north
toward the Iguyamada area,
along the Isuzu River.
- [Kunikida] Understood.
Get the team there immediately.
My body feels
heavier and heavier.
I'll be with you
soon, Susano-Oh.
(Imarogi growls)
Get out of my way.
What the...?
(Kusanagi yells)
Kusanagi.
(bell jingles)
(Imarogi growls)
(Kusanagi groans)
(helicopter whirs)
Hey, are we there yet?
- [Pilot] We'll
be over Ise soon.
The feeling is getting stronger.
It's the same as
the time Susano-Oh...
- [Matsu] Look at that.
- [Yaegashi] Wow,
it's not spring,
but the cherry
trees are blooming.
What's going on?
The Aragami isn't there.
I really wish I
could use my arms.
Kusanagi, hang in
there, plant boy.
Its skin is extremely tough.
Aim at the inside of its
mouth with the bioreactor.
Roger.
(rocket blasts)
(Imarogi roars)
- [Koume] Yeah!
All the parasites
inside the missiles
have spread into its stomach,
and are eating away at
the monster's cell wall.
(Imarogi explodes)
I've done it.
(Kusanagi groans)
- [Takeuchi] How's Kusanagi?
- [Matsu] I think he'll
be fine after he rests.
He has incredible
recuperative powers.
That Aragami.
It was looking for
you, wasn't it?
I guess they don't want me here.
Try and get some rest.
- [Momiji] He's been
chasing after Kaede
for such a long time.
Today is the first time
in a while I've seen him.
And I want to be with him.
So, are you giving up on him?
No, of course not.
Well, then don't worry.
You know, you're
only young once.
So do what feels right.
Do what feels right?
Yep, that's what I said.
The only way to win his heart
is to go for it, Momiji.
Yeah, that's right.
Thanks, Ms. Takeuchi.
Go girl.
- [Matsu] Who's
saying go for it?
Matsu, I didn't
know you were here.
(laughs) It's easy to say,
but pretty difficult to do,
isn't it?
What did you mean by that?
I wonder.
See you later.
I guess I've soaked too long.
Oh man.
So do what feels right.
Huh?
Where's he going?
(gasps)
Sir?
(evil chuckling)
What's up, girlie?
Why don't you come
and play with us?
Taxi!
Stop it.
Stop, or I'll...
Stop it or what?
Tell me?
- [Punk] Ah yeah.
Want some candy, little girl?
Help me, boss.
(fighting groans)
Sir, it's you.
Get your paws off her,
you dirty stinking apes.
I oughta rip your head off.
Please stop, sir.
- [Punk] We'll get you.
Are you all right?
Yes, thank you.
I just wanted to see
where you were going.
(sighs)
The epicenter of the earthquake
and the abnormal cherry blossoms
are both focused
in the same area,
and I don't think
it's a coincidence.
I looked at the map and
one place jumped out at me.
Which place, sir?
Amano-Iwato.
The Cave of the Sun God?
Isn't Amano-Iwato in Takachiho,
on the island of Kyushu?
I thought so, too,
but there was another
Iwato here, in Ise.
Something has
occurred to produce
an incredible amount of energy.
What's going on there?
That's what I'm
going to find out.
- [Murakumo] You might get
hurt if you get too involved.
What are you doing here?
You really wanna know?
(chuckles)
All right, then.
I'm here to wipe the human race
from the face of the Earth.
Then this country will
become our kingdom,
the kingdom of the Aragami.
(Kunikida grunts)
(gun shots)
Not a very wise move, human.
(Kunikida groans)
- [Takeuchi] Daitetsu!
If you come any closer,
I'll kill you now.
Somebody, help me!
Is he going to be all right?
He's resting
comfortably in his room.
We will go into
the cave, won't we?
It's too dangerous to
go there unprepared.
I wonder what Susano-Oh
intends to do.
We don't know the details yet.
But I'm sure things will get
worse if we don't do something.
I guess we don't
have time to wait
for the boss to recover.
(everyone gasps)
My god.
Oh.
I'm still going with you.
I'm still the boss.
Don't be foolish.
Now you stay here and rest up.
We'll handle this one, sir.
Please take me with you.
I can't just sit
here and do nothing.
I need to do something.
Anything.
I've got to decide what
it is I have to protect,
and what it is that
I want to protect.
I thought you wanted
to protect Japan
and the rest of the
world from the Aragami?
Japan.
Where has the Japan
we dreamed about
when we were young gone?
Japan was what killed Yamatomai.
Tell me the nature of the
Japan that I have to protect.
And Japan took my Kaede as well.
And everyone else
exploited the Earth
and contaminated the rivers.
And all the while,
they pretended they
were being cautious.
Please stop it.
Why should we fight for Japan?
Why should we protect all
the dirty, murderous filth
that destroys the Earth?
Why should we protect the scum
that attacked you in the alley?
Why are we the ones
that make the sacrifice?
Why should we risk
our lives for Japan?
It's better off dead.
The Aragami can have it.
You don't really mean that.
I'm sorry, Ryouko.
Something must be wrong with me.
No.
Nothing's wrong.
You've just been working
yourself too hard lately.
(explosion)
What the hell was that?
Huh?
Yes, Takeuchi here.
- [Momiji] Ms. Takeuchi,
Kusanagi is missing.
Where is he?
The Cave of the Sun God.
All right, Murakumo.
Where is Susano-Oh?
Is Kaede here, too?
So, Kusanagi,
are you feeling better now
than you were earlier today?
What does that mean?
Kusanagi.
It means we have
completed the ceremony
for Lord Susano-Oh.
What ceremony?
Explain yourself, you...
(Kusanagi gasps)
It's Kaede.
That's Kaede?
My sister.
Kaede, why did you
help Susano-Oh?
Kaede.
Kaede Kunikida is no longer.
(everyone gasps)
I have become Kaede
the Kushinada.
But why?
Why did you leave us, Kaede?
I wanted to be protected.
What was that?
Because the Japan
that the Kushinada
was to protect has disappeared.
Don't you hear it
crying, father?
Listen closely.
You can hear Japan weeping.
Dear god, Kaede.
What have they done to you?
What have those monsters
turned you into?
Farewell, father.
Kaede.
Kusanagi, come back.
The cherry blossoms
are like tears.
Sir, I,
I wanted to tell you.
- [Kunikida] Tell me what?
I love...
Japan.
I mean, I really love Japan.
That's it.
(chuckles)
You're blushing.
Am I really?
Know what?
I love Japan, too.
Unbelievable.
Sacrifice girl.
I won't let you be the heroine.
I'm number one.
Sakura Yamazaki always
says stuff like this.
She's usually in a
really snotty mood.
I thought she was
just another showoff
that used to live in America.
I didn't know that
she had a secret past.
It's the next episode of
Blue Seed number eighteen.
Jeez.
Oh man.
Sakura's not good enough?
Memories of a mother
can be painful.
("Touch and Go" by
Megumi Hayashibara)