(upbeat music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(crowd chattering)
(crowd screaming)
What's going on?
I've never had a feeling
like this before.
Kusanagi?
Susano-oh's, energy emissions
are getting stronger
and stronger.
I can hear his thoughts.
- [Announcer] I'm home, Izumo,
the prologue of hope.
(phone ringing)
- [Woman] I wouldn't
tell you anything else,
but it's a very big monster.
(office chattering)
Yes, that's right.
- [Woman] This is TAC.
- [Woman] You don't
have any tanks?
Well, do you have any?
- [Woman] TAC Monster Division.
- [Man] And did it eat
mother in law before
or after your dog?
- [Man] These are
basically the same as
the ones that appeared
at Kogure the other day.
- [Woman] TAC.
What's going on?
These things are
popping up all over.
Here's another pile
of incident reports.
All of these?
Yes, we've already
confirmed over 200 reports
of these root like
objects all across Japan.
- [Man] I don't care
how many there are.
What I want to know, what the
Japanese people want to know,
is what these things are?
- [Man] Yes, sir.
If we try to keep the
Aragami's existence
a secret much longer,
it can foster distrust
in our government
and other countries
will demand to know
what's going on.
We're trying to solve this
as quickly as possible, sir.
- [Man] Don't
promise, just do it.
The future of your organization
will depend upon it, Kunikida.
Right.
(phone ringing)
- [Woman] TAC, will
you please hold?
TAC, will you hold it?
Yaegashi, get me the
information on Takachiho.
Takachiho, you mean
in Miyazaki in Kyushu?
That's right.
Well, around the area
of Takachiho we've got.
Any reports of cherry
blossoms out of season?
Oh yes, sir.
Over a dozen reports already.
Exactly as I thought.
This means Susano-oh
is now in Takachiho.
- [Everyone] What?!
Kusanagi.
Takeuchi, we're going to
go to Izumo right now.
Izumo, not Takachiho?
That's right, I noticed
something while examining
this map of the mass
foliage die offs
besides the big cities,
which have few tracks
of green land,
there are some spots
that have been skipped
by this phenomenon.
Ise, Takachiho and here, Izumo.
You're absolutely
right, how strange.
Now what do Ise and
Takachiho have in common?
Amano-Iwato?
Yes, but the Iwato in
Takachiho is better known.
Right, we know that Susano-oh
has been growing in
the Iwato on Ise.
In all likelihood,
he visits all the Iwatos
and absorbs the
energy they've stored.
The last time of Iwatos
must be in Izumo, there.
- [Yaegashi] That's the
place where Susano-oh
and the Kushinada met during
the Age of Legends, isn't it?
And that's why we're
going to Izumo.
I'm sure that this holy
place must be the Iwato
that's most important to
Susano-oh and Kushinada.
Damn, now I know
what a potato baking
in the oven must feel like,
but this is going to lead
me right to you, Susano-oh.
(dramatic music)
Why are you here?
- [Kusanagi] I've
got a lot of reasons.
You must want to die.
Only a fool would challenge us.
Maybe I've just got nothing
left to lose blue boy.
On the other hand,
if I kill Susano-oh
it might just solve a
whole world of problems.
You have been very foolish,
but merciful Lord Susano-oh
will forgive your impudence
if you surrender
your mind to him.
Well, isn't that nice?
But I'm afraid I'll
have to refuse.
Stand back, Kaede!
No, I won't!
- [Kusanagi] You've
changed Kaede.
(yelling)
You're attempting to
harm Lord Susano-oh.
The penalty for that is death.
(tense music)
Die!
(screaming)
The time has come to complete
Lord Susano-oh's ritual.
Further struggle
is quite pointless.
Try this point you
blue haired jerk!
What?
Die!
(screaming)
What incredible
power (chuckling).
Amazing, don't you
know when to die?
And now Kusanagi I'm
sending you to hell.
- [Kaede] That's enough!
But princess.
- [Kaede] I said that's enough.
If you don't kill me now, Kaede,
you'll regret it later.
Please, spare me your
ridiculous bolstering.
Murakumo we must leave
for Izumo at once.
I understand.
Kaede, wait!
(car whirring)
Is something wrong Momiji?
I'll bet you're nervous
about going back home.
No.
At least you'll have
a lot of time to visit
with your mom and grandma.
I think we can do without
you for a few days.
No, I want to help you, sir.
I've been feeling extremely
sensitive for the past few days.
I think it's
because of Susano-oh
because his power is getting
stronger and stronger.
Something terrible will
happen if we don't find him.
Takeuchi could you
stop the car, please?
This is the place
where it all began.
Remember Momiji?
I'm sorry, but I
have to kill you.
How strange, what a terrible way
to have met you
for the first time.
(dramatic music)
Go on Momiji.
Welcome home!
Mom!
You're more beautiful
than I remembered.
I'm really home.
There that ought to cover
the sentimental stuff, right?
Mr. Kunikida we gotta
tart searching as soon as
we put our bags away.
Well.
Oh, don't worry I'll
get another chance
to see mom again, right?
Momiji!
Noogies, noogies,
and more noogies.
Akiko, what are you doing?
You're mother told
me you were coming.
Why didn't you call me you rat?
I'm sorry.
Well, sir, why don't we leave
while the getting's good?
Right.
But.
You've been gone a
long time, Momiji.
Yeah, but.
Hey, you heard her.
Why don't the two
let's head on down
to the good old karaoke palace
and catch up on lost time, huh?
But, I.
Mm, yum.
I wonder if we should
have disconnected
the phones like that?
It was either that
are starve to death,
You really gotta wonder
what Susano-oh's up to
growing those dumb
roots all over Japan.
Well I just heard that the boss
and the others can find
something in Izumo.
Yeah, I think that it's pretty
strange that nothing's happened
to any of the roots
since they first appeared
besides the fact that they
grew in the first place.
I keep wondering if all
those roots are going
to suddenly start moving.
- [Woman] Quiet, you idiot!
Geez, why'd do you have to
say something like that?
Things are bad enough without
you putting a jinx on them.
I'm sorry, I've gone
through everything we have,
but there is no
Amano-Iwato in Izumo.
That's impossible!
Hey Momiji, where are you going?
Akiko, do you know where
the Amano-Iwato is located?
What the cave of the sun god,
what is it with you Momiji?
The last time it was the
Kushinada and now this?
Well, I'm pretty sure I
saw something like that
the last time I
came here to pray.
There it is!
This could be it.
Uh huh.
What are you doing Momiji, hey?
This isn't it.
- [Man] What are
you doing girls?
Oh, excuse me, I was looking
for the Amano-Iwato.
The Cave of the Sun God,
that's just an air
raid shelter, my child.
An air raid shelter?
What's the problem Momiji?
I don't understand it.
Why would they put
an arch in front
of an air raid shelter?
Have you finished
what you're doing yet?
Hey, what's wrong?
Another vision it was
Izumo in ancient times.
Momiji are you there?
Huh?
Hey, you're not in love
with someone are you Momiji?
What are you talking about?
You fell in love with
someone in Tokyo,
didn't you know?
No, I mean not exactly.
You're turning into
such a pretty big,
well come with me lover girl!
Wait, this is nothing
to do with love.
The Yaegaki Jinja
Shrine is a place
to make your love last forever.
The whole shrine's
dedicated to Susano-oh
and the Kushinada.
What?
- [Akiko] Hey?!
Susano-oh and the Kushinada?
So anyway, tell me who...
Momiji?
(dramatic music)
- [Akiko] Go ahead, I'm going
to go buy some ice cream.
Okay.
Mr. Kunikida said that there
will be one last ceremony
at the Iwato in Izumo.
I wonder what Kaede and
Susano-oh intend to do.
Momiji!
This is Tokyo.
Shinjuku in Tokyo.
Kaede what is this?
I don't understand.
Are you going to
do this to Tokyo?
Why, why?!
I'm sorry, I'll get
you another one.
What's wrong with you?
Something's wrong
with you, Momiji.
Sorry, Akiko.
Momiji, you've changed somehow.
I was so happy when I heard
that you were gonna be back,
but there's something's
definitely wrong with you.
Akiko.
I'm sorry, I'm going home now.
If we succeed in
finding the Iwato
all of this will be over.
Please God, help me.
Help me to find the
location of the Iwato.
It's got To be here in Izumo.
(children playing and cheering)
Thanks, weird kid (laughing).
Lord Susano-oh, we
have come to Izumo.
This is the place where we
first met in ancient times
so many years ago?
Akiko!
Look I'm sorry.
Momiji, you've changed
since you went to Tokyo.
I have.
I mean, no, I haven't.
Then why do you keep
suffering in silence?
I've been your friend
for over five years
and it's as plain as
the nose on your face
that you've got a problem.
Akiko.
This is about the
Kushinada, right?
Wait, Akiko, slow down!
(dramatic music)
Six months ago that
monster destroyed
the old school building and
then you just disappeared.
They're connected, aren't they?
I know you've been
purifying yourself
since you were in
the fifth grade.
Is that related to all this?
I'm sorry, I just can't
tell you right now.
You jerk, you stupid,
dimwitted little turnip.
Akiko?
Why must you always be
such a pathetic loser!
Not only are you
dumb and clumsy,
you're selfish as well.
Hey, look who's talking here?
You couldn't even
get up the nerve
to give that love
letter to that senior.
You wanted to get me to
give it to him for you!
Why'd you bring that up?
Because you piss me off!
Then my plan worked.
Huh?
It's about time that I
saw the real Momiji again.
But I.
You've been putting
up a false front
ever since you got here.
You shouldn't have
done that, Momiji.
Akiko.
Momiji, I've been really,
really worried about you.
I'm sorry.
- [Akiko] Geez, I've never
seen anyone cry so much.
Oh, well, at least it proves
you're the real Momiji.
- [Momiji] I'm
really sorry, Akiko.
Well, I guess I'll
forgive you for now.
That's a strange way to put it.
(laughing)
But please Momiji,
don't forget this.
You're the kind of person
who can't control herself
once she's decided to
give something her all,
but think about a balloon.
If you put in too much
air it'll explode, right?
So call me, okay?
Yeah, thank you.
Right, and the
next time we meet,
why don't we bring
our boyfriends?
Both of us.
What, why?
Of course someone might
need to bring her kids too.
But what are you talking about?
Well, you've
already got your man
picked out, don't you?
He's got nothing to do with me.
(chuckling) Yeah, sure.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Do you remember
when you were little
you wanted to play
with the fireworks
and screamed and cried?
Oh, really, I don't
remember that at all.
(chuckling) To be honest,
I was like that too
when I was a little girl.
At least, that's what
grandma keeps telling me.
Really (laughing)?
- [Mother] We share
the same blood,
so please tell me anything when
you're having a rough time.
- [Momiji] Okay.
- [Mother] That's the only
thing I can do for you
to pay you back for.
Oh no, no, no, I
really appreciate you
for giving birth to me.
I've got a lot of troubles
right now, of course,
but there's some
people I never would've
met if I wasn't the Kushinada.
A wonderful chance to meet
someone was given to me.
Grandmother, if there isn't
an Iwato in this area,
what should we look for?
Look at this picture.
(gasps)
But this is a picture
of the giant plants
that have been appearing
all over Japan.
That's right.
Grandmother, where did
this picture come from?
This is the ceremony of Tamafuri
from a book on the Kushinada
that has been passed
down through my family.
(dramatic music)
Finally, it's time to wipe
away the miserable human race
who've acted as if
they own the earth
and contaminate
its very essence.
Soon you will use
your awesome powers
to revive the real
Japan Lord Susano-oh.
The ceremony of Tamafuri will
the clean this filthy earth
and make it green again.
Then this planet
will be at peace.
Susano-oh and the Kushinada,
originally those two
were husband and wife.
Then the ceremony
of Tamafuri might
be a way of creating mitama.
Could this ceremony be a
way to create more Aragami?
Impossible, do you mean
that Kaede, the Kushinada,
will create Aragami?
How can this be?
If I'm right, something
terrible will happen soon.
Susano-oh has already taken
control of the Kushinada.
He intends to create a whole
country filled with Aragami?
It's my future.
I won't let our future
become like that.
Right, Kusanagi?
Kusanagi!
Is that Momiji?
Kusanagi, can you
really hear me?
This is incredible, I'm
actually hearing you.
But why?
I don't know, but it
could be that our mitamas
are somehow calling each other.
Our mitamas did come
from the same Aragami.
Orochi, remember?
That makes sense, right?
I understand,
eight beads in one,
so the two of us are one.
We're together no matter
how far apart we are.
Huh, I guess that's
true, isn't it?
Well, let's do the
best job we can.
Even if I'm alone, I'm with you.
I'll be able to survive no
matter what happens to me.
(dramatic music)
Do you feel it coming trees?
Do you feel the time of the
revival of Lord Susano-oh?
At last the earth shall be
reborn as our ideal heaven.
The time of the opening
of the Iwato is at hand.
I won't let you go Susano-oh!
Until I've killed you,
I'll follow you wherever you go!
- [Momiji] Susano-oh is
about to turn all of Japan
into the land of the Aragami.
I've always believed
that we can stop him
as long as we're able to
use my power and Kusanagi's.
But something's wrong.
Kusanagi, what's happening?
Talk to me please,
where are you?
You've disappeared,
and it feels as if
my heart has turned to ice.
It's the next episode of
Blue Seed, episode number 21.
Goodbye, no way.
A tearful farewell.
I won't let you
die on me Kusanagi.
(sensual music)
(singing in a foreign language)