(thunder crashing)
(pop music)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
(singing in Japanese)
♪ Mysterious Tokyo ♪
♪ Take it easy dangerous night ♪
♪ Pick me up foxy night game ♪
- [Narrator] All across Japan,
strange, giant plants have
suddenly begun to grow.
The Aragami, mankind's
ancient enemies,
have awoken the
sleeping God, Susano-Oh,
from his millennia long
slumber, and we now know
that they intend to do
something horrible to Japan.
But what?
Nobody knows.
And the danger continues to grow
as more and more of
the root like plants
keep emerging from the ground.
The key to solving the
mystery seems to be
the Amano Iwato, the
cave of the Sun God,
which we think is located in
my old home town of Izumo.
But we can't find it anywhere.
Together with Mr.
Kunikida and Ms. Takeuchi,
I've returned to Izumo
to search for the Iwato.
And there's someone
else here, as well.
For some time now, I've
been sensing the presence
of Kusanagi in the
back of my mind.
It's so strange.
Even though we're
really miles apart,
sometimes it's as if he was
standing right next to me.
Kusanagi thinks that
we share this link
because of our mitamas, which
came from the same Aragami.
But maybe it's something more.
If we get through this alive,
once we've finally beaten
Susana-Oh and the Aragami,
maybe we'll have time to get
to know each other better.
To do the sort of things
normal people do together.
I think I'd really like that.
Goodbye?
No way!
A Tearful farewell?
(wind howling)
My diary.
I haven't written in it at all.
Not since I met...
(gasp)
Kasanagi.
Lord Susana-Oh and I must leave
for the last Iwato.
(gasp) The Iwato!
But where?
Marakumo, I'll trust
you to make sure
that everything
is taken care of.
- [Marakumo] It will
be done, Kushinada.
(stone whirs)
Mitamas.
What does this have
to do with them?
Huh, you don't really
think those two
will get to consummate the
ritual of Izumo, do you?
I'm going to break
up this wedding!
(chuckling) I don't think so.
Oh yeah?
Hm, I'm afraid that you
just weren't invited.
(both yelling)
What?
I'll meet you in
Izumo, Princess Katy.
Very well, take care then.
(Marakumo yells)
Huh?
Aaaah!
(explosion)
Katy!
What are you trying to do?
Momiji.
- [both men] huh?
(gasps)
Momiji!
Well, you sensed our
presence, even here.
You're getting to
be quite a nuisance.
But how?
How can you hear me?
Hello, sister.
We're going to
return Japan to the
way it should've been.
It should've been?
You mean by destroying
entire cities full of
people with your strange plants?
But why?
Why?
(wind howls)
That was my sister.
Kusanagi, please tell me that
everything will be alright
if we both do our best.
But, why?
(sobbing)
Why is Katy doing
something like this?
Why did she go to Susano-Oh?
The Kusanada is supposed
to protect Japan.
(crying)
I don't understand.
Why Katy?
Why?
(continues sobbing)
If we follow the reactions
of Momiji's Matama,
I'm sure that we can
find the Iwato that
Susano-Oh is heading towards.
I suppose it might work.
Huh?
Oh, thanks.
Roar!
Just making sure
that you're alert.
I'm just trying to take your
mind off your problems, sir.
Yesterday may have
been long and hard,
but I'm sure something
will come up today
if we put our minds to it.
That's a good point,
we can't let the
stress get to us.
We ought to relieve it somehow.
You bet!
We both need it, sir!
Ahem.
Am I interrupting?
Uh, well.
You couldn't sleep well
last night, could you?
Uh huh.
And what about the Iwato?
Um, we're still looking.
Would you mind hurrying
this up a little?
Just be quiet and follow me.
Yes, Grandma.
Huh?
What is that?
(dramatic music plays)
This is the Aiashi No Hokora,
the cave of restoration.
It's the birth right
of the Fujumia family,
the family of the Gushinadas.
Nobody knows much
more than that.
Not even me.
Oh.
This is what we're looking for.
Why didn't you tell us?
Sorry, this place has
been in the family so long
we don't even think of it
as being unusual anymore.
This must be the last Iwato.
It's possible.
Well, I've shown it to you.
The rest is up to you.
Mrs. Fujimia?
You must do whatever you
think is best, Mr. Unakita.
(groans)
I understand, sir.
I'll keep searching for
Susano-Oh with Momiji.
Her Matama should let us
know when he's in the area.
I'm sorry about the
change in our plans.
I've just got a feeling
about this place.
Sir?
Huh?
Oh, thanks.
I'm just glad you're
feeling better, sir.
You look better, too.
Full of hope.
I am, huh?
(giggles)
I've got to contact the
Izumo Self-Defense Force,
but, I'll see you later.
Well, I think that we can
keep ourselves occupied.
But in case your hunch is wrong,
we'll keep an eye out
for strange caves.
Yeah!
This Eragami detector
will find Susano-Oh first!
Mrs. Takiuchi, you're not
gonna let him score on you,
are you?
Uh...
You're in charge.
- [Momiji] Roger!
(tires squealing)
Hmmm.
(dramatic music)
(grunting)
Damn!
Why must you float
around so much?!
(laughs menacingly)
Come on!
(dramatic music)
(explosions)
Look at this.
This city was such
a peaceful place
until just a few days ago.
What's going to become of Japan?
Why don't you ask
one of these things?
(groans)
Come on!
Get a move on!
Grab that ammo!
Get your butts in...!
[helicopter pilot] Offensive
engine is in position!
Division in range!
(whirring)
Susano-Oh is coming.
When that time comes,
can I really shoot Katy?
(sad music plays)
Hey, are you ready?
Say "limburger!"
- [Katy] Come on, Dad,
don't make me laugh.
(laughs) But everyone
prefers the way you look
when you smiling to that
pouty face you're making
right now.
I don't like it when I laugh.
I always end up looking weird.
Okay, cheese!
Cheese.
(gunshot)
(gasps)
Katy.
It's a heavy burden, isn't it?
Huh?
Mrs. Fujimia.
Hesitate,
and you may cause the
end of all you hold dear.
Huh?
I understand.
(sad music)
Katy, I didn't want
to see you again.
Not now, not like this.
(sad music continues)
It's hard.
Mrs. Fujimia?
Things are about to
happen all over Japan.
But still, one mustn't
act too rashly.
It's too easy to make mistakes.
Ah, listen to me, talking to
myself, just like an old woman.
(sighs)
How were you able to survive
with such pathetic powers?
(explosive music)
(chuckles) How inconvenient it
must be to be unable to fly.
An intelligent fighter
uses his brains
to offset his physical
disadvantages.
(dramatic music)
I'm a lot better
than I used to be!
Oh, sure!
(upbeat music)
Well, we've arrived
at our destination.
So, I guess I ought
to start the ceremony.
I hope you like surprises.
What?
(laughing)
What the...?
(ominous ringing)
(whirring)
Uh oh!
Marakumo, what are you up
to now, you spiny freak?
Moe, what are you doing?
Forming a barrier.
With her blood?
Mmh.
(high pitched ringing)
(whirring)
It's still coming
from way up ahead.
What does the map say?
Looks like we should take
Route 431 to Shinjiko Lake.
Okay.
Momiji, you look pretty eager.
Mmm Hmm.
I'm going to do my greatest
detective work today!
You will, huh?
Isn't it great when you
both share a common goal?
Yeah!
(water rushing)
(screaming)
What?
What the hell was that?
(ominous music)
A mirror.
(laughs menacingly) Our
great lord, Susano-Oh,
will be arriving at
the Iwato any time now.
And when the sun's rays
finally strike that mirror.
The bells will announce
Susano-Oh's ritual.
And toll a death knell
for the human race.
And then the world of
the Aragami, our world,
will at last be born!
Not if I can help it!
Aaaaaaargh!
(dripping)
Moe was once a Kushinada.
Huh?
The full power of her
line has been passed
to Momiji's generation.
But, there should be enough
left to make her seal
worth that sacrifice.
I know my blood can't stop them,
but it might delay them.
Hmmm.
All the troops have taken
their positions, sir.
Very good.
Thank you, sir!
(tapping)
Susano-Oh is coming.
I know he's coming
to this Iwato.
The trees sense their presence.
Yes.
They're here!
- [Soldier] There they are!
Stop them!
Don't move lady, or we'll
shoot you and the kid!
(whirring)
(crackling)
Aah!
(dramatic music)
Momiji, what's wrong?
Susano-Oh is over there!
Huh?
Then what have we been chasing?
(whirring)
What are you going to do
with this thing, you monster?
I see no reason
to tell you that.
I guess I'm going to
have to shatter it, then.
Aaaaah!
- [Marakumo] How dare
you interrupt me!
(crashing)
Kusanagi!
I told you!
I'm a little different
from the way I used to be.
Quite impressive,
you're not as weak
as I believed.
And in appreciation for this,
I'm going to stop
playing with you.
Goodbye Kusanagi.
Kusanagi!
Momaiji, you've got to
get back to Izumo, now!
If Katy and Susano-Oh
seal off the Iwato,
it'll be all over!
But you!
Stop arguing with me
just get out of here!
But, Kasanagi!
Kasanagi!
Momiji.
Mrs Takeichi, we've
got to get back now!
(gunfire)
(screaming)
(crackling)
(sad music)
Why must I see you this way?
Perhaps the time
and nature of this
meeting were inevitable.
I had no choice.
This is my destiny.
For I am the Kushinada.
Huh.
But, Katy,
this technological
travesty that we live in,
modern Japan, is an
assault upon my senses,
an assault upon the
sanity of the Kushinada.
The Kushinada is
Japan's protector.
(explosion)
(dramatic orchestral music)
Hold it, Katy!
Please, stop!
I love you, Katy!
I raised you as if
you were my own child!
Please, Katy, don't make
me shoot my own daughter.
You never answered any
of my questions, Father.
But, Katy.
Japan is crying.
It is my duty to create
a Japan that deserves
the protection of a Kushinada.
But, to do that I must
regress all of the
more advanced life forms
to the most basic level.
Every human must
be transformed into
something I can control.
You're insane!
All human lives must therefore
be reduced to the
level of plants!
Katy!
What do you mean when you
say that you'll reduce
everyone to the level of plants?
I'm not even if what you
say is even possible.
But how could you think
of doing such a thing?
You'd turn Mom and Grandma
and my friend Keiko
and Mr. Kunakita
and Mrs. Takeuchi
and everyone else at
the TAC into plants?
Even Kusanagi?
Turning people into plants?
How could anyone think
of such a horrible,
monstrous thing?
I don't understand!
Kusanagi used to
protect you, didn't he?
And this is how you repay him?
(dramatic music)
(whirring)
Kusanagi!
Ahhh!
Be gone!
Kusanagi!
The time has come for you
to die! (both yelling)
(shouting) Leave him alone!
Aaah!
An insignificant
little bug like you
can't destroy Lord
Susano-Oh's plan!
(laughing maniacally)
(screaming) Kusanagi!
Katy!
(gunshot)
I've got to fly faster!
I must fly faster!
(yelling) Katy!
(whirring)
Why won't you die?
Imperfect soul!
Kusanagi!
Kushinada?
Get back, Momiji!
Kusanagi!
I'm the only one that
can protect a Kushinada.
Kusanagi!
(groaning)
(screaming) Kusanagi!
(rustling)
(dramatic music)
(crashing)
(dramatic music continues)
- [Soldier] Sir, the light!
It's coming from the
construction site
where Katy disappeared!
Oh my god, the light!
The light!
Nooo!
(sobbing)
At long last, it has begun.
Katy is no longer in this place.
Go back!
Go back to Tokyo!
(splashing)
Kusanagi.
Kusanagi!
(sobbing)
Kusanagi, why?
What's happened to you?
I keep calling your
name in my mind
over and over again.
But, I can't see
your face anymore.
I can't hear your
response at all!
If you die, Kusanagi,
I don't know what I'll do.
It's the next
episode of Blue Seed,
number 22.
Sadness,
fate,
Momiji Kushinada.
I'm sacrificing
my future for you.
(instrumental music)
(singing in Japanese)