(thunder crashing)
- [Radio] All units, all
units, West and Main.
What's going on?
I don't know.
- [Man] Does anyone
know what's going on?
- [Woman] Are those real guns?
(sirens blaring)
Move it, move it, come on!
(tires squealing)
Oh, terrific.
Here comes Kunikida
from the TAC.
Going to fight your monsters?
- [Kunikida] They're
Aragami, not monsters.
If the order hadn't
come down to cooperate,
I'd've had you
hauled out of here.
I work with human
beings, real crime,
not all this mumbo jumbo.
That's right, and
you're not supposed to
smoke on duty, either.
What?
(grumbling)
Kaede, can you hear me?
Kaede, please come back.
Kaede!
Matsudaira.
Mr. Kunikida.
Status?
I'm sorry, but I...
Apologies can wait.
I need information.
All right, she's in there.
- [Kunikida] How'd
she get down there?
I looked away for just a second.
Miss Takeuchi's gone
in after her, but...
She what?
Give me that!
Kaede, please, come in!
Can you hear me?
Come back now!
Don't be a fool!
- [Matsudaira] I've been
transmitting again and again,
but there's so
much interference.
Dammit!
Haven't you realized that
the fate of the entire world
depends on what
happens to that girl?
(ominous music)
I, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I snapped.
She is my daughter.
Why, why does it
have to be Kaede?
It's not fair!
- [Takeuchi] Kaede, no!
Please don't do this, Kaede!
Kaede, please, please come back!
- [Kaede] It's calling me!
Calling me!
- [Takeuchi] Kaede!
Please come back with me.
Everybody loves you.
- [Kaede] I'm sorry.
Kaede.
Kaede!
(screaming)
I'm sorry, but I, I have
to find out the truth.
The secret of my destiny.
But you can't go now!
I must.
My future calls.
But if something happens to me...
- [Kunikida] No!
Something goes wrong.
You can't!
There is another Kushinada.
Guard her carefully.
What?
(gasping)
The other one, of course.
(wind howling)
Can you hear me?
Takeuchi!
(gasping)
What, what's that?
Come on, it's too late!
(eerie music)
(growling)
I'm too late.
(shouting)
- [Narrator] Surprisingly
little mention
was made of the incident.
The papers ran a cover
story, explaining how
a buildup of gas in
the construction site
had been responsible for
the spectacular explosion.
(energetic rock music)
(singing in foreign language)
(eerie music)
This is Izumo, a region famous
as the birthplace of
many Japanese myths.
A month has passed
since the occurrence
in the Tokyo construction site.
But it is in this
remote location
that our story really begins.
(gasping)
- [Old Woman] Momiji, Momiji!
Huh, Grandma?
- [Grandma] Don't
let your mind wander.
You haven't finished
the ritual yet.
I feel as though
something's not quite right.
It's strange.
I sense it.
(haunting music)
- [Grandma] It's your blood.
Your destiny is calling.
(wind howling)
(tires squealing)
(laughing)
They look like they don't
have a care in the world.
Kunikida, about Kaede.
I know you raised her as if
she was your real daughter.
I'm sorry.
I'd rather not talk about
that subject right now.
Our number one priority is to
protect the other Kushinada.
I understand.
I feel so helpless.
- [Kunikida] All right then!
Can you update me on the status
of our replacement staff?
Of course, sir.
Actually, our latest recruit
is scheduled to report in today.
I see.
Terrestrial
Administration Center.
Hmm.
Oops, now that's a lousy omen.
(chuckling)
Hey, you!
Okay, this goes over here, uh.
Uh, yes, ma'am?
How may I help you?
Yeah, I'm looking for
someone named Kunikida?
Man, what a dump.
What am I doing here?
Uh, I'm sorry.
Oh, are you Miss Kome...
Kome Sawaguchi,
transferring to the TAC
from the National Defense
Agency, as ordered, ma'am.
Say, just what's
going on here anyway?
(shouting)
- [Matsudaira] Oh, are
you all right, miss?
I don't like it.
Bye!
I'm going now, Grandma!
(gentle music)
I can't believe I
felt so worried.
It's a perfect day.
Then again, let's face it.
Climbing up a mountain
and purifying yourself
in a cold dark
cave would probably
give anybody a
case of the creeps.
Listen, Momiji.
Of course, Grandma.
But I already know what
you're gonna say next.
(clearing throat)
Listen, Momiji, your life
really doesn't belong to you.
It belongs to all
the people of Japan.
(giggling)
Don't be tempted by
frivolous things.
Some day there may come a
time where you may have to
sacrifice everything for
the sake of the people.
Right?
- [Grandma] (chuckling)
Yes, that's what I'd say.
I wonder what that means?
Why does she say that?
(gasping)
Oh, I'm late, nuts!
(panting)
(gasping)
Excuse me?
- [Man] You.
You're the daughter of
the Kushinada family.
- [Momiji] Kushinada?
My name's Momiji Fujimiya.
You're one of two twins born to
the Kushinada 15 years ago.
Now I'm very sorry about
this, but I have to kill you.
(gasping)
You know, your twin
sister is already dead.
Sister?
And now it's your turn.
But why?
Why me?
(cawing)
No, stop!
Damn you!
How long have you been
following me this time?
(growling)
(screaming)
Back off.
You're too late this time!
If I kill her now, the Aragami
will be banished
back to oblivion!
I'll slit your precious
Kushinada's throat
and freedom shall be mine.
What's wrong?
No powers in the daylight?
- [Creature] Kushinada.
(growling)
(gun firing)
(groaning)
Are you an Aragami?
And if I'm not?
That makes you a murderer.
TAC, I admire your work.
Later!
What?
All right, follow him!
I'm on it!
Thank God you're all right.
Can you stand?
- [Momiji] Yes.
Thank you.
Well now, so you're
Momiji Fujimiya.
How did you know my name?
I think you'd better
skip school today.
I'll take you home, okay?
School!
Oh, I'll miss the bus!
I, I'm really sorry,
but I gotta go!
Momiji, wait!
- [Momiji] Thank
you for saving me!
Ah, the bus, wait for me!
- [Bus Driver] It's
the last time I'm
stopping for you, miss!
(haunting music)
I understand.
Kaede is.
I'm so horribly sorry.
I thought that adopting
Kaede would be best.
But somehow, the
Aragami found her,
and now they found
Momiji as well.
- [Grandma] I see.
I'm so sorry.
- [Girl] Hey, Momiji,
just what is your problem?
- [Momiji] Huh, what?
- [Girl] Don't "huh, what" me.
You were late for class,
and you've been
acting like a zombie.
Wake up!
Hey, that's cold!
Well, it woke you up, didn't it?
Why'd you do that, Akiko?
Because you weren't
listening to a word I said.
So like, what's your problem?
You weren't out late
with some guy, were you?
No!
Some really weird things
have been happening.
I have to kill you.
I'll die to
sacrifice everything?
Grandma, is this what
you're talking about?
Huh?
I don't have a twin sister,
and I don't even know
what a Kushinada is!
Boy, are you running
a fever or what?
Is there any way I can help?
Akiko, what's a Kushinada?
You're kidding, right?
You've lived in
Izumo for 15 years,
and you really don't know?
Are you incredibly
dense, or just stupid?
- [Creature] Kushinada.
(growling)
(tapping)
Yes?
Huh?
(screaming)
Since the time before legends,
the Aragami have always
been a threat to mankind.
It's been over 100 years
since my family's blood
last put them to rest.
Foolishly, I believed they
would sleep on forever.
I never suspected that they
had reawakened 15 years ago.
The time of the
Kushinadas has passed.
There is nothing
left that we can do.
We have all failed.
No, my lady.
As long as Momiji is
alive, hope still remains.
Please, let the TAC take
Momiji into protective custody.
Hmm.
I'm sorry.
He got away.
I see.
Takeuchi, we've got
to protect Momiji.
I want you to contact
her school immediately.
The time has come!
My lady, we have no choice!
Sir?
I called the school three times,
but I couldn't get through.
Nobody is answering the phone.
What?
(phone ringing)
(eerie music)
Right, let's go.
Yes, sir!
Wait, please!
Take me with you, I beg you.
Moe!
I can't.
Please!
- [Sawaguchi] Hey, Yaegashi,
what's the big deal
shoving me on this helicopter?
When we get an order,
we don't ask questions.
You jerk!
Do you know we took off
without any weapons?
Not at all, we're
quite well-armed.
I've got the ultimate
anti-Aragami weapon
right here in my lap.
The ultimate
anti-Aragami weapon?
Yes sir, we got it
ready just in time.
It's TI plasmids in a
concentrated vector.
Right, but keep
in mind that it's
never been field-tested before.
I'm sure it will.
We must stop the Aragami.
No, that won't happen.
We mustn't forget what
happened to Kaede.
I've already cleared things
with the Self-Defense Agency.
Don't be late!
Once, long ago, an old husband,
his wife, and eight
daughters lived together
beside the stream
of Hi in Izumo.
However, every year, a
monster with one body,
eight heads, and flame-red
eyes, the Orochi-no-Orochi,
would come to eat
one of the daughters.
At last, there was
only one daughter left,
and the old parents
were reduced to tears.
Then, one day, the
outcast god Susano-o
appeared before the old couple.
Susano-o made the
Orochi-no-Orochi drunk
by feeding it sake,
then slew the monster
in a terrible battle.
The last daughter, who had
almost become a victim,
instead married Susano-o.
She became the
Princess Kushinada.
(sighing)
Oh, this doesn't make any sense!
This stuff is driving me crazy?
(laughing nervously)
Just what does this Kushinada
stuff have to do with me?
- [Creature] Kushinada.
(gasping)
What was that?
This whole Kushinada thing
is just getting too...
(growling)
(screaming)
- [Creature] Kushinada!
(suspenseful music)
Kushinada!
We've got to get
there right now!
If we lose Momiji,
the consequences
will be catastrophic!
This is it.
If we fail again, the
human race is doomed.
Momiji.
(engine revving)
(breathing heavily)
(groaning)
(screaming)
I must.
I must!
I must get Momiji!
(screaming)
Help me!
- [Matsudaira] There's
no way we can make it
to Izumo in time.
- [Creature] Kushinada!
(gasping)
We're too late.
- [Narrator] The huge monster
which suddenly appeared
in Izumo has been identified
as an Aragami by the TAC.
Now, the birthplace of
legends has given birth
to something far more deadly.
In the stream of human history,
one tiny eddy has swollen
into a vast, yawning vortex
that threatens to
engulf all mankind.
The future of our planet
is about to be decided.
(roaring)
- [Momiji] No, wait, I
still don't understand!
Who is the Kushinada?
And what's this business
about me being twins?
I'm just a normal girl,
why is everyone after me?
I'm in great danger now,
and I don't even know why!
I'm just a high school student.
I haven't even had a boyfriend!
What's happening now is more
than crazy, it's impossible.
Oh, but it's happening
to me anyway!
Don't miss the next
episode of "Blue Seed."
"It's Cruel! It's
Mysterious! It's My Destiny!"
(mellow music)
(singing in foreign language)