Um...
Er... why are you sitting next to me?
If you want to know your companion,
it's most effective to sit beside them.
That's Dating 101.
See? And now you know!
Now you won't commit the boorish blunder
of sitting across from your date.
Whoa--way too close!
Please, back off a little!
I want you.
Huh?!
In between the Zepharos Empire to the north
and the Chevron Kingdom to the south,
lies Lautreamont Knight Country.
Known as "the Dragon-Rearing Land,"
it boasts the largest dragon
population on the Arc Strada continent.
This small country with
fewer than five million citizens
is home to a unique school:
Ansullivan Dragonar Academy.
It aims to educate
and guide dragon masters
and the so-called Breeders,
young men and women
who have entered
into bonds with dragons.
Meeting you smack
in the middle of the world
It leaves me breathless
The "something" you and I have
Starts with a tiny thrum
Now teach me about
the sky one more time
"Dragonar Academy"
The weight of flapping
wings that only a bird knows
Everyone longs for it,
though they know nothing about it
You smiled with
a slightly sorrowful look
I... I have nothing
But if your tears can be fewer
And you'll smile like you mean it
Then I can be a hero--any kind you need
I'll embody any kind of hero for you
I'll never, never,
never, never let go
Even if I die,
I'll be your knight alone
But you cried for
real and got angry:
Saying "Don't be so cold to me"
I wipe your tears
Even without a sacred blade
I don't care if I'm not a hero
If I can protect you with all I have
Yes, you--here in the student
council room. I must ask:
Ash Blake.
Y-Yeah?
Don't you want to
be on the student council?
Huh?
"Riot in the Streets"
How's it taste, Lancelot?
Oh, Lancelot. I became a Dragonar
all because you grew into a Maestro.
Next I'll be an Archdragonar.
I promised him I would.
That I'd be a fine, upstanding knight...
But still...
...what is with that joker Ash Blake?
Being able to ride others' parrs
like that is beyond common sense.
He must have something up his sleeve...
Watch out!
Dragon on the loose!
Y-Your Highness! A young Strada just up and--
M-Me? On the student council?
That's right.
But...
About that sketchy pair
you ran across in the woods...
Just supposing
they were Imperial spies,
there is a non-zero chance
that the Academy is in their sights.
Ever since the war fifty-two
years ago, the Zepharos Empire
has mistaken Ansullivan Dragonar
Academy for a military school.
But it's not.
Exactly.
And as long as Rebecca Randall
and Cu Chulainn are around,
they won't get away with it, either!
Which is why I'd like your help,
as a student council member.
B-But I--
Think it over, won't you?
What's that?!
A Level 2 alert?
Now calm down!
Behave yours--
What?! Why would the
princess do something so rash?
Probably out of a rivalry with you.
Huh?
Her Highness is a perfectionist
and an extremely sore loser.
She wouldn't have blithely
accepted having a classmate
who can expertly ride
any dragon you throw at him.
No need to worry.
Rebecca!
Heed my call...
Cu Chulainn!
Rebecca Randall commands thee:
Present the Arch thou hath created unto me!
So that's Arch!
Mmm, scrumptious!
All that commotion--
Everything worked out
in the end, thanks to Rebecca.
But the princess? My rival?
Ow! Ow ow ow!
You've got a lot of nerve
to ignore me like that!
S-Sorry! I was just thinking...
I said, what's with all
those people gathered there?
Those are tourists,
come to see the statue of St. Durham.
St. Durham?
First-generation paladin
Durham Lautreamont.
This was some
five hundred years ago now.
That armor... it's Arch, right?
You can tell?
The Draguarth includes
some Arch design sketches.
Huh...
Although the sketches
our ancestors left behind
are really just for reference.
So will you make me
an original Arch one day, too?
I guess you'll have
to become a Maestro first, huh.
How dare you?! Why should
I have to make an Arch for my dog?
It's against the laws of nature!
Sheesh, where did that come from?
That's right--we learned about it in class.
For dragonkind,
presenting an Arch to their master
is part of giving
up their entire selves--
Ow!
It can't be! Is he the same...
How am I going
to tell Master Milgauss?
Well, well!
We meet again, I see,
and in such a lovely setting!
The Dragonfang Inn is
second to none in taste and volume.
Plus, student council
members can eat here for half off.
Go on--eat up!
But why are you two here?
That date ticket
from the Dragonar Festival.
Her Highness must fulfill
her obligations as the winner, too.
She seems to have
a lot on her mind lately.
I wanted her to open
up and talk to me today, but...
well, you see how she is.
Ow ow ow!
Anya?
Anya!
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
How are things in town?
Carefree. They've all
but forgotten about the war.
Of course. No one here
uses dragons as weapons.
Ansullivan is a very kind town.
But its kindness is without meaning.
Now: Deep One.
A darkness and light more
irresistible than death's abyss.
Its blood, its flesh...
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
Come forth, promised
child of magica-technica!
What is it?
Nothing good!
"Dragonar Academy"
Hurry--run!
Wh-What is that?!
A... a dragon?
Its flesh--it's rotten!
Eco!
Hold it, you oaf!
Just who do you think I am?!
This town is full of fantastic
boutiques, you know!
What on earth is she doing?
So be a good boy
and back off, wouldja?
Eco!
Watch where you're grabbing!
Why, you...
That is enough !
Dammit! What do we do?
Rebecca!
Manifest now...
O ye sure-striking mystic spear...
Its name...
...Gae Bulg!
Get him!
Yes!
It's growing back?
What is this thing?!
Ash! Take the princess
and get out of here! Hurry!
Princess!
Snap out of it, Princess!
Geez! What's with this thing, anyway?
Eco...
It's not done with her yet!
Princess!
Hmph! Some princess you are!
This is no time to question
your capacity as a royal!
Here, I'll apologize in advance:
Sorry!
Ash...?
I need to ask you a favor!
Summon Lancelot and let me ride him!
Ride him? Where?
Over there!
I can ride any dragon--
I might be able to hold him off!
What ? Are you crazy?!
C'mon, just call Lancelot already!
Eco!
Eco !
Get on! You might still have a chance!
H-Hey!
Don't be touching me there!
Do you know who I am ?
I'm of the proud dragon race, and--
Hey!
That's enough!
Hello, Eco. This is the
Highdragon Workshop,
and I am Navi.
Navi?
Someone to teach and guide
you while you're still immature...
Yes, that sounds about right.
Why... do you look like that?
Listen. If this keeps up, he will die.
Are you all right with that?
Ash!
True, he has a natural
talent for riding any dragon at all.
But he needs more. The way he is now,
he can't win against a Necromancia.
Necromancia?
A dead dragon,
resurrected by artificial means.
When you say he needs more...
His Arch?
Bingo.
This Highdragon Workshop
was built by the sacred Maestro,
a shared space for craftworking dragons.
The Arch is one of
the things Maestro produce.
But an Arch is a made-to-order set of armor.
A mere copy would fit poorly,
perhaps even endangering
the life of the one who wears it.
So what do I do?
Simple: Pick and
choose the best-fitting parts
from among the many sketches here
and put them all together.
I have his size data right here.
Where did all this come from?
I fiddled around a bit in
his dreams before you were born.
Don't mess with my dog, you hear me?
So what will you do?
Are you put off by the
sheer number of sketches?
Is the idea of selecting
each part so daunting
that you'll give up
before you even begin?
That smirk of yours really ticks me off!
Of course!
Of course I'll do it!
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah... Sorry.
Lancelot's reached his limits...
...and you won't hold
out much longer yourself.
I know!
But... I know .
The astral flow is telling me,
through my starbrand.
Eco's still alive!
As long as this is glowing,
I'll never give up.
So you better hang in there, too, Eco!
I'll save you--don't give up!
Hmph... pretty full
of himself for a pet dog...
The mana is increasing...
The bond between Breeder and parr--
no, between Ash and Eco...
I see it!
Almete , gorjal , peto ,
espaldar , brafonera , falda !
Bujeta , hombrera , brazal ,
guarda , greba , escarpe !
Espolazo !
Ash!
What a waste, giving this to a dog...
Huh?
Take it!
B-But this...
It's Arch!
How awe-inspiring...
I-It's not like I made
it just for you or anything!
It's not an original--it's just
some makeshift armor!
I didn't, like, present it to you!
Thanks, Eco.
With this... I feel like I can't lose!
Princess!
Understood!
Lancelot sure is a good dragon.
What?
You've got the best parr.
Don't be trying anything
crazy like riding other dragons.
Wh-What are you talking about?
And why now ?!
Ash...
You may be deity or devil,
but as long as you're
a dragon, I will ride you!
Master Milgauss...
Quite the unexpected ambush.
The experiment has ended
in failure. But not for nothing:
We have that boy... and that girl.
The girl?
Let us retreat.
Necromancia? Is that you?
Ah, so you had a master once, too.
Are you... sure about that?
All right. Leave it to me.
Manifest now...
O ye light-graced sword...
Grant unto me the
power to purge all darkness.
Its name, the divine blade, Aix-les-Bains!
Eco!
Ash!
Congrats once again on getting your parr!
Thanks, Raymond.
This has made me painfully aware
of the student council's shortcomings.
Ash, Silvia.
Again, I urge you two
to join the student council.
If Lancelot and I would
be of any use, I'll join.
We mustn't let an attack
like that happen ever again.
And you, Ash?
I...
All right. I'll do it.
Then let's bring this little
joining ceremony to a close.
Hey! How dare my pet go all
googly-eyed over a human female!
Er, Miss President...?
That's not how my joining ceremony--
And to celebrate our new
additions to the student council...
Cheers!
I-I can't reach...
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Joy! Joy! Joy! First-class, right? Bomb!
Bomb! Bon! Cute! Bon! Bon! Bonsoir?
Gimme a supernova named love
Joy! Joy! Joy! So cliché
Dabba dabba poppi poppu--do
some scat then I'm outtie
Bomb! Bomb! Just more carnal desires?
Showing the chink in your manly façade--how
much girly cherishing can you do?
Can't you feel?
Gotta say it in your own words--
"Hear, hear!" "Here?" "Where?"
"How are you still a Homo sapiens?"
Drum up a lovestorm (One chance) An
avant-garde rhapsody (Oh, one more chance)
Compete, compete, compete!
Refresh my love--the mostest more than most!
Natural-born dreamer (Wonder)
Don't want it to fizzle out (Oh, falling down)
Not coming? Then I'll pull ya!
"That's premeditated crime!" (Big love)
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Yes! Rockin' on!
"Next Time..."
Hi, Ash Blake. You look
like a real masochist--am I right?
Wh-Where did you hear that?
Whereas I am a really
real sadist. And a real masochist.
Wow, uh, thanks for sharing!
"Next Episode: Iron Blood Valkyrie"
And so...
Yes?