What a foolish boy indeed,
putting his own life in danger
so that the girl's wish could come true.
And yet...
Ash Blake.
You deserve better than being left to die.
Let us take a chance
on the possibilities you hold.
Meeting you smack
in the middle of the world
It leaves me breathless
The "something" you and I have
Starts with a tiny thrum
Now teach me about
the sky one more time
"Dragonar Academy"
The weight of flapping
wings that only a bird knows
Everyone longs for it,
though they know nothing about it
You smiled with
a slightly sorrowful look
I... I have nothing
But if your tears can be fewer
And you'll smile like you mean it
Then I can be a hero--any kind you need
I'll embody any kind of hero for you
I'll never, never,
never, never let go
Even if I die,
I'll be your knight alone
But you cried for
real and got angry:
Saying "Don't be so cold to me"
I wipe your tears
Even without a sacred blade
I don't care if I'm not a hero
If I can protect you
with all I have
Huh?
I-I can't move!
It's all right. Don't be afraid, Ash Blake.
I'll treat every last inch
of your body juuust right.
H-How do you know my name?
Who--Who are you?
Why are you...
I am Navi.
This is a kind of ceremony.
For the Navi who's about to be born.
To... entrust her to you.
What a dream!
"A Boy and His Dragon"
G'morning!
I hope we're in the same class again!
It's almost here--
the Aries Dragonar Festival.
I can't wait!
Will you be taking part, Jessica?
Maybe. I'm still thinking about it.
Hey, look.
That's Ash Blake!
The school's number-one problem child!
It's amazing he's made it to Senios
when his parr hasn't even been born yet.
You know what they say:
They take after their masters.
I bet his parr'll be a problem child, too.
Ah-ah-ah!
Raymond!
Can't you do something
about that short fuse of yours?
I'm not going to stand here
and let them mock my parr!
I see you haven't changed a bit.
Hey, Max.
Ash, we're Senios now.
Develop some self-restraint.
I... I know, but...
Anyway, I sure hope we've got
some cute girls in our class!
You said the same thing last year.
Talk about arrested development.
The new term has begun,
and everyone who's
completed the basic Unios course
will now spend the next three years
in the advanced Senios course.
It goes without saying
at this stage of the game,
but dragons are extremely special entities.
The starbrands you all bear?
Those mark you as Breeders,
and are a portal to the astral flow
linking you to your parr:
the partner dragon born from within you,
where it has been since the
Orphan's Rite that bound you to your role.
Thus no one but the master
with whom it shares lifeforce
can ride a parr.
There are exceptions.
Lautreamont Knight Country
gained its independence
when the Chevron Kingdom gave it the task
of dragon rearing and management.
But we remain in a cease-fire with
the Zepharos Empire to the north,
with its mechanical and magical engineering.
War, huh? May as well be
another world far, far away.
With that in mind, please conduct yourselves
with the pride and
responsibility befitting students
of Ansullivan Dragonar Academy.
Yes, ma'am!
Don't let it get to you, Ash.
Let what?
That stuff about exceptions.
I'm not.
Still, how come you're the only one
who can ride other people's parrs?
You're asking the wrong guy.
Out of my way!
Standing around
chit-chatting there, of all places?
Don't you realize how annoying that is?
Oh! S-Sorry about that!
Did you hear her?
So stuck-up!
Oh, boy...
Wasn't that Whozis?
She's in our class for the first time.
Yep...
Silvia Lautreamont.
The fourth princess of
Lautreamont Knight Country.
Her grades are superb, but with
her personality and noble rank,
people tend to give her a pretty wide berth.
So aren't you running in the race?
What race?
That race.
The Aries Dragonar Festival.
Not without a parr, no.
Sheesh, you're not still
worried about that left arm of yours!
If you ask me, that starbrand is kickin' rad!
Yes, I'm worried!
Miss President?
President Rebecca!
Here comes third-year class
president Rebecca Randall!
The Archdragonar who commands Cu Chulainn,
the mightiest Maestro in the whole academy!
That's not to mention her
gorgeous face and seductive body...
Just once I'd love to take her on...
...if you know what I mean.
Idiot.
Uh-oh--do you think she heard me?
Don't ask me!
You traitor!
Now let's start our Dragonar battle training.
These weaponless techniques are
the basis for all Dragonar battle skills.
Thanks, Raymond.
Don't sweat it.
Good girl, Brigid.
Again, be very careful when touching a dragon
that's not your practice partner.
Don't want to cause any major accidents.
Ready? Mount up!
Begin!
Whoa! Seeing so many
all move at once really is something!
Go, Lancelot!
That's the Ice Blue Princess
for you--such power! How's Ash?
Hey, this is fun!
Ah--something's clicked!
Go, Brigid!
That's the way!
A body slam, then a rear dodge,
then straight for the jugular!
Yes!
Ash! Behind you!
It's okay, Lancelot! Calm down!
I'm sorry, Brigid! So sorry!
Hang on! Stop right there!
What do you think you're doing, Ash Blake?
I told you to be careful touching
any dragon but your own partner!
I'm sorry.
Hmm. Neither seems to be badly hurt...
...but don't let this happen again, all right?
Yes, sir.
Sorry, Your Highness. It was my fa--
What do you think
skill practice is for, anyway?
All this horsing around
on dragons is out of the question!
I-I wasn't horsing around--
This only happened because
you were riding someone else's dragon!
Now just hang on!
He has his own reasons for--
That's right--you haven't been
graced with a parr yet, have you?
That'll be one bonehead dragon,
just like its master.
Or maybe it already died ages ago.
Hey.
Is that some kind of joke?
What did you just say?
Did I stutter?
I said, maybe your parr is already dead.
Ash!
Sorry--he flies off the handle
when someone makes fun of his parr.
That's why they call him a problem child.
You take that back!
What?
I'm not enough of a Mr. Nice Guy
to take that comment sitting down!
Then how's this?
If you can beat my standing at
the upcoming Aries Dragonar Festival,
I'll take back what
I said--and apologize to boot.
Sounds promising. I accept.
It's high time someone put you in your place.
"Dragonar Academy"
Not again...
Don't look so scared.
Night after night, you touch
the body of a man who can't move.
Where's the fun in that?
Oh, it's fun, all right.
Your reactions are so... innocent.
Why are you doing this?
I already told you.
It's to entrust myself to you.
The Navi who's about to be born.
I'm examining your body.
Examining it?
Would you like to examine mine?
If you can move your arms, that is.
Don't look so scared!
This is our last night together.
Let's enjoy it.
Our last--
And that's why I'll be checking
that most sensitive part of you,
measuring what I've saved
for last all these nights,
with my mouth.
H-hey, whoa--wait!
Navi...
Ash! You up?
Ash?
Yeah, I'm up! I'll be right there!
Good morning, all!
Such lovely weather we're having...
But let's dispense with the pleasantries.
The Aries Dragonar Festival
is no ordinary race.
I'm counting on you again, Brigid.
The results of this traditional Ansullivan event
become public record for posterity.
Enter, and you must aim
for the center of the winner's podium.
But maybe winning alone
isn't motivation enough.
So to the winner I shall present
a ticket for one day-long date
with me, Rebecca Randall!
Is she serious?!
Hey, Ash, give Brigid back! I'm in!
Now, now...
Silence!
Now a word from the
competitors' representative,
first-year Senios student
Her Highness the Princess Silvia Lautreamont.
"One must do one's utmost,
no matter the contest."
So goes my family motto.
That's all.
What was that? Ugh, creepy!
She's getting carried away
just because she's royalty.
Like brother, like sister.
Oh, yeah--Julius the dragonslayer.
Didn't he get thrown in prison
for breaking the biggest taboo?
Not so loud!
What a rotten atmosphere.
Dredging up something
from over a decade ago...
She's suffering more than you'd think.
On your mark!
Go get 'em, Ash!
Here they come!
Go for it!
You can win this!
Bringing up the rear was a bad way to start...
Lancelot's already flown far ahead.
Is that...
...the princess and Lancelot?!
Those girls...
Hey, what is all this?
Let me be.
Blocking and team play
aren't against the rules.
Oh, is that so?
What are you doing?!
Sorry! It's a borrowed
dragon--kinda hard to control.
Hey, aren't you Ash Blake?
The problem child?
Stay away from us!
Get back!
That problem-child
reputation can come in handy!
Don't expect me to thank you.
Fine by me.
C'mon, Brigid!
I'm sorry, Brigid.
I shouldn't try to make an Earthia like you
keep up with a Maestro.
So much for my match against the princess.
Wonder why I don't feel so bad about losing?
Maybe because I had fun
back there, racing with her.
Is someone there?
Could be a dropout.
Wait here--I'll go take a look.
That's weird.
What the--
It's a Zepharos airship.
They used them in the last war.
Is that one of the
empire's mechanical weapons?
Are you an Imperial soldier?
Is that what you think?
Young man, how old are you?
Sixteen... but what of it?
How odd. To have an immature
dragon in you at that age...
How do you--
I can see it.
Thanks to the curse I bear, that is.
Curse...?
Get away from Master Milgauss!
What's going on?
What did I do?!
Your luck ran out when you met us!
This is insane!
That's war for you!
But there's a cease-fire!
The Empire and the Kingdom
are still fighting behind the scenes!
She could've killed me--why did she hesitate?
Let's go, Anya.
Yes.
A-Am I just going to die like this?
Could this be... my parr?
It's human... Not a dragon?
Why a human?
Although my starbrand did react...
For the Navi who's about to be born.
To... entrust her to you.
It can't be... No, this isn't Navi.
It looks like her, but... no.
This girl...
...is she my parr?
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Joy! Joy! Joy! First-class, right? Bomb!
Bomb! Bon! Cute! Bon! Bon! Bonsoir?
Gimme a supernova named love
Joy! Joy! Joy! So cliché
Dabba dabba poppi poppu--do
some scat then I'm outtie
Bomb! Bomb! Just more carnal desires?
Showing the chink in your manly façade--how
much girly cherishing can you do?
Can't you feel?
Gotta say it in your own words--
"Hear, hear!" "Here?" "Where?"
"How are you still a Homo sapiens?"
Drum up a lovestorm (One chance) An
avant-garde rhapsody (Oh, one more chance)
Compete, compete, compete!
Refresh my love--the mostest more than most!
Natural-born dreamer (Wonder)
Don't want it to fizzle out (Oh, falling down)
Not coming? Then I'll pull ya!
"That's premeditated crime!" (Big love)
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Yes! Rockin' on!
"Next Time..."
Hey, Ash, what's with that hottie?
How did that cute girl wind up as your parr?!
I have no idea! I was
hoping someone could tell me!
Lucky you, sharing a room
with a girl like that.
"Next Episode: Ties That Bind: The Astral Flow"
Such heart-throbbing, blood-pumping adventures await!
Yeah, if only.
"Next Episode: Ties That Bind: The Astral Flow"
What's that supposed to mean?