The princess is in high
dudgeon over your lack of ability.
She commands you
to visit St. Valeria tomorrow,
where you shall
offer prayers of repentance.
Intel indicates that this individual
may have infiltrated Ansullivan.
The former mountain guerilla terrorist:
Avdocha, She Who Condemns.
St. Valeria once said,
"Love the sinner, hate the sin."
Death to all sinners!
I am Avdocha, She Who Condemns!
Meeting you smack
in the middle of the world
It leaves me breathless
The "something" you and I have
Starts with a tiny thrum
Now teach me about
the sky one more time
"Dragonar Academy"
The weight of flapping
wings that only a bird knows
Everyone longs for it,
though they know nothing about it
You smiled with
a slightly sorrowful look
I... I have nothing
But if your tears can be fewer
And you'll smile like you mean it
Then I can be a hero--any kind you need
I'll embody any kind of hero for you
I'll never, never,
never, never let go
Even if I die,
I'll be your knight alone
But you cried for
real and got angry:
Saying "Don't be so cold to me"
I wipe your tears
Even without a sacred blade
I don't care if I'm not a hero
If I can protect you with all I have
"Blue Brionac"
What's with that smoke?
It's coming from St. Valeria!
No!
Princess, let us return to the Sylvanus .
Mmm.
Wait! Didn't you see that?
The princess might be in there!
Never fear.
We'll make the Magiship
Sylvanus our strategic HQ.
Transmission from
St. Valeria Church incoming.
Go ahead.
Long time no see,
Veronica Lautreamont.
I should have known you
were behind this,
Avdocha, She Who Condemns.
Huh? Could it be...
It's someone else entirely!
Why take over the church?
Are you after my head--again?
That's not all.
Look at this.
Jessica!
Is that...
An Imperial-made mechanical bomb.
If it goes off, this church'll be
blown to smithereens.
What's more,
I'm not what you'd
call a patient person.
Every time the church bell tolls,
I'm killing another hostage.
What?!
There's less than
an hour until the next bell.
I look forward to having your head.
Your Highness?
I refuse to give in to terrorists.
If it comes to it,
the Sylvanus 's guns can blow away
the whole church and everyone in it.
You wouldn't!
Don't get worked up, boy.
Stay vigilant!
Who knows what that woman will do?
Yes'm!
Jessica...
Wait.
Who knows what she'll
do to you if she finds out
you're Princess Veronica's sister.
But if I reveal who I am and
demand the hostages be released--
I know you want to help,
but not by sacrificing yourself.
Now hear this!
I am Jessica Valentine!
Despite all appearances,
I am well-known Lautreamont nobility!
Out of respect to my name,
swear you'll not lay a finger on
the remaining hostages!
Valentine, you say?
Never heard of 'em. But... very well.
And then...
...even as her clothes were torn from her,
even as they strung her up,
she never said a word...
and shed not a single tear.
Jessica...
You're a far higher-minded woman
than any noble in these parts.
And in return, I...
That's Avdocha, She Who Condemns.
If I tell her I'm a fellow Tantalos...
No, I'd better not.
I'll just let this play out for a while.
I just came looking for my friend.
What have I gotten myself into?
A firefight? Are you serious?
Calm down, Ash Blake!
Princess Veronica, I have an idea.
Yes? What is it?
I see. Interesting.
Avdocha!
Ash Blake,
we're sending you to
the church as a negotiator.
Whaaat?
Now hang on!
Why are you sending
him somewhere so dangerous?!
They have no idea
that Ash is capable of
Archdragonar-level might.
While he buys us time inside the church,
we Archdragonars will
use the underground passage
and break through the
church's foundation from below.
Oh, I get it!
What do you think, Ash?
Sounds like a plan.
Good. Now for a strategy meeting.
Hey, Eco...
What?
I have a favor to ask.
About the next Arch you make for me...
Huh? But I can't--
Sure, you can.
I know you can.
I'm counting on you.
This means triple the crepes.
Sure. But hold the anthar.
Halt!
I'm Ash Blake, sent here to negotiate.
I seek entry!
Ash!
They sent a brat like you to negotiate?
They must not think much of me.
The Sylvanus has its largest
gun aimed right at this church.
The princess will not yield to terrorists.
Silence!
You're not much of a negotiator, are you,
terrifying the hostages like that?
Enough pointless resistance.
You don't want to die for nothing.
The truth is...
I'm here looking for my long-lost sister.
I understand Veronica
has three sisters of her own.
She should know the sorrow
of being torn from her beloved siblings.
This isn't working.
There's no negotiating with her.
Eco, please! Hurry!
I'm working on it!
I'm working on it...
but it's not easy!
Just slap together
an original Arch already.
L-Like I'd bother for the likes of him!
He can ride any
dragon--very mysterious.
He should be riding you, too,
in your true form.
My true form?
While this human
form is indeed your reality,
you are of the dragon race,
and Ash Blake's parr.
It's high time you realized that.
Ugh! Be quiet! I can't work!
One day you'll see.
I have my hands full with this.
He asked me for an Arch
that can stop a mechanical bomb.
Ash Blake.
That's his name--I remember now.
Wh-What? You want to nurse?!
But there's nothing in there!
No! No squirming allowed!
What's that racket?
Very well. This one should
be good and hungry, too.
It's a bit early, but mother and child
shall be the first sacrifice.
No!
It can't be!
Wait!
What?! Are you crazy?
"Dragonar Academy"
Who's this?
I-I am...
I am the fourth princess of the
Lautreamont royal knight family,
Silvia Lautreamont!
Oh. Fourth princess, was it?
Out of respect to my name,
release these two at once!
What is she doing?
That fool.
So you must be Veronica's sister.
No! Don't touch her!
Silence!
If you're volunteering your name like that,
you must be ready for what comes next.
I-I am a princess! I can't just stand by
and watch my people be slaughtered!
I... I wish to die a knight's death.
That's the spirit!
Princess!
There's your true form.
By simply revealing your nudity,
you go back to being a woman.
Gone is the prestige
of your knightly name...
...along with any worth in killing you.
You disappoint me.
"One must do one's utmost,
no matter the contest."
So goes my family motto.
That's all.
Standing around
chit-chatting there, of all places?
Don't you realize how annoying that is?
Did you hear her?
She's getting carried
away just because she's royalty.
Like brother, like sister.
Sorry, Your Highness. It was my fa--
All this horsing around on
dragons is out of the question!
Now calm down!
Behave yours--
Such ineptitude you've put on display.
And you count yourself part
of the House of Lautreamont?
That's you in a nutshell:
You act pretentious, but really,
you're nothing but a little girl.
Never mind
your Dragonar ambition--
it's far more appropriate
for you to settle down!
I wasn't prepared.
If you don't like it, you'll have
to surpass Princess Veronica.
I expect my elder sister to
scold me, sure, but...
I'll carry you, and we can look
for the Mother Dragon together!
I made him a promise.
That I'd be a fine, upstanding knight...
I must thank you, Avdocha.
What?
You made me realize
how weak I am, how ill-prepared.
But the old me is gone.
She died when you cut her down.
And now...
...I am reborn as a
new Silvia Lautreamont!
This I declare:
I shall be that most
royal knight: a paladin!
Well said, Silvia!
We're under enemy attack!
O ye sure-striking mystic spear...
Its name: Gae Bulg!
O ye lightning-quick mystic brand...
Its name: Caladbolg!
Don't toy with me, brat!
Ash!
Sorry 'bout the wait.
Right on time!
Thanks, Eco!
I-I didn't do it for you!
Not so fast!
Stop right there!
Unless you want me
to push this detonator button!
Nice try!
Manifest now...
O ye sacred glacial carbine...
Its name: Brionac!
W-Wait! I--
Oh, my!
Guess those stories
are good for something.
The Heavenly Dragonar...
Sir Ash!
Huh?
We meet at last, Sir Silver Knight!
J-J-J-Jessica?!
Now to plant your seed in me...
K-K-Keep 'em on!
I decided that our first time
would be on the church altar.
Liar--you just came up with that now!
Off with your clothes, now, Sir Ash!
Are you even listening?
Cut that out.
Rebecca!
Off with you.
You all right?
Of all the times,
this is when my legs buckle. Pitiful.
Not at all.
You were amazing.
Th-That's preposterous!
C'mon.
Don't be shy.
Why is it?
Why do I feel a rush of nostalgia
when Ash is carrying me like this?
Underpants?
J-J-J-Jessica?!
I'm here to enter into the
Child-Bearing Covenant, Sir Ash!
H-How did you--
My preparations are complete!
But from the waist down, you're--
How about the rest?
That's not what I meant!
I thought you said our first time
would be on the altar.
I'm prepared to cast aside
my beliefs at a moment's notice
for you , Sir Ash!
Let's, uh, let's hang onto
that particular belief, shall we?
It's time, Ash. Plant your seed in me!
W-Wait! Stop!
Oh, Sir Ash... you're so hot...
and hard... and big ...
What shall we name our baby, hmm?
I knew it.
When you vanished from
the girls' dorm, I came right over.
What?
Jessica's joining the student council?!
Yes--because she learned
who the Silver Knight really is.
We had her quit
as president of the fan club
and had her join our group instead.
Call it leak prevention.
Let's hurry. Princess Veronica is waiting.
I am Avdocha, She Who Condemns!
Wh-What are you doing here?
It was all my elder sister's scheme.
A scheme?
To correct my unworthy sister.
Wait, so... you knew?
I wasn't at all sure, though.
As you know,
I was once part of
an antigovernment group,
where I failed in my task of
assassinating Veronica five years ago.
After that, I surrendered to her
and began working as her agent.
That's the shape of it.
Talk about eating humble pie...
B-But you look completely
different on your wanted poster.
One of my people made
that based on complete hearsay.
The timing was right, so I let it be.
But why would you
work for Princess Veronica?
To find my long-lost sister.
Her name is Shamara,
and she's turning fifteen this year.
So the part about your sister was true.
I can't give up the ghost until I find her.
We got to hear
this little tidbit, thanks to you:
I shall be that most
royal knight: a paladin!
--I shall be that most royal knight: a paladin!
--S-Stop that!
Ash?
Do you know where the
Magiship Sylvanus gets its name?
Where?
Don't the names sound similar?
Sylvanus and Silvia?
Huh!
Veronica! Enough already!
That takes some
real sisterly love, doesn't it?
Please, stop laughing and answer me!
During that incident, Princess Veronica
mobilized a detached force
and rounded up a bunch
of Avdocha-inspired agitators.
All that payoff from a single action...
I still have so far to go.
I think you'll be fine.
Huh?
Well, see...
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Joy! Joy! Joy! First-class, right? Bomb!
Bomb! Bon! Cute! Bon! Bon! Bonsoir?
Gimme a supernova named love
Joy! Joy! Joy! So cliché
Dabba dabba poppi poppu--do
some scat then I'm outtie
Bomb! Bomb! Just more carnal desires?
Showing the chink in your manly façade--how
much girly cherishing can you do?
Can't you feel?
Gotta say it in your own words--
"Hear, hear!" "Here?" "Where?"
"How are you still a Homo sapiens?"
Drum up a lovestorm (One chance) An
avant-garde rhapsody (Oh, one more chance)
Compete, compete, compete!
Refresh my love--the mostest more than most!
Natural-born dreamer (Wonder)
Don't want it to fizzle out (Oh, falling down)
Not coming? Then I'll pull ya!
"That's premeditated crime!" (Big love)
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Yes! Rockin' on!
"Next Time..."
Sir Ash! Sir Ash! Sir Silver Knight!
Stop it, Jessica! That's a top-secret agreement!
Whatever do you mean?
We have no secrets between us!
Are we talking about the same thing?
Now, then--let's get that seed planted!
"Next Episode: Lucca Saarinen"
"Next Time..."
Uh, see you next week!
To make babies?
"Next Time..."
No !