You've made it through
five days of intense training!
Be proud of yourselves--
you are mighty indeed!
And as a small gesture in recognition
of both your growth and the end of camp,
I would like to welcome
you all to our wrap party.
Now go on--enjoy yourselves!
--Cheers!
Are you all right, Ash?
Yeah, I'm fine. That healing
magic really did the trick.
I bet they saw right through that one.
Still...
Gawain--he's--
Gawain is gone?
But where could he be?
I don't know...
With our astral flow interrupted...
The Willingham Mausoleum.
Have you heard the fairy tale
about the Willingham Mausoleum?
Well, I... I've heard of it...
It's about the young Maestro Nuada
and his young master girl.
Pained at seeing his master
suffering from a grave illness,
Nuada closed off their
astral flow and vanished.
He didn't want her to
see him waste away and perish.
At long last, the girl recovered.
But only after Nuada
had quietly breathed his last
inside the Willingham Mausoleum... alone.
You don't think Gawain's
planning to pull a Nuada?
It's possible.
The mausoleum is a
resting place for young dragons...
...and Gawain is still a juvenile...
All right. We call off the wrap
party and organize a search party.
If we all scour the area
around Willingham Mausoleum...
Wait.
The camp was pretty grueling, right?
Everyone's been
looking forward to this party.
Okay. Just the student
council members, then.
No, that won't work, either.
If the whole student
council goes missing,
everyone'll know something's up.
So much for the celebration.
Then...
It's all right.
I'll handle this.
And you can bet I'll find you, too,
Gawain!
Hmph. The princess approaches.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
Come forth, promised
child of magica-technica!
Meeting you smack
in the middle of the world
It leaves me breathless
The "something" you and I have
Starts with a tiny thrum
Now teach me about
the sky one more time
"Dragonar Academy"
The weight of flapping
wings that only a bird knows
Everyone longs for it,
though they know nothing about it
You smiled with
a slightly sorrowful look
I... I have nothing
But if your tears can be fewer
And you'll smile like you mean it
Then I can be a hero--any kind you need
I'll embody any kind of hero for you
I'll never, never,
never, never let go
Even if I die,
I'll be your knight alone
But you cried for
real and got angry:
Saying "Don't be so cold to me"
I wipe your tears
Even without a sacred blade
I don't care if I'm not a hero
If I can protect you
with all I have
"Dragon Dance"
So Gawain's in there?
Hard to say. But we've received intel
that Professor Angela is holed up inside.
What's she doing here?
Wh-What the--
Look!
It's just like before--this
sense of foreboding...
I'm sure of it!
Look at that!
What are they?
They're in the lake, too!
And in the forest!
That's...
Stop!
This is highly indecent!
Nooo!
Princess!
Princess! Are you all right?
Yeah...
What about me, Ash?
I was pretty scared, you know!
Necromancia--at
the training camp!
All we can do is
trust the camp director.
Saddle up.
We're storming the mausoleum!
Troops, in formation!
Time to show off
the fruit of your training!
Here we go.
Commence counterattack!
They just keep coming--no end in sight!
Eco?
Bring out my Arch.
I can't help anyone like this.
What are you, stupid?
Even a fake suit of
Arch would put too much strain
on someone as wounded as you!
You're just going
to have to grin and bear it!
Couldn't you make me
something more lightweight?
Whaaat?
I bet you can make me
exactly the Arch I need now.
Why are you so confident?
Isn't it obvious? I have you for a parr.
Oh, all right.
But while I'm at the Workshop,
my spirit will be far from my body...
I know. I'll keep your body safe.
How's this?
M-Make sure you
hold me up properly, or else...
Gawain...
What is it, Lancelot?
We meet again, boy.
Milgauss!
Now hear this, Milgauss!
In the name of the
knight family of Lautreamont,
I shall rain down
divine retribution upon you!
What's so funny?!
To think: It wasn't one
of the greatest warriors alive,
Veronica Lautreamont,
but you , so cowardly and needy,
who made a pact with
a dragon in the Orphan's Rite.
What...?
My, how you've grown... Silvie.
Hey! There you are!
C'mon, big bro! Why are
you always talking with Glen?
You mean in that knightly family...
...is one who would
commit the greatest taboo?
Killing a dragon...
the Dragonslayer...
Prince Julius!
Lancelot has a
lot of fight in him, I see.
Or are you using some kind of
esoteric trick again, boy?
What?!
Though the Imperial Princess
of Avalon can't do much in that state.
Avalon...
What do you know about that?!
This Necromancia
here is no mere juvenile.
He lived as a Maestro.
You Knight Country people
are familiar with it, I believe?
The sad tale of the dragon who
loved his master so much, he chose death?
That's right... his name was Nuada:
the sacred dragon of Willingham!
"Dragonar Academy"
I see. You want to make some Arch,
but you don't have time,
so you want to sample my work...
...and remix it.
Yep. Much as I hate to admit it,
you do seem to know more than me.
Sure. You and I are
two sides of the same coin.
I don't mind helping. However...
You must promise me one thing.
What?
That one day,
you'll present the finest original Arch
to Ash Blake.
Wha--
Y-You mean...
Yes: for dragonkind, it's like saying,
"I offer myself to you, body and soul."
B-B-B-But I--
You can't?
Fine. I promise.
Almete, gorjal, peto,
espaldar, brafonera, falda...
What is it?
He's got himself into
a pretty sticky situation.
Can you hurry it up?
I suppose I'd better.
Why, you...
Let me go! N-No--stop!
S-Stop that...
No, don't! N-Not there!
What are you doing?!
I am of the house of Valentine! I--
No! Stop that! Not even Sir Ash has--
Thanks for that, Rhiannon!
They're not letting up.
We've got to break through somehow...
There's more ?
Princess!
Stay your hand!
I shall pacify Nuada's spirit!
No! Don't touch me there!
No--stop--
Nooo!
Lucca!
Eco!
Eco...
Ecooo !
Wh-What the--?!
What's going on here?
Eco!
Honestly! Whatever
would you do without me?
Espolazo!
Is this... Arch light?
That's the daughter of Avalon for you.
Are you sure you
don't want to take on Nuada?
The princess said to stay out of it.
Calm thyself, Nuada!
So you're not the real thing after all.
Ash!
That Arch is made for defense,
so lay off the kicking and punching!
Hurry up and make with the magic!
Got it!
Manifest now...
O ye impregnable shield...
Its name: Aegis!
Go!
Petrification magic!
I was sure that had been
outlawed in Knight Country...
Well? Come on, then, boy!
Then I guess I'll have to come to you!
Milgauss!
Ash Blake!
Stop right there!
Nuada's spirit
has returned to the heavens!
Accept your fate!
Surprised?
The left one was false all along.
It seems I must revise
my opinion of the fourth princess...
Wait!
Look at them all...
Lancelot!
Dammit...
We're in no position
to go help them, either.
Lucca?
Lancelot and Silvia...
...and you and Eco--
you all fought so hard.
Who alone among us didn't?
Ash!
Lucca?!
You risked your life
for me and for Gawain.
When I'm with you,
I feel like I can give it my all.
I want to help them.
No--I will help them.
You can do it. I'm with you.
I'm sorry, Gawain...
I won't be afraid of you anymore.
So please... take me back, Gawain!
Here, Gawain, have some.
Tap into my astral flow.
Drink me in...
After all...
...you're...
...you're my parr!
Caring for the injured
is our top priority!
We need tight coordination--don't
rush out into the fray!
There are just too many of them.
I think we might be done for...
Wh-What's that?!
Not another Necromancia!
No, not this one.
That's--
Lucca!
Grab on tight so you won't get flung off.
He's so fast!
You can do it, Lucca. I'm with you.
Dragon Dance, First Movement:
Cleansing Amrita!
The Necromancia! They're--
They're fading away!
Lucca...
Lucca!
You finally pulled it off, Lucca.
Since ancient times,
the Ecbladian Dragonars
have been known as "elfin dancers"...
...and now Lucca's shown us why.
I see.
But now we know the
extent of their military power.
With this single incident,
we alone have the technique
for calling Necromancia back.
So it's not a total loss, then.
I shall crush them both--
Lautreamont Knight Country
and the Chevron Kingdom.
My ambition demands it.
Just wait until the Continental Congress.
Cheers!
Congrats on leaving the hospital, Ash!
Thanks!
All student council
members are safe and sound,
and Professor Angela was
found in the mausoleum, unhurt.
So all's well that ends well.
Express delivery!
First-rank postal
courier Orletta Blanc here!
I bring a missive for Her Highness
Princess Silvia from the Paladin!
From Father? For me?
What's it say?
He wants me to attend Elysion,
the Continental Congress.
He does?
And... he'd like to meet you and Eco.
I'm to bring you with me.
You are?
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Joy! Joy! Joy! First-class, right? Bomb!
Bomb! Bon! Cute! Bon! Bon! Bonsoir?
Gimme a supernova named love
Joy! Joy! Joy! So cliché
Dabba dabba poppi poppu--do
some scat then I'm outtie
Bomb! Bomb! Just more carnal desires?
Showing the chink in your manly façade--how
much girly cherishing can you do?
Can't you feel?
Gotta say it in your own words--
"Hear, hear!" "Here?" "Where?"
"How are you still a Homo sapiens?"
Drum up a lovestorm (One chance) An
avant-garde rhapsody (Oh, one more chance)
Compete, compete, compete!
Refresh my love--the mostest more than most!
Natural-born dreamer (Wonder)
Don't want it to fizzle out (Oh, falling down)
Not coming? Then I'll pull ya!
"That's premeditated crime!" (Big love)
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Yes! Rockin' on!
"Next Time..."
You've blossomed into a fine pervert, Ash.
I"Next Time..."
'd be proud to take you anywhere.
A fine pervert?
Don't you start with this, too, Navi!
Don't you like it?
I sure don't.
It's all right.
What is?
It's... all... right!
"Next Episode: Assembly in Fontaine"
What is?
I'm sure Sir Ash can satisfy any girl around.
Hey, now!