Lancelot!
You can't go see the
Mother Dragon with your leg like that.
Better just give up.
As if I'd ever do that!
I need a parr!
I didn't come all
this way to turn back now!
I understand. So you need a parr, huh?
Then there's only one solution:
I'll carry you, and we can
look for the Mother Dragon together!
That was right after my seventh birthday,
the time of the Orphan's Rite,
when the Mother Dragon
gifted humans with baby dragons.
I wonder what that boy's up to now?
A... A dragon?
This looks like...
I can't remember.
In between the
Zepharos Empire to the north
and the Chevron Kingdom to the south,
lies Lautreamont Knight Country.
Known as "the Dragon-Rearing Land,"
it boasts the largest dragon population
on the Arc Strada continent.
This small country with
fewer than five million citizens
is home to a unique school:
Ansullivan Dragonar Academy.
It aims to educate
and guide dragon masters
and the so-called Breeders,
young men and women
who have entered into bonds with dragons.
Meeting you smack
in the middle of the world
It leaves me breathless
The "something" you and I have
Starts with a tiny thrum
Now teach me about
the sky one more time
"Dragonar Academy"
The weight of flapping
wings that only a bird knows
Everyone longs for it,
though they know nothing about it
You smiled with
a slightly sorrowful look
I... I have nothing
But if your tears can be fewer
And you'll smile like you mean it
Then I can be a hero--any kind you need
I'll embody any kind of hero for you
I'll never, never,
never, never let go
Even if I die,
I'll be your knight alone
But you cried for
real and got angry:
Saying "Don't be so cold to me"
I wipe your tears
Even without a sacred blade
I don't care if I'm not a hero
If I can protect you with all I have
"Iron Blood Valkyrie"
Today we welcome three new
members to the student council
of Ansullivan Dragonar Academy.
Allow me to introduce them to you.
First, in charge of public morals:
Silvia Lautreamont!
Thank you.
I am Silvia Lautreamont,
public morals officer.
As a novice, I'm sure
I have my share of flaws,
but I shall endeavor
to do my utmost.
I look forward to my service.
Next, our number-one problem child,
in charge of general affairs:
Ash Blake!
Ash Blake, general affairs.
To be honest, I'm still not
sure what I can bring to the table...
...b-but I'll do my best regardless!
Thanks in advance!
You can do it, Ash!
Go get 'em!
And finally, a familiar face to you all,
Ash Blake's parr:
the humanoid dragon Eco!
Let's give a warm welcome to
our new school mascot!
Say hello, Eco!
Rawr!
Wh-What's all this?
How irritating!
Making a laughingstock out of
the proud dragon race is a grave sin!
Stupid dummy dum-dum humans!
Cosette was being
thoughtful, in her way.
Besides, no one was
making fun of you--trust me.
Huh?
They saw how interesting
you are and felt a bond with you.
Is that a good thing?
Sure it is! It means
everyone wants to be your friend.
Hmm... Then I'd be happy
to make them all my servants!
Now listen here...
So...
...this is your first job
as student council member?
Yeah--take down anything posted
without permission.
Just remember who your master is.
Don't go letting anyone else
boss you around, you hear me?!
Actually, I'm your master.
"Silver Knight Fan Club"?
Who's this Silver Knight, anyway?
It's the hero from this popular novel,
The Heavenly Dragonar .
They say he got his name because
he resembled the Archdragonar
who saved the town from Necromancia.
So wait--is this your fan club?
I guess you could say that.
Watch where you're aiming!
I'm runnin' out of ammo!
It's her!
The Iron Blood Valkyrie!
Fire!
Little embers like you,
if left to burn,
can grow to engulf an entire nation!
Study hall, huh?
Hey, Eco!
You looked so adorable in that dress!
Say, Ash, wanna swap--
He had that coming.
Hello! I'm first-year
Senios Jessica Valentine,
president of the Silver Knight
Fan Club, or SKFC for short!
And I'm the SKFC vice-president,
first-year Unios Lynette Worth!
We have not met the Silver Knight,
the object of our admiration.
Therefore, we are seeking information.
Did anyone here see the hero
who vanquished Necromancia?
We're in the middle
of class here. Please leave.
Oh, my! If it isn't the princess!
Not now it isn't.
I'm warning you as the student
council's public morals officer.
Public morals? How very trivial!
Why, that pales in
comparison to my ambition!
What ambition?
Allow me to elucidate!
My ambition...
...is to...
...bear the Silver Knight's children!
Miss President!
That statement is in violation
of Statute 127, SKFC's motto:
"Pure, True, Lovely"!
That's our vice president for you.
Nice catch, Lynette.
I hereby retract that statement.
Retraction acknowledged.
Why so by-the-book?
Resistance is useless--and painful.
She's from a long and
distinguished line of nobility.
In point of fact...
Mm-hmm...
What's that? The princess
was at the Necromancia scene?!
Mm-hmm...
And riding Lancelot at that!
So mightn't you know
the Silver Knight's secret identity?
D-Don't be ridiculous!
Listen...
We are in the middle of class here.
Could you leave?
To think a mere commoner would
speak his mind to me, of all people!
Acting the fool again, eh, Jessica?
Rebecca! Can I help you?
I have business with
the student council members.
Perfect! As president of the SKFC,
I demand that the student
council disclose information
on the Necromancia incident!
I-I'll forgive you just this once, b-but...
...this isn't over!
"Dragonar Academy"
So Jessica isn't nobility?
That's right. Her family's been
in the service of us Randalls for generations.
So when she starts making trouble,
I threaten to expose her.
But why the ruse?
Jessica's a good person,
but between her dreamy personality
and her admiration
for royalty and nobility,
it seems she's come to believe
that she herself is high-born.
The things we talk ourselves into...
But if she finds the Silver Knight,
she really can be nobility.
What do you mean?
In this dragon-rearing country of ours,
Arch corresponds to a noble rank.
If she were to marry the
Arch-bearing Silver Knight,
her future would be all but guaranteed.
If she finds out
the Silver Knight is really you, Ash Blake,
Jessica will set her sights on
your essence for sure.
E-Essence?!
What's that? Is it yummy?
You do not need to know!
But if you know,
it's only fair that I know, too!
What kind of logic is that?
Hmph! I have a little
something called the Draguarth!
E-Essence?!
In any case, Ash, you must take
care to keep your identity under wraps.
Jessica is one tenacious woman.
Understood.
Now on to our main topic.
As it happens, First Princess
Veronica Lautreamont
will be paying a visit
to the town of Ansullivan
in the wake of its Necromancia attack.
A sympathy call from First Princess Veronica?
That's serious business.
First princess--that must mean...
Yes... she's Silvia's big sister.
No!
Setting course for Ansullivan.
Roger.
We'll be seeing her soon, Glen.
Indeed.
I'm so looking forward to it...
my little sister... Silvia.
M-My elder sister--that
tyrant--here, in Ansullivan?
Bye now!
Beautiful flowers for sale!
Master Milgauss told me to learn more
about the boy
who killed Necromancia...
...but he's not that easy to find.
What's gotten into the princess, anyway?
Must be Veronica's impending visit.
She's been like this
ever since she heard the news.
Well, then...
...shall I explain?
Cosette!
Are you concerned about the reasons
behind her state of shock as her classmate?
Or as a man?
Wh-What are you talking about?
We've fought together,
and we're both student council members.
It's only natural that I'd be worried!
Then let's leave it at that, shall we?
Even though Veronica
wasn't selected as a Breeder,
she rebelled against that rejection
by strengthening her body
and perfecting her sword skills.
Soon she earned herself another name--
The Iron Blood Valkyrie.
So intense was her personality
that she put her young sister
through various drills, all "for her own good."
Drills--now that's an exaggeration.
Not at all. Those were... brutal days.
Survival exercises in the mountains...
If you want to live, cut a path for yourself.
Take up that sword!
And so Veronica has become
a symbol of terror for the princess.
How traumatic.
No wonder she's afraid of her.
Princess?
Princess!
Um... if you like,
you could come to me for advice.
I, uh... I don't really
know how I could help, but...
Look how far I've fallen...
Huh?
To think you would pity me!
Save your concern.
Geez... I go out of my way, and--
She's just bluffing.
Tomorrow, eh...?
What a marvelous fragrance.
Lavender. It can make
mental tension melt away.
Mental tension, eh?
You haven't been sleeping well
these past few days.
I didn't realize you knew.
This should help you relax
and drift right off to sleep.
Y-You can skip that part!
I beg your pardon. Now, then...
Cosette!
I beg your pardon yet again. Let's see...
No--stop...
Isn't that quite enough?
Cosette!
It's been so very long since
I've seen you laugh, princess.
Cosette...
Pleasant dreams.
Then there's only one solution:
I'll carry you, and we can look
for the Mother Dragon together!
Okay, here we go.
I made that boy a promise.
That I'd be a fine, upstanding knight...
Behave yourself
around Princess Veronica, Eco.
And you behave yourself around me !
I don't want a big scene, all right?
Just be a good girl and I'll buy you a crepe.
You will?! Then I suppose I'll do what you say!
Where's the princess?
I couldn't force her to come--not
when she's that terrified.
You're right. Still, to be
that scared of your own sister...
Who's scared of what now?
Princess!
Greetings.
Are you all right?
To whom do you think you're speaking?
I am Silvia Lautreamont!
You may have seen me in
a rather... unbecoming moment,
but I'm fine now.
Ah. Well... good.
Here she comes!
Oh! That's First Princess Veronica's--
It looks like an Imperial airship...
That's Princess Veronica's personal vehicle,
the Magiship Sylvanus .
How does a thing like that even fly?
It runs on a special kind
of fafnirite called milenium.
There's other kinds of fafnirite?
Thousand-year-old dragon fossils
turn into mana-rich crystals.
So that's milenium.
Princess Veronica has come into view!
So that's...
Veronica Lautreamont, First Princess...
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Joy! Joy! Joy! First-class, right? Bomb!
Bomb! Bon! Cute! Bon! Bon! Bonsoir?
Gimme a supernova named love
Joy! Joy! Joy! So cliché
Dabba dabba poppi poppu--do
some scat then I'm outtie
Bomb! Bomb! Just more carnal desires?
Showing the chink in your manly façade--how
much girly cherishing can you do?
Can't you feel?
Gotta say it in your own words--
"Hear, hear!" "Here?" "Where?"
"How are you still a Homo sapiens?"
Drum up a lovestorm (One chance) An
avant-garde rhapsody (Oh, one more chance)
Compete, compete, compete!
Refresh my love--the mostest more than most!
Natural-born dreamer (Wonder)
Don't want it to fizzle out (Oh, falling down)
Not coming? Then I'll pull ya!
"That's premeditated crime!" (Big love)
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Yes! Rockin' on!
"Next Time..."
"If the nightingale doesn't sing, kill it!"
So goes my family motto.
That's your family motto?!
What's wrong with it?
Nothing... but how many mottos
do you Lautreamonts have, anyway?
1,086.
--That's a lot!
--And now I shall list them all!
"Next Episode: Ice Blue Princess"
Oh, no, you don't!
--One...
--Stop!