Pardon me, Princess.
Cosette... can I ask you something?
What might that be, Princess?
Why do I have to take a bath
just because my dress is in for alterations?
What are you saying?
It's only right for a lady to beautify her body
in preparation for tonight's masquerade ball.
I've prepared my special lotion.
And do what with it?
Give you a better full-body massage than before.
Now, Princess... let's get down to business.
S-Stop doing that!
How about this?
Not bad.
Then what about this?
It's all right...
It's not exactly
screaming "pick me," though.
Oh, no?
Everyone'll be dressed up
fancy at this ball thing, right?
Even though I'm just after the meat.
This daughter of dragonkind
isn't gonna be outdone
by any stupid dummy dum-dum human!
Understood! I'll find just
the right gown for you, Miss Eco.
I'll crush you if you don't.
I'm bored stiff.
It's not like it matters what
a man wears to these things.
Yes?
It's me.
Princess?!
May I?
Meeting you smack
in the middle of the world
It leaves me breathless
The "something" you and I have
Starts with a tiny thrum
Now teach me about
the sky one more time
"Dragonar Academy"
The weight of flapping
wings that only a bird knows
Everyone longs for it,
though they know nothing about it
You smiled with
a slightly sorrowful look
I... I have nothing
But if your tears can be fewer
And you'll smile like you mean it
Then I can be a hero--any kind you need
I'll embody any kind of hero for you
I'll never, never,
never, never let go
Even if I die,
I'll be your knight alone
But you cried for
real and got angry:
Saying "Don't be so cold to me"
I wipe your tears
Even without a sacred blade
I don't care if I'm not a hero
If I can protect you
with all I have
What's going on here?
Wh-What is all this?
Why am I sitting beside
the princess on--on my bed?
And what's that supposed to mean?!
Uh, P-Princess...
don't you have a fitting to go to?
M-My gown is being tailored.
It's gotten tighter in
the chest this past year, so--
Now look what you made me say!
S-Sorry!
Is... is something bothering you?
Yeah. Hear me out?
"Yggdrasil Rising"
Nope.
Nope!
Are you yanking my chain or what?
N-Not at all!
You're just so demanding, Miss Eco...
I told you: as a dragon,
I have to be better than these humans!
Especially that Silvia!
Do you dislike Princess Silvia?
Not exactly...
But she's been getting
really chummy with Ash lately.
It makes me feel all mixed-up inside.
You certainly have it rough, Miss Eco.
How so?
Well, Ash is human and you're a dragon.
One day he'll fall in love
with a human girl, get married,
have babies, and...
Ash is human and you're a dragon.
One day he'll fall in love
with a human girl, get married,
have babies, and...
M-Miss Eco?
Milgauss... is Prince Julius?!
Father could never bring himself
to go through with his execution.
The way Father was acting yesterday...
...the stolen ashes...
...what Milgauss said at
the Willingham Mausoleum...
...that first Necromancia...
The clues were all there.
I just didn't see them.
I'd be genuinely happy
if my brother were still alive.
But what do I do now?
You know, my dad...
He up and left right
after my little sister was born.
We were forbidden
to talk about him after that.
But one day, I asked my mom:
"Why did Dad leave?"
And?
She didn't answer.
But she promised
she'd tell me when I was older
and could better understand.
So I stopped obsessing about it.
What I mean is...
Rather than spending your
time worrying and wondering,
it'd be faster to corner
the guy and just ask him.
Right?
That sure would make my life easier.
You're right. Thank you.
It's nothing.
Um...
Er... Princess?
A-Are you all right?
The lightning's pretty
far off now, so you can let go--
N-No! No no no no no!
What the hell are you thinking?!
She's the fourth princess
of Lautreamont Knight Country!
She's got her mind on
this whole Prince Julius thing!
I can't--
Pardon me, Princess.
Your gown is tailored and ready.
I-Is that so? I'll be right there.
Pardon the intrusion.
Say...
What's keeping Eco?
I knew full well...
I knew all along, and yet...
this tightness in my chest...
One day he'll fall in love
with a human girl, get married...
with a human girl, get married,
have babies, and...
Ash is a human and I'm a dragon...
When he starts a family, I'll--
But... but that's...!
Eco?
She's gone. And with the
ball starting any minute, too...
Is something wrong, Ash?
Where...?
I'm so lost.
What the--?
What are they doing there?
It's her!
Where are you?!
Miss Eco!
Stay back! Get out of here!
Eco's gone?
Uh-huh. Prim can't find her, either.
Understood.
Please attend the ball as planned.
But--
We servants know this
castle like the backs of our hands.
Please don't worry.
We'll find her before you know it.
Thanks--I appreciate it.
Where could she be?
Ash?
I heard about Eco and Prim.
No need to worry.
Cosette will find them right away.
Yeah... you're right.
Milgauss!
What are you doing here?!
Dear me! You have
business with my servant?
Just a case of mistaken identity.
Wait!
Stop. I've seen that noble before.
What?
He's representing the Zepharos
Empire at the Continental Congress--
Margrave Klaus Vandenhul!
"Dragonar Academy"
Stay back! Get out of here!
Huh?
If I can just carry out
Master Milgauss's orders...
Quit glaring at him, Ash.
Huh?
He may be from the Empire,
but he wouldn't dare start anything here.
But--
Focus more on your footwork.
You're terribly out of step.
Easy for you to say--I've only
learned the basics so far.
Thank you, Ash. I feel better
now that I've confided in you.
Princess...
M-Make no mistake! I'm thanking
you for listening to me, that's all.
Yeah, yeah.
No sign of Miss Eco on these floors.
Nor these.
So that leaves...
I was so nervous...!
Think this is tougher than
the Dragonar battle skills exam?
Maybe so.
What a marvelous dance that was!
Won't you dance another round with me?
Another dance? Gladly. But...
...with that gentleman there.
Cosette!
It's Prim!
I've never seen anyone dance so beautifully.
Are you... my brother?
Why did you call me Silvie?
The Necromancia in Durham
Square--was that Mordred?
Answer me!
Is it proper in Knight Country
to ask questions during a dance?
Princess!
How'd it go? Is he--
I'm not certain. However...
He definitely dances
in the Knight Country style.
Princess Silvia, Master Ash.
We've found Prim.
P-Please forgive me, Ash!
Why are you apologizing? What happened?
If I hadn't said what I did...
Said what?
That Miss Eco was a dragon...
and you were a human...
That one day you'd marry
a human girl and have babies,
and didn't that make Eco sad?
You imbecile!
Eco's a dragon, sure, but inside,
she may as well be a human girl.
Why was she born in human form,
instead of looking like a dragon?
If I were Eco, I know I'd be
fretting about that very question.
And you...
I-I'm so sorry!
That's all right, Princess.
Thank you.
Prim says Miss Eco
was abducted at the old palace.
Abducted?!
Who was behind it?
What'd they look like?
They looked like they were from the palace.
Oh, but the one maid
who seemed like the leader,
she was a Tantalos girl.
A Tantalos girl...?
Milgauss!
Wait!
It'd be pointless to confront him directly.
But--
We scoured the castle for Miss Eco,
but she's nowhere to be found.
If they abducted her,
they won't be wanting to kill her.
What would be a safe place to
hide her during the ball?
Margrave Klaus Vandenhul's airship--
Beowulf !
There you are, Anya.
The experiment has begun, I see.
It's going smoothly so far.
Ubermana Beam No. 11, prepare to fire.
Cartridge loaded.
Preparations complete.
Commence countdown.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
Ubermana Beam No. 11: Fire.
We're shooting her with a
concentrated beam
of the immense
amount of mana in milenium.
Yggdrasil here can forcefully
awaken adult dragons
that never became Maestros.
Milenium, the mana-rich
crystals said to come from
thousand-year-old dragon fossils...
It's that mana we give to our subject.
And make her reveal her true form...
Am I going to die like this?
Ubermana Beam No. 12:
Fire.
Ow! It hurts!
It hurrrts!
Stop... please... please!
No change to Subject Alpha.
I guess we have no choice.
Set milenium output to the maximum.
Eco...
Nooo!
Ash!
Ash !
Ash...!
I can't feel it... my connection to Ash...
How stupid can I get...?
This is what it took for me to realize...
My feelings... for Ash...
All milenium engaged.
Final Ubermana Beam:
Fire.
Wh-What's this?!
The mana detector's picked
up an unknown mana reaction!
Yggdrasil is out of control!
It's not accepting the
emergency shutdown signal!
Wh-What...?
Quick, stop the device--before it runs amok!
No chance of that.
Huh?
All that energy harvested from the milenium
has been absorbed
into Subject Alpha's body.
E-Eco?
Princess! Look!
Beowulf ... What's going on?
Ash?
Ash! What is it?!
I don't know... but something's
happened to Eco, for sure!
Ash!
Y-You don't mean...
...Eco's in there?!
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Joy! Joy! Joy! First-class, right? Bomb!
Bomb! Bon! Cute! Bon! Bon! Bonsoir?
Gimme a supernova named love
Joy! Joy! Joy! So cliché
Dabba dabba poppi poppu--do
some scat then I'm outtie
Bomb! Bomb! Just more carnal desires?
Showing the chink in your manly façade--how
much girly cherishing can you do?
Can't you feel?
Gotta say it in your own words--
"Hear, hear!" "Here?" "Where?"
"How are you still a Homo sapiens?"
Drum up a lovestorm (One chance) An
avant-garde rhapsody (Oh, one more chance)
Compete, compete, compete!
Refresh my love--the mostest more than most!
Natural-born dreamer (Wonder)
Don't want it to fizzle out (Oh, falling down)
Not coming? Then I'll pull ya!
"That's premeditated crime!" (Big love)
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Yes! Rockin' on!
"Next Time..."
Hang in there, Eco... I'll save you, I swear.
After all, you're my parr,
and I'm your Dragonar.
Our bond is absolute.
"Next Episode: The Star-Branded Dragonar"
I won't let anyone tear us apart!
So please... please...!