That's Princess Veronica's
personal vehicle, the Magiship Sylvanus .
Princess Veronica has come into view!
So that's...
...Veronica Lautreamont, First Princess...
Meeting you smack
in the middle of the world
It leaves me breathless
The "something" you and I have
Starts with a tiny thrum
Now teach me about
the sky one more time
"Dragonar Academy"
The weight of flapping
wings that only a bird knows
Everyone longs for it,
though they know nothing about it
You smiled with
a slightly sorrowful look
I... I have nothing
But if your tears can be fewer
And you'll smile like you mean it
Then I can be a hero--any kind you need
I'll embody any kind of hero for you
I'll never, never,
never, never let go
Even if I die,
I'll be your knight alone
But you cried for
real and got angry:
Saying "Don't be so cold to me"
I wipe your tears
Even without a sacred blade
I don't care if I'm not a hero
If I can protect you with all I have
"Ice Blue Princess"
There is loyalty in coming to greet me.
Is Silvia here?
Yes.
It's been a while, sister.
Four years, two months,
and thirteen days.
Indeed. I see you're well.
How I've looked
forward to this day.
Do you mean to deceive me?
That's the Veronica I know.
There's no fooling you, is there.
Cosette!
Out with it: Where is the real Silvia?
H-Here I am!
It's been too long.
Sist--
What is it, little sister?
Weak in the knees, I see.
N-No, I--
Such ineptitude you've put on display.
And you count yourself part
of the House of Lautreamont?
You disappoint me.
Time for your punishment, Silvia.
It seems you've only grown in
your breasts and your behind.
Will you be this ashamed on the battlefield?
That's you in a nutshell:
You act pretentious, but really,
you're nothing but a little girl.
Never mind your Dragonar ambition--
it's far more appropriate
for you to settle down!
Now just a moment!
Humiliating your own
family in the public eye--
is that any way
for knight royalty to act?!
Ash!
He is merely a student, Glen.
Hey, now!
Don't talk to my dog like--
Ah, I see. So you're Ash Blake.
That simplifies things.
Glen: seize him.
As you wish.
What's the big idea?!
Dammit! Put me down! Why, you...
The Tantalos clan was in the
midst of a horrible ethnic conflict.
Because Master Milgauss put a stop
to it, we can live the way we do today.
And that's why I'd do anything--
Shamara! This is real bad!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm Anya now, head of the Tantalos!
Don't use my old name ever again!
I-I'm sorry, Anya... ma'am.
So what is it?
Well, uh...
The Iron Blood Valkyrie
has come to Ansullivan!
Once word got out,
everyone headed off into town,
bent on avenging their friends!
Rushing into the
fray with no battle plan?
I've got to stop them.
My goodness!
That suits you to a tee!
Er...
Why am I dressed like this again?
I have been charged with
providing you guidance, Master Ash.
My name is Primrose Shelley--
but please, if you would, just call me Prim!
O-Okay...
But, uh, what exactly
is going on here?
Princess Veronica's orders.
"Just a little diversion," she said.
Diversion?
Now off we go, Master Ash!
There's much work to be done!
P-Prim! Not that way!
Hmm?
Is... is she okay?
I'm beat.
And with all that,
Prim still handles her servant duties...
The Heavenly Dragonar ?
So this is where the
Silver Knight thing started.
Will you be this ashamed on the battlefield?
Eek!
P-Prim?!
I'm so sorry for kneading--
I-I mean, for reading
this book without asking!
I just... I'm sorry!
The Silver Knight is just the coolest!
Especially when he used ice magic
to freeze that mechanized dragon
and bring it to a stand-still!
An iced dragon, eh?
Oh, that's right!
The princess has returned,
and she's asking for you.
Eh?
What are you doing? Hurry up and get undressed!
But I'm a junior here! Can't I get a pass?
Why do I have to do this, anyway?
This is the undressing room.
So clearly, this is where you get undressed!
Now come on, Ash!
That's not really the issue...
Veronica is waiting!
I see I'll have to resort to
my special undressing technique.
Hi-yah!
P-Prim!
Undressed the wrong person!
Argh! Stay out of this, Prim!
Hey, er...
This is per the princess's command, Ash.
Wait!
I need more time to prepare...
mentally and physically!
There's no use arguing.
Shall we, Professor?
When else would I have the chance
to soak in the Sylvanus bath?
S-Stop...!
You two were affected
by Necromancia's attack.
What's your take?
It seems to me the
perpetrator has Imperial ties.
Necromancia is a fusion of
magic and engineering,
a product of scientific study.
Engineering? That's Zepharos's forte.
But without any definite proof...
Um...
Why might I be here in the bath with you?
What's wrong?
Does bathing with us
displease you in some way?
I-It's not that...
This bath smells great!
Kinda makes me feel all soft an' fluffy...
I thought I'd try
anthar-scented bath salts today!
Aaack! Eco!
Who'd think a couple of scrubs like you
could be the heroes
who defeated Necromancia?
So this is the young dragon Eco,
who threw together Arch
from whatever she could find.
And Ash Blake,
who can ride any dragon around.
Princess?
Her Highness the Fourth
Princess is here to see you.
Begging your pardon... sister.
P-Princess?!
Ash?! A-And Rebecca?!
Oh, Ash! Fancy seeing you here!
Is that you, Cosette?
Hi, sis!
Sis?
As it happens, Silvia,
I come bearing a marriage proposal.
Ever since the rightful heir,
our brother Julius,
was executed for
the crime of dragon-killing,
the future of our royal line
has remained uncertain.
You're already sixteen.
Bear a healthy child now,
while you're still young.
We can't let our bloodline
end here, now can we?
B-But--
Aren't you the first princess, Veronica?
The only affairs
that interest me are military.
Honestly... If only Julius were still here,
instead of losing his life to a foolish trifle.
I-I'm sure our brother had his reasons.
The way you talk...
You always did have a soft spot for Julius.
Good news, then:
Your marriage prospect
was a friend of his.
You don't mean...
That's right. One of
my knights, Glen McGuire.
You were equally attached
to them both, once upon a time.
I'm sure you'll be satisfied.
B-But my dream is to become
an Archdragonar with Lancelot.
To get married a-and have
children before that happens...?
Considering your poor
showing during this last attack,
it's an interesting ambition, indeed.
It wasn't like that at all!
If she hadn't sent Lancelot forth,
I could never have ridden Necromancia!
In other words, Silvia served
as little more than a courier.
No!
It only matters if she gets results.
Silvia.
With your dreams and ambitions,
you're all talk and no action.
Are you kidding me?
The princess can be
honest to a fault sometimes.
But she always does
the absolute best she can do!
You haven't even
seen what she's capable of!
Well, then...
As it happens, there'll be
a match in my honor tomorrow.
Prove to me the
value of your little dream.
I will.
"Dragonar Academy"
Phooey! I wanted to play, too!
You mean you want to be
out there with those dragons?
Why did I have to be
born looking like this, anyway?
Dragons are an
extremely intelligent species.
There must be a reason
you were given human form.
You'll understand some day.
A-Amazing!
Princess!
Hey!
My room...?
Are you all right, Princess?
Wh-What are you doing here?
Ash carried you here.
He... he did?
I was worried about you.
Lancelot's one great dragon,
but even he can't take a head-on collision
with the Academy's toughest, Cu Chulainn.
I had to show her.
To show my sister how
I fight as a real live Dragonar.
But now, even as Lancelot's master, I'm a failure.
No need to beat yourself up about it.
Silence! I knew Lancelot
should have been his--
Silvia, it's me.
Rebecca? Come in.
Pardon me. I need to speak with Ash.
And... I've brought a guest.
I've come to ask after
your condition, Princess Silvia.
I see. My apologies.
No--on Princess Veronica's orders.
As you can see, it's nothing serious.
I understand.
I also bring with me a message
from Princess Veronica.
Which is?
The princess will be touring
the town at noon tomorrow.
At which time...
I know: Don't make a
scene as her escort, right?
No. It will not be necessary
to accompany her.
What?
She commands you
to visit St. Valeria tomorrow,
where you shall
offer prayers of repentance.
Repentance?!
The princess is in high dudgeon
over your lack of ability.
Your simple tactics mistake
recklessness for bravery,
revealing how
shallow your dream really is.
And when you go to pray,
bring no servants with you.
You must do your
soul-searching alone.
So says the princess.
If you'll excuse me.
Wait, Glen.
Did... did my sister tell you
about the marriage proposal?
Yes.
Would you really be
willing to take me as your wife?
If Princess Veronica commands it.
I see.
That's all. Go.
Hey, what's with the attitude?
Ash!
Getting married is a lifelong deal
and you'll do it at a single command?
My mistress's word is law.
And if she told you to drop dead,
you would, no questions asked?
Of course.
You're a puppet!
Have you no will of your own?
Ash Blake, was it?
Perhaps you are riding
high after saving the town.
I applaud your
luck and skill. However...
Be mindful of your place.
Geez! What's with
that coldhearted creep?
He wasn't always like that.
But ten years ago,
when my brother
was executed for dragon-killing,
he grew despondent,
and became a whole other person.
My sister proved to be his salvation.
She's of high enough caliber
to tolerate a knight like Glen.
Princess...
Ash, I've got a message for you:
The student council is
meeting tomorrow morning
about the royal tour.
Don't be late.
B-But what about me?
We can't give you student
council work like this.
But--
If you don't like it, you'll have
to surpass Princess Veronica.
Surpass my sister...?
Excuse me!
Eco? What's going on?
You're laaate!
It's no use...
My body's so hot... I can't take it...
Is that anthar I smell?!
Hang on--what've you got in there?
In there?
You mean... in here?
No ! Not your skirt! Your mouth !
Candy? So that's the culprit! Spit it out!
Did you just--
A rather unhealthy
relationship you have there, no?
Though it made for a pretty good show.
Those are my underthings she's wearing.
And did you give her this candy?
She gets that pleading look
in her eyes--I just can't say no.
Now come on in.
Rebecca...
Our vice president and
secretary are absent today.
It's a little lonely here with just us three,
but let's get this meeting underway.
We will be accompanying Princess Veronica
on her tour through town.
However, intel indicates that this individual
may have infiltrated Ansullivan.
Five years ago,
this former mountain guerilla terrorist
attempted to
assassinate Princess Veronica.
She's been undercover ever since.
Avdocha, She Who Condemns.
Oh, Princess Veronica!
How nice of you to come all this way!
Do not slow your hand! Keep working!
Yes, Your Highness!
To think any one
of them could be a terrorist...
Your nerves are showing, Ash.
But...
My favorite crepe shop!
Hey, Eco, I might wind up
needing that Arch again, okay?
Hmph! You can have
that patchwork pile of parts!
Just... as soon
as that place is rebuilt...
Yeah, sure. I'll buy you
as many crepes as you want.
You will? Deal!
I hope the princess is okay.
O St. Valeria...
I pray before you with purest heart,
in punishment for my own arrogance.
Forgive me my imprudent behavior.
O St. Valeria...
May the Silver Knight impregnate me!
What kind of prayer is that ,
Jessica Valentine?!
Oh, Princess Silvia!
What do you mean, "oh"?
How dare you talk about...
g-getting impregnated
in such a holy place!
Whatever do you mean?
I'm simply praying for a safe pregnancy!
St. Valeria is the patron of the law!
You're saying the wrong prayers!
Nobles don't concern
ourselves with such trivialities.
Surely our dear
saint is generous of heart.
What a convenient excuse.
With nobility comes great capacity.
Why, that's true of
Princess Veronica, is it not?
What?
Though I suppose a fourth princess
wouldn't be nearly
as capable as her older sister.
Now you listen here!
St. Valeria once said,
"Love the sinner, hate the sin."
What imbecility!
Indeed, the foolish heart is
the very root of all evil!
Death to all sinners!
I am Avdocha, She Who Condemns!
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Joy! Joy! Joy! First-class, right? Bomb!
Bomb! Bon! Cute! Bon! Bon! Bonsoir?
Gimme a supernova named love
Joy! Joy! Joy! So cliché
Dabba dabba poppi poppu--do
some scat then I'm outtie
Bomb! Bomb! Just more carnal desires?
Showing the chink in your manly façade--how
much girly cherishing can you do?
Can't you feel?
Gotta say it in your own words--
"Hear, hear!" "Here?" "Where?"
"How are you still a Homo sapiens?"
Drum up a lovestorm (One chance) An
avant-garde rhapsody (Oh, one more chance)
Compete, compete, compete!
Refresh my love--the mostest more than most!
Natural-born dreamer (Wonder)
Don't want it to fizzle out (Oh, falling down)
Not coming? Then I'll pull ya!
"That's premeditated crime!" (Big love)
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Yes! Rockin' on!
"Next Time..."
I hear you're a complete pervert, Ash Blake.
There's some real
misinformation going around!
And that you really love
it when a princess berates you.
Oh, so it keeps getting better!
I'll heap invective on you until
you wish you were never born.
"Next Episode: Blue Brionac"
I'll take a big fat pass on that!