The Continental Congress.
Held every five years among
the leaders of five nations,
this most critical conference
determines the future
of the entire Arc Strada continent.
This time, Lautreamont Knight
Country was chosen to host.
Why would Eco and I be summoned
for such an important event?
And this city we're going to-- this Fon...
Fontaine?
Yeah, that. What kind of place is it?
The capital of Lautreamont Knight Country.
Cappy-tall?
It's so big, there's no
comparing it to Ansullivan.
So they might have
crepes I haven't tried yet!
Maybe.
There it is!
That's it?
Yes...
...our nation's capital, Fontaine.
In between the
Zepharos Empire to the north
and the Chevron Kingdom to the south,
lies Lautreamont Knight Country.
Known as "the Dragon-Rearing Land,"
it boasts the largest dragon
population on the Arc Strada continent.
This small country with
fewer than five million citizens
is home to a unique school:
Ansullivan Dragonar Academy.
It aims to educate
and guide dragon masters
and the so-called Breeders,
young men and women
who have entered
into bonds with dragons.
Meeting you smack
in the middle of the world
It leaves me breathless
The "something" you and I have
Starts with a tiny thrum
Now teach me about
the sky one more time
"Dragonar Academy"
The weight of flapping
wings that only a bird knows
Everyone longs for it,
though they know nothing about it
You smiled with
a slightly sorrowful look
I... I have nothing
But if your tears can be fewer
And you'll smile like you mean it
Then I can be a hero--any kind you need
I'll embody any kind of hero for you
I'll never, never,
never, never let go
Even if I die,
I'll be your knight alone
But you cried for
real and got angry:
Saying "Don't be so cold to me"
I wipe your tears
Even without a sacred blade
I don't care if I'm not a hero
If I can protect you
with all I have
"Assembly in Fontaine"
Welcome home, Princess Silvia.
I know you've just arrived,
but the Paladin awaits.
I'll show my guests around first.
That won't do.
First you must greet the Paladin.
Sorry about this.
If there's anything you need,
just ask Frieda here.
Princess?
Let's just get this over with.
Please follow me.
Security's pretty tight.
The host country must be responsible,
taking the utmost care to
ensure the visiting leaders' safety
and providing them with
hospitality during their stay.
It's only natural.
Yes, of course.
You understand we have
little time to entertain your type.
Huh?
If you need anything further,
please contact the attendant
provided by Her Highness
Princess Veronica.
Princess Veronica?
In here.
I-I-I-I'm so sorry!
Prim?
Why, you...!
Prim!
What is the meaning of this?!
My clothes get really
dirty while I clean, so...
...I clean in my underwear.
Your maid uniform
is permitted to get dirty!
I-I'm sorry!
--I thought I was doing the right thing!
--Hey! Quit staring!
Why so many outfits?
My clothes get so dirty,
I need a lot of changes on standby.
Ah, I see...
Ugh, so tight... I don't know
how you can wear these things.
Prim, will you take care of those two?
Yes, ma'am!
But first: tidy up!
Yes, ma'am...
Please excuse me.
Tidy up, hmm?
That's your behind.
S-So it is.
Sometimes we can get soaked
right down to our underthings...
See? I'm not wearing any, either.
I said , quit staring!
Oh, Prim...
I-I'm sorry!
Silvia Lautreamont has returned.
How long I've waited for you,
my darling daughter!
This old familiar pain...
the bite of your fist...
How closely you resemble
your late mother, Elisabeth!
How irritating.
And you sound just like her, too!
You should be ashamed,
getting off on your daughter scolding you!
Now, where were we?
Father, to what do I owe the pleasure
of my invitation to the Congress?
I am but a mere student, still in training.
You're the fourth princess and
a Dragonar. You're plenty qualified.
I'm not the one who recommended you.
That was Veronica.
My elder sister?
She talks tough,
but she recognizes your skill.
Then why bring Ash Blake
and Eco here at such a busy time?
It is indeed a busy time for our nation.
But as you know, I'm just a figurehead.
The more everyone buzzes
around me, the more free time I have!
In other words,
you wanted someone to kill time with.
And I've been hearing so
many rumors about those two!
You're such a child.
Thank you so much.
Now, then...
Shall we check it out?
Well, if you insist,
I suppose I could go with you.
Let's do it!
Then allow me to lead the way!
Ugh! Let's hurry up and change
so we can get out of here!
Whoa, whoa!
Father, there is one more matter
after which I must inquire.
Why so stuffy?
It's about my brother, Julius.
Was he really executed?
Of course. What are you saying?
He was a dragonslayer who had
killed his own parr by his own hand.
Such a crime is unforgiveable--
even for a prince!
Yes, of course...
Princess?
He's a terrible liar.
Wow!
Wow !
This place really is
nothing at all like Ansullivan!
500 years ago,
King Lionel III of Chevron
named Durham the very first Paladin.
This statue commemorates that ceremony.
After that, Durham became
independent of the Chevron Kingdom
and went on to establish
Lautreamont Knight Country.
Ooh, what's that?
Hey, reel it in, wouldja?
Sorry for running you ragged today, Prim.
Not at all... I apologize for
lacking the energy to keep up.
Ash!
Hurry up or I'll pop ya one!
I can't very well come
all the way to the capital
and not eat crepes!
What kind of logic is that?
Got it! I'll have a choco-mint
and a cheese and raspberry!
Hey... why are those
people so stuck on each other?
Huh?
And why are you staring
at them like you're jealous?
Was I?
Like a starving dog.
Ouch!
So why are they all
over each other like that?
Well, uh...
...probably because they're lovers.
Lovers?
Oh.
You... you can hold my hand if you want.
Okay--if you say so.
Hands only! Hands only!
That's as far as I'll allow!
I know, I know!
But do you? Do you really ?
I do, really!
That...
...that crest...
It's the crest of the
House of Witershausen.
He's attending the Continental
Congress from the Zepharos Empire.
as a representative of the emperor.
Cosette! Wh-Where'd you come from?!
I'm here to pick you up.
"Dragonar Academy"
--Banquet time! Time for meat!
--Guess I'm not used to these clothes.
--They just feel so stiff...
--Banquet time! Time for meat, meat, meat!
Just don't make a scene, okay?
If we offend the head of state...
I'll be quiet. I've gotta make
it through the very last dessert!
What is it, Ash?
Uh...
I-It's just... I was just
thinking how beautiful you are.
Now you listen here...
You didn't say a thing about my dress!
Y-You're beautiful, too, Eco!
Like a forced compliment
is going to make me happy!
The preparations are complete.
She's going commando!
Hey!
You may enter.
Ah, so you're Ash!
What a pleasant face you have!
And you must be Eco!
Just look at those horns!
Thank you both for coming all this way.
Please, relax and enjoy yourselves.
Here we were all nervous
about meeting the Paladin...
I like 'im! This dude is super easy to talk to!
Eco!
Let me thank you again for
handling that Necromancia incident
and the Willingham Mausoleum affair.
P-Please, don't bow to me!
And so, Ash, from this
day on, you are a Dragonar.
Y-Yessir.
Wait...
What ?!
That's why I called you here.
But, uh...
Isn't that title given to Maestro riders,
like the princess?
Eco is a special dragon in
the shape of a human.
It would be odd to measure her
and regular old dragons
by the same yardstick.
Besides,
given the splendid
showing she's made so far,
can you swear she's not a Maestro?
Well...
And so I, as Paladin, have decided
that you are a Dragonar as of today.
Frieda, if you would.
Certainly.
In the name of Paladin Oswald, Ash Blake
is hereby appointed Dragonar.
I humbly accept.
Ash--a Dragonar?
If he goes on to become an Archdragonar,
he'll have the same standing as nobility.
Which means he can marry royalty...
M-M-M - Marry ?!
Your face is awfully red, Princess.
I-It's nothing!
So, Father,
I heard the emperor of Zepharos
won't be attending this Congress.
He declined, citing his advanced age.
And they have sent
a mere noble in his place?
They had no choice. No one
is immune to the ravages of time.
You're too trusting, Father.
First we talk. We must not cause another war.
Which is why tomorrow's
masquerade ball is so important.
A masquerade ball?
Attendees cover their faces
with masks and speak freely,
with no thought given to country or delegation!
Say, would you two like to go?
Us?
I know I'm going.
What about you, Eco?
If they have meat, I'm there.
Then it's settled!
Make the most of your evening
at tomorrow's masquerade ball!
Y-Yessir...
By the way, Ash...
Yes?
There's just one thing I have to ask.
Wh-What might that be?
You're not in an impure
relationship with Silvia, are you?
Pardon?
Father! What are you--
Ash... if you ever lay
a finger on my darling Silvia...
I, Oswald, shall punish you myself!
Honest! There's nothing
between me and the princess!
C'mon, Your Highness--tell him!
Master Milgauss!
You're looking well, I see!
Not bad.
Looks like you didn't
know about Milgauss's arm.
Mahogany--the color of maturity.
Perfect for me now,
facing this particular juncture.
Are you that Tantalos
girl he's got working for him?
Y-Yes. Anya.
I am Klaus Witershausen.
Klaus... Military nobility
from the Zepharos Empire.
This is ten years ago now.
A young man wandered
lost throughout my country
having lost his name, his rank, his fame,
and, finally, his left arm.
He carried a curse,
having committed a taboo in his homeland.
You talk too much, Klaus.
Whoops--a gag order. Too bad.
Do you know what this is?
A magica-technica device?
Well, aren't you observant.
I call this the magic Yggdrasil device.
Who cares what it's called?
The question is, can we use it?
We can start testing it tomorrow.
All we need is a test subject...
A subject?
This device will force
the young dragon Eco to awaken.
It was Milgauss's idea.
You mean... in there...?
So your duty is?
To... capture Eco.
Correct. What a splendid
little underling you have, Milgauss.
Is this a dream?
How did I never notice?
That face, that build...
That was none other
than my brother's parr, Mordred.
Silvia?
My sister! And Glen...
and even Avdocha?
What do you mean, "even"?!
Are you saying you
don't want to be around me?
Maybe I'll just lay
bare those udders of yours!
Ow!
Since when have you ranked
high enough to insult my sister?
K-Keep that up and
I'll get taller and taller!
The very idea that you'd grow
another inch past the age of twenty!
I heard that!
What business do you
have here so early in the morning?
Oh... just something on my mind.
Mordred's ashes?
You, too?
Yes. After the Willingham incident,
I investigated all of
the dragon mausoleums.
And?
As expected, someone
had removed dragon ashes
from every mausoleum in the country.
Mordred's ashes,
interred here, were no exception.
I knew it.
Did this Mordred thing ring any bells for you?
This man I saw at the Willingham
Mausoleum the other day,
calling himself Milgauss...
We know of him.
This is just a hunch, but...
I think that man might
actually be our older brother.
Impossible!
For him to have survived--
and become an Imperial army spy?
It's just not possible!
There's more.
I sensed Mordred among the
Necromancia that attacked Ansullivan.
Silvia...
Don't talk to anyone else about this.
The Lautreamont name
stands to be deeply wounded
just by Julius being alive.
I won't... sister.
How beautiful it is!
Yggdrasil is complete. With this,
the dragon's power will be ours.
Soon the imperial throne
will be a dream no longer...
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Joy! Joy! Joy! First-class, right? Bomb!
Bomb! Bon! Cute! Bon! Bon! Bonsoir?
Gimme a supernova named love
Joy! Joy! Joy! So cliché
Dabba dabba poppi poppu--do
some scat then I'm outtie
Bomb! Bomb! Just more carnal desires?
Showing the chink in your manly façade--how
much girly cherishing can you do?
Can't you feel?
Gotta say it in your own words--
"Hear, hear!" "Here?" "Where?"
"How are you still a Homo sapiens?"
Drum up a lovestorm (One chance) An
avant-garde rhapsody (Oh, one more chance)
Compete, compete, compete!
Refresh my love--the mostest more than most!
Natural-born dreamer (Wonder)
Don't want it to fizzle out (Oh, falling down)
Not coming? Then I'll pull ya!
"That's premeditated crime!" (Big love)
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Yes! Rockin' on!
"Next Time..."
We meet at last, Ash Blake.
--Shoo.
--What?
This is where I have
a fun time chatting with girls.
I don't need men in here.
Go on now, scat!
You call me here
only to treat me like this?
You've got some nerve.
"Next Episode: Yggdrasil Rising"
I'll have to show you a thing or two...
Wait, how exactly did you mean that? Hey!