Gawain... why are you rejecting Lucca?
Tell me how you feel!
Ash! Above you!
Ash !
Ash!
Meeting you smack
in the middle of the world
It leaves me breathless
The "something" you and I have
Starts with a tiny thrum
Now teach me about
the sky one more time
"Dragonar Academy"
The weight of flapping
wings that only a bird knows
Everyone longs for it,
though they know nothing about it
You smiled with
a slightly sorrowful look
I... I have nothing
But if your tears can be fewer
And you'll smile like you mean it
Then I can be a hero--any kind you need
I'll embody any kind of hero for you
I'll never, never,
never, never let go
Even if I die,
I'll be your knight alone
But you cried for
real and got angry:
Saying "Don't be so cold to me"
I wipe your tears
Even without a sacred blade
I don't care if I'm not a hero
If I can protect you
with all I have
"Moonlit Roar"
I'm sorry.
I failed.
I'm just glad you're not hurt.
Still, such extreme opposition...
It's absolutely pointless to try talking to him.
If we only knew why Gawain
was rejecting Lucca...
The upcoming training camp
would have been a good chance
for the two of them
to reconnect. But now...
Now, I'm not sure if
Lucca should even attend.
Rebecca?
May I have permission to
enter Meabh House?
I'd like to speak
with Lucca one more time.
Whaaat? What've you got up your sleeve?
All right. You may enter.
Huh?
But take Eco with you.
It's unseemly for a man to
be alone in the women's dorm.
Thank you so much!
Now wait just a minute! I never said
anything about coming along!
Gawain...
It's Ash Blake from the student council.
May I come in?
Please, have some tea.
I wasn't able to get
Gawain to tell me how he felt.
I'm sorry.
Ah.
Um, you're going to camp, right?
They say the nearby
Nog Woods has been
a kind of dragon
health resort for eons.
If you go there, I bet Gawain
would get better in no time.
And they say a change of
scenery can do a lot of good, too.
I'd like you to face
Gawain one more time.
Parr and breeder--it's like...
It's... something irreplaceable.
It's like your destiny.
And that's why...
Argh! Get off the fence already!
E-Eco?!
You stupid dummy dum-dums
and all your pointless worrying!
Hey! Cut that out!
How dare my pet dog
speak to me in such a tone!
I'll crush you!
I'll crush you,
and you'll take it, and you'll like it!
What are you going on about?!
This is going way off track!
I'll go.
Huh?
I'll go to the training camp.
Master Milgauss!
It's good to see you again.
When did you return?
Just recently.
I see you've infiltrated the Academy.
Yes, to research
Ash Blake and his parr Eco.
I'll be accompanying them to
their training camp on kitchen duty.
Training camp?
Ah, yes--the Willingham Mausoleum
on the shores of Lake Allonnes.
Yes?
The ashes of dragons who
died young are interred there.
Though young, they do not
lack in material for experiments.
We'll meet up there.
Stay close on their heels until then.
Yes, sir.
So you have been born
among us, descendant of Avalon...
Eco, eh?
Quite an ironic name
your master has given you.
Still...
No matter what name you're given,
it's far better than being killed.
Don't you agree... Julius?
Now to set out for
camp--at Lake Allonnes!
And we're off!
I hear Gawain's
gone ahead. Don't worry.
He's a smart one--I'm sure
he'll go straight for the resort.
Uh-huh.
Don't even think
about riding my Arianrhod.
Yeah, yeah. Look, I'm not
even touching your dragon, okay?
Hey, not so tight!
S-Sorry!
Off you go!
Lancelot's gonna be
the first to Lake Allonnes!
Hey! Don't be bossing him around!
And Lancelot, don't you listen to her!
He's a good dragon--he respects me!
Isn't that right, Lancelot?
Between you and Ash, I barely
even know what's going on anymore...
Wh-What are you doing, Eco?
Wow! They're so big! And soft!
Mmm, nice and bouncy!
H-Hey, now, cut that out!
That Ash--I catch him looking
at your chest, and Rebecca's, too!
Even though he doesn't seem
to care about mine at all!
It ticks me off!
A-Ash looks at my--
There must be some
male-bewitching magic involved!
It's high time
I get to the bottom of this!
N-No, just s-stop that!
Th-That's enough, Eco...!
Now, then...
Camp is about to begin.
Your experience these next few days
will have a huge impact on your futures.
All of the Sacred
Dragonars of Lautreamont
completed their training
here with flying colors.
If you wish to
be among their ranks,
I want to see your fighting
spirit as you aim for the top.
Everyone's so serious...
You should rest today in
preparation for tomorrow's training.
That is, you should ...
but since we're here...
I suppose I could permit a
little splashing around.
Take that!
Huh? Where are
you going, Professor?
It's a secret!
Jessica?!
Come now, Sir Ash, let's go!
G-Go? Where to?
On our honeymoon, of course!
Hey, now, Cosette...
You don't really mean for me to...
But of course.
You'll have all eyes on you for certain.
Well, I don't actually want...
For certain , miss.
No, it's just that...
If you continue to be unreasonable,
I'm afraid I shall have
to change you into it by force.
Wa--Wait-wait-wait-wait!
This must be heaven!
Seeing the student
council prez in her swimsuit?
Now I can die happy!
Look! Here comes the princess!
D-Don't you think there's just
a tad too little fabric?
I can't relax with the
breeze whipping my flesh like this!
Not to worry. I'm sure
Ash will be very pleased.
What? Ash?
Why would you bring him up?
Please, stooop!
This isn't half what my
parr Rhiannon is capable of!
Lancelot... and Eco?!
I'm borrowing your parr!
W-Wait! Why--how--?
I'm gonna stop
that Jessica in her tracks!
After all, I'm Ash's master, not her!
That's not what I meant!
Well, come on!
Are you with me or what?
I'm coming, too!
Attagirl!
Hey! Wait!
Jessica!
Help meee!
"Dragonar Academy"
Ooh, my aching body...
Too much horsing around today.
Lucca?
Whoa, look at that mud!
This must be the way.
Gawain...
Hey... Won't you talk to me?
I was so happy
when you became a Maestro.
I wanted us to be
together forever and ever...
So please,
one more time,
like it used to be...
Why...?
Why? Why won't you say anything?
What are you doing here?
You know, I'm a little ticked off.
We keep trying to talk to you,
but you just keep brushing us off.
Isn't that right, Gawain?
Stop--you can't--
So that means...
I'm going to have to
force those feelings out of you!
Can't afford a single
hit without my Arch...!
Over here, Gawain!
No... Stop it!
All right! And now...
S-Some kind of...
reflection magic? For defense?
Is he mistaking
my ability for an attack?
No!
If I leave him like that, he'll die.
Punishment for getting
in Master Milgauss's way.
Wh-What do I do?
Hands off!
His life is in danger!
I'll handle this. You go get help!
And you are...?
Just go! Hurry!
I-I'm going!
Now we're even.
Wh-Where am I?!
Hello, sleepyhead.
Navi?!
This is Highdragon Workshop,
a special place that
only the spirit may enter.
I summoned you here
to tell you how he feels.
What? Who is this?
Gawain.
This thing?!
He may be a Maestro,
but he's still emotionally immature.
Hence this form.
He's apologizing to you.
Says his back belongs only to
his master, Lucca, so he got serious.
I get it...
That's not all.
Three months ago,
Lucca Saarinen was
riding Gawain and fell off his back.
She did? Three months ago now?
Have you heard of the Dragon Dance?
No.
It's a secret Ecbladian art
passed down through generations.
Mastery requires natural
talent and unflagging effort.
While practicing that...
there was an accident.
She's had an unconscious
fear of riding her dragon ever since.
In that state,
it could be deadly for her to ride,
and so, Gawain
has been rejecting her--
even if it means breaking their bond
and cutting himself off from the astral flow.
Gawain...
You would go so far as
to put your own life on the line
to protect Lucca?
But Gawain has
only five days left to live.
Huh...?
Wh-What's this?
Seems the time has come...
Good luck.
I'm sure you can
bring back their bond.
And I look forward
to seeing how you turn out...
...knight of Avalon.
I hope you can ride me soon...
Is this... the infirmary?
Fafnirite?
Oh, right...
from the healing magic.
Wh-Why are you--
Your temperature was dropping,
so I thought I'd warm you up.
Er, uh, th-thanks.
Oh, hey, Lucca!
I talked to Gawain!
Huh?
I don't know
if you'll believe me, but...
All to protect me?
Yeah. He was thinking
about you this whole time.
And now... because of what I've done...
Get a hold of yourself!
Gawain's not long for this world.
He has maybe five days left.
This is... the sixth day of camp...
Already?!
We've got to get to Gawain right away.
We have to think about him now, and only him!
Just like he was thinking about you!
O-Okay...
Could this be...
A hidden dragonkind chamber?
How marvelous!
The fruit of their history and culture!
It can't be--
The Old Covenant?
I thought this was banned ages ago...
"Two great bloodlines broke off
from the wise dragon king Imbolc:
"the sacred empire of Avalon
and the dark kingdom of Nehalennia.
"These two houses
fought one another unceasingly..."
All that really happened,
in the Zono Toen era.
You're those Imperial--
Stop. Your power is no match for mine.
It's always been that way, hasn't it...
Ann?
Th-That nickname!
Prince... Julius?
What now?
I don't care. Kill her.
Master Milgauss?!
Damn you...
Think you can stand in my way, do you?
Leave her. Instead...
I shall unleash Necromancia.
Y-Yes, sir!
Ash!
Ow! Eco?
You idiot! I thought you were a goner!
Don't be wandering off
where your master can't see you!
Ow! Ow ! That hurts!
I can't breathe! Ouch!
Give her this.
She's been worried sick for five days.
Too worried to sleep, in fact.
Has she?
I'm sorry, Eco.
At least you've come back around.
L-Lucca? What is it?
I-It's him--it's Gawain--
Gawain--he's--
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Joy! Joy! Joy! First-class, right? Bomb!
Bomb! Bon! Cute! Bon! Bon! Bonsoir?
Gimme a supernova named love
Joy! Joy! Joy! So cliché
Dabba dabba poppi poppu--do
some scat then I'm outtie
Bomb! Bomb! Just more carnal desires?
Showing the chink in your manly façade--how
much girly cherishing can you do?
Can't you feel?
Gotta say it in your own words--
"Hear, hear!" "Here?" "Where?"
"How are you still a Homo sapiens?"
Drum up a lovestorm (One chance) An
avant-garde rhapsody (Oh, one more chance)
Compete, compete, compete!
Refresh my love--the mostest more than most!
Natural-born dreamer (Wonder)
Don't want it to fizzle out (Oh, falling down)
Not coming? Then I'll pull ya!
"That's premeditated crime!" (Big love)
Ain't it su-su-su-su-super awesome?
Top-quality training in love
Makes me wanna
kiss-kiss-kiss-kiss ya, so watch close!
Yes! Rockin' on!
"Next Time..."
Cosette Shelley here.
Raise your hand if the word "maid"
makes you think naughty thoughts!
What brought this on?
Come now, Ash--raise your hand!
Aren't you listening?
Ooh, you're such a perv!
This is just like it was with Lucca.
"Next Episode: Dragon Dance"
But I like you. Tee-hee!
Oh, is that so. Wait, what?