"A giant robot that only we
can build!" I believe we have
succeeded in creating a
robot that is faithful to
that idea and imbued
with our passion.
Thanks to each of you!
Now for the big moment. Da da
DA! The "Let's make a life-size
version of GUNVARREL"
project, Mark 2.
Or just GunBuild-2, for short!
What's that stuff it's
got stuck to its head?
It's a small but necessary
symbol of my defiance.
A robot has
no need for a face.
But its face is
part of its identity!
I believe we've already been
through all this numerous times.
Or have you developed a
more convincing rebuttal to
my well-reasoned arguments?
If so, I'd like to hear it.
You big jerk!
Hey! Stop, will ya?
You guys ready? Let's do this.
The start-up test?
Now? What about Tennoji?
She's not here yet.
You know the rule
about working on the robot.
We're not supposed to
operate it without supervision.
We can still go over all
the pre-launch information.
Okay. Yashio.
You're the operator.
Daitoku. You're
the sub-operator.
Yeah, that's right!
Furugori, you're the
drive system supervisor.
NO U, thnx!
But. We discussed this!
D00d, IJK. Plz continue.
The most unique aspect
of the Mark 2 is its...
monopole motors... which give
the unit certain advantages.
Its maneuverability,
for example,
far surpasses
that of the Mark 1.
Operation is remote,
using the KILL-BALLAD system.
The monopoles are amazing.
Although, I think we were all
surprised when they started
falling from the
sky every morning.
Now, we needed to use
one additional piece of
equipment that was not
found in the Mark 1. Namely.
A laser power transmitter!
Man, it's big.
Is that a canon?
It converts electricity
into a laser beam
as a way to transmit power.
Kai, Jun, as operators,
you're in charge of it.
Huh?
Be very careful.
Don't point it at anyone.
Okay, but what would
happen if it hit somebody?
Then they would die.
No. No! No, no,
I don't wanna!
Yeah, same here. It's
too dangerous. I'll pass.
Don't worry. It has
a safeguard in place.
It will only discharge when
aimed at the satellite dish.
It's plenty safe.
R-Really?
You're great at this sort
of thing. You should be fine.
Actually, it's fighting
games that are my specialty.
Shooting games are
another thing entirely.
Hey, you guys!
Oh there you are, Nae! I'm
glad you could make it out.
Sorry I'm late.
I was in a meeting,
and it ran a little long.
A meeting? On Sunday morning?
Oh. Well, yes.
Okay, now. The start-up test!
Are you guys ready to get going?
You can do it! Yeah!
Right!
Well? Now?
Yeah.
Fire!
Wow! Amazing!
The b-battery is
ch-ch-charging, OK!
'Kay, Subaru! Set it down!
Alright, I'm on it!
We're all set up, Nae.
We just need the final call.
What d'ya say?
Are we ready to begin?
Yes! The start-up
test is a-go!
Okay, powering up!
Prepare for lift off!
S-Skeletal GUNVARREL
has started up.
OS is f-f-functioning normally.
D-Deploying laser scanners!
Detaching crane cables!
This is it, Kai, time to
take the historic first step.
'Kay. I'll just start
off by moving it forward.
Roger that.
Okay, GUNVARREL.
Let's do this!
Well? What d'you think?
It's amazing!
Wow! It's incredible!
You would never guess that this
was made by high-schoolers!
I knew all along what
you guys were capable of!
There is one thing.
What? What's wrong?
Unfortunately, it looks like
the club, and the Mark 2,
will have to be completely
moved out of here by next week.
Huh? Moved out?
What do you mean?
You know that meeting
I mentioned earlier?
Well, they've just scheduled
the first rocket launch
from Tanegashima
in five years.
Oh!
Really?
Really. So, for security
reasons, we can't allow you to
continue using this
as your workspace.
I know it's
disappointing. I'm sorry!
Wow! So baby soft!
Since the twenty-fifteen
Crash, our company has
taken extra precautions.
Our powered suits are
fully protected from
solar storm EM waves.
If the suits are so safe,
what was the cause of
the wide spread
malfunction last summer?
I can't comment on that
while the trial is underway.
Sometimes I can't
decide if I'm more amazed
or dismayed by the chief.
This is the promotional
video she developed.
She'll submit it
to the expo committee.
This should be good.
From Chuo-Tanegashima
High's Robot Research Club.
Club leader Akiho Senomiya.
I'm eighteen years old.
Why did I dream of
building a giant robot?
Because giant robots
are adored by everyone!
are children's heroes!
Because giant robots
are defenders of justice!
Because I love giant robots!
And I hope you do, too!
The attack on the Diet
Building changed things.
GUNVARREL's image in particular
was hurt and people have
started to become leery
of robots in general.
Maybe some people are
frightened. But not Aki.
Are you there, Gezi?
What is it, Yashio?
Give me the candidates
for today's search.
Yes. The search for
Kimijima Report Number Seven.
The candidates for
today are as follows:
Homan Shrine.
Kumano Beach.
A rocket launch.
Cape Kadokura.
Yeah! Alright!
Go, Hot Dog, go!
Listen. Years from now,
when you're all grown up,
I want you to be a man
with the "right stuff."
That old thing?
It's just a
giant piece of junk.
Forget about him.
Forget about Kou Kimijima.
Stop poking around.
These are logs of Twipo
posts made from Tanegashima.
Though it was quickly
deleted, there was a post
referring to Kou Kimijima.
It was posted by Junna Daitoku
and deleted at the
behest of Kaito Yashio.
I gave you an order
to investigate this boy.
Yet, somehow,
you failed to find this?
My apologies, sir.
Apparently, he not only
attends your alma mater,
but he's also good friends with
your little sister. Interesting.
You think I'm protecting him?
If you'd like me to,
I'll dispose of him myself.
No. There's no need.
Mr. Nagafukada
certainly is late.
I w-want to go home.
Where's Yashio?
I went to his house to get
him, but he was long gone.
Where could he hav--
Koujiro! Your skirt!
Subaru! Don't even
think about looking!
M-My back is turned!
What nonsense!
Are you really sure
we should be doing this?
We'll only move it around
a bit. It's important.
We don't have much time
before the next screening.
Doesn't look like it's
around here, either.
Huh? I found it.
That's kinda weird.
It wasn't there a second
ago. Well, it's here now.
Gezi. Are you sure that
this is Report Number Seven?
Yes. Would you like
me to download it?
I've come this far, right?
I can't just turn back now.
Yes, Gezi. Download the--
Stop what you're
doing, Kai. Now.
Mizuka, hey!
Come on, Mitchi.
Where are you?
Uh. Hey guys, I think--
Hold on a sec.
What's the matter, Jun?
Is there a problem?
Well, something seems off
each time it takes a step.
Huh?
"Off," how?
It's like, when it moves its
legs, they get stiff like this
for just a second
before they set back down.
Could the motor gears have
gotten stripped somehow?
What do you think?
Not sure, but I'll take
a look. You run the laser.
Why are you here?
I told you, you shouldn't
go sticking your nose
where it doesn't belong.
Now just do what I told you
and forget about this already.
What're you talking about?
Wait a second. You mean
the Kimijima reports?
Go home, Kai.
Find a new hobby.
Or are you talking about
Kou Kimijima himself?
Please, Mizuka. You
know something, don't you?
Just let it go!
Th-That ringtone. What?
Okay, make it walk, please!
Yeah, you're right.
It does seem like it's
teetering a little bit now.
But why?
Maybe it doesn't
have enough power?
All systems show normal.
That's it! Keep it going!
Are you okay?
Look out!
"Kagome, Kagome!" But why now?
Who is this?
Mizuka, where are you going?
Huh? What the? I'm not-!
What is this? What the hell?
Hey, come back!
We're not done talking.
Kai! I really hate to ask,
but, uh, could you gimme a hand?
Do wha?
Uh. It's my suit.
Thing seems to be actin' up.
I can't get it to stop walking.
It's moving all by itself?
What's happening?
If the suits are so safe,
then what was the cause
of the widespread
malfunction last summer?
Oh god! No!
Mizuka!
Kai!
Crap! What the hell?!
Hurry, Mizuka! Shut it down!
I already tried that!
It won't turn off!
Please, don't let
go of me, Kai!
Mizuka! Are you okay?
Thank you, Kai.
I really owe you one.
C'mon, quick.
We need to get this off.
No, not again!
Kai. It's all right.
No, it's not all right!
You have to let go.
It'll only take you with me.
Stop!
Mizuka!
Listen, Kai.
Please. If you
ever get to see Misa.
Aki! Kai!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Tell her. Tell her thanks
for giving me these legs.
Following the
accident with Gunbuild 2,
the Robot Research
Club is disbanded.
Powerless to act, Aki falls
into a severe depression.
The club members drift
away. Heartsick and weary,
Kai investigates the
cause of Mizuka's death.
Unwilling to allow Aki to give
up, he challenges her to battle.
Episode 17.
Let's hit it off everybody!
Later days!