Whoa! How much?!
Man, those don't come cheap.
Even the less expensive models.
It'd cost a lot
less just to get the parts
and assemble it myself,
but with two weeks,
we don't have time for that.
Even with an advance on
my allowance,
I can't afford these!
Well, then, I guess
that only leaves one option.
Yeah? What's that?
Forget about
entering ROBO-ONE altogether.
You jerk!
Come on!
Not while I'm eating!
How can you even think of
admitting defeat so quickly?!
We hafta fight
for all we're worth!
What's the point?
The tournament's
just two weeks away!
And besides, I don't see how
we're gonna take
first place when
we don't even have
a robot to enter.
That's it!
What is?
We do have a hobby
robot to work with!
Where?
In the club room!
The Robot Research
Club's "Honorary Chief"!
The Tanegashi Machine!
Come on! Work!
That thing's what,
eight years old now?
Of course it isn't gonna work.
Genki's bravery gave
GUNVARREL strength, remember?
You can do it! I know you can!
Work, GUNVARREL!
The most likely problem
is that the battery's dead.
And we don't have a charger.
So buy a new one, right?
They probably cost a lot.
You sure you wanna
dismantle it like that?
It's fine, I'm just
taking out the screws.
Hey, would you do me a favor and
go find a servo
test board for me
in the storeroom next door?
No problem.
Right after you
beat me at KILL-BALLAD.
Come on, Kai.
I'm not asking much.
Go see the storeroom
and then tell me
if you're not asking much.
Lazy!
Okay, I'll take care
of finding a test board.
And all you have to
do is be the operator.
The operator, huh?
The one who's in charge of
Tanegashi Machine's controls.
I just figure since you're
always playing KILL-BALLAD,
you've gotta be
way more used to
that kinda thing than me.
I'd rather play KB.
What if I rig up
a cannon for it?
That'd be cool.
Would you operate it then?
Why would you want
to add a cannon?
Just for decoration.
A good appearance is vital
for maintaining
positive club morale!
I'd love to give it
super-special attacks
and the ability to transform!
Hey, Aki.
What's up?
What's more important?
The appearance or the results?
The results.
Yes. Good girl.
Okaaay! I get it already!
I think we can set
all the little stuff aside,
at least for the moment.
The main issue
is the power supply,
and we can't just switch
to a different power source.
What're you gonna do?
That's simple!
I'm going to negotiate!
Hi! Is anybody home?!
Doc!
Hey!
The music! It's really loud!
Can you turn down the music?!
It's bad enough that
you're old and deaf!
Do you have to--
Hey there, Doc.
How're you doing?
I already gave you some parts
the other day, little girlie.
I got nothin' else to
sell ya. What about you, boy?
Too good to say hello?
Oh. It's good to see you again.
Anyway, we didn't
come down here today
to get parts for GunBuild-1.
We're here about this.
Oh? ROBO-ONE, again, huh?
I can tell ya right now,
there's no way
to get a hold of
somethin' this old anymore.
Oh, really?
You gotta go with a
different manufacturer.
How's an Ogawada
S-Plug sound to ya?
Well, uh, how much are those?
A little over eight thousand.
No deal! That's way too much!
That's knocking off
shipping for you!
You and your damn club.
Hey, there's no reason
to get nasty about it!
All right, little girlie.
Are there any
other parts you need?
I'll think
about lowering the price
if you make a big purchase.
Really, you will?!
In that case,
I'd like a three hundred
and sixty-degree camera!
You idiot. A camera
isn't even a good decoration.
"I'll be frank, here.
I don't like it one bit."
Right. For ROBO-ONE,
you'll want a gyro.
Including the other thing,
I can do twelve thousand.
Or maybe you could
make it ten, instead?
This is pointless. Deal's off.
Please, I don't have any money!
I'm just a poor
little high school student!
That's it! How 'bout
a student discount?!
Forget about it!
I got a livin'
to make here, ya know!
You don't like it,
you can leave!
Well, do you have a plan B?
He made it pretty
clear you won't be getting
any parts from him unless
you can come up with the money.
What about you?
Maybe you can get an
advance on your allowance.
No problem, just beat me at KB.
You can be a real
pain sometimes, you know?
Preparing for ROBO-ONE?
Everyone at school's
been talking about it.
About how slim
your chances are.
Let 'em talk!
It's worth the risk.
If we do win, we get
a ton of money for the club!
That's sweet, but it's
never going to happen.
The ROBO-ONE
tournament is prestigious.
Third-rate amateurs entering
at the last
minute is, well, rude.
This is the stuff
that legends are made of!
It all began when I sought
the help of Subaru Hidaka,
who took third place at
ROBO-ONE in junior high--
I won't join your club.
Rejected once again!
Why are you
doing this, Yashio?
You know her club is
nothing but a waste of time.
Yeah, I guess you're
right but the club room
is the perfect environment
for playing KILL-BALLAD, so--
What?!
That's why you're a member?
Interesting.
I see that your reputation
as a pair of weirdos
is well deserved, indeed.
Goodbye.
Hold on. You're leaving?
What did you
come here for, anyway?
No reason. I was
just passing by, that's all.
I hope you enjoy the final
days of the Robot Research Club.
You jerk!
You can't just
say that and drive off!
Well, jerk or not, he kinda
does have a point, you know?
I mean, spin it
however you want,
but there's
no way we're gonna win.
How can you say that?
What'll happen to GunBuild-1?
There's no reason you can't
keep working on it on your own.
That's true, I can,
but I wanted it
to be something
the club did, you know?
After all, it was my
sister who founded this club
and began work on GunBuild-1
in the first place.
It should be the
club that finishes it.
We'll fight! We just have to!
Robots exist because
of dreams, hopes, and passion!
Ah, man. What's her deal?
And she calls me
a pain in the neck.
You will look out
for Aki for me, won't you?
Thanks for coming in.
Oh, it's just you again.
I'd like a Passion Fruit Bun.
You got it.
All in one go.
I can do this!
Mercy!
The lukewarm dough
conceals a sickly sweet
and sour filling that
explodes after one bite
and violently
assaults the mouth.
Passion fruit is
delicious on its own,
but preparing it like this.
It's an invention of the devil,
from the very pits of hell!
There!
All right, then.
We have reached
a Passion Accord agreement,
but can't you at
least pretend like
you enjoy them
a little bit?
No way.
Just keeping 'em
down is hard enough.
Well, whatever.
The Accord
still stands, anyway.
You can ask me one
thing you want to know.
I wanna know more about Doc.
Doc? The crotchety
old robot man?
Yeah, I was wondering
if he has any weaknesses.
Something that'll make him lower
his prices, no questions asked.
You're gonna
blackmail the geezer
into giving you
a discount? That's hilarious!
Sure, no problem,
I'll see what I can find.
I appreciate it.
Well, I'll see ya.
I've noticed the favors you ask
always have
something to do with Aki.
I'm curious. What are you
to that girl anyway?
Dunno. A replacement for
her big sister, Misa, maybe?
Now that she's not around.
He's a good kid.
Aki's lucky to have him.
So's Misa, for that matter.
Daitoku?
In the class
next door. You know,
that quiet girl
who's in the Karate club.
Wait, I'm confused.
Isn't Doc's family name Fujita?
She may have a different name,
but apparently
she's Doc's granddaughter.
Granddaughter, huh?
If she'll ask him for us,
maybe we'll get lucky!
Normal people sit
down to eat, you know.
Okay! You said she's
in Class 1, right?
Thanks for the information.
It should help.
Stop by if you need anything.
I have plenty of passion fruit
buns just waiting to be eaten.
Oh, one more thing.
I know. I won't
tell Aki about it.
All right. My work
here is done.
Hey, Daitoku!
Huh? My grandfather?
I'm sorry to ask
for something like this,
but I don't know
what else to do.
Our club will get shut down
unless I can get all
the parts we need from Doc!
Pretty please!
I'm sorry, but I can't.
Huh?
It's just that, well I mean,
I haven't even
seen Grandpa Fujita
in years so, you know.
It would be weird.
Oh, really? But--
I'm sorry. Oh,
forget about it.
I was just hoping
for a teensy little discount,
but it's no big deal.
I can't help.
Hey, you know,
I've been trying to come up
with some special attack
techniques for the club robot.
Do you know any
good karate moves?
Something you use
to level an opponent.
I dunno, maybe a move that
you're especially good at doing?
A move I'm good at doing?
Yeah!
There are none. Sorry.
What? So not a single one, huh?
Well, what about a kata? You
must be good at one of those.
Let me see. I'm okay at the
"Suparinpei" kata, I guess.
Whoa! That sounds awesome!
How does it go?
Will you tell me?
Oh, but it's
probably more involved
than what you're looking for,
and I'm not really
all that good at it, anyway.
If all you want
is to knock someone down,
maybe a front kick?
A front kick?
How does it work?
Oh, well, you go like this.
Oh! You raise your leg up
like this, and then you just-
Hey, are you okay?
Ow ow ow ow ow.
That's perfect!
A robot can totally
do that! Here, watch me.
Like this, and this!
That's good, um,
but I should tell you.
Your panties are showing!
Huh?
Here you go.
One battery,
complete with charger.
Oooh! Sooooo shiny!
Hope yer happy!
I rushed to get 'em for ya,
then I don't hear
anything for a whole week!
That isn't
my fault. I was busy.
My mom spent the whole
week lecturing me.
The cash?
Hey. Hey, let go already!
Come on! You can knock
off a little bit, can't you?
You little thief.
Take your goods.
You money-grubbing geezer!
Like I said before,
I got a living to make.
I also ordered you a gyro
and some other parts
I thought you'd need.
If you're really
serious about winning,
you should take all of it.
Oh-ho!
That'll be 15,000 total.
Look, I can't pay you,
but I'll do whatever you want!
That does exclude anything
painful or perverted, though.
Like anyone would bother
with an infant like you.
What are those,
raisins on your chest?
Watch it, old man!
I could sue you for that!
We'll pay you when we get
the ROBO-ONE prize money.
Should be plenty
for those parts.
Does that work for you?
Wow, Kai. I didn't
think you knew how to be cool.
So, what do you say, Doc?
Do we have a deal?
You kids have
no respect these days.
Even so. You guys rock.
Aki started working
like crazy after that.
Sometimes she'd do
research on her own,
other times
she'd ask Doc for help.
She spent every second
assembling Tanegashi Machine,
barely even sleeping.
She worked so hard
I started to worry.
'Kay, I'm here.
You're late.
You dragged me
out of a warm bed
on a Sunday morning to
help you. I'd say I'm early.
Is that the
finished product, then?
Yep! Behold! The rebirth
of Tanegashi Machine!
I call it
Tanegashi Machine Advance!
Looks like you
found all the screws.
That's the first thing
you say? Yes, don't worry.
I got Doc to order the
necessary replacements for me.
Ah, so some really
did go missing, huh?
Look, all that matters
now is that it's finished.
So, are you ready? It's time
to test the competitor.
Now that is pretty cool.
Isn't it? I made it so
that when it's turned on,
all its servo-motors
reset to their home position.
Wow.
Okay! It's time to show off
what it's really
capable of! There!
Well, no, that's not it.
Let's see. Oh, urgh-
What's the problem?
Whoa. That's a lot
of switches.
I didn't know
it was so complicated.
Can you do this?
I hear it was too complicated
for most people back then, too.
In fact, my sister
was the only one
who ever
managed to master it.
But once she had, she beat
one opponent after another!
It was nearly
impossible back then,
and now you're gonna try to
get it down in just one week?
Well, yeah.
"I can see the enemy waiting.
It's as clear as day!"
There's no way.
Why don't you help
me instead of giving up
like a stupid, stupid coward!
Man down.
There! That's perfect.
Now watch this!
Whoa.
Cool, huh? It's called
Killer Technique:
Tanegashi Accel Impact!
You ripped that off.
It got brakes?
Sure doesn't.
Go after it, Kai!
Huh?!
Aw, man. No use.
Maybe it's time
to give in and call it a day.
Hey. I really think
you should be the one
to operate it
at the tournament.
Won't make any
difference who operates it.
The thing's
way too complicated.
But you've got quick fingers.
You're about
as fast as my sister.
Just because I'm good
at KILL-BALLAD, doesn't--
Wake up, Aki.
Oh, whoops. Sorry.
You feeling okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Hey.
You aren't fine though,
are you?
Sorry. It's happening.
What should we do?
Wanna leave?
No. Here is okay.
The "Elephant-Mouse Syndrome."
It's like pressing
fast-forward.
Whenever Aki has an attack,
she experiences
five minutes worth of
time in just one second.
It first started
happening after the accident.
Nine years ago.
Kai. Kai.
Hey!
Is it over?
Yeah.
I'll call your mom
and let her know.
This happens
when you're exhausted.
You need to learn not to push
yourself so hard... Got it?
Yeah, yeah.
You just had an attack,
you don't get to be defensive.
So, Kai. What'd ya say?
Will you please
take over as the operator?
Without me having
to beat you at KB?
Man, you don't play fair.
Fine. I'll do it.
Huh? Really?!
Yeah, really. But only if
you'll change the controller
to be more like KILL-BALLAD.
Is that possible?
I don't see how.
I think we can do
it. I know somebody
who might be able to help.
FRAUKOUJIRO?
He's the creator
of KILL-BALLAD, remember?
Which means he
should have access to
all of the game's
programming code.
There's no harm in asking him
about it, don't you think?
No, none at all!
All right!
Now I'm really fired up!
Whoa. Take it easy.
You're still exhausted.
I'm fine!
We have no time to waste!
Contact him immediately!
Okay, okay.
Aki and Kai head
to Tokyo to compete
in the ROBO-ONE tournament.
Their destination
is a large arena
in the metropolis of Odaiba,
filled with fierce competitors
from around the country.
Bearing the legacy of
Misaki, a former champion,
the two enter
the ring to represent
Chuo Tanegashima High School.
At stake is their right to
continue the GunBuild-1 Project,
but when the Pleiades shine,
something inside Kai
will be set off!
Episode 3!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!