Sounds like they're
heading your way this evening.
They're gonna be
spending the night there.
Oh.
You agreed to meet up with
them while they're there, right?
Have you called Aki?
Come on, Misa.
She really misses you.
How hard would it be
for you to see her?
I mean, really. It's not like
you've got a man or anything.
Look, just call her, alright?
She's your kid sister.
Whoa! There are ads everywhere!
We're in Tokyo,
for sure. Oh hey, Mitchi?
That's "Mr. Nagafukada" to you.
We'll check in first,
but afterwards,
can we go out for a bit?
Go out? Sure, why not?
I don't think
that'll be a problem.
Really?!
Yeah. You wanna know why?
'Cause we aren't gonna check in
anywhere in the first place.
No way.
Are we seriously gonna spend
the whole night
in this restaurant?
When you got no money,
you got no place to stay.
That's how it is.
Not a tip from me to you,
just the way o' the world.
You understand?
Could you be
more useless, Mitchi?
What?!
Hey. Let's get outta here.
It doesn't matter where
you play your game, right?
No, not up in the city.
The connection here's
better than on the island,
and there's almost no lag.
Makes the game
way more responsive.
Then come on.
Go with me to the BYC-DAM!
What do you mean?
They have a
life-sized BYC-DAM here.
It's on display
in Hamakaze Park.
Well, too bad.
Okay, now watch this maneuver.
Forward, crouch button,
and punch.
Oh! GUNVAL Uppercut!
And then he can do
this little move, too.
That's amazing!
If I was going to operate it,
I wanted our robot to have
the same controls as KB.
Surprisingly enough,
FRAUKUJIRO,
the game's creator,
quickly agreed to help out
and sent the programming code.
From there, it wasn't too hard.
Despite all my doubts,
we actually pulled it off.
We managed to
finish Tanegashi Machine
and get it ready
to fight in just one week.
Wow. There are
so many lights in the city.
I can't see the stars at all.
Yeah, bummer.
Huh?
But that's still easy to see.
Yeah.
She wouldn't still be at
work at this point, would she?
Well, it is pretty late.
Sister.
Not tonight.
We'll get in touch
with her tomorrow,
after the match is over.
The future of our club
hangs in the balance.
I need to focus on that.
Sure, okay.
Now, let's amp things up!
Tanegashi Accel Impact!
Here we go again.
What's up? Is something wrong?
No. It's nothing.
The rules are very simple.
Knock your opponent
to the ground or out of the ring
three times to claim victory.
Your first battle is
against Devil Stronger.
I hope you're ready, Kai.
It was a finalist last time.
Hmm.
What kind of a response is that?
This'll be a tough opponent!
But if you do defeat him,
you're gonna be a hero!
What's the point
in even worrying about it?
It's all about
taking first place, right?
Nothing else matters.
I guess you can
look at it that way.
Ah, man. This is bad, It's even
worse than it was yesterday.
Chuo Tanegashima High School
to Ring Number 4, please.
Well. Sounds like
it's time for us to go.
Oh, hey, Aki.
Ya got any candy?
Oh, are you talking
about Space Candy?
Yeah, I think so.
Only one, though.
Here.
Mm. That's the stuff.
Ugh, to each his own, I guess.
Well, let's go.
We have a fight to get to.
Okay!
Let's win this.
In the blue corner,
Chuo Tanegashima
High School Robot
Research Club's
Tanegashi Machine Advance!
And in the red corner, Shizuyama
Maekawa's Devil Stronger!
Surprise, surprise! A finalist
from the last tournament
has finally entered the ring!
ROBO-ONE doesn't
have different divisions?
Not anymore.
Don't worry, though.
It's just like he once said:
"I will tell you very
something important.
A unit's performance
is not solely determined
by its brute strength!" Eh?
Lemme get this straight.
What yer implyin' is that
yer boyfriend there is
a better operator than me?
It sounds like the little
lady's controlling you, boy,
and not just in the ring.
If you know what I mean.
Wha?!
It's okay, Aki.
Let this idiot babble.
You don't bother me, pal.
That kind of empty trash talk
is exactly what you expect
from a guy who's about to lose.
What're you saying?
I thought I was
pretty clear, actually.
Hmph. Think you're hot stuff?
I'll slaughter you!
Kai. Destroy him.
Huh?
Crush the jerk!
Justice shall prevail!
Ready. Fight!
Whoa, it's slow!
This should be a cinch!
GUNVAL Uppercut!
Oh! Devil Stronger is down!
What an unexpected turn!
Hey, Aki.
You think you could stop
shouting out the attack names?
Why?! Special moves
are meant to be shouted out!
Yeah, that was
just beginner's luck.
Don't get cocky, kid.
You're screwed.
No way! I can't believe it!
Yes, it's Devil Stronger's
"Double Lariat from Hell!"
Die!
Kai! He's doing
something major!
No big deal. He's got the
robot's upper body spinning
around like crazy. That makes
its lower body unstable.
Which means-
Got him!
No. No way!
That's the match!
Devil Stronger can't continue!
Tanegashi Machine Advance
has destroyed the competition!
A new ROBO-ONE hero
has been born, folks!
They have some
interesting moves, indeed.
What do they teach at
Chuo Tanegashima High School?
Isn't that your alma mater?
Yes.
It all happened
pretty fast after that.
We passed through
all the qualifying rounds
without a hitch,
and tore through the
championship rounds, too.
Before we knew it, we'd
made it to the final match.
Everyone was talking.
Implementing the KILL-BALLAD
control system was big news,
but not as big as the fact
that Aki was the sister of Misa,
a former ROBO-ONE champion.
Crazy. This almost feels
like a dream, doesn't it?
You're surprised?
You're the one who was so sure
we were gonna win.
Yeah, I know what I said,
but- Mr. Pleiades is amazing.
He already has two
tournament wins under his belt.
This isn't gonna be
an easy win.
Kai?
You, look rough.
You feeling okay?
Not exactly. I barely slept
at all yesterday, too.
What's with that
funny look on your face?
Oh, you gotta go?
The bathroom's just
down the hall a little.
You jerk!
Hey! What did I do now?
I'm sorry. I realize
this is all my fault.
I'm the one who
dragged you into this.
Chuo Tanegashima High School.
You're needed onstage.
Yeah, okay. Let's go, then.
There's no point
in thinking about what
we could've done differently.
Ridiculous optimism, remember?
Don't lose that now.
Yeah, you're right.
We have made it this far,
all thanks to you, and we only
have to win one more time.
Then we can return home
with our heads held high!
You're always so confident.
I'm not sure if I'm
really feelin' it this time.
Yes huh!
Oh, all right.
I suppose I can
give it my best shot.
In the blue corner, Chuo
Tanegashima High School's
Tanegashi Machine Advance!
This team has shot
its way straight through
to the finals on the strength
of Misaki Senomiya's legacy
and a revolutionary
control system!
Can the Robot Research Club
recapture the glory
of eight years ago?
Man, big audience.
And they're so loud.
Everyone is really fired up.
In the red corner is
Mr. Pleiades' M45! Ready?
A mysterious comet
blazing onstage,
destroying everything
in its path!
No opponent in history
has ever escaped his clutches!
The two-time ROBO-ONE champion!
Mr. Pleiades!
Alcion... Electra...
Maia... Tiegeta...
Celaeno... Asterope... Merope.
By the blessing
of the Seven Goddesses.
I now make my advent
of four hundred light years.
I am...
Mr. Pleiades!
One minute! That's how
swiftly I shall end this.
Ooh! Pleiades has
already claimed victory!
That guy looks, familiar.
Victory in one minute?!
You have to say
something back! Kai!
No need to shout, Senomiya.
Take it from me.
Keep your cool.
Mitchi...! When the heck
did you get here?
Snazzy costume, but, um-
You're actually
Subaru Hidaka, right?
No. I am not.
Who is this "Subaru"?
What do you
think you're doing?!
Are you crazy?!
Please! It's just so obvious.
They sound exactly alike,
and "Pleiades" is another
word for "Subaru," right?
You think that
cold fish and Mr. Pleiades
are the same person?
There's no way!
That's why I'm surprised.
He's acting so different.
Hey, man, could you take off
your mask for a second?
Oh-ho! The Robot Research Club
comes back with a
challenge of their own!
Contestants, no more talking.
Prepare yourselves!
The final match of ROBO-ONE
will now begin! Ready.
Fight!
Time to assess the opponent.
Given its body type,
grabbing and throwing moves
are probably its specialties.
It'll wait for the enemy
to charge and then throw him.
That's bad manners
in fighting games,
and can ruin your reputation.
Ohh! M45's tackle connects.
Tanegashi Machine
is down! That's one!
What's wrong?
Listen to me, kid,
I get that you're rattled now,
but it's important
that you try to-
Hey, nobody
asked your opinion!
What did you say?!
What, do you want
me to say it louder?!
Keep your stupid mouth shut!
I can read his movements.
All I have to do is
hang in there
and look for my opening.
Once you get too close,
there's just no escaping it!
It's M45's patented
omni-directional attack!
There!
What?!
He evaded the omni-directional!
And to top it off,
he scored a knockdown!
Alright! That was
an incredible move, Kai!
I suppose your KILL-BALLAD
-style control system
does give you
some advantages. However.
This match is
just full of surprises!
The M45 extended its arm!
A secret trump card saved
expressly for the final round!
What else does Mr. Pleiades
have up his sleeve?
Projectile weapons, huh?
That's really cute.
Tanegashi Machine Advance
has two downs.
M45 has one down.
If the challenger is
knocked down one more time,
that's the end of the match!
Kai, look!
Uh-oh, something has happened
to Tanegashi Machine Advance!
One of its legs
is malfunctioning!
Such a disappointment. Yashio.
It's happening!
I can see!
Unbelievable! Those were
what I call serious moves!
What was that new technique?
Tanegashi Accel Impact!
Okay! The move we just
witnessed has a name, folks!
Tanegashi Accel Impact!
Stay here and get me a
detailed report of the match.
And you, sir?
I'm going to pay the
committee a little visit.
You're in
charge while I'm gone.
Still obsessed with it, I see.
You keep on fighting,
even though you
don't have the "right stuff."
That final Tanegashi Accel
Impact did what it was
supposed to do. But it
propelled both competitors
out of the ring. So it counted
as a knockdown for us, too,
and victory slipped
through our fingers.
Frau! Is it really true?
Are you moving here?
Hey, Frau! Frau Koujiro!
Frau who?
Tell us, Frau. Why have you
concealed your identity?
As agreed, the Robot
Research Club is disbanded.
Please remove all of your
things from the club room.
Please, ma'am.
There is nothing more
to say on the matter.
Hey, Aki. If you had the
choice of gracefully accepting
a game-over or
using a continue cheat,
what would you choose?
Use the continue cheat.
I figured as much.
Although I didn't expect you
to answer that so quickly.
I heard my name, and-
The announcement worked!
I had the Broadcasting
Club call you here.
Perfect! Come on in.
Wha-What's going on?
Oh, it's nothing. I just
got a quick favor to ask you.
I looked all over
but I couldn't find any
that were the same,
so I made my own.
You called me here just
to look at some awesome--
I mean some
totally bizarre mask?
You wouldn't mind putting
it on for a sec, would you?
Huh? Forget about it!
I'm not into--
Come on, it looks good.
Get off! Back off man!
So, by the blessing
of the Seven Goddesses-
I now make my advent of
four hundred light years!
I am Mister Pleiades!
Oh no! No fair!
Once I donned the mask,
I couldn't help it!
No way.
You mean they're actually
the same person after all?
Yup and you know
what that means, right?
Chuo Tanegashima
really did win the tournament.
As agreed, the club
gets to stay intact.
Impossible.
No! I do not
bewong to dat cwub!
You look so impressive here,
I thought I'd give this
to the Newspaper Club
and let them know
that the ROBO-ONE champ
is none other than
our very own Subaru Hidaka.
Robot Research Club
will live on.
I just knew we would
do it somehow! Now.
Are you ready, men?
It's finally time for us
to get to work
on our real project!
I didn't agree to this.
If we're gonna have GunBuild-1
ready for the expo,
we're going to need help
from some professionals!
Pros? Like Doc?
Think bigger.
I mean real experts.
We've got some
right here on the island.
And it's time we got in touch!
No. You don't mean--
Yes! We are going to JAXA's
Tanegashima Space Center!
You gotta be kidding me.
Aki and friends
convince the school to let
the Robot Research Club remain
intact. They head to JAXA
to get GunBuild-1 up
and running again.
Unfortunately, they run
into some complications.
A father who likes
to play it safe,
and a prospective sponsor
who only cares about impact.
Meanwhile, a stranger
has moved to the island.
She speaks in Internet slang,
profanity, and lewd suggestions.
Just who in the
world is this girl?
Episode 4!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!