Trevor 1 to Wyvern.
This is Wyvern.
What's wrong, Trevor 1?
Large, moving object
spotted to the northwest.
A large, moving object?
We are unable to get
a data pull from IRUO.
It's over fifteen meters
in height. What should we do?
For now, nothing. You
Trevors are to remain there
on standby, as planned.
Focus on preparing
for the launch.
47 minutes to launch.
Liquid fuel
preparation complete.
Wind speed: one.
No precipitation.
The unknown moving
object is expected to
reach the launch site shortly.
Request use of
missiles to defend.
Request received,
Trevors, but I'll be calling
all the shots out there.
You're to remain at your posts.
You came.
Hello, Misa.
Kai. Misa.
Chief!
Yes, I know.
AR decoys!
Let's go!
So this is a battlefield,
huh? Still, WTG, Sawadie!
Is everybody okay out there?
Yes!
I'm all right!
Plan is successful
so far. The AR decoys work.
'Kay, what now? With the
missiles outta the picture,
the coast is clear,
right? Let's get closer.
No. The missiles won't be
a hundred percent ineffective.
The AR decoys interfere
with IRUO and make the dummies
seem genuine, and the
real one harder to target.
It's basically a
doppelganger technique.
Although the chance
of getting hit is lower,
they could get lucky
and shoot at the real robot.
It's headed your way!
Now, Aki! The button!
Hurry!
Oh, no!
I'm okay.
The Pile Bunker is destroyed.
Still got the one on the right.
Is that all,
Misa? Running away?
SUMERAGI in combat with unknown
object. Rocket status, green.
Continue countdown.
Kay, here we go. I'll charge
when I can. You guys are backup.
Huh?
All right. Down
to thirty minutes.
You can't fire missiles.
Not at this close range.
Isn't that right?
What the hell are those?
Come on, you can do it!
Nothin' to worry about.
He ain't gonna lose.
I tuned that thing myself.
Alright, you monopole
motors! Show 'em what you got!
Alright!
Not yet!
Aki!
Let's go!
GUNVAL Ankh Striker!
Wow, he hit it!
He destroyed the camera section
for sure. That might be it.
Misa! I know you can hear me!
Now come on out.
Come out and tell Aki.
Tell her the real
story now, face to face.
Tell her why
you abandoned her.
I want to hear you tell her
why you said she was mediocre.
Go ahead! Explain
everything to her!
She deserves
to know all of it.
That's why she's chased after
you all this time, to find out.
And now she's caught up!
Kai.
Don't you dare run away!
Unfortunately, it's
too little, too late.
Her mind has already crumbled.
She has nothing more to offer.
I plunged her
into darkness, you see.
What does he mean?
What?
S-Self destruct?
Huh? Look!
The Misaki you thought
you knew is nothing
but a mindless puppet now.
That's all.
My own, dear little puppet.
She can't be gone. No.
This is B Team. We have
re-secured the control room.
Now implementing the plan
to abort the rocket launch.
Stand by.
It's no use.
The rocket cannot be stopped.
Why not?
This is my ultimate experiment
and I mean for it to succeed.
Oh, Kai!
Oh, no!
You guys! Run!
I'm gonna die. Totally
gonna die. Epic death scene.
Hey, is everyone okay in there?
Yeah, we're all right. But that.
It's totally fried.
GunBuild-1 will have to
run on internal batteries.
And they won't last
long. Five minutes or so.
Come in, Akiho! It's
no use. Whatever we try,
it won't accept the
abort launch commands.
Looks like the
admin's blocking them.
Current admin listed as--
It's him. It's Kou Kimijima.
Do you know how much time I've
dedicated to this experiment?
I've literally
given my life for it.
I will make sure it succeeds.
You can count on that.
Uh, WTF?
What is it?
W-W-W-W-W00000t.
Go Sawadie. FTW!
What are you doing, Frau? This
is no time to be goofing around!
I'm not. The program's arrived.
The one for deleting Kimijima.
Really? It's here?
Here are the instructions.
"To activate it, first install,
then lock on to
Kimijima's AR while
he's displayed on the
pad's screen." Sounds simple.
So far but there's
more. And it isn't good.
When you install the program,
you'll also have
to reboot your pad.
Wait, reboot it?
Yeah. And we'll also
have to find a way to
get my sister out
of the cockpit somehow.
If we do that,
Kimijima is sure to show up.
Please, don't notice!
Time remaining. Ten minutes.
It seems he's cut off all
communication with the others.
He must be up to something.
Let's find out what.
Still no reaction?
Here he comes!
He knows what's going on?
No!
This is bad! Yashio's still
in the middle of rebooting.
He can't see anything
the enemy's doing!
Kai.
Chief, no!
Misa. Misa.
Stop, Misa! Don't do this!
Listen to me! Please,
Sis! You know me! It's Aki!
Misa!
Impossible. There's
still something of
your mind remaining?
Aki. Get back!
Okay. Bring it on!
Aren't you gonna attack me?
You know that smiling
person you pretended to be
on TV was just a friendly
fake. You're someone who wins
without showing so
much as a hint of emotion.
A cruel woman who
never shows mercy.
Kai.
I looked up to you for
trying to build a giant robot.
For watching robot anime
even though you're a girl.
But you're just a jerk who drags
everyone into your messes.
Now tell me, do you
seriously think you have
the "right stuff?"
Answer me, Misa!
You keep talking
like that and I swear.
I'll destroy you!
All right. Now it's
time for our game.
I know what's coming, Misa.
It was the same in
every KB game we played!
Aki, now!
It's the same. Always the same.
You always dodge to
the right four frames!
Are you okay?
Pathetic.
What did you expect?
Misaki is gone for
good now. It's all over.
Look at this!
It's GunBuild-1. The robot you
used to work on. Your robot!
Is that really what you
came here to say to me?
It was built with our passion.
Yours, mine,
everyone's on the island.
And it actually works.
It's actually fighting
to save the world!
How amusing. It seems
both sisters have
the same curious
way of thinking.
What's happening?
Think back, Sis. To when
Dad showed me a robot
for the very first
time. Do you remember?
Well, I do. You looked
at me and said...
Aren't they amazing.
I love robots.
More than
anything in the world!
Do you still love them?
Think about it, Sis. Tell me.
Do you still love
them more than anything?
Shut up!
Say goodbye!
I was so close to
succeeding. What a shame.
Just wait. Someday, a
second, a third me will appear.
Yeah, maybe. But...
You still won't
win in the end
because good
will always triumph.
At least that's what
our chief likes to tell us.
Well, who knows.
You may just be right.
I've got you!
Aki.
I'm here, Sis.
Thank you, Aki.
There we go! Kimijima
is no longer the admin.
Entering abort
command. Please work!
Countdown halted. We've
stopped the rocket launch!
W00t!
Ah, man.
Yeah! Ow!
Now that's impact!
Boing boing boing boing!
That's what I call rockin'.
Yes! Alright!
Order. Quiet down,
all of you. Honestly.
Aki! How's she doing?
She'll be okay.
She just fainted, that's all.
Hey. Let's go
back to the hangar!
So, Kai.
What's next? What
do you think you'll do?
What do you mean "next?"
You know, like
after we graduate.
What do you want to be?
Like, when I grow
up? Why do you ask?
No real reason.
Not sure, really.
Who knows what'll happen.
Maybe I'll shoot for the stars.
Huh? What do you mean?
Hey!
Well, Misa. What do you
think? The dream that we had.
The robot we built. It was
more than just a machine.
It became a beacon of hope.
For everyone.
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Lift off!