Yeah, TAKANO_EYE
is totally cheating.
No wonder they're
in first place.
Hey, Airi.
What is it, Yashio?
Oh. I wasn't in Gezi mode.
What're you doing here?
I am here to monitor the
progress of an experiment.
August Eleven,
two-thousand-nineteen.
Today's date.
I am set for observation
to verify a prediction
for Verifacatory Experiment
Number Two Nine Four Six.
Experiment.
One that employs the EGI System.
Oh, that thing that sends beepy
static sounds into the sky?
How's it going?
Do you have any results yet?
Yes. Just now, in fact.
A rock?
Geez! What is that thing?
A magnetic monopole.
Oh yeah! A monopole!
Wait, what is that again?
I'll overhaul it for free.
But you're the one
who installed this piece
of junk without tuning it up.
Don't go pinning it on me.
You're still going to put all
your energy into GunBuild-1?
Of course I am!
How many times have I said
I'm not gonna give up,
no matter what?
What's this you sent me?
It's the results
for some start-up
simulations for GunBuild-1.
I tried to find some way to make
it work in its current state.
It's not going to happen.
The only option is to rethink
everything from the ground up.
Otherwise, it'll just
be a repeat of last time.
It's from Yashio.
A monopole.
Yeah.
So this is a joke, isn't it?
Say that again
after you touch it.
See? You ever seen
a rock like this before?
True, I've never seen
a mineral that produces
an electric charge like that.
But what makes you
say it's a monopole?
Huh? Oh, well,
uh, the thing is.
Actually, what
exactly is a monopole?
Really? You don't know?
I did have it explained
to me, but I'm confused.
By that weird Airi app of
yours or whatever it's called?
You know about? Frau told you.
Yeah, I remain skeptical.
I'm not inclined to
believe so outrageous a claim.
Yeah, I'm not really sure
I believe it, for that matter.
Normally, breaking a magnet
in two will simply create
two smaller magnets,
rather than creating two pieces
with different magnetic poles.
A monopole,
however, only possesses
one magnetic pole:
North or South.
It's said they
could theoretically exist,
but one has never
actually been seen.
It was just lying
here like this?
Well, uh.
To be precise, it fell here.
Like, out of the sky.
There's only this one now,
but according to Airi,
there's a chance more could
come falling down, too.
No way!
You brought Aki
down here with you?
That's not cool, man. I told
you to come alone, didn't I?
Looks like she'd really
like to join us over here.
Why don't you let her?
No way.
And now she seems
utterly forlorn.
Okay, okay. Hey, Aki.
Yes, I'm right here!
Alright, did you hear
everything already?
Yeah! Yeah! That is a mono--
Let's not broadcast
it to everyone, okay?
What's the big idea?!
This is a major discovery
if it's the real deal!
We could sell it for millions.
No, maybe even billions!
Just think!
We could pay off our debt and
buy all the robot parts we need!
This is a bigger
deal than you think.
It's the discovery
of the century!
Or it could be.
Assuming it's actually
the real thing, of course.
It's that awesome a find?
These things appear
often in science fiction.
The theory is
that they're capable
of producing tremendous
amounts of energy.
Producing energy.
This monopole thing's
a magnet, right?
Does that mean we
could use it as a motor?
It's not impossible, but I
don't think having just one
would be enough
for our purposes.
Well, that's it then.
What's it?
Make more monopoles fall.
How do you expect
me to manage that?
A monopole rain dance, maybe?
I see you're finally awake.
You guys! Why'd you
let me fall asleep?
It was easier for me to
concentrate on my game this way.
And it meant not
having to deal with you.
Have you ever heard
the term "sugarcoating"?
What's our monopole status now?
How many more came down?
Not a one.
What?! Airi did say more of
them were going to fall today,
didn't she? Didn't she, Kai?
Sorry, I'm fighting
TAGIRINGER now.
I can't let anybody
distract me. Not even you.
Aki, in the fighting games,
Misa would attack,
and then she'd always swing
to the right, wouldn't she?
I wouldn't know.
Never mind that!
What about the monopole?!
Whoa, it's that late already?
Won't your dad be
angry with you, Subaru?
It shouldn't bother him too much
as long as I'm not
working on a hobby robot.
Forget the
monopoles for a second.
Won't you rethink
the plan with GunBuild-1?
Whatever your convictions,
there is no merit in sticking
to such a hopeless project.
Well, Doc did promise
to fix the engine for us.
That'll help, huh?
Even so, it won't make much
difference. It'll still have a
heavy body it's
barely capable of moving,
so I just don't see any point.
I know, but it's GunBuild-1.
You should just
do what Tennoji said.
Build a new robot
from scratch. Think about it.
You'll even get
support from JAXA.
But...
See you.
Hey, what are you lookin' at?
It's a GunBuild-1
simulation Subaru worked up.
He says however much we
wanna try and modify it
it'll still never be
the robot we imagined.
What'll you do?
Oh, I don't know.
Well, not yet, at least.
But I think we can
be done for the day.
WTF, just kill me now.
Mega Solar Death Ray!
Can you try to walk a little?
I don't know how much
longer I can hold you up.
You smell tera-good,
karate girl.
Ah! Could you
please not do that?!
What is this scent? Vanilla?
Curse you and
your seductiveness! GTFO!
Okay! Today I'm gonna
stay completely hands-off,
so you kids can brush up on
your debating skills. Got it?
Is that just an
excuse for you to be lazy?
If you need me,
I'll be taking a nap.
Be sure to report the outcome
of the meeting
to me, Little Senomiya.
Talk about irresponsible.
It's okay. I make a point of
not expecting much from him.
Let's do this ourselves.
I see. So you haven't
changed your mind, then.
You're still dedicated
to finishing the Mark 1.
Yes. It's about more
than just the five of us.
It represents the hopes and
dreams of years of club members.
I understand. If you're that
determined, then why don't we
spend today taking
a further look into
what we can do about
improving your robot?
If you'll allow me.
I've put together an abstract
in preparation for this.
May I pass out copies?
That's terrific! By all means.
"Causes of the Mark 1's failure
and suggestions
regarding future work."
I apologize for
the poor presentation.
It's not poor at all!
I think you've done a very
professional job with it.
Ugh, try to swallow your
embarrassment and keep going.
Wha-? I'm not embawassed!
Huh, that's a surprise. I never
expected him to get nervous.
Epically virginal.
Now you wisten here, I--
Why don't you
read it for us, Aki.
Then Subaru can go back
and explain anything
we don't understand.
Oh, yeah, okay.
It starts, "Regarding
the Mark 1's failure..."
That's not true!
It didn't fail!
Come on, Aki.
All right, all right. Let's see:
"The chief contributing factors
to the failure were the
lack of technical prowess
and the inability to procure
quality materials." Wow.
Yes. The blueprints
themselves were well executed.
However, due to
insufficient funds,
attempts were
made to compensate,
including the use
of materials not planned
for during the drawing stage.
Chief among these was an engine
with inadequate power output.
But like I said, it didn't fail!
It actually walked!
It was a dud. It's a
miracle it moved at all.
Well, um, it is impressive that
it moved despite its weight.
Yes. Which just goes to show you
how solidly planned out
the original blueprints were.
With that in mind, I have a
recommendation. Start over.
Use this experience
to build a new robot.
Oh? Do you really think so?
But Subaru.
This shouldn't be
news to you, Chief.
I told you as
much the other day.
Moving on. If you will turn to
the next page of the abstract,
I've outlined the key
points of robot constwuct--
Pardon me. The key
points of robot construction:
Basic structure,
materials, power source,
motors, control
mechanism, programming.
Of course, at the very least,
these fundamentals will need
to be constructed on a level
superior to that of the Mark 1.
Well, that goes without saying.
Personally,
I think it'd be great
if the arms and body
could move independently, too.
Yeah! You know, like the M45!
The M45?
The partner of the legendary
ROBO-ONE champion, Mr. Pleiades!
I'm a big fan,
if you couldn't tell.
I think making a giant version
of that robot would
be a super-smart way to go.
How many servo motors does
this hobby robot of yours use?
It needs twenty-four.
That's the first issue
right there. A bigger version
of the same robot
model would need
to have a motor
at each joint, as well.
Their weight alone would be
tremendous, and remember,
making something
ten times as tall
increases its
weight a thousand-fold.
It does, really?
Remember your geometry?
That's how volume works.
Here we have a robot
approximately five times
the hobby robot's size. We can
lighten it as much as possible
by constructing
it out of aluminum,
thereby enabling it
to walk, as seen here.
Giving it that many operational
joints would be very difficult.
We would need to lighten it even
further, and that would require
the use of composite materials,
like diamond film
or carbon fibers.
I don't think that
would really be feasible,
in terms of the
expense involved.
In that case,
I'm afraid it will have
to look something like this.
Huh?!
But that's so lame!
Maybe so, but the Mark 1
was pretty lame, in my opinion.
That's just how it ended up.
It didn't start that way!
However you want to
spin it, lame is lame.
You take that back!
Those two aren't ever
going to get along, are they?
of club members had to
piece it together bit by bit!
This is some good moe.
Give me some room, will ya?
You even admit that it didn't
turn out well. So why do you
still refuse to consider
Hey, could we make
it look like GUNVARREL
on the outside by
using something like this?
What are you talking about, Jun?
Huh? Oh, I just noticed that
Yashio is using some kind of
app on his pad to make you look
like a cute little cat ear maid.
Kai! Again?!
Oh, err.
I never thought of that.
Using AR to alter its
appearance. Interesting.
That could actually
be a possibility.
We could use AR to make this
look like GUNVARREL at the expo.
People would just have
to view it through a pad.
We won't have to worry
about its actual appearance.
I think I see, and when it
moves around, people looking at
their pads will see GUNVARREL
moving around, instead.
That sounds like
an awesome idea!
In other words,
it's a Spirit Bla--
Okay, now we still have
the control
configuration to consider.
Wh-Wh-Why don't we just use
the same system as KILL-BALLAD?
Indeed, that would
be quickest, and, naturally,
that means the
operator should be...
Whoa, whoa, hold it.
I'm not gonna--
Easy. The Mark 2
will use remote controls
and an external power source.
You won't mind
doing it then, right?
Wha?! He won't be in it?!
Of course he won't.
Not when weight is the
biggest issue we're facing.
Subaru!
This makes it possible
for you to build a robot.
One you can take to the expo
without fear of embarrassment.
How did it go? The meeting
with my daughter's club.
It was certainly interesting.
We've got some kinks we'll
have to work out along the way.
I would imagine so.
They're all such unique
individuals, you know,
but that actually
makes them a great team.
I'm sure it'll
work out in the end.
Misa! I'm gonna
do it, you'll see!
I'm gonna join the club
and make your dream come true!
You'll never be anything
more than just mediocre, Aki.
Hey, Aki.
Why're you here?
How many times have I told you
it's important
to get enough sleep?
Honestly. I really do want to
go to the expo with GunBuild-1.
But, I think Subaru's right.
It's not going to happen.
Really?
I know what you think,
but I'm not blind.
I saw the test run.
I realize we've got no
choice but to build a new one.
And I know Subaru's
got the right idea.
It's just
difficult for me to...
Tell me, Kai.
What would you do in my place?
You have to ask yourself:
is your dream to enter
the Tokyo expo or to finish
construction on GunBuild-1?
You're right.
I have to make
that decision, don't I?
Maybe I'm not as
good as you, Sis. But...
I'll do whatever I have to
to make your dream come true!
You can just wait
in Tokyo until I do!
That's not fair Koujiro!
Let someone else have a turn!
GunBuild-2, huh?
The "Let's make a life-size
version of GUNVARREL" project,
Mark 2. Or just GunBuild-2,
for short.
I think it's high
time we move forward
with Tennoji and
Subaru's suggestion.
So, then, you'll be
giving up on GunBuild-1?
No, I'm not. I will
finish GunBuild-1. Later.
But for now, we're going
to build GunBuild-2
and take it to the expo.
All five of us!
All five?
Uh-huh. There's me, you,
also Jun and Frau Bow,
and Subaru, of course.
Very well. Count me in.
Was some reaction
too much to hope for?
After all the heartbreak I went
through making this decision!
Jun, Frau Bow, listen up!
Today the Robot Research Club
will begin work on GunBuild-2.
The theme will be "a giant
robot that only we can build!"
I want there to be parts of it
that only Jun could contribute,
and you, Frau Bow. Something
from every member of the club!
Subaru's ideas.
Kai's control skills.
We'll build a robot that
combines all of these things!
And that's how I want us
to make GunBuild-2: together!
All right! Let's do it!
Sorry, but do what, now?
Haven't you done this before?
Put your hands out, guys!
Robot Research Club,
Spirit Blast!
Let's hit it ooooooffffffff!
Yeaaaaaaah! Huh?
Come on, you guys! Say iiittttt!
Good afternoon! How are you?
Would you like to
hear today's weather forecast?
Still the
same as ever, I see.
It's actually
kind of frightening
how little you've changed.
We have a very
pleasant forecast today.
The Tanegashima region will have
clear skies and winds blowing
in from the east,
with occasional strong gusts.
Tell me, Airi.
Have you been bound here
for nine years straight now?
Airi's sorry,
but she doesn't understand
what you mean by "bound".
Listen, Airi.
Could you please disappear?
The Robot Research Club
now finds itself
building a new robot.
Meanwhile, Kai and Frau
set out to locate another
of the mysterious
Kimijima Reports.
The information in the report
seems too incredible to believe
but too important to dismiss.
Can the report's
assertions be trusted?
Before Kai can decide, a
shocking development further
complicates the situation and
threatens to change everything.
Episode 11!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!