Predicting the weather.
Forecast for
Tanegashima and nearby areas.
Skies will be cloudy.
Showers are likely
beginning in the afternoon,
and continuing on into tomorrow.
Airi thinks there's
going to be a storm today.
I don't get what's happening.
Any of it.
We're somewhere inside
the space center, aren't we?
But why here?
D-Do you wanna know
what happened to me?
I went out to get some food
from the convenience store
near my place, and,
and JAXA was there!
I don't have any idea where
they came from, or why.
Everything happened so fast,
it's all kind of fuzzy.
I'm assuming you
were shoved into a van
without explanation, like us.
P-Pretty much, yes.
Okay. I might know
what's going on here.
I've seen this
sort of thing before.
Hey, Chief, are you
doing a "Gendou Pose"?
Clever boy.
So, where have
you seen this before?
Oh. These abductions happen
all the time in robot anime!
If they follow the normal plot,
it means we've been chosen
to operate a robot of justice!
You really are full
of nonsense, you know that?
Uh. Hi.
You're behind this?!
Hold on, I don't understand,
Dad! What's going on here?
Please. Allow me to explain.
My name is Nae Tennoji.
I am a member of
JAXA ARD's Innovative
Technology Research Center.
Nice to meet you.
And now for the reason
we've asked you here today.
Here it is!
Project name: "Let's build
a giant robot with JAXA!"
Huh?
You want us to work with
you on building a giant robot?
Yes, that's right.
The project's officially known
as the Research Support Project
for Technical
Innovation in Robotics.
Basically, we want to
lend what support we can
to people working
on large-scale robots.
Innovative roboticists
like yourselves, of course.
The goal is to have something to
show at next year's Tokyo Expo.
The expo?!
With that said,
our budget is relatively small.
Smaller than the
tears of a sparrow.
Unfortunately, we'll only be
able to support one project.
And while I was trying to decide
what to go with, I saw ROBO-ONE.
I was impressed. You really
held your own against
the famous Mr. Pleiades in the
final round of the tournament.
As it happens,
Mr. Pleiades has joined us.
Why can't you keep
your big mouf cwosed?
After the tournament,
I ran across the interview
you gave to the Kaiyomi Times.
You spoke so passionately
about your dream
to build a robot that was
more than ten meters tall.
I knew I'd found what
I was looking for!
And, at last, you're here.
I had no doubt all
kinds of organizations
and corporations had
already started courting you.
Because of that, I'm afraid I
went to rather extreme measures
to bring you here in secret.
I do regret that necessity.
You think that many people
would be interested in us?!
Don't you know flattery
when you hear it?
So can you be more specific
about the support
you're offering?
We'll provide
developmental funding.
And, you'll have the
benefit of valuable advice
from our engineers
during the building process.
Hooooboy!
There's gotta be a catch. That
sounds way too good to be true.
Well, at this
point all I can really do
is ask you to trust me.
But something else to keep
in mind. If your completed
robot is well-received at
the expo, you might be asked
to develop other large-scale
robots in the future.
Together with JAXA, you can
build a robot of justice
that will kick all
kinds of bad-guy-butt!
Just like you've always wanted!
Well, what do you say?
Now you're making it
sound like a weapon.
I'm afraid I can't
condone that type of project.
I was just, um, exaggerating.
I like the picture you're
painting! It sounds amazing!
Here we go; it's like
a dog with a bone.
Oh, really? Fantastic!
We had already planned on
entering the expo, anyway.
So why not partner up with
JAXA to do it? Okay, we're in!
That's incredible news!
Now, about the robot
you guys have already
begun constructing...
Do you think maybe
I could have a look at it?
Yes, absolutely!
Unbelievable. You actually
turned down support from JAXA.
I had to.
She wanted us to
put GunBuild-1 on hold
and start on a new robot.
Neat blueprints.
You drew these yourself, Sis?
Is it true? You're really
gonna make a GUNVARREL?!
That's the GunBuild Prototype
Mark 1. GunBuild-1 for short.
Completing GunBuild-1,
that's my dream.
But, making another
robot from scratch?
That's not even an option.
Are you sure, Akiho?
And you, Yashio? What do
you think about all this?
I don't really care.
You won't be getting much
help outta me either way.
Come on, Kai! Are you
really gonna be like that?!
If you want me to help, all you
have to do is beat me at...
You jerk!
More nonsense!
Does it ever stop?
Stupid boys and their stupid...
Look at this weather.
I imagine you'll want to head
home before the storm hits.
Probably. You know,
I wonder, are you positive
that was the right decision?
Not telling Akiho that this was
all your idea to
begin with, I mean. Sir.
It would have been too
embarrassing to tell her.
I'm shocked by
how it turned out.
In a million years, I never
thought she'd reject the offer.
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Not at all!
It was a really
nice thing to see.
A group of friends
getting together
to create something
they're passionate about.
I admire that kind
of drive and conviction.
So I'm not ready to
give up on them just yet.
Hey, Brother!
A typhoon is blowing in.
Yeah, I noticed that.
Airi, tell me something.
What do you know about these
"Kagome, Kagome" phone calls
everyone has
been getting lately?
"Kagome, Kagome"? That's
a song, isn't it, Brother?
I'm talking about the
ringtone, here, not the song.
Maybe Gezi knows
something about it.
Your access has
now been confirmed.
Switch to Gezi
mode was successful.
So all these
"Kagome, Kagome" phone calls.
Do you know anything about them?
They appear to have
occurred throughout Japan.
And what about
the "Kimijima Reports"?
Is there a whole series of them?
Yes. They go up
to Report Number 7.
Whoa, that's more
than I would've guessed.
Do you have any idea
where the other ones are?
All the remaining reports?
Negative, I'm afraid that
neither Airi nor Gezi knows
where all of the
Kimijima Reports are hidden.
Okay, so, you do know
where some of them are, right?
Yes, Kimijima Report
Number 2 is known.
It is located in
the Uchugaoka Park area.
That puts it right around here.
Yes, but do not
bother searching for it.
The Kimijima Report
AR markers will not appear
on your IRUO
display at this time.
And why not?
Each Kimijima report
has flags attached to it,
conditions that must be met
in order to make it visible.
Conditions, huh?
So, I guess the
"Hidden Hand" password
isn't gonna cut it this time.
Hold on a minute.
Hey, Gezi. In what
year did Kou Kimijima die?
Two thousand and ten.
Did IRUO even exist back then?
An alpha was indeed in
development at that time.
Wow. So, Gezi, what are these
flags for making it visible?
Report Number Two flags.
File download
in progress. Please wait.
The requested file has
been successfully downloaded.
First flag: Find and read
Kimijima Report Number One.
Additionally, make contact
with Airi at least once.
Check!
Second flag: Press the green
button beneath the radar dome
located near the old folk museum
and then press it
again one hour later.
Third flag: Compete in
the Uchugaoka Park's
go-kart time
trial and achieve a time
below the
thirty second mark.
Then post and sign your
name on the IRUO geotag there.
Okay, on the fourth and
final flag: Earn a triple-S rank
while playing the arcade mode
of the "Golden Wolf
Fighter IV" fighting app.
Once you have succeeded,
upload your record to
the online leader board.
This is ridiculous!
Why do I have to jump
through all these hoops?!
Only my master knows that.
This is basically one big game.
'Kay, start with the radar dome.
Hey, there really
is a green button.
Whoa! What was that?!
Aw, man.
Why didn't I just go home?
Blast from the past.
Didn't know there
was an app version.
Everybody I knew was playing
this game about ten years ago.
Misa used to wipe the
floor with me when we played.
Got an hour. And since
I don't have anything
better to do to pass the time.
Send!
Oh heck yeah! Flag cleared!
It's been so long
since I played this;
it was actually pretty tough.
Crap, that's bad.
I believe Airi
warned you beforehand
of the typhoon's arrival.
Yeah, she did.
Don't blame her.
What the crap was that?
And what is that thing?
It looks like a
plate from the radar dome!
Typhoons have been
known to damage equipment.
Do you think it's
gonna survive the storm?
There is a risk of
damage to the structure.
And not only to the dome,
but to the antenna itself.
I believe that
opening the dome earlier
may not have been a good idea.
By doing so,
you left it vulnerable
to the wind and the rain.
Great. You're blaming me now?
So? What'll happen
to the second flag
if the dome gets wrecked?
It is possible that you
will be unable to clear it.
Then what? Are you
saying I gotta find a way
to protect the
antenna from the storm?
Beginning shutdown
process for Gezi mode.
How bad is it? Is the tower
going to be okay, Brother?
That's the first thing
you're worried about?
Airi is very worried.
If the antenna breaks,
I'll have one less task to do.
Wait, what do you mean?
My master gave me
various tasks to do.
One of the tasks is to listen
and make sure the
"bee-bee-boo" sound plays
once every day, as scheduled.
And then, after it goes off,
I'm supposed to look for
anything out of the ordinary.
Really? Is that your job?
Yes. I've been doing
it for about ten years now,
but if something
happens to the tower,
that task won't be possible,
and Airi won't have
as much to do anymore.
Man, I really should've
kept my mouth shut.
That's one way
to wake up from a nap.
Hey, Aki! Do you have
any idea where Kai might be?
Wha?
Apparently he hasn't
come home yet today!
Why am I doing this?
I must be crazy!
Airi's just an AI.
Why should I care if some
overblown operating system
gets to keep her job or not...
Damn!
Thank you so very much
for doing that, Brother.
Now Airi can do the
job her master gave her.
You're hurt! Airi wishes
she could make you better,
but that's not
in her programming.
You seem to be
surprisingly calm about this.
Airi's sorry, but she can't
say when the storm will pass.
Airi only has access to
data that has been uploaded
to the IRUO system. So, even
though she wants to very much,
Airi can't comprehend
the pain you must be feeling.
Please, Brother,
you have to stay strong,
just for a little while longer!
Kai! Kai! Wake up! Kai!
Is that you, Aki?
Idiot! Why the heck
are you up on the tower?
Why are you here?
When you didn't
come home, I thought you
might be in the park,
so I came to look for you.
Then a girl named
Airi showed up on my IRUO.
She told me
something had happened,
that you needed help,
and I should come up here.
So, how are we
supposed to get down?
Huh? Uh, don't worry about it.
We've got plenty
of help down below.
Thank you for coming.
I guess I really
owe ya one now, don't I?
This is kinda like on
the Anemone. Just you and me.
I had to get checked out
at the hospital after that.
And then I spent the entire
afternoon today apologizing
to people for all
the trouble I'd caused.
And telling Aki all
about Airi and how we'd met.
And, as for the final flag.
The go-kart course
was long shut down,
but I solved that
problem easily enough
and cleared the flag by posting
a made-up time to the geotag.
And that's how I netted
Kimijima Report Number 2.
NASA was forced into
their scientific cover up
by a body known as the
Committee of Three Hundred,
a group that controls
the world from the shadows.
They are supporters of
the Human Cultivation Project.
The aims of this program are
to reduce the human population
to one billion people, and to
create a single world government
through the use of propaganda.
Pay heed to "Kagome, Kagome."
This seemingly
innocent song is a symbol
to the Committee
and their followers.
You are certain
to come across it
wherever they are doing research
or conducting experiments
toward the
furtherance of their goals.
The Robot Research Club
members enjoy summer vacation
and take a break from their
work to attend a local festival.
Meanwhile, Frau asks Kai
if he knows anything
that might help her
learn more about what
happened to her mother.
A celebration, fireworks,
a summer night.
And then, at last,
GunBuild-1 is complete.
A crowd gathers as the
club members wait anxiously
to see how the robot built from
their dreams and
passion will perform.
Episode 9!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!