It was a totally ordinary life.
An average family
on an average day.
Ah! Why do I
always do this?
I've gotta run. See you
later! Have a good day!
You too! Bye, Mom.
That was it. She
left that morning
and never made
it back home again.
It's so cold.
If I stay long enough,
maybe it'll freeze me
and preserve my
body for all eternity.
Man, I'm lame. Talk about
epic delusional poetry.
As November rolled around,
temperatures dropped,
and the wind grew chilly.
The Mark 2's construction
is progressing
at a fairly decent
rate, I guess.
Amazing.
The real robot still has a ways
to go. That's just the AR.
Yeah, we have to decide
on a drive system soon.
We can't do much more until
then. I wish we could use
the mono-- I mean I wish we
could find some totally awesome
new material to
use for the motor.
Hello, all! You're up early.
Nae returned from her Tokyo
trip last month. Now when we
use this place she's always
there to supervise our work.
Good morning, Nae.
Don't leave me hangin!
I'm not really
big on high fives.
Hey, it's the weekend,
right? Don't you have some
wild parties to go to today?
You should know better than to
tease your elders by
now, Kaito. Be careful!
Because bad kids like you get
the dreaded tickle punishment!
Uh. Hey, Nae, when
you're done with that
we've got a little
present to give you!
Huh? A gift for me?
Yes! Ready? Happy birthday
to our dear friend Nae!
Come on, you guys! Sing!
I-I can't, I'm sorry.
I would be too embarrassed.
The same goes for me.
Sorry. I can't sing either.
I've been tickle-punished.
I can't believe it. You
guys knew it was my birthday?
That's incredibly sweet of
you. And a total surprise, too!
Here you go. It's
something from all of us.
Thank you so much!
I don't know what to say!
May I open it right now?
Of course! Go ahead!
I hope you like them.
Kai picked 'em out.
It's a pair of
cycling sunglasses!
I needed some of these!
And they're cute, too!
I'll take really
good care of them.
They look nice
on you. Very hip.
Where's Frau Bow?
It's been a long time.
Well, I doubt she'll show
up today. We've been talking
a little bit on Twipo
but I haven't really
seen her in the last
two or three months.
Hey, Doc, what's
that you're working on?
What does it look like to you?
Seems to be a dish antenna.
Four eyes and you're still
blind? It's a Vernier thruster.
Built it myself. It'll
attach to your Mark 2--
It most certainly will not! The
blueprints we have don't call
for GunBuild-2 to fly or jump!
Doesn't have to be for fancy
stuff like that. You can just
use it for fuel injection.
By the time I'm done,
it's gonna be loaded
with ten thrusters in all.
How many on the back? Six?
Heck no. Four in back.
We can also add
hover capabilities.
Like, "Hey, did you
just step on me?" Right?
And we can paint it
black and purple, too!
What in the world are the
two of you talking about?
Black Tri-Stars, of course.
Nonsense, in other words.
Y-Yeah! Total nonsense!
Doc, we are not gonna attach
any thrusters, ya got that?
Bah. You kids don't
know how to rock at all.
You've gotten too
spunky for your own good.
You did just check
out of the hospital.
Well, what'd you guys
come here for, anyway?
Oh, yeah! I, uh, I
have a favor to ask you.
What is that thing?
It's a monopole. Do you
think you could use it to make
a high-tech
motor for the Mark 2?
All right! This
could get interesting.
I keep reading it, but
I still don't understand.
Messages. A robot
uprising and Project Atum.
Say that again?
I summarized it
in three phrases.
That doesn't make
me any less confused.
I mean, the idea of a robot
uprising is ridiculous.
Finally! There you are.
Yeah, what's up?
What were you looking at?
Oh....
It's nothing. So, did
Doc agree to do it, then?
Yeah. He's gonna look into
some stuff first, he said,
which just leaves us with
the motor control program.
I'm counting on you to
persuade Frau Bow, 'kay?
You know the rules.
If you want something,
you have to beat me at KB.
I thought you might say that.
Nae's doing really well. She's
shot to the top two hundred
in the KILL-BALLAD
rankings. Impressive, huh?
Four months left until
the expo! We're gonna do it!
We will finish GunBuild-2!
Don't forget that there's
a preliminary screening
next month. Will we
be ready for that?
I'll personally fill out the
entry form. It'll be perfect,
you'll see! And the theme'll
be "May Love and Justice bring
Peace for all Humankind!"
Well, what do ya think?
Sound like it's
from robot anime?
It sounds like nonsense.
Yes! Woo-hoo!
She can't say I didn't try.
Yashio? That you?
Yeah. You're not sounding
so good. Feeling okay?
I'm hungry. Need food.
You're in luck. I brought
provisions. Some yummy
Kagoshima sweet
potato-flavored Pocchy.
No! This is no time
to worry about food!
Just forget what
I said before, okay?
I-- I have a
favor to ask you.
Look, I need you, okay?
Uh, what kind of favor?
I-I'm not asking much, really.
I just want to lick your
fingertips, that's all!
You're more perverted
than I thought.
No, it's not like that!
This is about human instinct!
Our fundamental identity!
All mammals do it!
Babies suck their
thumbs, you know?
Why do you think that is?
"Because he's a little
boy." Solo comedy, HY.
You seem to be in pretty high
spirits. What's going on?
Have there been
new developments with
the cheater stuff
or something?
No, no more info. My associates
Chuchu and Sumasa said
the police aren't taking
them seriously but--
But what?
About Kimijima
Report Number Four,
the one you
uncovered the other day.
Did you find something out?
I realized there was something
similar between the report's
content and the final episode
of GUNVARREL that was leaked.
Like what?
Like a password. A dark
past. Subliminal stuff.
You don't have to summarize
it in three phrases.
Feel free to give details.
I see what you're getting at.
You want to stretch out our
time together for
as long as possible!
All alone, just us two.
Our own little erotic game?
This would go faster if you'd
stop changing the subject.
I just had to look more
closely at the final episode.
It was only four minutes
and thirty-one seconds long
to begin with and the
editing was tera-rough.
But after analyzing it,
I discovered there were
cryptic images inserted in
nineteen spots throughout.
So, I isolated the
images, de-noised them,
and then adjusted their color
levels. That's when I found the
subliminal messages that
were hidden even deeper.
Here, this is an
example of what I mean.
It's not clear where it is,
but have a look in this area.
Okay, I see what you mean.
It looks like the letter B.
Correct! Lemme lick
your fingers now!
Hey, stay away from me,
you freaking pervert!
That was just one of them, as I
said, eighteen other pics were
hidden inside the subliminal
images embedded in the episode
and every one of them
seems to be a photo of the
same abandoned building. All of
them have this in common, too.
Each one has a
letter drawn onto it.
Were you able to
arrange them in a way that
spells anything meaningful?
No, I wasn't. However--
What's this?
The dark past.
A homepage that my mom
set up in high school.
She abandoned it
twenty-plus years ago.
Kinda hard to
believe it's still up.
It had comics my mom drew,
angsty poems she wrote,
and a message board
for contacting her.
Whoa, hold on a sec,
are you saying your mom
posted a message there?
Looks like it's dated
October 4th, twenty-fifteen.
Two weeks after GUNVARREL's
last broadcast was cancelled.
That's when it was posted.
What's at that address?
It needs a password.
"Yes!" "Those letters in
the pictures were actually
a password!" "Oh, my!
They were? Really?"
Solar storms hitting
and Project Atum.
Odd request. You're telling
me you wanna borrow a bow from
an old archery club member
and why exactly would that be?
Oh, you know how it is.
Fine. Finish that bun and
I'll stop asking questions.
Although--
I would like some
reassurance that you're not
looking into those
Kimijima Reports again.
Kimijima Report Number
Five's flags are as follows.
Are you ready?
"Flag one, find and read
Kimijima Report Number Four."
Message from Gezi. This flag
has been successfully cleared.
"Two. Go to the old
Tanegashima Airport runway.
Run from Point A to
Point B, as indicated,
in under five minutes."
I got creative and cleared
flag two by taking my moped.
"Three. Go to Nakatane Central
Sports Park. Complete a lap
around the track there
in under sixty seconds."
For flag three, I moved
from moped to bicycle.
"Four. Hit a bull's eye
on one of the targets at
Chuo Tanegashima High
School's archery range."
Good thing you never
said how far back from
the target I had to stand.
All right, Gezi, I've
cleared all the flags now.
And I'm here at the
school. You think this is
where the fifth
report is hidden?
Yes. Please retrieve
it as soon as possible.
That guy is so weird.
I looked. And finally,
I found the report
in front of the school.
Man, these things are always so
long and I don't get half of it.
I could reread this
a dozen times, Gezi.
Could you just
give me a summary?
It says that solar activity is
now at its peak. Because of
this, Earth's magnetosphere
has become unstable.
The Committee of Three
Hundred is attempting to
use this instability
to artificially induce
something akin to a
coronal mass ejection.
Are you telling me that
mankind will be destroyed?
Yes, that is correct.
Never thought I would say
it but I really think we should
go public with
this information.
Uh-oh.
Great, more cleanup to do.
Yes, exactly! Just
like that! Good job, Jun!
Let's try that other
one now, okay? Superinpei!
This pad seems to be
acting up for some reason.
Hello, yes-- What's that?
An explosion?
Doc, we--
Hey, what's up, Robot Girl?
Well, we heard there
was some kind of explosion.
Ol' Goh told ya, did he?
That nosy, loud-mouthed jerk.
Please, Grandpa Fujita.
You're not fully recovered!
Y-You should really
be more careful.
Oh, um. I am sorry for
getting you all worried, Jun,
but this is the kinda thing
a man waits his whole life for
and you can't afford to
be timid if you're gonna go
messin' with something
like a monopole.
I was prepared to blow
up the whole island.
I have no regrets.
Then you might
consider getting some.
I didn't realize the monopole
was in danger of exploding.
For now, I went ahead and cut it
in half. All's still well, so--
What do you mean, "for now?"
Check it out.
Interesting.
Like monopole fillets.
How dangerous are they?
Can they be touched?
You'll get a little
jolt, but not enough to
get burned or anything.
We've truly entered
the realm of the unknown.
Don't have to get all
mystical about it, boy.
Doc.
I want you to give
it to us straight, okay?
Are these things safe
or safe enough, at least?
What do you think?
Can-- Can we use them?
That look in your eyes.
Just like your sister's.
R-Really?
Yep. You're a chip off
the same block, all right.
Now I'm fired up!
A text?
Sounds more like an
earthquake alert to me.
Neither. It's a solar storm.
It appears the Kanto region
has taken a direct hit.
Earlier today at approximately
4:30 p.m., the Kanto region
was hit by a
massive solar storm.
Hey.
I'm worried. Things
are going crazy in Tokyo.
You haven't been able
to get a hold of Misa?
No.
Complete blackout! Tokyo, said
to be a city that never sleeps,
is totally dark. Is that a
fire in one of the buildings?
It appears to be
a residential street.
Several homes have caught fire!
Dammit!
I'm thirsty, Genki.
I need a drink plz.
Don't let a little thing
like thirst get you down!
Keep your spirits high,
and I just know we'll
get through this together!
You're a big help.
Genki bot, mute on.
Absolutely! Enabling
mute! Talk to you later!
It appears the capital remains
in a state of
complete paralysis.
There are also reports
of robots malfunctioning--
Apparently, according to
witnesses, going berserk.
The government
is working quickly...
What a screwed-up
world we live in.
That's Kona.
A massive solar storm
in twenty fifteen disabled
electronic devices
everywhere, what is
commonly known
as the 2015 Crash.
Huh? Who's that?
It's Hanjuro Hattori.
Right, answer call.
H-Hanju! U OK, d00d?
You psycho! Quit this
crazy crap right now!
Taking over the RI robots'
OSes is way more than a prank!
Huh? I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Could you make
more sense, plz?
You've got robots going
nuts and attacking people,
and you want me to make
sense? Don't try to deny it!
You posted about it on Twipo.
I did? On Twipo?
"You know how all those robots
in Tokyo are malfunctioning
and attacking people? Yeah,
you got it, that's me."
No, I didn't do that.
I didn't post this.
Someone's hijacked my account.
Man, it's cold!
Kona?
Hey, Kona, are you in here?
Oh, no, Kona!
You're alive!
It's being defiled. GUNVARREL.
Someone is defiling GUNVARREL.
You have to do something,
Yashio. Do something.
The solar storm
hits and before long,
robots are running
amuck through the city.
Desperate, Kai and
Frau turn to KILLBALLAD
in the hopes of
finding a solution.
The enemy seems invincible,
almost superhuman.
Robots everywhere are going
berserk. What can Kai do?
Will he be able
to turn the tables
when things spiral
out of control?
Episode 14.
Let's hit it off everybody!
Later days!