You little idiot! What
the hell were you thinking?
Just take a look at what you've
done! Go ahead and look at it!
So many doubts still.
Is this right? Do I really
belong here with them?
At the start of September,
the second school term began.
Forget about Kou Kimijima.
Stop poking around.
What do you mean "forget
about him?" Why should I?
Just do it. Do you understand?
Was that supposed
to be a warning?
It just makes me
even more curious.
But at the very least it
does confirm that Misa knows
something about Kimijima.
Kimijima Report Number
Four's flags are as follows.
"Flag one. Locate and read
Kimijima Report Number Three."
You have done this.
"Two. Locate photographs
of rocket launches taken from
the four specified
points on Tanegashima.
Upload them to IRUO."
"Three. Find a
matchlock gun, geotag it,
and test-fire at least once."
"Four. Go to the Robo
Clinic in Tanegashima.
Find Gojiro and activate it."
Activate it? What is "Gojiro?"
Well, if it's
at the Robo Clinic...
Attention! Today we
start building GunBuild-2
and this is our workspace!
Huh? Here? You mean, they're
letting us use this place?
Yes. I don't see any problem
with letting your club make use
of this room as long
as somebody supervises.
It would be a waste
to let it stay empty like this.
There's even a crane here.
Which means that this time
around, we can actually
build it standing up!
Isn't it so exciting?
You do realize we haven't even
decided on a drive system yet.
I wish there was a way we
could talk to Doc about that.
His advice would be
helpful. And the mono--
There are a lot of
things he could help with.
You are never going
to give up, are you?
When the final episode leaked,
it tarnished
GUNVARREL'S reputation.
It was like everybody just
forgot the true meaning of
the show. I think by
creating GunBuild-2,
we can repair some
of the damage it caused.
What's the matter, Jun?
Uh. One sec, I'm sorry.
Sure.
Hello? Oh, hi, Dad. Yeah.
I'm hanging out
with some friends.
What?
Well, hello. Are you
here to see a patient?
Huh? Oh, yes, I am. Mr. Fujita.
This is his room, right?
I'm his granddaughter, you see.
Not here.
Get her. Get her
out of here now.
Jun! Doc okay? How'd he look?
I-- I didn't get to see him.
What do you mean? Why not?
Yeah, are they not letting
him have any visitors?
Oh n-no.
He just didn't wanna see me.
What? You mean you saw Doc?
Well, yeah. I paid him
a get well visit yesterday.
What's the deal? He wouldn't
see Jun the day before,
but he'll see you?
So how'd it look
like he was doing?
Well, he seemed pretty
weak, to be honest.
Not just physically,
weak in spirit, too.
Wha-- How d'you mean?
I think I'll close the
shop when I'm outta here.
Time to call it quits.
That's awful!
This is a surprise. Don't
see you here too often.
You're not feeling down
on yourself 'cause you're
too scared to visit
the hospital, are you?
No, it isn't like that.
Grandpa Fujita and I were never
really that close to begin with.
Hmm. Then--
Anyway, I think it
might be time for me to
quit the Robot Research Club.
I was afraid you'd say
that. Yeah, well, I guess
it's your call. For now,
though, why don't we go inside?
Man, you can't keep
a secret, can you?
Sorry, I couldn't help it.
You're not poking
that nose of yours into
any more weird stuff, I hope.
Not me. Anyway, did you
get the info I asked you for?
First, you should know that Doc
used to be a NASDA engineer.
NASDA? You mean the
agency that turned into JAXA?
That's correct. And
that's not all, either.
When he opened the Robo
Clinic eighteen years ago,
it was meant for little kids.
Doc would make robots
and then line them up
in front of his shop.
I still remember it
like it was yesterday.
Back then he was
a very different man.
He always said robots were
built to be people's friends.
That's almost hard to believe.
So what happened to those
robots? Where are they?
Asleep, deep inside
the Robo Clinic.
How come?
Because there was an accident.
Oh, um, I have to--
Sorry, I have to go. Goodbye!
Jun, what's the matter?
Eleven years ago...
a robot toppled over and
injured one of the children.
That child was Doc's
granddaughter, Junna Daitoku.
Hello there! Nice to meet
you! My name is Yoshiro!
I'm a friendly robot.
Do you want to be friends?
Come on, friend.
Go away! You're not my friend!
You're not my friend at all!
Stop talking to me!
You idiot! What the
hell were you thinking?
Just look at what you've
done! Go on and look at it!
So that's why
Jun's afraid of robots.
What now? What d'we do?
I don't think
this is a good idea.
We heard all about Doc's
robots from back in the day.
We should restore them
to their former glory!
That's sure to
bring his spirits up!
Yeah, I don't know.
Doc's losing his will to fight.
You want him to
get better, don't you?
Of course, but
it's not that simple.
We get it, you're
terrified of robots.
Is that the reason you
want to quit the club, too?
What? She's quitting?
You didn't tell me that!
That was a secret, Yashio!
Why do you want to quit, Jun?
I-I only joined on a
whim in the first place.
It seemed like an okay
replacement for the karate club.
Even though I was bad
at karate, I kept doing it
because I liked it. But
when it comes to robots--
They really
scare you that much?
In that case.
I'm afraid I can't allow
you to drop out of the club!
Huh?
I'm not going to let you
go until you find something
you like about robots, and
that's all there is to it!
Now, come on! I'm giving you
an order, as your club leader!
Akiho, wait!
Think we'll still
be able to turn 'em on?
Ah!
Uh-oh.
What is it?
The cords,
they've all been cut.
So they didn't just die. Doc
killed all these robots himself.
Uh-- Where'd Yashio go?
He's inside, working
on the one called Gojiro.
He insists on being
the one to fix him.
Hooray! Hooray! Go Brother!
I'm getting this one fixed up
but would you
mind operating it, Jun?
Huh?
I don't know why, but I have
a feeling this is something
only you can do.
Say you will. Please.
There. It should
be good to go.
You're finished
already? Wow! Good job!
Now we just get some
power going to it, and--
What's this?
Hey, this looks like--
Hello. Nice t-- --eet you.
What was that?
My name is Yoshiro.
I'm a friendly robot.
Well, what d'ya think,
Kai? I was able to
get it talking
again. Nice, huh?
If you call that talking.
Come on, friend.
Let's shake hands now.
What's up?
I'm a friendly robot.
Hello there! Nice to
meet you! My name is Yoshiro!
It's the same one as before.
I'm a friendly robot.
Aki, shut the robot off!
Huh?
Come on, friend.
Let's shake hands now.
Hurry! Do it!
You're not friendly!
You're not my friend!
Wait, Jun! Come back!
I guess we knew that's
where this was headed.
Alright. I gotta go.
I got some stuff to do.
Huh? Leaving at
a time like this?
But what do we do about Jun?
Well, the way we were
approaching it before
wasn't helping at all.
"And if pushing doesn't
work, try pulling instead."
Wait a sec. Isn't that
an old proverb about love?
Crummy Girl, watch me!
How's my punch?
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Now, now, I asked you not
to call me that, didn't I?
My kick's way
better than his punch!
Hey, will you make
cookies for us again?
I'll bring some with
me next time, okay?
Really? Yay!
You seemed, I dunno,
different out there.
Yeah. I'm usually
more nervous.
So you're really
quitting the club?
Robots frighten me too
much. I just can't do it.
And as far as Grandpa goes,
he'll cheer up faster
without me around.
Actually, I think
you're the one Doc needs.
You can encourage him
like no one else can.
I'm sorry, but you're wrong.
I've been avoiding him
ever since the accident.
I'm sure he's still mad at me.
I'm afraid I'm not a
very good granddaughter.
You know the robots in the shop?
All of 'em had their cords cut.
Why do you think
he would do that?
Here, I found this
in the storeroom.
Think about it some
more before you decide.
It's like I always say,
"robots are built to
be people's friends."
Really? Then that means
I'm their friend, too!
Yeah!
My video of the
GunBuild-1 test?
If that's okay.
Here, all yours.
Oh great. Thank you.
How lame!
It's huge!
Yeah, huge and dumb-looking!
It's got weapons,
right? Where are they?
Nobody's scared. They all
seem to be having a good time.
Man, it's slow!
Can you even call that walking?
It's like I always say,
"robots are built to
be people's friends."
Doc blamed himself
for what happened.
He said he was being arrogant
for thinking like he did.
That all robots
were people's friends.
It's thinkin' you're always
to blame when something
goes wrong that's
arrogant, if ya ask me. Eh?
Just a tip from me to you.
Oh, you again.
We're worried about you,
Doc. You're looking frail.
Could you come with us
down to the Robo Clinic?
It shouldn't take very long.
I decided to shut that place
down. Shoulda done it years ago.
Place was never worth it.
You shouldn't say things like
that when you don't mean them!
You love the clinic,
and you know it!
I understand what you're going
through, but I love GUNVARREL,
so I'm gonna finish it,
no matter what! Please, Doc!
It's over. I'm
through with it.
I know you think that, but your
robots are waiting for you.
What did you do?
Don't tell me. You didn't!
It's exactly like it was right
after its grand opening.
Idiots! How dare you!
Just come with us
and see for yourself.
Then decide if we're idiots.
We got your doctor's
permission to take you.
How 'bout it?
No, don't. Stop this now!
It'll hurt her again.
She'll be so scared!
My fault, all my
fault. Because of me.
Jun got hurt because of me.
Yoshiro?
Hello there! Nice to meet
you! My name is Yoshiro!
I'm a friendly robot.
Do you want to be friends?
Come on, friend.
Let's shake hands now!
Please! Won't
you shake my hand?
Please, Mr. Fujita!
How-- How did you know my name?
Because somebody taught it to
him. Your granddaughter, Jun.
She taught Yoshiro
how to say your name.
My granddaughter?
Let's be friends again.
Okay, Grandpa Fujita?
Are you sure? Can
you really forgive me?
I'm the one who should apologize
for staying away for so long.
Sorry, Grandpa. I'm so sorry.
Honestly, they
still scare me some.
But I can learn to like
Yoshiro again, and all your
other little ones. You'll
see, I promise I can do it.
I'll try hard and I'm sure
we'll be friends but please,
you have to get better,
Grandpa! You will, won't you?
Thank you.
Hooray!
Well, we should get going now.
Get better soon. But
don't push yourself, okay?
I ain't so feeble I need
you brats to worry about me.
In this case I'll take your
grouchiness as a good sign.
Hey. You crazy kids
still workin' on
that giant robot of yours?
Of course we are!
We're determined as ever!
Lemme take a look at
it when I get outta here.
I can tell ya if
it rocks or not.
The construction of
GunBuild-2 continues.
Meanwhile Kai
and Frau head out
in search of another
Kimijima Report.
Frau is also searching
for clues about her mother.
Director Minami Furugori may
have an important connection
to the final
episode of GUNVARREL.
Kai and Frau
uncover a new truth,
and a prophecy comes
true, rocking the world.
Episode 13.
Let's hit it off everybody!
Later days!