What?
Stop it!
Kai!
Fool! What are you doing?
Aki! Find her!
Senomiya must be stopped!
Or else the Kimijima
Reports will come true.
It's Kagome.
Wait, Misa!
The center door is an
entrance only. When leaving,
please use the exit
located on the opposite side.
Oh, no! What is she?
How could you? Why, Sis?
Activate Guild Build 2!
"I have control!"
Please, Sis, why
are you doing this?
Misa!
No, don't! Please
stop! Stop this!
Don't, Misaaa!
Aki!
Oh, no! You okay?
Aki! Are you
having another atta-
She's gone.
My sister. She disappeared.
Oh, Aki.
Breaking news: a new
solar storm has begun.
Its strength is unprecedented.
The storm, which broke at
about 2:50p.m. has caused
electromagnetic interference.
As you see, the storm has
had a worldwide impact already.
It appears large-scale
explosions of unknown cause
have occurred at the expo arena
which has been mostly destroyed.
That bench. Let's sit
you down over there.
That's new. What the?
The Grand Obelisk. It was in
the final episode of GUNVARREL.
The orbital elevator.
No way. You're not telling
me that thing is actually real!
Kaito! Aki! There you
are! Are you two okay?
Hey. Would you mind
watching Aki for a minute?
Sure.
Thank you. I'll
be back soon, Aki.
Both the Haneda
and Narita airports
are currently shut down,
as all air transport
remains in a
state of paralysis.
Yes?
Come in.
♪ Kagome, Kagome. ♪
♪ The bird's in the cage ♪
♪ When, oh when,
will it ever come out? ♪
♪ In the night of the dawn ♪
♪ The crane and
tortoise slipped ♪
What the hell is this?
They're fake. Someone's
spreading fake images.
IRUO says this has
all been destroyed,
but that's clearly not true.
The truth behind the
magic, known as Noah's Ark.
An EM wave irradiation device.
It produces AR-like illusions
visible to the naked eye.
What's the matter?
Have you been injured?
The Anemone Mass Fainting
Incident was actually
an experiment meant to
test this on human subjects.
Huh?
What does this mean?
These past few hours, the
whole world has been plunged
into chaos. What do
you think is causing it?
Well, the solar storm.
No, that's not the cause.
There is no solar storm.
Huh?
A solar storm has
supposedly caused blackouts in
cities everywhere and brought
traffic to a standstill.
It's also destroyed Odaiba,
but from where is all this
information originating?
Where did you first hear it?
It's propaganda. That's
what caused this chaos.
A world panic over something
that isn't even true.
It's all fiction.
That's crazy. Why
would somebody want...?
For Project Atom.
Our first task is to load the
Black Hole Bomb acquired from
SERN into the fully
prepped rocket in the VAB.
We can then move on to the
ultimate goal of this project.
Launching the bomb into
space and detonating it,
artificially
producing a substorm
in the Earth's magnetosphere.
To this end, we must quickly
secure Points Alpha and Beta
and launch the rocket
before the government
and police organizations, which
are now in a state of chaos,
precisely as intended,
can take action against us.
If a substorm did indeed occur,
it would wipe out five billion
of Earth's population.
Just as Kimijima predicted.
And you're the mastermind
behind this brilliant plan?
Alright, so that is
how you see all of this.
Exactly as he
intended for you to.
Contrary to what you
believe, I am opposed to the
Committee of Three
Hundred's methods.
You're saying you're
not one of them?
That's correct. I caught wind
of the fact that the Committee
was assisting the
individual responsible for
conceiving Project Atom.
Misaki Senomiya and I
relentlessly
pursued this person.
Misa did?
Eventually, I made a
surprising realization.
Okay. What did you figure out?
IRUO. The Anemone Incident.
The mysterious reports,
the EGI System, Airi
Yukifune, Misaki Senomiya.
I realized that there
was only one individual who
connected all of these
things to each other.
You don't think?
I do. The man who released
information in the form of
mysterious reports. Reports
which directed suspicion
away from himself and
concealed the fact that
he was actually
the one responsible.
Arrived at Point Beta.
Securing site now.
Roger that. Point Alpha
has been secured, as well.
Of course there's rain.
There's always rain.
As for Misaki. I think she is
most likely Kou Kimijima's pawn.
Not Misa.
She created an illusory
version of herself. Using it,
she was able to keep us
occupied. And meanwhile,
she and the other SUMERAGI
headed for Tanegashima
and the site of the
upcoming rocket launch.
No. He's wrong.
It can't be true!
Aki! Aki!
Good, you're back.
Where did Aki go?
Well, ya see, I just
looked away for a second
and she up and disappeared.
Aki.
We need to go back home now.
We have to track
down Misa again.
I mean it. There's
too much going on that
we don't understand.
It's okay. It doesn't matter.
I don't want to talk
to her or see her.
You don't mean that.
I mean, come on.
This is the time for
ridiculously optimist--
Oh, yeah? Because I'm not
optimistic at all right now!
I don't know that I ever was.
I've always secretly been
scared that my sister
actually hates me.
I could never go
see her. I was afraid.
I see that now.
I was always afraid.
Afraid I could never,
ever catch up to her.
That I really was
nothing but mediocre.
Afraid that no matter what
I did or how hard I tried,
she would
never acknowledge me.
I never should've started
building giant robots.
I never should have even
tried catching up to my sister.
I never should've clung so
tightly to this stupid dream.
Misa was right all along.
GunBuild-2 is nothing but
a piece of junk after all.
I see.
I'm disappointed in you.
Misa was right all along.
GunBuild-2 is nothing but
a piece of junk after all.
Hey, Aki. I've decided
I am going to find Misa
and talk to her. I have to.
What for?
I don't like it. I just can't
accept being defeated like this.
I was deceived and
challenged to battle without
even realizing it, and I
won't take it lying down.
How much of our lives have
the two of us spent like this?
Pointlessly chasing
after your sister.
First she rescues us
after the Anemone Incident,
then she starts pushing
us away for some reason.
I just... Doesn't
that make you mad?
I don't know. Maybe.
It makes me mad! I'm sick of
this. Of being outdone by her.
More than that! Aki, I'm sick
of you being outdone by her!
Kai.
You came here so
proud to finally show
GunBuild 2 to Misa, right?
Then show her! Don't
let everything you've done
go to waste! Grab
her by her stupid,
pretentious neck,
look her in the eye,
and tell her "see, I am great!
I don't care what you think,
I am not mediocre!" Let's make
her say, "you've beaten me!"
Who are you? And what
have you done with Kai?
Huh?
Right now, the Kai I know would
be saying "what's the big deal?
What are you getting
so worked up for?"
Oh. Uh.
Thanks for that. And I
take back what I said before.
GunBuild-2 isn't a
piece of junk at all.
We're headed to the
island. Picking up my uncle.
Really? How?
Yeah, Haneda and Narita
airports aren't operational.
They ain't the only
airports in Tokyo.
Haven't you ever
heard of Chofu Airport?
Well, uh.
As it happens, there's a certain
facility right next to it.
This is a special
tip from me to you,
so don't say I never
did anything for ya!
Little place called the
JAXA Chofu Aerospace Center!
w00t! They match exactly!
The company paying
the electric bill for
Kou Kimijima's cottage
was the company Maguyan
was dealing with.
And it was the company
that financed the studio
when Mom worked on GUNVARREL.
I guess they must have forced
her to work on the show,
just like they forced Maguyan.
She managed to escape somehow
and tried to find a
way to get the truth out.
Oh, Mom.
Hey Frau, it appears
someone has come to visit you!
Ignoring them
would be impolite!
There's nobody out there.
Freeze!
Agh, get off of me!
This is Priest 1.
Target B is secured.
I repeat. Target B is secured.
What's wrong?
The two who went to the
airport aren't responding.
I wouldn't expect them to.
They're taking a
little nap right now.
Well, that takes care of them.
Do you always have
to drive like a lunatic?
Really. Gimme a sec.
I think I'm gonna puke.
We have no time
to waste on whining.
Especially when things are
about to get even bumpier.
A plane?
Tennoji told me about it.
She said there might be
a terrorist attack soon. If
anything like that happened,
she told me to
go to Chofu Airport.
She had a contingency plan?
Take that along with you. Who
knows, it could come in handy.
Also. One of my colleagues
is staying on Tanegashima.
We've never actually met.
But should you run into
each other, tell S Braun "hi".
Hey, wait a second.
Is S Braun actually...?
We need to get
going. Hurry up!
♪ Kagome, Kagome. ♪
♪ The bird's in the cage ♪
I know that voice. It's Airi!
♪ In the night of the dawn,
crane and tortoise slipped. ♪
♪ Who's in the front,
in the front of behind? ♪
It is her.
You mean the ghost-girl
that haunts Uchugaoka Park?
Actually, a real girl was the
model, but that was just an AI.
Made by Kou Kimijima.
Uh, Kai. This one seems real.
I won't allow you to
take off in that plane.
If you insist on going,
you'll have to run me over.
Airi, is that you?
I'm a living child. Run me
over and my flesh will tear,
my bones will shatter,
my innards will burst,
and my blood will pour out.
Are you willing to accept that?
Stop it! Who are you?
Very well. You did give me
a considerable amount of help.
I suppose I'll let you
have a glimpse of me,
and I assume you
know how. Go right ahead.
An A.I.?
Not quite. Converting
someone's personality into
data and transplanting
it into a network.
Does that sound familiar?
You're saying?
Airi Yukifune was a test subject
to see if it could be done.
Although it isn't perfect,
I accomplished
what I set out to do.
It was you all along.
As you can see, I am an
individual personality that
exists within the network.
One with everlasting life.
When Kai and the others
head for Tanegashima,
they find somebody
waiting for them.
It's Kou Kimijima with
Airi as his hostage.
Aki rails at the man who would
annihilate the world
in his bid for power.
But she is not alone. When
Tanegashima is threatened by
the world's greatest evil,
will its people shy away
or rise to the challenge?
Episode 20.
Let's hit it off everybody!
Later days!