Back in high school, I'd come
out here and watch Irei surf.
Did that a lot, actually.
And like you, I would
skip club meetings.
Wow. It sounds like
you were even worse at
running the club than Aki.
Yeah, I heard that all the time.
From Senomiya and from Irei.
So Senomiya sent a
condolence telegram, huh?
Oh, I mean the
older one, of course.
That reminds me.
She asked me to
tell Misa thanks.
Oh, and another thing,
Mizuka could really drink with
the best of 'em. I'm
gonna... I'm gonna miss her.
Drink up, Irei.
I'm just going to get right to
the point. As of today, I have
decided to officially disband
the Robot Research Club.
Really, Miss? Keep in
mind I'm partly to blame for
not providing
adequate supervision.
Hidaka's father is
exceptionally angry,
and for good reason,
indeed. Do you understand?
I do.
And while the help was certainly
appreciated, I'm afraid we can
no longer allow
you to work with JAXA.
We are deeply sorry,
too. We do regret the
lack of supervision
and the tragedy it led to.
Our bosses have weighed in,
too and we can no longer offer
the club any support.
Of course, that means there
won't be an
entry in the expo.
And does the
Space Candy Company
understand the
situation as well?
It is unfortunate,
but it can't be helped now.
All robots that were made
by the Robot Research Club
are to be dismantled
immediately. Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
We went to the hospital
straight after the meeting.
Even so, we didn't
get to see Subaru.
His father had told
the hospital staff that we
weren't to be allowed
visitation privileges.
We heard his
injuries were severe.
So severe he might
never fully recover.
Meanwhile, Jun went to Subaru's
house to apologize to his dad.
I know what happened
wasn't your fault.
I know that, but please, stay
away from my son from now on.
He seemed so very sad. I know
that by accepting the blame
I won't change
anything and I know
that what I've done
can't ever be forgiven.
What happened
wasn't your fault, Jun.
Please don't be
so hard on yourself.
I want to say sorry
to you, too. I let you down.
Frau!
Look out!
He got hurt and
it was all my fault.
So, I'm quitting
the club for good.
I don't really see any
point in doing that now.
There isn't even a
club to quit anymore.
Hey, shut up, Kai!
What?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Accept call.
Hi. Um. LTNS.
Hey. How are you holding up?
I'm working on tweaking
the auto-balancer.
P-Part of the reason Skeletal
GUNVARREL fell over was because
my program code wasn't up to
snuff. So I've been using data
collected over the last
few days to improve it.
Actually, the club
has been disbanded.
And all the
robots have to go.
Oof. W-Would have been cool if
you'd told me that sooner, TBH.
Yeah, sorry. I've kinda
had my hands full here.
Yeah, of course.
What is it? What's wrong?
It's just... all of this.
What?
Doesn't it seem... scary?
Scary?
R-Remember what you said? About
how "Kagome, Kagome" played
just before her
powered suit went crazy?
D-Do you think it might
have something to do with
the stuff in the
Kimijima Reports?
I told you.You shouldn't
go sticking your nose
where it doesn't belong.
Now just do what I told you
and forget about this already.
Tell her. Tell her thanks
for giving me these legs.
Do you think it was a
warning for me or something?
A warning? No, that's not
what I was saying. Just.
S-Sorry.
It's okay. Anyway, I'm
gonna go now. I'm tired.
Shall I download it?
Kaito Yashio.
I'm Sawada of
Exoskeleton Company.
I have a few questions about
the powered suit malfunction.
Uh, what kinda questions?
Look, I've already told
the police everything I know.
Yes, so I'm aware. They tell me
there was some audio playing
when the suit went out of
control. Were they sounds you
were familiar with?
Something you knew?
Something you had heard
somewhere else perhaps?
No, never.
I see. And have you heard of a
man by the name of Kou Kimijima?
No, sir.
Really? You see, Kou Kimijima
was connected to a young girl
named Airi and I'm
told you were the one who
discovered Airi
in a cold-sleep state.
I-- I just found
her, that's all.
I see. One more thing.
I hear you were a victim
of the Anemone Incident.
What does that have
to do with anything?
It's another interesting link.
That's when Kimijima died,
you know, almost exactly
when the Incident occurred.
Let me ask again.
Is the name "Kou Kimijima"
familiar to you at all?
No, it's not.
I see.
Misa?
Accept call! Hello?
Hello, Misa? Are you there!
Kai. You cannot give
out the Kimijima Reports.
Huh?
You must safeguard
the information.
Wait. What do you mean?
Do not fail.
That's it, Sis. Mizuka's gone
and the club's been shut down.
It's all over.
Why'd this happen? Why, Sis?
Sis calling! Accept!
Accept call! Misaki!
Is that really you?
Sure is.
I can't believe it!
Have you been doing okay?
Yeah, how about you?
Nothing's changed much here.
So, tell me, how's
GunBuild-2 coming along?
Huh? Oh, um.
You're going to be in the
expo, right? I got your emails!
Well, actually...
I figured you'd
fail in the end.
I did try to
tell you, didn't I?
I said you would never be
anything more than mediocre.
What?
You'll never make my dream come
true. You're a failure, Akiho.
You dreamt about Misa?
Yeah.
Is it me or does
he look like he's sad?
Dunno.
What is it?
Hey Kai. Will you please
listen to what I have to say?
Uh, sure.
Attention, Chuo-Tanegashima
High Robot Research Club.
Our organization is hereby
disbanded. Thank you all
for giving your utmost to
the achievement of our goals.
That was great!
So?
Well that's it, I'll do
things on my own, somehow.
What are you talking about?
We're not allowed to
meet as a club anymore,
so I'll just figure out a way
to do this as an individual.
So despite everything,
you still haven't given up?
Do you really think everyone
is going to be okay with that?
I doubt it. I think the
vice principal will be angry.
And I think Jun, Subaru,
and Subaru's dad will be
furious, too. And I realize
it might seem disrespectful,
so soon after
Mizuka passed away.
Even so, you still
won't let go of this.
I want to catch
up to my sister!
I'm not special like
her. I'm mediocre.
But I can't just give up.
I refuse to give this up!
Please, Kai.
Tell me I'm not crazy.
I don't think I can.
But...
Mizuka is gone. Dead.
Subaru is seriously injured.
And you're still
thinking about the expo?
You can't just go off on
your own and expect it to be
all right. You aren't the
only one who's disappointed.
We all made GunBuild-2.
I mean, do you honestly
not see how selfish
you're being right now?
Yes, I get it.
Well, I'm not convinced!
I do!
Kai.
I'm going to see
the vice-principal.
The sooner we get all these
robots dismantled, the better.
You don't mean that.
Hold on! Kai!
Come back! Stop walking!
Please, Kai. This is
the last hope I have left.
It's the only link
I have to all of you.
My only link to my sister!
Don't do this. Please, Kai!
You know. It kinda sounds like
you're asking me for a favor.
Huh?
And you know what that means.
You're gonna have to beat
me in a KILL-BALLAD match.
That's not fair.
What'll it be?
Gonna play or not?
You know I can't beat you.
What about
refusing to give up?
Come on. Let's play.
Show me how serious
you really are
about doing this.
You jerk.
What's the matter,
Snapping Turtle Aki?
You jerk.
Not so ridiculously
optimistic now?
You are such
a jeeeeerrrrkkkk!
Is that all you've got?
Come on.
Comeoncomeoncomeon!
I want to catch
up to my sister!
She says I'm mediocre. That
our robot's nothing but junk.
I'll prove she's
wrong about me!
I have to. I have to!
I have to! I have to!
Huh?
Well, that's that.
Wait, what?
Did I just beat you?
Sure did. It was
close, but you won.
But how could--?
I mean did you?
Hey, do you have any candy?
Yeah sure.
Great, thanks.
I'll pay you back later.
You managed to beat me.
I'll stick with you to the end.
To the Tokyo expo
or wherever else.
Looks like it's just
the two of us again, huh?
It shouldn't make much
difference I think we were
the only ones who could
make it to the expo, anyway.
Ya damn brats!
Gettin' frisky in public!
Oh. Hey, Doc.
Wait, you're
the one in charge of
dismantling
the club's robots?
Well, that's what the school
hired me to do, anyway,
but now I've changed my mind.
See, I'm thinkin' of fixin'
up these two robots here.
Just for my own personal
entertainment, of course.
Would you guys have any
interest in helping me out?
Oh, Doc!
Hey! What are you doing?
Mitchi?
What the hell, who said you guys
could get started without me?
Look, we're not
gonna tear them apart!
I'm sorry, but
we refuse to give up!
We're gonna fix up
GunBuild-2 and enter the expo!
Huh?
You heard the girl
loud and clear, Mitsuhiko.
Well, that's a relief.
Wow! I thought Doc here was
about to start dismantling
'em. Glad to see I was wrong.
Here. For you.
Money! Where'd
you get all this?
Aw, man, you didn't
steal it did you?
Idiot! I just made
the school give it back.
What do you
mean "give it back?"
You already forget
you took second place
at ROBO-ONE last year?
This is the prize money.
So, what d'ya think?
It should be enough to
keep you funded for a while.
Thank you, Mitchi!
But why would
you do this for us?
I can't let the
club end like this.
Can you imagine how
pissed off Irei would be?
You're not half bad.
You're in trouble if the
vice-principal finds out.
That's a problem
for another day.
Kai.
Huh?
We can make it to the expo!
All the way to
Tokyo! And my sister!
You must safeguard
the information.
Hey Gezi.
Yes?
Kimijima Report Number
Seven is on the screen.
Download it now, please.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
I want to have
all the information
before we go to Tokyo.
Command confirmed.
Kimijima Report Number Seven.
Download now in progress.
What's happening?
Hey, Gezi. I'm not seeing a
report here. What's going on?
It appears that Kimijima
Report Number Seven does not
contain text as
previous reports did.
Huh? What do you mean
there's not any text?
Kimijima Report Number
Seven execution complete.
Copies of the six previous
Kimijima Reports have
now been disseminated
worldwide through IRUO.
Disseminated? What
are you talking about?
Aki and Kai arrive at the expo
hall with Gunbuild 2 in tow.
As in previous years,
the site is filled
wall-to-wall with robots.
People have come to
see their dreams come true.
Aki learns that her sister,
Misaki, will attend the expo.
Aki's anticipation and
anxiousness for their reunion
is tempered by what
Gunbuild 2 does next.
Episode 18.
Let's hit it off everybody!
Later days!