I have been waiting eagerly.
For the bright, chilly sky.
For the freezing wind. For the
fluttering, white snowflakes.
It has to be more than just
an ordinary snow, though.
It has to be something special.
A snow that's surprising,
almost miraculous.
Yes. Like soft, powdery snow
on Christmas Eve, for example.
Weather lady! Weather
lady! Will it snow on
December 24th this year? Is
there going to be a miracle?
Man, this thing is
acting all screwy.
Do you think it's messed up
because of the solar storm?
I heard it's interfering
with a lot of
pads' function
and connectivity.
Makes sense. Kona was actually
griping to me earlier about
a bunch of PCs
being broken, too.
Well, it was a
pretty major storm.
That may be it. The storm could
be the reason IRUO's needed
so much maintenance lately.
Yeah, and maybe it's also
the reason we haven't decided
what to do after we graduate.
Hey! Good point! Which means
the horrible grade I got
on my finals was obviously...
No question. Totally
the solar storm's fault.
Oh, my. What is this
place? Hello, excuse me!
Is anybody there?
Guys, it's a ghost! A ghost
in my pad! What do I do?
Airi?
Yeah, it's her. She's been
acting pretty strange lately.
She doesn't usually do this.
I don't think she's ever tried
to start a conversation
with anyone but me until now.
Do you think this is because
of the solar storm, too?
Okay, solar storm, GTFO!
Being responsible means
not blaming things on others.
Keep your spirits high.
We'll get through this!
GTFO, too, Genki bot.
What the--? Uh-oh.
That was truly pathetic.
I didn't think it was even
possible to be that
bad at something.
Well hey, I warned you I
wasn't going to be any good.
Why do you think I ate ten
passion fruit buns up front?
'Cause I knew teaching me wasn't
gonna be easy for you to do.
I know, but seriously,
you're not even watching
the waves, Kai! It's no wonder
you can't so much as stand up.
That's all I can
take today. Let's go.
Wait, hey! Come back, Mizuka!
The real world is big,
but Airi's world was small.
That's why master made
Airi like this, so she could
learn a little about
the big, wide world.
Hey. Pay attention, will ya?
There's only one flag left
for the sixth Kimijima
report. "Go to the beach
and surf a wave for
three or more seconds."
That's the last thing
I hafta do to unlock it.
The weather forecast
for today, December 12th,
through tomorrow,
December 13th.
Those living in the
Tanegashima region can
expect clear,
cloudless skies. On the--
What the. She's glitching
up now? Not Airi, too.
Okay, Mom, I'm back now.
Yo.
So. What're you doing here?
Inviting you to
a Christmas party.
More like a drinking party.
I guess you could say that. All
the usuals are gonna be there.
Never thought I'd see the
day when you'd go down to
the ocean again. You
must be really passionate
about this gig as
Yashio's surfing coach, huh?
I don't think passionate's
the right way to put it.
I dunno. I guess I just...
Epic surfer fail, huh?
If you're gonna be
like that, I'm hanging up.
H-Have you seen
the IRUO notice?
Why? Something going on?
Th-They're doing extensive
maintenance. On the 24th.
It just had to be
right around Christmas.
When all the real-lifers come
crawling out of the woodwork.
What about people like me?
What about the shut-ins who
wanna see the world from the
comfort of their own homes?
That's tragic, but I don't
get what it has to do with me.
Well, there's always a chance
they'll do a server reset
and wipe all
the existing data.
So, in other words,
Airi might go bye-bye, too.
This really sucks. I have to
access all the Kimijima Reports
by Christmas Eve, or they're
gonna disappear for good?
Wow, you're a jerk.
What about never getting
to talk to Airi anymore?
Talk about an epic sadface.
Although, if I had to choose,
I would pick Gezi
over Airi, so many more
possibilities for
depraved conversation!
Snow, snow, snow! Snow
is falling, falling down.
Snow is falling,
hit the ground!
Aw, loli-girl!
Oh, yeah. That reminds me,
Akiho said she wants to
throw a Christmas
party. And, uh.
She wanted to
invite Airi, too.
A C-Christmas party?
Like, IRL?
She was also very
enthusiastic about
the idea of
exchanging presents.
Ooh, Christmas
presents? Really?
I have lots of erotic
novels. You can have as many
as you want, my
lovely little loli! w00t!
The only present Airi wants
is snow! It would be like
a dream come true if there
was snow on Christmas Eve!
You see, that's what Airi
wishes for every year,
with her whole heart!
A white Christmas!
Watch the waves.
Gotta watch the waves.
I'm surfing!
Did you see that, Airi?
It was awesome!
I must've surfed that wave
for five whole seconds!
Fun! Now, would you like to hear
tomorrow's weather forecast?
The Tanegashima Region
can expect clear skies.
Gezi. Hey, what the--?
Will you please stop poking me
like that. It doesn't feel good.
'Kay, sorry. But I
really want to know
the flag completion status.
Right! Airi is on
the case! Let's see. Oh!
It looks like the final
flag has just been cleared!
The AR annotation
has been made visible!
Let's hurry up and find it!
Quick, it's going to snow!
Snow is falling, falling
down. Snow is falling.
December 23rd. The day
before Christmas Eve.
Yhe day Airi might've
disappeared for good.
That was the day I finally
found Kimijima Report Number 6.
Utilizing the media to
disseminate fabrication as
reality is already an
outdated method of persuasion.
Rather, twenty-first
century propaganda will
function by augmenting
fantasy into reality.
Why do these things have to be
so complicated and confusing?
They make my head hurt.
All right, Report Number 7
should be the final one.
What are the flags?
Leeet's seeee. In order
to access Report Number 7,
all six previous reports
need to be unlocked.
And that's all!
Wait, so that's it?
No missions to complete
like with the other ones?
Apparently not. It sounds
like it's been made visible now
but unfortunately,
I don't know where it is.
Man. Gimme a break.
Umm. Airi would really like to
go back to her home now, please.
Airi's birthday is tomorrow!
Airi wants to go home
for her birthday and Christmas
Eve. Would that be okay?
Wait, hold on. You were
programmed to have a birthday?
That's unusual.
Not really "programmed."
But Christmas Eve was the day
Airi first woke up, so
it's sort of like a birthday.
Oh. Okay, well, in that case,
what was programmed
as your home?
It isn't programmed!
It's really Airi's home!
It's the actual place where
Airi and her master lived!
We have to go to
Kimijima's place. Really?
It's completely falling apart.
Is that how you see it?
For Airi, it's still as nice
and tidy as she remembers
it being nine years ago.
So it is.
There's something about
this room. It seems familiar.
My master was an amazing
person! So sweet and kind!
Sometimes Airi would
cook for him as a way of
saying "thank you." That's
what this room was for.
I don't know how
that would work.
I've never heard of
an AI cooking before.
A basement?
Down there is where my
master has his work room.
Look at that.
It's just like the door in the
old museum. Which should mean.
Hidden Hand.
What does this machine do?
There should be some buttons
there. Do you see them?
Airi, what--?
I-I don't understand!
I haven't seen her in a long
time. Her name is Airi Yukifune.
She is the original Airi.
The original?
It's untreatable. That's what
the doctors said. "Untreatable."
My illness is serious, though
not actually life-threatening,
but I would suffer greatly
for the rest of my life.
That's what they said, anyway.
Eventually, I found the only
thing I ever looked forward to
was the weather forecast.
As I lay there, I told myself
that if a miracle happened
and our southern island had snow
on Christmas Eve, then maybe,
just maybe, I would
miraculously get better, too.
So as the end of December
rolled around every year,
I'd watch the weather
forecast a dozen times a day,
sighing every time
they predicted sunshine.
That's when I
met Kou Kimijima.
The man who would
become Airi's master.
He knew all about my
illness and how sick I was.
So one day he gave me
the most wonderful present.
It was something he was
working on at the time.
Something incredible.
He gave me an
alpha version of IRUO.
With it, I got to travel to
places all around the world
and I could
talk to him about
all the exciting
adventures I had!
However, it wasn't long before
those pleasant days were
nothing more
than a nice memory.
My illness steadily worsened and
I gave up the childish idea that
a miracle would happen
and I'd be healed.
But when Kimijima
found this out, he said...
Oh, Airi, I'm so sorry.
But I think I may know a way
to make your wish
come true. However.
It would be very dangerous.
This is the
chamber you'll sleep in.
It will likely be
decades before you wake up.
But when you do,
things will be different.
You'll wake to an era when your
illness has become curable.
Although, I'm sure you'll be
lonely sleeping all that time,
so I'll make sure
you're able to dream.
And that's when he
created the Airi you know.
Inside IRUO.
My new dream world.
Good night for now,
my Sleeping Beauty.
Good night, Kimijima.
Thank you so much.
Sweet dreams, little one.
I went back and forth over it
for a long time, but I ended up
reporting the simple
truth to the police.
Time for tomorrow's weather
forecast. As usual for this time
of year, the Tanegashima region
will experience clear skies
and a zero percent
chance of precipitation.
Guess what Airi learned today.
"A kiss on a white Christmas
will make love blossom."
That's what the
weather lady said, anyway.
Hey, Brother, are you in love?
Dunno. That's a good question.
Evading it isn't fair.
All right, what about
you? Are you in love?
Airi can't be in love. That
sort of thing isn't included
in her programming. But,
as a girl, it is interesting.
If it snows, will you.
What?
If a miracle does
happen, a kiss would be
a nice way to commemorate
it. Will you give me one?
Well, that's it.
Merry Christmas Eve!
It looks like it isn't
going to snow after all, huh?
I did have my hopes up a
little. Even so, Airi still had
a very nice time in her dream.
I'm so glad I got
to meet you, Brother.
Airi really loved
talking to you.
I'm glad we met, too, but
do you have to talk like that?
Like it's the end of
everything? It might not be.
There's still a chance
that whatever maintenance
they're doing won't
erase you, ya know.
I guess that's true. But
still, since it never snows,
I gave up believing in
miracles a long time ago.
Snowflakes. Look,
Brother, it's snowing!
Airi can see it, too!
All white and soft!
Looks like today's
weather report was wrong!
So now here's the
updated forecast for tonight!
In the Tanegashima
region, there will be...
...clear skies followed by snow!
Hey, Brother!
You remember the
promise from earlier?
Promise? Wait! You
really want me to kiss you?
I do! So, where
is it going to be?
On the forehead,
or on the cheek?
Or maybe it's on Airi's lips?
In case you're wondering,
the forehead would
be Airi's first choice.
Are you serious?
Oh, no! You're not going to
break your promise, are you?
Just when it's
finally snowing, too.
Brother. What's wrong?
Why is Airi crying like this?
I don't understand what's
happening. I don't feel sad.
Who knows, maybe
it's another glitch.
If that's the case, then
I should thank my master.
Because this is one glitch
that Airi doesn't mind so much.
Thank you, Brother.
Having a crane
makes this a lot faster.
So what do you think?
Is the monopole motor
really going to work?
Oh yeah! I'm totally fired up!
So, Yashio, what's the deal.
Have you tried calling for
Airi since they finished
the maintenance on IRUO?
Why would I? There's
no point. She was erased.
Well, why don't you
give it a try, anyway?
Like right now, I mean.
What could it hurt?
Airi.
See? It's like
I said, she's gone.
They deleted her like
a virus from a hard drive.
You're sure? But I could have
sworn I saw Airi just yesterday.
Really? Well if so,
then why didn't she
show up when I called her?
Because she isn't here.
Airi is gone.
The only one left is--
It's Gezi!
Yes. Accordingly, there will be
some changes to our interaction.
There is no need to
touch, no need to tap,
and certainly no need to
kiss me on the forehead.
Kiss your forehead? But.
Hold on a second! You
actually remember that?
I am not sure. It is
not immediately clear why
Gezi referred to you kissing
her on the forehead just now.
A check is underway to search
for any possible viruses.
Well, I couldn't say if it's
a virus or not, but either way
it's perfectly all right with
me. I know this is a little
late, but Merry Christmas to
you, Gezi, and to Airi, too.
And the same to you,
Yashio. Merry Christmas.
Gunbuild 2 is finally
on the way to completion.
A Monopole motor-drive system.
A laser-based power supply.
Despite the many
obstacles to be faced,
Aki is excited about
the upcoming expo,
but what tragedy will occur
when Mizuka confronts Kai
while he searches for yet
another Kimijima Report?
Episode 16.
Let's hit it off everybody!
Later days!