Password?
And how am I
supposed to know that?
I haven't even met you yet.
Maybe you could just
tell me what the password is?
Marco
Polo?
R T F M.
Okay, how about ROFL?!
GTFO.
Man, this is
real thirsty work.
Hey, could you go get
me something to drink?
I'm afraid not.
No one ever told you
to respect your elders?
Please stop acting
like you're my superior.
I don't come out here for
the joy of being bossed around
by older club members.
But you know it's
gonna happen anyway,
so why do you come out here?
I happen to find this
to be an ideal environment
in which to work.
Until now, I had to perform
the M45's maintenance in secret.
Having a masked
alter ego must be tough.
So, you ever get the
KILL-BALLAD control
system installed, or what?
Not yet. I'm in talks with
Furugori regarding that,
I tried to speak
with her yesterday, but...
Um, hi!
A-Are you Furugori?
No, dude, that's Daitoku.
Uh, hello, it's nice
to meet you.
Sorry. Am I
interrupting something?
No way, not at all.
I'm glad you came!
Oh, good. Because I thought
about what you told me
the other day.
That I should come out
and visit the club's
hangar at least once.
Oh, that's Subaru Hidaka,
our club's great hope.
He's in his second year.
Hello.
Sorry, he's unfriendly
to everybody.
Don't take it personally.
What is this? Has she come
to confess her love for Kai?!
Huh?
What are you yelling
about Aki? You're scaring her.
She's here to check out
the Robot Research Club,
so chill out.
Oh! Is that why you're here?
Wonderful!
I'm so glad you came!
Come on take a look around!
By the way, the wind out
here gets pretty strong.
Personally, I like
taking naps on the runway.
Though not necessarily at
this time of year. Too breezy.
Yeah, I think I can
see what you mean.
All right! This one's for
our new club members,
Subaru and Junna!
To you guys!
To you.
T-To us?
This is awesome!
I gotta say,
I didn't expect you
to join the
club right away, Jun.
Yeah, I know. I wasn't
expecting to join either.
And it's thanks to me,
and my willingness
to fall to my knees and beg.
Uh, Chief, that's not really
something I would boast about.
So, Robot fear conquered?
I seem okay with
GunBuild-1, at least.
Hey, I know what your
first act as a new member
of the club should be.
You can come out with
us to the Robo Clinic!
I-I can't.
I just can't, I'm sorry!
Uhh. No, no, no
I was only kidding!
Just please don't cry, okay?
I know, why don't you
have another Skal, huh?
If we're done, it's time
for me to be going now.
Really? It hasn't even been
three minutes since our toast.
Three minutes is plenty of
time for a welcoming party.
So goodbye.
Thanks for the drink.
Huh? Hey, hold on a minute!
Subaru! Come back here!
Kou Kimijima.
Where did you get this?
Uchugaoka Park. Inside the
abandoned folk museum.
Tell me, have you seen
a girl named Airi?
How did you- do you know
something about this?
Yes, actually I do.
Well, sort of,
but not anything about the
convoluted stuff written here.
I met him a long time ago.
It was back when I was
still in high school.
Airi was one of Misa's friends.
That's all, really.
She knew Misa?
Hey Dad, I'm home.
Hey.
Oh, you see,
the scooter's been acting up,
so I was just fiddling
with the engine.
Don't worry,
I'll wash it myself.
Hey! I know you're there!
Well? Are you going
to come out here, or not?
U-Umm, hello? I'm sorry,
but are you speaking to Airi?
Listen, there's something
I wanna talk to you about.
Sure. May I call you "Brother,"
like I did before?
Yeah, go right ahead.
Okay, Brother! What would
you like to talk to me about?
The weather forecast, perhaps?
Never mind about the weather.
Oh. Okay then.
Alright, so tell me, do you
know someone named Misa
or Misaki Senomiya?
Of course I know Misaki!
She and Airi are friends!
Yeah? So you guys,
hang out and stuff, then?
Oh, yes.
She talked to me a lot.
She'd tell me about
what was going on at school,
and about her friends.
Let's see if I remember
what their names were.
Mizuka, Keiko,
Mitsuhiko, Yuuichi.
Oh, and she spoke about
Akiho all the time, as well.
And you, Brother!
She talked about me?
She often remarked
about "kicking your butt"
at fighting games.
Then what about
Kou Kimijima? Who is he?
Oh, yes, Kou Kimijima?
He's Airi's master, of course.
The one who created Airi!
There, that noise.
It's dark down here.
Airi, can you see like this,
without any light?
No. I can't see
where you are now.
My visual capabilities rely on
IRUO, so I can't see anything
if you're in an
unmapped location.
That's a big help.
That hurt!
What was that?
Did something open?
Not that I can see.
Hey. What is that? A door.
Uh. Hidden Hand.
There's electricity down here?
Hey, this looks
like one of those
old music players
that use cassette tapes.
Wow. What is going on here?
Airi, this tape.
Is it the source of that
"beee-boo-boo" sound?
Do you even know
what I'm talking about?
Oh, you mean, "bee-bee-boo"?
You're right,
what was I thinking?
Is this what causes it?
Airi can't see what
you're referring to.
Please ask Gezi, instead.
All right.
Your access has been confirmed.
Switch to Gezi
mode was successful.
Can you tell me what
this machine is, exactly?
The EGI system.
EGI?
Yes, that is correct.
It emits sounds
with specific wavelengths into
space at regular intervals.
These sounds can be picked up
by PhoneDroid pads, as well,
which play them as audio files.
Can you tell me what
this Kou Kimijima guy
was trying to
accomplish on this island?
That is confidential.
Well then can you at
least tell me how he died?
My master was murdered.
S-Somebody killed him? Who?
Data pertaining to that question
have been deleted from memory.
Excuse me, Frau, it appears
someone has come to visit you!
Ignoring a visitor would
be very impolite, you know.
Boys with glasses are mega hot.
Your breathing sure
is getting heavy.
But that doesn't apply to you,
3-D boy with glasses, oh no!
You annoy me! Now, GTFO!
Hi... I'm Subaru Hidaka...
Will you at least hear what I
have to say? That's all I ask.
I've reported you.
Ugh. Curse this griefer!
IANAL, but this is
so lawsuit material!
No! Please, just wait.
I came to discuss the
KILL-BALLAD control
program you wrote.
Nothing else! You and Yashio
know each other, right?
Yashio? Oh. You mean UMISHO?
He and I are going
to enter the ROBO-ONE
world championship together.
I was hoping you would write
a control program for us.
With your help, we have a real
shot at winning the tournament!
Please, you have to help us.
Taiyou Development.
Why would they buy
an abandoned building and
then pay its electric bills?
And how does
Kimijima fit into this?
I give up. This is nothing
more than one man's fantasy.
What's the point in
playing along?
I would just be wasting
my time if I kept digging.
I have made an
arrangement with Furugori.
And so, Kona Furugori
is the newest member
of the Robot Research Club!
Let's give her a hand, huh?
Still! Why didn't
you come here in person?!
I'm a shut-in?
Urgh! What is it that
makes all these new members
think they can get away
with being so freaking cheeky!
So you know, I'm including
you in that group, too.
Fine. All I care about
is getting her to do
the programming for the M45
in time for the tournament.
And don't forget the payment.
A full-nude photo shoot.
The glasses can stay on,
but otherwise,
you'll wear nothing
but your birthday suit.
You're- You're posing,
fully nude?!
That is not at all
what we agreed on!
The deal was that Yashio
would help you hunt cheaters.
You can't change it now!
A naked photo of you
guys on an African safari?
He said "cheaters," Jun.
Not "cheetahs".
Like as in, highly ranked
KILL-BALLAD players
who find ways to cheat
during their battles.
Can't you do that kind
of thing yourself, Kona?
I mean, you did
create KILL-BALLAD.
I don't like being
called Kona, plzkthx.
All right, then how
about I call you Frau Bow?
Yes, NP. That's A-OK.
I'm glad that's settled,
but we do need
to meet in person
to discuss things.
I see. You're a pervert!
Huh?
I only just moved here,
and you expect me
to invite a boy from
school into my home?
Sounds like porn to me.
I've got an idea.
Why don't you leave me alone
and spend the night
at Yashio's place?
Something tells me I'm not
going to like that girl.
She's even harder to
deal with than Subaru.
I have no intention of being
"dealt with" by anyone.
That attitude is exactly what
makes you so hard to deal with!
There's a lot more to
this club than I expected.
You're all so
smart and talented!
We are amazing, aren't we?
Oh, that gets me fired up!
What are you
so fired up about now?
Amazing things can happen
when amazing people
get together, Kai!
You know, I think it's time to
storm the Space Candy company!
Come on guys, let's go!
After all of that
Jun and I were
the only ones who came?!
What? It's finished already?
Are you kidding?
Seventy-two hour stints
are nothing to me, nOOb.
You worked on it for
seventy-two hours straight?
That's how I operate.
Once I start something,
I don't sleep
until I'm finished.
Don't go thinking
I pulled three all-nighters
in a row just for your sake.
She sounded weird.
What was that?
It's nice and smooth.
Pretty responsive, too.
It's almost impossible
to believe. How could she
create something of this
caliber in only a few days?
Hey, how did things go
with the company?
So now you're
pretending like you care?
After the two
of you refused to go?
Still...
Hi-ya!
That's impaaaaact!
Well done!
You finally found it!
This is precisely the kind of
impact that I was looking for!
He really took a liking
to Jun for some reason.
So. He agreed to sponsor us,
all thanks to her!
Now we can finally work
toward our ultimate goal!
We'll start by putting the
star on GUNVARREL'S waist.
Oh! I almost forgot! I was
thinking it would be really cool
to add an exact replica
of its scarf, too.
You're glowing, you know.
Huh?
People who are passionate
about their dreams
have a glow about
them no one else has.
I was like that before
my dream came to an end.
Somethin' wrong?
No. It's nothing. I'm fine.
Now let's get to work.
Could you help me conduct
a test battle with the M45?
Man, that move
is really amazing.
You can be a real jerk
sometimes, but figuring out how
to use the Pile Bunkers like
that makes you okay in my book.
I had you pegged
as more of a sword
or hammer person
this entire time, actually.
Sheesh! Can't you be nice
while I'm complimenting you?
You all set down there?
We're ready when you are!
I don't think you boys know
what you've gotten
yourselves into.
I'll kick your butt
in three seconds flat!
Don't get worked up. Geez,
you're just a sparring partner.
Robots to your corners.
Ready and fight!
Go!
Oh, you're just comin' straight
at me with no fancy moves, huh?
Speed's what counts.
You'll see!
Lemme try again!
Take this! GUNVAL Uppercut!
You're pretty bad at this,
Aki. Wanna keep going?
You leave me no choice!
As swift as the wind!
As strong as the sea!
Tanegashi Accel Impaaaact!
You just wanted an excuse
to shout that, didn't you?
You dodged it! No fair!
Get it, Jun! Go on, hurry!
Oh, right!
Wow, she's fast. I guess
it's from all that karate.
I should have her on hand
whenever I practice the
Tanegashi Accel Impact.
C'mon, Aki. Take this seriously.
That's enough. This was
more than sufficient for
a test match. I'm surprised
you were able to master
the M45 in such a
short time. Good job today.
Whoa. A compliment?
From you?
I admit that your skills
as a gamer are formidable.
Asking you to be
the operator was a great dec-
Who's he?
Who are you?! What the hell
do you think you're doing?!
Please, Chief.
I would appreciate it
if you would stay of this.
It's okay. This is
between me and my father.
He's your father?
You will explain
what's going on here.
This was my dream.
I couldn't just give it up.
Don't give me that dream crap.
You made me a promise
two years ago that you would
give up this robot nonsense.
That you'd follow
in my footsteps
and become a fisherman.
Or were those
just more lies?! Well?!
It wasn't like that.
Oh, yeah? Then what
the hell is this?!
This lousy toy!
No, don't! Don't hurt it!
It may just seem
like a toy to you, but to
us it's a living thing!
It's been brought to life
through Subaru's
passion and hard work!
So please don't hurt it!
If you do,
it's the same thing
as hurting Subaru himself!
Please, Chief. I meant it when
I asked you to stay out of this.
Subaru.
Come on, boy.
We'll talk about this at home.
I have to go now.
And please, dispose of
the M45 however you see fit.
Just throw it away?
It doesn't matter.
My dream has come to an end.
Goodbye.
Such an incredibly
sad thing, having a dream end.
What's happening?!
Are you having an attack?!
Can you hear me?!
Aki!
After Subaru's father discovers
what his son has been up to,
Subaru gives up
everything in his life
having to do with robots.
Refusing to take
no for an answer,
Aki fights to keep
him in the club.
Meanwhile,
Kai pays Frau a visit.
He learns about her
tragic past and the mystery
at the heart of it.
Murder, secrets, conspiracy.
Little does he
know that, for all of them,
the mystery has only begun.
Episode 7!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!