I remember May twenty-first
of two thousand and ten well.
Aww. I lose again?
Twelve wins in a row! You need
ten more years' experience
if you want to
beat the master.
One more match! Please!
I promise I won't ask again!
Oh my gosh!
You guys ready?
It's almost time!
Wake up!
Sleepy.
Worried face. Pig snout!
Come on, sleepy head!
The rocket's about to launch!
[QUIET CHATTER]
Wow! It's so awesome!
Amazing! There it goes!
Yeah! Alright!
Go, Hot Dog, go!
What does that mean?
It's a line from an old movie.
Listen, when you grow up, Kai,
I want you to be a man
with the "right stuff," okay?
Yeah, I remember that day.
It was four months
before the incident.
What's taking Aki so long?
Drawing upon
our long relationship,
the Chuo Tanegashima High
School Robot Research Club
requests the following
three things from JAXA.
Number one. Facilities
for assembling a robot.
Number two. Personnel versed
in robotic engineering.
And number three. At least one
million yen in research funds.
One million?
Yes. That is the
absolute minimum we require.
One million.
Very well.
I understand your requests,
but before we speak further.
Your dear old dad
could use a restroom break.
No you don't! You're just
trying to avoid the whole issue!
No, it's not like
that at all, I promise.
But you're the director of
the Tanegashima Space Center!
You can make
this happen, can't you?
Sure, I am
technically the director,
but I have all the power
of a mid-level manager.
I basically just do what
my superior asks me to.
Don't ruin my image of
you like that! You're my dad!
You're supposed to be my hero!
Come on, Kai, help me out.
Say something!
Uh.
GunBuild-1 is a special project!
It's not some ordinary robot!
Misaki was the
one who started it, and now
it's the culmination of
both your daughters' dreams!
Hmm. Oh, okay.
Tell you what, sweetie, I'll
talk it over with your mother.
You know she
doesn't understand dreams
or lofty ideals or
anything like that!
Not like you, Dad.
You were different!
You were the passionate one,
always daring to
go for your dreams
and stay true to yourself!
My whole life,
as long as I can remember,
I've loved that about you!
Thank you, sweetie.
But not now, it's like
all of your passion
has just evaporated!
It makes me so sad!
But if there is still
some fire in your heart.
If you still are the dad
I love. Then you'll help me--
Hello?
Exactly what do
you think you're doing,
barging into your
father's workplace
and pestering him for money.
Please, Mom, I just wanted--
Oh, no... Don't give me that!
Your father may
be lenient with you,
but I don't remember raising
such a conniving little-
Well, that was an epic bust.
I was just about ready
to let loose with a
GUNVAL Ankh Striker in there.
It was never gonna happen.
Your demands are crazy.
What did you expect
them to be able to help with?
The TNSC is just
a rocket launch site.
I know that, but JAXA does
have an astrorobotics branch.
I thought they'd be interested.
Like I told you before
you left for the meeting.
If you want help
from the Robotics Division,
look further out.
You should go to
Tokyo or Tsukuba, instead.
"Why must you always
insist on quibbling?!"
Sorry to say it, but I
think he might have a point.
Huh?! You're siding
with him, you traitor?!
And here I was planning to let
you be GunBuild-1's pilot, too.
Pilot that monster? Me?
Yeah, that's pretty
much the last thing I want.
What?! But the
pilot's the star of the show!
It'd be an honor!
You know what they say:
"One man's honor
is another man's
human sacrifice."
You're too kind-hearted
for your own good, Yashio.
If it was me, I'd be
headed for the hills by now.
You two are impossible!
Fine, then!
At least there's still the
ROBO-ONE prize money
to work with.
I'll just use that to
finish GUNVARRELL on my own!
So, here's the deal. There's
no money coming your way.
You know I'm talking about
the prize money, Mitchi,
and not a
personal contribution. Right?
Yeah. I know that.
I swear, I will call
the police!
You really think
I would pocket your money?!
This is how things work
in the public school system.
The prize money
will be added to
your club's funds
for the next school year.
The next school year?
Yep. Next April, to be exact.
But I'll have
graduated by then.
You might get held back.
Yeah, thanks.
A tip from me to you,
Little Senomiya.
Don't call me that, Mitchi!
Oh yeah? Well,
then don't call me Mitchi!
Now, listen to me yo--
Great! What am I
gonna do now?
I still owe
Doc a ton of money!
Guess the only choice
at this point is to give up.
I'm with him.
Ugh! I hate you two!
Huh?
What's up?
I'm gonna go home now.
Yeah. Fine, go!
According to this.
That's where
I'm supposed to go?
That's the Thunder Emperor.
Well you're not exactly dressed
for the occasion are you?
Huh?
Listen. When you're
doin' stuff like this,
it's usually a good idea
to wear your gym clothes.
Just a tip from me to you.
What do you mean
"stuff like this"?
All I got was a
message to come here.
Yeah. It kinda
took me by surprise.
I didn't think you and
Furugori knew each other.
Furugori?
When did you two hook up?
When we went to Tokyo?
You're a stud!
It sounds like somebody's
just been messing with me.
Kay, I'm outta here.
No!
You would go without helping me?
I hate this stupid island.
Totally unacceptable.
Hold on, you're
FRAUKOUJIRO, aren't you?
That's a new one.
A nickname or something?
Huh? So, her real
name's Furugori?
Yeah, that's right.
Kona Furugori.
She's transferring to
Chuo Tanegashima High School
starting tomorrow.
Kona.
Use that meatspace
handle and die!
Tera-barfy.
I don't really understand,
but whatever.
C'mon, let's get started.
There's a lot to do.
Huh? Start what?
Well, helping her
move in, obviously.
That stupid assistant
principal. Why should I have
to help some new student
lug around stupid boxes?
Moving in?
This is where you live?
It's been bought.
By who?
By me, obviously.
Hey! Yashio!
Come here, gimme a
hand, will ya?
Forget it.
I'm getting outta here.
Look, if you really want
my help moving your stuff,
you're gonna have to beat
me in a KILL-BALLAD match.
You-- You asked
for programming code,
and I gave it
to you, didn't I?
Y-You owe me one, IMHO.
See, Frau is
willing to help others,
but not without getting
something for it in return.
Remove the cockpit? No way!
Giant robots are
designed to be ridden in!
Once, but these blueprints
are from ten years ago.
These days,
the remote-controlled
types are the norm.
This exterior
needs to come off, too.
What?! That would look stupid!
Look, I'm sorry,
but it's gotta go.
This robot already has
enough weight issues as it is.
Do you honestly hope to
take something as defective
as this junk pile
to the Expo? I mean--
Don't talk about it that way!
GunBuild-1 has been
around from the start.
The first Robot Research Club
members worked hard on it!
It represents
the club's history!
There's no way I'm gonna
tear it apart, piece by piece!
So that's a big, fat "no"
to everything you
just suggested okay?
Fine. Whatever. I was
just trying to do my part
as a member of the club, but
if you don't want to listen.
Dismantle it? I can't.
Hey, what's up?
How're you feeling?
At the moment? Horrible.
Then I have something
equally horrible to tell you.
You know the
Space Candy I always eat?
Guess who runs the company?
No idea.
Mitchi's uncle, apparently.
This sucks.
I've been giving money
to the Nagafukada family
this whole time.
And?
It kinda makes me
want to ask for it back,
and then the club would
actually have some money
to continue the project.
Once again, thank you
for the infor--
I see you're as good
a friend to her as ever.
What's up? Are your
legs bothering you again?
No, just doing a tune-up.
I like to take care
of this much myself.
The Crash happened
back in twenty-fifteen,
so I've had this
for about four years now.
It's held up really well.
Good thing, too. I bet it
would be pretty hard for you
to toss out something
Misa sent you.
Hey! Is there anybody in here?
I've got a delivery!
Hello?
thx.
Man, you look like
a ghost back there.
Whazzis?
Oh, it's Skal. I guess you
don't see it much in Tokyo.
TY.
What?
thx.
Your comprehension
is full of fail!
Sure, whatever.
Anyway, I'm leaving.
Are you gonna be
okay here all by yourself?
The renovations are
scheduled to begin tomorrow.
Securing this place is
my top priority. No question.
There's my collection
of sordid images to think of.
It easily exceeds
one tera in size.
In that case,
wouldn't a normal house
have been the better choice?
GTFO! The "abandoned ruins"
vibe here is way cute, IMO.
I just need hot shirtless
men to guard it, plzkthx!
What about your parents?
AFK.
What?
NSFW.
Uh.
Did I say AMA? Fine.
My dad's in Tokyo,
and my mom...
Your mom is?
I'm home.
All right, it's the
bottom of the third
and the pitcher takes the mound.
Know what I heard today?
Apparently there was
one of those
robot tournaments last week.
Oh was there, really?
I wouldn't know.
I've given up robots,
after all.
It appears that Yokoyama
is back in full form, indeed.
We all know he was plagued
with injuries last season,
but from his pitching
form today it's almost as if
nothing ever--
I never knew you
had such adorable pupils
at that school of yours!
Look at her!
She's a darling little thing!
I dunno. You got the
"little" part right, though.
I can't believe I'm asking
these people for help.
Anyway, what do you
think of my proposal?
Will you consider
backing our club?
I'd like to sponsor you,
but I'm afraid you
lack impact, you see.
No, I don't see.
Something that'll
make the young bucks sit up
and pay attention.
Somethin' with pow!
Chesty! Chesty!
Boing, boing, boing, boing.
Exactly right, my friend.
Just like that.
Um "boing, boing?"
I don't follow.
Well, you know,
a girl who's got a bit more
to offer in the chest area.
Come on, Uncle, that's not a
very polite thing to say,
especially to her.
Right, Little Senomiya?
Ah! I get it!
GUNVAL Ankh Strikeeeer!
Hey, can we talk?
I must be hearing things!
The great Mr. Pleiades
wants to talk to me?
Don't call me that. I actually
want to ask you something.
It's about ROBO-ONE.
The first world championship
is next month in Las Vegas.
I've been chosen
to represent Japan.
You don't say.
I was wondering if
you would team up with--
I think I'll pass, thanks.
Already? But I haven't
even finished talking yet.
Don't worry, it's alright.
I wasn't gonna
pay attention anyway.
You fought so well
in the last tournament.
If we were a team,
we could take on the world,
doesn't that interest you?
Hold on a sec. Are you
into me or something?
Okay, I'll be frank.
I honestly cannot stand you.
Well, I'm glad
to hear it's mutual.
But, I admire your
skills as an operator.
Yeah, I really couldn't care
less what you think about me.
Then I challenge
you to KILL-BALLAD.
If I beat you,
you'll do whatever I say.
No questions asked.
So. Do you wanna play?
Or are you afraid of losing?
That was a complete
and utter waste of time.
Kai?
Seriously?
You lost at KILL-BALLAD?!
Well, I won
twenty-one in a row,
but then lost the
twenty-second. I'm an idiot.
I should have set a limit
on the number of matches.
What?
Oh, I just find it funny that
you're Subaru's sidekick now.
I have to do it,
on my honor as a gamer.
Then play me! And if
I win, you'll be my underling!
I dunno.
Don't think that'd happen,
even if I didn't limit
the number of battles.
Oh, that's it!
Now I'm fired up!
I doubt that's gonna help.
Where is Subaru, anyway?
He went over to talk
to Frau. Apparently he wanted
to ask her about this
thing's control program.
Frau who?
From KB. She just
moved to Tanegashima.
What's the password?
Hi. My name's Subaru Hidaka.
I'm in the same class
as you-- U-Umm. Hello?
It's her program.
Her intellectual property.
I can't use it unless
I can get her permission.
Whoa, in that case,
you can count me out. Sorry.
We had a deal, remember?
You agreed to do whatever
I said if I beat you.
It's nice to see you
put in your place.
Hey, hold on a second! If
you two are gonna be spending
all your time getting
ready for this tournament,
then what's gonna happen with
construction on GunBuild-1?
It won't be much different,
it's not like I
was gonna help out anyway.
What?! Ahh..
GUNVAL Ankh Strikeeer!
All right. Let's begin.
We can worry about the
control program another day.
For now, you need to
familiarize yourself with
the M45's specialties
and fighting style.
Just "hang back
and wait," right?
Yes. You stay put until
the opponent rushes forward,
then grab and throw.
The passive approach
really isn't my thing.
That's not all. I've added
something to make up for such a
short-range attack.
See those Pile Bunkers?
How do you aim?
You don't need to.
If you fire one of them off
at this speed while
the enemy is in range.
You can't miss.
Hey, you can't use the Honorary
Chief as a punching bag!
Except when we fought,
you were able to dodge it.
Your reaction time during
that battle was inhuman.
I can't dismiss it as nonsense.
It was unbelievable. Do you
think you could show me again?
Not right now, thanks.
I've racked my brain,
but I still can't figure out
how you managed it.
Please, explain!
I'd rather not.
Go on, Kai.
I can tell you this.
It wasn't some kind of
special attack move
or anything like that.
It happened four months
after the day we all watched
the H2 rocket launch.
It was on September 11th,
two thousand-ten.
There was a mass fainting aboard
a ship called the Anemone.
We had just finished
a sightseeing tour
as part of a school field trip.
We were sailing back from
Kagoshima when
the incident occurred.
To this day,
nobody knows what caused
everyone onboard
that ferry to pass out.
There was more to it than
fainting for Aki and me, though.
We were the only ones who
experienced severe
side effects afterward.
Something known as the
Elephant-Mouse Syndrome.
It causes "Slow-Motion"
and "Fast-Forward" attacks.
The guy's younger than I am.
I can't let him get to me.
Oh, well.
That's over and done with.
Who the heck's TAGIRINGER?
What the--?
Who's Gezi? Signal
interference or something?
Huh?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Kai sets out to learn more about
the strange encounter he had
in the park and the confusing
message that he received.
While he and Junna are looking
into the island's urban legends
and rumors about
supernatural occurrences,
they discover a series
of odd events that have
taken place on Tanegashima.
Inside an old
abandoned building,
Kai comes upon what appears
to be the ghost
of a young girl,
one who has been watching
him for a very long time.
Episode 5!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!