Look, I haven't eaten
anything today, d00d.
Well, considering I barely
even move, one meal a day
is probably enough for me, TBH.
Keeps me from becoming a fatty.
Or are you saying
you like 'em plump?!
I'm not saying anything.
Just calm down
already, will ya? Here.
I know! You filled it with
knock-out drugs, didn't you?
And while I'm asleep,
completely helpless,
you'll have your way with me!
What a dirty plan!
Right out of an erotic game.
Suit yourself. If you
don't want it, I'll eat it.
TY. Come to mama, baby! Yum!
Well. I'm here.
Now, what's this about?
Most of @channel has it down
as a fake, but I don't want
to write it off yet. According
to unauthenticated rumor,
the final episode of
GUNVARREL has been leaked.
Really?
It's been almost four years
since it went off the air.
IDK why it's the
center of attention now.
It's been trending
on Twipo, even.
So with all that's going on
lately, I wanted to know
what's up with those
Kimijima reports of yours.
Kimijima reports, please.
I seriously doubt there's
any connection between
those reports and
what happened with your mom.
I mean, they're ridiculous.
Probably some
weirdo's practical joke.
Even so, they're still
the only lead to my mom
I've found since
I've been on the island.
I wanna check
them out, at least.
The reports I've read so
far are all about some group
that rules from the shadows
and wants to use solar storms'
magnetic fields to obliterate
humanity and end the world.
Like I said, it's ridiculous
stuff out of science fiction.
Of course, a monopole
did fall from the sky
like Airi said it would.
Kou Kimijima.
Kaito. Where did
you hear that name?
Now that I think about it.
I never did follow up
on all this with Mizuka.
All I'm sayin' is, wouldn't
it be easy to just stick
GUNVARREL's face
on here like this?
Do we have to go
through this again?
Just give it up, already!
No fair!
It's another
sweltering day today.
Why are we here?
Because, Aki and the
others are at the hangar.
They might have spotted
us if we met at your place.
As you requested earlier,
Report Number Three Flags.
File was
successfully downloaded.
Okay. First flag: "Find
Kimijima Report Number 2."
Second flag:
"Photograph Kandelia Obovota
flowers and upload to IRUO."
Third flag: "For three days
in a row, focus on the geotag
in the Chikura Cave
for three hours straight,
starting at one p.m."
Fourth flag: "Place
thirty-six geotagged stones
on the buried Shinto gage.
However, you must not knock off
any stones that
are already on it."
I'll say it again, this has
to be a practical joke.
Epic suck. What a PITA.
Let me know when
you're done. I G2G.
Hold it. Where do you
think you're running off to?
You're the one who had to see
the Kimijima Reports, remember?
Okay, Airi?
Do you happen to know
exactly how many other people
have tried to hunt down the
Kimijima Reports before?
Like, how many people have tried
these Number Three challenges?
Well, uh... zero.
Zero? Epic fail
on an epic scale.
Hey, hold on.
How does this even work?
How can IRUO
know whether or not
we knock over any
of the other rocks?
Because Airi is watching you.
Airi has to be watching
when you clear it, or it won't
count. Those are the rules!
And what if I ask you to
overlook this particular flag?
Oh goodness! Brother!
You're not really saying
that you would cheat, are you?
Oh no, you're
distressing the loli!
She's totally freaking!
How shameful!
Isn't there anything
you can do about it, Frau?
You know, maybe hack the
programming or something?
OIC. Cheats, huh?
But hacking IRUO would be
impossible. Even more impossible
than hacking into CERN
and warezing its files.
I guess we just
have to do it, then.
That one fell!
It doesn't count!
Oh, man, and this is
still the first stage?
Forget Hard Mode, we're in
Nightmare Mode already.
Since there're two of us here,
we might as well split the work.
Piling these stones without
dropping any, or focusing on
the geotag in the cave for three
hours: which job do you want?
Neither, thx. You can have both.
That's not an option.
Now, pick one.
Okay. This job.
Man, the water's cold!
Here we go!
Accurate focus confirmed!
He went through all the
trouble of sticking a geotag
in this obscure spot!
Ugh, who was this
Kou Kimijima guy anyway?
Airi told you! He's her master!
Hey, is it okay if I play
KILL-BALLAD while I wait?
Yes, Airi thinks that
should be okay, Brother.
Keep multitasking on.
That way Airi can tell
you're still focusing
on the geotag, too!
Great. Thanks.
Frau Bow isn't home, either.
Honestly! It's like she
and Kai aren't even a little
fired up about this!
What happened to
all the excitement from
when I announced GunBuild-2?
Where did
it all go, huh?!
Well, you know, to be fair,
you were the only one
who was particularly
excited at the time.
Kona?
You all done?
This sux, sux, sux.
Three hours and I
couldn't get a single one!.
It's hopeless,
I tell you! Hopeless!
Yes. That sounds terrible.
The devil's work!
It's the devil's doing!
Well, now that I think about it,
it probably wouldn't
have counted, anyway,
since Airi wasn't
watching you stack them.
What?! You lousy troll!
Two thousand-year banhammer!
Sorry about that. Anyway.
Thought you'd wanna know,
I just beat TAKANO_EYE!
The suspected cheater?
Man, I'm fired up!
I beat the best
KB player alive! Yeah!
Careful. You'll hurt
yourself. Oh, and FWIW.
One win isn't enough
to change the rankings.
Yeah, I know. But it's
still cool. Never mind.
Your cheat analyzer's
installed on here, right?
Hey, Rozetta. Status, please.
Virus check. Running.
In some cases,
this may take several minutes.
Why do a check?
These WTFs have me freaking.
Virus check is now complete!
Results of scan. Virus detected.
Huh? What's going on?
Wanna know what's
going on? I'll tell you.
The cheat analyzer that
was supposed to be analyzing
the KB matches was
actually infected by a virus!
A virus?
Outfoxing the game's creator
and implanting a virus?
That is totally not kewl.
Who did it? TAKANO_EYE?
Maybe, but it's set
for random opponents now,
so if we want to catch this
creep, I'll need to contact
my associates in Tokyo,
get them to pay IRL visits
to the cheaters' homes and see
what they can find out about it.
From a recent press conference
with the Exoskeleton Company.
Don't you have anything to say?
Can you give us some details?
Miss Senomiya!
Do you know anything yet?
What have you uncovered?
Hey, Mizuka! How's it g--
Don't you feel responsible?!
So, what? You still insist the
powered suits aren't defective?
I, uhh...
What's your company's response?
[RAPID-FIRE QUESTIONING]
It's you.
You look nice, as always.
Are you here for
a passion fruit bun?
You haven't been ordering
them as much these days.
Yeah, sorry,
I've been kinda busy.
Hey, have you talked
to Misa at all lately?
Why do you ask?
Well. It's just that
Aki says she never replies
to her emails or anything.
She's never been much of one
for electronic communication.
Actually, there're a few things
I wanna ask her about, too.
Y'know, like about
Airi and Kou Kimijima.
When I asked you a while ago,
you mentioned that she
knew them, didn't you?
Seriously? This again?!
Whoa, what's gotten into you?
Just drop it! Stay out of
Kou Kimijima's business, okay?!
Why should I?
What is it? Something bad?
No, but, it's just. It's just
that I wouldn't get involved
in his nonsense if I were you.
Okay, then, if I
eat a passion fruit bun,
will you tell me what you know?
The same deal we always do.
Eat all you want, be my guest,
but it won't change
the fact that all I know
is Misa was acquainted
with Kimijima and Airi.
That's it. All I've got for ya.
Kou Kimijima?
That's correct. There are
records indicating that Kimijima
had been investigating
solar storm activity.
What's more, he died
on Tanegashima the day
of the Anemone incident.
I believe there's a chance he
learned something
about Project Mars.
I'd like you to dig
into his past, if you would.
I understand. Goodbye.
I guess in the end,
robots have no choice
but to fight. Like us.
Good morning.
It's a little late
for "good morning."
Have you seen Twipo?
No, I guess you haven't, huh?
I know this is
gonna sound crazy,
but Frau Bow
called a club meeting.
She wants us to
come to the hangar
so she can show us something.
You're talking about Kona?
Th-They arrived this morning.
Four RGB cameras,
all equipped with depth sensors.
Are we gonna attach
them to GunBuild-2?
Why would we?
It's going to be
remote-controlled,
so there's no point.
Well, think of the KB System,
and the combat moves it uses.
Those aren't going work well at
the expo. Everyone will be like
"WTF? Who the heck are j00
supposed to be fighting, d00d?"
IMHO.
I'm kinda lost. Could somebody
please translate what she said?
I believe so.
Frau is saying that we need
to create new movements
that the giant robot's joints
can withstand.
Well, that's the gist of it.
And we have the
perfect guinea pig
for the new moves:
K-Karate girl.
Huh?! Why me?!
Because you're so
tiny and vulnerable-looking
in a sexual sense!
You look like one of
the classic villains now.
The ones who get taken out by
the good guys in five seconds.
And just like that,
war was beginning, huh?
Well, set up us the bomb,
'cause all your karate girl
are belong to uuussss!
Quit it, Kona.
Can't you tell she's scared?
CNR.
Hey, it's okay.
Nothing to be afraid of.
All you'll have to do is move
around for the cameras, I think.
Good, right there.
You ready for this, karate girl?
C-C-Cause I'm gonna be
spying on you from all angles!
Spying? On me?
Why not start out with a
kata you're comfortable with.
That "Suparinpei" one, maybe?
All right, then. Suparinpei.
How's it going so far?
Can you see it?
Awesome!
This'll be the base.
We'll use it to create
several new movements, and then
I'll add them into the system.
Ooh! I'm gettin' fired up!
It's a good idea and all.
But is this kind of thing
really necessary yet?
I mean, we haven't even
completed the
Mark 2's blueprints.
Yeah, I see your point.
Necessary or not,
it does mean I'll have
the afternoon to myself.
Oh, that looked like...
Hey Kai!
I'm heading to Tokyo!
Oh, really? When do you go?
Tomorrow! I'm going to discuss
the plans for GunBuild-2 while
I'm there. So look
forward to hearing good news!
Great! I will, thanks!
By the way,
you're sweating so much,
I can see through your shirt!
Thanks for the warning.
It's just not my day.
I wonder where he's going?
Hah. It didn't say anything
about the size of the rocks.
How's that?
Yay! The flag has
been cleared, Brother!
Okay, that takes care of the
most difficult one, at least.
Which leaves.
Well?
I wanna die. Worst game ever.
I did for two days.
I don't think it's asking
very much for you to do one.
Okay, it's four p.m.
It's been the
required three hours.
So, the flag has
been cleared, then?
Yes, it has. Congratulations!
You worked really hard,
Brother. Airi's proud!
You're a good cheerleader.
Thanks a lot, Airi.
I worked hard, too, plzkthx.
Since the final flag
is clear, Kimijima Report
Number Three's AR annotation
has been made visible.
So, now...
Let's see here.
There. That must be it.
Report Number Three
has now been downloaded.
You can see it at
any time in the viewer.
Ooh! Kimijima Report, please!
Just remember,
there's no guarantee
it contains anything helpful.
Of particular
concern is Project Autm.
The Committee of
Three Hundred's Human
Cultivation Project
Number One-one-four,
which is led by the
Tavistock Institute.
This project involves directly
interfering with the sun
during a period of maximum
solar activity to artificially
generate a solar corona, as
well as solar magnetic storms
discharged by said corona,
to dramatically alter
the global environment.
Rough estimates
suggest the number
of casualties will
reach five billion.
Groundwork for
implementation is scheduled
to be underway
by twenty fifteen.
In preparation,
droves of manufacturers
that are affiliated with the
Committee of Three Hundred
will most likely
enter the robot research
and development
sector by twenty twelve.
In America, U.S. Robocom.
In Britain, Liverpool Tech.
In Japan, Exoskeleton.
Uh. WTF?!
I warned you, didn't I? All
of the Reports are like this.
But it mentions Exoskeleton.
Where Misa works.
Almost made it
safely inside, too.
You, shirtless, playing
around with cheeky glasses boy
in the pouring rain-
that would be classic!
You're welcome
for the cab, B-T-dub.
What's going on?
R-R-Remember my Tokyo friends?
One of them just emailed me.
They went to all the
top three players' homes.
So? They find anything out?
Let's see.
What is it? Something wrong?
A-A-All three of them
were dead in their homes.
A-All accidental deaths, and all
of them were half a year ago.
You're messing with me.
That's impossible.
Then who played
TAKANO_EYE until yesterday?
D-Dunno. There are
no signs of his account
being hijacked or
any cheats being used.
What? You think a
ghost was playing his account?
Hey. Kona.
I-I wonder if this could
possibly have something to do
with my mom's disappearance.
Maybe she's trying to use
KILL-BALLAD as a way
to warn me about something.
Oh, Kai! Did you see?
Huh?
It's GUNVARREL!
It's awful, Kai!
They've established a countdown
until the next solar storm?
Sheer idiocy.
These people are a pain.
What is it?
Are you watching
the evening news?
Not now. What happened?
Looks like it's been leaked.
What, Kaminagi?!
No. The final
episode of GUNVARREL.
Understood, I'll review
the footage when I can.
Now return to Tokyo.
Yes, sir.
The timing can't possibly
be a coincidence. It must be...
Kai?
Are you okay?!
It's all so wrong. This isn't-
It's not GUNVARREL!
The leaked footage
was four minutes
and thirty-one seconds long.
They're all making their
way to the space elevator.
But the robots,
good and bad alike,
suffer power malfunctions
and fall into the blast furnace.
The elevator then fires a laser
gun right into a large sunspot.
It's the same.
The solar storm that
results destroys
Anubis, the final boss.
But it also destroys
life on Earth as we know it.
It's the same.
Rozetta collapses lifelessly.
Genki, the hero, looks out at
the decimated
landscape and mutters,
"It's over.
The world has ended."
It's all wrong! That's not
the GUNVARREL I know!
This isn't how it
was supposed to be!
Solar storms,
the end of the world.
It's exactly like what
Kou Kimijima was saying.
The same stuff that
was in the reports.
Gezi's master was murdered.
Just drop it! Stay out of Kou
Kimijima's business, okay?!
All three of the top players
were found dead in their homes.
Maybe she's trying
to use KILL-BALLAD
as a way to warn
me about something.
That you, Misa?
Forget about him.
What?
Forget about Kou Kimijima.
Stop poking around.
Tetsuharu Fujita, the owner
and operator of the Robo Clinic,
falls ill and is
hospitalized. His granddaughter,
Junna Daitoku, attempts to
visit him but is turned away.
The sad story of their long
estrangement comes to light
when Kai seeks to clear a flag
from the next Kimijima Report.
What piece of history will Kai
unearth in the Robo Clinic?
Will it be enough to repair a
long-neglected relationship?
Episode 12!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!