Someone said it was a battle
to save the world
from a cruel fate.
Someone said all hope for
the future of humankind
rested squarely
on our shoulders.
Counting down!
Three, two, one. Liftoff!
But I don't care
about any of that stuff.
That's not why I'm here.
Okay, we've loaded
the laser thingy.
Wait, I mean,
the laser turret, right?
It's in the Thunder Emperor!
System link: Online.
Connect PhoneDroid pad.
It's the red cable.
The perimeter map
is loading now.
Three meters.
Five, seven,
ten, fifteen, twenty.
Maximum range!
O-Okay.
Topographical
assessment AI ready.
All checks complete.
Kai, we're going
into this unrehearsed.
Well, we always knew that was
how it was going to be, right?
We've already come this far,
no sense backing down now.
Thank you.
Status!
We're all green!
This is the final call. Go!
GUNVARREL!
Forward!
Performing voice
recognition test.
Please say something
toward the screen.
Okay, My name is Kaito Yashio.
I'm a student at Chuo
Tanegashima High School.
Which is lots of fun.
What else is there to
tell a PhoneDroid pad?
My grades are mediocre at best.
Welcome to IRUO.
Update was successful.
Jeez, do you ever stop gaming?
I was just running an update.
Found a cool little app
while I was at it, too.
Hello, kitty cat.
I don't understand
how you can be
so relaxed when things
are looking terrible for us!
Things look bad, huh?
No! Terrible!
Hey, this thing
really does work.
Awesome.
You and I are the only
remaining members
of the Robot Research Club.
You know that, right?
Me-ow.
We have a new contender
for my favorite app.
Okay, okay. What now?
Were you able to pin
down the vice-principal?
She's in another meeting.
Apparently she's "too busy to
meet with every single student
who drops by," so instead,
I'm supposed to submit a
detailed budget breakdown
for her to look over.
Lemme guess, you're gonna
request a huge amount
of funding for the club again?
Well, yeah.
We need money to stay afloat.
Found it!
Wait, you're just gonna
turn it in like that?
Sure.
What do we have to lose?
I mean, it's just
like he always said:
"Don't give up!
This isn't over!" Eh?
Pay attention! Come on.
We have to go down
to the faculty office now.
It's not really
a two-person job.
Can't you go by yourself?
You're a member, too.
Would it kill you
to act like it?
Come, let us face this together!
Okay, you win.
Just lay off the noble hysterics
and I'll go with you as
far as the office door.
As soon as I'm done
with this battle.
Whoa!
FRAUKOUJIRO?!
Really?
Who is that?
He created this game.
I heard he plays a lot,
but this is the first
time I've run into him.
Ah, sweet.
Wow.
Hey! You're good!
I can overpower any
technique an opponent uses
in just eight frames.
But hey, I am ranked
fifth in the world.
Kai, that's incredible!
You beat the game's creator!
Well, that ought to
preserve my standing
in the game's
rank system, anyway.
What's that?
It's a message from
the creator himself.
Huh? What's he talking about?
What's the matter?
It looks like I'm too good.
The creator thinks
I'm using cheats
to make my reaction time
faster than physically possible.
Cheats, huh?
Just like it sounds, they
help you cheat at the game.
Gah!
Can't he lose graciously
or does everyone
who beats him get
labeled a cheater?
Must be jealous.
Accusations like this
are pretty common
when you're as
highly ranked as I am.
Didn't expect it
from him, though.
Stand up for yourself!
Say something!
Nah, I don't care.
It's not like I've actually
done anything wrong.
Really? Hold on.
Where are you going?
The office, remember?
We've got a meeting, right?
You guys are seriously gonna
give this to the vice-principal?
Why wouldn't we?
You're the one who told me she'd
want to see a budget, Mitchi.
First of all, say
"yes," don't just nod.
And please, remember
what I keep telling you:
call me Mr. Nagafukada.
So, how do you think
she's gonna react to this?
I think it's going to convince
her for sure this time!
Huh.
Well, that's weird.
I've never seen such an
aggressive STEINGMA user before.
Great. What am I gonna do now?
Hey, Yashio!
Hey, what's up?
There's something I've gotta do.
Do you think you
could do me a favor
and take out the trash for me?
You're on clean-up
duty, too, right?
Don't even bother.
It's no use talking to him.
Shut up, it's not like
he's doing anything.
Yeah, sure, no problem.
I'll take out the trash for you.
Oh! Really?!
Of course.
Right after you beat
me at KILL-BALLAD.
I'll take care of the trash
and whatever else you want.
Ya see, what'd I tell you?
Let's just go.
What's with that guy?
So how did the appointment go?
She wasn't there, so I left
the proposal with Mitchi.
Mitchi? Really?
You sure that's a good plan?
Why wouldn't it be?
He is our club advisor.
And don't worry,
I plan to grill him later to
make sure he gave it to her.
Maybe I should start calling
you Snapping Turtle Aki.
Snapping Turtle?!
I don't like that.
Hi!
I didn't see you standing there!
Aha! I've got you now!
There's nowhere to run!
It's not too late.
Join our club and help us
with our grand endeavor t--
I will not join your club.
You'd say no just like that?
Just like that?
I've given you the same answer
more than twenty times now.
So please, stop bothering me.
But the Robot
Research Club needs
your unparalleled
technical prowess!
We have a lot of fun, you know.
We pour all of our
blood, sweat, tears,
and oil into one noble creation!
Racing ever forward toward
the ultimate triumph together!
I said, quit bothering me!
Goodbye.
One way or another,
I am going to convince
him to join our club!
He tries to shake you off,
but you won't let go.
Snapping turtle, alright.
If you're not going
to be helpful,
then just shut uuuuuuup!
Feeling okay?
Sure am.
Are you going straight home?
Whaddya got in mind?
I was thinking about
maybe stopping by
the hangar for a little while.
Again?
Well, yeah.
We do need to keep it
well maintained, you know.
It's vital for the
club's future.
Come ooooonnnn!
We don't have to
stay for very long!
Hangar, open now!
Why do you say that every time?
It's important to set the
right mood for stuff like this.
This place could use
some spring-cleaning.
I don't see anything.
Are you sure it's still in here?
Of course.
Where else would it be?
It is the reason for the Robot
Research Club's existence.
The "Let's make a life-size
version of GUNVARREL,
the giant robot
of justice" project,
or just "GunBuild-1" for short.
Construction began when
the club was founded,
and work on it continues
bit by bit, to this day.
The robot is stored here, in
an abandoned airport hangar.
It looks really unlikely that
it'll be finished by
the time we graduate.
But that doesn't faze Aki.
She has total faith that we'll
be able to complete it somehow.
It's good to see you, GUNVARREL.
There we go.
Now that leaves.
Just a little, there.
I swear, it's like a
sauna this time of year.
Start pulling your weight!
This is not a warning!
Refuse and I'll fire!
Technique: GUNVAL Ankh Striker!
Something wrong?
Some oil just dripped on me.
Nice legs.
Hey!
Back off, you pervert!
Yeah, kicking around like
that just shows 'em
off even more, you know.
Keep looking and I'll kill you.
What were you doing, anyway?
Hard to explain.
It's just, being here.
This place.
It's like it's the
hangar that time forgot.
Oh, wow.
I sound like a
thirteen-year-old girl, don't I?
No, I get what you mean.
And that's exactly why
weirdos like us have got
to work together to keep
the club and its goals alive.
'Kay?
I'll be happy to
help however I can.
As soon as you beat
me at KILL-BALLAD.
Exoskeleton Company's
Powered Suits have been
specially designed
to be accessible
and useful in the daily
lives of ordinary people.
Like cars and PhoneDroid pads,
Accept call.
With voice only.
Hey, Kai! Wait a sec.
What's up with voice only?
I'm changing clothes.
Oh, good call then.
Anyway, I was curious,
have you gotten
your English homework
finished for tomorrow?
I bet you haven't yet, huh?
You're always jumping
to conclusions.
But no, I haven't.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Why don't we split the work?
It's just like he once said:
"When it comes to battle,
thinking two steps ahead
of your opponent
often means victory." Eh?
Well, when it comes
to English homework,
I don't think you're even
one step ahead, are you?
But splitting up the work
sounds like a good plan to me.
Okay, perfect!
We'll meet up in
the club room, then.
Reserve your Powered Suit today.
Exoskeleton provides
the support you need.
Put your trust in us.
Morning, thanks for coming in.
Never mind, it's just you.
Where's Aki?
She probably went
on ahead to school.
If that girl thinks
she can ignore me,
she's got another thing coming.
Come on, Mizuka,
why would she ignore you?
It's nothing like that, really.
She's just flat
broke, that's all.
Give Mitchi a message for me.
He needs to come in and
pick up his order already.
Why do I have to get involved?
Can't you call him yourself?
I'm too busy.
Yeah, okay.
I just don't want
to talk to him.
That isn't really something
I want to do, either.
Oh, crap!
I completely forgot!
And I don't have
any money on me!
This is why no one
wants to talk to him.
He spits!
Well, I've done my part.
Bye.
How did she seem?
Was she angry?
Uh, I dunno.
Yeah, I guess,
maybe she was a little.
Now listen up, kid!
Mizuka Irei gets seriously
scary if you make her mad.
Just a tip from me to you!
Yeah, I know that.
And I have one
other piece of advice!
Listen carefully!
Fine, what is it?
As swift as the wind!
As strong as the sea!
GUNVARREL!
Keep flailing around
this tiny room,
and you'll bust
your PhoneDroid again.
A Skal!
I was just talking to Mitchi
and the guy wouldn't shut up.
Huh? What anime
are you watching?
What seriously?! Are you blind?!
It's GUNVARREL!
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
What?!
"Oh, yeah?!" Tell me, that
KILL-BALLAD video game
you play all the time.
What is it based on?
"GUNVARREL."
And what has our club been
working tirelessly to build?
GUNVARREL.
And this anime is?
That's better.
You had me really
worried for a sec.
I thought maybe
you'd finally lost it.
Here.
Why don't we go through
it all from the top?
No, please.
Not again.
I've got it.
From the top!
Now, then, the current
robot boom is pretty much
entirely the result of
GUNVARREL's popularity.
The show represents
the culmination
of a half-century
of robot anime.
It aired in a hundred and
sixty-eight countries
and was an
international sensation.
Yet, despite its success, the
final episode was never aired.
GUNVAL Ankh Striker!
It's been four years now,
and the final episode
still remains a mystery.
It must be an ending
of epic proportions.
There's no doubting it!
Oh, by the way.
What?
Mitchi asked me to
pass along a message.
The vice-principal's agreed
to see you during lunch break.
You're kidding.
No, I'm not.
The time has come!
C'mon, Kai!
Show some club spirit!
Yeah, do I really
have to go in too?
Of course you have to go!
You are a club
member, aren't you?
I guess so.
Are you aware of the reason
for which I summoned
you to my office?
Yes, ma'am.
It's about the
club budget, isn't it?
I'm guessing that you must've
finally made your decision...
We really appreciate it!
Yes, well.
It would seem you
are still not thinking
with a clear head, young lady.
Now would you care to
explain to me again why
you think such an exorbitant
budget request is justified?
This is an extremely large sum.
Oh, that's a good one, ma'am,
since I've explained it to
you a bunch of times already.
I said "again" or
weren't you listening?
Robots from all over
the world are going
to be showcased during the Tokyo
Expo being held next February.
We intend to participate,
entering our club's giant robot.
However, completing
it in half a year's time
will not be an easy
task to accomplish.
It will require a
substantial budget increase.
Well, it's all over now.
I see nothing has changed.
Your analysis of the
situation is no different
than any of the
previous attempts.
Naturally!
Perhaps you can at least explain
why it must be a giant robot?
GunBuild-1 is the reason
for the Robot
Research Club's existence.
It has always been my dream
to take it to the Tokyo Expo.
I will not give that dream up!
One additional question.
Can the two of you
alone honestly hope
to complete a project
of this magnitude?
And with such a short deadline?
Determination will prevail!
I must deny your request.
"Everyone makes mistakes,
though the young
are particularly
unwilling to admit them."
Do you wanna fill me in
on what you're doing, Aki?
Oh, very well.
But I do have some conditions.
Okay, like what?
Eight years ago, your
older sister turned a circle
of aficionados into
an official school club
by producing results,
and now it is your
turn to prove yourself.
If you manage that,
I will give this absurd
budget genuine consideration.
Thank you so much!
We're not finished.
We aren't?
I haven't stipulated the
terms of the agreement.
Now listen closely.
The following condition
is non-negotiable.
No time to waste!
Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go!
What do you say, Kai?
Do you actually
think this is possible?
Sure!
We just have to win
ROBO-ONE, right?
The Robot Research
Club did it before,
eight years ago,
and we'll do it again!
Well, yeah, but didn't
they have like a whole year
to get their entry ready?
Whereas we've only got
two weeks until this
year's tournament opens.
Time is no match for passion!
I hear it's gotten a lot more
competitive and high-tech,
what with the robot boom.
Determination will prevail!
And the club will
instantly be shut down
unless we take first place.
Never consider defeat before the
battle has begun!
Problem is, we don't
even have a robot, do we?
No, I guess we don't.
You're just realizing that?
No, no, no, no, no!
Ridiculous optimism
is my one saving grace!
I don't know how yet, but
I swear I will make it work!
I have to because
GUNVARREL is waiting.
Now preparing Report Number
two-eight-eight-seven.
The date is June Thirteenth;
the year is
two-thousand-and-nineteen.
Current time: Nineteen-oh-nine.
Assessing status:
the report is ready.
It is confirmed that the
situation remains unchanged.
Those eyes.
Whose are they?
With the club's
future on the line,
Aki and Kai focus on winning
the ROBO-ONE tournament.
They modify
Tanegashi Machine--
one of the club's old robots--
elicit the help of Karate
Club member Junna Daitoku,
and develop their strategy.
All the while, shadows linger
in the back of their minds.
A red aurora, a
childhood memory,
and thoughts of Miskai Senomiya,
Aki's older sister who
left the island years before.
Episode 2!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!