This is bad! Very, very bad!
Since it happened, Subaru
hasn't been to school even once!
Yeah. I know what
you mean, it was bad enough
to spark one of your attacks,
and it's getting worse.
Never mind me,
think about Subaru!
There's only one
thing we can do now.
Are you with me?
We have no choice but
to storm the Hidaka house!
Just leave well
enough alone, Aki.
In the real world, nobody gets
to hold on to
their dreams forever.
You know that from first-hand
experience, don't you?
Hang in there, Rozetta!
Your dream doesn't have to die!
As swift as the wind!
As strong as the seaaa!
Hey, Yashio.
The GUNVARREL anime, huh?
Yeah, all one hundred
and fifty-five episodes.
Akiho lent them to me, I'm
only on episode seven so far.
Sounds like you've got
a long way to go, then.
Yeah, but at least
it's a good show.
Besides, the final
episode of GUNVARREL
is an urban legend
in its own, right?
So, I figure I should
watch the rest at least once.
The mysterious
final episode that,
for reasons unknown,
was never aired?
Ah, man, you really are
into urban legends, huh?
Oh, that reminds me.
You remember how
PhoneDroid pads all over the
country froze up the other day?
I was curious to see
if anything like that
had happened before,
so I looked into it.
Yeah?
It turns out that this isn't
the only similar incident.
There've been a bunch. One time,
there was this weird email.
It showed up on millions
of pads at the same time.
That was already creepy
but the message itself
was a little scary, too.
Scary, like how?
It was the lyrics
to "Kagome, Kagome."
Is something the matter?
Oh, no, it's nothing. I-
Tell me when you
plan to keep your end
of the deal and
hunt down cheaters for me.
You should come to my place.
And then, while dressed
indecently in a musty, chilly,
air-conditioned room,
you can game as hard
as you want and make
boys with glasses
cry out in sweet,
sweet anguish!
It's freezing in here.
You oughta turn down the AC.
This can't be good for you.
You're concern for
me is touching, but STFU!
And besides,
I like it when it's cold.
Now, come in.
You, you want a drink?
Only if it's something warm.
Heating water up is for lamers.
Your hospitality leaves
a lot to be desired.
Well, it looks like we won't
be competing in ROBO-ONE now.
So I got nothing better
to do than help you out.
Sssee the top five
handles on the leaderboard?
Well, up until last month,
I suspected them all
of cheating during battles.
Well, we know I'm
not a cheater, at least,
and neither is the
fourth place one, TAGIRINGER.
Yeah? How do you know that?
Oh, trust me, I know.
When you're as good as I am,
you can just instinctively feel
it from the way someone fights.
And besides,
I think TAGIRINGER is...
Nothing. Never mind.
Anyway, the top three
are all using cheats,
I can promise you that.
I've seen them pull
off moves during battle
that no real person would
be able to on their own.
Agreed.
So, how do I hunt for them?
Simple, all you have to do
is challenge them in battle.
I whipped up a scanning tool
that can detect cheats.
I'll execute it
during those matches.
And how do we arrange
for me to battle them?
We just have to wait until
you're matched up
with them, I guess.
Fantastic, I have to sit
here waiting for these guys,
without any idea when
they're gonna show up?
Who's that?
Oh, um, hello.
Hey, what's the deal? You've
been AWOL for awhile now.
Aki's been really
worried about you.
Wh-What are you doing
here without her, anyway?
I just came from Kona's place.
I've been there all day.
Fulfilling my part of the
agreement you made with her.
Oh, the nude photo shoot.
Hunting down cheaters.
None of them showed
up this time around.
We're gonna give it another
shot tomorrow, though.
Is that...?
Hey, did you patch things
up with your old man?
No, no chance of that.
My dream is over for good.
Tell the Chief I said thanks,
but she doesn't need
to worry about this.
I'll dispose of the M45 myself.
That will give me a better
sense of closure. Goodbye.
What were you looking at
all those times, Brother?
You've come to visit this
spot over and over again
during the past nine years.
In fact, you came once
every two days, on average.
Sometimes you'd come
with two other people,
sometimes with one other person,
and sometimes by yourself.
Listen. Years from now,
when you're all grown up,
I want you to be a man
with the "right stuff."
When I was younger,
I wanted to grow up
to be an astronaut someday.
But the Tanegashima Space Center
has never sent
anyone into space.
Yeah, I knew that, but even so,
it's something every little boy
from here thinks about,
at least for a while, anyway.
Is it true?
Are you really quitting
the Robot Research Club?!
That's right. There's no
reason for it anymore.
Why?! What about your robot?!
That old thing?
It's just a giant piece of junk.
I gave that dream
up a long time ago.
There has been
a massive series of
malfunction incidents involving
the latest Powered Suit model
from Exoskeleton Company.
According to the
Consumer Affairs Agency,
over one hundred similar
incidents have been reported
in the past two years alone.
Many of these resulted
in serious injury,
including broken bones.
Exoskeleton Company has pledged
to look into all potential flaws
in the product that
could have caused
this recent...
Excuse me? They tell
me you're the Robo-Doc.
My name is Misaki Senomiya,
and I'm a member
of the Chuo Tanegashima High
School Robot Fan Club.
I was hoping for
your advice on something.
Here, let me show you.
That a hobby robot?
No. These are
plans I'm working on
for a full-scale giant robot!
I've seen enough.
Get outta here.
I'm not gonna bother with
some kid's dumb pipe dream.
You can't just kick me out!
I do what I want
in my shop. Now, go on!
In that case...
Did everything go okay?
Yeah, fortunately.
It's such a relief to
finally pay off my tab.
Thank goodness for
our sponsor! And thank you too
for coming here with me.
I just stood here.
I'm really sorry
but I couldn't
bring myself to go in.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Just having you here gave me
the boost of confidence
I needed! Well!
Now that we actually
have money, I'll have to
look through the catalogs and
decide which parts we'll need.
When you get down to it,
robots are nothing but robots.
Terrible news, Kai.
All the malfunctions
they announced yesterday?
Well, that's terrible, too.
But my sister is
handling it, so it'll be okay.
I'm talking about Subaru.
I noticed that the M45 was gone
when I stopped by
the hangar this morning.
Oh. I guess
I forgot to tell you.
He came and got it. Said he
was gonna get rid of it himself.
You mean you actually saw him?!
Why didn't you
talk him out of it?!
There's nothing
we can do now, Aki.
Seriously, just let it go,
okay? It's out of our hands.
Oh, GUNVARREL.
I'm so lost. What do you
think I should do about this?
Subaru! Are you there?! Hello?
If you're there,
come answer the door! Subaru!
"Wipe away your
tears and stand tall!
That's the only way
you can see tomorrow!"
We could, you know,
talk about stuff.
I mean, you are the one
who created KILL-BALLAD.
Genius programmer
FRAU KOJIRO, FTW. Ready!
Well, since I'm just
waiting around to be matched,
maybe you could talk about
behind-the-scenes stuff,
or the programming
quirks of each mech type?
Of all people, you don't
need tips like that, IMHO.
Y-You already have amazing
l33t skills as it is.
Which skills are
you talking about?
Oh, do you mean Slow-Motion?
That isn't actually a fighting
technique, just a spasm attack
I have sometimes. I don't want
you getting the wrong idea.
Spasms that give you
super-human fighting reflexes?
That's been an anime
cliché for ten years now.
Look, quit trying
to be funny, will ya?
The attacks get so painful it
feels like I'm about to die.
So maybe you could
do me a big favor
and stop making fun of them.
In exchange, I'll reveal
a secret of my own.
S-Something personal.
All right, shoot.
Do you know the reason the
much-anticipated final episode
of GUNVARREL never aired?
No, and I haven't
really lost any sleep over it.
Th-The final episode
was never broadcast
because people on the staff died
just before it was set to air.
Not just a single death.
At least thirteen
people died that day.
Then, immediately after,
the director
mysteriously went missing.
Some people think she
killed them all, ROFL.
And you actually
believe that story?
Y-You know my real
name is Kona Furugori.
Which can also be
shortened to Kogori.
Minami Kogori was
the name of the woman
who directed the show.
She was also my mom.
That's who I am: the daughter
of a suspected murderer.
How's that for a secret?
Before she disappeared,
my mom was last seen
on this island. And that's
the reason I
moved to Tanegashima.
That's a pretty heavy story
you decided to dump on me.
I think it's best if
I pretend I didn't hear.
I don't want
to get involved in--
Sweet, finally! It's BOBLEE,
the dude in third place!
ESL!
I was wondering why
you weren't at the hangar.
What's the deal, you were
with Frau Bow all day?
Yeah, kinda, it was part
of that agreement Subaru made.
Wasn't very productive,
though. We didn't find
any signs of the guy cheating.
Which just frustrated Kona.
You were alone at her place?
Well, she lives by herself.
Maybe I should start
calling you "Casanova Kai."
Yeah? You think so?
Not really.
Gaming's the only thing
that gets you hot and bothered.
What about you? It's a
weird time of night to be out.
Where were you?
Subaru's place. But don't worry,
I didn't cause any trouble.
Nobody was home.
I just went over to drop off
some stuff he
forgot at the hangar.
Stuff? What stuff?
Just something
I saw lying around.
I think he'll treasure it,
no matter what happens.
Even if he does have to
quit the Robot Research Club.
What was it?
A piece of the M45.
As you know,
summer break begins tomorrow.
But, college entrance exams
are only half a year away.
So make the most
of the time you have.
I'm sure you all have plenty
of work to do. Good luck!
The expo is coming up fast.
This summer break is
gonna be crucial for us!
Did you hear anything
the teacher just said, Aki?
To make things worse,
Subaru still hasn't
come back to school.
The rest of us are gonna have
to work extra hard without him.
Good to see you, Yashio. Chief.
Subaru! This is fantastic!
You smoothed things over
with your dad, after all?
Unfortunately,
my father isn't one
to let things go that easily.
I'm not here for the club.
This just happens to be
a nice, quiet place to study.
Yeah, that's pretty thin.
Do you really think
your dad is going
to buy that story?
Don't worry about it.
I dismantled the M45
while my father watched.
That should be enough.
Of course, that means our plans
for ROBO-ONE are cancelled.
It was unavoidable,
Yashio. I apologize.
No, that's totally fine by me.
Now I can spend all summer
vacation playing KILL-BALLAD.
That must have been so hard.
Wha--?! I, hard, no.
I'm huh?
I'm so sorry. I can't imagine
how much that must have hurt.
The M45 was your partner, almost
like an extension of yourself.
To take it apart
with your own hands.
So what do you say, Subaru?
Shall we race forward?
Huh?!
Oh you know!
Toward the ultimate triumph!
What? No way!
Whaaaaa--?!
But, Chief.
Well, you tried to protect
the M45 when my father came,
and you returned
the final piece of it to me.
So... So I want to
thank you berry much!
"Berry much"?
Wow! Subaru's finally
opening up to us.
Isn't that nice?
It's not like I'm baring
my soul to you or anything!
Like I told you before, I just
came here to study and, umm...
And, maybe, occasionally,
to give you a hand
with the remaining
construction on GUNVARREL.
Huh?
Hello, Doc!
Whaddya want today? I see
you got Mr. Pleiades with ya.
How did you know?!
What, did ya
think I was blind?
Anyone can see through
a lousy disguise like that.
It's just a stupid mask.
Anyone?! Oh no! This can't be!
So, what brings you to the shop?
I'm here for parts, of course.
For another hobby robot?
Not this time.
I need parts for GunBuild-1!
In that case,
how about we make a bet?
On what?
I bet you that the Robot Fan
Club will win the ROBO-ONE
tournament this year.
If I can make that happen,
you have to promise to share
your years of expertise with me?
What do you say?
What do you think?
The parts for GunBuild-1!
And it's all
thanks to the money
your company so
generously gave us!
Oh and we're in the process
of developing a sticker for it.
A sticker?
A big ol' giant of a sticker!
With "Space Candy Company"
written across it!
Boing-a-boing!
Cool, huh? Just stick it right
on the robot, so it's like POW!
You know what I mean, dontcha?
Always gotta
have impact, my girl.
O-kay. But, sir...
And you know what would be
even better for advertising?
If Junna here rode in it.
Oh, please, no!
I can't do that!
Umm, we were planning
to have Kai pilot it.
He's good at that sort of thing.
No, think about it: a cute
karate girl who rides around
in a giant robot.
Impact, all the way!
Chesty, chesty! Impact!
Boing, boing, boing!
So very tired.
Dealing with that man
is a truly
exhausting experience.
I see the parts have arrived?
It's about time
you showed up, Subaru!
Just to be on the safe side,
you should check them.
Make sure they weren't
damaged by the solar storm.
What do you mean?
What solar storm?
Oh, it's been trending
on Twipo since this morning.
Apparently there was
a big solar storm earlier.
I hear it knocked
out a ton of machines,
all along the west coast
of the United States.
Large-scale solar storms
will occur in succession
in twenty-twelve,
twenty-fifteen,
twenty-nineteen,
and twenty-twenty.
The twenty-fifteen
solar storm in particular
will have serious
effects on the Earth
and its magnetosphere,
and no one will see it coming.
Wow. So do you think
it's going to be like
the 2015 Crash all over again?
It's not that bad yet.
But it does sound like
there could be a
stronger storm later on.
Scientific evidence
indicates that the sun
is on the verge of explosion.
It's "Kagome, Kagome".
Weird. What's going on?
I don't know, but it's
coming from my pad, too.
Hello.
Sorry. Are you the members of
the Chuo Tanegashima High
School Robot Research Club?
Um. Yes, yes, we are.
Excellent. I know this
is sudden, but I'd like
to speak with
you about something.
If you would
kindly come with us.
Following their abduction
by a mysterious woman,
Aki and friends find
themselves presented
with an unexpected offer.
Later, Kai endeavors to learn
more about the Kimijima Reports,
and what he
discovers is shocking.
The Committee of
Three Hundred, Project Atum,
a devastating storm.
The Reports are filled with
conspiracy and catastrophe.
How has Kai landed himself
in the middle of this tempest?
Episode 8!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!