"Let's hit it off festival"?
Yeah, that's a local expression.
"Let's hit it off" means...
Something like, "Let's all
get together and work hard."
Not that anyone
actually says it.
Oh!
Okay, club! Let's hit
it oooooooofffffffff!
Hey! Get into
the spirit, will you guys?!
This is a celebration of
GunBuild-1's near completion.
The whole club
should be partying.
Can we do it quickly?
I'm not staying.
If it's a club party,
where are the other two members?
Kai went off to get Frau Bow,
but neither of
them have shown up.
Man, some festival
this is shaping up to be.
I feel like drifting off to
sleep held in the safe warmth
of your capable arms.
Or maybe you would
prefer it if I held you?
Hold me so tightly
I break. Please! w00t!!!
Uhh, you know. I really
only came to invite you
to the festival, not to
help you hunt for cheaters.
A festival?
That sounds pretty lame.
Look at this place.
You could stand to clean up.
Loli-maid plzkthx.
Rozetta might even work.
You mentioned that name before.
Who or what is Rozetta?
Wha?!
Hi, Yashio. How are you today?
I am Rozetta Yuuki!
Oh!
With all the KB you play,
h-how in the world could you
forget the name of
GUNVARREL's main heroine?
Y-Y-You poseeeeeeer!
Hi, I'm Genki! Genki Dotou!
And I'm GUNVARREL's
pilot! Nice to meet ya!
Pretty cool bots.
Did you program 'em yourself?
I'm l33t!
Do these guys just talk to
you whenever they feel like it?
No, because that
would be really annoying.
Oh, I know. I wish Airi
could hear you say that.
Airi?
Did somebody call me?
Lot of good it did me,
telling you to stay away.
Hey, what is that? A bot?
No, it's different.
OMG! It's for reals!
Switch to Gezi
mode was successful.
Hi, Gezi. Do me
a favor and explain
what you are
to this pervert here.
Understood.
Go ahead. Launch IRUO.
Make it quick, though, will ya?
Aki's waiting for
us at the festival.
True or false? Girl characters
gotta have wife material,
but with guys it's
all about the slash.
Ellery plus Genki equals OTP.
ITA. There are no
girls who dislike boyslove.
Zoh-my-God! QFT!
Wow. Didn't see that one coming.
It's HANASONO!
He's ranked Number 2!
It's time to go hunting!
Could you pwease wet
go of my arm aweady?
No, don't listen to him!
You know he's gonna
bolt as soon as you let go.
Right!
Why can't I leave?!
Look, there's a
shooting gallery over there!
Awwww. But I
don't like those games!
Look, Sis! It's Gunbam!
Sorry. It's too much.
Aww.
Besides, you don't want a mask.
A robot's not
something you can be.
It's something you make.
So good!
When does the
fireworks show start?
Aw, is it too hot
to handle, sweetie?
Unlike you, Chief.
Quick, you guys! Get down!
Why? What's happening?
Mr. Nagafukada? And he's
with that lady we met from JAXA.
Nae Tennoji. I don't see how
those two could know each other.
I bet the slut's
trying to gain access
to the club by seducing Mitchi!
Do you really
think she'd do that?!
Bah! "Now just what
are you up to, JAXA lady?"
He's reaching. She's reaching.
They're gonna...!
Don't do it!
Oh! Hi, Akiho.
I didn't know you were here.
Hey, what are you doing?
You can't be that hungry.
It's not nice to
steal other people's food.
Someone could even call
the cops on you for that.
Ugh, you smell
like a distillery.
I didn't realize you
two knew each other.
How did you meet?
I dropped by the school
to say hi to you guys,
and he kindly offered to
show me around the festival.
Yeah, that's right.
I thought I'd show her
a good time,
for your club's sake.
Looks like I broke up their
little party just in time.
Is the robot coming along well?
Yeah, it is! As a matter
of fact, we're connecting
the upper and
lower bodies tomorrow.
Wow! So it's
almost finished, huh?
Just about, yeah!
Our blood, sweat, and tears!
That's what we've poured
into it for nine years!
At long last, the day
has come for GunBuild-1
to stand, proud and tall!
Yeah, yeah. I get it. I lose.
So, what's the verdict on him?
Epically epic fail!
My analyzer got nothing.
I even had my buddies in Tokyo
running online checks, too.
I can't believe
we struck out again.
And the fireworks
have already started.
Minami Kogori was the name of
the woman who directed the show.
She was also my mom.
Hey, uh.
Remember what I
said like, the other day?
I'm in major
need of info, plzkthx.
I-If there's
anything on the island
you think might be relevant.
Something on the island?
Have you ever heard
of the Kimijima Reports?
Hey there, Sis. I mentioned
this in an earlier message,
but we're finally finishing
up work on GunBuild-1 tomorrow.
The dream you and the original
Robot Research Club started
is about to be realized. I wish
you could be here to see it.
But I'm sure you're really
busy with work and everything.
Well, I'll let you know
how it goes. Talk to you later.
Okay! Let's move 'em on in!
Right!
I didn't know Jun was
in the Robot Research Club.
Nice and easy, bub!
Nice and easy!
This is an important day!
I can't believe those
other two didn't
show up! And you, Kai!
You never came to the
festival last night, either.
Hey! Robot Girl!
Uhhh. Hey, sounds like
he's calling you!
Oh! I'm coming!
Almost there! Let's go!
GunBuild-1! Standing at laaaast!
Wow!
Damn.
Yep! That's serious
impact all right!
Eep, eep! Eep, eep, eep,
eep, eep, eep!
You know, Aki.
I would really
love it if you could
make my dream
come true someday.
Well, later days!
Later days!
And don't forget,
tomorrow's start-up test
is at ten o'clock sharp!
Yeah, I know.
Oh, never mind, it's just
my mom. I'm standing outside!
Still nothing?
No word from Misa yet?
Nope. Man. I thought if I
sent her pictures of GunBuild-1,
she'd find the
time to say something.
You know, Kai, sometimes,
sometimes it makes me wonder
if she really wanted me
to finish what she started.
Like, maybe she
doesn't care anymore?
Well, she said it, didn't she?
She told you she wanted you
to make her dream come true.
Yeah, I know. But then,
when she left for Tokyo...
Misa! I'm gonna do it. You'll
see!
I'm gonna join the club and
make your dream come true!
Aren't you happy?
You'll never be anything
more than just mediocre, Aki.
It's like I told you before.
I'm sure she only said
that to get you fired up.
Do you really think so?
And I bet she's not replying
to your messages now 'cause she
doesn't like that you
finished what she couldn't.
Maybe.
Hey. Is that the face
you're gonna wear tomorrow?
You really gonna look all
sad on GunBuild-1's big day?
No. You're right. There's no
point in worrying about it now.
What is this?!
Thanks. Enjoy the show!
Quite a turnout.
Looks like my advertising
had some real impact. Huh?
Check it out.
So many people!
Uh, I'm all in
favor of calling it off.
This is the very
first test. It might--
As swift as the wind!
As strong as the sea!
GUNVARREL!
Huh?!
The Robot Research Club
will regain its former glory!
I'm fired up!
All fired uuupp! Right!
Hello, everybody!
I'm Akiho Senomiya.
On behalf of the
Robot Research Club,
I welcome you to today's test.
This is a giant
robot of justice!
Our club has worked on
it for the past nine years.
And now, at long last,
the day has arrived!
For the first time ever, a pilot
is going to board this robot
and conduct an
operations test. Oh, and...
The blueprints for
Gunbuild-1 were drawn up
by my big sister,
Misaki Senomiya.
Please, relax and enjoy!
Whoa, whoa, hold on!
What?
What are you doing?
I was planning to get in it.
You're not piloting that.
If I don't, then who's going to?
My stomach. Ahhh, oooh...
Aw, man. Okay, okay.
D'you got any candy?
Thank you, Kai.
Oh, wow, it's hot in there!
Yeah, answer call.
Kai! How is it?
Like a sauna.
I guess we should've installed
some fans in there, huh?
I'll look into it.
You can do that,
but it's a metal tube.
Okay. Now look
over the controls.
Seems simple enough.
Can we get started now?
I'm roasting here.
Okay, wait for my signal,
then rev up the engine!
All right, everybody!
It's time to
start up GunBuild-1!
Countdown! Three! Two! One!
Okay, GunBuild-1! Let's go!
That's it, Kai.
Now try taking a step!
Huh?! What did you say?
GunBuild-1... prepare to walk!
You want me to make it walk?!
Damn! This thing's loud!
Counting down!
Three! Two! One! Let's walk!
Hey, Aki! What's going on here?!
It's okay!
Oh, really? 'Cause it
doesn't sound okay!
Is this thing
even moving forward?!
Man, it's slow!
That is underwhelming.
Hey! Don't talk
about it like that!
It's walking, right?
Okay, so it may be going slowly,
but it is walking
which is amazing!
It's an incredible achievement!
Woulda been
nine years ago, but...
Times change, kid. That's just
the way of the world.
It's constantly evolving.
Oh, come on! This is boring!
Make it do somethin', already!
Guess it must be broken, huh?
About what you'd
expect from a kid's club.
Why isn't it moving?
It stopped?
Aw, come on. Is that it?
What happened?!
How should I know? The engine
cut out all of a sudden.
Do something!
Try starting it again!
No good. It won't go.
No way!
That diesel engine was
practically scrap metal.
It must've died.
It's time to let it go.
I'm sorry, Aki.
Well, good work, Kai.
You can come
down now. Thanks a lot.
My sister probably would
have done a better job,
don't you think?
If she'd built it.
It would work.
That's cold!
So, what do we do now?
I don't know. I just want
my sister to acknowledge me.
No, that's not quite it.
I guess I just... I want to
step out of her shadow, somehow.
Poor GunBuild-1.
He seems sad, huh?
So they finished it,
after all this time.
It looks so different, though.
It's nothing like my blueprints.
What is that?
Nothing. Just a
big piece of junk.
After GunBuild-1's failure, the
Robot Research Club is forced
to consider a
different plan of action.
While Aki and Subaru clash,
JAXA renews its
offer to collaborate.
Weight and motion.
Stubbornness and compromise.
Dreams and reality.
After striving so hard for so
long to bring her sister's robot
to life, what choice
will Aki ultimately make?
Episode 10!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!