"Gezi" Where have I heard that?
Uchugaoka Park? Seriously?
Who would go there on a dare?
It's not scary at all.
You know what I heard a girl I
met in the Karate Club say?
There's a ghost
haunting that park!
You're kidding, right?
What are you doing?
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, of course
I know about Uchugaoka Park!
I didn't know
you had any interest
in urban legends, though!
That's a surprise!
Of all people,
I never woulda expected her
to be so into this stuff.
She sounds even more perky
and excited than usual.
Freeze! Right there!
I need you at the club
today. A local newspaper
is sending reporters
to interview us
about taking second place
at the ROBO-ONE tournament.
I'll pass on that. Just tell
'em whatever you want.
Hey! Come on!
You might want to work up
something to say ahead of time.
If you play your cards right,
a company might even want
to sponsor you after
reading the article.
Yeah, maybe!
Kai!
I gotta go see Daitoku.
I'll catch you later, okay?
From Karate Club? Oh yeah,
I did notice you started
following each other
on Twipo. What is this?
"A youthful mistake
in the making?"
I'll drop by the
hangar if I have time.
'Kay, have fu-
No! Don't have fun!
Around here?
Yeah.
When it happened, do you
remember hearing anything?
Like a kind of buzzing
sound or something?
"Bee, boo-boo, buh buh-bee-bee"
You know, like that.
Something like that, I guess.
I thought so.
There a legend
about the beeping?
Mhmm
What's that?
It's "The Buzzer." This same
buzzer sound has been playing
non-stop on a shortwave
radio station in Russia
for the last
thirty years or so.
One of the theories
people have come up with
is that it has to do with
ionosphere research. Who knows?
JAXA does have a station
pretty close to here.
Maybe the Uchugaoka Park beep
has something to do
with ionosphere stuff, too.
Hey! Could that be what caused
my PhoneDroid pad to freeze up?
Oh. I think that happened all
over the country, actually.
The real issue is that
email and the girl you saw.
If anything, they sound
more "occult" to me
than "urban legend."
There's a difference
between the two?
They're totally different.
The occult deals with
ghosts and demons
and stuff. It's scary.
There've been rumors
going around for awhile.
Stuff about a ghost
at Uchugaoka Park.
They say it's
a girl with long hair.
She's about
junior high age, or so.
Look, there she is!
What ghost would show up now?
The sun's still up.
That wasn't nice.
I admit. I've got
goosebumps now,
after hearing what you said.
The girl I saw here was exactly
like the one
you were describing.
Huh?! Really?!
Now that I think of it,
she's actually been seen
in other places, too.
Like at the Chikura Cave.
Yeah. I think I've heard of it.
Want to go look. My house
is that direction anyway.
That'd be cool, but do you mind
if we stop by the hangar first?
What hangar? Oh, you mean
that club you're in.
That cool?
I'm sorry. Robots are just...
Oh. Never mind.
I don't really need
to stop by
there anyway. Let's go.
We'll check out the cave.
Yeah, that sounds good.
And now, let me introduce you
to the incredible, GunBuild-1!
Yeah... as we said,
we were hoping
to hear about ROBO-ONE.
I understand. But please.
That tournament is long over.
It's old, stale news by now!
I'd much rather discuss our
current activities and our futu-
Are you in here talking
nonsense to yourself ag--
Is he in the club, too?
What? Oh, yeah. That's our
new member, Subaru.
Whoa, is that what
I think it is?
No! It's not!
It's the M45! The winner
of the tournament!
Nope! It's totawy diffwent!
No doubt about it!
That's the one!
Absolutely! But what's
it doing here?
Well, Subaru belongs
to the club,
and that robot belongs to
Subaru, so there you have it.
Oww! Ow! Oww!
What was that for?
I'm sorry. You see.
Mr. Pleiades is a visitor here.
He's training for the upcoming
world championship tournament.
Oh, really? He is?
That's awesome!
Why didn't your club leader
give us that
information sooner?
We'd love to hear
all about it for our story.
I'm not finding
anything so far.
Mmm. Everything seems to
be normal with the pad, too.
Not freezing up or anything.
What's that?
Aww. It's a poor, dead whaley.
There've been a lot lately.
Apparently fourteen of them
washed up all
at once a while back.
Yeah, that was
in March, wasn't it?
I hear there have been lots
of wormies dying out,
and froggies, too.
A lot of strange things have
been happening on this island.
I don't think it's
just on the island.
I think, there's more to it.
Like how temperatures
in Russia were as hot
as summer this past winter?
Or how America's west coast is
getting slammed with snowstorms.
Or how heavy rains
have eroded the Nazca Lines.
You're right.
That is a lot of anomalies.
Yeah, sure is, but I guess
there's no way to know
if they're linked
at all, is there?
Even so, it is pretty strange.
It reminds me of the Anemone.
Thanks for your help today.
Here's a token of appreciation.
Man, you can't catch.
Wanna trade?
No, that's okay.
So, do you have training
tomorrow or what?
Like, karate?
No, I'm done with it.
It's my last year of school,
and I just had
my last tournament, so--
Oh! How'd you do?
I lost in the first round.
Wow. You're that bad
at it, huh?
Unfortunately. It's not
like I didn't try to improve.
I thought
three years of practice
in the school club
would help, but...
Then why don't you
join our club?
But I'm graduating this year.
So what? The same thing
goes for me and Aki.
I know, but,
robots aren't really...
I get it, there's something
with you and robots.
Still, you should come check
out the club at least once.
Although, I totally understand
if you're not a big fan of Aki.
No! That's not it!
Not at all!
Believe me, I have nothing
against Akiho whatsoever.
Really. In fact,
I actually think it would be
kinda cool if we
got to be friends.
Oh, yeah? That's awesome.
I'm sure she'd love to hear
that. You should tell her.
Well, maybe.
I'll think it over.
That's a bonus.
By the blessing
of the Seven Goddesses,
I now make my advent
of four hundred light years!
I am Mister Pleiades!
Will you go home?
GUNVAL Ankh Striker!
Hello, anybody home?
Dude, knock!
Oh, come on.
How'd the interview go?
Okay, I guess.
What about the Space Candy guy?
You did say you were going
to see him again, didn't you?
No dice. I even took
Tanegashi Machine with me,
but it didn't help.
Meh. Once again,
completely lacking impact.
Chesty, chesty!
Boing, boing, boing!
Why don't you take
Subaru with you?
If that guy's got
one thing, it's impact.
I already thought of that.
I asked him earlier.
You know I'd never go.
What kind of fool are you?
How about you take a good
look at what you're wearing
and then ask me that again?
Kai. What're we gonna do?
Well, good luck
figuring that out.
You act like it's got
nothing to do with you.
You're GUNVARREL's pilot,
you know. Start acting like it!
This conversation again?
I already told you no.
I don't wanna get
squished when it falls over.
It's not gonna fall over!
Geez, you'll do
what Subaru says,
but not me?
Some kinda friend you are.
Well, you can
always challenge me.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what about Daitoku?
Did she beat you, too?
Huh? That was
totally different.
She was doing me a favor.
I asked her to show me around.
Around where?
Some local urban legend spots.
Yeah? What for?
Well, well.
Are you interested?
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
I don't care if you and Daitoku
want to go on a silly date.
It's really none of my business.
It's just, well,
you don't go places
with anyone all that often,
so I'll admit, it's kind
of surprising. That's all.
Actually, I was just asking
if you were interested
in spots around town
associated with urban legends.
"Kai! You are skilled, indeed!"
How so?
Oh, shut up!
You jerk!
What's with you?!
I hate you!
Just Mom asking about dinner.
Yeah, this kinda
thing never happens
when you're actually
waiting for it to.
Can you hear me?
Bingo!
Hello? Is anybody there?
One of the theories
people have come up with
is that it has to do
with ionosphere research...
Getting closer doesn't seem
to make any difference.
I probably had that coming.
Well, I guess that's that, then.
Don't I have an infrared
camera app on this thing?
Huh? What is this?
What password?
Airi knows the password.
I'd like to tell you what it is.
Are you here? In this room?
Yes, I'm here.
Airi was getting
so worried that
you wouldn't be
able to hear her.
What's going on?
Hey. Would it be alright
if I called you "Brother"?
I'd like to talk to you.
Is this real?
Testing, testing.
Tomorrow's weather report.
Looks like we
can expect good weather
for the Tanegashima region.
Clear blue skies!
How was that? Can you hear me?
It's an A.I.? That's good!
I can hear you loud and clear.
Airi's so glad. I'm great
at talking, actually.
In fact, I even know how to
say your full name, Brother.
You are Kaito Yashio!
How do you know that?
Are you asking
for a full explanation?
Then please tap Airi
to call for Gezi
and Gezi will
answer your question.
Go on. Just tap.
Access confirmed. Switch to
Gezi mode was successful.
Oh, so, you're Gezi.
Airi is the name
that has been given to a
communication interface that
resides in the IRUO servers.
Gezi is different.
Gezi is designated as a
fully-automated data
collection engine.
Okay, now will you tell me
how you know who I am?
Airi was initially
put into operation
on December 24th of the
year two-thousand-and-eight.
You visited the park frequently.
You were also approximately
Airi's age at the time.
For these reasons,
you were selected
as a priority target
for possible contact.
Over the course of eight years,
twenty-nine distinct attempts
at contact were made.
Of those twenty-nine attempts,
you reacted in
some way three times.
However, this is the first time
that successful contact
has ever been achieved.
That many?
Let me see if
I've got this straight.
Basically you're an IRUO app
that took a liking to me?
Yes, that is correct,
Mister Yashio.
Do you think you could
call me something else?
You are welcome
to register a nickname
if you would prefer it.
Go ahead.
Oh, let me think a second.
Just Yashio is fine
or Kai, maybe?
"Oh let me think a second.
Just Yashio is fine
or Kai, maybe."
Is this nickname correct?
Uhh. Cancel please.
Go with Yashio.
Canceled. The nickname
"Yashio" has been registered.
Is this nickname correct?
Yep. So, What do I do
to turn you off?
Do I just press this?
Warning: Guest users
do not have access privileges.
Please input the
required geotag password.
It's the same box as before.
The password is
H-I-D-D-E-N H-A-N-D.
Pronounced Hidden Hand.
I dunno, this kinda
seems like a trap to me.
Oh, well: Hidden Hand.
This is a secret data file
located on the IRUO servers.
Codename: "Kimijima Report"
Number One.
Written by Kou Kimijima. Date
created: November 7th,
two-thousand-and-nine.
Kimijima, huh? 'kay.
"I am creating this
backup report in the event
that I meet with an untimely
death. Someone has been
making threats on my life.
I expect it won't be long before
I am permanently eliminated."
Here goes: NASA is perpetrating
a massive cover-up.
During a solar survey
conducted in November of 2000,
magnetic monopoles
were discovered
in the sun's
southern polar region.
These findings are accurate
and cannot be disputed.
However, NASA organized
a full-scale
propaganda campaign in order
to convince the public that
the information leaked
regarding this discovery
was part of a hoax.
But the fact remains that all
scientific evidence indicates
that the sun is on
the verge of explosion.
Large-scale solar storms
will occur in succession
in twenty-twelve,
twenty-fifteen,
twenty-nineteen,
and twenty-twenty.
The twenty-fifteen solar
storm in particular will have
serious effects on the Earth
and its magnetosphere.
The sun will slam the
planet with energy so great
that it will plunge the
entire world into crisis
and no one will see it coming.
There's always talk
about solar storms.
And NASA cover-ups. It's not
like it's anything new.
So, like, it could
just be a story
some random guy came up with,
or I dunno, maybe even
a chapter from a
sci-fi novel or something.
Yeah, that seems likely.
But you said it was labeled
Number One, right?
Shouldn't that mean there's
a second part out there?
We'd want to look
at that, too, and besides.
Yeah?
There's still the fact that
it predicted the
solar storms perfectly.
Even the auroras started showing
up in Japan in twenty-twelve.
The years twenty-twelve,
fifteen, nineteen,
and then twenty.
What brings you here so late?
Mizuka, you're looking
nice, as always.
You wanna use
the bench, buy something.
The 2015 Crash. Oh, yeah.
When computers all around the
world started malfunctioning,
they said it was
because of a solar storm.
Oh my, you're looking
pretty serious.
And that isn't like you.
Yeah, you're right.
Sorry. I just read
something strange.
Had to do with some
guy named Kou Kimijima.
Kaito. Where did
you hear that name?
So he did briefly demonstrate
abnormal behavior at the time.
I was right. It seems it wasn't
my imagination, after all.
I've compiled my report.
Would you like to see it now?
I would.
Kaito Yashio.
Currently eighteen years old.
Born May 5th,
two-thousand-and-one.
Hails from Tanegashima.
And one of the victims
of the Anemone incident.
After finding the mysterious
and cryptic Kimijima Report,
Kai goes to explore
the old folk museum,
following the suggestion
made by the AI named Airi.
Meanwhile, the search
for somebody to sponsor
the construction of
GunBuild-1 leads Aki back
to the Space Candy Company,
this time, with impact!
Just when things seem to
finally be falling into line
for the Robot Research
Club's sponsorship,
yet another conflict arises.
Episode 6!
Let's hit it off, everybody!
Later days!