GUNDAM 08TH MS TEAM
[OPENING THEME]
[PILOT] Altitude 9500
wind speed 0.526.
[PILOT 2] Surrounding area
clear of enemy presence.
[MAN] Escort plane. Stay on
guard. [PILOT] Yes sir.
[PILOT 3] Flight program check.
[PILOT] Linking to
main computer.
[TECH 2] Gyro system activated.
Trim control arm.
[PILOT] Generator system RGA.
Activating all control systems.
[VOICE] How's the pressure
in the plasma cylinder look?
[PILOT] 3% lower than normal.
It's barely within the limit.
But I'll make it work somehow.
[VOICE] Good.
[MACHINE POWERING UP]
[TECH] Preparing to release
cables. All set?
[PILOT] Yes I'm ready
when you are.
[TECH] Cable release on my mark:
5, 4, 3, 2, 1... takeoff!
[TECH] 9000. 8500. 8000.
7500. 7000. 6500. 6000...
[TECH] Minovsky particle
compressor is
functioning normally.
[TECH 2] Plasma propulsion power
at point zero. Within
predicted values.
[TECH] No instability
detected in gyro system.
[PILOT] The vibration is less
than I thought it would be.
Increasing power!
Big brother: I believe
your dream has come true!
THE DEMON OVERHEAD
[SOLDIER] Hey check it out!
The Reaper's hard at work.
[SOLDIER 2] Oh yeah! Boy do I
feel sorry for Karen. What did
she ever do to get stuck
with a jinx like that guy!
[SOLDIER 2] No kidding! I feel
sorry for the rest of 'em too.
[MICHEL] Chief what are
those guys talking about?
[SOLDIER] Hey Sanders doesn't it
bother you that all your
teammates die?
What do you wanna bet that
newbie Commander of his will be
the next one to buy it?
Uh wait a minute sir.
Pretty sad to have no friends
because you killed 'em all. Hey!
Wait sir!
[SOLDIER] You son of a bitch
come here.
[SOLDIER 2] Alright Reaper.
You asked for it!
This is no good. Commander!
Commander! Oh for crying out
loud where is he?
Commander! Commander!
We got trouble!
[MAN] Hey The Reaper's in a
fight!
[MAN 2] Cool who is he fighting?
[MAN 3] Two guys from the 07th.
[MAN] I'm betting on the 07th
guys!
[MAN 2] My money's
on The Reaper!
Place your wagers boys! Hurry
before the fight's over! Ha!
I don't see it. Where are they?
It's at 380 meters at 10 o'clock
sir. But sir is it true
that everyone
who has served with Sanders
has died so far?
[SHIRO] Who told you a
ridiculous story like that?
[MICHEL] Ow!!!
Alright Reaper! Now the time has
come for you to rest in peace!
Get out of the way! Come on!
Lemme through!
Hey 3 against one? They aren't
even fighting fair!
What th‐
[SOLDIER] You bastard!
Who's next?
[JEEP HONKING]
[KOJIMA] Just what the hell
are you people doing?
Sir a friendly competition!
A sporting exchange
between MS teams sir!
A friendly competition? Well you
chose one hell of a
hot day for it.
And you guys the 07th team?
You're supposed to be out
providing rear line support
to the western zone.
Sir! Will do sir!
[KOJIMA] Good. 08th team: I want
you ready to move on a
moment's notice.
[SHIRO] Sir!
[KOJIMA] MS teams dismissed!
[TEAMS] Sir!
[KOJIMA] The rest of you get
back to where you belong.
Well I believe I won the bet.
Hehehe.
[SOLDIER] How'd it start?
Better beware of
The Reaper Commander newbie!
Don't let those punks
get to you. It's not worth it.
[SANDERS] Right. But sir I...
Come on. Let's go.
[GINIAS] Thanks to all of your
extraordinary efforts we
have successfully
completed the first stage of the
Apsalus project. The
completion of the Apsalus is
close at hand! On the day it is
finished our power over the
Earth system shall be
renewed and the light of victory
will fall upon Zeon. Sieg Zeon!
[CROWD] Sieg Zeon! Sieg Zeon!
Sieg Zeon! Sieg Zeon!
And that's what finally
convinced Duke Degin I was
worthy of being in command
of this project.
[STUNNED VOICES]
Aina my dear. You look
lovelier than ever this evening.
Thank you brother.
You test flight was magnificent.
It was a wonderful feat.
I can hardly describe how
wonderful it felt. Although I
admit the ventilation
system could use just a little
work. I was really hot in there.
But then again if it
weren't for that my victory
drink wouldn't taste quite as
cool now would it brother?
You did do very well.
Now please just enjoy yourself.
[VOICE] Ginias! Ginias where
the hell are ya?
Oh great. Admiral Kellanay.
Outta my way! Move!
Lemme through here!
Ah yes! Ginias there you are!
How are ya?!
Yuri stop it. People
are staring.
[YURI] Ah what the hell do we
care? Hahahaha! I got a
report your high‐priced
toy was finally working so I
came over from Europe
to have a look.
It's no toy to me.
Hahaha! What have we here? My
little Aina all
grown up at last!
And wouldn't you know it
you grew up pretty.
The last time I saw you you were
just a simple little kid. Women!
You are amazing creatures.
You flatter me too much
mister Kellanay.
[YURI] Hey whoa quit being so
formal. It's not like we're
strangers or anything.
Aina how about it?
How'd you like to be
my girlfriend?
What?
I know most guys are intimidated
by the Sahalins but I've
never been afraid
to have a little fun.
You must be joking. Please
excuse me while I step outside.
This room is
becoming unbearable.
Pardon me please.
Heh. She won't let her guard
down for a minute. Get it?
Hmph. Those two have
never been any fun.
[AINA] Why does he have to
show up now of all times?
With him here my brother's
concentration will be thrown
completely off! If Ginias
hadn't been there I would have
loved to have just
punched him out.
Miss Aina may I ask just what
this project means to you ma'am?
My brother's dream is
everything. Perhaps you think
I'm being too dramatic?
No.
[AINA] Once his Apsalus is
completed this war will
finally come to an end.
I guess I'm having a hard time
celebrating a weapon that will
wipe out a lot of lives
before this is over.
The Sahalin family will win the
war. And from now on my
life will be forever
linked with your family.
I appreciate you sentiment.
Power, prestige, nobility...
it's all part of
being a Sahalin.
It's kind of like
being a puppet.
[NORRIS] Ms. Aina...
[WISTFUL MUSIC]
[SHIRO] What's a matter Sanders?
I'm... I wish to resign sir.
I would like a transfer.
You don't mean that.
[SANDERS] Eledore take my
place as a mobile suit pilot.
[ELEDORE] What? What are you
talking about? I can't do that.
Will then I suppose I could
pilot it.
‐What's this all about?
I won't go out there. At least
not as a pilot. If I do I'll
just get you all killed.
[KAREN] Ugh! What a wimp!
[SHIRO] Karen!
[KAREN] You're still hung up on
that bullshit? OK so you've
lost every team you've
fought with so far. But now
because of what those morons
said you believe you are
the Grim Reaper. You let what
they said get under your skin.
Yes! That's why I want out.
You think quitting's gonna solve
anything? Where's your
damned balls soldier?
So you do have a pair after all?
[SHIRO] Damn it Karen.
This team would be better off
without a goddamn coward like
you on it anyway.
That's enough. You need to
back off Chief.
What for?
No. It's alright. In my career
I've had to watch every team
I've ever served with get killed
on the 3rd mission every single
time. And I always survive.
[GULP] You mean you're a
3rd time jinx?
This will be our 3rd action
together and if I'm part of it
the 08th team is going to die.
That's why I have to quit now!
Before I cau‐
Isn't it a little conceited to
think that it was you who got
your friends killed?
Sanders who do you think you
are? Just shake that doomsday
crap out of your head!
Permission denied. I'm sorry but
I can't accept your transfer
in the middle of
a mission. Now get back
to your post.
But sir!
That's an order Sanders.
Right.
Don't worry about it. You know I
think we'll be the ones who will
break this run of bad
luck you've been having.
Oh yeah there's nothing to
soothe your nerves like a
dose of bad rations.
You know I was just thinking: I
hope we don't see any
action tomorrow sir.
Come on. If you want to survive
you have to believe in it.
[MICHEL] Hmm?
You have to have faith.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[BEEPING]
[TECH] We have a warning alarm!
[GINIAS] I can see that.
[TECH] The telemeter is also
off. We may be at its limit.
And there may be no problem.
Have all our forces on the front
begin forming a strong
perimeter. I want the Apsalus'
flight path secured.
[GINIAS] Norris report. What's
the condition of the unit?
[NORRIS] Sir I see no
apparent changes.
[GINIAS] That's good. Continue
to monitor the load rate.
[AINA] Right.
[NORRIS] Ms. Aina don't push it
too hard.
‐I'm aware of that.
[GUNFIRE]
We have reports of enemy fire.
Something must be going on. OK
Sanders get ready we're
moving into area 376.
[SHIRO] I'll take point.
You follow me. Do you read?
I read.
I've got a bad feeling. Tell me
you're not writing a letter.
I'm writing my will!
Great. You do that.
There's a strong vibration in
the main body. Altitude 4000.
The load is too high!
I can't maintain this altitude.
I'm going into a dive!
[TECH] Try to override the
control computer's codes.
[NORRIS] We're inside
Feddie‐controlled territory.
Be careful!
I can't climb!
[NORRIS] I know you can do it
Aina. Just stop its descent.
[AINA] Right!
Broadcast Minovsky particles.
We'll keep you in contact
with the base.
[AINA] Thank you.
[TECH] Increasing altitude.
[GINIAS] Can we pull in support
from the Northeastern
defense line?
[TECH] Yes sir. They're
initiating a diversion attack.
Abort Ginias. Enough already.
Have Aina punch out
of that thing.
We can't afford to lose the
Apsalus. I know Aina
can save it.
[TECH] This is the escort unit.
I can confirm that she's pulled
out of the dive but just barely.
Excellent work Aina. Send out
the reserve troops as well. We
have to make certain
those Feddies don't spot the
flight path of the Apsalus.
[TECH] Yes sir.
Typical. You brainiacs get
overconfident and we've gotta
clean up the mess.
Excuse me sir. I
have the report.
[TECH] Sir we've regained
partial latitude control.
[TECH 2] Power systems
are overheating.
Ginias the time has come for me
to head back to the European
front. Be sure to
send me your plaything once
you've worked the
bugs out of it.
I didn't build it just
for you Admiral.
[YURI] Yeah whatever. See
you Mr. Genius.
[SHIRO] Eledore can you pinpoint
the enemy's location for me?
[ELEDORE] 2000 meters away at 11
o'clock. Karen's
pursuing them now.
[GUNFIRE]
Huh? What are they up to?
Commander! The enemy is
pulling back!
[KAREN] It's like she wants
us to follow him.
That's weird. They must be
up to something.
What am I picking up?
I hear it too what is it?
[ELEDORE] Quiet!
[KAREN] What do we do Commander?
Do we follow them?
[SHIRO] No wait. There's
something here.
[ELEDORE] Commander
check this out.
[RADIO] About 25 clicks to the
east! [RADIO 2] Recover it.
[RADIO 3] Roger. We should reach
the Apsalus momentarily.
It's somewhere in the jungle.
[RADIO 4] Base I need a
confirmation on the signal.
What the hell?
[ELEDORE] I can barely hear it
because of the Minovsky particle
jamming but I think
there's some sort of enemy unit
headed this way. Hey. Why
isn't this in code?
Alright. We'll lay low and wait
for it here. All units
ambush formation!
[MICHEL] Eledore do you really
think it's coming our way?
Definitely. Commander it'll pass
right over your head
in 40 seconds.
[SHIRO] Got it. We'll let 'em
pass &amp; then see what happens.
I wonder if this is Sanders'
fault.
‐Pipe down!
[ELEDORE] Picking up some
vibration. This thing
is beyond huge.
It's way bigger than
a mobile suit.
[ELEDORE] Fighter planes.
Multiple units.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Here they come!
Now let 'em through...
[GUNFIRE]
Who's shooting?!
[NORRIS] Concentrate on that
point of fire. Secure the
Apsalus flight path!
[PILOT] Roger!
You stupid shit! Why
did you fire!?
I didn't know I...
[SHIRO] They're coming right
for us! Scatter!
Just what we needed!
[GUNFIRE]
[KAREN] Are you
reading me Sanders?
Roger!
[KAREN] I am not gonna
die just watch me!
[SHIRO] Karen! What the
hell are you doing?!
[YELLING]
There! That's the wa‐ uh?
[CRASHING SOUND]
Karen!
Ugh!
Karen! Wha‐...
It's huge!
What the hell is that thing!?
[GUNFIRE]
Did I get 'em?
Norris!
[NORRIS] Forgive me Ms. Aina!
Can you make it back
to the base?
[NORRIS] I'll be fine. Please
Ms. Aina just get out of here!
No I'm gonna cover you. In the
meantime you get outta here!
[NORRIS] Ms. Aina!
‐Alright let's do it!
[DISCHARGING SHOCK]
Goddamn monster!!
[SANDERS] They're not going to
die. Do you hear they
aren't gonna die!!
[GUNFIRE]
You like that?!
[SCREAMING]
He must be out of his mind!
I am not... I am not
the Grim Reaper!
Not this time. I will not lose.
I swear I will not lose again!
[GUNFIRE]
Give it everything you got!
Shoot! Shoot at it until your
guns are overheating!
[GUNFIRE]
[NORRIS] Ms. Aina! You can't
take fire from that close! Get
out of there now!
Roger!
[SHIRO] Sanders! Ha ha!
You were great!
[LAUGHING]
See Sanders I was right.
I'm alive!
Uh huh. We're still alive.
I guess we are alright.
Yeah. I can't believe it
but I guess we really are.
And we all made it. We can
overcome anything. Even
break a jinx.
As long as we have
faith in ourselves!
[ENDING THEME]
[SHIRO] The existence of the
enemy's new weapon sends a shock
through our forces.
Now the 08th Team is sent out
every day to search and gather
intelligence. And then
we get word that Eledore &amp;
Michel have been captured by the
Zeon! I hope those 2 will be
alright. They have to
find some way to escape!
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam
The 08th MS Team: The Broken
Order to Stand By.