GUNDAM 08TH MS TEAM
[OPENING THEME]
[CANNON FIRE]
[MAN] Rear turrets! Do something
to suppress that lead Musai!
[MAN 2] Ship #3's
been taken out.
[MAN] Concentrate main
guns forward. Stop that thing!
[MAN 2] It's too fast! The
predictor's useless!
[MAN] Oh damn it!
[SOLDIER] Zeon mobile armor has
broken through defensive line 3!
Speed mach 11 and accelerating!
[SOLDIER 2] Intruder will reach
Jabrow firing range
in 9 seconds.
[MISSILES FIRING]
[GROUND COLLAPSING]
FRONT LINE
Jabrow's destroyed.
[TECH] End of simulation.
[CPT.] So are you telling me
they're planning to use
their new weapon
to attack Federation
headquarters?
[MAN] Yes. According to
intelligence we've
managed to gather sir.
‐Well then we'd better not waste
time.
‐Yes sir.
[KOJIMA] Seek and destroy
the enemy base.
Synchronize watches.
Commence the operation.
A weapon designed to smash right
through the atmosphere.
I think Revil's Antarctic Treaty
may have backfired on us.
Captain are you certain you made
the right decision by
deploying the 08th team?
Because of Shiro Amada?
If his friendship with the
enemy is that deep,
we may be able to make use of
it to find out more.
But what if he betrays us?
Don't worry. I have him under
close observation.
Extremely close.
[SHIRO] Sanders are you with us?
Yes sir.
[SHIRO] After we make the
drop at point alpha,
we'll proceed to point beta
while we search for the enemy.
We'll rendezvous with the Medea
which will bring us
back to base.
Now the purpose behind this
operation is specifically to
find the enemy base.
Gathering intelligence is
paramount. We have to do all we
can to avoid combat.
[MICHEL] You mean we
don't have to fight?
I guess that means if your
girlfriend comes out we don't
have to hurt her.
[ELEDORE] Girlfriend?
The Commander's girlfriend?
Of all the bum luck! The women
in the hospital were all fat.
Bleargh.
You never saw women this big, it
was all I had to choose from.
Meanwhile you managed to get
lucky on a mission.
Full of himself
that's what he is.
We should be able to have as
much fun as him.
Eledore!
You with me?
Will you zip it?
[ELEDORE] Come on Karen what's
the matter with you? Why
are you so uptight?
This isn't uptight this is
getting ready. It's my first air
drop and you aren't helping.
You're no fun.
Go take your fun outside!
[SANDERS] Sir! There's... uh...
something...
[PILOT] Coming up on drop point!
5 minutes and counting.
Alright. Now everyone move out!
Roger that!
‐Ah well. Let's do it!
I'm sorry you were about
to say something Sanders?
Um... nothing sir.
Okay.
So is his girlfriend pretty?
No idea!
Hey! Better be careful spy guy!
We'd hate to see you get
lost out there.
The Commander could never be an
enemy spy he's not devious
enough to pull it off!
OK everyone let's cut
out the chatter!
We're almost in position.
Better get inside your coffins.
Come on. We have to go.
[PILOT] Seal confirmed.
Night vision activated. All I
have to do is remember
the simulation.
She's a female Zeon pilot? What
a hopeless romantic! It's
doomed from the start.
I still don't buy it. The
commander's not a spy!
[KAREN] Oh my God! Commander!
I've got a Gau transport.
Engaging!
Karen are you alright? We have
to hurry! Get us out there!
[PILOT] No not yet! If we send
you out now we'll be
in danger too.
Well just hurry!
[GUNFIRE]
Karen don't just stay there
get away! Karen!
I'll be with you soon my love...
[PILOT] Unidentified
machine directly above us!
[PILOT 2] Get some flares up!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Shit!
[SHIRO] Stop your shooting at
once! If you don't I'll
shoot you down.
[SHIRO] You're going to shoot
yourselves to get me?
[MAN] Sir! Number 2
engine is on fire!
Then put it out!
All weapons turrets cease fire!
[KAREN] We're out of
their firing range.
Do we fire sir?
No forget 'em for now. We have
repairs to work on.
Why didn't he?
[YURI] The rest of our men
should've been here by now.
We believe the Gau was
only on one engine Admiral.
[MAN] I sighted what looks like
a Gau! It's off the
plotted course though.
[YURI] You see any
Feddie aircraft?
[MAN] No sign of any. But it's
trailing an awful lot of smoke!
Let's get some more men on
the defensive line!
Let's hope the only trouble
they have is a damaged engine.
130, 120, 110... firing!
Landing confirmed. Ah...
It's beautiful.
[ELEDORE] Karen are you alright?
Great location for inspiring
words of love don't you think?
Would you just give me a minute
to‐‐
‐[BEEPING]
[KAREN] Where is it? The
opposite shore?
From the water?!
Karen!
[CRASHING]
No way you are killing Karen!
Michel, distract him with
the hover truck.
But I can't use the
machine gun alone.
[ELEDORE] You're gonna let Karen
die out here?
‐Oh no...
Come on Michel! Hurry!
[MICHEL YELLING]
No no no!!!
[ELEDORE] Karen! Talk to me!
Tell me are you alright?
Eledore?
How's your mobile suit?
Michel's in big trouble.
Well my monitor and my
scopes are out.
[ELEDORE] Forget 'em. I'll give
you directions. Let me be your
targeter! Beam rifle up!
Take it up and to the right.
Too high! Down a little.
Now stop.
He sees what we're doing
hurry up and fire!
Correct right 6 degrees. Now!
[ELEDORE] Come on Karen fire!
[BEAM FIRING]
Eledore... Eledore!
Eledore!
What's wrong, are you alright?
Eledore?
I'm not sure. I think I pissed
my pants. We made it though.
Thanks to you. I owe
you my life.
Well if you die what happens
to all my plans for our future?
Huh?
[MICHEL YELLING]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[CPT.] We lost most of our cargo
as well as 14 personnel.
I'm sorry sir.
Forget it. I'm the one to blame
for forcing a crippled Gau onto
a mission like this.
Captain forgive me.
Thank you for understanding.
You've done very well.
Now let's
finish this evacuation.
All this smoke will be
visible for miles
and not even Feddies are
dumb enough to overlook
something like that.
[LAUGHTER]
[CPT.] Excuse me Admiral?
I wonder if you'd let me
borrow one of these.
One of those pieces of junk?
Captain are you trying to
commit suicide?
I wanna buy some time for our
main forces to pull out.
And I'm itching for the chance
to meet up with those
Feddies again.
Permission granted.
Just promise to come back alive.
I promise.
Sir I'd like to volunteer.
Same here sir.
You're aware I can't promise
you any support or supplies?
We're aware of that sir.
Just look after the
safety of the men.
Get 'em back into space Okay?
You're good soldiers. Alright
Magella attack force
let's move out!
Sir!
[ELEDORE] Come on! Don't be mad.
Gimme a break!
Uh the beam rifle cannon
should be operational now!
[KAREN] I've got
video on my scope.
[ELEDORE] Tell ya what! I'll
treat you to a dinner when my
song royalties come in!
Everyone listen up! We're
changing the plan a little bit.
[SHIRO] Karen &amp; the hover truck
will head for the
rendezvous point.
Sanders &amp; I will carry
out the mission.
We'll be in a lot of trouble if
we run into a fight
along the way.
Let's hope that doesn't happen.
[SHIRO] But if it does, run!
[ELEDORE] Maybe we could come up
with a better plan?
Great plan!
[KAREN] I'll use my state of the
art mobile suit to run away as
fast as I possibly can.
Ah forgive me for
having to ask you for help.
Well I know a bit about
medicines I might as well.
Thank you very much.
Can I help you with some
of that ma'am?
That's alright. I've got it.
You get some rest.
Wait that looks heavy.
[MAN] I... I'm sorry.
No. Is this what
you're giving them?
Yes.
And you have the nerve to call
yourself a doctor?
We have no other options if we
wish to finish the
Apsalus on time.
My brother put you up to this!
No. It was my decision to make.
I am not without a conscience.
However I am also a professional
soldier who is fighting a war
for the independence
of the colonies
and will do whatever is
necessary.
With the Apsalus we'll be able
to hit the enemy's headquarters.
And to make that happen as a
soldier I feel certain
sacrifices have to be made.
[AINA] So Ginias is ignoring the
order to stop work. I
have to stop him.
[MAN] Looks like you've managed
to convert the Rick Dom
generator successfully sir.
[GINIAS] Of course. Cut phases
7, 8, and 9 out of the project.
Increase the
construction efforts.
Admiral Yuri is requesting
evacuation support.
Support? And risk revealing
the location of this facility?
But we can't stand by &amp; let
our people be killed.
So let him deal with the
evacuation himself.
Sir you're forgetting the
lives of the brave men
who've made the long march from
Odessa to make it to this place.
That's irrelevant. Nothing is
more important than the
Apsalus being completed.
Damn! Ginias are you really
going to abandon
your own forces?
I'll find a way to get us
back into space no matter what.
I'm counting on you
Magella attack team.
Uh commander?
What? The enemy?
Something like that.
[SANDERS] The truth is I've been
ordered to keep an
eye on you sir.
I've broken too many
regulations huh?
[SHIRO] Don't worry about it
Sanders.
‐Oh. Good.
I knew Kojima would do
something like this eventually.
It wasn't him. It was Captain
Ryer who asked me to do it.
It was Captain Ryer.
Some of the men from the
inquiry must still not trust me.
Mines now active!
Now I wonder if the
Federation will ever trust me?
[SANDERS] We've got battle
wreckage 2 clicks ahead.
Multiple metallic
objects detected.
[SHIRO] Perfect place for a
trap. Let's double back
into the forest.
[SHIRO] Sanders pull back!
[CPT.] HEAT ammo on the one
with the horns! Fire!
Hit his ventilator next! And
finish off the one in front.
Fire!
[SANDERS] Pulling back!
[SHIRO] Sanders!
Keep it up! Fire at
will full barrage.
He's locked on us! Let's
get out of here!
[SHIRO] My optical sensors!
[CPT.] Barry! Lunen! Formation
A! Once the smoke clears
we'll settle things.
But first a little psychological
warfare. Federation mobile suit!
[SHIRO] That voice!
You're the captain of that Gau!
[CPT.] Captain Bjorn Abust.
I have a question for you.
Why didn't you fire on our
Gau when you had the chance?
[SHIRO] What?!
My men &amp; I were very
appreciative. But I don't
share your weakness.
We are a proud people &amp; we
haven't much use for
Federation mercy or pity.
[SHIRO] I just wanted to avoid
any more needless deaths.
[CPT.] Is that why you were
about to shoot me down?
I thought so.
Our men are suffering too much.
Please stop the Apsalus project.
And after that what happens?
Maybe you were planning on
stopping this war all
by yourself?
Hardly Ginias. However we both
know you received orders to
stop construction.
Giving the men drugs so
they can keep working is wrong.
Very touching. Unfortunately we
happen to be fighting a war.
The Apsalus will be completed.
And I'll get the order
rescinded if I have to.
[YURI] Hurry! Move!
[MAN] Sir! What about you?
My place is right here. I'm not
going in until my men get back.
[SANDERS] Commander!
[SHIRO] Sanders? You Okay?
[SANDERS] My left leg is
broken. I can't help you.
How bad is the wound?
Are you bleeding?
[SANDERS] I meant the
mobile suit's leg sir.
[SHIRO] I forgot the most
important thing.
So you're really gonna shoot
this time?
[SHIRO] Yeah!
[GUNFIRE]
Everyone fall back while firing.
That's enough. We've got
plenty of time!
[CPT.] Don't get killed now!
We're getting pretty good
at falling back while firing.
Well after all it is what we've
been doing all the
way from Odessa.
Good. Now let's finish this Fed.
[SHIRO] I won't fight for the
Federation but I'll sure as hell
fight to save my friends!
You've had a change of heart?
I don't buy it!
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
[LAUGHTER]
Eh?
Well we made it back Admiral.
Unfortunately we lost the fight.
I'm glad you made it back.
Very glad.
[MAN] Where is everyone? They
all made it inside.
Thanks to you.
[MAN] Now let's get back into
space.
[MAN 2] I'll bet a fat‐ass like
you prefers zero g.
Oh you're one to talk.
‐Oh come on lighten up.
[MAN] Hey what's going on?
[MAN 2] What the hell? Shit!
[GINIAS] Well Rear
Admiral Yuri Kellanay.
Let us in Ginias!
Your private secretary has
told me all of your plans.
What have you done to Cynthia?
[GINIAS] I found out Commandant
Giren doesn't know yet
that you've ordered us to
stop construction.
That means if you perish on
the battlefield
the Commandant will never find
out the Apsalus was
to be scrapped.
Run for it! Get out
of this tunnel!
So Admiral Kellanay was
unfortunately killed in action.
Barry! Lunen!
Ginias!!
What was that?
[ENDING THEME]
[SHIRO] The Federal forces have
found the Zeon base. And now a
full‐scale battle is on.
Suddenly a blue mobile suit
appears. He can take out three
Gundams single‐handedly.
And that can mean only one
thing: He's an ace pilot. One by
one he takes out the Federation
soldiers until... is it my turn
to die too? Perhaps!
Next time: The Shuddering
Mountain ‐ Part One.