GUNDAM 08TH MS TEAM
[OPENING THEME]
[MAN] 03rd team moving out!
[MAN 2] Moving out? How the hell
am I supposed to fight on
a full stomach?
[MAN] Shut up! You're too
big to be full.
[RADIO] Look we can't pull out
of this base until the 08th
team gets back. Damn!
Where can I find Lt. Nickard?
‐Still on his lunch break sir.
Ah! Dumb shit watch where you're
going! You trying to kill
us or something?!
Good. Just the way I like it.
[ELEDORE] We're back a bit late.
You want me to pop the hood?
Where the hell have you been!?
THE BROKEN ORDER TO STAND BY
Hey hey! That looks great.
[LT.] Looks like your
Commander's late coming back
from your mission again.
[ELEDORE] Yeah whatever
you gonna work on my truck?
[LT.] I'm busy.
‐What a lazy old coot!
Insults get you nowhere.
Wait a second! I think you guys
got some mail while you
were out on patrol.
Go over to HQ and get it.
But I was hoping for some stew!
I said go get it!
‐Oh alright.
And quit dragging your feet!
Damn!
[MICHEL] Ok I'm going.
Shit. What's so damn
funny you old geezer?
Well truth is I got this here
from a little cutie who's
going sweet on me.
Yeah right.
Her name is Maria and she lives
in a village to the
west of our base.
Right. And just how old and
shriveled up is this cutie
you horny old fart?
[MICHEL] Eledore! Hey I got
a letter for you!
For me?
[MICHEL] Here you go.
Is it bad news?
[CELEBRATORY YELLING]
Eledore what?
I have done it! I have
finally done it!
What is it? What did you do?
Hold on to your hat the song I
wrote is gonna get recorded &amp;
it's gonna skyrocket
all the way to number 1!
I guess congratulations
are in order!
You bet your ass on it. I earned
it let's go celebrate! Hey why
shouldn't we go out and
party it up? Who knows when the
Commander &amp; the rest of the
crew will get here.
Come on! Let's go!
[MICHEL] Wait a minute go where?
[ELEDORE] You just leave that to
me. I'll go alone if I have to!
But we were ordered to
stay here until...
[ELEDORE] What? Your boss' good
luck finally rubbed off on me &amp;
you could care less.
I do care but I'm kinda worried
about getting in trouble when
the Commander finds out
about it.
That's fine Michel just remember
when the money starts
rolling in don't come
trying to be my friend!
‐Money? Ha! How much are you
gonna
make off that song anyway?
[ELEDORE] What do you care?
[MICHEL] Wait up!
I wanna party along with you!
[CELEBRATORY YELLING]
[MICHEL] Are you sure it'll be
alright if we take off
with this thing?
[ELEDORE] Sure it's fine! We
needed it to complete an
important mission.
A recon mission.
‐A recon mission?
That's right so we have to
hurry! Tomorrow I'm gonna put in
my request for a discharge.
I'm not dying out here
with you guys!
[MICHEL] Don't say that!
[ELEDORE] I smell women!
Hello ladies we're looking fo‐
[MICHEL] Yeah! Huh?
[ELEDORE] This
doesn't look right.
I wonder what could've
happened here? Ah!
Eledore... ?
[MAN] Pressure is still low.
What's the delay?
[MAN 2] We can't fix it until
we know where the damage is!
[MAN] Alright then bring
that tank around this way!
What's that? You caught Feddie
soldiers?
[MAN] Yes sir.
‐We need to get out of here as
soon as we can.
‐Right. Push those repairs
through.
[NORRIS] And increase security.
[SHIRO] What's the situation?
Sir! Michel and Eledore have not
been seen on base since they
last reported in.
Where could they have gone?
[GARBLED SIGNALS]
Lt. Nickard! Say again I can't
get a clear signal on you. Over!
It's no use.
All I heard was village in
area whiskey 208.
Well we're not too far
from there now.
If they did go there
it's a violation of orders.
Later. First we have to figure
out where they are. Karen you
and I will go to the
village &amp; search the general
area.
[KAREN] Right.
Sanders I want you to stay
here. Await communication.
[SANDERS] Yes sir.
[ZEON] You there!
Where are you going?
[MOM] Please!
I'm begging you let us go!
[ZEON] You were told
no one is allowed to leave!
But my baby has a fever! The
only doctor we have is in
the next village!
Like I said no one is
allowed to leave!
[MOM] Please he has to see a
doctor! If anything
happens to him‐
[SOLDIER] That's enough!
[GUNFIRE]
Is that really necessary Norris?
Can't we do anything
to help her?
Not until the Apsalus is
working Ms. Aina.
We can't allow anyone to leave
until it's in the clear.
[NORRIS] We have rooms here.
What is it?
[AINA] What about the villagers?
[NORRIS] There's no reason for
any of 'em to come here. And
we'll be finished soon.
[PAINED YELLING]
[ELEDORE] No please! Stop!
What was that?
That's the Feddie soldiers.
They're being interrogated now.
I can't stand this war. I'll be
in the Apsalus if you need me.
Yes as you wish.
[ELEDORE] No!
[MAN] So are you ready now to
tell us what unit you're from?
Fine! Whatever we're from the
408th Federal Forces
infantry division.
I see. And tell me why
did you come to the village?
Well that's simple we‐‐
‐Eledore...
We want to defect and act as
double agents for the
glorious Zeon.
[MAN] Enough!
Were you serious back there?
About wanting to be a
double agent?
You idiot! If I hadn't
said that we'd already be...
[MICHEL] Oh I see.
Right you wouldn't do that.
Of course I wouldn't!
Um...
[ELEDORE] What?
I'm kinda hungry.
Huh? We have other things to
worry about like maybe finding
ourselves in front of a
firing squad in the morning!
Firing squad?
[MARIA] Surely they'll be
no harm it's just a little food.
[ZEON] But ma'am they're
being executed tomorrow.
[MARIA] Everyone who stays in
this hotel gets
treated the same.
[ZEON] OK Ms. Maria.
‐Maria?
[SOLDIER] Just please don't
tell my Commanders about this.
Alright Feddies we're coming in.
Maybe you can pay me back with
some wine next time?
We'll see. Now you
wait for me out here OK?
Oh dear. I wasn't aware you
needed medical attention.
But I did bring you
some good food. Here.
[MARIA] This will help. And
try to cheer up.
Here. As long as you don't lose
hope you will never lose
the will to live.
So my dear. May I ask
how old you are?
Please sir I'll ask you to
leave her alone.
Don't forget.
[ZEON] Please Ms. Maria.
I didn't mean any harm.
[MARIA] Come on dear let's go.
I am still waiting for you to
give me the key to my room.
I'm so sorry for the delay.
Your room is on the
second floor.
Thanks. Good night.
Good evening sir.
[ANIMALS CHIRPING]
[SHIRO] Is this it?
[KAREN] This is definitely
area whiskey 208.
[SHIRO] Doesn't look like
anything's wrong. Just a sleepy
village. Wait a minute.
What's that?
Heat. Steam. It's man‐shaped.
Zaku!
It's watching over the village.
I bet that's where Eledore
and Michel went.
Karen I've spotted a Zaku.
Come back to this position.
[KAREN] Yes sir. Wait
someone's coming!
[SHIRO] Zeon? [KAREN] I can't be
sure yet. Should I take him?
[SHIRO] Can you do it?
[KAREN] Consider it done.
I got ya!
I know you!
[COUGHING]
♪♪
[MICHEL] It's no use
‐Eledore. What are you doing?
There's no way you can get
out through there.
[ELEDORE] I'll find a way out
of here somehow. Goddamn it!
[SOBBING]
[ELEDORE] Just when I thought I
was gonna finally turn pro this
has to happen. They
were gonna press my song. It was
gonna be heard by everyone.
Poor Eledore.
[ELEDORE] I'm a musician. I'm
not cut out to be a soldier.
Even you can see that right?
I wanna go home! It's not
my time to die!
Well I don't like the idea
either you know.
Yeah but I wrote a love song
damn it that was really good!
“Love and Peace” I called it!
And now here I sit in a dark
cellar awaiting execution. I
finally got my big chance &amp; now
my dreams are falling apart.
Fading away. Slipping away...
[SOBBING]
Eledore you've got‐
‐Shit just leave me alone!
[MICHEL] But Ms. Maria told
us not to lose hope. Remember?
How can you stay so calm in this
situation? My career is over, my
heart is broken, and you
don't give a damn one way or
another for the
tragedy of it all!
Don't be so self‐centered! You
know this situation was your
fault in the first
place Eledore.
‐What are you talking about?
How dare you gimme that crap!
Well it's the truth isn't it? I
don't even get to write a letter
so I can say goodbye
to my BB one last time!
I warned you those long distance
love affairs never end happily.
But me! I was
gonna have a hit song and all my
dreams were coming
true goddamn it!
[CRASHING SOUNDS]
[MICHEL] That's dangerous! You
could hurt somebody are you
out of your mind?!
[ELEDORE] Shut up! I can't
take it anymore!
[MICHEL] Eledore please stop!
[ELEDORE] Shut up!
[MICHEL] All you ever worry
about is yourself! I'm in this
cell too!
And you got
me into this!
[ELEDORE] Look pal I never
forced you to come with me!
[MICHEL] See there you go again!
Not taking responsibility!
[ELEDORE] Hey!! I got
seniority on you!
[MICHEL] Well there's no
seniority in here. I don't care
what you say anymore.
All you ever do is whatever you
want to. And I'm supposed to
just follow along after you?
[ELEDORE] Shut up!
I didn't deserve that. I didn't
do anything what's the
matter with you?
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[MICHEL] That's playing dirty!
You're nothing but a big bully!
[ELEDORE] Who's the bully?! Eat
this you stupid
little son of a...
[MICHEL] Ow you did it again!
Bastard!
What the hell are you morons
up to?! What? Hey stop that!
I said stop it! Stop it now!
I hate you!
Come back here!
Hold on! Both of you
get away from each other!
[ARGUING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[HARD BREATHING]
The final repairs on the
Apsalus have been completed.
Good work. Now what?
Ms. Aina you should get
back to headquarters at once.
Right. Be careful
Norris. I'll see you there.
[APSALUS ACTIVATING]
Ah! Is that some kind of
new Zeek weapon?
What the hell?
‐A squall! No too big for‐ look
over there!
[SHIRO] It's that thing!
They must have had it here since
last night. We don't know what
their troop strength is
so we have to confuse 'em.
[KAREN] Roger.
[EXPLOSIONS]
Halt! The Feddies are
attacking. Take us back!
With our luck a stray
bullet will take us out.
Hey check it out! Over there!
[YELLING]
No way. I'm not touching it.
What are you saying?
I don't know how to
operate a stupid mobile suit!
[MICHEL] But it's just a
construction tank!
Sorry no can do. I'm not
touching those controls.
[GUNFIRE]
That does it!
Now I'm really pissed.
[MICHEL] Hurry up! Come on get
in there!
[ELEDORE] I can't! Stop it!
[MICHEL] Do you see any
other way to save ourselves?
Lemme think!
[MAN] You there! What are you
doing? Shit they're
Feddie soldiers.
Eledore! Hurry! Hurry
up and get in!
[ELEDORE] No! No way!
Eledore! We've got to
get out of here.
[MICHEL] Now is this the hatch?
[ELEDORE] Don't shut it!
Close the hatch!
I said no! I need to see out I
can't work the sensors. Ah!
[MICHEL] Do it! Get us
out of here fast!
[MAN] Take us around!
We're sitting ducks.
You've gotta shut the hatch now!
You shut that hatch and
I'll kill ya!
Then let me drive this thing!
Right if I let you do that
then you'll close the hatch!
[GUNFIRE]
♪♪
[MICHEL] Oh my God! Eledore.
Are you OK?
We're leaving.
[MICHEL] Eledore! No! Eledore!
Looks like they're pulling out
of the village. Let's hammer the
ones that are left!
[KAREN] Roger!
Eledore you have to let me
drive. This isn't going to work!
You'll just get us killed.
Will you shut up for once?!
We're getting out of here alive
because I wanna hear my song!
You hear that?!
[SCREAMS]
Alright! You did it! You took
out that armored car Eledore!
I told ya. I gotta
hear that song!
[MICHEL] Eledore!
Eledore speak to me. Eledore!!
[ELEDORE] Ah whaddya think? My
legs hurt, my arms hurt, my
whole goddamn body hurts!
I'm a musician don't cut my arms
off whatever you do
please don't!
[KAREN] Shut up! Recon mission
my ass. You do whatever you want
whenever you want to.
Michel hold it.
‐Right.
Hey! Wait a minute you're
forgetting something! What
about the anesthesia
for the pain?
[KAREN] Fine!
Right. So we'll be sending Petty
Officer Eledore to the
rear line then.
Right thanks over and out sir.
That boy's lucky he's
still alive.
Yeah. And I never realized Karen
used to be a medical student.
Did you know that?
Her husband was a fine surgeon
before he was killed in battle.
[MARIA] Excuse me Lieutenant?
I'm afraid we're out of
disinfectant.
Oh right! I'll go and get
you some right away.
Oh that's alright. We can just
use this for the time being.
Oh. OK!
Ms. Maria? I'd just like
to thank you for everything.
No problem at all I've gotten
quite used to helping out
people in need.
I'm just glad I could be
of some assistance to you.
There now. You better take
that over to Karen. Go on!
She is a special lady.
[LT.] She's the most
wonderful woman in the world.
I'll just make this one point:
In the 08th team we act as a
team. Always got it?
If we all go off and do whatever
we want all of us
will end up dead.
[MICHEL] You're right.
I'm really sorry about this sir.
But I'm glad you made it back in
one piece. Why don't you
take the day off?
Yes sir.
[CHOKES UP]
[SHIRO] Karen. It's me
I'm coming in.
How is he?
Well Commander all we need to do
is wait for his fever to drop.
You did good work today.
Take care of him OK?
[KAREN] Yes sir.
Don't! Don't cut off my hand.
Need the fingers to
play my song.
You jerk. All you want
is to be a musician huh?
I don't wanna die.
You're safe now. You're
not gonna die.
[ELEDORE] My arm!
Relax! You'll find it's still
connected. Both of them are.
What're you doing?!
Goddess for sure.
[SHIRO] Don't worry Eledore.
You'll be fine.
Now you behave yourself in the
hospital with all
those nurses OK?
Hey nurses sound good!
That's exactly what I was
worried about.
By the way pal you're
only alive because of Karen.
Shall I give your
regards to Karen?
Why would a cold‐blooded woman
like her care? Alright it's
time to go Commander.
Right. OK then Lt. Nickard
the patient is all yours.
I'll take care of him.
Here we go!
[ELEDORE] See you guys!
Eledore! You get well soon
and hurry back OK?
♪♪
[ENDING THEME]
[SHIRO] The 08th team arrives in
the perfect spot to ambush the
new Zeon monster. We hold
our position day after day
watching our trap and all we can
do is wait. But the harsh
environment and the endless
waiting is putting us all on
edge. Snap out of it guys!
We need teamwork for this
plan to succeed.
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
The 08th MS Team ‐ Battle Line
on the Burning Sand.