GUNDAM 08TH MS TEAM
[OPENING THEME]
[MAN] Yeah I saw it myself. A
star dropped from the sky and
lit up the whole desert.
[KIKI] Uh‐huh. So where and
when did you see this star?
I saw it 3 days ago. In a desert
somewhere toward the west.
Thanks. Shiro we've got a
witness!
[MAN] Oh my god!
[SHIRO] Michel! I want you to
contact headquarters and every
team in the area.
Hey! Did you hear me? Michel!
Yes sir. What is it?
[SHIRO] Contact headquarters!
[MICHEL] Yes sir stand by.
OK go ahead.
[SHIRO] The 8th team has
possibly discovered the location
of the Zeon weapons
testing ground. We're
moving in to confirm. Copy?
[MICHEL] Roger!
BATTLE LINE ON THE BURNING SAND
Ah! Great time to break down.
Listen up guys! My left foot is
screwing up again.
Go on ahead of me.
[KAREN] Will you be okay
by yourself?
[SHIRO] Yeah Michel and I can
manage.
[KAREN] Roger!
[SANDERS] I don't read
any radiation.
[KAREN] Good!
[KAREN WHISTLING]
[MICHEL] One two pull.
One two pull.
[MICHEL] One two pull. Ah!
Tell me what you see down there!
Right right I'm getting to it.
Ow!
[BREAKING SOUND]
It's glass... it must have been
melted by some sort
of beam weapon.
[GASP]
Commander! This packet is in
bad condition.
The filter seems to be clogged
with a lot of sand.
[MICHEL] Can you get me an M18
filter please?
Yeah I'll bring
you one in just a minute.
[KAREN] Angle of fire indicates
it came from low altitude.
[SHIRO] I'm sure this has to
be some kind of testing ground.
[KAREN] I Agree!
[KIKI] See I knew my
informants were right.
Sure looks that way.
Well you called this one Kiki.
I appreciate your help.
‐Well of course you do.
‐[SHIRO] You better stay here.
What?!
[SHIRO] Michel and I can handle
it. You have a safe
journey home!
‐Well you heard what he said.
‐Shall we go?
Who said I was going anywhere?
[SHIRO] Michel get
inside the cockpit alright?
[MICHEL] Yes sir.
[SHIRO] Beam weapon. A high
energy beam weapon at that.
The monster.
They must've tested it here.
[SHIRO] Alright! Michel you
ready? Move the leg a little
bit. But just a little OK?
Um right!
Michel!! Stop it!
Shiro!
Shit!
[KIKI] What're you doing?!
Are you trying to kill
Shiro or something?
Well I was... oh...
[MICHEL] Commander! Are you
alright?!
[SHIRO] I'm still alive. But
just barely.
Hey! Keep your mind on
what you're doing.
[MICHEL] I feel so far away BB.
Hey Michel! You can
start erasing my tracks now.
[MICHEL] Alright I'm
doing it now.
[KAREN] Michel while you're at
it wipe out my footprints too.
Roger! I'm on it!
[KAREN] Michel run a
point check on the balloons.
Michel cut the wireless. Switch
everything over to
wired systems!
Yes Commander! Michel, Michel,
Michel... I'm only one person. I
can't do it all at once.
They treat me like I'm a kid.
Like I'm an idiot!
[MICHEL] Come on pull yourself
together Michel. You're
on a mission.
[KAREN] And don't make excuses
because Eledore isn't here.
That's not what I'm doing.
Just wait.
I haven't even finished
making preparations for
the trap construction yet.
‐[SHIRO] Michel!
‐Alright. OK OK OK!
Go back to the camp and
let them know where we are!
Well... but...
What? You want us to ride off
and leave you with the Feddies?
The Feds are only here because
of the information I provided.
I'm gonna see this
through to the end.
The Commander must mean an awful
lot to you if you're willing to
risk your life to help 'em out.
[MAN] Hold on! Stop!
Go on! Get out of
here you jerks! Ugh!
The drone is now proceeding
down the ravine.
It's heading into the testing
site and should arrive at point
delta on schedule.
[SHIRO] Initiate Minovsky
particle broadcast. You
ready Michel?
[MICHEL] Yes sir! Passing
point alpha now.
[SHIRO] Karen raise
the balloons!
[KAREN] Balloons raised.
Retreat path is closed!
Simulation is confirmed.
[SHIRO] Sanders be ready
to pick it off.
[SANDERS] Locked on!
I'm verifying simulation.
Passing point bravo sir.
[SHIRO] Now! Release the net
to the blind alley!
[KAREN] Net released.
[MICHEL] Confirmed!
Passing point charlie. Oh...
Alright! Now concentrate
all fire straight ahead
on the area right in
front of point delta!
[SHIRO] This time we're
gonna get you.
[SOUND OF IMPACT]
What the hell happened?
[KAREN] Michel would you wake
the hell up?! ‐I was!
[KAREN] You have to stay twice
as alert now that
Eledore isn't there!
But it wasn't... no...
it really was my fault. God!
Hey Commander! I've brought some
food and water and stuff for ya!
What? Still here?
Now what does that mean? And
after I bring all this stuff
out here for you!
If a battle breaks out...
thanks... I'll have no way of
guaranteeing your safety.
Did you hear what I said?
Your shirt has a rip. You
know I can fix that.
Oh. Never mind.
[KIKI] Come on take it off &amp; let
me have a look.
[SHIRO] I said never mind.
[KIKI] What in the world
are you being so shy about?
[SHIRO] Hey watch it!
Cut it out!
[KIKI] Why are you giving me
such a hard time? Come on
just take it off!
[SHIRO] Oh alright fine.
But just this once!
Ugh! Damn it. What
are they doing?
[MICHEL] Hey Karen.
Do you read me?
What's wrong?
[MICHEL] Nothing. Nevermind.
What are you doing?
Water is precious here.
I'm collecting some for later.
Hmm...
[SHIRO] It's barely been a half
an hour since the last
time I looked.
[KIKI] Shiro! Shiro!
What's wrong? What is it?!
Can I come over for a little
visit? Your shirt's all fixed!
[SHIRO] What do I need a shirt
for in this heat?
[KIKI] You don't. But it'll
get cold tonight!
Michel is there any
word from the other units?
Nothing sir! Nothing yet.
[SHIRO] Then don't tie up
our comm system!
Oh brother. Just because he's in
command he gets all tough.
Stubborn fool.
Kiki. Tell me. You have a big
crush on the Commander
don't you?
Is this a letter from
your girlfriend?
What're you doing? Give it back!
Hey!
[KIKI] Dear Michel!
Thank you for all your letters.
[MICHEL] Stop that! Come
on give it back!
[KIKI] The letters you send to
me are the one &amp; only
comfort I have.
All I can do is wait for your
letters while I wait for you.
Boy this is really good!
But I'm always afraid because I
always end up wondering
if this is going to be your
last letter to me.
I feel as though the war is
pulling you further
away from me.
[KIKI] And I'm afraid that one
day the letters will
stop coming.
I don't think I'd be
able to take that.
Sometimes I wonder if it would
be easier for us to forget
about each other for a while.
I think I'm
done reading. Sorry.
Don't be.
I'm... I'm going to make it back
alive. Kiki, my feelings for her
are just so strong.
I tried to tell her that
distance doesn't make a
difference.
So tell me
why doesn't she understand that.
[KIKI] You know Michel I'm
sure she already does.
[MICHEL] You think so?
These feelings you have. All you
can do is keep sending them
to her. Believe me.
I know how it feels.
Yeah. Maybe you're right. But
I'm too far away to get those
feelings through to her.
[KIKI] Yeah but you know
sometimes you can feel
too far away even when you're
right next to them
Maybe it'll come tomorrow.
It'll come.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Beans never seem to go down very
smoothly if you ask me. Hey! Let
me take care of that.
Did you like it? I
cooked it myself.
It was pretty good. I mean for
a plate of beans.
Commander? How long
until it comes?
Well. I wish I knew.
We've been waiting 5 days now. I
thought you said this would
only take 3 days at the most.
[SHIRO] I know it's frustrating
buddy. Believe me I know.
What I wouldn't give to take a
nice long shower and
drink a cold beer.
And this heat is
driving me nuts!
I just... I just...
I can't take
another day of this!
As long as I'm stuck here I
can't mail my letter!
And I have to mail it.
BB is waiting for me. I don't
want her to forget me!
And I don't want to forget about
her! Damn it! Damn it!
Michel wha‐
We all have our problems. The
ones we keep private are the
ones that hurt the most.
[SHIRO] What does that mean?
[KIKI] Don't worry Michel. I can
take your letter back for
you if you want.
This is about a letter?
I'll deliver it for you Michel.
I just have to get it to your
headquarters right?
My people will help. They have
too much free time on
their hands anyway.
‐[MICHEL] Really?
‐[SHIRO] Just a minute.
[KIKI] Now what's wrong?
It's time you two stopped
treating this mission like
it was a picnic.
[SHIRO] We don't do things
because we feel like it. We do
as we're ordered!
For your information my people
do things because we feel
they're important.
[KIKI] I'm free to do what I
want you're not my leader.
I appreciate all the help you've
given us. But stop butting
into our business.
Butting in? So that's
how it is is it?
[KIKI] Did you give an order
saying he can't mail the letter?
Let go!
You always hang on too tight!
What's with her? She's
practically hysterical. Oh.
The one who's hysterical
would be you Shiro.
Idiot.
‐Kiki!
‐[KIKI] No!
Commander! Why can't you be
halfway nice to her after all
she's done for you? Don't you
understand? Don't you realize
that girl has feelings like
the rest of us?
Don't you care? Haven't you ever
loved someone?
That's why you keep that girl's
watch Isn't it? Isn't it?!
Michel!
Is unrequited love the only kind
that means anything to you?
I don't think that's your
concern!
You think you can
understand everyone's feelings.
What the hell do you
know anyway?
I understand better than you do!
I care! And when you care you'll
find it's even harder to tell
someone how you really feel.
Not you though. No
you're a disgrace!
That's enough. That's
more than enough.
At least we'd be able
to complete the mission.
You're right. It's the best way.
I'll head back.
‐Michel I want you to pilot my
mobile suit.
‐What?
‐Switch positions with me.
‐I couldn't.
If we leave you in charge of the
truck in your state of mind our
team will end up dead.
What am I doing?
I don't act this way. It's
almost like I don't even know
what I'm really feeling.
It's nice and cold. It'll
keep you awake.
But I thought you said
water was precious?
[SANDERS] We can
always get more.
Well thank you. So
what are you up to?
[SANDERS] Talking isn't
my strong point.
What makes me keep this
thing anyway?
Aina Sahalin. Does she have a
boyfriend? I wouldn't be
surprised if she does.
Damn it. Michel sure does
have me figured out.
[SANDERS] Commander. That song
on the radio. That's
Eledore's song!
[SHIRO] That's Eledore's song?
[POP MUSIC]
It has a beautiful melody.
It's good.
What's the matter with me?
Stupid.
[DJ] That song came to you by
request from someone who's
mending up in a field hospital.
Petty Officer Eledore
Massis who was honorably
wounded in action.
You've got to be kidding. You
mean Eledore requested
his own song?
That idiot.
[LAUGHING] That's so
like Eledore!
He is completely honest with
himself though. He
lives his life.
[BEEPING]
Minovsky particle
broadcast initiated!
Everyone! It's here get ready!
‐[SHIRO] Karen!
‐[KAREN] Point Charlie sighted
and locked!
‐Michel. Aim well.
‐[MICHEL] Yes sir.
Raise output on beam weaponry.
‐[MICHEL] Commander?
‐Yes what is it?
I apologize for yesterday.
I shouldn't have said anything.
‐Don't worry. No big deal.
‐[MICHEL] Right.
[SANDERS] Here it comes.
I'm not going to die. BB all I
can do is keep sending my love
and feelings to you.
Wait for me. And believe in me!
[SANDERS] Stand by...
ready... release balloons!
[MICHEL] Locked on!
Those mobile suits have beam
weaponry! Escort
units do you read?
[BEAM WEAPON DISCHARGING]
[MICHEL SCREAMING]
[SHIRO] Michel!
[GUNFIRE]
[SANDERS] Commander!
2 fighters coming in high!
[GUNFIRE]
[MICHEL] Locked on. Huh?
[WEAPON CHARGING]
Michel!
[MICHEL SCREAMS]
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
[SHIRO] Go down damn it!
Let go you fool you're going
to kill both of us!
That voice... it's you!
[MICHEL] Damn it! Damn it!
[MICHEL] Commander!
Ah shit I lost it!
Oh no. Please Shiro no.
He was still on that thing.
[KIKI] SHIRO!!!
[ENDING THEME]
[SHIRO] I can't believe Aina is
the pilot of that new Zeon
weapon. In the heat of battle
I nearly ended up killing her.
But as soon as we each figure
out who the other is we find
ourselves in a race towards a
huge mountain range. We have
to find some way to
survive. Aina live or die
we're going to do this together!
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
The 08th MS Team – Reunion.