GUNDAM 08TH MS TEAM
[OPENING THEME]
Finished at last! Apsalus!
My son!
What happened to your research
staff? Why aren't they here?
They're all off probably
getting drunk somewhere.
We have to get going. Better
put on a normal suit.
THE SHUDDERING
MOUNTAIN – PART TWO
They've launched it! Damn!
[YELLING]
[ELEDORE] They're not
pulling any punches!
Oh yes they are! That beam
could've cooked us, no problem!
Oh let's get out of here!
Is that how it's going to
be Aina? More war?
It won't end here, will it?
Everyone listen up: I'm
leaving the service.
What?!
Commander!
Desertion in the face of the
enemy? They're going
to shoot you!
I don't intend to desert. I
intend to stop her!
Mr. Pure Love. I knew
he'd do this.
If he deserts, execute him.
[SHIRO] Karen take up command &amp;
link up with the main force.
That's my final order.
[SANDERS] Huh? A weapons lock?
It's from Karen?
[CPT.] You want to clear your
Commander of these spy charges,
don't you?
Looks like they got to Karen,
too.
Will you please
reconsider your actions, sir?
[CPT.] I would prefer it if I
didn't have to execute
your entire team.
I have to say I'm sorry for
leaving you. And for
getting you involved.
That's fine for you, but
what about us?!
No! Don't do it Karen!
[GUNFIRE]
No! Please! No!!
[MOBILE SUIT SOUNDS]
Every man I know is
exactly the same.
They always end up
leaving me in the end.
Shiro Amada...
I've met some bad soldiers in my
life, but you're the
worst by far.
OK fine. Hey Michel! What now?
Uh, I don't know.
[FED] Scramble jet
core boosters!
[FED] Mobile suit forces!
Damage report!
It's going to attack. All units
open fire!
[AINA] Attention Federal Forces
units!
This is Aina Sahalin speaking.
I am the pilot of this mobile
armor. I am requesting a
temporary truce.
Are you insane? Shoot their
control center and end this
ridiculous standoff!
That would still leave the
Feddies with air superiority.
We must take into account the
number of fighters they have.
The Kergeren won't
make it otherwise.
Then do whatever you wish.
That attack just now was
only a warning.
[GM] Hey! You alright?
[GM 2] I think so...
[AINA] And as long as
that burning line
isn't crossed, no further
attacks will be made.
[TECH] We've got video back!
[TECH 2] No damage from the
previous attacks, sir!
What in the devil is going on?
What are they up to?
I knew it had to be Aina!
[SHIRO] This is how
she operates.
[AINA] The sick and injured will
now be evacuated from our base.
So I beg of you: For the moment
at least please agree
to a ceasefire!
[KAREN] Ugh for crying out loud!
I can see why the
Commander likes her.
She's as naïve as he is.
But war is never that simple.
Your request is denied.
[GASP]
[LAUGHTER]
Surely you understand.
A truce at gunpoint is
no truce at all.
[CPT.] Our forces will not
be intimidated!
If what you need is proof
then so be it.
[MAN] 98... 97...
Eh?
Are you insane?
You just watch! We can win!
If we can play it my way.
Alright cease fire.
It's a truce. We thank you.
Deploy the GM Snipers.
But sir, you just‐
I don't recall agreeing
to any indefinite ceasefires.
Yes sir.
[PILOT] We're heading for
the rendezvous.
Good luck!
[RUMBLING]
[MAN] 2... 1... ignition!
[TAKEOFF]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
No don't!
Ginias!
[EXPLOSIONS]
They've drawn first blood.
Get me a lock on that
thing's cockpit!
Sniper 2 is still moving
into position, sir.
Blast that hospital ship
out of the sky!
We're no better than they are.
Hook up that coolant
pipe immediately!
[SNIPER] Long beam
rifle standing by!
[TECH] Coolant system ready!
[BEAM FIRING]
[TECH] Keep that
coolant pumping!
[EXPLOSION]
[LAUGHTER]
The peaceful Federal
Forces turned out
to be quite warlike in the
end didn't they?
They were reacting to what you‐
Take a look around Aina!
Take a good look around!
Finish it.
Have a look at everything
you've sacrificed
in the name of peace.
[TARGETING NOISE]
You wanted a fight,
well here it is!!
Shiro?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[EXPLOSION]
She fired her main weapon!
[KAREN] Incoming shockwave!
Sanders protect the hover truck!
[SANDERS] Roger!
[SANDERS] Eledore! Michel!
Whoa boy! This armor
is getting hot!
Hey if our ammo gets
cooked we'll‐
Would you just shut
up and pray?!
Oh heavenly father... and BB!
I didn't mean really pray! Ah!!
Oh Lord just get us the
hell outta here!!
[SANDERS] Did we make it?
[KAREN] Is everyone alright?
[SANDERS] What about the base?
What happened?
What sort of game are you
playing with them Aina?
No game.
But I want us to show them
that we can draw the
line somewhere.
She shot right over us.
She asked for it.
Is that sniper in position yet?
[SNIPER] Give me 7 more minutes.
Maybe 5.
You would spare them after
they've shown how vicious
they could be?
Yes. Because even if I were to
take revenge for what they did
it would never bring
the dead back to life.
We seem to speak different
languages these days my
dear sibling.
For a long time now
I've had my doubts about
your dream. But...
That's ridiculous! Love is
just an illusion.
A weakness of the glands!
Like mother!
It was love that caused
her to leave us!
I truly pity you Ginias.
Is that why you've
done all this?
Is that why you've built this
iron womb around yourself?
[SNIPER] In position. Capacitor
charge in one minute.
What do you know? You
don't know anything!
This is a war damn it!
No Ginias. This is a
personal matter.
Damn you!
We can surrender together! We
can rid ourselves of this
burden we've carried.
[GUNSHOT]
Aina! Aina no! Aina!
Say something!
Hold on Aina! Don't die!
This is all your fault!
It was your fault that Aina
threw her life away in the end!
Time to wake up.
Stop it Aina. Don't do this.
You wanted to be with him.
Now you can be with
him in death.
You killed your own sister!
I swear... I'll make
you pay for this!
That's doubtful.
But it would be interesting if
you came back to haunt me. I've
always wanted to see a ghost.
[GINIAS] I do hope you can
forgive me Aina.
Please know that I
never hated you.
Get away Shiro...
[LASER FIRING]
[GROANING]
Aina!
[LASER FIRING]
[EXPLOSION]
Got him!
[CRASHING]
[SOLDIER] Did they get it?
[SOLDIER 2] All units!
Damage report!
[KAREN] Our main forces
survived! Talk about
your dumb luck.
08th team reporting
back to base sir.
Very good Karen.
Unit 81 has captured the enemy
pilot. You are to find them &amp;
escort them back.
Correction: Whatever the reason,
Ensign Amada
deserted in the face
of the enemy. You will carry out
his execution as ordered.
[KOJIMA] Execution?!
Do you believe he saved that
pilot because he intends to
surrender her to us?
I've already given an order
for his execution.
I was never informed
about this plan!
Why this is nothing
but a lynching!
Rob, Sally, Michael... we've
lost so many. They were all
excellent soldiers.
Just one more won't
make a difference.
Wrong sir! Quite the contrary!
Karen assemble your
team and head out.
We're running a different
mission as of now!
[KAREN] Sir!
[KOJIMA] When you opened fire &amp;
destroyed that hospital ship
you crossed a very
important line.
There are rules to be followed,
even in war.
At least that's what
I believe...
[CPT.] I hope you're comfortable
at your desk in Jabrow...
That's fine by me, because I
always hated air
conditioning anyway.
Your new orders are to stop that
mobile armor once &amp; for all
and to take Shiro into custody!
[AINA] Shiro! Shiro!
Hello there. Ah!
I'm glad... I'm glad
you're here...
[SOBBING]
Shiro!
We're together.
We found each other
one more time.
How can you be alive?
How did you survive that bullet?
[BEEPING]
[BEEPING SLOWS]
It seems this watch my
brother gave me
has finally brought us back
together again.
But he is a brilliant
engineer and I know
he won't let it end like this.
The Apsalus has plenty of
life left in it.
Let's go.
[SHIRO] We have to end this
with our own hands.
It's time we faced your
brother together.
Right!
[AINA] You've gotten stronger,
Shiro.
Commander I think what you did
back there was cool!
Shut up and keep driving.
We have to get there before
that sniper does.
Or Ensign Amada's a dead man.
And then I'll be looking forward
to that little idiot's
court‐martial.
[KOJIMA] Now move it!
Right!
[SHIRO] Manipulate the controls
for the right arm, OK?
Got it.
[AINA] Let's get to the beam
generator &amp; disable it.
Good idea.
[SHIRO] I'll take us around to
the beam cannon barrel.
[FED] The EZ‐8 is on the
move again, sir!
Sniper 2 report.
[SNIPER 2] Confirmed.
[CAPTAIN] Fire!
[SNIPER 2] Roger!
If only I had time to
make repairs. Huh!?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[BEAM FIRING]
Well Aina you've
managed to survive!
You'll be out of your
misery soon!
[GINIAS] That's for
crushing my dream
of destroying Jabrow with
the Apsalus. Now...
[GINIAS] It's time for you two!
[AINA] He's preparing a
full power blast
To wipe all of us out
in one shot!
I'm sorry.
But now I have to kill him.
We've both suffered so much
and now we can't let him
hurt anybody else!
Farewell Ginias! I loved you!
We have to keep it from
firing its main weapon!
Now do you see the vision?
This is what I wanted!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[MAN] Evacuate!
All personnel
evacuate immediately!
There's no time for that.
[EXPLOSION]
[BEAM FIRING]
Ah...
[EXPLOSION]
A double suicide!
No way! That isn't
true is it Chief?
[MICHEL] The Commander's
not dead is he?
Of course not.
Right! Of course not.
Buck up! Time to go.
Eledore...
Don't really know why you opened
fire on him, but I'm sure
newbie forgives ya.
Are you sure of that?
Well as sure as sure can get.
We're all friends aren't we?
Come on let's go!
Hey newbie! Come out of
hiding already!
Commander!!
Sir can you hear us?
Are you alright?
Commander! Where are you?!
[08TH MS TEAM YELLING FOR SHIRO]
[SHIRO] Not long afterward
the war finally ended...
[ENDING THEME]
[MICHEL] PS: In the end BB,
we never did find the Commander.
But I believe he's still alive!
All my love... Michel.
[AINA] You're heavy.
[SHIRO] I'm sorry. But we can
share the burden.
Together.
[AINA] Right.
[FOOTSTEPS]