GUNDAM 08TH MS TEAM
[OPENING THEME]
[MOBILE SUIT SOUNDS]
[GUNFIRE]
THE TIME LIMIT ON TRUST
Guess all that combat
training is paying off.
Joshua!
What the hell?!
[SHIRO] You OK Chief?
Yeah thanks to you. But I've
never had support fire
come that close.
Well at least now you've
seen what I can do.
[SANDERS] Where did that
come from Eledore?
[ELEDORE] Pill box! Top of the
hill!
[SANDERS] But why is it so
accurate?
Ah shit! Now they're shooting at
us! The Zekes sure have damn
good ears over there!
[MICHEL] Yeah.
[KAREN] Commander!
The enemy fire is thinning out.
[SANDERS] All units! It looks
like they're moved
in to trap us.
Shit. They're all around us.
[SHIRO] Team scatter and fall
back. We'll have to
change our strategy.
[ELEDORE] Moving out!
[SHIRO] OK they've got 3 pill
boxes out front, a trench
covered by Zakus,
and some nasty hill terrain for
good measure. That's
the highway huh?
Yes. It's the most vital route
they have for getting
supplies to their forces
waiting on the front lines.
[SHIRO] I bet the Federal Forces
could use it too. We could
probably take it
but that village
presents a problem.
[KAREN] Right! We can't let
the Zeeks continue to occupy it.
[SHIRO] How to attack pill boxes
that use the natural terrain so
well? Wish we could
call in some support for this...
But they'll hunt us down
if we wait for backup to arrive.
Yeah you're right. If only
we could... what's this?
[KAREN] A waterfall.
[SHIRO] If one of us follow the
river around these hills
we could hit them
with a sneak attack.
[KAREN] Much easier said than
done.
That area is crawling
with guerrillas.
Guerrillas?
So how do we run this sneak
attack? ‐I've seen the falls
once already so I'll go.
You have sir?
[SANDERS] You'll run the sneak
attack?
The Commander's got the least
experience of all of us
which means he's
the most expendable right?
Joshua I'm turning over
command of the team to you.
[KAREN] But sir...
No “buts” that's an order.
[KAREN] Yes sir. Right.
Very good. So we'll do it in,
well let's say 3 hours. I want
the team to start its frontal
assault at that time. I can
definitely be there by then to
start the sneak attack.
Right. But be aware that without
you we can only hold out an hour
or so against that
kind of heavy fire.
I know that. Chief take the team
through the viaduct beneath the
highway and wait there
until 1500 hours. At that time
hit the Zeeks with all you got.
That is all.
Try not to get caught by
the guerrillas.
[MICHEL] Well I thought the
guerrillas were just civilians.
You kidding? Those civilians are
the ones you gotta
watch out for.
[KAREN] Men! Get ready to move
out.
‐Yeah yeah.
Watch yourself Commander.
[MOBILE SUIT SOUNDS]
Welcome back.
Of course nobody's even here.
[BANGING]
[YELLING]
Hey what's going on here?
Leaving the front line Mr.
Ensign?
[MAN] Looks like the little
pervert didn't learn his lesson
from the last time.
[MAN 2] Who would? Lucky
bastard.
[LAUGHTER]
You want on the water slide?
You gotta pay admission.
Thought you were gonna get
another peep show now didn't ya?
Hell we've never even seen that!
[SHIRO] Cut it out it
was an accident!
[MAN] Hold him down I'll
get his stuff.
Mighty fancy equipment!
Wait you don't know how to
work that thing.
Just watch me.
Hey hey wait! Wait what're you
doing? Wait! Stop! Wait make it
stop help me! Make it stop!
[MAN] Make it stop!
Stop don't fool with that
suit get away from there!
[MAN] You can't tell us what to
do!
[LAUGHTER]
[GUNFIRE]
Be honest you wanted to have
me now didn't ya?
What, I mean?
I swear you military men are
always the same. Rude with
dirty little minds.
You've gotta hell of a lot of
nerve. And who are you to judge
me? What would you know?
What do you mean?
You're a kid what could you
know? [SLAP SOUND]
[MAN] Bastard.
Well then if I'm a kid why
were you watching?
Well... well 'cuz you're
nice to look at.
Now that we're clear whaddya
say? Will you let me go?
[THUD] [LAUGHTER]
[MICHEL] Dear BB: There's been a
break in the combat yet I can
feel the tension building
inside all of us. Now as I ready
myself for battle Eledore is
tracking the enemy's
movements. He studies the sonar
panel listening, his
concentration
so intense that...
[ELEDORE YAWNS]
What idiot made this song a
number one hit?
ANOTHER LOVE LETTER?
Don't you ever work?
[MICHEL] Hey I'm ready for
action! I was just writing‐
I told you not to overdo it or
she'll dump your ass!
[KAREN] Eledore!
‐Yeah?
It's time.
[ELEDORE] Roger.
Come on! I said I was sorry!
Shut up you little shit!
How many times do I have to tell
you I have no time to waste
with you people?!
Believe it or not we're
busy too pal.
[SHIRO] Damn it! I don't have
time for this where are
you taking me?
And quit poking me with that!
[MAN] You're about to meet
someone so you better be polite.
[THUD]
[MAN] Well introduce yourself.
The boss I presume?
What brings you to our part of
the world Ensign Shiro Amada?
Look I'm sorry I came without
permission but right now I'm on
a mission that just can't wait!
And?
You can't possibly have any
reason to keep me! I beg of
you please let me go.
Did you hear what I said?
Oh my God. Please
you have to let me go!
Please excuse me we do
this every day at this time.
Damn it! You've gotta
listen to me!
[CLOCK STRIKING]
Let's move! Well Eledore?
[ELEDORE] Pretty quiet up here
Chief. Must be teatime
for our friends.
Say Chief do you suppose
the Commander made it through?
[KAREN] His confidence
convinced me. Let's move out!
[SANDERS] Right.
[ROCKET FIRE]
Just listen. Try to understand.
The Zeon are your enemies
as well as the
Federation's right? If we can
take out the gun
emplacements in that occupied
village doesn't that help you
guys too? My friends are waiting
for me and they need
me to pull this plan off!
If we liberate that village from
the Zeon your friends and family
who live there will
be free of them. Please!
Let me go!
[ARTILLERY FIRE]
That's it! Hit 'em with
everything you've got!
Hope he's there.
[MAN] Might as well give up
soldier boy! [LAUGHTER]
[MAN] Hey! You think you can try
something like that in
front of our boss!?
[SHIRO] My team is my first
concern! If you don't let me go
they'll die before I even get
the chance to know any of
'em. Damn it let me go!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[MAN] Rude little fart ain't he?
[MAN 2] You can say that again!
[MAN 3] Fart head. Hehehe!
Daddy what if... what if we use
him to take back the village
from those Zeon bastards?
All of us have friends and
family living in that village.
If his plan works they won't
have to work for the
Zeon anymore.
Yes that is true.
Yes! I promise! We're
going to free them!
What do you think dad?
You know there are many sick and
injured people in the village.
You need medicine we'll get it
for you no problem!
On top of that we want the
Zeon to suffer.
Oh we'll make 'em suffer! And
you can have all the war spoils!
[MAN] Talk's cheap kid!
Still the word of a captured
soldier isn't very reliable.
Is it Kiki?
I think it'll be alright daddy.
Besides he owes me one.
He sure does!
[MAN] A little one.
[LAUGHTER]
Very funny you guys are a real
crackup. I'll watch 'em dad. Let
me keep an eye on him. OK?
As if you'd listen to me if I
said no. Ensign for the time
being we will have a truce.
Close call for you pal.
And you better be
thanking the girl!
Kiki I want you to show the
Ensign the way back to
the waterfall.
[SHIRO] Oh this is great!
There's dirt all over the
controls!
Damn it I don't have time to
clean up all this crap! Ow!
Why'd they beat me up anyway?
It's not like I was
putting up a fight.
Hey are you coming or not?! Get
in! We're running out of time!
Shit.
[KIKI] Any funny business
and I'll plug ya.
Why would I try
anything with a kid?
I bet I'm smarter than you.
[SHIRO] What?
What is wrong with you?!
Hey that's not yours!
I took it fair and square!
You can't have it! This is on
loan from a friend. 3:30?! I
only have a half an hour left!
That thing doesn't really
suit you anyway!
Now listen...
It's Kiki!
[SHIRO] Kiki?
[KIKI] Kiki Rosita. That's my
name. Who gave ya the
watch Shiro?
Shiro? What the? Oh kids should
show more respect! And you're
blocking my view!
Come on hang in there guys. Kiki
do you know of any shortcuts?
Following the river
is the fastest.
Alright.
But there's no path!
Eledore any activity
on the hill?
[ELEDORE] Still nothing.
Come on Commander.
How long is he gonna take?!
If they notice us it's all over.
Yeah I know.
[ROCKET FIRE]
He's late! Any sign yet Eledore?
[ELEDORE] Nothing I can confirm.
Uh oh. We got company.
[MICHEL] What is it? What's
wrong?
[ELEDORE] Quiet!
[KAREN] Is it the Commander? No.
There's 2. Flying.
Headed this way.
Just great! All units prepare
for an airborne attack!
[SANDERS] Roger!
We're having bad luck.
Must be The Reaper's fault.
[MICHEL] The Reaper?
[ELEDORE] You'll find out.
Captain Norris. Our units on the
ground can easily take care of
these foolhardy rats
who've crawled out of hiding.
We can't afford any
more mistakes.
You mean because they beat us
before? Perhaps the Commandant
was premature in sending you to
inspect us Captain.
[PILOT] And how is Commandant
Ginias? I've heard his sister
Aina has grown into
a lovely young woman. Eh!
Nevermind.
Well hell this what I get for
trusting that gung‐ho Commander.
Sanders! We're done here.
Fall back under that viaduct.
[SANDERS] But...
We have no choice!
[MICHEL] Chief!
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSIONS]
It is the Commander this time!
There's no doubt about it!
He made it! Now the fun
really begins. We're moving out!
[MICHEL] Right!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Heh! Sure took him long
enough to get here.
Any job the Commander
starts he finishes.
Where?
It's coming from over there.
They're attacking
from the river.
[NORRIS] Shit they got
us surrounded!
Take me to my Zaku.
I'll take 'em out!
I did it! I blew away
their ammo dump.
You seem surprised about it.
‐Not very. But if you want out
now's the time.
And abandon my job
as protector and guide? No way.
Fine whatever.
[YELLING]
They have 2 Zakus deployed.
I'm on 'em.
Fire in the hole!
[PILOT] Shit.
Charge!
Great they all made it!
[BEEPING]
They have a Zaku headed
right for 'em!
[GUNFIRE]
Now! Hustle!
[NORRIS] Damn it! Now the
guerrillas are attacking too.
It's only a matter of time
until it falls.
Masado! Withdraw! I can
run interference.
Sir! If I go to the north slope
I can hold them off from there.
[NORRIS] Do it! I'll take that
mobile suit on the west slope.
Yes sir. Ha!
[GUNFIRE]
[YELLING]
[KAREN] Move in! We have to
provide cover for those
civilians. Got it Eledore?
[ELEDORE] I'm on it!
This could get messy! What
the hell? Guerrillas? Damn it!
[SHIRO] Do you read me?
Commander!
Sorry I took so long. Is
everyone alright?
[KAREN] Yes.
We're freeing the village. Make
sure not to hurt any civilians.
Right! Hey Sanders got that?
I got it! Huh?
Die!
[SCREAMING]
The Feddies and the
guerrillas in a joint operation?
Heads up!
Damn we're going down!
Your sneak attack was
a success. Now it's over!
Damn move!
Fine! Well let go! Ah!
Close your eyes!
Eat this!
Did I get 'em?
I'm not sure!
So now they've found a
guy who can fight underwater!
Go get 'em don't let
him get away!
Just forget about him. I'm in no
condition to go
chasing after him.
Damn! And we had 'em too!
[GUERRILLA] I got it!
[GUERRILLA 2] We hit the jackpot
today!
They're taking everything!
It's our right isn't it?
Damn. You guys really
don't mess around do ya?
What an ungrateful
bunch of morons.
What do you mean by that?
We free their whole village
and not one word of thanks.
Yeah they could
show some appreciation.
[ELEDORE] Now what?
What do ya want?
Come here!
That was a mistake!
[MICHEL FALLING]
[MAN] Hey look! Nudie pictures!
Hey I know 'er is
that your wife?
[MICHEL] Commander!
[KAREN] All prisoners and
transport vehicles are
accounted for sir.
Good work.
But the situation...
Do something about them please!
We had a deal! Anything they
take we can re‐order. Anything
else Chief Joshua?
Uh please call me Karen.
Sorry I was a little
late today Karen.
[KAREN] It's alright.
Hey Shiro wait up! Hi! Her? Is
she the owner of the watch?
Of course not I'm her
commanding officer!
[KAREN] This guy actuality got
the guerrillas to work
with us... hmm!
[ENDING THEME]
[SHIRO] While on a mission in
the western area I'm surprised
when Sanders suddenly
demands a transfer out of the
08th team! But before we can
discuss it something
terrible looms over our heads.
Is this the enemy's newest and
deadliest secret weapon?
We're about to find out.
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam
The 08th MS Team: The
Demon Overhead.