GUNDAM 08TH MS TEAM
[OPENING THEME]
THE SHUDDERING
MOUNTAIN ‐ PART ONE
[PILOT] This is squadron 386.
Course ahead is all green.
Proceeding with operation.
[PILOT 2] Don't get shot
down by any Cyclops!
[PILOT] Same goes for you buddy.
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
Tunnel entry sighted!
Coordinates ar‐ huh?!
[PILOT] Transmitting
coordinates now!
[GUNFIRE]
[GM PILOT] Ha! The idiot left
himself wide open.
[GUNFIRE]
Typical Feddie scum. Some of
them may have been born &amp; raised
on the colonies but they
can't escape gravity. We've
been spotted! Fall back now!
[NORRIS] Get to the tunnel
before the shelling starts.
We've got 'em! We have
the coordinates to their base!
[ELEDORE] Michel this
is incredible! Check it out!
Transferring data to
Guntank team.
I can't believe how many planes
are up there. They've reshaped
the whole mountain.
[MICHEL] Eledore we're starting!
[ELEDORE] Right!
We'll be going by the book.
10 shots &amp; then we move out.
I'm ready. Let's do it.
That was a direct hit. Their
gunners are good.
You think we can hold them off?
We don't have much left
to fight with.
Don't worry kid. The Apsalus
will be finished very soon &amp;
besides that we already have
plans for the Kergeren's escape.
Ms. Aina's making sure everyone
makes it to safety.
I bet we're going
back to Side 3!
[NORRIS] Abandoning a base. The
final sign of a
commander's incompetence.
[FED] Preparations to blow the
tunnel entrance are complete.
We've blown the shutters &amp; are
now sending Kojima's
battalion 07th team
into the tunnel.
[CPT.] Do we have video?
[TECH] Yes sir.
Switching to hard line.
[PILOT] No sign of the enemy.
[PILOT 2] Looks like they're
flooding the area with
Minovsky particles.
[PILOT] Cut the chatter Sally.
[PILOT 2] Yeah, yeah.
[FEDDIE VOICE] Explosives
discovered! Proceeding
with disarmament.
[VOICE 2] This is our 4th
penetration. Please let them
make it through.
Pull back the GMs until the
bombs are disarmed. We've
already had 9 units blown up.
But we've only lost 6 sir.
The count is not the point here.
Commander. I expected you to
understand our purpose here.
Since we can't find
a way in,
what what would you say to
making the mountain
disappear altogether?
That could get ugly sir. We'd
have to use nuclear weapons.
[EXPLOSION]
[MAN] Mobile suit reactor
explosion may be imminent. Lock
filters over all optical
sensors or they'll burn out!
[MAN 2] All units brace
for shockwave!
Secure from alert. No
meltdown this time.
Since mobile suits are powered
with nuclear reactors we
have no way of
guarding against accidents.
But sir! You're
suggesting that we?
Operation Star 1 is very near.
At all costs I want to avoid
Admiral Revil laughing
at me for letting that
thing get away. Are we clear?
[MOBILE SUIT MOVING]
[GUNFIRE]
Let them come out.
Hey there's one more!
[SHIRO] Karen it's one of
the skirted ones and it's fast!
[KAREN] I got 'em.
Ugh! He's in the air!
If I open fire I'll
hit his reactor!
[EXPLOSION]
[GUNTANK] You alright GM head?
Yeah I'm fine. But if you call
me that one more time you
will regret it.
[MAN] Propellent loading now 70%
complete. Continuing countdown.
You were right sir it's
getting ready to take off!
Our suppression forces in the
mining cities still
haven't reported in.
They may have failed to secure a
route for our escape. I'm going
out. My weaponry has ammo?
Yes sir. But this is all the
ammo we have left.
Ms. Aina will have a hard time
pulling off this
evacuation without help.
Anybody who isn't busy please
get aboard the Kergeren
immediately!
Move
all the wounded
into the gravity block. Anyone
who can't find a seat get into
the cargo hold with a suit on!
You in the mobile suit! Please
help get the wounded aboard.
[MAN] What are we part of the
base defense now? Did Commandant
Ginias order this?
Please I can't command you.
Do it as a favor for the men.
[NORRIS] You lose soldier.
Do as she says.
Norris is that you?
You're alright!
[NORRIS] So you finally got
master Ginias to see your point.
I can't let these soldiers die
because of my brother's
arrogant delusions.
You've become a much stronger
person. Must be because you're
in love. I am a little envious.
I was born with feelings too
although it might be a little
hard to believe. Yes I used
to have them before I
became a professional soldier.
[AINA] I think of you as a
father Norris. Though I know
so little about you.
As a father?! You really think
of me that way? What an honor.
Now I know what I've gotta do
out there.
You can't! If you go now we'll
have to evacuate without you.
It doesn't matter. A person's
life is about the things they've
accomplished. Master Ginias
has made his dreams come true &amp;
that's commendable. If you
want the Kergeren to
escape and there's a way I can
help, then as a soldier it's my
duty to find a way to make
that happen. You watch Ms. Aina
I'm going to make sure there's
an escape route for you.
Be careful!
On! Gouf! Awaken!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I can't stop you.
Damn it Norris.
But if he should come to any
harm out there...
[SOLDIER] Good luck sir!
Then I'll be the one
who killed him.
And when that happens he
will not die alone!
Ms. Aina's grown into a person
who is the very image
of her father...
[SANDERS] Sanders here.
In position sir.
[KAREN] Karen here. In position.
[SHIRO] All units prep for
cannon fire. Stand by until we
get further orders.
Grab some chow.
Roger.
Hey you hungry for something?
Shut up a second!
Look I made breakfast you make
lunch.
I know this sound from
somewhere.
This is Eledore Commander.
Better save the chow for later.
Something's coming.
Coming from where?
[ELEDORE] Damn it the sound
keeps moving around!
It's an elevator!
It's underground!
[ELEDORE] Sanders!
Front left of you!
He's fast!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[NORRIS] One command truck. 3
human types.
Protecting 3 Guntanks.
And one of 'em right below me.
They only sent one unit? I'm
a little offended.
[SANDERS] He's too close. He's
in my blind spot.
Take him Karen!
[NORRIS] These human
types have beam weaponry.
That slow poke Kergeren will
be easy pickings for them.
[NORRIS] Gotcha.
[KAREN] Damn it! He's in
that bombed out building.
[SANDERS] Leave it to me. I can
guess where he is if he's
falling. There he is.
[KAREN] Did you get him?
[NORRIS] That's one Guntank.
[YELLING]
[EXPLOSION]
He was just playing with us
while he found an opening.
He took that tank out
easily. This guy is an ace!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Very considerate of 'em to give
me an escape route. You
have my thanks.
[SHIRO] Damn! My field of
vision sucks. Eledore!
Right here!
[SHIRO] I want you to take
command!
‐You want me to what?!
There's no way for us to follow
his movements out here. I need
to depend on your ears.
That's fine! Leave it to me.
Rock &amp; roll! You're under my
command now 08th team!
[MICHEL] Oh God help us.
‐You got something to say?
Uh nothing whatsoever sir!
[SHIRO] Sanders!
[SANDERS] Yeah?
[SHIRO] The second you start
thinking of him as a regular
Zeek you'll be dead.
[SHIRO] This guy is better than
any of us.
Really? 'Bout time for a real
fight.
[GUNFIRE]
Oh! Hiding in the dust huh?
He's coming right for ya!
[KAREN] Damn it! Which way
will he come from?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[KAREN] Son of a bitch!
Not there? Aw shit!
He's going right for the crew!
[YELLING]
[SANDERS] I've got
him now Karen!
[GUNFIRE]
I've got a lock. Overhead
649 by 23. Unit 301 fire!
One tank left...
[TECH] Apsalus final
checks initiated. Now running.
All green! The
Apsalus is complete.
It's been a long and very
difficult journey.
And I thank you.
Victory!
[COUGHING]
I hope everybody finds
the wine to their liking...
[SHIRO] Good work Eledore!
[SHIRO] Come on... ah!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[NORRIS] That's right! Cower! Be
afraid! Die knowing you lost to
someone who really
knows how to use a mobile suit!
He wants me to retreat. Time
to attack. Ah!!!
[GUNFIRE]
Haha! This is getting fun now!
Now it's your turn!!
[GUNFIRE]
[NORRIS] Well that looked
impressive. Now say
goodbye to your tank.
No you don't!
[NORRIS] It's over now.
[GUNFIRE]
Huh? Hahahahaha!
Well Ms. Aina the Kergeren
will have to leave without me.
I have found the place
where I am to die.
[SOLDIER] Ms. Aina! We just
spotted a signal flare from
Captain Norris!
How is he? Tell me what
color was the flare?!
It was red.
Unable to return. Launch
the Kergeren now.
Yes ma'am.
[VOICE] Kergeren ready for
liftoff! Cutting energy
pipes to the base now.
Gentlemen, while it pains me to
say goodbye to you all
the time has come.
Relax and get some rest.
And now the Apsalus is mine.
And mine alone!
The Kergeren is due to take off
in about 20 minutes. I better
throw in a few more tricks!
Out of ammo?!
My left arm is out of action!
Ha! Pretty good reflexes. Not
bad for a Feddie. But I bet
you're not ready for this!
Your good vision is your
fatal weakness!
Where's the main
circuit damn it!?
Why don't you shoot?!
Just finish me for God's sake!
[GUNTANK] Thanks! We
owe you one.
[KAREN] Shut up and go already!
[GUNTANK] Right!
[SANDERS] So what do
we do now "acting commander?"
[KAREN] If we could just
get to the weapons depot...
No way he got the Guntanks when
we tried it! Make sure blue boy
stays off the tank.
[ELEDORE] Just do it!
It's time I stopped playing
games with them. What'll it be?
You gonna fire on me while the
pilot's still alive?
[KAREN] Here he comes Sanders!
[SANDERS] Right!
Come on hands. Stay steady. My
friends! Unit 301? Do I really
care if they get out of
this alive? Right now all that
fighting for my friends talk is
sounding ridiculous!
All I know is I'm really scared.
I wanna live!! I wanna live!
So you're awake huh?
[SHIRO] I'm gonna live! And I'll
marry Aina! And we'll
grow old together!
You're the one that... damn it!
The Commander! He's lost it.
Yeah once he stops thinking
about it he'll be a force
to reckon with.
I think he'll be OK.
I know that sound.
No time to celebrate yet guys!
Aina's about to pay us a visit!
[JET ENGINES]
Now firing.
Good. Let's get started.
[GM] What the hell?
[SCREAMING]
Oh yeah...
[BREATHING]
So I've met Ms. Aina's Feddie
lover. Life can be real
funny sometimes.
[NORRIS] But I won't be stopped!
[SHIRO SCREAMING]
Victory is mine! Ah!
[GUNFIRE]
Damn it! No!
[EXPLOSION]
They're all gone...
Everyone listen up: I'm
leaving the service.
[ENDING THEME]
[SHIRO] Karen. Sanders.
Eledore. Michel. Don't die my
friends. We'll meet again.
Next time: The Shuddering
Mountain – Part 2.