[KISHIMOTO gasps]
--[KURONO grunting]
--[SEI moaning]
[SEI] I can't believe
this is happening,
especially in a place like this.
[SEI]
I thought I was dead.
[KURONO]
I said we're not dead.
But at least one of us is
still a little stiff, I hope.
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
--[BOTH] Huh?
Yeah, we're dead...
[KURONO]
Who the fuck cares?
[TOMAO]
"Ferocious Alien"?
[KONTA]
Man, I just don't get it.
[MIYAFUJI]
It must mean something...
[IKE] Well, there's a TV show
called "Ferocious Shogun"...
[MIYAFUJI] You seem to
know an awful lot here.
Just how do you fit into this?
It's not just me.
Actually, all of us on this
side of the room know it.
Because we've been here before.
But I have to warn you that
we only know a little more
about the rules
than you guys do.
It should open soon, so be
careful. Any second now.
[ALL gasp]
I think you should
go change first.
[OKAZAKI]
Whoo-whee! Oh yeah!
Good grief...
Look at the fine details.
There are suits in these
containers, so put one on.
There's one labeled
for each of you.
If you believe what he says,
then you are truly fools!
This is a place of
trial, remember?
That's right!
He's not even human!
He represents our
foulest passions!
All those foolish
enough to follow him
will be lead down
the path to Hell!
Why else would he
have placed tools
for the murder of others
in your hands? Eh?
Hey, wait a minute!
I'm a human just like the
rest of you. Believe me.
[TOKUGAWA]
Don't let him get to you!
He only appears to be human!
Aw... This hurts my brain.
If you listen to this
priest, you'll die.
With me, you at
least have a chance.
--[KISHIMOTO gasps, pants]
--[TOKUGAWA laughs]
Everyone here is already dead!
[KATO]
Hey, what's wrong?
Uh, well, Kurono's back
there... And he's kinda busy.
[KATO]
He is? What's he doing?
[BOTH grunting, moaning]
[KURONO] By the way...
you need... a suit...
[SEI]
A what?
[KURONO] A suit...
You should put one on, okay?
But not now... Later.
[SEI]
Su-Sure...
[SEI] So what's this thing for?
You never really explained.
You'll find out soon enough.
[SEI] Well damn. This thing fits
like it was made for me exactly.
I've got to say, Heaven sure
isn't what I was expecting.
Haven't I told you
that we're not dead?
[KISHIMOTO]
Wait! I don't--
What's up, Kei?
[KISHIMOTO]
Um, I--
[KATO]
Don't worry. I'll stay with you.
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
You were in danger the last time
and the time before
that, remember?
I don't want anything
to happen to you again.
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
Like what else could happen?
[TOKUGAWA]
Namu Amida... Namu Amida...
[ALL]
If you've got an idea
on how to get these guys
to wear their suits,
I'm open to it.
Why should we even
bother with them?
If these jerks don't wanna play,
we can handle it ourselves.
[KISHIMOTO] Please tell
me you're not serious!
I don't want anyone
else to die, okay?
[KATO] And the more of us that
are prepared to fight...
...then the greater the chance
becomes for us all to survive.
So you've got a gun
fixation, too, huh?
[OKAZAKI]
Mm... No.
So could I ask you
guys a few questions?
Uh-- Sure.
What's with that guy in
the ball? Does anyone know?
No...
You don't know, huh?
Then do you at least know who
"sponsors" this hunt of yours?
[KATO]
Who "sponsors" it? I don't know.
I see. So there are great
gaps in what you know.
I'm afraid so.
Right. But you still
expect me to believe that
we're going to
put on these suits
and go out and hunt aliens
for a big black ball?
Yes. That's correct.
And these things we'll
hunt... these aliens...
They're from space?
[TOMAO]
Ooh...
Quit screwin' with us!
You mean aliens and shit?
Probably...
On the other hand,
that ball did draw people out
of the air with a laser beam.
And there's no human technology
that can do that, is there?
So that just leaves aliens or
an act of Divinity, doesn't it?
It's a dream! Who cares
if it's divine or not?
[MIYAFUJI]
No, as far as I can tell
this is really some kind of
teleportation device,
just like in the movies. I don't
know exactly how it works,
but it's possible that
it can teleport a person
to a different place,
the second the person dies.
Ha! That's ridiculous!
You said that we'd die if we
didn't wear these suits, right?
Let's just say that...
...your chances aren't
so good without it.
In that case, I'll wear it.
The game's starting!
Hold on, look at the clock.
It's different!
It's 30 minutes longer.
The first two games both lasted
60 minutes. So does that mean...
...that wthis time,
we're going up against
something even
worse than before?
[KURONO]
Still, it's no big deal.
It's just 30 minutes
more; I'm up for it!
You see? They're all being
pulled back down to Hell.
Listen to me, if you don't put
on the suits now, you'll die!
Put 'em on!
Put on one of those gay
things? Forget that!
Yeah, only an otaku or
a fag would wear that!
I don't hear anyone else
saying their prayers!
Actually that shit's
pretty gay, too.
Yeah, and I'm not even Buddhist!
They're not leaving
us any choice.
We're really gonna have
to do this by ourselves.
[TOMAO] Hey, let me down!
What the hell are you doing?!
[BOTH grunting]
You broke my knee!
Yeah, chill!
It's the suit... that
gives me this strength.
[JJ yells]
[ALL]
Whoa...
[KATO] As you see,
the suit also protects me.
You don't have to wear them,
but at least take them with you.
Okay, so where are we?
A temple?
You! Goddamn it, now you're
being transported with me?!
[MUROTO] So, what song do
you wanna sing this time?
[KAJIURA]
Oh, I'll let you decide.
[MUROTO]
Hmmm...
Do you know that exercise
song, "Brand New Day"?
[KAJIURA]
Huh? Oh yeah!
What made you pick that?
This is our workout.
High-impact even.
--[MUROTO laughs]
--[KAJIURA] Oh, I get it!
[KONTA] Man, no matter
how many times I see that,
it creeps me out.
[TOKUGAWA] Yes, divine
judgment has now begun.
They're falling into
the pits of Hell!
You don't mean "Hell" like
in the Old Testament, do you?
Hellfire and brimstone?!
Save me! I haven't had
a chance to confess yet!
Aah! I thought this was a dream!
It's okay, you're only
being sent outside.
You're not going to Hell.
Namu Amishinrai...
[KATO] Look, you don't have
to wear them right now.
But hold onto the
suits and the weapons!
And wherever we end up,
don't try to leave
or go anywhere else.
Kato, there's
something that I--
I'll see you outside.
Please don't worry.
Everything'll be fine.
See?! Now do you fools see
what happens when you ignore
the words of a priest
who knows these things?!
Now you will burn in the
eternal flames forever!
[gasps, yelps]
Where is everybody? Dear Lord,
what's happening?! Ahh!
[KATO]
Listen, everyone!
Whatever you do,
don't try to leave!
[SEI] Are you thinking...
that we shouldn't have...?
[KURONO] No. And it's
not connected, okay?
[SEI]
Well, if you say so...
I don't get it! What's
the big deal about here?
Well, at least we
can walk home now!
Wait! It's important
that we all stay together!
[KONTA]
Right...
How long are you gonna
keep feeding us this shit?
[TOKUGAWA gasping]
Hold on... Isn't this Ratenin?
Hey, dude, have you been crying?
Don't be ridiculous!
[MIYAFUJI] You know, given all
the weird stuff that's happened,
it might be wise to accept
what's happening and go with it.
[IKE]
Screw that!
I'm finding a station and
catching a train home.
They're still runnin'
this late, right?
Wait, you can't leave!
It isn't safe!
Yeah? Why not?
Weren't you listening to what
Kato said earlier? There's--
Oh, yeah, "ferocious aliens,"
right. That's not half as scary
as my ferocious supervisor
if I'm late! See ya!
No! Please!
This is so screwed up.
[KURONO] Just listen to
those two! Birds of a feather!
Gimme a break!
[IKE]
Yo! Taxi!
[HOJO]
Hey! Those are the same statues
the ball was showing
us, aren't they?
[SEI] Wait. Are you saying that
they're supposed to be aliens?
[KATO]
I honestly don't know.
But the Gantz always
pits us against
different kinds of aliens.
As far as we know,
these could be anything.
[MUROTO, KAJIURA laughing]
Now where are they hiding?
Ah... My little nose
tells me they're...
...right over there!
Mm... Instant ramen
on the campfire!
Shit, they keep igoring me!
Who's walkin' to the station?
[KATO]
No! Wait!
[KONTA]
Up yours!
[TOMAO] Yeah, we're outta
here, you otaku freaks!
The one thing I
don't undertand is
who would want to play such
an elaborate joke on us?
Wait! Please don't leave!
You're in danger! Please!
Kato! Forget about them!
If those assholes
wanna go, let 'em go!
[KISHIMOTO]
Kurono, how could we do that,
knowing what will happen?
[KURONO] They're not gonna
believe anything you say.
And since the Gantz gave us
an hour and a half this time,
it's high time we
started kickin' ass!
[KATO]
But Kei...
For God's sake! Listen to
what you're saying, Kurono!
[KATO]
L-Look, you guys just wait here!
Get back!
[KATO gags]
Smells like alcohol...
This is what'll happen
if you go any further!
Step outside the playing area,
and your head explodes!
This is so fucked up...
This could...
be divine judgment!
That smell of alcohol
represents a life of excess!
It could be brandy
or maybe whiskey!
It's not divine
judgment, goddamn it!
Now get the hell back to the
temple area, where it's safe!
What was that? He just...
Beats me.
For all I know, it could be
some kinda divine judgment.
I'm not the one to ask.
Well, I ain't never been in
a game where somebody's head
got fuckin' blown off.
But baby... These big
honkers are sweet!
[KISHIMOTO] Huh?!
Exactly what does that mean?
Uh, nothin'...
[MUROTO]
Mmm! Looks yummy!
However, my good friend here
is going to show you a
much faster way to eat it!
[screams]
[MUROTO, KAJIURA laughing]
[MUROTO] ♪ Oh, it's the
beginning of a brand new day! ♪
♪ A day filled with hope! ♪
Hey, you! Where do you
think you're goin', huh?
Come back here,
you homeless bastard!
[BOTH laugh]
[HOJO] So what now? Should we
force the doors open or what?
There's a whole mess of them
in there. Should we go for it?
Do we have any other choice?
[KATO]
Okay. Everyone stand back.
[KISHIMOTO]
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna shake this gate. Maybe
I can knock the bolts loose.
What is it, Kei?
Just let me handle it, okay?
[KURONO]
Now remember,
our job is to go in there
and kill the enemies.
No more, no less.
So let's get on with it!
[TOMAO]
I still don't get it...
[TOKUGAWA]
You fool! How dare you!
That temple gate is sacred!
What do you think you're doing?!
[KURONO] What I'm doing is
giving us a chance to beat
whatever we're up against!
It's what you call
a preemptive strike!
What I call it is a sin!
Can't you see that this
place is a holy shrine?!
[KATO] Everyone, listen up!
We're about to risk our lives
fighting alien creatures,
do you understand?!
And while this may all seem
like a game, it's quite real.
If you make a mistake,
you'll be dead.
However, these suits
will give you
some protection
and added strength.
As for the guns, remember
that you must pull both triggers
at the same time. And we have
to defeat all our enemies
within the time limit.
Many have died in this game!
But we can live if
we fight together!
A war... A real war...
And this time, I'm ready...
I hate to bring this up,
but it's bothering me...
How do we know that these things
aren't really the aliens?
[HOJO]
Can those things even move?
[KATO] I don't know,
but they seem too big,
at least compared to the
other ones we've fought.
I haven't seen enemies
like these before, but...
[MIYAFUJI]
Well, if you're sure...
The radar says they're
inside the temple, right?
Yeah...
[MIYAFUJI] Isn't there some
way to find out for sure?
Hey, what about the X-gun?
The X-gun?
Yeah, the X-gun.
[MIYAFUJI]
What's an X-gun?
We decided to call this
the X-gun for two reasons.
It has an X-ray-like display
and it makes an X shape
when you fire it.
Actually, Kato came
up with the name.
[KURONO] What the fuck?
When did he start namin' things?
And how the hell does
she know about it?!
Of course, X-gun's not
an official name...
I just call it that.
It's not bad. And actually,
I like the sound of "X-gun."
So now that you've named it,
just what can we do with it?
[KISHIMOTO]
Well, with the X-ray part,
you should be able to see
through an object, right?
[KATO] That's right.
If they're living creatures,
we should be able to see
their bones like in an x-ray.
[gasps]
[KATO]
Oh my god...
[HOJO]
What is it?
[KATO] They're alive...
They're really alive...
And we're supposed
to fight them?
How can we do that without--?
[KURONO]
He can't... He can't shoot it.
But why?! He doesn't have
any other choice left!
[KONTA] Whoa! Reality check!
These things are really aliens?
[TOMAO] Yeah, are they
gonna move or what?
So what now?
Since they're not moving, can't
we just take them out right now?
[KATO sighs]
What about the capture mode?
Maybe we can trap them!
Are you sure?
[KATO]
Somebody lend me a trap gun.
[OKAZAKI]
Here, but I want it back.
[KURONO]
Damn it, wait!
♪ So open your heart
up big and be happy! ♪
♪ As you look up at
the big, blue sky... ♪
--[singing continues]
--[HOMELESS MAN screaming]
[KATO]
Kei! Wait!
[KURONO] I'm so fucking
sick and tired of this!
But Kei...
We don't need to capture it!
All we have to do is kill it!
[KATO]
Yes, that's true, but--
[KISHIMOTO]
Kurono, a-are you sure...?
[KURONO]
I'll handle it!
This is the fastest way and we
can't afford to waste any time.
[TOKUGAWA screams]
[KISHIMOTO screams]
--[KAJIURA laughing]
--[MUROTO] Told ya. Hobo season.
--Vagrant season.
--[loud thumping]
[BOTH]
Huh?
What the hell was that?
A traffic accident
or a backfire.
In any case,
it's not our problem.
♪ Oh, listen to...
the singing voice... ♪
--♪  And ex-- exercise! ♪
--[splatter]
[HOJO]
These guys aren't bad at all.
They've actually started
working together.
Huh? No-- No, I'm not!
Don't look at me like that!
I told you, I'm normal!
Next episode,
"I Can Shoot Them, Can't I?"