Stop this this instant!
[KAJIURA]
Hmm?
Just what in the Sam Hill
do you two think you're doing?!
[KAJIURA] Like I said, we're
trying to kill the Kurono Alien.
And that girl doesn't have
anything to do with it!
--Let her go!
--[gasps]
Why don't you tell Kurono that?
Things are like this
right now because
he had to go putting up a fight.
[FURUTA]
What?! B-But--
[gasps]
What the hell...?
Kishimoto!
He's seeing things.
More hallucinations?
Kurono! Tell me what you see!
Kurono, it's too late.
It's time to give up.
You know you won't make it.
Fuck you, Gantz!
You can't possibly think I'm
gonna fall for this shit again!
Death is the only thing
left for you.
Kiss my ass! I'm not
gonna die for you.
None of us...
wanted to die, Kurono.
[KURONO gasps]
[KISHIMOTO] Why are you the only
one of us still alive, Kurono?
It's not fair!
Shut up, damn you!
[KISHIMOTO] You think you're
the only one who wanted to live?
We all wanted to live!
Kato, Sei, and
everyone else is dead!
Why were you saved
and not us, Kurono?
It's not true, damn it!
It's a fucking lie!
I don't think it's true either!
[ALL]
Huh?
[KISHIMOTO, MIKA]
Can't you all see that Kurono
must've lost everyone
that meant anything to him?
That terrible pain
must be the reason
that he's acting like this now.
Shut up! Shut up, you dumb slut!
What if it's all the truth?!
What if Kurono
really isn't an alien?!
What if the real
bad guys are the Gantz
and these two Kurono
warned us about!
Shut up or I'll kill ya!
Then go ahead
and kill me, damn it!
I've already died once,
so who cares?!
Pull the trigger!
Just do it already!
Both of you keep talking
about who's an alien,
but all you really
wanna do is kill Kurono!
Am I wrong?
You said this is
so we can survive,
but all you really
wanna do is kill somebody!
You just wanna kill anybody,
isn't that right?!
[KURONO]
Kishimoto...
[KISHIMOTO]
Kurono...
We will get out
of this together.
'Kay?
We will go back together.
[KAJIURA]
I warned you!
[MIKA screams]
[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[MIKA yelps]
[KAJIURA cackles]
[MUROTO]
What a fuckin' moron.
Why are you losing it now?
[MIKA yelps]
[KAJIURA cackles]
[KURONO]
Ki-Kishimoto...?
Have you gone totally mad?!
[ALL gasp]
[KAJIURA screams]
Kurono!
[KAJIURA] Hajime! Don't let
him get away, you little shit!
Get off your ass
and wake the fuck up!
Yes, okay, sir.
Right!
Hey, wait! Huh?
It really isn't true, is it?
[MIKA screams]
[KURONO yells]
[MIKA]
Hey...
Hey!
You, uh... really aren't
some kind of alien, are you?
Of course I'm not!
[KAJIURA]
Let's go! Move!
[FURUTA]
Wait, damn it!
Did you two really kill
those bums like he said?
Just shut the fuck up!
Let's move it, kid.
[ALL gasp]
[FURUTA]
Don't do it! Put that gun down!
Can't you see these
fuckers are sick, Pops?
[FURUTA]
And shooting them proves what?
Put it down!
Come on, we don't
have time for this!
Answer the question!
Did the two of you kill
those homeless people
at the temple or not?
[MIKA]
Wait... Stop.
You wanna stop?
I dropped something back there.
Oh, fu--! What was it?
My book. I have to
go back and get my book.
[KURdONO] Forget it!
It was all bloody anyway.
I know it sounds stupid,
but it's important to me.
There's this wonderful line
on the first page.
I just wanna finish
reading the rest of it!
Is it worth dying for?
[MIKA]
"No labyrinth is inescapable."
[KURONO]
What?
That's what it says on
the first page of the book.
The name of the book is
Labyrinth by Miranda Foster.
[KURONO gasps]
I'm waiting for an answer!
So maybe we killed
a few, what of it?
[ALL gasp]
We're talkin' about killin'
a coupl'a drunk-off-their-asses
pieces of
human garbage, Old Man!
Does anyone really give a fuck?
[FURUTA]
And you... You did it, too?
Well, actually, I, um...
[YOSHINO]
Did you or didn't you?!
Hell yeah, he did.
[MUROTO gasps]
His eyes say so.
I had no choice!
He made me kill them,
I swear it!
I didn't wanna kill
those poor people!
What the fuck?
You little goddamn liar!
I told him I didn't wanna
kill homeless people, but--
Mr. Kajiura always
forced me to go out with him
and do all
those horrible things.
[MUROTO]
I really didn't mean to.
One time, Mr. Kajiura
went out of control.
And before we knew it,
we were surrounded
by these angry homeless people.
They were the ones who attacked
us with the metal baseball bats.
I had to fight them!
Just cut the bullshit,
you lying little cocksucker!
You're a worse murderer
than I've ever been!
That's not true. I got scared
and tried to run away,
so I just swung the bat
all over the place.
I accidentally hit
one of 'em on the head,
but it was self-defense!
I swear the whole thing was
an accident, please believe me!
So what do you think?
Do you believe him?
I'm still not sure.
But whether he's lying or not,
he's still a minor.
Which means...
Um, which means it's not
too late to let him start over?
What he's doin' now ain't
self-defense, you jackass!
[FURUTA]
But he's--
[YOSHINO]
Nozaki's right, dammit!
Are you done preachin' yet,
you clutch of assholes? Huh?
[KURONO] And this woman...
just let you have it?
Yes, there was a beautiful
strength about her.
She said I needed it.
And she had a bike helmet
with her name on the back.
Sakuraoka... S. Sakuraoka!
[KURONO gasps]
I... see.
[MIKA]
It's strange.
But I feel like it's
all connected somehow.
And yet, she's...
out there somewhere,
and I'm trapped
in this labyrinth!
In any case, I feel
like I have to try
and get that book back for her.
She gave it up for me, and I'd
feel awful if I just left it.
--[glass shatters]
--[gasps]
Please... Please
stop it, Mr. Kajiura...
Stow it! Your stupid act
is really pissing me off!
If you'd like,
I'd gladly accompany you
to the police station
to turn yourself in.
What?! Just who in the fuck
do you think you are?!
At least I'm not a monster
that preys on children!
That poor boy's just a minor!
And you've been forcing him
to help you kill people!
You already know how to
use these suits, right?
[MIKA]
What?
No, I don't.
[gasps] Hey! What are you doing?
[KURONO]
Don't worry.
You used it when that
psycho was giving you
the hot towel
treatment, remember?
Wait downstairs,
and you'll be fine.
[MIKA]
Downstairs?
But I told you I had to--
Don't worry.
I'll get your book.
[MIKA gasps]
Wait! [screams]
[KURONO]
Watch that first step!
[MUROTO sobbing]
Put the weapon down, dammit!
For his sake and all of ours,
just surrender!
He's right!
Please stop this, sir.
[KAJIURA]
Ya know what, Old Man?
You're down to
my very last nerve.
'Cause there's nothin'
that pisses me off
as much as bein' preached at!
Oh-ho!
Teacher! What are you doing?
[YOSHINO] I was willing to shoot
my own student to save my life.
Don't think I'll hesitate
to shoot you.
Put your gun down now!
[FURUTA]
Stop it, everyone! Just stop it!
This book that Mika
had is about situations
like this that seem hopeless!
[KURONO gasps]
Come on!
There's a line on the first page
I want you to think about.
And the point is...?
Will you just listen?!
It says, quote:
"No labyrinth is inescapable."
Do you understand the
meaning behind that line?
Oh for God's sake, you old fuck,
that's just a stupid paperback!
And they're called
labyrinths because
you can't get out of them!
I can't believe that a man
your age doesn't know
the difference between
facts and fiction.
[FURUTA] What does my age
have to do with it?!
There's nothing wrong with
believing in something!
[SAITO] Look, I know
you run a bookstore,
but now's not the time
for yammering about
this new age mumbo-jumbo!
[FURUTA]
You're wrong!
If there's a way out
of every labyrinth,
there must be a way
out of this game.
I'm absolutely sure of it!
So could you put the guns down?
I've already pointed a gun
at one of my own kids,
if I make it back... how am
I supposed to live with that?
[KURONO] You humiliated me
regularly anyway;
don't do something
stupid, you bitch!
You know what, bitch?!
I'm just gonna kill you!
I'll shoot!
Your brains'll go splat,
and then I'll
stomp on what's left!
[BOTH gasp]
[KAJIURA]
Oh, motherfucker!
Kurono, look out!
[KAJIURA]
Aah! Damn you!
[ALL scream]
You murdering psycho shit!
Son of a bitch!
[KURONO screams, groans]
Kurono!
[groans]
Hajime! Let's go!
[KAJIURA]
Get your ass in gear! Move!
[MUROTO yelps]
[gasps]
--[KURONO] Damn it!
--[FURUTA] Stop, dammit!
Calm down and back off!
[FURUTA]
If you go after those guys now,
it'll just turn
into another brawl!
So use your brains!
They've got the teacher,
so it'll take 'em a while
to get downstairs.
Let's plan this out first.
[KURONO]
Yeah, right.
--[KAJIURA] Move it, you cunt!
--[YOSHINO yelps]
Why did Kurono try to
rescue us after what we di--
[KAJIURA]
Why don't you shut up?
He could've escaped,
but he came back.
What was I thinking when
I pointed a gun at him
in the first place?
Oh, god... Kurono, I'm sorry.
I'll rape your corpse if you
don't shut up, you bitch!
[FURUTA] So Mr. Saito,
you say you're familiar
with this building's
layout, right?
[SAITO]
Uh, me...? Well...
[FURUTA]
When we were up on the roof,
you sounded like you knew
this place real well.
Look, I've only been to this
place a couple of times.
With my old office
supervisor, you know?
All we need to know
is where's the best place
to corner that pair
of psychopaths.
[SAITO] Probably the bar
on the first floor.
It has higher counters
than the topless place,
so if they started
shooting at you,
there's a better chance
of finding something
to hide behind.
In that case, let's herd 'em
down to the first floor,
dry-gulch the fucks,
and grab the teach!
[NOZAKI]
And what if they use her
--as a shield again, smart guy?
--If they do, then I'll try
talking them out of it, okay?
And what makes you think they're
gonna listen to you now?!
Which part of "psycho"
don't you get?!
The ones who are gonna get
dry-gulched is us!
Well, killing
each other won't help.
By the way, what happened
to the other girl? The coed.
Oh, she's fine. I just showed
her a quicker way downstairs.
[FURUTA]
Let's get one thing straight.
We can't go around
killing people,
so I want you to fire
warning shots only.
It's a bit late for that, Pops.
We can do it.
Have faith.
[SAITO]
I have faith we'll get killed!
[sighs]
Jeez, will you come off
the gloom and doom trip?!
I swear, how can
he be so negative...
[NOZAKI]
Hey, Kurono.
You mind if I ask you
a personal question?
[KURONO]
Fire away.
You could've run away from us
easily back there,
so what did you come back for?
For my teacher.
I've always admired... her tits.
[NOZAKI]
Huh?
[laughs]
Man, that's a good one, dude.
Don't just stand there!
Blast the door so
we can get out of here!
Who in the hell do you think you
are, bossing me around?
I'm killing you when we
get back, you little shit!
Ooh...
[YOSHINO]
Kurono, I'm so sorry.
[KAJIURA gasps]
Oh, what the fuck now?
We're not gonna make it in time!
Jump between the landings
and you'll learn
how to use the suits at
the same time like this!
Come on, everyone jump down!
[FURUTA]
Right!
I'll shoot this time;
I swear I will!
You haven't got the balls, cunt!
[laughs]
[YOSHINO yelps]
Let the lady go!
[KAJIURA]
Oh, shit!
[KURONO]
Good, we've got 'em cornered.
Let's go!
Okay, I'm going in
to rescue my teacher.
It's too dangerous
for someone your age!
Let me do it!
No way. I have
the most experience
with the weapons and the suit.
I have to do it.
[FURUTA]
But if you'll just listen--
[KURONO]
No, you listen.
You wanna be the leader?
Great. I'm no good at it.
We had a great one before,
and we need one now.
You've got a conscience
and care... about all of us.
Just like Kato.
You can keep us focused.
And that's something that
I'll never be good at.
We need someone who's...
trying to get all of us home.
[KURONO] I refuse... to let
Gantz jerk us around anymore!
You know... You kinda
look like someone...
[KURONO gasps]
Now that you mention it...
Oh, forget I said it.
Then let's do this.
[ALL gasp]
[KURONO gasps]
Motherfucker...
You bastards!
Why can't we have
a little fun, huh?
The bitch is
already dead, right?
Hey, I didn't do it!
Mr. Kajiura swung
a knife at her!
He used this... knife...
Oops!
That does it!
When we get back, I'm gonna
carve your lying little ass up
the same way you did her!
Yeah, cut the bullshit act, kid.
What could cause that boy
to do something like that?
He's what they call
a "sexual predator."
But he's--
If you say one
more thing about that
bloodthirsty little loon
being a kid, I'll hurl!
Ah, the hell with all
this hostage crap!
This human shield business
is too much work.
[gasps]
Take the bitch!
[YOSHINO groans]
Kurono, dear,
please forgive me...
I was crazy to think
I should shoot you.
[YOSHINO] When you...
got hard-ons in class,
I knew you were
fantasizing about me...
[gasps]
Why does everything
come back to my dick?
Actually, I got off...
on how hard I got you.
I'm sorry!
[grunts]
[screams]
[ALL gasp]
[cackles]
That was wicked!
[MUROTO cackles]
[ding]
[KURONO gasps]
Oh, baby, that hurts so good!
[KAJIURA groaning]
[KURONO yells]
[ALL yell]
[ALL panting]
Where... did they go?
Did they get away?
Are you all right, sir?
[NOZAKI] All right?
If you'd bother to look,
you'd have seen our shit's
already hit the fan.
[MIKA gasps]
I told you that I'd get it back.
And I promise, we'll
protect you. We all will.
Isn't that right, Mr. Boss-Man?
Well, I hope you have more
of a plan than that.
Oh, trust me, since
that train ran over me,
I've learned to plan
for the unexpected.
[gasps]
[MIKA]
You're...
[KURONO]
Huh?
[MIKA]
You're that guy!
[FURUTA]
Hey, everyone, look at this.
It looks like they're
leaving a trail of blood.
Ms. Uehara might have given us
the chance to stop her killers.
[MIKA]
What?! You mean... she's dead?
[gasps] Oh my god...
[KURONO yells]
This whole fucking thing
has been a grudge match
between me and the Gantz.
I don't know how it'll end,
but I promise you this:
Before it's over,
those two are gonna die.
No, not until we've
heard them out first.
[KURONO]
What?! Damn it!
You'll never make it
out of this labyrinth
with that attitude, Old Man!
I could care less
about the big one,
but that boy deserves
a chance just like you did!
And I will bring him back!
[SAITO] Screw this! I'm past
the point of caring anymore.
[KURONO gasps]
Mr. Saito?
I'm gettin' sick and tired of
this old fuck tellin' me
what I have to do!
To hell with this
inescapable labyrinth shit!
If you wanna go on,
you can do it without me!
Forget it! It'll be too
dangerous if we're separated!
[SAITO]
I said, I'm not going, dammit!
And if you try to make me,
you old prick,
I'll blow your balls off!
[ALL gasp]
I-I really will do it!
I really will pull the trigger!
[MIKA]
I won't lose...
I won't die!
I won't die... ever.
I'll never die!
Next episode,
"Let's All Go Back Alive."