I just wanna go home now, Kei.
More than any of you.
[KISHIMOTO shrieks]
Nishi!
Kato! Please come back!
Get back here!
Dude, is he nuts?
[NISHI panting]
You dumbass!
Now you're gonna die, too!
How can you say that?!
What's that? Hey, hot tits,
why don't you blow me?!
Do something! For god's
sake, Kurono,
you've got to help Kato!
[grunting]
[SUZUKI ALIEN]
Raah...!
No!
--Aah...!
--[gasps]
[loud screeching]
[groaning]
Nishi!
[screeching continues]
[screaming]
--[KATO] Stop it!
--Aah!
[screeching]
[NISHI screams]
[gasps]
[KATO]
Nishi!
[RYOTA]
Grandma! My ears hurt!
[KAYO] There, there.
You'll be all right.
Shut up! Can't you gag
that brat, grandma?!
[KAYO] But he says
his ears are hurting!
[RYOTA wails]
What?! We all thought it.
[KAYO]
There, there...
[TETSUO]
Forget about that!
What about that asshole?
Is he dead? What's happening?
Who cares if he is
or not? Dumbass.
It serves him right!
[HARUYA, KINJI laugh]
[panting]
[KATO]
I'm too late...
[SUZUKI ALIEN growling]
[NISHI gasps]
Nishi!
[BOTH gasp]
[rasping, retching]
He don't give up easy, do he?
Aw, I bet he still dies.
Yuzo, bro.
Will somebody please
kill this guy?!
[NISHI sobs]
[NISHI] Then we can all go back!
We can all return safely!
[sobs]
Hurry! Waste his ass!
[KATO]
Kill him...?
[SUZUKI ALIEN growls]
Yuzo!
[gasps]
[NISHI]
Use your gun... kill him now!
NOW!
He's coming now! Kato, move!
You've gotta get out of there!
Go! Move it!
He's after you, Kato!
But... But I can't!
I have to save Nishi!
I have to!
[KURONO]
Are you fucking nuts?!
If that's the case,
just shoot him then!
He's right! Either you
shoot him or you run!
But if you don't
choose soon, you'll die!
[whimpers]
[KISHIMOTO]
Shoot him! Do it now!
Come on, Kato! What the hell
are you waiting for?!
He can't... He can't shoot it.
But why?! He doesn't have
any other choice left!
[KURONO]
We all know the situation...
But Kato can't shoot!
That's just the way he is...
...and how he'll always be!
I've never shot anybody either.
But I know...
I could do it if I had to.
But Kato won't fire
that gun. He can't!
Oh, God...
[KURONO] Did that sound
cold and calculating?
I wasn't trying to
talk shit about Kato
just 'cause I wanna nail her...
I mean, it's not like I said
anything bad about him, anyway!
I'm just saying. Kato is too
kind a person to shoot.
Yeah. That's it.
It's true...
You just can't shoot!
We have to
help Kato! Please!
If we don't do something,
then he's going to be--
Hah! So what?!
Go do it yourself, tit-girl!
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
Ah, man...
Fuck it all anyway...
Why the hell are we
wasting our time here?
[HARUYA]
Yeah, let's blow.
And you!, If you've got
time to kick my ass,
why don't you go down there
and help out your leader, huh?
No! Don't go!
[KINJI]
Time for some ramen.
[HARUYA]
Ahh... My fuckin' mouth hurts.
Ryota, I think it's time
for us to be going home, too.
Somebody, please! Help him!
[KURONO] A-Are you kidding? You
want ME to help you help him?
[KISHIMOTO]
Fine, then!
[KURONO]
Whoah, wait!
I'll do it myself!
I want to help Kato and
I'm sick of all you saying
that I need other
people to survive!
So I'll... go.
I'll...
[KURONO]
Wait!
I'll... go... Okay?
[panting]
[KATO]
What should I do?!
What... can I do?!
I know! Maybe I can use
this to keep him at bay!
[KATO yells]
[KATO]
Nishi! Nishi, can you move?!
My ears... I can't
hear anything...
--[NISHI groans]
--At least he's light.
[KATO] But can I make it
back over there?
[KATO panting]
[NISHI]
Stop...
Stop moving...
Huh?!
[screams]
[KATO panting]
Nishi!
Huh?! Where's the gun?!
--[splashing]
--[gasps]
[SUZUKI ALIEN growls]
Oh, Yuzo!
Raah...!
[KURONO]
Kato!
[KATO screams]
Oh my god... No...
I missed... Fuck!
Kato!
Where are you...?
Where are you?!
What the hell? What just
happened down there?
[splashing]
[BOTH gasp]
It's Kato!
--[SUZUKI ALIEN screeches]
--[KATO screams]
[HARUYA] So... I wonder if
they're all dead by now?
Like I care! All I wanna do
is eat some fuckin' ramen!
Aw, shut yer hole.
Say wha...?
Oh, yeah, you wanna see
a dentist, right? [chuckles]
[HARUYA] Anyway, what kinda
dentist is open this late?
[RYOTA] Grandma, I really
want something to eat.
Of course you do, Ryota. All we
need to do is phone your mother,
and she'll be here
soon to pick us up.
We'll have her pick up a
hamburger you can eat
in the car. How does
that sound to you?
Is that all right?
[RYOTA]
Yes! That sounds great!
[music plays]
Well, that's odd...
I wonder if this
phone is broken?
[KINJI] Hey, kid... What the
hell are you lookin' at, huh?
Sheesh... Hey man,
you got any smokes on ya?
Nah. But those things'll
kill ya, ya know.
Are you kiddin' me?
[grunts]
Well, I'm motorin'.
Time for some ramen.
[KINJI]
Hey, let's go.
[HARUYA]
Ya headin' out?
[KINJI grunts]
Didja see that, Grandma?
That guy's head just blew up...
It's all... all over the place!
Yes, yes, of course it is...
[gasps]
[KAYO shrieks]
[KAYO]
Ryota, we have to leave!
--[HARUYA screams]
--[RYOTA] Grandma!
--Oh, Kinji! [screams]
--You're hurting me!
[KURONO]
Kato! Are you okay?!
[KATO grunting]
I... think so...
[SUZUKI ALIEN yelping]
K-Kurono...? What do we do?
Uh... Well...
[KATO] Don't come
any closer! Stay away!
[KATO groaning]
[SUZUKI ALIEN screaming]
[KATO yells]
[roars]
[KISHIMITO yelps]
What in the fuck is that...?
[SUZUKI ALIEN screeching]
[KATO]
What's happening?!
[screeching continues]
[KISHIMOTO]
What a terrible smell...
Yeah... It's awful.
[KATO]
What the hell... do we do now?!
Well, if I remember correctly,
I think Nishi... used this one.
[KURONO] It's okay...
That thing is gross,
but it's just a bird.
Just a bird!
[SUZUKI ALIEN screeching]
[KATO] What's happening?
Kei, what did you do?
[KURONO] I think it warped.
It shot it up in the air...
[KURONO]
It's... over...
Yeah... At least for now.
Nishi? Nishi!
Nishi!
[KATO]
Hey... are you okay?
It's over now! Nishi!
Can you hear my voice?!
Oh... i-i-it...
hurts... Hurts...
His ears are bleeding, too...
I guess his eardrums
must've burst.
So now we go back to that room
and get healed, right?
[KURONO] Yeah, but...
The last time, the transporting
started right away...
I don't get it.
--[NISHI rasping]
--There's something wrong...
Why isn't it
transporting us back?!
How should I know?
It doesn't make any sense.
Maybe it's not time
for us to go back.
But why not?
You mean...?
[KATO]
Maybe there are more of them.
Just like with
the Green Onion Alien!
That's what happened then!
[KURONO]
But... How can we be sure?
What about that
radar device that he had?
I bet that's it;
he should still have it.
Dammit, no good...
It's broken.
Hold on. Do you mean
one of these?
[KATO]
You mean you have one, too?
I was right. There's one more!
[HARUYA] What the fuck is going
on?! Kinji's head got blown off!
But he didn't do anything!
And he didn't even get
near that fuckin' alien!
His head blew up?!
So, when you said
we couldn't go back
till we get the other one...?
[KATO]
Yeah...
Hurry... Gantz...
I... dont... want... to die...
Um, Kato?
[KATO]
What is it?
I think... that his neck
must be broken.
[NISHI]
Cold... I'm cold...
[KISHIMOTO]
You're cold?
My spine... is severed...
I can't... feel...
The last time... my neck...
...it was...
It was... It...
Before... it was...
I'm Joichiro Nishi.
Eighth grade. And I fell.
So you... fell?
I jumped off...
from the... Gonna die...
[KISHIMOTO]
Then... you mean that you...
I... I'm dying...
This is bad... So dark...
[NISHI] I don't...
wanna die... not so soon...
[NISHI whimpers]
I'm not... ready to... die yet.
Don't give up on life
so fast, please!
Never say you're
gonna die! Never!
[KURONO] That's right.
She must understand how he feels
more than anybody else...
[NISHI]
I never...
I never... hated anyone...
I-I just hated society...
because... it's all fucked up.
I always felt... that... I
needed to stay on track...
But it's all...
fucked... up...
That's why I could never...
stay on track...
I-I... don't wanna die...
Mom... Mom?
I-I-I have to
apologize to her...
Mom... I'm sorry... [sobs]
Mom, I tried hard, but...
Oh, Mom, I'm sorry!
Oh, Mom, I'm so sorry!
[NISHI] Mom... I'm so scared...
Mama... Mama, I'm cold... I'm so
cold, Mama... I'm gonna die...
Just... wanted to hang on...
long enough...
Just... a li-little longer...
So close. So close...
[HARUYA]
Hey, answer me!
Is there any way
we can get outta this?!
Shut up!
How can you be so damn
selfish
while he's laying there
like that?! Look at him!
Mama... 100 points...
My score was... I had 90
points... 90 points...
I just... I just needed
ten more to be free...
[NISHI whimpers]
I was so close, Mama...
[KATO]
He's... dead.
[HARUYA] You probably
think we're idiots, huh?
Well, no big deal, but listen:
Now I'm running
things around here.
You wanna get shot, Testuo?!
Next time on GANTZ :
"Kato, You Wait Here."