[REPORTER] It's already been
a week since Ratenin Temple,
previously located in
this quiet neighborhood,
was suddenly destroyed
by unknown means.
According to police statements,
the details behind
this incident remain unclear,
with the only lead at this point
being the bodies of two homeless
men found behind the temple.
[KIDS giggling]
[KID A]
Let's go down to the canal!
[KID B]
Yeah! Let's throw stuff in it!
[KID A] My mom is
waiting there! Come on!
[KID B]
Hey, wait for me!
[GIRL]
Hey! Let's drink tea!
[GIRL moaning]
In any case, I don't
know what my other self
is going to do from now on...
But this girl here is just
going to live her own life.
[FURUTA] How many times do I
have to catch you?!
Come back here!
Come back, you little shit!
[WOMAN A panting]
Uh... is there something wrong?
[WOMAN B]
You fucking cunt!
[YOSHINO gasping, whimpering]
[WOMAN B snarls]
[growls]
--[BOY screaming]
--[MOTHER] Help me!
Someone, help me!
[screaming continues]
[MOTHER]
Manabu! Somebody help! Manabu!
Hang on, baby! Hang on!
[BUSINESSMAN yelps]
[BUSINESSMAN]
Aw, dammit!
[COLLECTOR A]
There he is!
[MAN grunts]
[BUSINESSMAN gasps]
Hey! Wrong way!
[MUROTO]
♪ Oh, it's the beginning ♪
♪ of a brand-new day...
A day filled with hope. ♪
[KAJIURA]
Hey-Hey, you little psycho.
Don't kill her
just yet, all right?
Heh.
[shutter clicks]
You know, they make
no bread when they're dead.
[MUROTO] Eh, this cunt's
already tapped out.
[KAJIURA] Guess we'll
just have to find ourselves
another runaway then, huh?
[gasps]
Oh, shit!
[SEI] We'll pick up that book
together, Kei, all right?!
I'm going to win,
and then we'll go home!
Together!
[KEI groans]
[TEENAGER groans]
[MANABU coughs]
[MOTHER gasps]
[MOTHER]
Manabu! [sobs]
[TEENAGER] Come on, lady! Gimme
a hand here!
[TEENAGER grunts]
[MOTHER sobs]
[screams]
[STALKER grunting]
[WOMAN A screams]
[WOMAN A groans]
[WOMAN C] Hmph. It's like I was
saying the other day--
There's nothing you can do about
that.
You have to think more about
other people.
[FURUTA panting]
[FURUTA] Hey! Look out! Hey!
Come back here!
[laughs, gasps]
[FURUTA screams]
[gunshots]
[KAJIURA groans]
[MUROTO gasps]
[WOMAN B] I'll fucking kill you,
you bitch!
[YOSHINO gasping]
[grunts]
[ANNOUNCER] The express train
will be passing through
the station on platform 2.
Please remain behind
the yellow line.
[BUSINESSMAN panting]
[COLLECTOR A]
You little shit!
You're not getting
away this time!
[BUSINESSMAN screams]
[KATO] Remember,
the Gantz always attacks
us in ways we can't predict.
Therefore, we have to
fight all of its attacks.
Eliminate every adversary
it puts in front of us.
[KATO] That's the only way
we'll be able to survive.
Here comes another one!
Huh...?
Hey! Don't I know you?
Huh?!
You came to my bookstore...
This afternoon, right?
Yeah... that's right.
[FURUTA]
Well, let's have a look-see here
in the backorder file for
Miranda Foster's Labyrinth .
Okay, here it is.
Hold on... Wait a minute.
You didn't place this order,
did you, young man?
No, it was ordered
by Sei... Sakuraoka.
So you're picking it up for a
friend, are you? Is that right?
Well, uh...
Well, if we do
get out of this...
...how'd you like
to go out with me?
Yeah... She's a friend.
Promise we'll still take
that drive together...
She...
[SEI] There's a book...
A book that I ordered
by Miranda Foster
called Labyrinth .
It's supposed to
come in next week
over in the bookstore
by the train station.
[KURONO]
Huh...?
Kei, if something does happen,
would you... do that for me?
[KURONO]
Look, has it come in yet?
[FURUTA]
Hmm...
I'm sorry it's not in, but it
should be in by tomorrow.
[KURONO]
Oh... Okay...
Also, I'm afraid I can't
give you a special order
unless I check with the person
who ordered it first.
But it's not like
I don't trust you, you know?
Hang on a second. I'll just
give the nice lady a call
at the number she left us.
Hang on!
[FURUTA]
Yes?
I don't think...
you can reach her
at the number
she left you to call.
Just forget it, okay?
So you're...
[YOSHINO]
Hey. You're Kurono, aren't you?
[KURONO] What the fuck?!
Now my teacher's dead?!
Just what are you doing here?
And in that outfit!
It's not easy
to explain all this.
[YOSHINO] Huh? You mean
you know what's going on?
Yeah, I do.
Let's start with your affair.
[gasps]
[YOSHINO] You really are
a pervert, aren't you?!
That's not what I meant!
Tell me what's going on here!
[KURONO] I could, but you're not
gonna understand any of it!
[WOMAN A] Huh...? Have I seen
him somewhere before...?
--Huh?
--Huh...?
[KAJIURA] Hey, it looks
like it stopped raining,
so why don't we all
get outta here?
I mean, what's the
point in staying?
Yeah, this place sucks.
[gasps]
[KURONO] Oh, shit! It's them!
What the fuck are
they doing here?!
[KATO] Why?! What in the hell
have we been fighting for?!
This man was killed, and his
only crime was being homeless!
We've suffered and bled
for this stupid game,
but what kind of a place are
we fighting to get back to?!
[KURONO] Those sons of bitches
are still alive!
No, they're standing
right in front of me,
which means they're dead,
but--it isn't fair!
How could Sei and Kato be gone
and these bastards
here in their place?!
Instead of Kishimoto, goddammit!
[KURONO gasps]
Hold up! Wait, please.
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh?
Uh...
Do you want something?
Well, I've never done something
like this before, but...
Uh... I kind of like you, and...
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
Please wait!
[KISHIMOTO]
Are you... hitting on me?
Uh, no. It's just... I usually
don't do stuff like this...
I mean, I...
[KISHIMOTO]
What's your name?
Uh--
You have one, don't you?
Uh... Um... Kurono. Kei Kurono.
It's Kei?
Yeah. Just like yours, right?
[gasps]
Hang on... And just exactly
how do you know my name is Kei?
[KURONO]
Uh... Um...
[KISHIMOTO]
Do you know my last name?
[KURONO]
It's Kishimoto.
[gasps]
[KURONO]
Wait!
[KISHIMOTO]
Mom! Mom!
[KURONO]
Wait!
You look exactly like this girl
I used to live with!
This girl I knew used to live
with me at my apartment.
She was great and...
I liked her, but...
But then she...
One day, she was killed.
And I... look like her...?
And have the same name...?
That's just creepy!
Let alone impossible!
[KURONO]
Yeah... You're right.
It sounds creepy as hell.
[train horn blares]
--[YOSHINO] Kurono!
--[gasps]
If you know
what's going on here,
just explain it to us now.
And not one more word
about my affair, got it?
[KURONO] I can't explain it
as well as Kato did.
Well, let's see...
That black ball is gonna open
and there'll be all
these weapons inside.
[BUSINESSMAN]
Weapons?
[FURUTA]
What do you mean, "weapons"?
Big guns.
You mean the real kind
you shoot people with?
[KURONO]
Yeah.
Kurono, what are
you talking about?
That doesn't make any sense.
No, what doesn't make sense
is that it'll tell us
to go out and kill some aliens,
and we'll go out and do it.
[BUSINESSMAN]
Huh?
Oh, please.
You're talking about some
dumb-ass roleplaying game shit,
--ain'tcha kid?
--[chuckles]
I'm sorry to interrupt this
fascinating conversation,
but I think it's time
to go home now.
I'm not lying.
And if we don't
kill them, we die.
Um, now that you mention it,
didn't we all come to this place
after... uh... passing away?
But no matter how you look at
it, we're obviously alive now.
[TEENAGER] Yeah, man.
I can see Tokyo Tower.
That's right.
It's rather hard to think
that we're actually dead.
So, what's really
going on here, Kurono?
I told you.
[KURONO] Dammit, Kato,
I'm not good at this kinda shit.
What should I do next?
They don't believe me!
[FURUTA]
Look, why don't we just go ahead
and introduce ourselves.
We could explain how we died,
the circumstances, the places,
and whatnot, and then
we might be able to piece
all this together, right?
I'll even go first, okay?
I'm Giichi Furuta, age 50.
I run a bookstore
by the train station.
--And I died when I was hit by--
--But did you really die?
How should I know?! That's why
we're trying to get to
the bottom of this whole mess!
Anyway, I died in a car
accident. I got hit by a car
while I was chasing a
shoplifter. So who's next?
How 'bout you? The one
who was having the affair.
Who, me?
This is the only way
to find out the truth.
You don't need to go
into any sorta details.
Yoshino Uehara. I'm 26.
[KURONO] What?! You're 29 if
you're a day, you fuckin' liar!
[YOSHINO]
I teach high school mathematics,
and I'm also his
homeroom teacher.
His name is Kurono, a tenth
grader, and a poor student.
And how did you die?
Uh... Well, that's really...
kinda touchy...
I think I got stabbed,
but I'm not sure.
[KURONO]
Because you were
porking someone else's
husband maybe?
I'm Daichi Nozaki,
and I drowned.
[FURUTA]
And you're how old?
Seventeen. Unemployed.
Well, in that case,
shouldn't you be in school?
[NOZAKI] That's none of your
goddamn business, is it, baldy?!
Ryuji Kajiura.
Twenty-eight years old.
I do some odd jobs
here and there.
The kid's Hajime Muroto. He's
16. I'm... taking care of him.
I guess you could say
that I'm his guardian.
I'm pleased to
meet you, everyone.
[KURONO]
He's my age?
[MUROTO] I died in an accident.
A car accident.
Oh, the same as me, huh?
Do you suppose that
they could be related?
[FURUTA]
Hmm... well...
Um, can I say something here?
[FURUTA]
Sure, go ahead.
I've got the feeling that
maybe we really are dead,
and I've got proof.
For months, I've been
followed by some guy
who's been stalking me. He
stabbed me a little while ago.
When he attacked me,
I fought as hard as I could,
but his knife...
Look at this book.
[gasping]
His knife must've gone through
the book when he stabbed me.
Isn't that some kind of proof?
I know it's just a book, but...
But if I'm not dead,
then why would I be
carrying something like this
around with me?
Oh, and I'm Miki Kanda.
I'm 20 and a college student.
Ah... So in that case,
we would have a total of
two car accidents--no, make that
three car accidents--
two stabbings, and a drowning.
I wonder if the car accidents
and the stabbings
are connected somehow.
[YOSHINO] What about you,
Kurono? How did you end up here?
A few weeks ago,
I got hit by a subway train.
Kurono, you've been at
school every single day!
That can't be possible.
Now, stop this outrageous lying!
I'm telling the truth!
And didn't I tell you that
you wouldn't understand it?!
[BUSINESSMAN] Um, excuse me,
but I should mention
that I jumped in front
of a subway train, too.
[gasps]
Um, my name's Naozumi Saito.
I just turned 38,
and up until last year,
was employed by one of Japan's
most prestigious banks.
Well, it's kind of embarrassing,
but I got rightsized, so I
started a business of my own,
and got into debt.
Well, a pair of bill
collectors were after me,
so I jumped off the platform
in front of the express.
But since I've been here, I
mean, aside from wondering about
what's really going on,
I'm actually kinda relieved.
All I care about is that
I don't have to run
from those
bill collectors anymore.
I shoulda done it months ago!
[gasps]
[screams]
[SAITO]
Of course, the weirdest thing is
how calm I feel about it.
You! Wipe that
smile off your face!
[SAITO]
W-W-What the...?
I'm sick of listening to you!
It makes me sick!
Wh... Are you crazy?!
Leave him alone, Kurono!
Knock it off!
[SAITO whimpers]
Kurono! I want you to put
that man down, right now!
You killed yourself,
didn't you, you coward?!
Yeah, sure! I guess so.
Well, you got your fucking wish.
But as everyone who comes
in here gets killed,
every single one of 'em,
you have no idea how many!
Some of them got here by
killing themselves like you,
but they changed! They tried
to find a way back, but...
...they still died!
They tried to escape!
To find a way out!
But they all died anyway!
From now on, you keep
your fucking mouth shut!
You got that?!
Right! I apologize! [yelps]
[KURONO] Whether you wanna
believe it or not,
a massacre is about to begin.
And when it does start,
I guarantee that some
of us are going to die.
I thought we were already dead.
[KURONO]
Shut up! Shut up and listen!
If you wanna survive, I can try
to help you!
But I can't help you unless
you're prepared.
Okay. So we just have to follow
your lead on this, right?
[KURONO]
Uh... Yeah.
Well, now... I'll be the first
to admit
I don't understand all this,
but I don't think
he's making it up.
All right then, Kurono.
Now, I'm not saying
I'm buying this completely,
but just to be sure, what should
we expect to happen next?
Let's see... First--
[music starts playing]
[gasping]
All right, Gantz.
What alien is it now?!
No matter what you bring on,
I'll fucking kill it!
Come on, show me now!
Which alien is it, Gantz?!
[gasping]
What in the fuck...?
Me?
That can't be right!
[NOZAKI] Okay, it's not like
he's done anything bad.
He did tell us
about the weapons,
the aliens, and everything.
But... it looks like
we won't be able to go home
unless we kill this guy, right?
Next episode, "Kurono Alien."