[KURONO]
Drop your stuff!
[KATO]
I've got to keep the umbrella!
[KURONO]
Huh?! Are you out of your mind?!
[KATO]
It's for my kid brother!
He went to school without one!
Oh, fu--!
Wouldn't you love...
to kill him?
[KURONO gasps]
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh...?
[gasps]
[NISHI]
C'mon, hurry it up!
[NISHI] He had no problem
killing the others, right?
Including your
boyfriend over there.
Just look...
No!
[KURONO whimpers]
[yells]
[NISHI] C'mon!
What're you waiting for?!
Are you some kind of pinhead?
He's not human.
He's more like...
a dangerous animal
and you're doing
a public service.
And the suit makes it feel
all the better right?
Don't deny it. You can do
all these amazing moves.
It feels good...
[KURONO]
You saw that? You were there?
[NISHI] I told you
I was hangin' out.
I saw you goin' at it.
It feels good destroying
things, doesn't it?
The suit makes
you feel stronger.
[KURONO]
What the hell are you implying?!
[NISHI]
Oh, come on! Just admit it.
Beating the crap out of
this creep felt awesome.
It was better
than sex, wasn't it?!
[KURONO] Oh no...
Don't look at me like that.
Stop looking at me! Please...
That isn't true!
I-It wasn't like that!
It turned you on, didn't it?
How 'bout corpses? Pictures...?
I'm not like that you freak!
I may buy girlie mags and
watch porn, but that's it!
All that crap
you're talking about
is way too sick
and twisted for me!
Oh, god, what am I saying?!
[NISHI]
Yep. Knew it.
I could see it.
In your eyes from the moment
I first saw you across the room.
You're just like me...
Deep down you really
wanna see it.
[NISHI]
So here's your chance.
The real thing.
Death.
[KURONO]
No. I don't...
I... don't...
I do not!
You lie.
And don't compare me to you.
All that's different is
that you're in denial.
Just another hypocrite.
[KURONO]
A hypocrite?
I'm not sure what you mean...
...but I sure as hell
don't want someone like you
calling me that,
you sick, little freak!
I guess you're not as
smart as I thought you were.
What a disappointment.
At least my view of the world
didn't come out of comic
books and video games.
You're living in a fantasy!
You just don't get it, do you?
If I were like that, I wouldn't
have survived in this world
for as long as I have...
[KURONO]
What does that mean?
[NISHI]
Oh... nothing.
[KURONO]
Oh yeah. Play dumb, again!
That's what you do whenever
something's important, isn't it?
[NISHI]
Not really.
Okay, to prove that
I'm not caught up in
that stupid fantasy crap,
let's talk about
something that's real.
Just... what do
you mean by real?
For example, let's say
that there's someone
about to die right
before your eyes.
Someone who there's no point
in even trying to rescue
because they're going
to die at any moment.
That's something that
we could all witness
in our everyday lives, right?
Perhaps in something
like a horrible
traffic or train accident.
Now, in that situation, what's
the first thing you think of?
That you've got to find
a way to rescue them?
Yeah, right.
You're first thought is
"I might be able to
see someone die today."
And it's not just freaks who
think that way; it's everybody.
It doesn't matter whether
it's a plane crash or a war.
When you see that
stuff on the news
your heart is
pounding, isn't it?
Why is it, I wonder...
that the news programs ratings
always go up when they
run stories like that?
It's because it's
just human nature.
They're all secretly
hoping they'll get a chance
to see a dead body.
It's an excitement
that defies all logic.
You're sick!
A sick little freak!
[NISHI]
Like I care...
You see, when I jumped,
I realized that it's
all the same in the end.
[KURONO] If this is the
way it's gotta be...
[NISHI]
You know I'm right, don't you?
In the end even
death is no big deal.
And I'm perfectly
fine with that.
Sure you are!
But you're only able
to talk so tough
because you're still alive!
And what makes you
think we're alive?
[NISHI] It just doesn't
make a difference.
I really was going let
you score the points
for shooting him, you know...
[NISHI]
Oh well. Whatever.
[yelling]
[NISHI] Strangely beautiful,
don't you think?
This is what death is like.
[NISHI]
The gun that transports them...
...is the gun that kills them.
Transports them? But, where?
[NISHI]
Where? Somewhere there.
[KURONO]
So, you know all about this?
Well, I don't know everything.
But, I know more than you.
Oh, do you. So what's next?
[NISHI]
First we return to the room.
[KURONO]
And then what?
[NISHI]
Then you're free to go.
You can even go
home if you like.
[KURONO gasps]
We can go home?! You mean,
we're not really dead?
[NISHI]
No, we're alive.
Just wait, you'll see.
[KURONO]
We can go home?!
We can really go home?!
I didn't--
[KISHIMOTO whimpers]
No! Kato!
Hold on please!
Kato!
[KURONO] Nishi! We were
brought back once! Can't we--
I'm sorry.
But only those who're still
alive at the end of the mission
can return to the room.
[KURONO] But-But if he's
not-not dead yet! Kato! Kato!
[KISHIMOTO]
Kato, please!
Did you hear him?
We can go home!
It's over!
[KURONO]
God. Listen to her.
And this is a girl
who puked on me!
[NISHI]
Hey, he's a lost cause.
No, he's not!
Actually, the sad thing is,
it doesn't matter how badly
your body's been hurt
if you survive the game.
If you make it back alive,
it's all fixed.
Yeah, right!
Fine then, you don't
have to believe me.
[KISHIMOTO]
Please Kato, get up!
[KURONO]
Come on, Kato! Wake up!
[gasps]
See ya 'round!
[KURONO] Damn it!
C'mon, Kato! Hang in there!
--[KURONO] Kato, C'mon!
--[KISHIMOTO] Kato! Talk to me!
Kato! Kato!
We can all come back together!
Kato!
Kato! Kato, please!
[KISHIMOTO]
Kato!
[sobbing]
[KURONO]
Kato!
[KURONO, KISHIMOTO sob]
[NISHI]
Hey! You guys did pretty good.
It's been a long time
since anyone besides me
made it back here alive.
Hey, we made it back,
so show us our scores!
You're ignoring me? Huh?
[KURONO gasps]
Dog...?
Oh yeah, he always
comes back as well,
useless little sack o' shit.
[DOG whines]
Ah! Hey! No!
[whimpers]
[KISHIMOTO]
Cut it out!
[KISHIMOTO whimpers]
Kato...
He can't be...
[NISHI]
So, Big Tits, tell me somthing.
Would you normally fall
for someone this fast?
I haven't fallen for anyone.
Oh, like hell you haven't. Damn!
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
It's Kato. It is! Isn't it?
Yeah! I... think it is!
I cant tell by his height.
Oh, give me a break!
Another survivor?!
[gasps]
[KATO]
K-Kei?
Hey! What happened to me?
And where'd the alien go?
Don't worry. He's gone.
And that means that
we can go home!
We can go?
We can really go?
[KISHIMOTO]
Kato... I...
[sighs]
--[bell dings]
--[gasps]
[NISHI]
It's about time.
Gantz is going to
give us our scores now.
[KURONO]
Huh? What's Gantz?
And it's giving us what?
So the sphere's name is Gantz?
Did you give it that name?
Nah, it's always been Gantz...
And you know this because...?
Because, that's what the
ones before me called it...
[KURONO gasps]
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
[KISHIMOTO]
Is that supposed to be me?
Hey! Boobs?! And no points?
I think this thing is
trying to piss me off!
[KATO]
Uh? Kato-cha?
[KURONO]
It likes puns...
Lame ones.
So it's deliberately
trying to be funny?
It's weird, but for some reason
I can't wait for my score.
[KURONO]
Three points? Is that good?
[NISHI scoffs]
Only three points?
[KURONO]
Okay, okay. Where's mine?
[KURONO gasps]
What the--
You've been looking at her
and getting stiffies, huh?
[KISHIMOTO]
Ew!
[KURONO stutters]
For shame...
But it's not true!
Huh?
That's... it?
[KURONO gasps]
[KURONO] Hey, where do
you think you're going?
The door's been unlocked
and I'm leaving now.
Oh, no you don't.
Before you walk out of here,
you're going to tell us
everything that's going on.
That's right.
You owe us some explanations.
Yeah.
[NISHI]
All right.
If you keep the
questions to what I know.
[KURUNO] And no bullshit
this time, got it?
Fire away.
[KURUNO]
Oh! Ok. Let's see...
Well, what the
hell's goin' on here?
Too vague! Next!
Uh. Wait a second.
I guess what I meant was...
Why did all this happen?
Sorry. I don't know
the answer to that.
We're not buying that,
you psycho!
Just what is your game here?
You said "fire away,"
didn't you?!
I can't answer vague
questions like that
because I only know limited
details about the situation.
Then why do you know so much?
Exactly who in the hell are you?
Moi?
Well, I'm... an alien.
[gasps]
[KURONO]
You're full of it.
[NISHI laughs]
[NISHI]
Yes, you're right.
[KURUNO]
Why you--!
The truth is I'm just an
ordinary middle school student.
I first came to this
room a year ago.
Don't you see?
C'mon, use your imagination!
The truth is... that I don't
know when this was all started,
but I've had to live through
many nights like this.
And long before I came here,
this room was bringing people
together a few at a time,
people who should've
been dead by all accounts.
And if they happen to die
during the course of a mission,
it brings in others
to replace them.
In the year since my first game,
I've seen dozens like you die.
I've seen people die in
the most spectacular ways.
While I've managed to
survive through it all.
[NISHI] Oh, Gantz! Show them
all the people who've died.
[NISHI]
Hey, Gantz!
Listen to me when
I'm talkin' to you!
[NISHI grunts]
[NISHI]
Okay. Look at the bottom row.
Do ya see 'em?
Those are the guys
who died tonight.
[sighs]
[NISHI] They were a particularly
dumb bunch, of course.
But you fortunately were
different from them.
You realized the importance
of the suit as if by instinct,
and that's why you survived.
[KURUNO] It's his
calmness pisses me off.
Is he really still--?
[KATO]
So why didn't you tell us?!
If you had explained all
of this at the beginning,
then more of us
might have survived!
In fact you intentionally fed us
a story that was
completely false!
[gasps]
[KURUNO]
Yeah, he has a point.
Why didn't you tell
us what was going on?
Yeah! Why didn't you?!
[KATO grunts]
I want answers.
Because I knew that
while they were dying,
the target would drop its guard.
[gasps, grunts]
[whimpering]
Monster! Those were human
beings who got killed!
How could you just
stand by and watch?!
[NISHI] Hey, it's not my problem
whether they live or die.
[gasps]
I know what you're thinking.
You really wanna
hit me, don't you?
God, you reek of hypocrisy!
Out of the three of you,
you're the worst!
You're a hypocrite.
Hypocrite!
[KATO grunts]
Go on, Kato! Smash his
snotty little face in!
Kick his ass!
[NISHI]
Oh, come on!
You guys really are
complete and total idiots.
And you just don't
you get it, do you?
The fact is that I'm
the strongest one here!
[KATO screams]
I was cluing you in out of
the goodness of my heart,
and this is the way
you decide to treat me?
Don't you think there's
something very wrong
with that scenario?
Maybe I should crush your arm.
That way you'll
know who to follow!
[gun clicks]
Let him go now!
Kei, don't!
Let go of him, please!
If you shoot, it'll be
your head that explodes.
[KURUNO]
Okay, then. How about this?
An arm for an arm.
Next question. A while ago,
you said that we were alive.
But, if we were alive, then
why couldn't anyone see us,
or anyting that we did.
It was like we were ghosts.
So, I'm going to ask you
once more. Are we really alive?
[NISHI]
Yes, we are.
You're not shitting us?
The people who come here
were rescued just moments
before they were
supposed to die.
Is that what you want me to say?
Is it true?
[NISHI] It could be. The way
I see it, there was a person,
an original. But that
original really is dead.
[ALL gasp]
And everyone who
comes to this room,
comes out of something
like a human fax machine.
And... the originals. Are they--
[NISHI]
Oh. And when you go home...
...you shouldn't talk
to anybody about this.
--[KISHIMOTO] He's gone!
--[KATO, KURONO gasp]
[NISHI laughs]
[NISHI] They wouldn't
believe you anyway.
[laughing continues]
[WOMAN ON TV laughs]
Oh! Next question please!
[laughing continues]
[phone beeping]
[dial tone]
[KURUNO]
Hi, Mom.
Money?
Oh, no. I'm fine.
Uh... What?
No.
It's nothing.
[gasps]
[phone clicks]
[dial tone]
[phone beeps]
[TV ANNOUNCER]
And now, this morning's news.
A forty year old woman gives
birth via Caesarean section
but dies of from shock and loss
of blood. More on this later.
[KURONO]
Was it just a dream?
There's no way it
could've been real.
[TV ANNOUNCER] In other news,
a member of the Lower House
of Parliament died last
night in a Tokyo hospital.
Goro Suzuki was a veteran
member of Parliament,
five times elected
to the Lower House,
since the end of last year
he'd been hospitalized
for liver cancer.
--[KURONO gasps]
--A date for the special
election to replace
Mr. Suzuki's parlimentary seat
has not yet been announced.
[KURONO]
It... had to be a dream.
[TV ANNOUNCER] ...intersection
of the Oume Highway and Loop 8,
a tragic collision between
a scooter and a compact car
left a local teacher dead.
Masashi Yamada, an
elementary school teacher,
was killed instantly...
This is a real-live mystery.
Two high school
boys have vanished
under mysterious circumstances
while in front of a
crowd of witnesses.
They say the two rescued a
homeless man from the tracks
and were apparently...
[KURONO] My umbrella! If it's
here then-- Yeah! A dream!
It must have been!
...the Tokyo Metropolitan Police
Department is investigating
the case. Back to you, Mori.
Yes. Thank you, June. And now
for an update on the weather,
we turn to our friendly
neighborhood weatherman...
[gasps]
[KURONO]
No way!
[gasps]
It wasn't a dream.
[KURUNO] Sex. Violence. All I
know is that she had to change.
To get that way...
Her clothes, I mean--
Which means she was...
[KURONO sighs]