[REPORTER]
This morning, once again,
we have a special follow-up
on those two missing
high school boys.
[AYUMU]
Okay, see you later!
[KATO]
See ya!
[AYUMU laughs]
[REPORTER] The two boys
suddenly disappeared
in the subway.
Since then, we've been
looking into this incident
from every possible angle.
However, the identities of the
two missing high school boys
have yet to be determined.
If you want to know my opinion
of most of these high school
students today...
...they're nothing more
than a bunch of
good-for-nothing degenerates!
Two punks disappear, and now
that's all they can talk about!
It's outrageous!
Simply dreadful.
[REPORTER] However,
we believe that by tracing
the sales receipts of
the adult magazine...
[KATO'S AUNT]
And I'd better not find out
that you're up to
anything strange like that.
I refuse to let you bring
that kind of shame
down on this house.
[KATO]
Excuse me...
[KATO] Could we
please eat something now?
[KATO'S AUNT]
What?! Don't make me laugh!
Do you have any idea why
I made you sit down there?!
This little monster tracked
mud on my carpet yesterday!
It took me half
the day to get it out,
--so why should I cook for you?!
--[KATO] Stop it!
There's no way that his socks
could've been that dirty!
Don't you talk back to me!
You free-loading punks!
[KATO growls]
[KATO'S AUNT gasps]
Let go of me!
Why are you looking
at me like that?!
Look, you can do
whatever you want to me...
...but let my little brother
have some breakfast!
I told you to let go of me!
Take your hands off me now!
I'll let you go this time...
But first, I want you to promise
me that you won't ever
hit my little brother again.
How dare you?!
This is my house, and if you
don't like it, you can get out!
[REPORTER]
Stay tuned to this station
for information on new
developments as they occur.
[AYUMU] So my brother said
he'd make me a new one...
[KATO]
Ayumu...
Your brother's no good at all...
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
[KURONO]
What's with her?
[KISHIMOTO]
So... Is this okay?
[KURONO] What?
You want that for breakfast?
[KISHIMOTO]
Well...
You've at least gotta eat some
bread or chips or something.
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
Look, it's only pet food,
after all. This'll be fine.
[KURONO sighs]
Well, it's not fine with me.
[KISHIMOTO]
Please, you don't have to...
[KURONO]
Don't worry.
Do you have enough money?
What?
Kurono, how are we
supposed to pay for it?
Aren't you almost out of cash?
[KURONO]
That was a damn good point,
but she didn't have to
be so harsh about it...
Hey, don't worry. I've got it.
Yeah, right.
[OLD LADY] Excuse me...
Could you show me
the way to Hinodedai?
Huh?
Which platform should I take?
You... No fuckin' way!
[OLD LADY]
You can have these for free...
...if you point me to
the right platform.
Where do I go?
[KISHIMOTO]
Hey! Kurono!
[sighs]
What's the matter?
Found it!
[KISHIMOTO]
Hey, wait, isn't that...?
Look, just hold your questions,
okay? There's no time.
Huh? Time for what?
[KURONO]
That old bag...
When we got called to
that apartment the other day,
she kept trying to talk to me!
Didn't you see her?
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh?
[KURONO] I think we'll be
getting a call from Gantz soon.
Anyway, we have to learn
how to use these
so we'll be ready
no matter what.
[KISHIMOTO whimpers]
[grunts]
[KISHIMOTO]
Kurono...
I'd really rather not look
at your pale behind
while I'm eating.
Uh... Sorry about that?
[chuckles]
[RYOTA]
Hey, Grandma! Let me do it!
All right, darling,
if you think you can.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know how to do it!
Here you go...
[RYOTA chuckles]
[RYOTA]
Grandma, which button do I push?
[KAYO]
Oh, my...
[RYOTA]
Grandma!
[KAYO]
Well, let's see...
Oh... Well... Oh, yes!
That's the button right there!
This one?
Lady, I'm in a little
bit of a hurry here.
I'm sorry. We won't be much
longer, now, will we?
Here, here, push this one...
[KAYO] Oh, dear...
You pushed the wrong one!
Let's try again.
What's wrong with that one?!
Um, why don't you let me give
you a hand with that, okay?
Where do you need to go?
[KAYO]
Oh! We're going to Hinodedai.
[SAITO] Ah, okay,
then this is your button.
Thank you so much for your help!
[SAITO]
Oh, no, it's my pleasure...
[KAYO]
Oh, dear. Nothing's coming out.
[RYOTA] Grandma, you have
to put more money in.
[KAYO]
Oh, goodness gracious!
[BUSINESSMAN]
Hey, lady! Move it!
I'm sorry. I think
they're almost finshed.
[CROWD yelling, moaning]
[WORKER]
Hey, check out the ta-tas...
[HARUYA] So, Testu,
I'm thinking it's about time
for me to get a bigger one.
[TETSUO]
A bigger what?
[HARUYA]
Bike, dipshit!
When a biker says a bigger one,
he means a bike!
[TETSUO sighs]
[HARUYA] I thought
I could break the engine in
before the Hachioji race
on New Year's Eve.
[TETSUO]
Uh-huh...
[HARUYA]
Hey, I'm serious, dammit!
[TETSUO] I didn't say
you were lying, did I?
[HARUYA] Fuck, Tetsu!
What's up with you these days?!
Huh?
Since you had that kid,
you've been acting like a pussy.
D'ow! Shit! Fuck, man!
What the fuck?!
What the fuck is your problem?!
[TETSUO] I'll tell you
what my problem is!
It's your big,
fat mouth, fat ass!
So who's the pussy now?!
Go on. I dare ya to say it.
Jeez, it was just a joke, Tetsu!
Hey, Kosuke, I guess it's time
we got off of Tetsu's
old lady, huh?
Yeah, but you know, if he'd
gotten off her a little sooner,
He wouldn't be playing
"Biker Daddy."
[BOTH laugh]
[TETSUO]
Hey, asshole!
What the fuck's wrong...
with a biker...
...having a kid, huh?!
Yo, what in the fuck's
wrong with you, man?!
Calm down, Tetsu!
We're just kidding!
[TETSUO]
Hmph.
[FOREMAN]
Hey, ladies?!
Break time's over!
Get back to work!
[KINJI and KOSUKE]
Yessir...
[KURONO]
Huh...?
[KISHIMOTO]
Um... Is this right?
Yeah, that's it! I mean,
that looks just fine.
[KURONO] Wow, I bet those guys
who go to those cosplay sites
would cream their
jeans over this!
[KISHIMOTO]
Uh, is there something wrong?
[KURONO]
N-No, nothing.
But, uh, you haven't worn one
of these before, have you?
[KISHIMOTO]
N-No...
Well, um, they're pretty
important, y'see...
Because when you have
one of those suits on,
I think your chances of
survival go way up.
So, you need to get
used to wearing one.
[KISHIMOTO]
Well, how does it work?
Well, uh...
You do know, right?
Uh...
[KURONO]
I-I can't tell her that...
Well, Kurono, how do I use it?
Well, you just...put it on...
And then I guess you just
give it your all, you see?
At least I...
think that's all...?
If that's all it takes, couldn't
you have just said that
instead of making
me change clothes?
Oh, well...
You gotta point there...
Hey!
I think you just wanted to watch
me undress, you little perv!
Ugh! I am not a perv!
And I've gotta get to school.
What? You're going?
Yeah, do I have a choice?
[sighs]
I'm jealous...
Of what?
At least you can go to school...
You know, if I was you,
I'd be glad I didn't have to go.
[KISHIMOTO] Yeah, but...
You only think that way
because you can go.
[gasps]
[KISHIMOTO]
Can I...
...maybe meet you somewhere
after school's over?
[KURONO]
Could this be my lucky day?!
[KISHIMOTO sighs] There's
someplace I need to go...
[KURONO] All right!
I'll go wherever you want!
Dinner? A movie? Or...
[KURONO chuckles]
I just want to see the place
where I used to live again...
Huh?!
And I want to see how the
other me... is doing now...
[KURONO]
That's what she wants to do...?
It that too weird?
No. You're as normal as I am.
[KISHIMOTO]
Hmm. You're not so bad.
[KURONO sighs]
[STUDENT A]
I'm sorry... I'm sorry!
[DELINQUENT A]
You'll be worse than sorry, kid!
[DELINQUENT B] So, what
do think we do with him, huh?
I got it. Let's pants
the little bitch.
Ah...!
You heard me. Drop 'em, now!
But I said I'm sorry!
[DELINQUENT B]
Stop whining...
It's not like you have
anything to show.
Come on, guys!
Don't do this!
Please, stop! Stop it!
Oh, let me go!
Huh?
Hey, Kato!
[DELINQUENT A]
Hmph!
[DELINQUENT B] Ugh,
I think we gotta get to class.
[STUDENT A]
Thanks, you saved my life!
No problem...
I didn't know what to do.
I thought those guys
were gonna kill me.
Let's go in...
Class is gonna start.
[STUDENT A]
Yeah...
[DELINQUENT B]
Man, we gotta do somethin'
about that tenth grader.
[DELINQUENT A]
No shit, asshole.
[DELINQUENT C]
Well, then, let's get to it.
[DELINQUENT B]
Today?
[DELINQUENT A]
Yeah, today.
[DELINQUENT B] Let's hit
him in the head with a bat,
and everyone take turns
wailing on him!
[DELINQUENT C] Yeah,
then we'll strip him down...
[DELINQUENT A]
Huh?! Why would we do that?
[DELINQUENT B]
To shove the mop up his ass!
[DELINQUENTS laugh]
So, uh, does this guy
have a pretty face?
Onizuka!
Hey, dude, this is the
eleventh graders' john!
I could... fuck his ass good.
And I've shit wherever I've
pleased since the tenth grade.
So, just who is this
mothafucka anyway?
Oh, he's a real fuckin' nut-job.
The one who's always
hanging out with the nerds.
Oh, so he's the wimpy type, huh?
No, he's fuckin' huge.
I'd say the bastard's
well over six foot tall.
I tell you one thing, he doesn't
scare easy, that's for sure.
Then his ass is mine.
Count on it.
[STUDENT A]
Hah! [laughs]
Oh, man...
[DELINQUENT A]
Yo! Kato!
[KATO]
Huh ?
We got business. Come on!
[KATO]
So... What do you want with me?
There's a bunch of eleventh
and twelfth graders
that are planning on jumping
you after school today.
And one of the twelfth graders
is a heavyweight boxer,
who just so happens
to be queer...
He says he's gonna fuck you.
I thought you should know.
[STUDENT A]
O-Oh! Kato!
Hey, are you all right?
Of course.
You sure?
Don't worry about it.
Now lets get back to that game.
[TEACHER] When Philip
the Second was assassinated,
Alexander was crowned as king.
Now, if you'll turn
to page 34...
[HOJO] Look, how many times
do I have to tell you?
I'm just not into chicks
with large breasts.
Oh, wow, he's gorgeous!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL B] What?
You've never seen him before?
That's Hojo Masanobu.
From East Setagaya High.
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL A] Wow...
He looks just like a model.
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL B]
Where have you been?
He used to work for one of
the top male talent agencies
up until last year.
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL A]
Last year? Why'd he quit?
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL B]
Rumor has it that his agent
wanted to do him.
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL A] Ooh,
yeah, I've always heard stories
about stuff like that...
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL A]
Ooh~!
Take it easy.
It's just a book; nothing
to get all worked up about.
[MIKA]
Uh... Uh... I'm sorry...
I didn't mean to react like
that. You can have the book.
I was just looking at it,
I didn't wanna buy it.
Here, take it.
Ah! Oh, no... I-I couldn't.
[SEI]
Just take the book.
Um, well, thank you.
Man, you're jumpy.
Is... it that obvious?
Could it be...
you're being stalked?
How could you know about that?
Well... I'm just... perceptive
about things like that.
Well, I'll be okay. It just has
me a little shaken up, y'know?
So, have you informed
the police yet?
[MIKA]
Not yet...
I think I may have to
if it gets any worse,
but I'd really rather not.
Okay. Well, watch your ass.
Are you really sure
you don't want this?
You can have it.
No, you keep it.
I find that the books that you
read are far more interesting
if you read them when you want!
Thank you, then.
Hey, have you been waiting long?
Not too long.
[KISHIMOTO]
So, what were you looking at?
[KURONO] Uh, never mind...
Come on, let's go...
[KISHIMOTO]
What're you in such a hurry for?
I'll bet it was a
dirty book, wasn't it?
[BOTH gasp]
[HOJO] Ladies... Could one
of you loan me your bike?
I'll pay you 10,000 yen.
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL B]
What?!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL A] Um,
my boyfriend's bike is outside,
but... what do you need it for?
To ditch a stalker.
She's right behind me.
She won't leave me alone.
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL A] She looks
like the chick from "The Ring."
What a freak.
Okay, look: I'll try asking
my boyfriend about his bike,
but in return, can I sit
behind you in class?
Wait a second!
[HOJO] Okay, okay.
That's fine with me...
But it's not like a date, okay?
Really?!
[SHOPLIFTER]
Oh! H-Hey!
[FURUTA]
Hold it right there!
[SHOPLIFTER]
Ow! That hurts! Let me go!
I'm not gonna call the police,
but you're going to listen
to what I have to say!
[SHOPLIFTER groans]
Just how long do you
think you can keep this up,
you little malefactor?!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL A] Come on,
just for a little bit...?
You're crazy!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL A]
I'll make it worth your while...
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL B]
Yeah... We both will...
[DELINQUENT A]
Hey!
[ALL gasp]
[ONIZUKA]
Huh?
[ONIZUKA] Man,
what the fuck are you doing?!
[ONIZUKA grunts]
[ONIZUKA screams]
Shit!
[KATO grunting,
ONIZUKUA squealing]
[squelching]
[AYUMU]
Masaru, it's my fault...
[KATO]
"You are already dead."
Ken's the toughest...
[KATO grunting]
[wet thudding]
Whatever. It really
doesn't matter anyway...
[KATO yelling]
[blows landing]
[DELINQUENTS gasp]
Oh, man... We're fucked.
[STUDENT A snickers]
Aw, man! You totally
kicked my ass!
[STUDENT A] Well, if there's one
thing I'm good at, it's shogi!
[KISHIMOTO'S ORIGINAL]
I'll be right back!
You've gotta be kidding me!
[TETSUO]
There you go... Upsy-daisy!
Don't throw up! Ha, ha, ha!
I'm going out to get cigarettes.
Well, could you get some milk?
More milk? Again?
Yeah, babies drink a lot of it.
So, are you ready
to go home, dear?
With your new toys?
Do I have ta?
[KAYO]
Hmm...
Almost time... It might
even be tonight...
[KISHIMOTO]
So many new people drawn in,
and this game of death
goes on forever.
Will the newcomers
be able to understand?
Can they even survive?
And if they can't,
what will they do?