And another one
bites the dust...
[train horn blares]
[mechanical whirring]
[mechanical whirring, chirping]
Oh, now what?
Shit! What'll I do?
[whirring, chirping continues]
[KURONO] Okay, gotta think, how
the hell do I get outta this?!
[KURONO] Oh, God! Please don't
come this way!
Change, you stupid,
fucking light!
[KURONO] What am I doing?!
Get a grip, man...
How will this stop
that damn thing?!
[KURONO] Holy shit...
It actually stopped! Fuckin' A!
[KURONO] H-Hey, man,
don't ignore the lights!
[KURONO] Kishimoto...
I'm gonna die. This is it!
And I'm still a...
[KURONO] What the hell is this
thing? It's freaking me out!
Huh...? What the...?
[KURONO]
Huh? What's it doing?
Maybe it can't see me...
Would I be a pussy if I just...
...shot him in the back? What do
I do? Will I even hit him?!
I can end this right
here, right now.
It's just a robot, no
matter how you look at it...
And if it's only a robot...
If it's only a robot...
[KURONO]
Ah! What the hell?!
Bones? He has bones?!
This thing must be alive!
What the hell do I do?
I've never killed anything
this big before...
[KURONO] No, there's just
something wrong with that kid!
Dammit, I can't do this!
--[loud chirping]
--What the--?
[grunting]
[SUZUKI ALIEN]
Yuzo-ro?
Hey, Yuzo!
[SUZUKI ALIEN]
Hey, Yuzo?
No, I'm not.
Hey, there... Kantaro!
--[KURONO] What...?
--[SUZUKI ALIEN] Kantaro!
Okay, all together now!
I wonder where we are now...
We're here! We made it
outside, grandma!
You're right. I guess
we can go home now.
[KATO]
Wait! Wait a minute, please!
Huh...?
[KATO] Could everyone please
come over here for a minute?
Ah, screw you! We're outta here!
Yeah, we've had enough
of this crap!
[TETSUO]
Stop right there.
[HARUYA]
Huh...?
Do you think you're
just gonna leave
Kosuke's body there like that?
Well, I sure ain't
diggin' him a grave. Fuck 'em!
[KURONO] Anyway, I need to run.
I need to be with the others.
[chirping]
[growls]
Kantaro!
[KURONO]
Kato!
[KATO]
Huh...?
Kei... He made it!
But... isn't... that thing...?
Hey, wait...
Is that the Subaru Alien?
Yeah, that's it.
What the hell?
Hey, Kinji, you wanna
stick around a while?
This looks like it
could get interesting!
Hey, look, Grandma!
It's a real robot!
A rather impressive robot.
Hey, Kurono!
[KURONO] Sweet ass!
She was worried about me!
Couldn't you have
gotten rid of him?
[KURONO] What?! Is that all
she cares about?!
[KATO]
Stay back, everyone!
Ah. He's not angry now?
So, what now? What do we do?
Well, would you look at that?
it's nothin' but
a piece a shit!
Ya know, motorcycle companies
are making robots these days.
I bet that's what it is!
Can I please go now?
Wait! Everyone needs
to stay right here.
I don't think this is
a good time to leave.
Kei, tell me...
Is that thing really dangerous?
I'm not real sure...
But do you remember how those
Green Onion Alien things were?
What about them?
Huh?! You fought a
green onion before Yoshida?
What a pile a bull!
It's Suzuki! Suzuki Alien!
You were saying?
[KURONO] Well...
Remember how Gantz showed
the Green Onion Alien to us,
but it showed us
the little wimpy one?
[KURONO]
But then...
So maybe there's another one!
A stronger one than this!
C'mon, man! Can't you
even make up your mind
about kicking this stupid
robot's ass?
I mean, what a fuckin'
waste of time...
Come on, let's blow this
scene. I'm fuckin' starving!
Yeah. Let's get ramen.
Good call.
Hmm?
But I'll be goddamned if
you're coming with us.
Ryota, dear, do you
want to go now?
No! This robot looks so cool!
Oh, my goodness...
But we really must get you back
to your mother's house soon,
you know. I wonder
if there might be
a payphone somehwere
in this vicinity...
[chirping]
[SUZUKI ALIEN growls]
Yaah...!
[ALL grunting]
[NISHI]
Damn!
It's him...
So you're back!
And where in the hell
have you been this time?!
Hiding like a coward again?!
How 'bout you...
...FUCK OFF!
[yelps]
Hey! What're you doing?!
Don't hide behind me!
[KURONO]
Well, what am I supposed to do?!
I'm not wearing
my suit, you know!
[KURONO] Besides... aren't YOU
always hiding behind Kato?
Ten more points...
[KURONO gasps]
[NISHI]
Ten more points...
[KATO gasps]
Don't do it, Nishi!
[KURONO yells]
[KISHIMOTO shrieks]
[NISHI]
Huh?!
[KINJI]
Woah-ho! That thing can fly!
[HARUYA laughs]
How did it do that?!
Dammit... This is
startin' to stink bad.
Hey... look! It's flying!
Can I go home now?
Yaah...!
[ALL scream]
[ALL yell]
Yeah, whatever... Bring it on.
He disappeared!
I think I'll stick
with you guys...
Okay, all together!
[NISHI yells]
[TETSUO] What in the hell
is that robot shooting at?
I think that...
was Nishi just now, wasn't it?
Yeah, I think so.
It looks like that robot
can see him somehow.
Wow, Grandma! Did you see
that stuff blow up?! Awesome!
[KAYO]
Hmm...
Yaah...!
[NISHI grunts[
A direct hit... It sure
saw him that time, huh?
Yeah...
Grandma, didja see? That weird
guy just turned invisible!
Yes, he did...
That little shit! How come
he can do stuff like that?
I don't know...
Why don't you try asking Gantz?
Ask Gantz?
What in the hell is that?
We don't really
know what it is,
but it's one annoying
son of a bitch.
[NISHI]
Damn!
Come on, come on...
[SUZUKI ALIEN growls]
[NISHI whimpers]
Aw, what the fuck? He ain't
disappearing anymore!
Come on, kid, what gives?
Show us all your
little trick again!
[grunting]
[robotic whirring]
Yaah...!
Ten more points...
Ten more points, goddamn you!
Stop running away! Just give up!
Yaah...!
[screams]
Shit!
[KISHIMOTO] Hey, do you
think that thing is broken?
He stopped disappearing.
[KURONO] That thing
could see him anyway,
so I guess it really
doesn't make any difference
[KATO]
Maybe it doesn't, but still...
[KURONO] "But still" what?
To hell with him!
[SUZUKI ALIEN growls]
What the fuck are
you all looking at?!
Help me out here!
Hey, did you hear that, Haruya?
Yeah. I guess he's the one who
doesn't "get it" now, ain't he?
Hey! Why don't you
kiss my big, fat ass?!
All we are is garbage, right?
How can we help YOU?
[KINJI] Yeah we'd love
to help, but we can't
since we're garbage and all...
[HARUYA]
Yeah, get it?!
[KINJI, HARUYA laugh]
Ah!
[gasps]
Hoo-boy! Your little
peashooter's gone!
So, whatcha gonna do now,
you little piece a shit?
[NISHI whimpers]
Just shut up and help me out!
Shut the fuck up! After the
way you talked to us earlier?!
You can just stay there
and fucking die! DIE!
And speaking of death,
shithead, you told us that
we're all dead anyway, right?!
So what difference
does it make?!
You can just keep dying
and dying, right?! So fuck you!
[TETSUO]
Haruya, that's enough, okay?
Shut up... You stay out of th--
[HARUYA wails]
My fucking tooth!
[sobs]
[KINJI] Tetsu, why the
hell did you do that for?!
[KURONO] Man! Thugs must
really like knocking out
each other's teeth.
Hey, kid! Looks like this
isn't just a game, is it?
I get the idea you're in a lot
of trouble about now.
But you did, in fact, blow
Kouske's fucking head off!
And I hope you haven't
forgotten that!
You murdered another person!
Give us a sign that you have
some remorse about that!
There's nothing more
disgusting than a murderer
beggin' for his own
sad life! You hear me?!
Speak up! You gonna apologize
for murdering Kosuke
in cold blood?! Are you going to
show any kind of remorse
for what you did?!
Say something! Come on!
[KURONO]
Wait!
What?!
Are you really gonna help
that little shit out
if he just apologizes?
And just what does that mean?
Yeah, what do you mean?
Surely, you don't...
Give me a break. He's just
trying to save
his own pathetic skin.
The only thing that bastard's
ever really given a rat's ass
about is his goddamn score!
Are any of you honestly
willing to help out
a piece of shit like that?!
Well, since I'm not like your
indecisive fuckin' "leader,"
this is about owning up
to moral responsibility.
His and ours.
Do any of you...
Any of you...
...really understand
the preciousness of life?
How rare and valuable it is?
Does it mean anything?
You don't get it, do you?
Look, I'm not saying that I'm
gonna believe what he says,
but at this rate, that kid's
a dead man for sure.
So, what now, huh?
What're YOU gonna do?
[NISHI]
Dammit...
[growls]
Yaah...!
Now, don't get me wrong.
None of this means I'm gonna
save the little murderer
just because he apologizes.
I'm saying I might consider it
only if he does.
He's treated all of us like
shit, myself included.
But, even so, I'd help him
as long as he says, truthfully,
that there's some remorse in his
heart for all the rotten crap
that he's done.
Can you say the same?
Yaah...!
[NISHI yells]
Huh...?
[NISHI gasps, whimpers]
Somebody, help me!
Goddammit, help me!
You useless fucks!
Shit! What's wrong?! What in
the hell's happening to him?!
My suit! My suit
is all fucked now!
[KISHIMOTO whimpers]
Hey, Grandma... What do you
think's wrong with him?
What happened?
Look away, dear...
Huh? But why?
[KAYO] Because I'm afraid
he might die again...
[RYOTA]
What do you mean?
Time's running out!
Kid! Say you're sorry!
[TETSUO] I'd hurry up and say
I'm sorry if I were you!
[NISHI] If anyone ever
points a gun at me... EVER.
I WILL kill them,
and I WON'T apologize!
[TETSUO]
Goddammit. Well, fuck 'im, then.
[SUZUKI ALIEN growls]
Help! Goddammit, help me!
Help!
Why can't you just
say you're sorry?!
[KURONO]
Kato?!
[KISHIMOTO]
What're you doing?!
Maybe I don't know that
much about life, but...
[KATO] Look, we're
all going back together.
He can apologize anytime!
Kei, please! I need you to
tell me how to use this suit!
Huh?
[KATO]
If he dies...
...nobody will be able
to tell us what's going on.
Wait a second... You're really
gonna help that son of a bitch?
Kato, don't do it, please!
If Nishi can't beat it,
how can you?!
Yeah, Kato...
It's... not a good idea!
How does it work?
Well, you should...
...be okay, as long as
you stay focused, but...
Thank you, Kei.
I want... to go home.
[KURONO]
Wh... What?
I want to go home...
[KATO]
...more than any of you.
[RYOTA]
Grandma, what's that guy doing?
Huh? He disappeared!
Now he's being shot!
He's gonna die, Grandma!
Next episode: "He Can't Shoot."