[FEMALE TEACHER] So, if triangle
ABC is a right triangle,
and AC equals one,
then BC equals the square root
of three, and AB equals two.
This also means that BA
equals DB, and BD equals two.
And since triangle BAD
is an isosceles triangle,
it also follows that its
base angles are equal.
So BDA equals BAD.
Therefore, BDA is--
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Teacher!
Yes?
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Kurono's got a hard on!
[STUDENTS laugh]
Man, you're such a horn dog!
Is making it with a girl
the only thing you think about?
Ha, ha! Shut your hole,
you fucking cow!
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
It's true!
You just wish I did... ho!
[FEMALE STUDENT A] Then
stand up and prove you don't!
[FEMALE TEACHER]
All right class, that's enough!
Settle down!
And as for you.
[KURONO gasps]
Ah. Yes, ma'am?
Let's bone up on math here and
save that for when you get home.
[car horn honks]
[KURONO] God. Can't you
sleep somewhere else,
you stinking bum?
[KURONO] Whoa! Oooh, baby,
you were made to make me...
[FURUTA]
Come back here!
Damn! That's the third time
this has happened now!
That little bastard!
Keep an eye on the store, honey!
Come back here, you!
[KURONO]
Third time's the charm!
Isn't this rain ever gonna stop?
What the...? Twenty-three
hundred yen and no bush?!
What a rip!
[DEBT COLLECTOR]
Damn! His office closes at five.
He's gonna lock himself
in there and hide. I know it!
[HOUSEWIFE]
What'll I do?
At this rate, my husband
will get home before I do...
He'll kill me...
[SALARYMAN] Come on,
I don't believe this crap!
I'm supposed to score tonight...
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL]
This is so not fair!
If I don't meet him soon,
Ryosuke'll go home
and I won't get laid!
God, this sucks.
Uh... Please excuse
me, young man,
but could I ask you something?
Is this the right platform
for the train to Hinodedai?
[KURONO] Aw, why'd you
have to ask me, Grandma?
You're in the wrong place,
but explaining where to go'll be
such a pain.
Yeah... That's right.
Thank you so much for
your help, young man.
[KURONO] Oh, jeez, that wino.
Get a job, and take a bath.
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL]
Ewww! God, he's gross!
[HOUSEWIFE] I'd better make sure
I'm not stuck in the same car--
That smell...
[SALARYMAN]
Goddamn bum.
Boozing in the middle of the
day, not a care in the world.
Ain't that kick in the head?
[DEBT COLLECTOR]
Man, does he stink!
Keep out of my way or I'll
shove your ass onto the tracks!
[BUM]
Just what are you lookin' at?!
I wasn't put here
for yer amusement!
Young man...
I hate to bother you, but this
seems to be the wrong platform.
Well, in that case,
maybe you shoulda tried to
figure it out yourself
instead of relying on a complete
stranger to do it for ya!
Well, I apologize then...
[KURONO]
Sorry, Granny, I may look nice,
but I've learned
that most people
just aren't worth my time.
Like those two--
I bet they've never had a
single deep thought between 'em.
And those girls are even worse.
Empty-headed cock teasers
and social climbers.
Hmm... and the further I stay
away from someone like him,
the better...
And that one's not even worth
wasting the brain cells on.
Hey, wait...
[KURONO]
Come on, Kato! You slow poke!
[KATO]
Kei!
Please, Kei! Wait for me!
[KURONO] No way. Masaru Kato?
That's gotta be him.
He hasn't changed that much
since we were in grade school,
but I heard he turned
into a real punk
after he switched schools.
I bet he doesn't
remember me though,
even if we did
always play together.
Look at him now.
Talk about your total thug.
[BUM yells]
[WOMAN A] Hey!
Somebody fell on the tracks!
[MAN B]
What happened to him?
[MAN C]
He was staggering and fell.
[MAN D]
C'mon, man. get up!
[KURONO] Aw, man, you're in for
it now, you poor, drunk bastard.
The station attendant's
not coming, and no one else
is gonna risk their life
to save your sorry ass.
[HOUSEWIFE]
Everything's wet from the rain!
He must've slipped.
[SALARYMAN] Will somebody
just call the station attendant?
[OLD LADY]
Someone help him.
[DEBT COLLECTOR]
Oh, he's a lost cause.
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL] Wow,
I've never seen someone fall
on the tracks before.
I've gotta text message Ryosuke!
[SALARYMAN] Sure, helping him
would be the humane thing to do,
but someone else will step up.
Sure they will.
I've got a mortgage to pay.
[OLD LADY]
But if...
[SALARYMAN]
...no one helps him...
[HOUSEWIFE]
...then we'll all...
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL] ...get to
see a real dead body...
[DEBT COLLECTOR]
...getting ripped to pieces...
[KURONO] I've never seen someone
get torn apart except in movies.
And look at Kato; even
a tough snot like him's
getting freaked out...
But, come to think of it,
he was always kinda squeamish
back in the day...
Fine, That does it!
[KURONO]
Huh?! Oh, what the fuck?!
Are you outta your mind?
This is no time to be acting
like a hero, you idiot!
What are you trying to prove?
That you can do it by yourself?
[SALARYMAN]
That kid jumped on the tracks!
[DEBT COLLECTOR]
He's gonna get himself killed!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL]
Wow! Now both of them
can get ripped to shreds!
[HOUSEWIFE] Hmm...
he's kinda cute... Nice ass.
Hey! You gotta get up!
Will someone up there please
come down and give me a hand?!
[SALARYMAN] Where the hell
is the station attendant?
Didn't someone get him already?
[HOUSEWIFE]
I think someone went.
He should be here any second.
Don't just stand there!
You can't just watch us die!
[SALARYMAN] Gimme a break!
He's just a bum! Leave him!
[DEBT COLLECTOR] No one's gonna
help you, you stupid punk!
[KURONO] Get real, Kato!
You're the one who's
being crazy here...
[KATO]
Is that...?
[KURONO]
Oh, now you remember...
You don't really
think that I'll...?
Kei Kurono!
Shit...
[KURONO]
Oh, this is so not fair!
And what are all of you staring
at me for? One of you go!
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL] What are
you waiting for? Get going!
[HIGH SCHOOL BOY]
Go on, he's your friend!
[KATO]
Come on! Hurry up!
[KURONO] Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
What am I doing down here?!
Why the hell am I doing this?!
Are ya happy he remembered
you now, you fucking idiot?!
[KATO]
Okay, bend down.
[KURONO]
What?!
[KATO]
Under him! For leverage!
[KEI, KATO grunting]
[SALARYMAN] Great. Looks like I
don't have to go down there.
[DEBT COLLECTOR] You just signed
your death sentences, kids.
[KATO grunts]
[KURONO]
Aw, jeez, does he reek!
[MAN A]
This isn't looking good!
[MAN B]
Hurry up, damn it!
[GIRL A] Hope someone
gets him off the tracks!
[MAN C] Where the hell's
the station attendant?
[STATION ANNOUNCEMENT]
The next train will be
arriving at platform two.
Please stand behind...
[KATO]
Come on, lift him up!
I know, I know, damn it!
[KURONO]
But I feel so sick...
What are you doing?! Hurry up!
[KURONO]
He's too heavy! Push, Kato!
That's what I'm doing! Stand up!
[KURONO]
Oh, shit! The train's coming!
I think I'm gonna puke...
[BUM groaning]
[SALARYMAN]
Come on, you two! Climb up! Now!
[train horn blares]
Kei! Start running!
Run? But that's a train!
Oh, God! We're fucked!
Trains slow down as
they reach the station!
If we run, we can make it past
where the first car stops!
Oh, yeah! I didn't
think of that!
[SALARYMAN]
Good luck!
[KURONO] We've still got a
chance! We can make it! But...
Kato! Lose the bag!
[KATO]
What?!
Drop your stuff!
[KATO]
I've got to keep the umbrella!
Huh?! Are you out of your mind?!
[KATO] It's for my kid brother!
He went to school without one!
[KURONO] Oh, for... Then at
least lose the stupid bag!
If you don't outrun the train,
your brother'll get that
umbrella at your
godammn funeral!
[KATO]
All right already!
[STATION ANNOUNCEMENT]
The express train for Hinodedai
will be passing shortly.
For your safety, please stay
behind the yellow line...
[KATO] An Express?!
But only local trains...
[KURONO]
...stop at this station!
I don't believe this!
I'm gonna die and the last thing
I did was buy a girlie mag!
[KATO] I swear I'll get you
your umbrella, little brother!
Kei, are you
all right back there?!
Of course not!
[KURONO]
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
I'm so fucking scared and...!
An opening! Look for an opening!
There's gotta be one!
There's nothing, dammit!
[PEOPLE gasping, murmuring]
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL 2] No way!
I gotta get a picture of this!
[SALARYMAN]
They're not gonna make it!
[KURONO]
What the... What's happening...?
[KURONO gasps]
[KURONO] Kato! That's what you
get for being a good samaritan.
Serves you right...
[CROWD shrieking]
[KURONO]
Aw, come on!
Why the fuck are you
taking pictures of this,
you stupid bitch?
Do you think this
is some kind of show?!
Just shut up and stop screaming!
[KURONO] Well... if this is
the way it's... gotta be...
[BOTH panting]
[YAMADA]
Wow! There are two this time!
[MAN A]
Their heads flew off!
Do you see those two
kids who died on the tracks
just now, you lousy bum?!
They died to save you!
[SALARYMAN retches]
[BUM]
Man. What a mess.
So did you two...
almost die, too?
[KURONO] What the...
hell is going on here?
[KATO]
I dunno...
...but somehow or other
we made it out alive! Look!
[KURONO]
"Made it"? Made it where?!
None of us made it.
[INAMORI]
Oh... Just shut up...
This place is heaven. And we're
all here because we're dead.
[INAMORI] Speak for yourself.
We're not all senile, gramps!
[YAMADA chuckles]
[YAMADA] Well, I suppose that
is one possible theory, but...
[SUZUKI] All I know is that I
was lying in a hospital bed
dying of cancer,
and then I was here
and the pain's completely gone.
How else would you explain that?
[KURONO]
Dead? That can't be...
My heart's still beating!
And I'm breathing, too!
Wait... hold on...
If we're dead...
...why's the Tokyo Tower
out that window?
[KURONO]
You're right! We're in Tokyo!
Hey, why can't I
touch the latch?!
[KURONO] What do you mean
you can't touch it?
[KURONO]
What the hey? What's going on?!
[YAMADA]
It's pointless.
We've all tried and
we can't touch the doors
or even the walls.
If we could, we wouldn't
still be sitting in this room.
Even our cell phones
are blocked.
Please tell me you're kidding.
Did you try making
noise or something
to get the neighbors attention?
[YAMADA]
Yes, but there was no response.
The front door's no good either!
[STATION ATTENDANT]
I don't see anything.
Where did you say
the bodies were?
[SALARYMAN]
Over there somewhere...
[STATION ATTENDANT] There isn't
any sign of blood, either.
[SALARYMAN] But I saw
their heads fly clean off!
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
I know I took pictures
of their heads flying off,
but for some reason, they're...
they're not here...
Yeah, well, their
heads may be gone
but their school bags
are still here.
This bag...
[YAMADA]
Excuse me, everyone!
May I suggest that we
all introduce ourselves?
Names and what you do first,
--and then how you died...
--[INAMORI] Oh, get stuffed!
You sound like you're
teaching kindergarten here!
Well, I teach
first grade, actually.
[INAMORI groans]
[YAMADA]
I'll go first.
[YAMADA clears throat]
[YAMADA]
I'm Masashi Yamada.
I teach at Nerima Higashi
Elementary school and...
...I had an accident
while riding my scooter.
Um, so... how about you?
Huh?
[KURONO] Damnit, why did you
have to pick me first?
Kei... high school
student.. and I'm dead.
[KURONO] Even though I don't
think I'm actually dead...
Because of this jerk.
[KURONO]
That's right. It's your fault.
[KATO sighs]
Yeah, and I'm so sorry, Kei.
I guess I just naturally assumed
that you'd wanna help.
[KURONO]
Right, as if!
And... you are...?
[KATO] Oh, yeah,
Masaru Kato. Hit by a train.
[KURONO] "Hit by a train"?
It tore us to ribbons!
And are you even sorry for
getting me killed, Mister Hero?
You make me sick!
Hey, I think I know this guy...
Well... your turn.
Goro Suzuki.
[KURONO] Yeah! He's a politician
or something on TV.
You've probably heard of me.
[KURONO]
Heh, yeah, right.
And... you?
Dude. I told you.
Not playing. Pass.
[KURONO] Oh, sure,
make me look like an idiot
for going along with this crap!
Introduce yourself, you ass!
Hey, anyone got any smokes?
[KURONO] And I bet you
smoke like a girl, too.
I'm Joichiro Nishi.
Eighth grade. And I fell.
[KURONO]
What a freak.
And why are you staring at me,
you little psycho?
Okay, no one's got
any cigarettes then?
[YAMADA]
All right, good. And...
Um... next?
Um, please, sir?
[YOSHIOKA] He's a Yakuza.
Like me. No more questions.
[YAMADA]
Oh. Okay. Is that everyone?
[DOG panting]
I guess so...
[DOG whines]
[KATO] Kei, there's something
different about you.
[KURONO] Yeah? Besides being
dead like you, you mean?
The Kei I remember
had more of an edge.
Back when we were kids...
...I didn't think there was
anything you were afraid of.
That's why we thought
of you as our leader.
Me? Your leader?
[KURONO]
Oh, man, when was that?
Either you're laying it on thick
or my memory's fucked.
What caused that change?
[KURONO]
Well, you've changed a lot, too.
Yes, but remember those
games of tag we used to play?
Yeah...
[KATO] Whether you were
running away or chasing us,
you were so fast it was amazing.
I remember how you'd jump down
a whole flight of stairs.
Okay, enough!
Oh, and there was one time,
it was totally awesome...
I don't remember exactly why,
but all the tough kids from
school had you cornered.
And you just jumped off the
overpass and landed on the roof
of a passing truck!
It just blew me away,
and I remember thinking,
"I wanna be like him."
So, when my grades went south
and I got sent to the school
with all the hoods and punks.
I patterned everything
I did after you.
[KURONO]
Oh, give me a break!
Are you trying to
tell me it's my fault
you turned out like this?
[KATO] Huh?! Kei, are you
seeing what I'm seeing?!
Ah! What the fuck?!
[YAMADA] I don't believe it!
Here comes another one!
[INAMORI]
Yeah! Looks like a girl!
Do you think...
this is how we got here?
Kei, is she...?
Not now!
[KURONO] Oh, jeez, I will
not get a stiffie, I will--
Aw, fuck!
[INAMORI chuckles]
Yeah! These coochie shots are
all going up on my web page.
[INAMORI] Hey! Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
You're blockin' my view!
[YAMADA]
Uh, excuse me,
but I don't think you
should be doing that!
[KURONO]
Mmm?
Uh! But I... just...
[INAMORI]
You're just what, peckerhead?!
Hey! She's bleeding!
But... there aren't
any cuts on her wrists.
Do you see this, Kei?
[YAMADA] A suicide.
In the bathtub I guess.
Is she alive?
Yeah, I can hear her heartbeat.
[YAMADA]
Um, you know...
Y-You could have checked
her pulse at the wrist.
Oh, yeah...
[INAMORI] Yeah, so stop
playing musical crotch with her,
you sleaze.
What? Why can't she...
I mean... couldn't we... just...
[DOG panting]
[INAMORI]
Yoo-hoo!
What's... happening?
What's going on...?
[KURONO] What's with her?
Does she think she's dreaming?
I know I do.
You stay here... All of you!
[KURONO]
Stay here? But...
Oh, hell, don't tell me
you're gonna--
Holy shit!
That guy's something else, huh?
[gasps]
[INAMORI]
Hey!
--You did have cigarettes!
--[KISHIMOTO screams]
[KISHIMOTO]
Stop!
[KURONO] I know I should help
her, but what's the point?
Who in the hell could go up
against that monster?!
[screaming continues]
[KISHIMOTO]
No! Please!
[KURONO] Oh, no way...
His friend's right over there!
NO!
[INAMORI]
That's not a good idea...
[KISHIMOTO]
Nooo!
It's hard to find such a brave
young man these days.
Hey, I don't see
you helping her!
Because that yakuza would
kick my cancer-filled ass.
All right!
[KATO]
Hey, leave her alone!
[HATANAKA]
I'll fucking kill you!
[DOG barking]
[KATO]
I said stop it!
[HATANAKA]
Let go, you little...
I'll kill you!
I'll fucking kill you!
Back off... now!
[HATANAKA growls]
[KATO grunts]
Just piss off!
I said stop!
Just back off and I'll let go!
Otherwise I'm gonna keep
squeezing until something gives!
[KURONO] If he keeps this up,
he's gonna kill him!
Say it! Say you
won't do it again!
[HATANAKA gurgles]
[KATO]
I said, "Say it!" damn you!
[KURONO]
Holy shit, Kato.
[jingle plays]
[KURONO]
Huh? What's that?
[HATANAKA]
Move!
What in the hell...?
[KURONO]
Do you remember who you were?
When darkness spawns monsters in
the middle of a neighborhood,
when the targets snarl in fury
and blood covers the streets,
could your old self have
faced... the fangs of darkness?