[KURONO]
This... could be really bad...
[RYOTA]
Grandma, where are we going?
I'm finally taking you
home to your mother, dear.
[KURONO]
Yeah, this is very bad...
Kurono, I...
[KURONO] I'm actually
getting used to this.
I don't feel sick anymore.
I'm not even... scared or
sorry when I see people die.
Did you just say something?
Are you all right?
Ah, it's nothing...
[KURONO]
This is Japan, right?
And we're in the middle
of a residential area...
So why does it feel
like a warzone?!
A-And what am I doing
with this thing anyway?
All I do know... is I better
make sure to hold onto it.
If I don't, it's gonna be bad.
[TETSUO]
So... What do we do now?
[HOJO] You said there's
more of them, right?
[KATO]
Yeah.
Hold on. Where'd the
old lady and the kid go?
Where did--
They're gone!
[HOJO]
Oh, great.
If Grandma Senile and her
annoying brat run into an alien
on their own, they're both
going to be dead meat!
Hey, cry me a fucking river!
Why should we give a
fuck about that old bag
and her annoying little shit?
Because it's right!
And kids are supposed to
be like that, you dumbass!
Yeah?! Well, why don't
you shut the hell up?!
You're not the fucking
boss around here!
Or have you forgotten
that Kosuke and Kinji
got their heads blown off?
And you couldn't do a
fucking thing about it!
So tell me, who in the hell do
you think you are, asshole?!
[retches]
It's just like the guns.
I guess here even
puking has a time-lag.
Kurono, that's not
in good taste!
How can you be the big man if
you can't hold your lunch? Huh?
Go fuck yourself.
And instead of talkin' smart,
how 'bout you
gimme back my tooth?!
Come get it, fat boy!
--[KATO] Enough!
--[ALL] Huh?
If you wanna be free
from this, listen up!
I'm going to try to find and
destroy that other Suzuki Alien,
do you understand?
And I'm going to try to find
the old lady and the boy
while I'm at it.
And if any of you want to
make it through this alive,
then you've got to help me out!
You said something before...
...about freeing
ourselves from this...
I think you mentioned a score.
I don't know if that
part's true or not,
but we'll never find
out unless we try.
It's our only choice.
To be straight up with you,
I'd really rather not
trust you with my life.
But seeing as how that stupid
biker got his head blown off
for no reason...
Just where did that happen?
If ya head back that way,
there's a pay phone that's
covered with Kinji's fuckin'
brains. That might be it.
[HOJO]
I get it!
You die if you
leave this area.
It's about one square kilometer.
But how is that even possible?
You don't think there's a
bomb or something like that
planted inside of each
of our heads, do you?
And why would someone wanna
keep us here like that?
Does any of this shit
make any fuckin' sense?
Unfortunately, I'm just as
clueless about it as you are.
What I don't get is how
we're supposed to find
two of those monsters in
a square kilometer block
in just an hour!
Well, we did last time.
But that doesn't mean we'll
be able to do it every time.
Then again...
We do know that Nishi'd survived
a lot of rounds before us.
[HARUYA]
Ha! That little turd?!
He took out Kosuke
easily enough.
Look, the fact is that we
have to find that other alien.
And right now, we're
wasting precious time!
Kei, you're not wearing
a suit this time.
So I want you to
stay somewhere safe.
--[KURONO] Huh?
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
[KURONO]
Aw, look at her now.
Just a minute ago,
you were looking at me
like you thought I was cool!
Damn, you're flakey!
--[gun cocks]
--[KURONO gasps]
Okay, junior, now you
do what I tell you to.
[KURONO]
Huh?
[HARUYA]
Not the right answer!
What the hell are you doing?
[HARUYA]
I'll tell you what I'm doing,
you dipshit, fuckin'
has-been of a leader!
I'm taking your damn gun.
God, that hurt... Huh?
Hurry up and hand it over!
[TETSUO] You're a worthless
piece of shit, you know that?
[HARUYA]
Hey, you!
What do you think you're
doin'?! Get back over here!
[HOJO]
Damn it. Where are they?
[KATO] Who? The old lady
or the Suzuki Alien?
[HOJO]
Either of them.
Why don't we ask that taxi
driver for some help?
Because in case you
haven't figured it out,
we're completely
invisible to everyone
until this whole thing is over.
So then... does that mean
we really are dead?
[RYOTA wails]
Now where in the world
do you suppose we are?
[RYOTA crying] I'm hungry!
I can't walk anymore!
Oh... You poor thing...
[HARUYA]
Who the fuck told you to stop?
[KURONO groans]
That really hurt!
Are you crying?
You make me sick!
Ow!
[KURONO]
Son of a bitch...!
Start walking, kid. Move it!
[KISHIMOTO]
Hey, um, Kato?
[KATO]
Mm-hmm?
Is it true you can't use a gun?
[KATO sighs]
I really think that you should.
Just to be safe, you know?
[KATO sighs]
I mean, I... know you're
trying to do everything that
needs to be done without them,
but... I just... think that--
If you'd pulled that
trigger a little sooner,
that kid would be alive.
Think about that.
That isn't what I was
trying to say at all,
so don't put any
words in my mouth.
I'll just say this: Females have
stronger survival instincts.
I don't think
that's true at all!
No, you're right.
And... I agree.
But, Kato!
I have to be prepared to do it.
--[beeping]
--[ALL gasp]
[HOJO] It's close!
It's gotta be nearby.
[KISHIMOTO]
But which one?
Is it the Suzuki Alien or
the old lady and the boy?
[HOJO]
I can't tell.
We'll know soon enough.
Here they come.
--[HOJO] Huh?
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
[KATO gasps]
[HARUYA]
Hurry the fuck up!
Haven't ya figured that
damned thing out yet?!
[KURONO] This isn't mine,
so I think it works differently.
So if it were yours,
you'd know how to use it.
[KURONO]
Not exactly...
Stop your mumbling! Where'd that
other fucking monster get to?!
This thing is only showing
the streets along the river!
How do I get it to show
me the other areas?
--[HOJO] Hey, there's more now!
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
[HOJO]
There must be more than one!
--[rapid beeping]
--[footsteps]
Oh...
[ALL sigh]
[KISHIMOTO] Wait a minute.
Do you think that screen's
showing people as dots, too?
How the fuck should I know?!
But in that case,
it should be showing
Kei and the others, as well.
Does the display show the river?
[KATO] Either way, he wouldn't
be walking around on his own...
So that must mean...
This dot is...
[rapid beeping]
--Here it comes!
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
Ah! The scary thing is back!
Don't you worry, Ryota, the
others will take care of it.
You two get out
of here! Right now!
Get moving, damn it!
There's no guarantee that
we'll be able to protect you
from these things!
[gasps]
[KATO] Run as far as you
can within the safe zone!
[HOJO]
What-- What the hell?!
[gasps]
What's wrong? [gasps]
It's... another one!
[rapid beeping]
Take them on with your hands.
What the fuck did you just say?!
If you miss with a gun,
you're screwed.
But your hands are
a lot more reliable.
You are nuts, aren't you?
--[mechanical whirring]
--[gasps, screams]
[KATO]
What is it?!
Oh, shit! How many
of them are there?!
Yuzo-bro...
[KISHIMOTO screams]
[gasps]
[SUZUKI ALIEN B growls]
No!
Yaah...!
[yells]
[KATO grunts]
[KISHIMOTO]
Kato!
[SUZUKI ALIEN B yelling]
This is how you catch
them! Pay attention!
[KATO growls]
[yelling]
[BOTH gasp]
[yelling continues]
[squeals]
[HOJO gasps]
[SUZUKI ALIEN B screams]
There's more of them!
This is... This is just...
[SUZUKI ALIENS screech]
[gasps]
[screeching continues]
[KATO screaming]
[growls]
--[SUZUKI ALIENS screeching]
--No! No, Kato!
[KATO groans]
[panting]
[KURONO]
He can't... He can't shoot it.
But why? He doesn't have
any other choice left!
[panting continues]
[SUZUKI ALIENS screeching]
[screams]
[KISHIMOTO screams]
[grunts]
[HOJO gasps]
--[screeching continues]
--[KATO yells]
[RYOTA]
Grandma, do you think
that scary robot'll
come back again?
I think we'll be just fine.
I'm sure we'll be okay if
we find somewhere to hide.
[HARUYA] You just bring
that Suzuki Alien on!
I'm going to tear that fuckin'
freak's head right off!
Hey, you found it yet? Huh?!
[KURONO]
There it is.
But it's...
[HARUYA]
What? Spit it out!
This thing... It's huge!
Huge, huh?
[HARUYA]
So fuckin' what?
[beeping]
[KURONO]
It's in there.
[HARUYA]
Right. Go check it out.
You want me to go in there?!
[HARUYA]
That's what I said, dipshit!
[KURONO]
Fuck...
I could waste him,
but what's the point
unless we kill all the Suzuki
Aliens first?! Damn it!
[KATO yelling]
[growls]
[gasps]
[SUZUKI ALIEN B squeals]
[KATO yells]
[squealing]
[yells]
[screeches]
My suit...
[mechanical whirring]
His suit's gone!
But if his suit is...
[SUZUKI ALIENS screeching]
[HOJO, KISHIMOTO gasp]
[SUZUKI ALIENS gasp]
[KISHIMOTO yelps, gasps]
[KATO gasps]
[KISHIMOTO] If you can't
shoot them... then I will!
[KISHIMOTO]
Stay down, Kato! Stay down!
I won't let you kill him!
Stay away from him, damn you!
I'm doing this for Kato!
I'm doing this for all of us!
That's enough now!
Start running!
Get out of there now, Kato!
No, you run!
[SUZUKI ALIENS screeching]
[HOJO growls]
I think I've got him!
Hojo!
[gasps]
[SUZUKI ALIEN C squeals]
[squeals]
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
[HARUYA]
So... This is it, huh?
[KURONO]
Yeah... I think so.
Oh, yeah, this is it.
[KURONO] But... there's
s-so many of them in there.
Well? Get your ass in there!
[KURONO gasps]
Huh?
[TETSUO] I thought you were
gonna tear 'em apart, big man.
[HARUYA]
Shut up!
Get your nut sack movin'!
Or I'll blow your
fuckin' head off.
[RYOTA whines]
I gotta pee! I gotta go!
[KAYO]
Oh... Can you hold it in, dear?
[RYOTA]
I gotta pee! It hurts!
[KAYO]
Then just do it here!
[HOJO]
Shit!
[KATO]
Huh?
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
So what now?
Just wait...
What the hell is wrong with it?
[screeching]
Where'd the old lady
and the kid go?
I think they ran
in that direction.
That's not good.
Then the other aliens are
probably after them by now.
[HOJO gasps]
[KATO]
Let's go!
[mechanical whirring]
[SUZUKI ALIEN D growls]
[gasps]
Grandma! Help, Grandma!
[heart beats pounding]
[KURONO]
Shit... I'm not wearing my suit.
What do I do if they attack me?
What the fuck am I gonna do?!
[RYOTA whimpering]
[KAYO]
Listen carefully, Ryota.
I'm going to stay here. You go
on and run out the back way.
[RYOTA]
What about you?!
[RYOTA sobs]
Grandma will take care
of them, all right?
But I don't have any clothes on!
Go on now. Run!
[KAYO gasps]
[RYOTA whimpers]
[RYOTA]
Grandma!
[RYOTA] Officer! Help!
My grandma, she's...!
[sobs]
[RYOTA wails]
[KAYO groans]
[RYOTA]
Grandma!
Grandma...! Grandma...!
[RYOTA screams]
--[KAYO whimpers]
--[RYOTA sobs]
[SUZUKI ALIENS screeching]
No! Please don't!
[screeching]
[KAYO]
Don't worry, Ryota...
[RYOTA whimpers]
There's nothing.
Do you think I'm
stupid, you dumbass?!
You forgot upstairs!
I said there's nothing here!
You're the one who said
there was a bunch of them,
shit for brains! So, find them!
Or I'll cap your ass!
[stairs creaking]
[KURONO] It's possible the
machine could be broken.
I've already told him there's
nothing here! Fat fuck...
[SUZUKI ALIEN G]
Yuzo-bro... Yuzo-bro...
[SUZUKI ALIEN H]
Yuzo.
[SUZUKI ALIEN I]
Yuzo...
[mechanical whirring]
[KURONO]
What is that bird?
Huh? Something got shot.
It's falling.
Next time on Gantz,
"Please D.E.I."
It's not "D.E.I.," it's "Die!"