[KATO] The next 30 minutes
will decide everything!
We're not just
fighting to go home,
we're fighting for survival.
If we don't kill all of them,
none of us will live either!
So, no matter what happens now,
we've got to keep fighting.
We've come too far to give up!
[KATO] Remember, focus on
staying alive and we can win!
Let's go!
Hey, Kei, are you
and Sei a thing now?
[KURONO] Dammit! Don't say stuff
like that in front of Kishimoto!
It's bad enough
she saw me porking--
We will be if we live
though this, right?
Oh, then I guess we're all just
going to have to live then,
won't we?!
At least it's good to know
someone else believes
that all of us can
get back home alive.
Well, since Kei already killed
the "boss" of this game,
eliminating the rest of
them should be easy!
By the way, I'm really
happy for you guys!
[KURONO]
Just shut up, already!
[KURONO gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Is that what I think it is?
[TOMAO]
So where do you live, again?
[KONTA] Higashi Nagasaki,
on the Seibu line.
[TOMAO] Oh! That's close
to Ikebukuro, right?
[HOJO] No, honestly, you're
actually kinda cute.
Come on, let me see
your face again. Please?
Jeez!
So in that case, uh, how 'bout
if I, uh, came by tomorrow?
Tomorrow, yeah. Yeah, I could--
Okay, let's go!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[KATO]
Damnit!
What kind of a monster
would do something like this?
I guess those two
assholes got him...
You sound so sure.
Couldn't this have been
the work of the statues?
Statues might have beaten him,
but they wouldn't take
such pleasure in it.
[KATO crying]
Why did we bother?
What was the point in even
trying to save his life?!
You can't give up, Kato.
But why keep going on?
I mean, what's the
fucking point?!
We've been trying so hard
to make it back together.
But now the priest is dead,
and so's the military guy!
No matter what we do,
it's the same as last time
and the time before that!
I've never understood
any of this!
But this is the
most senseless yet!
Why?! What in the hell
have we been fighting for?
This man was killed, and his
only crime was being homeless!
We've suffered and bled
for this stupid game!
But what kind of place are
we fighting to get back to?
A world where no one bothers
to help a homeless man
who's fallen on the tracks?
A place where
innocent human beings
get their heads smashed in
for no reason at all?
[KURONO]
Kato! Get a fucking grip!
Do you remember what
you said to us earlier?
You said you wanted to go
home more than any of us.
[KURONO]
If that's still true,
then going back is your
only option, right?
The same goes for the
rest of us...all of us.
[gasps]
[KURONO]
Wait! What's wrong with me?
Until about a minute ago,
I was sure this is
where I belonged.
When... did that change...?
Oh, yeah...
I get it now.
I... I-I really do
wanna go home.
I don't wanna die yet!
We should get moving.
[gasps]
Uh-huh.
Well, let's get going!
We don't have much time!
[KATO]
Yeah! Right!
So, is it all right with you?
If I take your spare?
Huh? Oh, you mean Kurono.
So no hard feelings?
No, Kurono and I are... just a
little too different, you know?
Different how?
A lot of ways.
It's complicated.
Come on!
[TOMAO] Oh, shit, I haven't
seen this many statues
since I saw Nana at
the nursing home!
[KONTA]
They're not movin', though.
[TOMAO]
But what if they start moving?
Hey, leader guy!
What do we do now?
[HOJO]
Hold on a second.
I'm going to scan them
all with the X-gun.
If we see any bones or organs,
we should attack them
before they start moving.
But can we take
these guys on alone?
Hey, after the big gold one,
how hard could these guys be?
[VISHNU STATUE chanting]
Huh?
[ALL]
Hm?!
[STATUES chanting]
Okay, never mind. We can
skip the scanning part.
It looks like the fast statue
from before! Surround it!
[STATUES chanting[
So we're really gonna
fight all of these fuckers?
Yeah, Boss! Just what do
you want us to do, huh?
Stay back! If you're not wearing
a suit, just stay out of my way!
[ALL]
Huh?
[KONTA] Hold on, I think
we have a challenger.
[HOJO]
Hey! Get back here, you idiot!
[BUDDHA STATUE chants]
[JJ growls]
Dammit! I said, get back here!
Dude, he can kill those
those with his bare hands.
Just chill out; he's
a fucking karate man.
Maybe, but I'm not so sure.
[yells]
Huh?!
[BUDDHA STATUE chants]
[yells]
--[JJ screams]
--[HOJO] Oh, shit!
[JJ groans]
What the fuck...?!
--[BOTH gasp]
--Damn it!
It's too fucking strong! Get out
of there! Before it kills you!
[yells]
--[TOMAO] Damn!
--[KONTA] Shit!
[panting]
[BUDDHA STATUE chants]
[ALL gasp]
[ding]
[KONTA screaming]
Oh, sh-shit, man!
You're not wearing a suit,
so get outta here!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Oh, shit!
[TOMAO]
What the fuck do we do now?!
You start running!
And don't stop!
[KISHIMOTO]
It's no good!
That thing's too fast!
I can't catch up!
I got him! Do it now!
[KATO screams]
Kato!
[gasps]
[KATO screams]
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
Kato?!
[KATO]
Th-The transfer...
The transfer
hasn't started yet!
Aren't they done over there?!
There can't be much
time left damn it!
[TOMAO]
What are we gonna do?
These-- These things
are fuckin' deadly!
[KONTA] And they're
blockin' the way out!
They're not gonna
let us get away!
[HOJO] Okay, then you guys need
to get close to me, real close.
and be ready to move quickly.
I never thought I'd say this...
But I could really use your
crazy ass up here, Sadako!
You guys get ready to run!
--[gun charges]
--[ALL gasp]
Let's start running now!
[KONTA]
Huh?
One...
Two... Three!
Well, dear, the only thing left
standing between you and me
is these fuckers.
[HOJO gasps, screams]
Oh, shit!
[KONTA]
Goddamn, we are limp pricks!
[TOMAO] Yeah, man!
We're always runnin' away!
[KONTA]
Hey, Suit Guys!
[TOMAO]
There's a whole bunch of them!
[KATO]
What?! Not just one?!
There were five
of 'em, for sure!
[KATO]
Five?!
[TOMAO] That creepy girl
and the gay-looking guy
are taking them all on alone!
[ALL gasp]
[HOJO yells]
[HOJO]
S-Sadako!
You... still back there?
[SADAKO]
Uh-huh.
[HOJO]
Good...
Save yourself!
Run now! Run, Sadako!
[KISHIMOTO] Um.. So your book
comes in next week, right?
[SEI]
Huh?
Your copy of Miranda
Foster's Labyrinth .
Hold on, how do you know that?
Actually, I overheard
you talking when I was
in the bookstore the other day.
[SEI] Wait a second, that was
you in the bookstore?!
So exactly what kind
of book is Labyrinth ?
Well, I haven't actually
read it yet, you know.
Oh, duh. I'm brain dead.
Still... I've got the feeling
that I'm not going
to like it very much.
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh?
[SEI] Right now, it feels
like we're in a labyrinth.
[KISHIMOTO]
Oh! Yeah, I can see that.
But the blurb on
the back of the book
says that there's no labyrinth
you can't get out of.
[KISHIMOTO giggles]
Let's do it!
S-Sadako...
[HOJO]
This is such... bullshit.
[HOJO] All of it...
I-It's just bullshit.
[ALL gasp]
[TOMAO] Aw, fuck, we dropped
our suits and guns.
Yeah... You wanna
go look for 'em?
[TOMAO]
Yeah.
[ding]
[KISHIMOTO screams]
[gasps]
Kishimoto! Kishimoto!
Don't look at it! If you lose
control and start to panic,
you'll never make it back alive!
Pull yourself
together, goddamit!
Kurono...?
We can make it back!
Do you understand me?
We will go back together!
[KATO]
We're going back.
We are going back!
I swore we would. We're all
going home together...
...now!
[KURONO]
Kato!
He got him!
[gasps]
[KURONO]
No! Kishimoto!
I've got to protect Kato!
I've got to protect him, Kurono!
I've gotta do it!
[KISHIMOTO] This feels...
right for some reason.
It used to make me happy
when someone told me
that I'd done the right thing,
that I'd been good.
But after I started school,
it stopped meaning
anything to me.
I didn't care.
I wanted praise
but nothing filled
that empty spot inside me.
Not until this.
This feels wonderful!
When I'm with Kato...
...when I can feel his
body against mine...
...so warm and full of life...
...none of the things we've
faced scare me anymore.
This is enough for me.
This is all I need.
[KURONO gasps]
[KISHIMOTO]
I'm sorry, Kurono,
but I have to spend my
last moments with Kato.
They say there's no labyrinth
you can't get out of.
Please, take care
of Kato for me.
[KISHIMOTO]
Protect him. Please, Kei.
[screams]
Just how late do you
plan on staying up?
All right, fine.
[KISHIMOTO screaming]
[ALL gasp]
[KISHIMOTO whimpering]
I love you, Kato...
I love you.
[ding]
[KURONO panting]
[KATO sobs]
[BOTH scream]
Kishimoto...
[KURONO grunts]
[yells]
This can't be happening...
This can't be happening!
This isn't happening!
[yelling continues]
[KURONO gasps]
[screams]
Fucker!
[gasps]
[screams]
Kishi... mo... to...
Kishi... mo...
I... won't let them...
beat me... I...
What now, you bitch?!
Are you going
to kill all of us?!
What do I do now?! Goddammit!
Tell me how to fight this
thing, Mr. Fucking Leader!
[KATO crying]
Damn it! You're not dead yet!
Look at Kei!
Do something to help him!
[KATO gasps]
He can't be dead!
Tell me that Kei isn't dead yet!
No, he's not dead yet.
But at this rate,
he will be soon!
We've got to get
him out of here!
While we still have a chance!
Can you carry him?
Can you carry Kei?
I don't know, but I'll try!
[SEI]
Stay alive...
You can't die.
You and I are going
for a little drive!
[KURONO groans]
We will!
[SEI grunts]
We... are not going to let
you kill us that easily!
[KATO]
Get moving, dammit!
[ALL panting]
Ka... K-Kato...
What is it? Are you...?
I want you...
..to kill me.
[BOTH gasp]
No fucking way!
[KURONO]
Kill me... please.
I'm not... gonna make it back.
I'm gonna die here.
Kato...
Please...! Shoot me!
[gasps]
[KURONO]
Kato...
Please just... shoot me!
[KATO]
Screams. Blood. Jealousy. Sighs.
Hope... And God, I hope.
Next time: "Big Brother."