[gasps]
[KURONO]
Uh... Kishimoto?
She is so hot.
[gasps]
[KURONO]
But... why is she at my place?
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh...?
[BOTH scream]
This... is yours?
[KURONO]
Uh... Huh?
[KISHIMOTO] You let me
borrow your jacket, remember?
I... think this fell out
when I changed in my room.
[KURONO] You came here
just to return this?
[KISHIMOTO]
Uh... Yeah.
Well... See ya.
[KURONO]
Uh, what?! B-But...
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
[KURONO]
Uh...?
Um, could I... please
get a glass of water?
Uh... Well, sure. Why not?
--[BABY giggles]
--[TETSUO laughs]
Up, ya go!
Up, ya go! Up, ya go!
[WIFE]
Hey!
Haven't I told you to cut the
engine on that fucking bike
--when you're near the house?
--[phone ringing]
The neighborhood bitch
squad's been on my ass again.
[ringing continues]
[phone beeps]
[TETSUO]
What...? Yeah.
Huh? Yeah... Okay.
I'm gonna go to the store
and buy some smokes, 'kay?
Get some milk
while you're there.
Okay, milk, it is.
[door creaks]
[slams]
[WIFE sighs]
[motorcyle revving]
[WIFE]
Oh, Jesus...
[KURONO]
I-Is tea cool with you?
Oh, yeah, I'm easy. I would've
been fine with plain water.
Hey! No problem.
I aim to please.
So, you live by yourself, huh?
Mm-hm. But you know, if you
would've just called me,
I could have come by and picked
up the I.D. at your place.
[stomach growls]
Uh... Hey, are you
a little hungry?
[KISHIMOTO gasps, whines]
--[motorcycle whines]
--[dog barking]
[laughing]
Did I miss something?
[KISHIMOTO]
Oh...
Uh-uh...
[KISHIMOTO] No... I
was just... hungry.
Oh! Was that your
dinner, Kurono?
[KURONO] Holy shit she said
my name! This could be my night!
Aw, don't worry about that,
there's a convenience
store close by.
Yeah?
[KURONO]
Mm-hm.
[door clicks]
[KISHIMOTO]
Okay, well...
I-I'm sorry about just
showing up like this...
See ya!
What was that about?
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
[knocking]
[KURONO]
Huh?
Hello?
I was wondering if...
If these apartments let
people keep pets here...
[KURONO]
Uh... I guess they do.
Huh... So, uh... Would
you consider keeping one?
[KURONO]
Uh... Keeping what?
Huh?!
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm being stupid.
[KURONO] No! It's all right!
It's-- It's all right!
You don't have to run off.
It's totally cool.
[gasps]
Are you sure?
Uh, yeah, but...
Whaddaya mean by "keep"?
In the same way that
you would keep a pet...
But if you can't,
it's really okay, really.
No! I-It's great!
I can... do that.
Look I... know that... what
I'm saying sounds crazy but...
Yeah.
Ah! I mean, no way! Not at all!
A-At least I don't think so!
Huh?
[KURONO] Oh, my god!
No way! This could mean...!
[KAYO chuckles]
Everything's fine.
And Ryota says he wants
to spend the night.
Oh, he's in kindergarten.
They won't care if
he's absent just one day.
Well, you were absent a lot
as a child, too. Remember?
[RYOTA]
Ya!
[KAYO]
Oh!
[RYOTA laughs]
There's been an accident!
Somebody call an ambulance!
Nee-naw! Nee-naw!
[KAYO]
Yes, yes!
I'll be sure to bring him
back tomorrow night.
Bye, now!
Hey, Grandma!
Did Mom say it was okay?
[KAYO] She said you
could spend the night.
[RYOTA]
All right!
So, where do you
want to go tomorrow?
[RYOTA]
THe Hinodedai Department Store!
I want you to buy
me a new toy truck!
[KAYO chuckles]
Of course, Dear.
I'll buy you whatever you want.
[KATO]
Ayumu...
Your neck. What happened?
[AYUMU]
Don't worry about it.
It happened again, didn't it?
I swear it's not a
big deal, believe me.
We really shouldn't be saying
bad things about our aunt.
[KATO]
Huh?
[AYUMU] I don't think
she's a bad person.
It's just that we showed
up here unexpectedly.
And... I think she's just a
little stressed, that's all.
[KATO]
I don't care.
That doesn't mean it's all
right for her to hit you.
Whatever, it really
doesn't matter anyway.
[NEWSCASTER] So, don't
you think the President
really put his foot in
his mouth this time?
Yes, I do. It makes you wonder
just what he was thinking.
[NEWSCASTER] Well, it seems
he certainly wasn't thinking
about the upcoming election.
Especially in light of his
other recent actions...
I wonder if...
Wonder if what?
I was wondering if I
could take a shower?
A shower?! I mean,
uh, be my guest...
[TV chattering]
[KURONO groans]
[KURONO] Hell yes!
Lady luck is so on my side!
Things could still
all go to hell,
but I can't think
about that right now.
--[motorcycles rumbling]
--[BIKERS laughing]
[HARUYA] Hey Tetsu... The old
hen been peckin' at ya again?
[TETSUO]
Eh, not so much...
[HARUYA] Well, if you're
not being p-whipped,
then what are you doing out at
night buyin' milk, ya big pussy?
[TETSUO]
Aw, bite me.
[MAN]
Hey, you punks!
[ALL]
Huh?
[MAN] There are decent people
trying to sleep around here.
Keep it down!
[KINJI]
What's up with this joker?
[HARUYA] It must really suck,
bein' a biker with a wife.
[TETSUO] No,it sucks
bein' an asshole.
[KOSUKE]
So... do we kill him?
[HARUYA] Come on, Tetsu...
Let's waste this fuck-bag.
[KID gasps]
[TETSUO]
Aw, shit.
[whimpers]
[HARUYA chuckles]
[gasps]
[HARUYA yells]
[KINJI, KOSUKE gasp]
What the hell?!
[KID]
Whoa!
[groans]
[HARUYA, MAN yell]
[KISHIMOTO]
Yes?
U-Uh! Nothing! Nothing
at all! I just, uh...
I'm gonna go out and
buy us dinner and drinks,
and snacks and stuff.
[KISHIMOTO]
That'd be nice...
[door slams]
[BIKERS laughing]
[HARUYA]
Rip the pants off of him!
Pull down his stinkin' pants.
I'm sorry! I-I'm so sorry!
[HARUYA]
It's too late, pecker-head!
[KOSUKE]
I bet he's got a tiny one!
[KURONO]
I wonder if...
[KURONO] Maybe she ran away
and has no place to go...
[dog barks]
[KURONO]
I mean...
She did ask me to keep
her like a pet, but...
...what's that mean?
Could it be... Just maybe...
Tonight's the night
I'm gonna score?!
But with a hot piece like her?
No fuckin' way!
This is too much!
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
I really just needed
to take a bath.
[KISHIMOTO breathes heavily]
[NISHI] Everyone who
comes to this room,
comes out of something
like a human fax machine.
[KISHIMOTO'S MOM]
It's your big sister, Kei.
She fell in the bathtub.
[NISHI]
We're all copies.
The original really is dead.
[KISHIMOTO'S MOM]
Don't worry, she's alive.
She just regained consciousness.
[NISHI]
A human fax machine.
[KISHIMOTO'S MOM]
She just regained
--consciousness.
--[NISHI] We're copies.
--She's alive... Alive... Alive.
--Dead... Dead... Dead.
We're all dead.
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
[BIKERS laugh]
[KINJI] Oh yeah,
he's squealin' like a pig.
[HARUYA] You're old
man's a real pussy, kid!
He should've
known better than
to fuck around
with the big boys!
--I mean, come on!
--[KOSUKE] Ready for beer, man!
--Let's go get some whiskey!
--[TETSUO] Here's a tip, kid.
Don't grow up to be a pathetic
loser like your dad, okay?
Let's go.
--Whoo!
--[BIKERS whooping]
[KAYO]
"Then Torao the Truck thought,
'Oh, no! At this rate, I'll
be asleep at the wheel!'
With all his might,
Torao rubbed his eyes
and flew down the highway."
[KAYO]
You are the most precious thing.
[KATO] "And then Ken went,
'Wah-ta-ta-ta-ta. Wa-ta!'
And he said, 'You are...
already... dead.'"
[NISHI] The way I see it...
The original really is dead.
[ALL gasp]
And everyone who
comes to this room
comes out of something
like a human fax machine...
So Kei...
Now that we really
are already dead...
What in the hell...
do we do now?
What can we do?
[KURONO] Of course you pick
now to look me in the face!
[KURONO]
I only bought Young Jump,
so I could buy the condoms!
[TETSUO] If you had cigarettes,
you should have said something.
Then I coulda saved myself the
trouble of goin' out to buy 'em.
Oh, please.
Spare me the bullshit.
If you wanna go out riding,
just say, "Hey, I'm
goin' out riding."
[TETSUO]
Here's your milk.
Just put it in the fridge
and it'll all be fine.
It'll all be fine... right?
[KURONO]
Uh...huh?
[KISHIMOTO]
Thank you.
I had a nice bath.
You're welcome.
[KURONO] Why is she back
in her clothes? Why?!
--Tell me why!
--[KISHIMOTO giggles]
That was a good comeback!
[laughs]
So did you... run away?
[KURONO]
She's blowing me off.
And what's with the distance?
This is not how I saw this
night going down at all.
But damn... I can't
just force myself on her.
That'd be too much like porn.
I guess you have to be in love
to make stuff like this work.
Like that can happen!
We only met last night!
--Of course...
--[KISHIMOTO] Hey...
--I could always throw
--Hey, do you have
--myself on her...
--another futon mattress?
[KURONO gasps]
W-What? Uh... Uh...
No.
I see...
[KURONO] That's right!
I don't have another mattress.
--Score!
--So then where would I...?
[KURONO]
And she knows it, too!
Finally... My time
has come! Yes! Yes!
Yeah... I guess I forgot
about the mattress.
In that case, could
we sleep... together?
Uh, actually, I guess
we'll have to... won't we?
Before I sleep I... need
to use the bathroom first.
[KURONO] Hell yes! Things
are really heatin' up!
[door clicks]
[KURONO]
Definitely!
[door slams]
[KURONO gasps]
So this is what they're like.
Well I... guess it's bed time.
I'm sorry... Could you
turn the other way?
Oh! Y-Yeah... Um...
[KISHIMOTO]
I can't sleep in my skirt...
...or it'll get all wrinkled.
[KURONO]
Oh... Uh... Right.
[KISHIMOTO]
Good night.
Yeah, well, here's hopin'.
Uh...
[KURONO]
Um...
[clears throat]
[KISHIMOTO]
What's wrong?
[KURONO]
Am I just supposed to do nothing
in a situation like this?
Or is... nothing gonna happen?
[KISHIMOTO]
What do you want... to happen?
[KURONO]
S... e... x...
[KISHIMOTO] I'm... your
pet, Kurono. Your pet.
And owners don't have
sex with their pets.
[KURONO]
What the hell does that mean?!
Uh... Hey, um... Y-Ya know...
I used to have a
dog back at home,
and I used to give him
lots of hugs and kisses...
[KISHIMOTO]
Yeah... Okay.
[KURONO]
Really?
[KISHIMOTO]
Mm-hm.
Oh... All right!
[KURONO]
Oh... This is so hot!
[KISHIMOTO]
When I...
When I was a kid,
I got into things.
And I was always cutting
myself up, you know?
[KURONO gasps]
Cutting?
Yeah, cutting.
But they're... all gone now.
All my cuts are gone!
The cut that needed
eight stitches...
The cut from two months ago.
And the cuts from...
[gasps]
[KISHIMOTO]
And... When I went home...
I... still existed.
[KISHIMOTO]
What am I... What am I?
I have no place to go.
No house to come home to.
No parents...
[KISHIMOTO]
I'm sorry, Kurono.
This isn't the time
for me to throw away...
...my virginity.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
We're at the subway once more.
And once again, our morning news
starts off with more information
about those missing
high school boys.
[TETSUO sighs]
[REPORTER]
Since the boys disappeared,
this story has been investigated
from many different angles.
But the identities of
the missing students
still remain a mystery.
However, authorities believe
that tracing the sales route
of a certain umbrella
and adult magazine
will yield some promising leads.
And we suspect even more
surprising developments
are in store in the near future.
And yet, so many questions
still remain unanswered.
What has happened to the boys?
Where are they now?
And why did they
disappear so mysteriously?
From the scene, this has been
your special morning report.
[KURONO]
In the end...
Two virginities remained
intact last night.
So when will Gantz...
call again?
[NISHI]
Domestic violence...
...milk and necessities...
...stalkers... shoplifters...
bikers... an idol...
...and obsession.
Shall we get down to business?