--[KAYO groaning]
--[RYOTA] Grandma! Grandma!
[SUZUKI ALIENS screeching]
No! Please don't!
[KAYO]
Don't worry, Ryota...
[heartbeat]
[KURONO]
What the hell is that thing?
I-It's... the final boss!
[KURONO]
There's no way...
...I'll ever survive this.
[KURONO]
Am I...
...gonna die?
[blasts firing]
Now what?
Kato... you wait here, okay?
[KATO, HOJO]
Huh?
What are you thinking?! Without
him, it's just you and me!
You do... know how to
use these guns, right?
[KATO]
But there must--
There must be something that
I can do, too, isn't there?
[KISHIMOTO]
Please... Just wait here.
Okay?
[KURONO]
I can't just stand here...
I-I've gotta do something!
[SUZUKI ALIEN]
Hey, Yuzo...
[blasts firing]
Kill them!
[KISHIMOTO]
Keep shooting! Kill them all!
[heartbeat]
Yuzo?
[KURONO]
Aw, damn! Not this again!
[SUZUKI ALIEN]
Yuzo. Yuzo-bro.
Hey, Yuzo.
[KURONO] And who the
hell is Yuzo anyway?!
We're screwed! These
bastards just won't die!
[KISHIMOTO]
But why not?!
[KISHIMOTO yelps]
[SUZUKI ALIEN]
Yuzo.
Yuzo-bro...
Yuzo-bro.
Hey, Yuzo.
[KURONO]
I'm not Yuzo, goddamnit!
[SUZUKI ALIEN]
Yuzo.
Yuzo-bro.
[KURONO]
Am I supposed to say something?
[SUZUKI ALIEN]
Hey ,Yuzo.
Yes! I'm fucking Yuzo!
[KURONO gasps]
Huh? Uh?
[SUZUKI ALIEN]
What place has the best melons?
Kantaro!
So refreshing...
Hah! Hah! Hah!
Were you able to make
some friends? Kagoshima?
Okay, I have to stay calm.
Just relax...
I should do something now,
while they're still smiling.
[gasps]
[KURONO] Why the hell is
that thing on me?!
[KURONO]
Ow...!
[squeals]
[KURONO]
Oh, shit!
[KURONO] It still hasn't
turned to face me.
[KURONO]
I still have a chance...
I might just be able
to get out of he--
--[gasps, whimpers]
--[squawking]
[heartbeat]
[snarls]
[HOJO]
Are they both...?
[KATO] Yeah... There was
nothing we could do.
[growling]
[HARUYA]
Where is that fuckwad?
Why is he takin' so long?
[KURONO whimpering]
[HOJO]
There's still more!
There's no end to it!
How long to go?
There's... only 15 minutes left.
How many of us
will survive this game?
[KURONO]
I'm not gonna die...!
I'm not gonna die!
Don't any of you move!
Or... I swear I'll kill him!
Cock-a-doodle-doo, motherfucker!
Do you want that?!
[KURONO]
Shit!
No... way!
[gasps]
[screeches]
[HARUYA]
Whoa! What the fuck?!
[KURONO]
I said... I'm not gonna die!
[KURONO yelling, grunting]
[screeches]
[SUZUKI ALIENS screeching]
[KURONO]
Oh, please, God!
[KURONO yelps]
[HARUYA gasps]
Whoa!
Ho-Holy shit!
[KURONO pants]
I did it... I did it!
[gasps]
[building creaking]
Oh, fuck!
[screams]
[screeches]
[KURONO screams]
[BOTH gasp]
[KURONO] Look at you now,
you piece of shit!
I showed you, you creepy fuck!
[KATO]
Kei!
Oh! Hey, Kato.
We heard the noise.
What's going on here?
[KURONO]
It's over now.
It's over.
[MAN]
Dude, what happened?
[PEOPLE murmuring]
[KATO]
It's over?
[KURONO]
Yeah, I fuckin' ended it.
I did it all by myself!
This is the end!
I guess they really
can't see us.
[HOJO]
No, wait.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[HOJO]
I don't think it's over yet.
[KURONO gasps]
But there's no way that can be.
That thing musta been
--completely buried!
--[HARUYA screams]
--[KISHIMOTO screams]
--[KURONO gasps]
[gasps]
Haruya!
What... the hell is that?!
What is it, Kei?
It's the final boss!
[KISHIMOTO] What?
What are you talking about?!
How the hell is that
thing not dead?!
[KATO gasps]
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
[ONLOOKER]
Huh?
--[ALL gasp]
--[KISHIMOTO screams]
[ALL whimper]
Ha... Haruya...
--[HOJO whimpering]
--[SUZUKI BOSS growls]
[GROUP gasps]
[whimpering continues]
W-W-What the hell is that...?
[whimpers]
[ONLOOKER]
Huh...?
Huh?
[KURONO gasps]
[roars]
[HOJO screams]
[yells]
[grunts]
Kei, it's coming after you!
[roars]
[KATO]
Run for it!
[KURONO]
No fucking way.
[BOTH]
Huh?
You think I'm some
kinda pussy, huh?!
Gimme a fucking break!
I'm done with this!
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
Kurono...?
I'll fucking kill you!
[KURONO growls]
[SUZUKI BOSS roars]
Watch out for his beak!
Hang on!
[KURONO grunting, groaning]
It hurts, you son
of a bird bitch!
[SUZUKI BOSS roars]
Let go!
Fuck!
Kei! Kei!
You piece of shit!
[screeches]
I'm not... going out like this!
[KURONO]
Damn...
[KURONO screams]
[KURONO]
Damn it! No... No!
[KURONO screams]
[police sirens]
[KATO panting]
Kei!
[KISHIMOTO]
Kurono!
[KATO]
Kei!
[KISHIMOTO]
Kurono!
[KATO]
Kei! Are you all right?!
Kei!
[KURONO groans]
I... I think so...
Oh-- Oh, thank God...
Thank God...
[TETSUO]
So... is it over... now?
[HOJO] I think so...
It stopped counting down.
[buzzing]
--[TETSUO] Whoa!
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
Am I going back to the room?
[KURONO grunts]
[KATO]
I guess, this...
--...is all that's left of us.
--[dog barks]
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
Well, don't take
this the wrong way,
but I am glad you're still here.
--Perversions and all.
--[TETSUO] Hey!
Can we leave now? Or what?
[KATO] Well... I think we
have to wait for our scores.
[TETSUO]
Scores?
Screw the scores.
[gasps]
The body's gone...
[ding]
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh? There, look! It's starting.
[HOJO]
Huh...?
[KURONO] "Do something"?
C'mon, he's a dog!
[DOG whines]
So we're sitting here getting
scored... But for what?
If what that Nishi kid
told us is the truth,
when your score
reaches 100 points,
you supposedly get to go free.
[HOJO gasps]
What the hell?
So this really is
some kind of game?!
Aw... Another boob joke?!
It says 90 points to go, so...
Does that mean I'll
be free at 100?
Oh!
I guess that's five points each.
Because I've killed
two of 'em so far.
[KISHIMOTO]
What?!
I-I mean, you fought so
many of those things!
[KATO]
Yeah, I fought them...
But unlike you, I only
killed one of them.
I get it! The more you kill,
the sooner you're set free.
So I don't just
have to survive...
I have to keep on killing.
[KURONO]
Sadako? Who's that?!
[KATO]
Yeah.
[KISHIMOTO]
Her! She's hiding! Over there.
[KURONO]
Following the fag?
[HOJO gasps]
So who here's the homo?
[HOJO] Maybe one of the
guys who died was gay.
[ALL gasp]
[ding]
What's with...
[yelps]
[HOJO]
Huh?! H-Hey! I'm not gay!
Uh-- Gimme a fuckin' break!
Stay the hell away from
me! I-I-I'll kill ya!
Yeah?! Like I would
even touch you!
[ALL gasp]
Yeah, right!
Aww... C'mon, Kato!
So what if he's gay?
But I'm not! I'm not gay!
[TETSUO]
Oh, my turn?
Hey, what's this shit about?
[TETSUO] What the fuck?
Now how did he score so high?!
That's incredible, Kei!
That's great! Thirty-eight
points! But how?
"The errand boy"? Me?!
[TETSUO]
Whoa! It actually opened!
So can we go home now?
[KURONO]
I wonder where she's going...
[KATO] Well I'm sure
it won't be too long
before we'll all be meeting
up again in that room.
So I guess, I'll see ya.
[KISHIMOTO]
Uh, Kato?
Um, you wouldn't happen to uh...
...to live by yourself
by any chance, would you?
[KATO]
Uh...
Well, actually my brother and I
live with one of our relatives.
Why...?
[KISHIMOTO]
Oh! It's nothing!
Really! I... was just
curious, that's all!
Okay!
[KURONO]
Uh...
Damn...!
Somehow... I managed
to survive again...
But right now...
surviving kinda sucks.
[TETSUO]
Children need to drink milk
in order to grow up
strong and healthy.
You could say that
milk and breast milk
are two of humanity's
greatest treasures.
All right, enough of this crap!
I don't wanna die!
[KATO]
Next time, "Goodbye."