[TAMAO] Hey, look, that--that
big gold one's comin' our way.
[KONTA]
Aw, shit!
You want... to try it now?
Yeah, now that we've found our
suits and guns, let's kick ass.
Kato... just shoot me...
Okay, dammit!
[SEI]
Have you gone crazy?!
Dear god! I'm sorry!
Please... just do it now!
[SEI whimpers]
[SEI gasps]
[screams]
It stopped melting!
It worked!
[SEI gasps]
You're right! It stopped!
[KURONO]
God, it fuckin' hurts!
How did you know...
...that shooting it would
stop the dissolving?
[KATO] I-I didn't.
I just hoped it would work.
--I'm sorry, Kei.
--[KURONO] Fuck...
I wish I... could do something.
Just keep him alive.
If he survives the game,
he'll be healed.
Huh?! Just what does that mean?
As long as we're able to
kill the remaining statue.
And if we win the game before
the time limit expires,
the Gantz will transport us
all back to that room, and
everyone who's still alive will
have all their injuries healed.
But how can that be... true?
I want you to stay here
and watch over him.
I've got one last idea
that I wanna try.
[TAMAO]
It hasn't noticed us yet.
[KONTA] You want to attack
from behind, right?
[TAMAO]
Hell yeah!
Quick and easy.
Right.
[BOTH gasp, scream]
[TAMAO]
Holy fuck, it hurts!
[KONTA] Sweet Jesus! Trying
to fuckin' stick my arm!
[TAMAO] W-What the fu--
That's not my hand!
Hey, asshole! Don't throw
it away! That's-- Ah!
The fuck?! It blew itself up!
We're gonna fucking die
if we don't do something!
[gasps]
Put 'em back on!
I can't, man!
[BOTH grunt]
[TAMAO]
Oh, my god...
[gasps]
[grunts]
[KATO]
There it is!
The trap gun.
Sorry...
[clattering]
Goddammit!
I don't have time
for this right now!
[groans]
[ding]
[KATO groans]
My suit's not... working!
[gasps]
[SEI] Kei, why did you
ask me to fuck you?
Honestly.
[KURONO groans]
I'm sorry, but...
I just thought you looked
like you might say yes.
--That's all.
--[gasps]
I thought you'd say
something like that...
[KURONO]
What's that mean?
That you're that kind of guy,
and I'm... you know...
That girl...
The one who just got killed.
I know you loved her.
And it's okay.
I'm a big girl, and I've
learned to live with it.
But she told me you two
were just a little too
different from each other.
I've been hoping that I'm
not quite that different.
Because I...
[KURONO gasps]
[gasps]
[KATO groaning]
[SEI panting]
Just leave me and save yourself!
Run, goddammit, Sei!
Move your ass!
[SEI]
There's a book!
What?!
A book that I ordered by Miranda
Foster called Labyrinth .
[gasps]
[KISHIMOTO]
Her name was Sei Sakuraoka.
It looked like she had ordered
some book called Labyrinth .
Sei Sakuraoka... Labyrinth ...
[SEI] It's supposed
to come in next week
over at the bookstore
by the train station.
Kei, I don't know
what's going to happen,
but if something does,
would you get that book for me?
[KURONO]
Huh?
If something does happen,
would you... do that for me?
[KURONO]
Wait a minute!
Please, Kei, I've been taking
a lot of kickboxing
classes lately.
I've even had some matches.
[KEI]
That's fuckin' nuts! Don't!
Maybe if I kill that thing,
you might end up falling
for me after all.
[SEI]
Kei, I will protect you!
[KATO screams]
Come on!
[SEI gasping]
[KATO groans]
[SEI yells]
[VISHNU STATUE screeches]
No way...
I'm actually winning!
Kei, look! I'm going to beat it!
[KURONO gasps]
[SEI] We will pick up
that book together, Kei.
All right?
I'm going to win.
And then we'll go home!
Together!
[gasps]
Fuck.
[screams]
[KURONO gasps]
[KURONO]
So I'm as goon as dead...
Not even worth killin', huh?
[KURONO]
It's over... Everyone's dead.
We're no match for those things!
[KATO groaning]
Goddammit!
[yells]
I can... still win!
[screaming]
I'm so sorry...
[KATO]
Kei! Are you alive?!
Please, Kei!
Goddammit, Kei!
Give me some kind of
sign you're not dead!
Ka... to...?
Wait for me.
I'll kill the other one!
Don't you die on me, Kei!
Please!
[KATO] Goku and Kenshiro
are really cool,
but you're way cooler, Kei!
[KURONO]
Who me? Really?
[KURONO] You're... the one
who's like Kenshiro, Kato.
I guess... he didn't
make it either.
I'm gonna sleep
with this tonight.
But then you'll have
dreams about the rain.
That's all right
with me, Brother!
Now I can't wait for it to rain.
I'll be damned. It really
is raining, Little Brother.
Wait! Hold on a second,
Kato! It's me!
[KATO gasps]
[VISHNU STATUE]
Really! It's me! Miyafuji!
[gasps]
I never even saw what
was coming, Kato!
But somehow, those
things must've...
...eaten o-or absorbed
me or something!
[KATO]
What's... going on here?
[VISHNU STATUE laughs]
Are you afraid of me?
I can't blame you
for being suspicious.
C'mon, put the gun away.
[KATO]
No!
[gasps]
[VISHNU STATUE]
This is amazing!
It feels totally
fucking awesome!
Oh, yes! It feels great!
I can do anything,
and you can't stop me!
You don't have a
chance of beating me.
Oh, by the way, this statue
has something to ask you.
Who in the fuck are
you people anyway?
Why do you exist here?
Who sent you?
We never did a
goddamn thing to you.
Now I'm the only one left!
[VISHNU STATUE] Are you just
gonna stand there and ignore me?
Sayonara, Fuck-Nuts!
[KATO screams]
[gasps]
[KATO]
The gun has two triggers!
Could one of them be...
for locking onto a target?
[KATO]
It's no good.
I can't get closer, but I can't
keep on dodging either!
[VISHNU STATUE]
Hey, you're pretty spry.
You wanna try doing this
for about an hour?
I've got all day, Kiddo.
You go to hell!
Shit!
[screams]
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah! Baby!
[VISHNU STATUE gasps]
Oh, crap!
[panting]
Damn it! What is this?!
Shit! Aah!
Oh! Hey, wait a second!
What are you trying to do?
[VISHNU STATUE]
Stop! It's me, Miyafuji!
You're not gonna
sacrifice me, are you?
You bet your ass I am!
I'm sending you...
where you belong!
[VISHNU STATUE screaming]
Ayumu!
[AYUMU groans]
Big Brother?
I'm sorry...
I guess... it really
did rain, Big Brother.
Don't you think you beat me yet!
You little hypocrite!
You really think you're
something, don't you?!
[KATO gasping]
It's time to party.
But first... all the
better to see you with.
Heh. Cool.
[MONSTER]
Aw, poor baby.
Are you scared stiff?
You're going back this time!
[MONSTER laughs]
[groans]
K-Kato...
[MONSTER yells]
[laughing]
Fall down, damn you!
Masaru? Big Brother!
I'll kill you!
I'm gonna fuckin'
kill you, meat sack!
[KATO]
I can't pass out!
[AYUMU whimpering]
Masaru?
Masaru!
[KATO]
I have to go back!
[MONSTER]
Why won't you fall down?!
I'm gonna rip you
limb from limb!
You sly son of a bitch!
[KATO]
I'm going back, goddammit!
I'm going to beat him,
and I'm going home!
[KATO yells]
[MONSTER groans]
That hurt! That hurt!
[yells]
You! You think you can beat me?!
Don't fuck with me!
I'm gonna eat your
brains for breakfast!
Imagine this, asshole!
[KATO]
What in the hell am I doing?
Is this for real?
There's no way I
can really beat him.
Look at all those hands!
[BOTH giggling]
[groans]
[KATO] You're so cool!
You really are, Kei!
Why is it that you
never get beat?
[KURONO] Kato, if you think
you're gonna lose, you will!
That's what causes it!
Huh? 'Cause I think I'll lose?
[KATO groans]
You're finished! [cackles]
You fool!
[screams]
[KATO]
I will go home.
Kei, don't die! I'm coming!
Ayumu, I'll keep my promise!
[thud]
[AYUMU sobbing]
Masaru..?
K-Kato...
[KATO groaning]
[KATO]
Please...
Let my little brother, Ayumu...
be strong... on his own.
And let him...
find happi... ness.
[ding]
[KURONO sobbing]
[gasps]
[sobs] No!
[KURONO]
Bring him back!
Do it!
Bring him back, asshole!
[screams]
[KATO]
Kei...
[KISHIMOTO]
Kurono...
[KURONO]
This can't be real...
I'm alone.
I'm... all alone.
[KURONO]
This can't be real.
No one's here.
This can't be real! Not yet!
Give me a break!
What the hell is that?!
Hey, stop screwing with me!
Next episode,
"Don't Ever Say That Again."