[ALL gasping]
All right, Gantz,
what alien is it now?
No matter what you bring on,
I'll fuckin' kill it!
C'mon! Show me now!
Which alien is it, Gantz?!
[gasps]
What in the fuck?
Me?!
That can't be right!
[KURONO]
Put your suits on, dammit!
Just put 'em on!
The transfer's gonna
start any minute now,
and you don't wanna
be without one.
[NOZAKI]
Hold on, we're fighting you?
No way!
The Gantz is just
trying to set me up!
I know it is!
Sneaky little shit!
It has to be!
But I'm a normal person! I am!
[KURONO] Look, just get
those suits on. Hurry!
[KURONO]
Stop fuckin' around, Gantz!
Gantz? Who the hell is Gantz?
This is Gantz!
This fuckin' thing here!
And all of this shit
is his fuckin' fault!
[MUROTO]
So, is this lucky or what?
Huh?
We already died once, right?
Those guys who shot
us think so, too.
Heh. So if we make it
back to the real world,
it'll be like hitting the
game of life's reset switch.
--Am... I wrong?
--[KURONO shouting]
[MUROTO] Plus, we can kill all
the others before we go back.
I mean, it's not
a crime to kill people
who are already dead, is it?
All six of them. Six...
[MUROTO] Or make that seven,
you slimy fuck.
You've been making me
do all your dirty work.
I'm gonna love this.
[KAJIURA] Heh.
You little murdering freak.
The juvenile laws may
protect you from the cops,
but you're not safe from me.
Stop acting like
you're running the show.
[chuckles] Okay, we'll play
this part a little longer.
If those stupid sheep
swallow our little act,
they'll play right
into our hands.
And we'll get to kill
all we want later.
Oh, you know acting...
is my forte.
So let me get this right.
If the rest of us all wanna
make it back to our real lives
in one piece, we're
gonna have to fight you?
No, that's not it!
Up until this time, one of us
has never been the target!
But that picture--
It is you, right?
[KURONO] No! Like I said,
Gantz is fucking me over!
But Kurono...
Exactly what is Gantz?
[gasps]
Oh, that... The big black ball.
Now wait just one minute!
This is a kid
we're talking about!
And a buncha grown-ups
are supposed to
gang up on him and kill him?!
That's just crazy!
So you're saying you'd
do it if he was an adult?
[FURUTA]
Hmph! Don't be absurd!
And where have you two been?
In the bathroom.
So, have you guys decided
anything out here yet?
We've been going
around in circles.
Well, okay.
How 'bout we try this?
Let's ask our new friend here
to give us a little proof.
More proof?
That's right.
There must be something
that could make us believe
this story about monsters
and weapons or whatever.
So do you have any proof?
I just showed you the power
of this suit, didn't I?
Yeah... But that could'a
been a trick, you know?
Any kinda proof will do.
That is, anything as long
as it's convincing enough.
[KATO panting]
K-Kato?!
Um, Kurono? What is it?
What's the matter with you?
Yeah, what's wrong?
Didn't any of you
see that just now?!
[KATO screaming] Stop it!
[MUROTO, KAJIURA
grunting, laughing]
Kei, help me!
Kato!
Kishimoto... is waiting, too!
Get away from him, damn you!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Stop, Kurono! For God's
sake, put this gun down!
[KURONO]
Stop it, Gantz!
You son of a bitch!
Why show me that?!
Kato is dead, Gantz!
You killed him!
[MIKA gasps]
[gasps] No way!
It can't be!
[gasps] Stay away!
You! Stay away from me!
What the fuck?
Hey, what is this?
[NOZAKI]
Jesus!
[yelps] Go away!
Th-They followed me here!
[FURUTA]
What's wrong with you people?!
Yeah, what's goin' on?
--Beats me.
--[MIKA] Go away!
[KURONO]
Kato, I can't shoot!
[SAITO whimpering]
I can't shoot!
[YOSHINO]
Stay back!
Stay back! No!
[MIKA] Get away from me!
Get away from me!
Damn you!
[ALL gasping]
Damn you, Gantz!
Stop fucking with me!
I'll make you pay, you
cock-sucking eight ball!
[gasps] Hey, no time lag!
Well, fuck!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
That's sweet...
[MIKA]
What happened just now?
He shot that gun!
He shot it right at us!
He really must be
the Kurono Alien!
I-I'm not a goddamn alien!
I just saw my friend who died
being attacked, you asshole!
Did anyone else here see that?
[ALL gasping]
Like we'd believe you now.
But I'm telling you the truth!
Or maybe you thought...
...it'd be a convenient excuse
to take a couple
of potshots at us.
You're full of shit!
Honestly, that's what
happened! Really!
[ALL murmur]
Something's wrong here.
There's no more time lag
on the fucking guns!
They used to have--
[SAITO]
That's enough!
All we said was that we wanted
you to show us some proof,
and what did you do?
You pulled out
that gun and started
shooting up the whole
fucking place instead!
There's no way we're
gonna trust you!
Wait a second, everyone!
We can't just jump to
conclusions like this.
--We can't!
--[BOTH chuckle]
Will you just listen to me?!
So what do you guys all think?
'Cause you know...
his story just doesn't seem
that plausible or
believable to me.
[KURONO growls]
Here's a thought.
How about we just put
aside those evil thoughts
of killing or not killing,
and just figure out on
our own what we should do.
Damn straight!
'Cause I sure as hell
don't trust this fuck!
Piss off!
Look, if our lives are
really on the line here,
then we need to stay
calm and carefully
talk our way through this.
Well if you ask me, I think
we should trust Kurono.
Trust a guy who shoots
at us without warning?
Well, how about this, then?
We all saw for ourselves the
power these suits seem to have
when our little friend was
hassling Mr. Saito there.
Why don't we all put
them on, just to be safe?
And to be even more safe,
we keep Kurono here
under an armed guard.
Makes sense, right?
What?!
--[gun cocks]
--[gasps]
It's all right, I'll keep him
covered while you change.
Hurry up and put on
those suits quick, okay?
And don't forget to grab a gun!
Come off it! I don't have a
reason to shoot anyone here!
Yeah? And just how
do we know that?
You just took a shot at us!
You bastard...!
Right, let's all get changed.
We can take turns in
the hallway for privacy.
Hang on! I think that
we should trust him!
I think we should get dressed.
It'll save a lot of time if the
two of us get dressed together.
Wait a minute.
I thought you were...
Yes, his teacher.
But none of that's going
to make a difference
if I die out there.
I have no intention
of using this, myself,
but it might not be a bad idea
to protect yourself, young lady.
[YOSHINO grunting]
[FURUTA grunting]
[KAJIURA]
Okay, we're all dressed.
So, if we can go
by what he said,
we're supposed to be
transferred somewhere--
[screams]
[ALL gasp, scream]
[KURONO yells]
What the fuck are you doing?!
[KURONO]
That's what I wanna know!
What are you two
assholes up to?!
[retches]
[MIKA] Does... anyone
know where we are?
Well, as I recall, this
building has ten floors.
There's a fairly expensive
European-style bar on the first,
and from the second floor on up,
it's all adult entertainment.
Been here a time or two, huh?
[SAITO stammers] Well--
[MUROTO screams]
Mr. Kajiura!
The little twat's got my gun.
Smooth move, Genius.
Too late now.
Okay, anyone still trust him?
[ALL gasp]
Now don't do
anything rash, Kurono.
We're not going to
do anything to you,
so come on down and
give us the gun.
There's nothing left
to discuss here.
You have to trust me if
you wann get out of this,
or else you're dead!
[FURUTA] Well, no one's
gonna talk to you politely
if you're pointing
a gun at them!
Give it here, and come on down!
This is no time for
negotiating with him!
Can't you see that he's
aiming that thing at us?!
And pretty words won't mean
jack shit if you get shot!
I know that!
But I don't wanna see
a kid with a future
getting screwed either.
That's worth taking
a risk in my book.
But we have to work
it out together!
We've got to help each other!
Those guys are
already murderers!
Huh?!
[KURONO]
It's true! I saw them do it!
They beat a homeless man to
death with metal baseball bats!
[BOTH laugh nervously]
[ALL]
Huh?
[KURONO]
Look, I'm not making it up.
They did it at Ratenin, th-that
busted up temple on the news!
[gasps] Ratenin?!
Do you know
something about that?
Well, uh...
[KURONO]
That's right.
They killed that poor homeless
guy on the temple grounds!
[KAJIURA] Hah! Are you really
gonna believe what he tells you?
There's no way we'd do
something awful like that!
Like hell you would!
Stop the fucking charade!
We all saw you!
[ALL gasp]
[FURUTA screams]
[YOSHINO groans]
[MIKA yelps]
Oh, what the fuck?!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Stop it, Gantz!
Stop fucking with me!
Like I said, this is all
some kind of sneaky trap!
He's screwing with
everything somehow.
Don't let him fool you!
[SAITO]
There he is again!
You don't look so good.
Are you all right, Saito?
Go... away!
Hey, is something wrong?
Leave me alone, dammit!
[gasps]
[screams]
[ALL scream]
[FURUTA] Knock it off!
Get ahold of yourself!
What were you shooting at?!
Did you see something?!
What's wrong with you?
Calm down!
[FURUTA]
Huh? Everyone just calm down!
[KURONO panting]
Kato... I'm in trouble.
No one believes me!
[KAJIURA]
Look, all we have to do
is kill the Kurono Alien, right?
It said if we do that,
then we get to go home!
An alien...
But if he's--
He's goin' bye-bye.
[BOTH grunt]
[gunshots]
Hey! What are you doing?!
Killing a monster, Old Man.
[gunshots]
[KURONO gasps]
[KURONO grunts]
[MUROTO]
He's not getting away.
He should be on
the eighth floor.
Fine, then let's
head to the seventh.
If we get under him,
he can't get out.
Then we've got him.
[KURONO panting]
[screams]
[KURONO]
Shit...!
Gantz, you fucking suck!
[KAJIURA]
Okay, here's how I see it.
Kurono's right above us
on the eighth floor.
You got that?
There's just one of him
and seven of us.
If we all charge him at once,
he'll go down easy.
Just wait a minute!
We all believe the story Kurono
told us at one point, didn't we?
What the fuck are
you talking about?!
I saw it fucking happen!
I saw him! He turned into
that goddamn leg-breaker!
Okay, but was it Kurono or Gantz
who made you see that illusion?
[SAITO]
Of course it was Kurono!
I just wanna go back!
For God's sake,
just let me outta here!
Hey, weren't you the
one who was saying
what a relief
it was to be here?!
[SAITO]
Uh...
Okay, let's just all calm down.
Arguing amongst ourselves isn't
going to accomplish
anything at all!
And as for you two over there,
why did you start shooting?!
Because we wanna
survive, of course.
Don't you wanna
survive, Old Man?
'Cause we sure do.
[FURUTA] You're talking
about two different things.
And you shouldn't
be using that gun!
[MIKA]
He's right!
Everything that's
happened so far
could have a lot of
different explanations.
We still don't know if Kurono's
really our enemy or not!
[YOSHINO]
But we have no choice!
Huh?
[YOSHINO]
We all want to survive.
So that means we have to--
What other choice do we have?!
[MIKA gasps]
But you're... Kurono's teacher.
And you're getting on my nerves!
Fine! I'm his teacher!
Who gives a shit?!
Now just hang on, dammit!
Not all of us agree that
we have to kill 'im.
If we stop and think it through,
there must be a way
of getting through this
without killing anybody!
And what if the
other way is wrong?
What if your fucking noble
intentions get us all killed?
[FURUTA] For God's sake, are
you even listening to yourself?!
Look, if none of you wanna
shoot him, you can stay here.
The two of us'll handle it.
[NOZAKI]
Huh?
Hey!
[FURUTA] Hey, wait a minute!
Come back here!
[water running]
You've given me shit,
Gantz, oh yes.
But I won't lose to you.
[KURONO]
I won't lose to anyone!
Kurono! I don't have any
personal issues with you,
but since it's either my ass or
yours that's on the line here,
guess who loses?
[FURUTA]
Please, don't do this!
The time for talk
is over, baldy!
[ALL gasp]
[KURONO yells]
[ALL scream]
[panting]
Kurono! No! Don't do this!
[MUROTO]
Son of a bitch!
[yells]
[MUROTO screams]
Die, Kurono!
[KURONO] You're not runnin'
this show, fuckwad!
And I'm gonna whip
your evil ass!
[KAJIURA groans]
[MUROTO screams]
Help! He's gonna kill me!
[YOSHINO]
Kurono! Stop!
Hi, Teach...?
[YOSHINO] You never listened
in class, so listen now.
If you make one more move...
...I'll blow you away.
No, wait! Put the gun down!
[YOSHINO]
Now, get your ass over here!
Now!
[pants]
Just what are... you doing?
None of us here wants to
believe that we're dead,
but I believe it! And...
...if someone's promising me I
can live by killing you, then...
...I'll do it.
I'll do it!
You would... really shoot me?
You bitch!
What the hell am I
supposed to do, dammit?!
[MIKA screams]
Okay, Teach, that's
enough for now.
I'll take over the
lesson from here.
But-- But I--
Just step the fuck
away from him, you cunt!
So, Kurono, are you still
gonna fight me now?
You're taking her hostage?
For God's sakes, man,
what are you doing?!
That girl isn't
involved in this!
Let her go!
Now, you know that
I can't do that.
We still have to kill the
Kurono Alien, don't we?
I have to do this!
[KAJIURA]
Kurono! What's it gonna be?
If you keep fighting, I'm gonna
hafta fuck this bitch up.
Are you okay with that?
[MUROTO chuckles]
What a fucking idiot!
Can't he think of something
better than this?
This is for your own good, kid.
Stop tryna fight with us, okay?
Give yourself up, and
I let her go unhurt.
You bastard!
Please, Kurono, I--
[KAJIURA]
Stop fucking around with us!
Everybody else here
wants to survive...
...don't we?
[MIKA whimpering]
[YOSHINO] Life is like
a maze, a labyrinth.
Once you get lost,
there's no easy way out.
Oh, well. It's not like
it matters anymore.
Next episode,
"No Labyrinth is Inescapable."