I'm sorry if I've been sending
mixed signals to you...
But we've passed the point
where we can hold anything back.
Yeah, you're right.
[KURONO] Maybe we will all
go back together. Shall we?
--[KATO] Yeah.
--[TOMAO] Dude! That priest
is gonna get killed!
[KURONO]
Not if we nail that alien first!
[KATO]
Yeah, let's do it!
...Amida... Namu Amida...
[TOKUGAWA]
Namu Amida... Namu Amida Butsu!
I-It stopped!
Could it be that
reciting scriptures
actually calms them down?
Stop shooting, you stupid fools!
I discovered that reciting
scriptures calms them down!
That's not possible, you ass!
It's true! For it is written
that with true faith,
one can always find
a way to--! [screams]
[ALL gasp]
[KURONO yells]
[BOTH gasp]
--[KONTA] Right on!
--[TOMAO] Yeah!
[OKAZAKI]
Aw, yeah! Woo-hoo!
If he did it, then...
...we can do it, too!
[KATO]
Kei?
Kill him!
[TOMAO]
Do it!
[OKAZAKI] Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him, dammit!
Kei, wait!
[OKAZAKI]
Kill him!
[gasps]
Dude... You're just
fuckin' awesome!
Come on, you guys! Let's do it!
[GROUP yells]
[TOMAO] Come on! Let's show
that mother who's boss!
[KONTA]
There can only be one! [laughs]
[KURONO yells]
He's nuts!
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh?
[SEI] I mean, he's gotten
too used to this.
[KISHIMOTO]
No! That's not true!
[SEI]
Isn't it?
[KISHIMOTO]
But how could he get used to--
to something like this?
That's why... he seems the
most likely to survive.
Kurono's strong, but--
But he's not a...
[TOMAO]
We can do this, guys!
Let's get that big,
red motherfucker!
[OKAZAKI] The legs!
Blow up his fucking legs!
[KURONO]
This is it! I'm gonna kill it!
I'm a hero, goddammit!
Nothing can beat me!
[KURONO] This is where
I belong! This world!
[KURONO yelling]
[GROUP groans, gasps]
[KATO]
Kei!
[grunting continues]
[KURONO grunts]
[yells]
[MIYAFUJI]
Um... Excuse me, please.
[KATO]
Huh?
[MIYAFUJI] Don't you think
we should do something here?
I mean, rather than just
standing around like this,
maybe we should go help.
[KATO]
Ah... I-- I guess so.
[KURONO]
Die! Die, you bastard!
[growls]
You are really pissing me off!
[KURONO growls, yells]
[KISHIMOTO screams]
--[KATO grunts]
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
[JJ growls, yells]
[KATO, KISHIMOTO groan]
Ah! Are you okay?
[KATO]
Yeah... My suit's working fine.
[KURONO growls, grunts]
[yelps]
Hey! Stay back, you stupid cunt!
[gasp] Shit...!
And I just spoke
to the bitch again.
[KURONO yells]
It's anticipating his moves!
Look out!
It's predicting your moves!
Stop, you bastard!
I said... stop!
I win.
Kei! Back off!
[KURONO] I stopped it, Kato!
I stopped it!
And that achieved what?
Shoot at its legs! Its legs!
[HOJO]
What the hell are you doing?!
Trying to prove who's
got the bigger dick?!
[KURONO screams]
[KISHIMOTO]
Kurono!
Oh, you're really asking for it.
Chill, dude...
Is he tough as nails
or just fuckin' stupid?
We got it!
Don't bet the rent check!
Run!
[HOJO]
Why isn't it getting weaker?!
[MIYAFUJI] All that shooting
should have damaged it!
Aim for its legs!
It dodged!
Shit! This whole time, he's been
watching and analyzing us!
[KURONO]
You're not going anywhere!
[growls]
[SEI]
Yes! Yes!
[KATO]
That should do the trick!
[SEI] What the hell?!
We shot the legs!
[KISHIMOTO]
Oh, shit!
You mean it's different
from the other one?
Shit. It don't look
like he's goin' down.
Those guys are gonna
take care of it, right?
Get back! We're too damn close!
Kato, look out!
He knows our every move!
Kei! You've gotta try
something different!
A new attack!
--[KURONO grunts]
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
Way to go!
That was just awesome!
Don't just stand there!
Keep on shooting!
[KURONO]
Shoot!
Man, that guy is one bad motha--
[TOMAO gasps]
Shut your mouth!
Yeah, yeah... But you
can dig it, can't 'cha?
[gasps]
[KURONO grunting]
Damn it! You son of a bitch!
It's gonna crush him to paste!
Even with the suit,
he's totally fucked!
You heard him, dammit!
Start shooting! Shoot it!
But what if we miss the statue
and hit Kurono instead?
Make sure you aim away from Kei!
[SEI]
The leg! Shoot the other leg!
[roaring]
[ROWDY ALIEN wails]
--All right!
--Oh yeah!
--Boo ya! [laughs]
--That was bad ass, man!
[GROUP cheering, laughing]
[OKAZAKI] We kicked his
big, red monkey ass! [laughs]
He went down like
one of my bitches! [laughs]
So, my man--
[TAMAO]
Dude...
Hey, Kei--
Welcome back.
[laughing]
♪ You ain't got no head ♪
Aw, take that!
Oh, whatcha gonna do now?
Nothin' 'cause you
ain't got no head!
[laughs]
Oh, he's so pretty now--
Hey, fat ass! Stop fucking
around! Enough already!
[KATO] So, those surprise
shots were yours, huh?
When you said we'd make
it back, did you mean it?
What? Oh, yeah.
Well, if we do
get out of this...
How'd you like to
go out with me?
[KURONO]
Uh--
Oh! Oh, I see.
The age thing. Or wasn't I...
...you know.
[KISHIMOTO] There's something
I want you to understand.
And that's that
I really like you.
I'm serious. I really do think
that you're a great guy.
I mean, I know you're
not at all like Kato...
But even so...
Well, if... you don't
mind the fact that I'm--
Oh, I don't.
Well, I just... got
my driver's license.
We could drive some place.
[KURONO]
Sounds fun.
[SEI sighs]
You know, you're
an amazing marksman
to have made all those
incredible shots.
What is this thing?
What kind of
nightmare are we in?
[BOTH gasp]
Dude! Up there!
[KONTA]
Huh?
[DOG whines]
[KONTA] Aw, shit.
What should we do, man?
[TOMAO]
Do you think it's pissed at us?
How the fuck should
I know? Am I a statue?
But unless I'm wrong...
it's floatin' right at us!
That guy has balls...
big hairy ones.
[KURONO gasps]
Why's that weird fat guy
starin' at me like that?
It's creepin' me out...
It could be that he's gay.
You are cute, after all.
[KURONO sighs]
He's gay?
The only reason he could
do things like that
is because he's wearing
one of the suits.
You've got one of those
suits on, Poindexter,
and it looks like
you're not doin' shit!
Actually, since you
brought it up...
Last time, he killed most
of them without a suit on.
[OKAZAKI]
Whoa...
Enough "gaydar." Who the
hell cares? Just move on...
[TOMAO]
Okay...
Now what?
Well, it looks small
enough for us to handle...
Are you kidding?! That
thing's over six feet tall!
Small my ass!
Chill. What I meant is that
it's smaller than the other one!
Should we get help?
Nah, it's cool. I think
I can handle this one.
[STATUE chanting]
Oh, man. And now he's
spewing nonsense at us.
He's all yours, dude.
[chuckles]
[SEI gasps]
[KURONO gasps]
Kishimoto!
Kishimoto... Kei?
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh?
I, uh...
[KISHIMOTO]
Mm-hmm?
It's strange, Kei...
Could you...?
What?
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
Kishimoto... is fine, okay?
I know calling me
Kei is confusing.
Um, yeah... It kinda is.
I like the way you say
"Kishimoto"... Okay?
Um, anyway, could you be the
sniper next time we go out?
[chuckles]
[KONTA yells]
Gotcha! [growls]
[TOMAO] Whoo! That's
awesome, dude! Kick his ass!
[KURONO gasps]
[ALL]
Huh?
[JJ]
Hm? [gasps]
Jesus H. Christ...
[OKAZAKI]
It's big...
But it's just a big
statue of Buddha, right?
I mean, we got a whole
bunch of guns over here.
We're gonna shoot
the shit out of 'em!
Oh, sweet Jesus. I don't
wanna die. I don't wanna die!
Next episode,
"What the Hell is That?!"