[TETSUO]
Hmph!
[TETSUO] Ah, hey there.
Is this Mr. Iwaki?
Heh, yeah it's me. I got some
pretty cool shit to show ya.
[KURONO]
Yeah, I have money.
Huh? Of course,
I've been going to school!
And, no, I haven't
been skipping class!
Ugh, look. I gotta go or
I'm gonna be late, okay?
[KURONO]
She thinks I'll be fine
as long as she
throws money at me.
[KURONO gasps]
--[KURONO] Oh, not again!
--Good afternoon.
The apartment building you
see here has been abandoned
since the collapse of the
bubble economy of the 1980s.
Apparently this building, which
one housed a popular restaurant,
suddenly collapsed last night.
--The incident is expected to...
--Was that your mother?
Duh!
What'd she say?
Nothing really, she was
just calling because
--she feels like she has to.
--[ANCHOR] There's been no
--Uh-huh...
--explanation for the collapse.
We've also been informed
that the second-floor roof
of a residence located
about 200 meters
from the apartment
building also collapsed...
[KURONO] What was all that
shit about last night?
I thought we'd become at
least a little closer...
I guess we just did
it to save Kato...
This sucks...
[ANCHOR]
Now, the latest on that story.
[REPORTER] Tonight, two
boys--are they missing or not?
And the only clue...
[KURONO] God, are they still
talking about that, too?!
Oh, except now of course
it's become the story about
the high school students
"with the adult magazine"!
Well, you shouldn't have left
your magazine
behind, should you?
At least, I'm assuming
it's yours.
After all, Kato wouldn't be
reading something like that.
And what makes you so sure?
Because he told us that he's
staying his relative's house
with his little
brother, remember?
He's too thoughtful for that.
[KURONO]
Yeah... Kato's a total saint.
Plus, he has too much
else to worry about.
[KISHIMOTO] I mean, he has to
take care of his little brother.
And when we're all
at that apartment,
he worries about us so much.
I think he's just an
extremely caring person.
[KURONO] Hmph. Or maybe
he just likes to butt in.
Well, sometimes people
need to do that!
If it weren't for Kato,
where would we all be now?
Think about that!
Yeah. Are you forgetting
who pulled the trigger?
[KISHIMOTO] Well, yeah,
that's true, but...
[KURONO]
Now that I've been there twice,
I understand one
thing perfectly.
Being caring doesn't mean
shit if you wanna survive.
Kato can babble all he wants
about us going back together,
but it's not that easy.
[KISHIMOTO] Yeah, in the
end... I agree with you.
[gasps]
[KISHIMOTO] No, really.
I think you're right.
And... that's good.
[KURONO]
What the hell's up with her?
[STORE CLERK]
Thank you. Come again.
--[AUNT] Look what you've done!
--[rattling]
You will not get
away this behavior!
How dare you ask me for
breakfast like that?!
And by the way, I know you
came in the house yesterday
with muddy shoes! Look what
you've done to the damn foyer!
I've been the model of patience
with you, but no longer!
[KATO] Ayumu! What in the hell
has been going on here?!
[AUNT]
This snot-nosed brat
has the nerve to
ask me for breakfast
after the shit he pulled!
What's wrong? Am I being mean?!
--[AYUMU groans]
--[KATO gasps]
[AUNT]
Stop your damn whining!
Why don't you just...
shut... the hell... up!
What's wrong with you?!
Insufferable little brat!
I'm not feeding either of you
unbearable little
ingrates today!
[KATO] Look, I just bought
some breakfast for him.
So you could please--
[AUNT]
Oh, did you now? Forget it!
[KATO]
Please stop! That's enough...
[AUNT] What was that?
Are you giving me lip?!
Please stop hitting him.
[AUNT]
Don't tell me what to do!
Who the hell do you
think you are, huh? Huh?!
[KATO]
Stop it!
Don't you dare look
at me like that.
[KATO]
Please stop hitting him!
If you do it one more time...
I swear, I'll--!
[AUNT yelps]
How dare you...!
If you continue to hit him...
I swear, there's no telling
what might happen to you.
[AYUMU]
No, don't!
Please stop it, Big Brother!
She really didn't hurt me
that bad, promise!
Get the hell out of here!
Get the hell out of my
house now, both of you!
[KATO]
All right... We'll do that.
[TEACHER] When AC equals 1,
BC equals the root of 3...
[KURONO gasps]
K-Kishimoto!
Kato was just trying his hardest
to help everyone else survive...
He's the kind of guy that values
all the life around him equally.
[KURONO]
Not this bullshit again.
[gasps]
[KISHIMOTO]
He's so strong and caring...
There's nobody like him.
Yeah... He's like no other.
[KURONO gasps]
What the hell is this?
Why does she look so hot
babbling about Kato?
Teacher!
[TEACHER]
What is it?
Kurono's got a hard on again!
--[gasps]
--[STUDENTS laugh]
Kurono, please, take
care of that at home.
--[STUDENT] ...it's too small!
--[laughing continues]
[YOSHIDA panting]
Oh, boy!
Finally.
[YOSHIDA]
Oh, pardon me.
That same little punk
stole some books again.
It's the third time this week!
And from what I've heard now,
he's selling the
books he shoplifts.
[deep breath]
I'm sorry. May I help you?
[SEI] I was wondering about the
book I ordered the other day.
Right... Let me see here...
[YOSHIDA]
Uh, what's your name, ma'am?
Sakuraoka. Sei Sakuraoka.
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh...
What a beautiful name. I wonder
what kanji she uses to write it.
[YOSHIDA] Let me see...
Oh, yes, I remember.
Miranda Foster's Labyrinth ,
that's right.
I'm afraid it's a very
hard title to find
since it's extremely rare
and seldom reprinted.
Any guess as to when
you might get it?
Oh, well... Hopefully,
I'll have it some time
around the end of next week.
But I'll be sure to call
you when it comes in.
That's great. Thank you so much.
[IWAKI]
It's a fuckin' toy!
[TETSUO chuckles]
Not even close.
[IWAKI]
Where'd you get it?
[TETSUO] Well, it's, uh--
It's kind of a long story...
[IWAKI] I doubt there's a long
story behind this piece of shit!
[TETSUO] Ahh! C-Can I use
it as payment for this month,
like... instead
of money, ya know?
Come on, you gotta be shittin'.
Who the hell would want this
piece of shit, you moron?
So... is that a no, then?
Are you saying you ain't
got my money, loser?
That's too bad. Give it up now!
Are you gonna take
it to the grave?
[IWAKI]
What did you just say?
See, you don't
need any money, man,
'cause you're gonna
be dead real soon.
[gasps]
Nobody... can fuck with me!
[laughs]
--[KIDS laughing]
--[KID] Pick me up! Pick me up!
[KATO]
This is it.
[AYUMU]
Huh?
[KATO] I was able to save up
enough money for this place
at my part-time job.
This is our home now.
Huh?
Yes! Yes! We did it!
I'm so sorry, Ayumu.
[AYUMU]
Huh? What for?
If I'd saved more, we could
have moved out sooner...
Are you kidding?
This is awesome!
From now on, I won't have
to put up with her beatings.
And that's what's
important, right?
[gasps]
Oh, Ayumu...
We'll make it together,
Big Brother.
I'll go get a job
and help out, too!
[KATO] Don't be silly!
You still have to go to school!
But wait... What are
we gonna sleep on?
[KATO] Oh, one of my friend
has a couple of old futons
that he can give us.
I'll go get them now.
[AYUMU]
Hey, I'll come, too!
They're too heavy for you
to lift by yourself!
[KATO]
I'll be fine, all right?
You just stay home and watch TV.
And since it's our place,
you can even watch anime.
[AYUMU]
Can I really?!
Yep, and you can
watch it every day!
[laughs]
[KISHIMOTO]
Well, here's the change.
Ya know, it's getting expensive
shopping in convenience stores
all the time, and I'd be
happy to cook as long as
it's nothing fancy.
Aw, don't worry about it.
[KURONO]
I mean...
It's not like we're
livin' together or anything.
I could cook tomorrow
if you'd like.
[KURONO]
It's fine!
What are you so mad about?
I'm not mad, damn it!
Well, you sure are
acting like you are.
[KURONO] And I be you
wouldn't be nagging me like this
if I were Kato!
[KATO]
Great. They're still here.
[baby cries]
[TETSUO] You know,
it looks like I'll be makin'
a little more money
startin' next month.
[WIFE]
Oh, really...?
[TETSUO] Ya wanna move?
To a bigger place?
We don't have that
kind of money.
[TETSUO chuckles]
We'll be just fine.
[WIFE]
Right...
[TETSUO]
Hey! Enough with your bullshit!
--All right?
--[WIFE] My bullshit?
[TETSUO] Yeah! And what
the hell are you doin'?
You're not producin' milk!
What else am I gonna do?
My husband wastes his money
on his fucking cigarettes
but never buys a damn
thing for his baby.
[TETSUO] What the hell
are you talkin' about?
I got a call from the
construction site, and they said
none of you assholes
showed up for work today.
They also said not to
bother coming back!
It's so fucking pathetic.
They fired all four of you.
Did you get the umbrella
from your friend, too?
Yeah. That's right.
Your friends are really cool.
[KATO]
Yeah... I guess they are.
Okay, it's all done!
Look.
Oh, that's so awesome!
It's just like the old one!
I'm afraid I kinda
spent all our money
getting us this new place but...
I'll start saving up again.
[AYUMU]
It's cool.
Heh, I'm gonna sleep
with this tonight!
But then you'll have
dreams about the rain.
That's all right
with me, Big Brother.
Now I can't wait for it to rain.
[AYUMU] Okay, good night.
I'm going to sleep now.
[KATO]
Ayumu...
Uh-huh?
I just... hope you
sleep well tonight.
[KISHIMOTO]
Hey, Kurono?
When I was killing time at
the bookstore this afternoon,
I noticed this beautiful
girl at the counter.
[KURONO]
Uh-huh?
What the fuck do I care?
[KISHIMOTO]
Her name was Sei Sakuraoka.
It looked like she had ordered
some book called Labyrinth .
[KURONO]
Really...
[KISHIMOTO] All I've been
reading are study guides
and collections from
the great masterpieces.
So it made me wonder... what
kind of book Labyrinth might be.
[sighs]
Do you read books like that?
I'm afraid not. I don't
go for that nerd stuff.
[KISHIMOTO] I wonder what
Kato's doing right about now.
[TETSUO]
What are you talking about?
Oh come on, now. It's like now
I'm asking you to give up
your bike, God forbid.
As if you would.
And speaking of that,
where were you last night?
What the hell do you mean?
You never came back last night,
and I don't know how many
times I tried calling you!
Why the hell did you
turn off your cell?!
I told ya, I was
out of the area!
Yeah, sure. I bet you
were out fuckin' around
with your boy Haruya again. And
all your friends' cell phones
were off lat night, too?
Is that a coincidence?
I was not fuckin'
around with my friends!
Then why was your goddamn
phone turned off?!
You wouldn't uderstand,
even if you tried to listen!
That's bullshit!
No, actually, you're bullshit!
And I was not-- I wasn't--
A-All fuckin' night!
[WIFE] So there was that much
hot snatch out there, huh? Huh?!
[KISHIMOTO yawns] I bet
Kato has a lot on his mind.
He seemed so troubled.
[KURONO]
Ugh, gimme a break!
I thought you were agreeing
with me this morning!
[KISHIMOTO] But even so,
he was trying so hard
to save all our lives...
[KURONO]
Oh yeah, he was trying.
But if you think about it, he
really wasn't all that helpful.
[KISHIMOTO gasps]
What?!
Why do you say awful things
like that? It just isn't true!
[KURONO]
Oh, really?
[KISHIMOTO] Yeah!
There's one for every person
in this world, you know?
[KURONO]
What?
[KISHIMOTO] A role.
Everybody has a role to play.
[KURONO]
Huh?
It's like how it was your
role to beat the aliens.
While Kato concentrated
on protecting everyone.
It all balances out.
[KURONO]
Whatever...
[KISHIMOTO]
But honestly, I think that...
...both of you... are amazing.
And Kato's just... the
kind of guy who values
the lives of everyone
around him equally.
[KISHIMOTO] He's caring
and strong... like no other.
I don't know... He's just
different from everyone else.
[KURONO]
Just what are you trying to say?
Huh?
What the hell are you saying?!
Are you saying...
that just because
you couldn't reach my phone
for one fucking night,
that I must be cheating on
you or some shit? Huh?!
Fine then, Mr. "Out of Area,"
why don't you prove to me
you weren't fucking
around then, okay?!
Because I can't,
you goddamn bitch!
I... was just...
Are you really trying
to intimidate me
with a fucking toy gun?
Give me a break, ass wipe.
You bitch... I'll kill you!
Oh, bring it on! Go ahead,
shoot me, big man!
[WIFE]
Oh, this is bullshit!
How are we supposed to
live with no money?!
And who's gonna give a
low-life biker like you
a job in this economy?
Huh? Come on, answer me!
Answer me!
Just make up your
mind and answer me!
Why are you so damn indecisive?!
Look... I'm sorry! I didn't
mean to... sound that way.
You move into my place
out of the blue,
but I don't even
get to touch you!
And it's always, "Kato this,
Kato that. Oh, Kato!"
[KISHIMOTO]
Hey! Now wait a minute!
[KURONO]
Kato! Kato! Kato!
I know what you were thinking.
Last night, when you asked
Kato if he lives by himself.
Okay. What did I mean?
You were asking because
you were thinking about
moving in with him,
instead of me, right?
Except I never said that, did I?
[KURONO]
Ugh!
You might as well have.
It's perfectly obvious
you're just using me.
I can't believe how
stupid I've been!
Why don't you just get out?!
Why don't you just get
the hell out of here now?!
[BABY cries]
What the hell
am I doing, anyway?
What in the hell am I
doing with you, anyway?!
Free food, free rent.
And for what?!
I guess you're right.
It's not like my keeping up with
my education means much to you.
I don't understand the way
this world works at all, Kurono.
And I guess it's not like
cooking for you is gonna make
--everything all better, is it?
--[KURONO] Oh, fuck!
I've crossed the line!
What do I do now?!
[KISHIMOTO]
And you're right...
I know that life isn't
supposed to be that easy.
[KURONO]
No! Whoa, hold up!
[KISHIMOTO]
But there's something
I want you to understand.
And that's that
I really like you.
I really do think...
that you're a great guy.
[KURONO]
What?!
[KISHIMOTO]
I'm serious.
I mean, I know you're
not at all like Kato...
But even so...
[KURONO]
O-Oh, man... What do I do now?
[engines revving]
[BIKER A] Hey! It's that
douchebag from the other day!
[BIKER B]
Oh yeah. The milk fairy, right?
[BIKER C] Hoo-hoo, is he
a ghost or somethin'?
We fucked him up good!
[TETSUO]
Why am I doin' this?
[WIFE] That's one fucked up
daddy you got there, huh?
[baby giggles]
[WIFE gasps]
[BIKER C laughs]
Look at this dumbass
with his toy gun!
[BIKER B laughs]
What a moron!
[BIKER A] Hey, let's
kill him one more time!
[BIKER B]
Yeah! Let's do it!
[TETSUO]
Why? What the hell am I doing?
Tell me why, Gantz!
[KISHIMOTO]
You don't think there's a bomb
or something like
that planted inside
of each of our
heads, do you?
[BIKER A]
Gantz? What the fuck is that?
[TETSUO groans]
[BIKER B]
Holy shit! He's bleedin'!
[BIKERS murmuring]
[phone rings]
[WIFE]
Tetsuo! I can breastfeed now!
Come home right now!
I can feed our baby!
No need...
for me anymore then...
[KISHIMOTO] I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry, Kurono.
But if it's what you
really want, I'll leave.
Thanks for everything. Goodbye.
[KISHIMOTO]
But there's something
that I want you to understand.
And that's that
I really like you.
I really do think that
you're a great guy.
I'm serious.
I mean, I know you're
not at all like Kato...
But even so... you're still...
[SEI] Gantz... Locked windows,
locked doors, Tokyo Tower,
strange people, strange songs,
a crying boy, and
a fearful girl...
Next time, "I Wanna
Be There Now!"