[GAME SHOW HOST] Okay!
Write your answers down, now!
[GAME SHOW CONTESTANT] Hey,
can't you give us a good idea?
[GAME SHOW HOST] If you
watched the video carefully,
then you'd know the answer.
I'll repeat the question
one more time. What is...
We have to make it
back alive. All of us...
Right. All together!
This shit rocks!
[KOSUKE chuckles]
[KURONO]
Oh, shit! My suit's not here!
What am I gonna do?!
[train horn blares]
[KURONO]
Goddammit...
[KATO]
Okay, one at a time.
Go to the hallway
and put on your suits.
Excuse me? Did someone die
and make you the boss?
No, not really, but I--
[HARUYA]
But what?! Maybe you should stop
bossing people around,
little Miss Fancy-Pants.
You think I'd wear this shit?
Fuck that.
[KISHIMOTO] Please, ma'am.
You really should put them on.
I'm sorry... but could you
tell us what we're doing here?
Kato?
I'll tell you once
you're all dressed.
You'll need the suits
to survive what's next.
Hey, Kato... Could we...?
Please, put them on.
But, I...
[KOSUKE]
Like I said before...
All of this Yamada alien
stuff is fucking bullshit.
It's Suzuki. The Suzuki Alien.
[KURONO] How can he say that
with a straight face?
But what's more important
is my suit...
Um, Kato?
[KATO]
Huh?
[TETSUO] So. You're telling
us that we all have to
put on these suits
if we want to survive.
[KATO]
Uh-huh.
But you also said you
aren't the leader here, right?
And what's your point?
Well, I have to make sure these
guys get home safe, y'see?
I guess you could say
I'm their leader.
The rest of you nimrods
can go to hell,
but the four of us
stick together.
And I'm the one who
decides if these three
wear the suits or not. And the
next time you order us around...
Then you'll do what?
I'll take you down before
we do this Suzuki whatever.
[NISHI]
Hmph.
Hey, you got somethin'
to say to Tetsu or not?
I'd like you to ask them
to wear the suits.
And that's not an order.
It's just a request.
[TETSUO]
Ugh.
Don't worry: I'll make sure you
make it home safe and sound.
Just wait a little longer, okay?
Hey, Grandma, do you think
this one's for me?
[KAYO]
Why, yes it is!
They have kid's sizes, too!
I just hope it's disinfected.
You know how easily
you get rashes!
Oh well...
God, what a stupid old fart.
[KINJI, KOSUKE chuckle]
[HARUYA] I told ya,
I'm not wearing that thing!
Yeah, yeah. I get it.
But, maybe...
[HARUYA]
You're not really gonna wear
that stupid-looking
thing are ya?
No, but I was thinking...
What if this wasn't a normal
situation, you know?
[HARUYA laughs]
Stop fucking with me!
[TETSUO] Yeah, all right.
Look, I'll just leave it up to
you guys. Do what you want.
[HARUYA] That's what
I was planning on doing.
What about you, Tetsu?
You're not really gonna
put it on, are ya?
You know that I'm not.
Yeah, damn straight
you wouldn't.
You won't put it on either?
I wouldn't be caught dead
in something that gauche.
Before long, we'll all
have to leave this apartment.
And when we do,
what you're wearing
will be the least
of your worries.
Forget it. I have
an image to uphold.
That girl with
the big tits is changing.
Yeah, I noticed. [chuckles]
Hey, where you going?
You can't go outside, remember?
We're goin' to the can.
To take a shit. [chuckles]
Oh yeah... I see. I feel
the dump comin' on.
[KATO] Please, ma'am...
Please put them on.
Oh, I don't know
about my grandson,
but I couldn't possibly
wear such a thing.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
I can't hold it anymore...
[KINJI]
Shut up... You ass...
[KISHIMOTO]
What's with this? It's so tight.
[KOSUKE]
Ooh! They're huge!
[BIKERS chuckle]
You don't have to
put that on. Right?
You can put it on later...
After we're done with you.
Know what I mean?
[BIKERS laugh]
It looks like the suits
are specially made
to fit their owner.
[KAYO]
But I don't want to!
Ugh, excuse me.
[KATO]
What?
Look, we need to talk, okay?
[KATO]
Is something wrong, Kei?
[KURONO]
Well...
Oh, not again!
Kato, wait!
[BIKERS gasp]
--[HARUYA] Whoa!
--[KINJI] Hey!
[KOSUKE]
What the hell?
[KISHIMOTO]
Ah! No! Not again!
Bad dog!
[KINJI] That scared the shit out
of me. What's up with that dog?
Hah! It must belong
to one lonely housewife.
That's so fucking hot!
Huh?
Tetsu!?
Time to knock it off.
[HARUYA]
And why should we?!
You can go home
to your fucking wife!
[TETSUO]
Oh. You just crossed the line.
There's no reason you had
to bring my wife into this.
[DOG whines]
Hey!
[TETSUO] But now is not the
time or the place for this!
[KURONO] Holy shit! Is she
totally naked again?!
You don't believe this Sato
Alien bullshit... Do you, Tetsu?
It's Suzuki.
[KURONO]
Ugh! Who the fuck cares?!
Well, from now on, you can
just forget this bullshit
about being our leader.
[TETSUO]
Hmm?
[HARUYA] I don't believe
this alien shit! Come on!
I didn't say I
believed it. But still...
When we get back home,
I better not catch you
riding around on our turf.
I'm putting my clothes
on top of the suit, okay?
That's fine.
[RYOTA chuckles]
Tetsu... What are you, crazy?
Just forget about that loser.
He can do what he wants.
[KURONO] Oh, shit...
everybody's got 'em on but me.
Even the fucking dog!
At this rate... I'm gonna die!
I know it!
What am I gonna do?
Think! Think!
[NISHI laughs]
No way... Don't tell me
you took it home?
[gasps]
Too bad. What a shame.
Your suit's gone?
[NISHI] Well, I guess that
takes one out of contention.
'Cause we've got
one dead man already.
Hey! It happened again!
Huh? You mean
the ghost that steals
the plastic prize capsules?
[CLERK A]
Well... Look.
Oh, yeah, right. You opened
them yourself, didn't you?
[CLERK A]
But it's not me!
I don't care about
the candy or the prizes!
I'm telling you, it's a ghost!
[CLERK B]
Yeah, whatever.
It's on the blink again.
No way.
[CLERK A]
Look! Over there! It's...
[CLERK B] It's from
the last customer, right?
Go ahead and ring it up.
What kind of ghost would pay
for it's stuff and leave?
[CLERK A] I'm telling you,
it's gotta be a ghost!
But where did...
...it go?
[KURONO]
It's at... my place...
I left it there...
What a pussy!
Looks like he's crying!
If they're that important...
you should put them on.
And I told you, we're not
gonna wear that shit!
[KURONO]
If that's the case,
maybe I could steal
one of their suits...
[KATO]
We don't have time for this!
We could be transported
any minute now!
That's right...
For god's sake, why didn't
you say something sooner?
[KURONO] I tried to,
but you wouldn't listen!
[door clatters]
Hey, where ya goin'?
Heh? I gotta shit for real now.
[KURONO]
All right... Now's my chance!
[KISHIMOTO] You! Isn't
there something we can do?
Right...
[KURONO] Just a little more...
Crap!
[NISHI]
That's theft, you know.
[HARUYA] Hey punk, what in the
hell do you think you're doing?!
It's not like you're
gonna wear it, fat ass!
But that doesn't mean
I'm gonna let you steal it!
[KURONO] That's probably
what would happen.
There's no way
I'd get away with it.
Damn it! I am in such deep
shit, I'm treading water!
[KATO] I'm asking you
nicely... to lend it to Kei.
Huh? Are you outta
your fucking mind?
[KURONO]
Kato...
C'mon. If you don't want it,
then there's no reason
you can't lend it
to him, now is there?
Like hell! It's mine, asshole!
Just let him borrow it, Haruya.
Don't tell me what to do!
Even if I don't wear it,
it's still mine.
Your butt-buddy's outta luck!
But if you don't--
[NISHI]
It's no use.
[KATO]
Huh?
Another person's suit
wouldn't do you any good.
[KURONO] If that's the case...
then I really am a dead man!
There's got to be something...
Some way for Kei
to survive this thing!
I wouldn't tell you
even if I did know.
Is there? Is there
a way?! Tell me!
You mean "Please
tell me," don't you?
All right. Please tell me.
I dunno... Should I?
Stop jerking my chain!
Tell me now!
Oh, die with dignity.
You son of a--
You're dead! Every last
one of you is dead!
But can you really
trust me? Huh?
Why, you stupid little shit!
Hey, let go of me!
Ow! What in the fucking hell
is in those gloves?!
[NISHI]
God, you're fucking pathetic.
Even if you are dead,
with human refuse like you,
it wouldn't make any difference
at all in the real world.
So there's no point in
moaning and whining
about who lives or who dies.
It just doesn't matter.
So what you mean is,
that you're dead, too?
Who cares? The people here
aren't your teammates,
so there's no need
for a leader.
The truth is we're
nothing but rivals...
All of us competing
for survival.
Did you hear that,
Mr. Let's-All-Make-It-Back?
It's just bullshit! And you're
still nothing but a hypocrite.
Last time, you
head-butted a Yakuza
and nearly choked him
to death, didn't you?!
Why would someone who wants
all of us to make it back
do something like that?
Who are you kidding?!
They call those "violent
impulses," you know.
Can't you use that
thick head for thinking?
Or would you rather just hit
people with it?
And you, Tit-Girl!
Me what?!
"Isn't there something
we can do?"
That kinda shit
really pisses me off.
As if shaking those money-makers
means we're gonna do
whatever you say.
Face it... A woman like you
is as helpless as a little baby.
You can't do anything
for yourself, can you?
But if you get in trouble,
you can just wave
a tit at him, right? That's what
you think, isn't it? Isn't it?!
[NISHI]
And you, Mr. Boner!
[gasps]
Are you that scared
of dying again?
You oughta be ashamed,
crying like that.
Remember how I thought you had a
little bit of potential
last time? I was wrong. You
should be the first one to die.
Why?! And so what
if I was afraid?!
[NISHI] I'm telling you,
it's disgraceful.
That kinda shit doesn't
phase me at all.
[wails]
Hey, you little brat! Shut up!
I'm sorry, but do you think
you could keep it down a bit?!
Hmph. You two are practically
pre-filled body bags.
You have no chance of
surviving on your own.
Oh dear...
You're just like Tits here.
Dead meat for sure unless
you rely on somebody else.
And who will you depend on?
It's not gonna be me, Grandma.
And since we're on that subject!
You spoil that grandchild
of yours rotten
without thinking about
the consequences.
You think it's okay to
warp his personality
just because he's cute? Huh?!
You know he won't grow up
to be a respectable adult,
but that's not your problem,
because you'll be dead by then,
won't you?! So that
makes it okay to let
a spoiled, rotten egg stink up
society, huh? Am I wrong? Am I?!
Honestly, this isn't even funny.
What's funny is these bikers
ass fucking each other
--over who's the boss!
--Say what?!
Heh! You're just
a bunch of punks.
The garbage of society. Hah!
And then you go on and on
with all this stupid
"I'm the leader" bullshit!.
Who's the king of the
trash pile? Who cares?!
You're still garbage!
And you. I bet you're the type
all the girls go crazy for.
But is there a
single thing going on
underneath that
trendy hairstyle?
Tell me, do you even know
what the internet is?
Have you ever used a
cell phone for anything
but chatting with girls?
I'm not an idiiot.
No? Then let me ask you
a question, smart guy:
When you read a newspaper,
where do you start?
[HOJO]
The TV listings, of course.
[NISHI] Are you kidding me?!
You really are an idiot!
Still, I guess you're better
off than the biker trash.
Those morons probably
can't even read the paper.
[gasps]
What the fuck?
So did ya hit him?
I-I don't know. It just
made some weird noise.
But it doesn't matter if
this stupid piece of shit
works or not. I'll fuck you up!
Stop waving it around! No!
Oh, shit!
[KOSUKE yells]
Oh, you didn't just fucking
shoot at me! Did you?!
Aw, man. That
thing's just a toy.
Oh yeah? You just watch!
There's always a time lag!
[whimpers]
Don't you fuck with us,
you little shit-wad
[screaming]
[RYOTA sobs]
Listen, assholes.
That's what happens when you
point a gun at me! Got it?!
And what's more, I'll snuff you
without a moment's hesitation!
Any of you! Imprint that
on your tiny brain stems!
And if any of you
cretins slow me down,
I'll kill you without
a shred of remorse.
Especially you.
Look at that. She's
relying on you already.
[KATO] I don't get it. How come
nothing happened to you
when you were shot?!
[NISHI] I'm not answering
anymore questions.
[KATO]
Was it your suit?
Gantz!
Hurry up and get on
with this already!
What are you waiting for?!
[gasps]
Kei!
Huh?!
[KURONO screams]
[KURONO]
Straight from the get-go!
[mechanical whirring]
[screeching]
[TETSUO]
Who the hell is that?
Huh? What are you
staring at me for?
I see, you're a robot,
aren't you?
You're one hell
of a piece of work.
Next time: "Yuzo."