[KISHIMOTO]
Oh, jeez! What's with this dog?!
Bad dog! Bad dog!
Hey... are you feeling okay?
[KISHIMOTO]
Ugh! Don't do that!
S-Stop it! Get down...
I mean away from me!
Somebody, help!
[KATO] Here! Put this on
before I attack you myself.
[KURONO]
What's the deal with that dog?
I mean, I've heard stories about
these single working girls
and butter but...?
[KURONO]
So what is it?
It's like some kind of message,
but it can't spell worth shit!
It says that,
"Your lives are now over
and what you do with your
new lives is for me to decide,
so there you have it."
Hey! What the...?
Is this thing trying
to screw with us?!
[NISHI]
It may sound screwy,
but if you stop to think about
everything that's
already happened to us
it's not all that funny, is it?
[INAMORI]
Uh-huh...
"Please go eliminate this
target now, you bastards.
The Greenonion Alien.
Traits: Strong, smelly.
Likes: Green onions, friendship.
Catch phrase: 'Green onions
are enough for me!'"
What the hell is this?
[YAMADA] I think this is
some kind of game.
[SUZUKI] Does this mean
it's going to let us out?
[KURONO screams]
[INAMORI]
Yeah, baby! [laughs]
Check these out!
They look real! Woo-hoo!
[YAMADA gasps]
Someone's in there!
[INAMORI] Whoo, I've heard of
being behind the eight ball,
but inside it?
[KURONO]
Oh, give it up already.
It's probably just a
dummy to fake you out.
[KATO] I don't know... For a
fake, it looks pretty real.
[KURONO]
Huh...?
Hmm? "Kato-cha"?
Bad spelling or a pun?
Kato! I think this
might be for you.
Wasn't there a
singer called that?
[KATO]
Cosplay?
[INAMORI]
Vinyl! Cool!
Here, you try it on.
Oh... screw you.
They don't really shoot! Crap!
Huh?
--[gasps, screams]
--Bang!
W-What are you doing?!
[INAMORI laughs] Get off
yourself, nothing happened.
Hey! Check out
this X-ray thingy!
[YOSHIOKA]
H-Hey! Wha--?!
[gasping]
[YOSHIOKA]
Hatanaka?
[HATANAKA]
Hey, what the...?
Huh?! W-What the--?!
[YAMADA yelps]
What now? If it's already
taken the others...
--...do you think...?
--[DOG whines]
[KURONO yells]
You mean it's happening
to me, too? But it doesn't...
[KISHIMOTO shrieks]
Wait!
[KATO]
I'm... outside...
[KURONO] Why the fuck... [gasps]
Oh, holy shit! But can I--
[KURONO]
C'mon, c'mon!
Oh, shit... It's too tight.
Right! Lose the boxers!
Yah!
Huh?!
[KISHIMOTO whimpers]
Huh...? Oh!
[stammers]
Is this Kei?
[KURONO] Oh, shit!
This is definitely not good!
Ah, there it is!
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
[KURONO]
Whew! Just in time...
So what were you up to with your
dingle dangling, short stuff?
[laughs]
Kei... you didn't...?
[KURONO] Huh? Hey!
It's not what you think!
[KATO]
Hey! Butter Dog!
So, are you okay?
Uh... Uh-huh.
[KURONO]
Aw, man...
He's scoring and
I'm playing dress-up!
[YAMADA]
Hey, which train system is that?
[SUZUKI] I couldn't see
which line it was,
but if we follow the tracks, we
can find the nearest station.
[KURONO]
Why is she following him?
I went to her rescue, too.
[SUZUKI] If I can get back
into the political arena,
I still got a chance
to turn things around.
All I need is a chance
to mop the floor
with that cocky,
little Prime Minister.
[YOSHIOKA]
I know what I need...
...a little parlor in soap land
to get the plumbing scrubbed.
[INAMORI] Man, I just wish
these were real guns.
[HATANAKA]
I'll tell ya one thing,
I'm gonna do that bitch...
[YAMADA] I'm so glad we
get to go home after this.
I've still got all
those tests to grade.
[NISHI] Hold on,
before we go any further...
It is my duty to tell you that,
unbeknownst to most humans,
there are alien criminals
secretly living here on Earth.
We have all been recruited by a
secret government organization,
and now it's our job
to get rid of these aliens.
[YOSHIOKA] What the fuck
are you talkin' about?
[INAMORI]
Aw, dude, you're so full of it!
[YAMADA] You mean,
like the greys and stuff?
[SUZUKI] Sonny, the current
government doesn't have
that kind of money.
And I should know.
Then go ahead and
doubt me, grandpa,
but for each one we kill,
we get ten million yen.
[gasping
[KURONO]
Whoa. No kidding?
You believe him, Kei?
[KURONO]
Oh, well, I--
[YAMADA] You've got
to be pulling our legs.
Nope, I got it
straight from my dad
at the Cabinet
Information Bureau.
Then... your father's...
Vice-Minister Nishi?
[INAMORI]
Who?
Nishi's one of the top dogs
in the Information Bureau.
They say he's
as sharp as a knife
and that he never tells a lie.
And that's how come
I know so much
about this stuff, Four-Eyes.
--[INAMORI] Shit!
--Ten million...
That kind of
dough could buy...
[NISHI] Well if you're
interested, it's all in here.
[gasping]
[INAMORI] Hey! If that's us...
it's right down the street!
[HATANAKA]
Ten million, huh...?
Now just hold on.
How can this be?
Because, old man, the bureau's
never told you politicians
the truth about anything.
You're just for show. A pawn.
And, whether you like it or not,
you've all been recruited
for this little alie--
[KURONO]
Recruited by who?
It's funny how I don't
remember any of that.
Have you forgotten...
...that stranger that
asked you for something?
[gasps]
And all we've got is one hour!
[YOSHIOKA]
Let's go!
[GROUP shouting]
[SUZUKI]
This is nonsense.
I'm going home!
Well, Kei? Now what?
[KURONO]
Huh? Uh... Well, uh..
[INAMORI]
Is he over there?
[YAMADA] I thought this
was the right place...
[HATANAKA]
He's not here, you dumb fucks!
You know, if you're fucking
with us, I'm gonna kill ya.
Oh, I'm scared. Except
I'm already dead, asshole.
Huh...?
[INAMORI]
There you are!
[YAMADA gasps, yells]
[INAMORI]
Hey, is he there?
[LITTLE GREENONION]
Green onions are enough for me!
Oh, shit, there he is!
[YAMADA] And, he's eating...
green onions...
[SUZUKI]
Taxi!
Damn. Why aren't
any of them stopping?
Agh!
But... if it hurts... I must
be alive. So bleeding is good!
[SUZUKI laughing]
[SUZUKI] This is perfect,
when I get back...
...I can...
start all over again...
[KATO] Ichinomiya?
Where the heck is Ichinomiya?
[KURONO] Damn! I can't
go home dressed like this!
[gasps]
[KURONO] Oh, yeah...
She is definitely my type...
And going home without
doing something about it
would be a shame...
Um... What's going on here?
Huh? What do you mean?
[KISHIMOTO]
What do you mean...
[KURONO]
She's got the cutest voice!
[KISHIMOTO]
...you don't know either?!
Well, I thought we
were going home, right?
Wait, hold on a second!
You can have my pants, too.
No, no! Please,
keep your pants on!
I... just wanna know what
we're going to do next...
And maybe... your names?
I'm Kei Kurono!
Kurono, right. And you are...?
Huh? Oh I'm Masaru Kato.
Ah, Mister Kato... I...
Just Kato's fine.
[KURONO]
Why are you cozying up to him?!
[KURONO] Hey! Maybe someone
should find the others.
You mean you're not
gonna stay with us?
[KURONO]
No, it's just...
Yeah. I've got the same feeling.
[KURONO]
Why is she following him?
[LITTLE GREENONION]
Just gimme two...
Hah! Do we plug him
or plant him?
Just two...
[INAMORI] Aagh! Oh, gah--!
Why, you sorry little-- Ugh!
Hmm? Oh, yeah... Let's see
if this is how to fire it.
[LITTLE GREENONION]
Just gimme two...
You've got two guns,
dickless?! Gimme one!
Hand one over, goldie locks.
[INAMORI chuckles]
Okay, let's do it!
[HATANAKA]
Huh? Hey!
[INAMORI]
Huh...?
Wait a sec... What's this?
[YOSHIOKA] Huh? What do
you mean, "What's this?"
[HATANAKA]
Huh?!
You shit! Watch where
you're pointing that!
[INAMORI]
Gah... Ahh!
Sorry! Really, sir!
[INAMORI yells]
You little turdball!
Just gimme two...
You fuck! You ruined my shirt!
Guh! Ahh!
[LITTLE GREENONION whimpers]
Upstairs!
[INAMORI]
Hey, you! Wait!
What an idiot!
Get outta my way!
[HATANAKA growls]
[LITTLE GREENONION]
Yeeee...
[gasping]
[KURONO]
Shit...
[HATANAKA]
Ugh...
[KATO]
Hey... Are you... all right?
[LITTLE GREENONION whimpers]
Wait! I don't think you
should be moving!
Just gimme green onions...
Hey! Come back!
[YAMADA]
He's getting away!
[HATANAKA]
Don't let him get away!
[INAMORI]
Come on! Let's get him!
[laughing]
[KISHIMOTO squeals]
[HATANAKA]
Come back here, you little turd!
Did you see that?
[KATO]
Uh-huh...
[HATANAKA]
Get him! Come on!
[KATO]
Kei, what was that?
And does it mean that
we really are dead?
Kato! Kato!
Why does it have
to be like this?!
[HATANAKA] Yeah. Yeah!
We almost got him!
[LITTLE GREENONION wails]
[LITTLE GREENONION]
Take my green onions!
[INAMORI] Hah! I don't want
them! Damn, you're fast!
Oh!
[COUPLE chuckles]
So, like, you told me
the other day
you'd go out and buy me
a nice diamond ring?
Kei, do me a favor and make
sure that the girl gets home!
[KISHIMOTO panting]
[HATANAKA]
There he is!
[INAMORI]
Woo-hoo!
[KURONO]
Score!
Uh... Are you...?
I'm fine. I can get home myself.
--[HATANAKA] We've got him now!
--[YAMADA] About time!
Now I've got you!
Take my green onions!
Sorry... I don't want them!
[LITTLE GREENONION squeals]
[LITTLE GREENONION screams]
Now what the hell...?
This thing had a helluva
good kick, but... Hey! Wait!
[LITTLE GREENONION whimpers]
[INAMORI screams]
Holy crap!
[gasp]
[INAMORI] One hit from this,
and you're smoked!
[LITTLE GREENONION whimpers]
Ahh...?
[grunts]
Hey, just how do you
shoot one of these things?
Well, I see that they
have two triggers...
[INAMORI}
Yeah, I got mine to fire
when I pulled both
at the same time!
[KATO gasps]
--[LITTLE GREENONION growls]
--[whistling]
[INAMORI laughs]
[INAMORI] Look at that!
He's like a little teapot!
[HATANAKA] He's funny,
but he pisses me off!
Especially that ugly face!
[LITTLE GREENONION yells]
[whistling]
[growls]
The little freak's
got some razors!
[YOSHIOKA]
Waste him!
[LITTLE GREENONION whimpers]
[screams]
[KATO]
Noooo!
[LITTLE GREENONION shrieks]
[squealing, gurgling]
[wailing, sobbing]
[KISHIMOTO whimpers]
[KURONO]
Is she...?
[LITTLE GREENONION whimpers]
My green onions! Green onions!
Take my green onions!
[shrieking, wailing]
[KISHIMOTO grunts, retches]
Ugh!
[KISHIMOTO coughing]
[KURONO] I'll forgive that
because you're cute, but...
Are you all totally insane...?
You sick, sadistic bastards!
How could you? How could you?!
[LITTLE GREENONION whimpers]
We... We've gotta call
an ambulance or something...
[stammering incoherently]
[KATO gasps]
So, are you having
problems with this, hero?
[stammering incoherently]
[grunts]
[KATO screams]
You can't...
...do things like this...
[INAMORI] Yeah? Sounds like
you're the odd duck out.
[HATANAKA]
That's right.
And it felt good to off the
little onion-sucking freak.
[KATO]
Dear God, forgive me!
I couldn't save him!
I couldn't...
[KATO sobs]
Oh, spare us, you poser!
That-That thing
wasn't even human!
[HATANAKA] And what
difference does that make?
So, what do we do about that?
[INAMORI]
Oh, shit! Someone saw us!
--[KATO] Help! Call the police!
--[HATANAKA] Huh?!
--[GIRL] Hey, Mom!
--What are you doing?!
The Saito house
is all messed up!
[INAMORI]
What the...?
[snarling]
[KISHIMOTO]
It was as if...
She couldn't see us... but...
[KURONO]
Does that mean that we're...?
We're the dead and damned.
[snarling]
Huh?
--[slicing, squelching]
--[KISHIMOTO gasps]
[growling]
[INAMOTO yelps]
[YAMADA whimpers]
[growling]
Oh, great!
Who the fuck is this?
[growling]
Maybe it's the little one's dad.
[HATANAKA] You gotta problem,
Greenie?! Just say something!
[KATO]
Shut up, you stupid bastard!
The last thing he needs
is more provocation!
--[BIG GREENONION growls]
--[HATANAKA] Stow it, punk!
[growling continues]
Spit it out!
What are you
looking at, onion face?!
[roars]
We're gonna die... aren't we?
[YAMADA] Yeah, I think this
might be the end for us...
[HATANAKA growls]
[gasps]
[BOTH growl]
[HATANAKA]
He's like... concrete...
[YOSHIOKA]
Just shoot the fucker!
[YAMADA]
No shit, asshole!
[HATANAKA grunts]
Wait!
Don't shoot!
[HATANAKA] Okay...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
--[HATANAKA grunts]
--[crunching]
You see what happens, you punk?!
You gonna tell us not to kill
'em even when he's killing us?!
Well, screw that!
[HATANAKA wails]
[whimpers]
[screams]
Don't shoot!
Didn't I tell you
not to shoot, you moron?!
[YAMADA whimpers]
[YAMADA]
I... I'm sorry...
Would you shoot one
of your kids
if he didn't listen to you,
you stupid idiot?! Huh?!
I-- I'm sorry!
[HATANAKA]
Fuck you!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It won't work on me! Not on me!
I'm gonna live through this,
and then I'm gonna...
[HATANAKA stammers, coughs]
[grunting]
[BIG GREENONION snarls]
[KATO] The Kei I remember.
The Kei that is...
The childhood friend... trapped
beneath the merciless claws.
What allies are left?
What choices?
Which path will he take?