[SHIORI] Mom! What should I wear
for my practice exam tomorrow?
[KISHIMOTO'S MOM]
Oh, I wouldn't worry about that.
Give me a minute.
Here's something special
for you to wear tomorrow.
[SHIORI] Oh, Mom! This is so
cute! Where'd you get it?
[KISHIMOTO'S MOM]
At Mikato! I splurged.
It's a very important day
for you, dear.
Thanks, Mom! I love it!
[KISHIMOTO'S MOM] Just remember:
I'm counting on you
to get a good score on the test.
[KISHIMOTO'S MOM] Wow, Kei!
You got an A+ on your exam!
I knew you could do it.
Didn't I tell you?
Good job! You've made
your mother so happy.
I love you, Kei. You know
you're my pride and joy.
Now, let's see if we can
try a little harder.
You can do it if
you keep studying.
I'm not worried. I
have faith in you, Kei.
[KISHIMOTO'S MOM]
Yes, that's right...
I'm just glad she passed.
This was her safety net school.
If she couldn't even get
in there, I'd have been
too embarrassed to
set foot outside.
Uh-huh... She's just like
her father, not very bright.
I just don't know
what to do with her.
What? Shiori? You know
how gifted Shiori is.
Her teacher said she'd
have no trouble passing.
We're all so proud of her.
[CAT meowing]
[KISHIMOTO]
Mm! That really hit the spot.
Thanks for picking it up!
[KISHIMOTO sighs]
[KURONO]
She's so calm.
I can't believe she's not
freaked out about this.
I mean, why are
there two of them?
[KURONO] So... What do
you think you'll do now?
[KISHIMOTO] I dunno. But for
some reason, I feel relieved.
Huh?
[KISHIMOTO] I feel as though...
my whole life I've been living
for my mother's sake...
Always trying to please her...
Trying to be a good girl...
I was always studying so hard.
But there was no point to it.
She never gave me a chance.
Not once.
[KURONO]
So...
In any case, I don't
know what my other self
is going to do from
now on, but...
This girl here is just going
to live her own life. And!
I'm in love! I've
found someone I love!
Wha--?
And I'll live!
For his sake and mine!
[KURONO] All right! And I've
still got plenty of condoms!
[KISHIMOTO]
Mrs. Masaru Kato!
Huh?
I love him! I love him!
I love Kato!
[KURONO]
Kato...?
[KISHIMOTO]
Say, Kurono.
Do you know where
Kato's house is?
[KURONO]
No, I don't.
Oh. That's okay! I've get the
feeling that I'll see him soon.
Our destinies are now linked.
Kato's and mine.
[AYUMU]
Masaru...
[KATO]
I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
I'll, uh...
turn off the light...
[AYUMU]
Did something happen?
[KATO]
No, no. Everything's fine.
Masaru... is it true...
that Kenshiro never dies?
Huh? Yeah, because
he's the toughest.
Yeah, but no matter what...
it's still really wrong
to hit people
and stuff, isn't it?
[AYUMU]
Just because you're tough
doesn't mean you can do
whatever you want, right?
Yeah...
Sure, right.
What's with you tonight?
Please don't die on me, okay?
[KATO]
What're you talking about?
It's just that... I want
to live alone with you.
So... don't die, okay...?
[AYUMU] I wonder if it hurt...
when Mom and Dad...
[KATO] I don't know...
I've never died... before...
[COMEDIAN B]
What?!
[KISHIMOTO laughing]
[COMEDIAN A] Then she
suddenly burst into tears!
[COMEDIAN B] Smooth move!
You didn't see that coming?
[COMEDIAN A] But I know
you can't get to third base
with a crying woman
no matter how drunk she is!
[KISHIMOTO grunting]
[KURONO] Holy shit!
That rack's gonna kill me!
Gah?!
[KURONO]
Say...
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh?
[KURONO]
Do you have stiff shoulders?
I could give you a massage?
[KINJI] Hey, man, no way these
bitches are gonna hook up
with us in a fuckin' alleyway.
[HARUYA] Oh yeah? Check out
this email she sent me.
I tell ya, this
girl's a total freak.
And she said she'd
bring three of her friends!
[KOSUKE]
Whoo! We all gonna get some!
I know this bitch.
She's pretty game for anything,
so I'll bet you we're all gonna
go home sore and happy tonight!
Cool!
Look, I'm outta here.
My old lady's waiting
on this milk.
[KINJI] Aw, c'mon, man!
Forget that shit!
[motorcyle revving]
[tires screeching]
[engines revving]
[BIKER]
Tetsuo!
Time to take you down a
notch, ya fuckin' pussy!
Now!
Tetsuo?!
Shit! It's a fuckin' set-up!
[SADAKO]
Is this safe?
Should we even be riding a
motorcycle on the expressway?
[HOJO]
If you don't like it, jump off.
[SADAKO] Oh, you'd like
that, wouldn't you? I'd die.
[HOJO]
That's right.
[laughs]
[HOJO gasps]
[HOJO] What-- What the hell
are you doing here?!
[SADAKO]
Oh, you never notice me...
[MAN A]
Oh, fuck me!
[MAN B]
Oh, shit! Jesus!
[MAN C]
Goddamn! What is that? A cat?
[MAN A]
It's been ripped apart!
[NISHI]
This isn't enough...
I gotta go after
something bigger...
[NISHI]
Here it comes!
It's about time, Gantz!
[gasps]
[KATO]
What was that?
[KURONO gasps]
I just felt a weird chill.
Yeah, me, too.
Do you want me to turn on
the heater or something?
I'll be fine. Don't bother.
[KURONO]
So, does this feel good?
Yeah...
I bet your shoulders would
get stiff... with these...
[KISHIMOTO]
Huh? What d'you mean?
With these what?
Ah! Hey! That's not-- Hey!
--[KURONO laughs]
--[KISHIMOTO] Kurono! Stop!
[KURONO] Boinga-boing!
Look! They're outta control!
--Boinga-boing! Look at 'em go!
--[KISHIMOTO] Stop!
[high-pitched ringing]
Hey, do you hear that?
Uh-huh...
Oh... Shit! Not again!
Huh? What?! Kurono!
[KATO gasps]
[KATO]
I can't move...
Hey, welcome back!
[BIKERS yelling]
Hi, Kato!
Uh. Hi there?
So... how have you been?
[KATO]
Huh? Uh...fine?
[KURONO] Kato, don't take
her away from me...
[KISHIMOTO]
I wanted to see you.
[blows landing]
Bastard!
[HOJO] I'm through
fucking around with you!
Get off the bike!
Get the fuck off!
[SADAKO]
Here? On the expressway?
How am I supposed to get home?
[HOJO]
Who gives a shit?!
[HOJO] I just want you
off this bike! Now!
[SADAKO]
Why are you so mean to me?
[TETSUO'S WIFE]
I guess...
...I must've inhaled too much
paint thinner or something.
Why?
I can't breast feed the baby...
I can't...
[TETSUO]
What about regular milk?
That'll be all right,
don't you think?
Huh?!
[TETSUO]
What the fuck?
[KOSUKE, KINJI]
Huh?
[gasping]
[KINJI]
What the fuck?!
[KURONO] Looks like it's
starting all over again...
[HARUYA] Hey! The goddamn
door is stuck! Shit!
[KURONO]
Yep. Just like before...
Where is this place, Grandma?
Well... I don't know.
[KURONO] And the new people
are doing exactly what we did
when we first came
to this place...
Tokyo Tower?
[KINJI]
Damn! What the hell is this?!
Can't use my fuckin'
cell phone in here!
[RYOTA] Grandma,
I don't like this place!
I wanna go home!
[TETSUO] Hey! What the hell
is goin' on?! Answer me!
Hey! What are you,
deaf or something?!
[HARUYA] Yeah! Tell us what's
going on, you bastards!
[KATO]
Um... Kei?
[KURONO]
Guh...
[KURONO] It'd be pointless
to explain anything...
Even WE didn't believe it...
Well? I'm gettin' pissed!
So start talkin'!
Yeah! Don't be
messin' with the boys!
Hey, you! Mr. Pretty Boy there!
[TETSUO]
Well? Say something!
Sorry. I know zilch.
You had better not
be fuckin' with us...
Fire...?
[police sirens blaring]
Damn. This is pointless.
I get it! This is a hospital...
We did get the shit
kicked out of us.
[TETSUO] Oh, right!! Does this
look like a hospital to you?
And none of us have
a scratch on us.
[HARUYA]
Hey! Lookit that!
[KINJI, KOSUKE, TETSUO]
Huh?
[KINJI] Whoa!
Check out the lungs on her!
[KOSUKE]
Son of a bitch!
[HARUYA] Hey! We can
still get some action!
[BIKERS laugh]
[KOSUKE] I don't know what's
going on here, but who cares?!
[KINJI]
Me first!
[HARUYA]
I'm not taking sloppy seconds!
[KINJI]
What?! Tiny dicks go last!
[KOSUKE]
Fine. You can go last!
[KURONO] Look at her!
She's all over Kato!
--Damn it!
--I'm first and that's that.
[KURONO]
Back off, assholes!
Say what?
Maybe you need a good fucking.
Do ya?!
[RYOTA wails]
I wanna go home now!
I wanna see my mommy!
Shut up, ya brat!
Or you're dead!
[RYOTA wails]
I'm so sorry!
Ryota, I'll figure
something out!
I'll find some way
to get you home!
[RYOTA sobs]
[RYOTA]
Grandma!
[sobbing continues]
Listen up!
Huh?
If you wanna live through
the night and get home,
you've gotta listen to me.
I'll give you as much
information as I can.
Huh? You fuck!
First of all, lemme tell you
the part that I know.
That's enough!
[KATO] Soon, everyone
here will get a weapon
and be transported to
a different location.
Huh?
Bull-fucking-shit!
The dude's lost his mind.
[KATO]
Maybe I have lost my mind...
But that's exactly
what will happen...
Is this some sort of game?
A reality show on TV?
[KATO] No. You're not on TV,
and it's not a game.
So what happens next?
All right. We have to capture
what appear to be aliens.
Uh, dude? Aliens?
[laughter]
Aliens?
He says we've got
to capture them.
But aliens aren't real, Grandma!
This guy IS out of his mind!
The people who were
here last time
didn't take it
seriously, either.
And all of them are dead now!
[KINJI] Yeah? Well?
Where are these "aliens?"
[KINJI laughs]
I'd like to meet them!
[KOSUKE]
The fuck do we do now?
[HARUYA]
Man, I am so lost.
[KURONO]
Who could possibly believe this?
You tell them, Kei.
Tell them how the suits work.
Huh?!
Well, there's really
nothing to them...
You just put them on...
[music plays]
What the fuck is that?
Sounds like a
radio exercise show.
What the fuck...?
[KINJI]
I dunno...
Whoa! Something's happening!
[KOSUKE]
Huh?
"Y-Your... lives
are now o-ver,
you bas-tards... What you do...
with... your new lives...
is for me to decide."
Shit, that clears it up.
We can go home now!
[BIKERS laugh]
[KINJI]
Really? We can go?
[TETSUO]
Wait, it's changing.
[BIKERS]
Huh? Whoa! Shit!
Huh...? Hmm...
"The Suzuki Alien.
Traits: Strong,
re-fresh-ing... Bird?
Likes: Birds, sweets..."
Catch phrase: 'Ha, ha, ha!'"
[HARUYA] Oh, this is starting to
feel like a fucking video game!
[KINJI]
Maybe we are on TV. Sweet!
[BIKERS]
Whoa!
No way!
Oh... Hot shit!
That's a fuckin' gun...
[KINJI]
No fuckin' way they're real...
[BIKERS murmuring]
I'm in love!
[KATO]
Here, go ahead and change now.
--Thanks, Kato.
--[KINJI] Are these things real?
Don't worry.
They're real, all right.
It's your choice
to listen to me or not.
But these suits could
be what determine
whether you live or die.
So, who died and made
Kato the class president?
Nobody did.
And it's not a position that
I really want, either.
Then why are you
spilling the beans?
Because I want us to
come back alive...
I mean, all of us.
You said we're faxed
copies, right?
Duplicates of the originals?
And your point is?
"You are already dead."
Remember that?
When I was growing up, I used to
admire that kind of bullshit.
But now...
Now it really pisses me off.
--[clatter]
--[KURONO gasps]
[KURONO]
Oh, fuck...
My suit...
[KURONO]
My suit... it's not here!
What am I gonna do?
[KURONO]
What am I gonna do?!
[KURONO] Oh, shit! I forgot
my suit. I am so fucked!
What will I face next?!
What IS that thing?
I don't know what's real.
I'M the one who's
gonna get killed.