[BOTH]
Huh?
[DOG whines]
[TOMAO]
Dude!
[KONTA]
Huh?
[TAMAO]
Up there!
[KONTA gasps]
[whines]
[DOG barks]
[ALL gasp]
[JJ]
Hm?
--[gasps]
--[barking continues]
[JJ]
Jesus H. Christ...
[KONTA]
Oh, fuck...!
[TAMAO gasping]
[TAMAO]
Holy shit.
[DOG whines]
How are we supposed
to fight so many?
Fuck this!
And fuck you!
[yells]
That crazy bastard!
[BOTH gasp]
I'm gonna kill you all!
[BOTH chuckle]
[laugh]
[KONTA]
You're goin' down!
[KISHIMOTO]
It's started! What do we do?
[KATO] First, the sniper
needs to get in place!
[TOGO grunts]
[KATO]
Okay, let's go!
[KISHIMOTO]
Right!
[KURONO]
Shit! What was that?!
[KATO]
I don't know,
but I don't think
we're gonna like it!
[ALL scream]
[TEACHER] Come on, look,
Yoshino. I-It's like I said--
It's-- It's not that I don't
love you anymore, really!
It's just that things are, uh...
...kinda delicate
for me right now.
Try to understand, baby!
It's not you, i-it's me!
Stop the cab, please!
[ALL gasping]
What... the... fuck is that?!
[KONTA] It's fucking big,
that's what it is!
[JJ] Damn! That's gotta be
the biggest daibutsu in Japan!
[KONTA] And the key word
is "die," you idiot!
What the hell do ya
think this is?!
[BOTH scream]
[KONTA]
Not again!
[JJ]
Aw, hell!
[SEI] Remind me again: Did I die
and go to Heaven... or Hell?
'Cause this is really
beginning to test my faith.
[KURONO]
You can have faith in one thing:
I'm gonna take him down!
[SEI] Are you out of your mind?
It's too dangerous!
[KURONO]
Too late! I'm doin' it!
No! Kei, come back!
[KURONO yells]
[gasps]
[KATO] Goku and Kenshiro
are really cool,
but you're way cooler, Kei!
[gasps]
[KID]
Wait up, you!
[KURONO]
Come on, Kato! You slowpoke!
[KATO pants]
Kei!
Please, Kei! Wait for me!
What if I lose this time?
[KURONO yelling]
[pants]
Damn it! How can that
not be enough firepower--
[gasps, screams]
[ALL gasp]
Kei! No!
[KATO]
It's moving! Everyone back off!
If you're not wearing a suit,
get the hell out of here.
Those of us with suits will
try to take care of it!
[KONTA]
Don't worry about us!
Do we look stupid?!
We've got these guys!
[JJ yells]
Don't worry, Kato!
We've got it! Heh.
Okay, but keep your eyes on us.
And if things start
to go bad, run!
All right! It's gonna be up to
us to take the statue down!
Let's all aim for
his feet together!
Does everyone understand that?
I said that statue is mine!
[KATO]
Huh?!
[KURONO]
I'll handle it myself!
That thing's way too big,
Kei! Be reasonable!
[KURONO] Too big for a
normal person maybe...
[ALL gasp]
But it's not too big for me!
[TEACHER]
Come on, Yoshino!
Come back, please!
Why are you getting
out of the cab?!
Go home to your precious wife!
[TEACHER cries]
Yoshino, please!
You can't be serious!
I know that look... from
when we were kids growing up.
It reminds me of the old you...
...right before you
did something crazy.
I-I can't hit it!
It moves too fast!
[HOJO gasps]
[TOGO]
That's one statue down.
Oh, fucking shit!
Ow!
Make that two.
[KONTA grunts, pants]
Damn! I'm totally wiped out!
[TOGO]
And that's four.
Please, Kurono, let's all
do it together, okay?
[HOJO] Hey! What the hell
are you guys doing?!
Do we even have
a plan of attack?
Huh...? Oh no!
[TEACHER, YOSHINO grunting]
[TEACHER] Please, Yoshino! This
place is under construction!
I-I mean, look!
We can't just go
in there without--
[YOSHINO]
Then don't follow me,
and you won't have a problem!
--[TEACHER] B-But--
--The obvious always eludes you!
For example, I've never once
asked you to leave your wife,
have I? That's right, I haven't!
[KURONO gasps]
How can that be my
homeroom teacher?!
I mean, what are the odds?
[YOSHINO] So why are you
doing this? Tell me that!
Where do you get off saying
that it's over for us?!
You don't normally have the
balls and I should know!
That statue's gonna crush them!
Come on, help me!
--[thud]
--[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
It... It just killed
the butterdog!
[dings]
Everybody! Jump!
[ALL yell]
[BOTH gasp]
[KURONO]
Oh, holy shit!
--[KURONO screams]
--[SEI gasps] Look out!
It's so fast!
[KATO grunting]
[TEACHER]
I-It's like I said, baby,
it's just that things aren't
feeling right now and--
[YOSHINO] Stop beating
around the bush, dammit!
If I'm perfectly fine with
things the way they are now,
why should it matter?!
[TEACHER] Because I think
she's catching on to us!
And if we are--
W-We're both teachers!
I-It's just so bad
on so many levels.
If you don't... move your ass,
it'll be a lot worse!
[BOTH growling]
Are you hanging in
there, Kishimoto?
Great... Couldn't be better!
You're the one that said
no one would ever find out!
[TEACHER] I was overconfident,
wh-what can I say?
Don't say anything else!
Fine, but I want those
pictures you took.
If those things were to surface,
my life would be a living hell!
We're the ones who're
in Hell, you bitch!
Just break up with him
and get out of here!
[SADAKO pants]
Huh?!
You! You're kidding me!
This is... the first time...
I've ever seen your face!
[KATO groaning]
It's getting stronger!
[screams]
[YOSHINO yelps]
[gasps]
There's something wrong here!
[TEACHER] No kidding!
Let's get the hell outta here!
Okay, everyone jump,
and we're outta here, too!
I can't! There's so much
weight that I can't get out!
Die, dammit!
[BOTH gasp]
[KURONO]
It's... gone!
It's just too much!
We're gonna be crushed!
I... can't hold it!
[ALL scream]
[SEI gasps]
Did they just...?
[KATO groaning]
Is everyone alive?
[ALL groaning]
I'm not dead?
They're all still alive!
[SEI] I think my faith
has just been renewed.
And as long as you're here...
we can make it back home.
Well, let's do it, then!
[KURONO screams]
Damn! I think he's mad now!
[STATUE murmuring]
[OKAZAKI laughing]
I'm so powerful, I can
kill you whenever I want.
Whaddaya think of that, bitch?
[chanting]
What's that Mr. No-Legs?
Are you beggin' me
for your life, huh?
[chanting]
I'm bored now!
[chuckles] Man, you're
just a pussy statue!
Huh?
[screams, groans]
[screams]
[KURONO yelps]
[KURONO]
Aw, crap!
Kei! Run!
Run faster!
[KURONO panting]
This is getting ridiculous!
Aw, shit!
[screams]
[ALL panting]
S-Shoot the feet!
Shoot its feet!
Do it!
[ALL scream]
We're so screwed. They don't
stand a chance against that!
[KURONO groaning]
Aw, shit!
[yelps]
[KURONO screaming]
[OKAZAKI panting]
Somebody... help me. Help me!
Oh my god!
[BOTH gasp]
Help me... H-Help me...
What the hell's that
fat fuck doing?
[KATO] Get back, you idiot!
That thing's dangerous!
--[OKAZAKI] Eyes... The eyes...
--[HOJO] What's he doing?!
Man, some people just wanna die.
No! I'm not gonna let
us lose anyone else!
Kato! What do you
think you're doing?!
[KATO yelling]
[OKAZAKI] Ah! He's got me!
Somebody help me!
[screaming]
But... how can I
stop that thing?!
[OKAZAKI screaming]
It hurts! It hurts! Let me go!
I'm sorry! Oh, God--!
[KATO]
No!
[screaming continues]
[gasps]
[KISHIMOTO screams]
[KATO groans]
[TOMAO]
It's-- It's eating him!
[KONTA]
Hey, you in the suits!
Weren't you supposed to
take care of that thing?!
[KATO grunts]
[KURONO]
I can do it.
I can kill that fucking thing!
And I'll do it! I'll... kill it!
[KURONO]
This... fucker... is... toast!
[ALL gasp]
[yells]
What just happened?
[ALL gasp, murmur]
[ALL gasp, scream]
[KONTA]
Fuck... Is it dead?
[TOMAO]
Well, it looks dead, but...
What do you think happened to
that crazy son of a bitch?
--[ALL scream]
--[JJ] Oh, my god!
[KURONO panting]
[KATO]
Kei? Are you...
[gasps]
Promise me something.
Promise we'll still take
that drive together.
[KURONO]
Don't worry. I'm not gonna die.
[KISHIMOTO]
She's right, you know.
As long as you and
Kurono are with us...
...we'll make it back.
[HOJO gasps]
There's still two
more of them left!
[ALL gasp, chatter]
How much time is left?
There's just over a
half hour remaining.
Only 30 minutes left, huh?
But as long as they're
the small ones, we're good.
Right! We'll split
into two groups!
Choose your side.
Go with him or with me!
[HOJO]
Huh?!
You want me to be a team
leader?! Are you nuts?!
We're all depending
on you. You can do it.
Listen up! The next thirty
minutes will decide everything!
Who's gonna win... us or them!
Whatever happens next, we've
come too far to turn back now.
[KATO]
Remember:
The Gantz always attacks us
in ways we can't predict.
Therefore, we have to
fight all of its attacks.
Eliminate every adversary
it puts in front of us.
That's the only way
we'll be able to survive.
[KISHIMOTO]
I've made it this far.
A lot of things have happened,
but I've been able to survive.
But now...
Next episode, "Just Shoot Me."