Rena...
Do you think that when we die
we'll end up like Ryu and Lowe?
I don't really know.
But...
But what?
When I thought
I might die alone,
I got so scared thinking about
what would happen afterwards.
But now I don't feel
that way anymore.
You don't?
No. Because no matter
what happens next,
I know that
I'll never be alone.
We'll be together.
Who is that?
I'm not certain,
but I think she's me.
Or rather, another me.
One born from Alecto.
Amazing.
Is that why you decided
to give her your ring?
Yeah.
I think that's what helped her
guide us back together again.
Oh, wow. Thanks, Alecto.
This isn't over yet. The others
are still fighting back there.
All right, Sis, ready?
Yeah. I'm ready.
Dear Mama and Papa.
Please watch over and
protect all your children.
[yells]
[pants]
[gasps]
They just keep on coming.
Become the flash which
pierces emptiness
and dwells eternally
within the charging blade!
[laughs]
All right, ladies, we're ready!
It sure took you
two long enough!
[KEI] Look out!
[INGRID gasps]
[NOA laughs] I don't know what
you've been up to over there,
but why don't you let
your big sister see?
Hang in there, Noa.
We'll save you!
[NOA scoffs]
[KEI]
Now!
[SARA, TIA]
Flight of Dragons' Teeth!
[NOA]
Not bad.
You're not getting away!
[BOTH]
Rolling thunder!
[KEI] Don't go
getting distracted now.
We're done playing with you!
Give us Noa! Now!
[NOA] I'll admit, you two are
better than I thought you'd be.
But all those attacks seem to
have cost you a lot of energy.
[JOHANN, NOA] It looks like
you've reached your limit.
[JOHANN]
No, you don't!
Sara! Tia!
[SARA gasps]
Noa!
[NOA groans]
[screams]
[grunts]
[yelps]
[panting]
Sara! Tia!
The orbis...
You have to break it!
[NOA] That's not an energy ring,
it's a prison for human souls!
Our people are the ones
who are responsible for
the creation of Lux Ex Machina.
But what was intended to
be our greatest triumph,
instead destroyed the world!
Now more human souls
are suffering
and we mustn't let that happen.
Not again...
[SARA] No... Please!
Stay with us!
[TIA]
Sara!
What should we do?
[whimpers]
[NOA] The most important
thing is to protect
those you care about.
[SARA]
What do we do?
Exactly what Noa told us
she wanted us to do.
Destroy that thing.
[TIA]
You sure?
Break it open and
take back the souls
of the ones trapped inside.
If we can pull that off,
we'll be saving a whole planet.
After that, you and I
will save our sister!
Okay!
[SARA, TIA]
Three edge blade!
[BOTH yell]
[INGRID gasps]
The shield!
[SARA, TIA gruntin]
[gasps]
--No! It didn't work!
--Why not? We were so close!
[KEI]
Get out of the way!
[yelling]
Spear of the Inferno!
We did it. This is for Noa.
[BOTH sigh]
[sighing]
Sara... Tia...
Thank you so much...
[BOTH]
You're welcome!
[grunts]
[RETSU]
What is that?
[CITIZENS gasping, murmuring]
[SARA]
Noa...
[JOHANN chuckles]
[SARA]
What's going on?!
--[laughing continues]
--[TIA] It's collapsing!
[INGRID]
Sara! Jump for it!
[SARA]
What about Noa?!
[NOA]
It's okay. I can make it!
[JOHANN] Controller of quanta,
present at the dawn of creation.
Pass through the infinite halls
and become corporeal.
Relic of wisdom, born
from the light of origin.
Come forth from the heavenly
void and reveal yourself.
Ahura Mazda.
Whoa! Is that him?
He's a lot bigger
than he used to be.
Johann. What have you
done to yourself?
[JOHANN]
Are you talking to me?
Because that's not
how you address
the most powerful being
in the universe.
I am not "Johann." I am the one
true king of Lux Ex Machina.
You're no king!
[JOHANN]
Watch your tongue, Princess.
After the trouble I went
through to capture every soul
on this planet,
you just let them all go.
[gasps]
[JOHANN]
Did you girls not hear me?
You are standing before a king!
In the presence of royalty,
one must bow down.
[SARA, TIA yelling]
[SARA]
How was that?!
[TIA]
Did we get 'em all?
[INGRID]
This is bad!
We need to take out
Johann quickly!
[grunts]
--[growls]
--[JOHANN] I've told you before.
Try as you might,
you can't kill me.
[SARA, TIA gasp]
[SARA]
Ingrid!
[TIA]
Kei!
[SARA grunts]
[TIA]
Big sister!
[SARA]
That's it! I've had enough!
Heh.
[SARA, TIA scream]
[NOA groans]
Must get up...
I have to help them...
Tia...
[JOHANN]
Nice knowing you. Buh-bye.
[panting]
[KEI gasps]
[SARA grunts]
[SARA, TIA groan]
[gasps]
It's Alecto!
[BOTH]
Yui did it!
Oh, no...
[INGRID]
Thank goodness.
[SARA]
We knew you could do it!
[KEI]
You saved her!
[TIA]
That's awesome!
It's good to see you again.
[JOHANN]
You've gotta be kidding!
You're not dead?
Fine. I'll start again
from the top.
Welcome back to the gloriously
reborn Lux Ex Machina!
Greetings to my fellow royal,
Yuinshiel Asteria,
Empress of Enastoria.
So now you're "king" of
Lux Ex Machina?
I am. Lux Ex Machina is the
greatest power in the universe.
And since I alone can wield that
power that makes me the king.
[JOHANN]
Why fight me?
We may both be rulers,
but I literally tower above you.
It may be just a hopeless dream.
But I came here for
the people I care about,
and I am not leaving
without them!
As the Empress of Enastoria,
and a member of the human race,
I will make you return
every soul you kidnapped!
[JOHANN]
Hate to break it to you,
especially after
the thrashing you took
and that stirring speech,
but your friends beat
you to the punch.
Humanity has already been freed.
[YUI]
Wait!
Why doesn't that bother you?
Are you just going
to do it all over?
[JOHANN]
Of course!
Once I eliminate you all,
I'll start from scratch.
--[YUI] Never!
--It's not up to you, Empress.
[YUI] I won't let you
keep doing this.
You're not hurting anyone else!
I'm putting a stop to you
right here and now.
[whimpers]
You've got some nerve,
you know that?
No puny human can stop me!
[BOTH gasp]
--They're goners!
--Run away!
What's happening to Alecto?
I don't know.
[RENA]
How is this possible?
Rena! Look!
She's here to help.
Is she crazy?
She should be on her knees!
Foolish mortal! Why won't
you bow down before me?!
[JOHANN]
Do you have a death wish?
Don't you understand
I am far more powerful
than you could ever be?
[RENA]
You have more strength,
but that doesn't make
you more powerful.
[RENA] When it comes
to individual might,
Yui has much less than
either you or I do.
But that's because
she doesn't need it.
She has something even greater.
She cares about others. That's
why everyone wants to help her.
They give her something, the
power of love and friendship.
That is humanity's power!
It's what makes Yui unstoppable!
It's the strength of
many voices calling as one.
The Regalia can never
come close to beating that!
[screams]
[JOHANN]
Die!
[laughs]
[JOHANN] You can't do anything
by yourself, Empress!
That means you're weak!
[JOHANN] Completely useless
without someone helping you.
But I'm not dependent
on others' charity.
I can do whatever I want,
whenever I want.
I don't need anyone else!
The only true power
a person has is their own!
And since mine is
stronger than yours,
I'm going to win, so surrender.
[YUI] Tell me the truth, Johann,
are you jealous of humanity?
Heh!
[YUI] When everyone forgot me, I
was shocked by how scared I was.
I had absolutely no idea
that being so isolated
could be that horrific.
[gasps]
Stop talking to me.
You've felt that way, too,
haven't you?
I thought I told you
to shut your damn mouth!
[JOHANN] I've got souls to
collect and more dolls to make.
I don't have time for this.
You're going to die, Empress.
It'll be quick, but painful.
[YUI] You just want someone to
care about, who cares about you.
[YUI] But that doesn't
excuse your actions.
We cannot let you
go through with your plan!
--Rena!
--Let's go!
[RENA, YUI yelling]
I'll blast you out of existence!
No! He can't!
[SARA, TIA]
Yui!
[grunts]
[BOTH]
Astral fist of Fire!
[gasps]
[BOTH panting]
[panting]
[INGRID]
Yui! Are you all right?
--[KEI] Rena!
--[SARA, TIA] That was crazy!
[JOHANN]
I despise you, Empress.
With every fiber of my being.
[gasps]
[JOHANN] You're right.
I don't have any friends.
There isn't a single
person I care about.
And the humans I collect end up
being nothing more
than lifeless dolls.
Yui... Rena...
[CITIZENS screaming]
Sara... Tia...
[screaming continues]
[RETSU]
Yui!
[JOHANN]
How dare you pity me.
You, who has everything!
I won't allow it...
I don't care if
I destroy the world.
I don't need anything.
Humanity can rot!
[gasps]
[JOHANN]
Yuinshiel Asteria...
...I will kill you.