Do you really think
we should do this?
Don't worry, it's
gonna be just fine!
This is higher than
the diving board!
You sure?
It's our only choice!
Okay, then.
Are you two ready
to take the plunge?
[TIA]
Mm-hm!
We're at your service!
[gasps] Well, well. This just
keeps getting more entertaining.
So, we transformed.
Now what're we supposed to do?
[TIA, SARA laugh]
This is awesome!
[TIA] Spinning faster and
faster, this is the best ride!
[RENA sighs]
What's the big sigh for?
Alecto and Tisis
aren't able to fly.
Huh?!
[TIA, SARA laughing]
[YUI screams]
[RENA gasps]
[YUI]
Sara, are you okay?
[SARA]
Yeah. I'm fine.
[YUI]
Let's get back-to-back.
Then they won't be
able to surprise us.
[SARA]
Good idea!
[TIA]
Uh! Ahh!
Big one coming in
at six o'clock!
Good. Face me.
If this was easy,
it wouldn't be fun.
[SARA grunts]
Get him, Yui!
[YUI grunting]
Hurry, try to get upright!
Yeah!
[RENA, YUI gasp]
[SARA, TIA scream]
We're gonna have
a rough landing.
[SARA, TIA scream]
[YUI screaming]
[RENA]
Are you okay?
[YUI] Yeah. What happened
to Tia and Sara?
[TIA coughing]
I thought we were
gonna die for sure.
Oh thank goodness they're safe.
I was so scared.
Tia! We're over here! Sara!
So this is what's
left of Rimgarde.
[TIA]
Why are we going in here?
We have to hide from
that Regalia Gear
that was attacking us.
Lay low. That's an absolutely
brilliant plan, Yui!
[SARA]
Whoa! Look at that billboard!
That's Ingrid, isn't it?
From back when she
was the princess?
I'm pretty sure that's the same
place where we found Rena.
You remember, don't you?
[RENA exhales]
Let's keep moving.
Okay.
[SARA] It's freezing in here,
my feet hurt, and I'm hungry!
I know. But just
a little farther.
Is your tummy rumbling?
I know mine is.
[stomach growls]
[stomach growling]
[SARA gasps]
[YUI laughs]
Watch!
[RENA, SARA, YUI]
Hm?
Ta-dah. Food!
Wow! Snacks! Nice going Tia!
Lucky for us you're always
thinking with your stomach.
[RENA] Did you swipe
those from the plane?
Sure did!
Finders keepers!
Uh?
[YUI, SARA]
[RENA]
Hm?
[TIA laughs]
[SARA]
No way!
Wanna check it out?
Yeah!
[MARGARET]
So you are certain
Yui and the others
landed safely?
[NARU] Yes. Infrared scanners
picked up four heat signatures.
Margaret, Yui did what
she did to protect us.
If she hadn't drawn their fire
it would have
destroyed the plane.
I understand that.
But you must rendezvous
with the Empress quickly.
Rimgarde is not safe.
[AOI]
Dammit!
Why didn't anyone think to put
parachutes on this thing?
[NARU]
And what if they had?
Would you really jump
out of this plane
right now and go after her?
Of course I would!
I'm worried sick!
Rimgarde has been
deserted for 12 years.
Nothing there works!
Yui lives in a castle.
She can't handle that!
[TIA]
Rena! Over here!
[SARA] Hurry up, Yui!
We need supplies.
Hm... I'll take one of
these, and one of these.
[TIA]
And this, and this, and this.
[YUI]
Huh...
[TIA]
Yui! Check this out!
Where are you, Tia?
Have you ever seen
one of these before?
Oh. Are those things tents too?
These are hanging cots for
sleeping on the side of a cliff.
Sara and I've used them a lot.
You two slept on cliffs?
Sounds fun. I wanna try!
Mm... Let's see.
U-Uh! How did you get up there?
[TIA laughs]
Yes. It's hilarious.
[coughs] Yui? Where did
you want to sleep?
I don't mind using
a dusty folding cot,
but is something like
that okay with you?
To be honest, I'm kinda
excited about it.
This'll be my first
camp out, you know?
Actually, can we sleep
in there instead?
I've always wanted to
try sleeping in a tent!
Tents are the best!
Everyone can cuddle
up and get cozy!
Yeah!
Uh... Works for me.
[YUI] Wow! I've never cooked
over coals like this before.
[SARA]
Oh yeah? Take a look at this.
Now we have high heat on one
side and low heat on the other.
Oh, so if you stir them,
you can adjust the heat.
Once you get a good fire going,
you can make anything.
Here. Wanna try?
Sure. Let's get this
heat a little higher.
Ahh! Whoops!
[laughs] I think
that's hot enough.
[YUI] Okay. We should start
with the vegetables.
[SARA, TIA, YUI]
Bon Appétit!
[SARA, TIA]
Seconds please!
That was super yummy!
Camping out is really fun!
Yup! And food cooked over
a fire tastes better too!
It's the bestest ever!
[YUI laughs]
[RENA] We're not exactly
camping for real.
You're right. We're
not out in the wild.
[RENA]
Even so, I'm surprised.
I didn't think you'd be
into this kind of thing.
Why would you think that?
I've never gotten to
go camping before,
so it's new and exciting for me.
I'll bet.
Hey, when we get home, let's
do some real camping outside!
Yeah?
Sure! We could invite Retty,
and Sara and Tia could show
us how to do everything.
We'd be happy to.
We're experts. I can even
start a fire without matches.
What? How do you do that?
Well, you take a stick, and spin
it fast against a piece of wood.
Oh! But I forgot to mention,
it's very important
the wood is dry.
This won't work if it's wet.
[YUI]
Okay. Then what?
[RENA]
Do you remember that place?
The plan is for all of us
to go there tomorrow.
Maybe it will trigger something
and my memory will come back.
[SARA, TIA snoring]
[TIA] Yui, the water's warm.
Come take a bath with me.
[TIA yelps]
[YUI]
This is it.
[RENA gasping]
That's Kei.
You're right, Sara. It is her!
Kei!
What did you do that for, Rena?
It's us.
Let's go.
[TIA]
We've missed you!
Can't you stop a second
and talk to us?
[SARA] We've been trying
to find you forever,
so a little hello would be nice!
[SARA, TIA]
Uh...?
[TIA]
Whoa...
What is this place?
[TIA]
I dunno!
[KEI laughs]
[TIA, SARA, YUI]
Uh?
I welcome you to the
Kingdom of Rimgarde.
What do you think?
Hello again, Ingrid.
[SARA]
That's the Princess of Rimgarde?
[TIA] Does this mean
she's bound to Kei?
I don't understand.
What happened here to
cause such a disaster?
Until 12 years ago, Rimgarde
was one of the world's
most technologically
advanced countries.
Our scientists had
long been investigating
a new type of energy,
but their research
hit a wall. Unable
to progress further,
the project ground to a halt.
[INGRID] Then, as if
by divine intervention,
someone appeared who had
expertise in the field.
He joined the team as an advisor
and soon got things
moving again.
The experiments he spearheaded
yielded incredible results.
However, trusting him ended
up being a deadly mistake.
[gasps]
[INGRID] It led to
The Fall of Rimgarde.
[BOTH gasp]
One person did that much damage?
[INGRID]
He deceived us.
He hadn't been furthering
our research.
Instead, he used Rimgarde
to revive an ancient power.
[RENA]
What ancient power?
Its name is Lux Ex Machina.
[ALL gasp]
[TIA]
But wait!
[YUI]
Lux was sealed away.
Yes. Erinius did indeed
fight Lux long ago.
The same Lux Ex Machina
that destroyed the world.
[RENA] So this scientist was
interested in Lux's power,
but you weren't?
[INGRID] That's right. Though
considering that I'm still here
while my country lies in ruins,
I can't blame you
for doubting me.
Unfortunately, once the truth
was discovered it was too late.
[YUI]
That doesn't make sense.
Uh?
Why are you doing all this?
If you don't want Lux revived,
why attack Enastoria
and try to take Rena?
And what about Kei?!
She's innocent!
Why's she involved?
She doesn't belong
to you anyway!
She's one of us and
we want her back!
Uh. Please?
I can explain.
[gasps]
[JOHANN]
There you are!
That was some fancy skydiving
stunt you pulled yesterday!
I know that voice!
Hey! It's the same one
that was after us!
Quit flying all over
the place! It's not fair!
[JOHANN]
Oh Ingrid, what a surprise.
I wasn't expecting to see you.
[growls]
[gasping]
[JOHANN]
This must be fate!
Everything's going to go down
right here, all over again!
Join the fun, Ingrid.
It's only fitting.
Come on.
I'll help you get started.
Johann...
Binding darkness born in light.
Arbiter of eternal truth
that dwells deep within me.
Unmask what lies beneath.
Expose the damned
and the false purgatory.
[JOHANN laughing]
[KEI]
Come forth covetous flames,
O sacred relics of
undying hellfire!
[RENA]
We need to get back!
[YUI, SARA, TIA panting]
[RENA grunts]
[KEI] By the name and
the power of Erinius...
Ingrid! No!
[KEI] ...reveal yourself
upon the earth!
[YUI]
Ingrid!
[RENA]
Yui! Watch out!
[GIRLS groaning]
[KEI]
Xeno Megaera.
[TIA, RENA, YUI gasping]
Why, Ingrid?
I have no choice.
There. Attagirl.
[RENA] Well if they want a
fight, then let's give 'em one.
But Rena...
[RENA]
Yui!
No. You're right.
This can't be avoided.
[SARA]
We should help 'em out!
[TIA]
Mm-hm.
[laughs]
[JOHANN]
Fantastic! The gang's all here!
Now that everyone is
dressed for the occasion,
I'll start things off.
Ha!
[SARA]
Yui!
[TIA]
Rena!
[SARA gasps]
[SARA]
No flying allowed!
[TIA]
Get back here!
Now! We've gotta go after them!
Aw. Good try.
[SARA, TIA yelp, groan]
Is that a gun?
I think so!
[TIA yelping]
[SARA]
Take this!
[SARA grunting]
[SARA, TIA scream]
Answer me, Yui. Are you
okay? Please wake up!
[YUI gasps] Yeah, I'm
all right. Don't worry.
[SARA, TIA scream]
[SARA] Ouch. That hurt more
than I thought it would.
I forgot how tough Kei is.
[YUI] Are you in pain?
Can you get up?
[SARA]
We're fine.
[JOHANN] Did Tisis bite the
dust? Oh, there they are.
I hope you girls
aren't giving up yet.
The real fun is just
about to get started.
I've had enough of this guy.
Me too!
[SARA]
C'mon, Yui.
Let's put our heads together
and take out that big jerk!
Yeah.
[JOHANN]
Hmph.
[SARA]
You missed!
[JOHANN grunts]
Ha!
Ooh, not bad!
Hurry!
[YUI]
I'm on it!
[JOHANN]
Whoa!
Impressive little trap.
We're stuck!
[RENA]
They grabbed us!
[INGRID]
Stop struggling, Yuinshiel.
I have something
important to tell you,
and I need you to stay calm.
[YUI gasps]
[SARA yelling]
[JOHANN chuckles]
[INGRID]
Listen carefully.
With the three Regalia of
Erinius gathered together
in one place, we can
create a resonance.
[YUI]
What's that?
[INGRID] It's hard to describe,
but it could free Kei!
[gasps]
[JOHANN]
You caught them!
Keep holding onto
them just like that.
And don't let go.
[INGRID growls]
[exhales]
[JOHANN] Aw... Clumsy Ingrid,
you let them get away.
I'll do all I can to help you.