[INGRID] Thank you for
honoring Abel's passing,
General Marshall.
It's kind of you.
[MARSHALL]
Not at all.
He's one of the
few people in this world
whom I considered a friend.
I can't help feeling as if
I've done him a terrible wrong.
It's not like that at all.
Well, this is just
between you and me,
but to be perfectly honest,
I'm feeling a little
envious of Abel.
He managed to fulfill most
of his deepest wishes
while he was on
that last mission.
He can rest, with the knowledge
that his life and
death had purpose.
What wishes do you mean?
[MARSHALL] All of you girls
are finally safe now,
and that's a
direct result of what
Abel had set in motion
when he came here...
This is exactly what he wanted,
and I believe he would've
died happily for it.
I'm sure he'd say he doesn't
deserve any recognition--
but I think honoring him
with this headstone
so we can pay our respects
is what's right.
[INGRID]
Yes. It is.
Thank you, General.
[KEI giggles]
[RENA]
Well... here's our place.
Follow me.
What are you waiting for?
Come inside.
Yeah, okay.
[INGRID] Is this really
the empress's chambers?
[KEI] I know, I thought
it'd be a bit bigger.
[RENA] Yui doesn't care
for the opulence
that comes with her station.
When she's given the choice,
she likes to keep things simple.
Heh.
[RENA]
Here.
[KEI gasps]
[INGRID] This is so
thoughtful of you, Rena.
But do you have anything
a little less frilly?
[gasps]
I'm sure we do.
Just give me a second.
[KEI]
Hold on, Rena.
What is it?
I want you to listen to me!
Sit down for a minute!
[INGRID]
Uh... All right.
I'm listening.
It's just that
I worry about you.
You finally have a chance
to live a little.
It's okay to let yourself
feel things and be happy.
It's not quite that simple.
Well, if it isn't,
then it should be!
Life has finally gotten better
and you deserve to
actually enjoy it!
You know... That's the best
advice I've gotten in a while.
Yeah?
I'll do my best. Okay?
Yes. And I'll help
as much as I can!
[INGRID chuckles]
[RENA giggles]
[NARU] Does this truly
mean that the Regalia
are no longer a threat?
Yes, I do believe
that's the case.
[MARGARET] What about the data
provided by Princess Ingrid?
We can't ignore that.
[THEODORE] It's a
research report from
the Kingdom of Rimgarde.
You'll find it fully details how
the Fall of Rimgarde came about.
It's all rather extraordinary
and difficult to believe.
Even after seeing
a Regalia first-hand.
Ingrid has spent
the past 12 years living
the fallout of
this single event.
I'm inclined to believe
whatever she says.
She has made it clear
that she'll accept
any judgement
that's passed down.
[gasps]
We must determine
a course of action,
including what to do
about the princess.
And there's still the
question of what exactly
Johann was trying to
accomplish in Rimgarde.
[GROUP sighs]
Whatever the case,
until we come up with a plan,
my opinion is that Ingrid should
remain here, just as you wish.
I see no issue with that.
[gasps]
I'm guessing Yui would
be very happy to take
the princess under her wing.
Well, then.
Do you mind if we left Ingrid
in your care, Empress?
I'd love that!
[SARA groans]
[TIA groans]
[groans]
[SARA]
Oh, my gosh, I'm so tired!
Oh, my gosh, I'm so hungry!
[RETSU growls]
I find that hard to beleive
considering you ate
all of our food as
soon as you got back!
[SARA, TIA]
Aww...
[gasps]
Come on, get up, she's watching!
You don't understand what
we've been through!
Yeah, it was hot, then cold,
then we fell out of the sky.
It was rough!
[growls]
[BOTH yelp]
Look, if you don't finish quick,
you won't get to visit Yui.
[SARA, TIA]
Aww, no way!
[BOTH panting]
[grunting]
Ya see? Worked like a charm.
[giggles]
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
Oh, wow! You look
so beautiful, Ingrid!
That dress was made for yo--
I'll have you know I was
just trying on the dress
to see if it would fit,
that's all I was doing!
You're already thinking about
what I said to you
earlier, aren't you?
I was just curious
to see how it looked.
I think it looks good on you.
[INGRID] If you'll excuse me,
I think I'll change now.
But my point is, if you're
happy in this dress,
then you should wear it.
[sighs]
Yeah, well... Maybe.
Heh.
[YUI giggles]
[YUI]
So, anyway.
I wanted to warn you that things
are about to get
a bit more lively.
[RETSU]
Oh. My. Gosh!
Who is this
darling little angel?!
Yui, this has to
be Kei, am I right?
[YUI]
Mm-hmm.
[RETSU] Dear God, I know I
haven't been a big believer
in your existence, but I swear,
I'll never doubt again!
[SARA, TIA]
Whee!
[RETSU]
Hey, stop that running!
[SARA, TIA]
Okay!
My goodness, your other friend
is quite the beauty, too!
You're incredibly striking!
Oh, sorry.
Please allow me to introduce
a good friend of mine.
Hi! Retsu Narumi,
pleasure to meet you!
Her Royal Highness,
Princess Ingrid of Rimgarde.
Highness? Oh, forgive me
for being forward.
I had no idea!
I'm not a princess anymore.
So we can dispense
with the titles.
[YUI gasps]
Oh? Wow! I can get to know you!
Uh-- Sure, okay!
[RETSU]
Yay! Thank you so much!
--How exciting!
--Calm down, Retty!
Hey, Retsu!
We need your help
over here, please!
Yeah, one sec!
Very nice to meet you!
[SARA]
Wait, now you're running!
[TIA]
You're running!
[RETSU]
Oh, I guess I am! Sorry!
Let's get to it!
[SARA, TIA]
Yeah!
[INGRID]
You've got very nice friends.
Yeah, I think so, too!
[GIRLS]
Cheers!
[glasses clanking]
[YUI]
Would you mind if I joined you?
[gasps softly]
[giggles]
[YUI]
You know,
this has always been a favorite
spot of mine and Rena's.
[INGRID]
Yeah?
[YUI]
When we're feeling down
or dealing with
something difficult.
this is where we like to come.
We don't even have
to talk, necessarily.
It's more that the
peacefulness of this place
puts things in perspective.
Sitting on these steps
brings back memories for me.
Huh?
You may not know,
but I was at your mother's
enthronement ceremony.
I was one of the
foreign dignitaries
chosen to deliver
a celebratory speech.
But before I took the podium,
I turned tail and ran
out of the building.
[YUI]
You did?
I suppose you could say
that I didn't really care much
for all the formalities that
came with being a princess.
Once the ceremony started,
I got nervous.
And then I couldn't figure out
how to go back inside
after having run out.
That's when...
[YUI'S MOM]
A-ha! Found you!
[INGRID]
Oh.
[BOTH chuckle]
My mom came to get you?
And as a matter of fact,
she was holding you in her arms.
Really? Oh, my gosh, I'm sorry!
I wish I could
remember all of this!
You were too little for
any memory to stick.
So... I'd honestly be
more surprised if you could.
What do you think those two
are talking about down there?
Eep!
Rena!
Be quiet if you're gonna snoop.
Sorry...
[INGRID] Your Highness...
What about the ceremony?
Is it okay for you
to leave like that?
"The new empress
suddenly fell ill
and was regrettably
forced to take her leave
partway through the
scheduled events."
Huh?
"Therefore, the ceremony
could not be continued
and all following speeches
from visiting dignitaries
were cancelled."
But, is it truly that simple?
I'm sure Margaret and the others
will know how to handle it.
Right?
[YUI giggles]
[YUI'S MOM chuckles]
--Wow, look at you!
--Your Highness.
Excuse me.
I was wondering...
Can you tell me why we have
kings and queens and empresses?
But you're royalty!
Is that really what
you were thinking?
Now that I think about it, it's
kind of an embarrassing memory
[YUI'S MOM]
Well, to be honest,
that's not an easy
question to answer.
[YUI'S MOM]
Let me ask you, Ingrid:
Are you fond of your country?
Well, yes, I suppose
I usually am.
So, what do you like about it?
I'm not really sure.
Um...
Sorry, it's hard
to pin it down exactly.
[YUI'S MOM chuckles] It's an
overwhelming thought, I know.
We love our homelands
for lots of reasons,
some of which are
hard to express.
[INGRID]
Yes...
[YUI'S MOM] I'd bet
most people feel that way.
[INGRID]
You do?
[YUI'S MOM] Sometimes,
things can get you down
and you wonder why
you're where you are.
I've felt it myself
often enough.
Don't let it get to you. 'Kay?
Remember to focus on
the things that remind you
just how special
your country is.
All of the things that endear it
to you. Like no other place
[BOTH laugh]
[YUI'S MOM] Those are the
things that keep us going.
Yes... I suppose
that you're right.
You see? I think that's
the role of a leader.
To be a reminder to her
people of what is good
and right about their country.
[INGRID] I don't know if I
can be that for them, though.
I'm not always
sure I can, either.
I get confused and overwhelmed
just like anybody else does.
But in the end, it comes down to
the fact that I love Enastoria.
That's something that is
never going to change.
[YUI'S MOM] I just have
to keep trying my best.
I'm still an
empress-in-training, you know.
[INGRID] I wish I could
see things the way you do.
Don't worry.
Your heart is in
the right place,
and that's what really
matters, don't you think?
I hope so.
And even if you and I
don't achieve greatness,
we've got Yui.
And later, you girls will
have children, as well.
[YUI'S MOM] I believe as long
as we pass these feelings
and ideals on to those
who come after us,
we will have done our duty
for our countries.
That's a really
beautiful thought, Empress.
You know, actually, we'll
both be in training together.
We can help each other out!
[INGRID]
Thank you.
[YUI]
Me, too, help!
[laughs]
That's right, Yui!
You're in training, too,
aren't you?
[laughs]
[YUI laughs]
[INGRID] You look as though
you might have a question.
Please tell me about Rena.
It was after the
Fall of Rimgarde
that I found out where she was.
Here in Enastoria.
So, Abel and I just waited.
We bided our time until you
could become bound to her.
[YUI]
But... why me?
[INGRID] We thought
it was destiny that Rena
was taken in by your mother,
and made a part of your family.
After your mother passed away,
we thought it was only
a matter of time
until you would bond,
since you were the only one
left by her side.
But once Johann discovered
Rena's whereabouts,
Abel and I knew
we were out of time.
We couldn't wait any longer.
[YUI] That's why you came after
her with the Regalia Gear.
[INGRID]
We did it to save Kei.
To cause a resonance,
all the Regalia need to have
someone bound to them.
So that explains
why Abel came, too!
Because you hadn't
been bound yet.
Without you, Alecto's power
was still incomplete.
[gasps]
Empress Yui...
Look after Ingrid for me.
She will need you...
He spoke of you.
It makes sense now...
[INGRID]
Yes... He fought for us.
Abel was trying to
protect us from Johann.
Kei and I, and you and Rena.
You know, I once sent
a letter to the empress.
I knew that she would
be concerned for me,
so I wrote to let her know
that I was still alive,
and that having Rena in
Enastoria could be bad for you.
I told her that if she cared
about the well-being
of her daughter,
then she might have to
make a tough decision.
[gasps softly]
[YUI'S MOM] Yui and Rena
are both my daughters.
[YUI'S MOM] I know that no
matter what happens,
they'll work together
to figure things out.
Because... they're my family,
and I believe in them.
[INGRID] Sometimes I think
her response kept me going
when nothing else really could.
[YUI]
I never imagined...
[INGRID] I'm truly sorry that I
had to involve you
and your beautiful
country in this mess.
It wasn't my intention.
[YUI]
I think I'm a little jealous.
[INGRID]
Huh?
I mean, it's just that I
never got to talk to my mom
about anything like that.
[INGRID] I'm sure there
are a million things
she would've shared with you
if she had the chance.
I've been watching you fight
for quite a long time, now.
You've been so lost,
and you've suffered,
but you've never given up on
what's most important to you.
Sweet Yuinshiel.
You may not realize it,
but you're exactly like
your dear mother.
[gasps]
[INGRID] I can't take
her place in your life.
No one can.
But you need to be told
that you've done well.
[INGRID]
Thank you... Yuinshiel...
[YUI whimpers]
[GROUP sobbing, sniffing]
[RETSU]
Quit crying, you guys!
[TIA] Oh, come on,
you're crying, too!
[YUI] Thank you, Ingrid.
Your words honor me.
[INGRID]
No need to be formal.
In that case, you have to
promise not to be so formal
with me, either.
Sounds good to me, Yui.
[BOTH giggle]
[RETSU sniffs]
Hey, what are you two doing?
You better come inside soon
or dinner is gonna get cold!
Quick! Everybody
wipe those tears!
[GROUP grunting]
Well, it looks like our friends
have gotten tired
of eavesdropping.
What do you mean?
[INGRID chuckles]
[JOHANN]
Doesn't this look cozy.
I'd love to join you.
[YUI gasps]
[JOHANN] Hey, there!
Been a while, hasn't it?
Actually, no, it hasn't really.
You bastard!
How rude!
[grunts]
[JOHANN]
Didn't even let me say my piece!
[SARA] What?!
How many of him are there?
[JOHANN] We hardly see
each other anymore.
We should make the most of
the time we have together.
Now don't you worry, Ingrid.
I don't need to use you and
your sweet little Kei
like I did before.
No. My new toy is so
much more interesting.
[gasps]
[TIA]
Woah. That's enormous!
[JOHANN]
Pretty great, huh?
I decided to bring 'em
along with me
to come pick you guys up.
[INGRID]
Pick us up?
[KEI] You think we'll
go somewhere with you?
I don't plan on
giving you a choice.
I want all of you
to have front row,
VIP seats for the
end of the world.
[CROWD murmuring]
Let's go!
--[grunts]
--[INGRID] Yui.
We've got your back.
It's time for us to
stop him once and for all.
You ready, Kei?
Absolutely!
Are we going to help, too, Sara?
Yui's home and city are
in danger. You bet we are!
[TIA]
Hmm!
[SARA]
Here we go!
[TIA]
Yeah!
[NOA]
Sara... Tia...
Who is that?
Big sister?
Huh?
--[RENA] Yui!
--[screams]
[SARA]
What happened?
Wake up, Yui! Can you hear me?
[JOHANN] Oh, my! Did she
collapse? What a shocker.
Huh?
[JOHANN] Come on. Don't tell me
you're actually surprised.
Surely you've noticed that
you and the empress
are in bad shape.
[gasps]
No...
I don't believe
this is happening.
They've only just been
bound to each other!
[JOHANN] True. But they
took quite a beating.
You saw it happen, didn't you?
Damn you!
[RENA whimpers]
Please, no... Not this...
Yui!
The real fun hasn't
even started yet.
I wonder how she'll handle
my next little curve ball.
[RENA gasps]
No! [screams]
[SARA, TIA screaming]
[KEI]
What can we do?!
Die, Johann!
No, I don't think I will.
We're done here, so, if you
would, Regalia of Erinius,
right this way.
[yelps]
[squeals]
Yui! [sobs]
[RENA sobbing]
--[alarm beeping]
--[YUI gasps]
[beeping continues]
Where is she?