[YUI hums softly]
[AOI]
Yui! Are you awake?
Oh! Good morning.
Good morning to you, too.
So, today we've got
a full schedule and--
Are you having some
kinda brunch buffet?
What are you talking about?
This is just breakfast.
Well, you're a growing girl
and you do need to eat.
But do this every day and
you may start getting chubby.
[YUI]
Hey, Aoi.
What is it?
Have you seen Rena
or any of the others?
They've been gone since
before I woke up.
Who's Rena?
Is she a new friend of yours?
[gasps]
Good morning, Yui!
[YUI]
Hey. Morning, Retty.
Last night, did somethi--?
Before I forget, were
Sara and Tia still at your place
when you left?
No. I didn't see them
at all this morning.
I assumed that they went
back to the restaurant.
Oh, good grief!
I told those two they were
scheduled to work
the breakfast shift today.
So, what were you
saying about last night?
[YUI]
Mm-mm. It's not important.
Okay.
[RETSU] But wait, I haven't
even gotten to the best part!
[giggles] Then I found
the cutest cutie ever!
Really? That cute?
[RETSU]
You should have seen her.
Her hair was so long and
the most gorgeous color...
Sorry, but we
can not let you in.
[YUI] Oh, is this
entrance closed right now?
[GUARD 10]
Hmm?
No, miss.
However, the general public
can't enter the castle
without special permission.
There are certain days
when it's open to visitors.
You should try coming back then.
Oh. Okay.
Thank you for the information.
[phone vibrates]
Aoi usually answers
right away...
Where is she?
[MAN panting]
[YUI grunts]
[WOMAN A]
He's in such a rush
you'd think the world
was going to end.
Can I give you a hand?
Yes.
Thank you for helping me.
You're very welcome.
But you also need to watch where
you're going in the future,
all right, dear?
Yes, ma'am. I will.
Ma'am?
Was there something else?
[YUI]
No... Never mind...
[WOMAN A]
Hmm.
[TEEN] Come back here.
Where you going? Wait up!
[BOYS laugh]
[BOY A]
I bet I can beat ya there!
[BOY B]
No way!
[gasps]
[YUI]
Retty!
Ah?
Retty! Oh, thank goodness.
Things are crazy.
--We're closed now.
--I feel like the whole world--
I'm afraid you're going to
have to come back tomorrow.
Thanks for stopping by, though.
We love new customers.
On your next visit, we'll give
you a dessert, on the house.
But, Retty...
[RETSU]
Hmm? What?
You're mistaken.
My name is Retsu.
I don't think we've
met before, have we?
[gasps]
[YUI]
It's me... It's Yui!
[RETSU]
Uh...
[YUI]
Nobody calls me "Yui" in school.
You're the only one who does.
And you have ever
since we were little.
It meant a lot to me that you
treated me like I was normal.
I really wanted
to be your friend,
so I gave you a nickname: Retty.
You always used to smile
and look so happy
when I called you that.
I'm sorry.
I hate to disappoint you, but I
think you have the wrong person.
[gasps]
Ah! What's wrong?
I feel... sleepy
all of a sudden...
Oh, my gosh, Retty,
are you okay? Wake up!
Yui... That's your name?
Thank you for helping me
get home and into bed.
You didn't have to
do that... Sorry...
Goodnight, Retty. Sweet dreams.
[gasps softly]
[gasps]
These rings are
for you and Rena.
A gift for me
and Big Sissy?
[giggles]
Yui?
Yes, Mama? What is it?
These rings are special. They
will help guide you and Rena
whenever either of you
may be feeling lost or down.
Guide us to what?
[YUI'S MOM]
To each other.
They are reminders
that you are family
and that you have promised
to work together.
[YUI]
Hmm... I don't think I get it.
As your big sister, Rena is
going to look out for you,
but I want you to look
out for her, too.
Will you promise me that?
[YUI]
Mm! Yes, Mama. I promise!
[YUI'S MOM]
Hmm. That's my girl!
[giggles]
Can I go give Rena her ring?
Pretty please,
with sugar on top!
Of course you can.
Give it to her right now.
[YUI]
Bye, Mama! Thank you!
[door creaks]
[sighs]
I miss you...
I made a promise.
Rena, Sara, Tia,
Kei, and Ingrid.
They need me! There's
no way I'm giving up now!
[yelps]
My friends, hang on!
I'm coming to help you!
[YUI gasps]
[YUI]
Sara... Tia.
Is that Yui?
You're right! I think it is!
[SARA, TIA sob]
Please, girls. Don't cry.
[ALL sobbing]
There's plenty left
if you two want seconds.
So please feel free to eat
as much as you want.
Thank you,
but I think I'm full...
[gasps]
I'm not hungry... Sorry...
Tell me what really
happened last night.
After I collapsed.
[gasps]
[JOHANN]
Hello, everyone!
Welcome to Lux Ex Machina!
You all get to be
front and center
to watch what happens next.
I hope you like your VIP seats.
Oh, no! Please tell me
you're lying. It can't be!
[chuckles] Look! Lux Ex Machina,
fully restored in all its glory!
Can you believe it?
[growls softly]
What does he mean?
Is he talking about the thing
we sealed up years ago?
[JOHANN] Once the Erinius
Regalia came together,
creating a resonance
and using it
to bring back Kei
was relatively easy.
What you didn't realize is that
meant breaking the seal
on Lux Ex Machina as well.
[INGRID gasps]
You never--!
Never told you about that?
Come now, don't be so naïve.
Why would I tell you
the whole truth?
[gasps]
[JOHANN] Still, I guess
I should thank you, Ingrid.
Were it not for your
12 years of hard work,
my dream would never
have become a reality.
[growls]
[INGRID snarls]
[gasps]
[growls]
[chuckles]
You have to try and
stay focused, Ingrid.
These aren't like the
Regalia Gear we've faced before.
[JOHANN]
She's right about that.
The old ones I gave to you are
pieces of junk
compared to these.
[KEI] If we just charge in,
the Gear will destroy us.
We need to work together
with Tia and Sara.
[JOHANN] You may have some
trouble getting their attention.
They seem to have
taken an interest in
another one of my puppets.
Something about this one
feels kinda familiar.
Big sister?
[JOHANN chuckles]
Wonderful. Happy family reunion.
Now it's about time
we started the show.
[snaps]
Lux Ex Machina is
starting to move. Look!
[gasps]
Oh, my god...
[JOHANN]
Breathtaking, isn't it?
[growls softly]
From up here you can
see the whole planet.
What better place to watch
the end of the world?
[RENA whimpers]
[TIA]
Sara, this is bad!
He's going to make
everyone disappear again!
I won't make them
vanish right away.
I thought we could
have a little fun first.
Now.
[gasps]
Yui!
[JOHANN] Little by little, I've
begun erasing people's memories.
Particularly their memories
of our dear, sweet empress.
She can't get
into her own castle!
That's awful...
[INGRID gasps]
[JOHANN] At this point even her
most precious, trusted friends
have forgotten her.
Retsu...
Not you, too!
[JOHANN]
Now, she's about to cry!
I almost feel sorry for her.
[growls]
[JOHANN]
All by herself...
Scared, confused, and without
a friend in the world.
She's lost everything
she ever loved or cared about.
She must be terribly lonely.
But what do I know?
I've got no soul and
don't care about anything.
[INGRID]
Johann!
I refuse to stand idly by
and allow you to torture Yui!
Go back to the void,
you monster!
[gasps]
Are you okay?!
Oh, no!
Sara, we have to help them!
Big sister...
[gasps]
[BOTH scream]
[JOHANN] Hah! You're the
only one left standing.
Batter up.
My little sister needs me.
And I'm going to protect her
no matter what!
[JOHANN]
Nice!
That's the ol' fighting spirit.
[RENA groans]
In the name of... Erinious!
Magna Alecto!
[laughs]
Well, that's no good.
[RENA whimpers]
[SARA grunts]
Rena!
[TIA]
Sara! Do something!
[grunts]
Get back! Get away!
[SARA]
Noa--listen, please.
If you're in there, help us!
Can she even hear us...?
[NOA]
Sara... Tia...
Run!
[BOTH gasp]
You have to get away!
[grunts]
[SARA]
What are you doing?!
[NOA]
Sara, Tia... Forgive me...
[SARA whimpers]
[NOA screams]
Don't make us leave you!
[JOHANN]
Bad Noa!
No more regaining
control of yourself.
[SARA]
I'm sorry, Yui. I feel terrible.
Here you were in
this awful situation
and there was nothing
we could do to help you.
It's okay
I'm sorry, too.
But I can't stop thinking about
that huge Regalia Gear,
and our sister trapped inside.
It was all very strange.
Noa should have been completely
swallowed up by Lux Ex Machina,
but somehow she wasn't.
What's wrong?
Were you very
lonely and scared?
Yeah, I was.
But... I'm not anymore
'cause you're here.
[BOTH gasp]
Thank you both so much
for coming back for me.
I can't tell you
how much it means.
[YUI] Don't worry. We will find
a way to reach the others.
But how?
Yeah. I can't fly.
I'm not sure yet,
but we'll figure it out.
I hope so.
We're stuck, but there are
some things we can do to help.
--Really?
--[TIA] Like what?
The three of us can
eat a hot meal,
and get a good night's rest.
[BOTH]
How will that help?
C'mon, Sara.
Don't you always feel happy
after you've eaten
a nice, hot meal?
[SARA] Mm-hmm! That's the
best part about eating.
And Tia, don't you always
feel your happiest
when you're sleeping
in a nice warm bed?
[TIA] Mm-hmm! I love
being under the covers!
[YUI] When you're
feeling sad and lost,
and you wallow
in those feelings,
they just keep getting
bigger and bigger.
You have to fight them
off with happiness
before they get too big.
Besides, if we want
to save the others,
we're going to need all
the stamina we can muster.
[BOTH]
Right!
[YUI]
I'm gonna roll up my sleeves
and make us
something scrumptious!
[SARA] I'll start
peeling the vegetables!
[TIA]
I'll help you!
[YUI] Let's cook up
a mouth-watering feast!
[SARA, TIA]
Yeah!
[TIA snores softly]
Hey, Yui, are you asleep?
No. Not yet.
Is there something
on your mind?
[whimpers]
Before he took us, while
you were passed out,
Johann said something. That you
and Rena were in bad shape.
If he's right, then pretty soon,
you're gonna end up
like Ryu and Lowe.
I see...
I'm sorry. I know I shouldn't
have said anything,
but I'm afraid of losing you.
No, Sara. It's okay.
Thank you for telling me.
Try to get some rest.
[RENA] Yui's out there,
fighting all by herself.
But I know in my heart
she still believes in us.
[RENA]
Please. Help me save her.
Rena...
[SARA] Yui, be honest with me,
are you afraid to die?
Sara!
Of course I am.
Yesterday, I felt for the
first time how lonely it is
when everything you know
and love suddenly disappears.
[YUI] I want to go on
living with Rena.
I want to keep
serving my people.
There's still so much
I have to do.
Yui...
[YUI] But the first step
that I have to take
is just to be brave.
So I'm wearing the clothes
that give me confidence!
[gasps, giggles]
[SARA] Everyone who's made up
their mind to do something,
raise your hand!
Don't forget we wanna
save our sister, too!
But--are you sure it's
even possible to save her?
Why not? She helped us
escape, didn't she?
She must be in there somewhere!
Okay, time to put
our game faces on!
[BOTH gasp, growl]
We'll do everything
we can. Together.
[BOTH laugh]
[YUI giggles, laughs]
[ALL laughing]
[sighing]
[gasps]
[SARA, TIA gasp]
It's her again?
[gasps]