[JONNY] The countdown has begun.
Time's running out.
What now?
Don't worry.
It's going to be okay.
[JONNY laughs]
Aw, nice try.
It isn't working!
Then we'll try harder!
[gasps]
[JONNY] Now, let's see here. How
many minutes are left, again?
No more.
Three!
[JONNY]
Two!
[JOHAN]
One!
[JONNY gasping]
[RENA] By the name and
the will of Erinius...
Alecto shall prevail!
Steel fangs, forged by darkness.
Heh.
Unleash Niero Assault!
[JONNY, JOHAN laugh]
Did you believe you'd won?
[BOTH gasp]
[laughs]
[JOHAN] Quite a show. Though it
would've been better at night.
[JOHAN laughing]
[YUI]
Rena?
[YUI gasping]
[YUI]
What's wrong? What's happening?
[gasps]
[YUI]
A Regalia?
[JOHAN] Aw, come on. We were
just getting to the good part.
I can live with that
small disappointment.
This means all the keys
have come together.
[YUI]
Rena!
No! Uh! Come back!
What is that?
I've got you!
[RENA panting]
Who are... you?
[gasps]
Yui!
[INGRID]
Stop. That's enough.
No fair.
Now that they're both here,
at least let me say hello.
What's the harm in that?
Uh. Fine, as you wish...
I'll go now.
Hmph.
[RENA]
Tisis.
Looks like Rena's found
her way back to herself.
Although, I don't think now
would be the best
time to talk to her.
Well, maybe we should go
back to the restaurant.
I'm starving!
Sure! Sounds perfect!
[RENA]
Are you okay?
I'm so glad you're safe.
[YUI]
Show me, Theodore.
[THEODORE]
Here.
As you can see, it's exactly
like the fall of Rimgarde
12 years ago.
Except for the involvement
of the Regalia Gear.
The Regalia Gear seem quite
similar to Rena's Regalia,
so perhaps they're related.
I would like to know
why the other one
stopped the fight
and disappeared.
That's something we're
currently looking into.
And what of the other
issue we discussed?
We still haven't found
definitive evidence.
Let's pin down a location
as soon as possible.
[THEODORE]
Yes, ma'am.
[YUI]
Thank you.
I think I would like to go and
see how the recovery work
is coming along so far.
[ALL]
Hm?
You must be exhausted, though.
Why don't you rest
for a little bit?
But, I don't want
to take it easy
while everyone else
is working so hard.
For tonight, just rest.
I've got a busy day planned for
you tomorrow, don't worry.
[YUI]
Uh?
[RENA gasps]
What's wrong?
[RENA]
Uh... Yui?
Uh! You're here!
How do you feel?
Are you in a lot of pain?
No. I'm perfectly fine,
thanks to you.
Thank goodness!
I was so worried.
Not as worried as I was!
I was starting to think you
were never waking up.
I'm just tired, is all.
Are you sure?
Uh-huh.
I'm glad to hear that!
Especially since I'll
be out tomorrow.
[RENA]
Uh?
The festival is
starting, remember?
[RENA]
Oh.
I'm going into town to see
how the preparations
are coming along.
While I'm gone, you can
get all the rest you need.
Shouldn't you take some
time to rest, too?
Don't worry. I'll be okay.
It might help to lift the
people's spirits if I go.
I'm sure it will, and it's
your duty as Empress.
[YUI] I knew you'd
understand. Good night.
[RENA]
Good night.
[OWNER 3A]
Welcome, welcome!
Excuse me,
are these candies?
They are. Take
whichever you'd like!
Your Highness! We set aside
our best just for you!
Freshly popped! Please
take some, Empress Yui!
Wow. You're all very
kind, thank you!
We brought you some
things, too, Empress Yui!
All my favorites!
Thanks! I hope we
see you again soon.
[sighs]
[RENA]
A green onion skewer, please.
Sure thing! Wait.
[RETSU]
Hey, Renny!
There's a little favor
I need to ask of you.
Uh...
You love being out among
your people, don't you?
Yes. Where do you think
we should go next?
Huh? Oh. I'd say that's plenty.
We've gone through the
whole street already.
Are you sure?
You did a great job today.
I think that you've earned
yourself a little break.
All right, then. Thanks
a lot. See you later!
That's quite a haul.
[laughs]
Oh.
[SARA yelping]
Uh! Can I help? Are you okay?
[SARA groans]
Ow...
Huh?
Hey! I saw you on TV!
[RETSU] Basically, you
want to use our kitchen
to make something for Yui,
and you don't want me to say
anything to her about it?
Well. That's very
big-sisterly of you!
[RENA growls]
Uh. I, uh, mean, it's not like
I'm surprised or anything!
Yui always talks about how
great her big sister is,
and now I can see it myself!
Hey, slow down or
you'll fall! Careful!
See, you should've
listened to me.
[whimpers]
That's my big girl. No tears.
Yep!
I'm tough, huh?
[BIG SISTER]
You sure are.
So, is that what the
two of you were like
back when you
were growing up?
Yui did cry pretty easily
when she was little.
But, since then, she's grown
into a strong and capable woman.
She sure has.
Do you miss having her
around all the time,
now that she's so busy?
I'm not some little kid
who needs her hand held.
[RETSU laughs]
[TIA grunts]
So heavy!
At least tell me what
you're making for her.
No way.
Oh, Retsu! You're back.
Uh?!
Uh.
[TIA]
Huh?!
Why are you here?
You two know each other?
That's so sweet. Thanks!
Now, don't forget to clean
it when you get a chance.
So, you said you're visiting
from another country?
Tia and I aren't from here.
Oh, "Tia"? Is that who you
came here with, uh, sorry?
Oh. Sara.
It's nice to meet
you. My name's--
[SARA]
Yuinshiel Asteria!
[gasps]
Like I said, I saw you on TV.
It's really cool
meeting a celebrity!
Right. Well, thanks.
You can call me Yui.
'Kay, I will.
The guy who gave us a ride
here said you're always
working really hard and
you're a great person too.
Well, that's very nice of him.
He said he'd like to have you
for a daughter-in-law,
but his son's no prince...
You're going to make me blush!
But he also thought it would be
better if you didn't go around
telling everyone in the world
what your measurements are.
[gasps] No! I didn't mean to!
[SARA] I like you!
You're funny. [laughs]
There you go.
I guess you're gettin'
the hang of this.
[laughs]
If you want, you can sit down
and have a cup with us.
Really? Yay!
[RETSU] Just until a customer
comes, all right?
Yep!
I'm surprised Sara's
not with you.
Yeah. She's busy right now.
She said something
about "forced labor"
and went off to
run some errands.
I had to stay behind
as a hostage.
[RENA]
Hm...
Wait, she doesn't know what
she's talking about, Renny!
We're actually
the victims here!
Thanks a lot, Sara...
You don't always have to
look so scary. Now, smile!
[RETSU]
Hey, stop manhandling her!
You're going to hurt my
precious little Renny!
Wait a sec. What do
you mean, "yours"?
You and Rena may be friends,
but it's not like
she's bound to you.
[RETSU]
Huh?
Break's over.
You're expected back at
the stall, so get moving.
[RETSU]
Aww...
[growls]
Uh! I thought I could enjoy a
little time with my friends,
but no, around here it's
all work, work, work!
We'll see you later.
[door closes]
[YUI]
Oh, wow!
You've been traveling around
the world all this time?
That's impressive for
somebody so young.
Yep!
Except now we're stuck in this
city as indentured servants.
I don't know when we'll
be able to leave again.
Huh?
I was sent to run errands, but
they're holding Tia hostage.
The poor thing must be
so frightened right now!
What are you doing?
Helping Tia. Can you
take me to her?
Uh.
[RETSU]
Aww.
And I thought I was finally
gonna get some time
to bond with little Renny!
[RETSU gasping]
[YUI] Impossible! I never
imagined it would be you!
What?
These poor, frightened girls
are guests in our country
and you decided to turn
them into your slaves?
That's it! I've had enough!
Whatever she told
you, it's a lie!
Seriously?
[gasps]
Sara...
[whines]
[TIA laughs]
This is so much fun! We haven't
cooked together in a while.
I'm really sorry
about yesterday.
We didn't like it,
but we had to stop you.
I know. Thank you for that.
[TIA]
Did you see Kei?
I did.
I wish I understood what's going
on with her, but I have no idea.
[TIA] If you two are in a fight,
I'm sure we can sort it out.
Once Sara gets back,
we can all go see Kei!
And then after the two
of you have made up,
we'll go back home with Sara.
We'll all live together again.
It'll be just like
old times, right?
But I've got Yui now.
Yui? You mean you're
bound to someone?
Cool! You can bring her along!
You'll be together forever,
just like me and Sara!
That does sound really nice.
[TIA]
So let's do it!
I can't. Yui has... obligations.
[TIA]
Hm?
[RETSU]
Whoa! Look at this line!
A skewer sampler
please, Highness!
Thank you so much for
waiting. Take care!
Ugh. I'm so worn out,
and I'm starving.
You're earning your
food this time.
I won't let you dine
and dash again.
Sorry, Retty. I guess I
misunderstood before.
I think it's probably
more accurate to say
that you were lied to before.
Quit spacing out!
Honestly! This is
the thanks I get
for letting you stay until you
could work off your bill?
I should've just reported you!
[SARA whines]
Oh, come on, you can give
the poor girl a break.
Get a little rest, Sara.
We can take it from here.
Huh? Uh?
Thanks!
[RETSU]
Okay, fine, you can go.
[SARA]
Woo-hoo!
[RETSU] You're too soft
on her, you know!
[YUI laughs]
[sighs]
[stomach growls]
[SARA groans]
[gasps]
[RETSU]
Hungry?
[SARA]
For me? You're the best!
[YUI laughs]
[RETSU groans]
Oh. What a long day!
It was really nice of you to
help run the stall with us.
Actually, I had a lot of fun!
You were a total natural.
Yeah! The skewers
were delicious.
[laughs] I'm glad, thank you!
So, a love for cooking
is something
you and Renny have in common?
I wonder what she's making
over at our place right now.
[YUI] Huh? I didn't know Rena
came to your place today.
Maybe you should head over there
and see what she's been up to.
Uh...
Hey, hold on. You know
somebody named Rena?
[YUI]
Huh?
It's all finished.
Aw, yay!
[RETSU, SARA]
We're back!
Oh! Looks like they're
done working the stall.
[YUI]
Something smells good.
[gasps]
[SARA]
Rena! [laughs]
Sara.
So, have you actually been
with Yui for all these years?
[RENA]
Uh!
Yui? The person you were
telling me about before?
Um, hello!
My name is Yuinshiel Asteria,
and you must be Tia.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a Regalia, like Rena.
Huh?
[RETSU]
Hm?
[SARA]
Wait. What?
[RENA]
Mm.
Really? You mean she
finally found somebody?
I'm so happy for you, Rena!
[YUI] I see now. Sara and
Tia, they're like us.
Yeah. Well, obviously, there's
something I'm missing here.
Did you finish it, Renny?
Uh! Yeah.
Oh, wow! For me?
I wanted to make you
something special.
We put some love into it!
You help so many people
without asking for anything.
So, thanks.
This is what you were
up to all day?
[RENA]
Mm-hm.
I love it, thank you! And
thank you for helping, Tia.
My pleasure!
Wait a sec. I think
I've seen you before!
--Are you the Booby Empress?
--[YUI]  What?!
That's right, the Booby Empress:
not just super nice
and an amazing cook,
she's also got a rockin' body!
She does!
Hey! Please don't call me that.
[laughing]
Aw, not you too, Rena?
[BOTH laugh]
No matter what, we'll
always be together, right?
Right!
So, anybody wanna
piece o' cake?
Yeah! Make sure I get
a really big piece!
Two really, really
big ones for me!
I'm not sure you
two deserve any.
[TIA] Aww! But we worked
so hard! Please?
In fact, I think I
deserve three slices.
[SARA] Well, in that case,
I deserve four, at least!