[JOHAN]
It'll be visible before long.
Soon, we'll see Lux's power.
[gasps] Tell me what's
going on here!
I don't understand
what Rena's doing.
[BOTH gasping]
[gasps]
What's happening?
Ingrid, you're here...
[OPERATORS scream]
[TV REPORTER] Everyone is
excited about this week's
National Foundation Festival.
Preparation is coming
along nicely in Asteri,
where vendors began setting
up their stalls today.
Many already line the
streets to Nornil Square,
and the surrounding area is
abuzz with anticipation.
[YUI hums]
[TV REPORTER] And now, your
worldwide weather report.
[TV REPORTER] First,
conditions across Enastoria:
The whole country seems to be
blessed with good weather today.
Silwia will be mostly sunny
with some scattered clouds.,..
[RENA grunting, gasps]
[sighs]
[YUI]
Good morning, Rena!
What's so good about it?
[YUI]
Uh?
Yui! I said I would take
care of breakfast today.
Class is starting back up,
so I wanted to make
something special.
I could have made
[RENA] You are good at
making breakfast, though.
[YUI]
Umm...
[RENA]
What?
[laughs] I haven't made tea yet.
Would you mind doing it for me?
[RENA]
Hmph.
I guess that'd be okay.
Thanks, Rena. You're the best!
Uh!
[RENA] It seems like your
break was pretty short, huh?
[YUI]
Yeah, just a week.
We'll be out before
noon today, though.
But I thought I
might stay behind.
Retty and I can spend some
time studying for exams.
I don't understand
why you would want
to spend your time with her.
[gasps]
[RENA clears throat] I don't
enjoy having Retsu around,
that's all. She insists
on patting me on my head
and ruffling my hair
every time I see her.
I hate it when she does that!
[YUI laughs]
That's her way of
showing she likes you.
She always treats me like
a snot-nosed little kid.
Never mind that I'm
actually the big sister.
[knocking]
[AOI]
Yui! Rena! I'm coming in.
[gasps] Good morning!
Good morning, Aoi.
Morning...
Anyway, I just wanted to
give you a heads-up.
It looks like we'll have
a couple extra hours
of free time this afternoon.
Okay, thank you.
No problem! Now, if you'll
excuse me, I've gotta go.
See ya!
[RENA] Too early for all
that running around.
She has a lot on her plate,
so you can't really
blame her, can you?
I'd say you have a bit more
on your plate than she does.
[YUI] I know! Now that
I've got some free time,
we can go on a sister date!
Let's go shopping!
And we can visit that café
you've been wanting to try.
It's okay.
You've been really busy, you
don't need to feel obligated.
I don't.
We haven't been able to spend
a lot of time together lately.
I just though that this might
be a good chance, you know.
Yeah, whatever.
Come on...
I'll think about it.
Well, that's good enough.
But I know it'll be fun!
All right, I'll see you later.
Okay, see you later.
[YUI] Hey. I'm actually pretty
excited about our date.
Would you stop
calling it a date?
What?
I was just thinking it's too bad
my ring doesn't fit anymore.
Uh!
[RENA hums]
[gasps]
Wait!
[YUI laughs]
[YUI]
Hold the door. I'm coming!
[RENA gasping]
[phone vibrates]
[RENA]
Kei?
How have you been, Rena? Well?
I didn't actually see you that
time, so it has been a while.
[RENA] What do you mean?
[KEI] You truly don't
remember? [laughs]
You should come with me, then.
[gasps]
You haven't forgotten
the incident
12 years ago in Rimgarde?
I don't think you'd want the
same thing to happen here.
[KEI] Because you've gotten
close to somebody too,
haven't you?
I'll be waiting.
[phone vibrates]
Hey Rena, where are you?
[RENA]
Well...
I thought you said you're
at the café already.
I'm sorry. Something
came up, and I had to go.
[YUI] All right. Well, let's
have dinner together, then.
Since I made breakfast,
I'll let you cook.
Make whatever you wan--
[RENA] I don't think
I can do that either.
I'm not sure when I'll
be able to come back.
Why? What's wrong?
[WAITRESS 1A]
Excuse me.
A young lady asked me
to give this to you.
[YUI]
I'm sorry. What is this?
It's a present from
your big sis.
I wanted to give it
to you myself, but...
Rena. What's going on?
I'm really sorry. I am.
But... I promise I'll
come back someday.
Wait for me, okay? Please.
[click]
[YUI gasps]
I don't understand.
[RENA]
Where is Kei?
[MORALES] She's not
actually here right now.
She sent me to bring you in,
so that's what I'm gonna do.
If you wanna see her, you're
gonna have to come with me.
Then let's go. Lead the way.
Uh?!
[YUI panting]
[MORALES chuckles]
I thought you'd put up
more of a struggle than this.
You're gonna ruin all my fun.
I'm no "messenger boy."
I came here to
fight you, girlie!
[RENA gasps]
[yells]
[MORALES yells]
[gasping]
[gasps]
[WORKERS gasping]
[MORALES] I've shown you mine,
now show me yours.
Come on, suit up 'cause me and
my Regalia Gear want a fight!
What do you mean?
[growls]
[RENA yelps]
[MORALES]
Well, come on. Let's see it!
Give it up. I know that
you're not human.
[gasps]
Huh? Ha, ha. You're
ready to fight now, huh?
I'm dying to see how much
power this baby's got,
so I'm done waitin' on you.
You can bring yours out or not.
It doesn't matter to me.
I'll get this party
started without you!
[WORKERS screaming]
[gasps] What's happening?
There are innocent people here.
Let's go someplace else.
If we leave, then I'll
do what you're asking.
People? You really think I care?
Every last person in
this city could die,
and it still wouldn't
matter to me.
[gasps]
[RENA] Eternal executor,
knowing darkness.
And destroying darkness.
I now summon the endless
destruction that lies within me.
Fill me with your
unwavering fury,
unfathomable sacred relics.
[RENA] In the name of Erinius,
reveal yourself.
[RENA]
Magna Alecto.
[MORALES] Now that's what
I'm talkin' about!
Goodbye, Yui.
I love you so much.
[MORALES yells]
[RENA yelps]
[MORALES chuckles]
[gasps] Rena.
Uh!
Rena! Wake up!
[crash]
How pathetic! That was
barely even a fight.
You better get outta my way.
You will cease and
desist at once.
Disarm and prepare yourself
for judgment and punishment.
Why would I do that? Who the
hell do you think you are?
She's Yuinshiel Asteria.
Do you know where you are?
The Enastorian Empire.
In our country we don't tolerate
this kind of violence.
You really think I care about
what you'll "tolerate"?
Heh. That's the funniest thing
I've heard in a long time.
[MORALES laughs]
[MORALES] Look. I don't give a
damn about you or your country!
No!
[MORALES]
You can either run or die!
[RENA]
Yui. Yui.
You've always been so reckless.
What were you thinking,
coming after me?
I was thinking,
"Why would my big sister leave
and tell me that she didn't know
when she would be back?"
I'm sorry. I have to go.
It's not safe for me
to be here anymore.
[YUI] Because of what's
happening now?
[RENA]
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
I have another name
besides Rena.
Magna Alecto. It's been
such a long time,
I can hardly even remember it,
but I was selected to serve
as Magna Alecto's core.
[gasps]
[RENA] I'd hoped to stay
here with you forever,
but that was a ridiculous
dream. I'm not human.
It could never last, and I was
stupid to think it could!
[YUI]
Stop that!
So maybe we don't
share the same blood,
and maybe you aren't even human,
but none of that matters to me.
We're a family, and there's
nothing that could change that.
[YUI] If you'll let me, I would
like to be your strength.
Okay.
[MORALES groans]
[RENA] Yui. Don't be afraid.
I promise I'll protect you.
Lend me your strength,
and we can beat him.
No more playin' around!
[MORALES yells]
That's enough.
I'm done listening to you.
[MORALES yells]
[yells]
[MORALES grunting]
Give up now. It's over.
[laughs] That's where
you're wrong!
This is just the beginning!
You and I are monsters.
We don't give up.
We fight until the other
one's ground into dust.
[YUI] You're wrong! It's true
that you may be a monster.
But she's not.
Rena's my sister!
[YUI]
Uh.
By the name and
the will of Erinius.
Alecto shall pierce through.
Demonic spear, blazing red,
crafted by darkness.
It isn't over! I'm not
finished with you yet!
Unleash Crimson Raid!
[COMMUNICATIONS 1A]
Two unknowns,
both of whom are
unaccounted for.
[TV REPORTER 1A] Just before
dawn today at 4:00 local time,
a large explosion
occurred in Asteri,
the capital of the
Enastorian Empire.
Two unidentified moving objects
were spotted at the scene.
[exhales]
Uh!
Uh...
You know, when I left the café,
I thought I'd never
see you again.
I still haven't forgiven you for
blowing off our date today.
Hey!
You'd better think about how
you'll make it up to me.
[YUI] Oh, that's right!
Your gift. Can I open it?
Sure.
[YUI]
Can't wait to see what it is!
Oh, my gosh.
I just figured that we could
both keep wearing them this way.
So. Uh.
I think it's perfect.
Thank you so much!
[YUI]
It's going to be okay.
[gasps]
[YUI]
Everything will be okay.
We've been through
a lot together,
and I know we can face
whatever comes.
So, I want you to promise
you'll stay with me always.
Forever.
[NARU]
Thank you for your patience.
The conference
will begin shortly.
We will open with a
word from the Empress.
After she is done speaking,
we will accept some
of your questions.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if I may have your attention.
I present the Empress
of Enastoria.
I ask that you all please rise.
[NARU] And now, we will begin
this press conference
with a few words from
the Empress of Enastoria,
Yuinshiel Asteria.