[YUI] Regarding yesterday's
events at Fostarosa Pier,
as yet, we know little
about those responsible,
but the government is conducting
a full investigation.
Though the pier was
badly damaged,
I'm relieved to report
there were no injuries.
And, above all,
no lives were lost.
Fellow citizens of Enastoria, I
know you must be feeling uneasy.
But I urge you to be brave
in the face of adversity,
and to continue going about
your daily lives as normal.
I am with you.
Together, we will carry on.
Let us stand united and
support one another
during these difficult times.
We are a nation of
courage and compassion.
If we can hold fast to that, we
can maintain our peaceful lives.
[NARU] The Empress will
now answer questions
from the assembled press.
Your Royal Highness,
photographs from yesterday's
incident seem to suggest
a connection to the Fall
of Rimgarde 12 years ago.
Do you or your Cabinet
wish to comment?
It's too soon to say.
But we are currently following
up on that possibility.
Would you support
taking military action
if these things came back?
[gasps]
[PRESS chattering]
[YUI] My personal beliefs
on conflict are well-known,
but have no place here.
If they harm this country
or any of its people,
we will respond in kind.
[NARU] Thank you. This concludes
today's press conference.
[JONNY]
Just a moment, Your Highness.
Our readers are dying to know:
what are your measurements?
[YUI gasping]
[AOI]
Huh?
[gasps]
[YUI clears throat]
I have nothing to
hide from my people.
[BOTH gasp]
[YUI] So, I will answer.
And my measurements are...
[sighs] I still get
so nervous every time
I have to speak to the press.
Why would you answer such
a personal question?
You didn't have to dignify
that with a response.
[YUI] I wanted to answer
every question I could
because I thought it would help.
[AOI] We know, but still.
It did help by
shifting focus away
from the incident quite nicely.
Even if you did have to reveal
our most closely
guarded secret to do it.
My measurements were classified?
--[AOI sighs]
--[NARU groans]
[ALL sigh]
I swear, Rena must have
the patience of a saint.
[YUI]
Why would you think that?
[MARGARET] In all seriousness,
Rena is the real issue.
The people are going to
demand concrete answers,
so we cannot just sweep
this under the rug.
We need to come up with a plan.
Though the battle
produced no casualties,
damage was extensive.
Repairs could take months.
And we've no guarantee
that something like this
won't happen again.
[MARGARET]
He's right.
Rena herself said as much
during the debriefing.
I found something that
I think you need to see.
What're those?
[THEODORE] Photos taken
in the Kingdom of Rimgarde,
12 years ago.
[YUI]
When Rimgarde fell...
[AOI]
Without warning,
an unknown cataclysmic event,
rocked the kingdom.
[MARSHALL] Countries from around
the world, including ours,
mobilized troops
for rescue missions.
But we couldn't find a
single person to help.
The entire population
had vanished overnight.
[THEODORE] These mysterious
giants, whatever they are,
were the only clue left behind.
[NARU] And one that was at
the pier today looks similar,
but we don't know for sure that
it's the same one from Rimgarde.
It is the same one.
[ALL]
Hm?
[AOI]
What? How can you be so sure?
Because that's a picture of me.
Huh?
That giant, it and I
are one in the same.
I was there that day.
I watched Rimgarde fall.
[gasps]
[RENA]
Regalia.
That was what they used
to call us. Long ago.
[gasping]
I have lived as you see me,
even before I came here,
but I have another form.
[MARGARET] So, the battle
earlier at Fosterosa Pier?
Yes. That was me fighting.
It was you?
[MARGARET]
And what of the other combatant?
Was that a Regalia
as well? Like you?
[RENA]
No, I don't think so.
It had a human pilot
who referred to it
as a "Regalia Gear."
An imitation perhaps.
Having a human pilot suggests
that it could be manmade,
and therefore this
attack on our country
was a deliberate
act of aggression.
I completely agree.
You're mistaken. His intent
was to take me away.
[AOI gasps]
[YUI gasping]
[MARSHALL]
Uh!
Why was he after you?
I wish I knew, but I'm sure
he won't be the last.
None of this would have
happened if it weren't for me.
I'm so sorry.
[YUI]
Rena...
To be honest, I'm having a
hard time processing this.
I can't quite wrap my
head around it either,
but difficult as it may be to
believe, Rena is a Regalia.
Yui was there, she
saw Rena transform.
[AOI]
But what's Rena's connection
to the Fall of Rimgarde?
[MARGARET] I'm not sure
what to make of that yet.
Did the Dowager Empress
know what Rena is?
I don't know.
If she did, it's not something
she ever discussed with me.
I see.
Your Highness, as Head of State
we need to know what are
your thoughts on this matter?
Rena is my big sister.
I trust her, and I don't care
what she is or why these
enemies might want her.
I won't let them take her away!
Are you sure of that?
Because if we were
to be attacked again,
we might not get off so easily.
[MARSHALL] The armed forces have
been placed on high alert--
[THEODORE] But if they
strike without warning,
like yesterday,
there's little we can do.
[NARU] Are you saying
there will be more damage,
or even deaths next time?
I've heard enough!
[ALL sigh]
If fighting is truly the
only option we have...
Clearly we aren't going to get
this all figured out today.
Let's adjourn for now
and reconvene tomorrow.
The Empress is tired.
[MARGARET] In the meantime,
nothing we've learned about Rena
or the Fall of Rimgarde
is to leave this room.
[THEODORE] Even if we
wanted to talk about it,
no one would believe us.
[MARGARET] We'll pick up where
we left off tomorrow afternoon.
That should give Yui
enough time to rest
and make her final decision.
Think carefully.
For your sake and ours.
[AOI]
Yui!
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
cut you off in there.
You just seemed like you
were struggling a bit.
[YUI]
It's all right.
If I had blurted out what
I was really thinking,
it might have been a bit
awkward for everyone.
Remember that we don't want
to make anything awkward
for you either.
Yeah. I know you don't.
[AOI] I can see how much
this is weighing on you.
Did you want to talk about it?
[YUI] Thank you for offering,
but I can handle it.
I'm Empress Yuinshiel Asteria,
ruler of the great
Enastorian Empire.
[DRIVER 2A]
This look like a good spot?
[SARA]
Yeah! Thanks!
[TIA]
We made it! That took forever.
I'm hungry. Let's eat!
[SARA]
Wait! We gotta make camp first!
Let's just set it up here!
Then, we can eat!
Okay!
I should go.
I shouldn't be here.
[YUI]
But why?
Because, it's only going to
cause more trouble if I stay.
It's okay. It'll all be okay.
[YUI] Thanks for coming
on such short notice.
No worries. I don't mind.
I'm always happy to see you.
Oh! But forget me. How are you?
Uh...
Yui...
[YUI]
What are you getting at?
You've got a bit of a problem,
my friend. See for yourself.
[gasping]
[RETSU "All clothing and
underwear in Yui's size
is flying off store shelves.
Bras, it would seem,
are especially popular.
Even men are buying them."
I can't imagine why
they would be doing that.
Did your boobs get bigger?
Retty!
[RETSU laughs]
[RETSU] So, you want
to protect Renny.
She's your sister.
That's understandable.
But, as the Empress, you have
to consider your people, too.
[YUI]
What do you think I should do?
I don't know.
The only family you've got left
versus the whole country?
That's a tough one.
But wait, Renny's a person
like me, isn't she?
[gasps]
[RETSU] I mean,
she's one of your people,
just like anyone else.
That makes her part
of this country.
[YUI]
Uh!
[RETSU]
Right?
Yeah, it does.
[RETSU]
There ya go!
Thanks! That actually
helped me a lot.
I think you knew what
you wanted to do
long before you
asked my opinion.
[RETSU] But, if saying I
helped makes ya feel better,
that's fine by me. Gotta go.
Retty, wait a sec!
[RETSU]
Uh. [gasping]
[YUI] I love you. I'm so
happy you're my friend.
Please don't ever change.
Uh...
Yui. Run away with me!
[gasps]
[laughs] I kid! I kid!
It was a joke.
[YUI]
Are you crying?
[RETSU] But I'm late,
and you must be busy.
Bring Renny with you next time
you see me, okay? See ya later!
Sure. See ya...
Bye.
[INGRID]
Hello, Your Highness.
May I join you?
[INGRID] That was quite
an impressive battle.
Hard to believe it was your
first time in a Regalia.
I apologize for the amount
of collateral damage.
It was more than expected.
Causing harm to this country
was not our intent.
Who are you?
I am Ingrid, and we are enemies.
At least for the time being.
I'll get right to the point.
Hand over the Regalia,
and we can be friends.
We'll leave quietly and
never bother you again.
And, as your friends,
we'd no longer pose a
threat to your nation.
Simple really. Your choice
should be quite clear.
I'm not giving her to you.
[INGRID]
Is that so?
[YUI] Rena is a very special
person and I love her dearly.
[INGRID]
Person? That thing isn't human.
[gasps]
[YUI] Being a Regalia doesn't
make her any less my sister.
If that is what you wish
to believe, you may.
But, are you really
going to put its life
before the lives of
your beloved people?
[YUI]
Rena is one of my people,
and I must protect her
as I would any other.
I see.
I'm starting to get a sense
of just what kind of
leader you truly are.
Speaking with you has been
an honor, Empress Yuinshiel.
May you be able to maintain the
courage of your convictions.
I'll be watching you.
Good day, Empress.
[JOHANN]
Hello there.
You're with her.
[JONNY] Forgive me for
my question yesterday
at the press conference.
It was, in poor taste.
But we couldn't have so
much focus on the Regalia.
That would be very bad.
I confess I was shocked
when you answered.
Who tells the world their
measurements?
Do you like having people
know the size of your chest?
[gasps]
Oh, my. You are so
cute when you blush!
Tell me who you are!
[JONNY]
Where are my manners?
I am Jonny Mabett, and this
is my assistant, Johann.
We'd like to invite
Your Highness
to a very special magic show.
It promises to be a
spectacle beyond belief!
But you won't be watching it.
You're the star.
[YUI gasps]
[JOHANN]
Heh. Ingrid is so sweet.
Telling you we didn't intend
to do so much damage.
[gasping]
[JONNY]
We'd hate for you to miss it.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
performance.
[JOHANN] Don't forget to
bring that Regalia with you.
[JONNY]
Farewell.
[YUI] Rena! So what if
they threatened us.
We don't have to go!
They're just going to try
and take you away again!
It's not about me, Yui.
You're the Empress. Your people
need you, and they come first.
I know that!
But Rena, just because
I care about my people
doesn't mean I
stopped loving you!
Yui.
It's my choice. I shouldn't have
to lose anyone I care about.
Everything is going to be okay.
[MARGARET]
So these two approached you,
challenged you and
Rena to a fight,
then just vanished
into thin air?
That's correct, and like the
other time, they're after Rena.
It was very clear to me that
they would not negotiate.
We'll assemble a tactical
special forces team immediately.
They'll intercept them.
Thank you, General.
However, your men wouldn't stand
a chance against a Regalia Gear.
Then tell us what it
is you plan to do.
I'll face them myself!
Alongside Rena!
I can't let you do that Yui!
Let me go in your place!
[YUI]
I'm sorry, but, no.
This is something I have
to do personally.
[AOI]
Yui...
I have a sacred duty
I must uphold,
and that is to
protect my people.
To put their needs
before my own.
But, if I were to let go
of Rena without a fight,
not only would I lose
someone precious to me,
I would fail.
I wouldn't be able to be
the leader Enastoria needs.
Margaret, everyone.
Please forgive me for
being selfish. I am sorry.
But this is what I must do,
and why I must do it.
I will do anything
to protect Yui.
Rena...
Thank you, Rena.
On behalf of the nation,
please keep our Empress safe.
Thank you. Thank you, all.
It's time to go.
[NARU] Do you believe that the
Empress made the right decision?
Yes. What if she had just
handed over her sister?
Could you serve a leader who
would do something like that?
But still, if something were to
happen to Yui, what then?
Perhaps this isn't
the right choice.
Nevertheless, a decision
has been made.
What's done is done.
Come what may, we stand
with our Empress.
We must be strong,
for Yui and Enastoria.
They need our support and
we will not let them down!
[JONNY]
That's it?
The Empress and the Regalia
really came all by themselves?
This country makes
no sense to me.
[JOHANN] Jonny and Johann
proudly present:
Attacks of Amazement!
So, step right up!
I have more questions for you.
But our follow-up interview
will have to wait!
Show time! Let the games begin!
I'm scared.
I'll protect you.
Everything's going to be okay.
[NARU]
That is Rena. It's all true!
Good.
Rapid response teams
are in position,
they're ready to
move on our signal.
Yui. Rena.
[JONNY] Are you brimming
with excitement?
Let's start with a little
sleight of hand.
Pick a card! Any card!
But watch out,
this deck cuts you!
[YUI gasping]
[JONNY] For my next trick,
pay close attention.
Hurry! Let's make our move.
[JONNY]
Don't blink! Or you'll miss it!
Where did I go?
We're not playing
hide and seek!
[JONNY] Ooh, you missed!
Better luck next time!
[JONNY] Look at my hand.
How many balls am I holding?
How 'bout now? And now? And now?
Fire balls!
[RENA grunts]
It's my turn!
[JONNY]
Ooh! Close! But no cigar.
Maybe you'd prefer
smoke and mirrors!
What? I don't see him!
[RENA]
There!
[JONNY] You may think some
of these are illusions,
but they're all real!
Now, Rena!
[yells]
[YUI]
Are they gone?
[RENA, YUI gasp]
[JONNY]
Now you see me...
[YUI, RENA groan]
[JONNY]
...now you don't!
[YUI, RENA gasping]
[JONNY whistles]
Over here.
[RENA panting]
Rena, are you sure you're okay?
Don't worry about me. I said
I'd protect you and I will!
[TIA]
More please! We're still hungry!
[RETSU]
Coming right up!
[TIA]
Hm?
[JONNY] Have you been
enjoying the show?
[JONNY] Because the
best is yet to come!
[JONNY] You are standing
within an Inescapable Box.
In exactly three minutes,
unless you find a way out,
the bomb will explode,
blowing you to pieces!
Can you do it, Empress?
Tick, tock! Tick, tock!
[JOHANN laughs]
The empress'll have to pull
off a major trick of her own,
or there's about
to be a big mess.