[BOTH whimper]
[grows softly]
[gasps]
[BOTH whimper]
[whimpers]
[yelps]
[screams]
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Rena!
[groans softly]
We're still together!
Where are we?
[YUI]
Rena?
[gasps]
[RENA]
She's not who I thought she was.
I didn't realize
I'd already met my maker.
What?
She is the source of
power for all Regalia.
The power of light. Lux.
She is Lux.
[grunts]
[RENA] I wonder how many
Regalia have passed through
these gates before us.
The ones with Ryu and Lowe
must have come this way.
[gasps]
[RENA]
Yui.
We tried our best,
but it looks as though
we didn't quite make it.
Still... I don't regret
a single thing.
[YUI]
Hold on. It's not over yet.
What...?
[YUI]
Everything we've learned...
...and all that we've
been taught to cherish...
We haven't shared
any of those things.
Huh?
[YUI] Mama and Abel showed us
what was really important.
We need to pass on what
we've learned from them.
And we will. We'll share
what they taught us.
We will make sure that
their legacy lives on.
It's nice to meet you Lux.
I'm Yui.
Guess I hadn't
introduced myself.
Can you help us?
Is there a way for you to
give us a little more time?
[gasps]
[YUI] Rena and I have
so much we want to give
to the next generation.
And we made lots of mistakes
we still wanna fix.
We're not done yet. We want to
live and keep moving forward.
[YUI]
We want to meet new people.
We want to connect with them
and to inspire them!
[RENA gasps]
Wait!
[giggles]
[gasps]
It can't be!
[chuckles]
Lux gave us a second chance.
[INGRID]
Yui! Rena!
My friends!
What the hell is going on--
[SARA]
Ingrid, Kei! Look!
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, that's the girl
Rena and I saw!
[gasps]
[grunts]
I know this. It's Lux's power.
She's Lux?
The embodiment of light...
Amazing...
It seems that Lux has
taken on a human form.
And for some reason,
she's helping those
I'm trying to destroy.
Empress...
Why is it always you?!
How did you get Lux to join
forces with you, a measly human?
One human alone is
weak and vulnerable.
But, you see, when
humanity bands together,
it can make us unbreakable!
We have to get up!
[INGRID groans]
[BOTH groan]
Help me, Tia--Push!
[TIA grunts]
We don't have to save
the future by ourselves.
We will all do it together!
[growls]
[RENA]
We fight for humanity. For hope.
And we won't stop fighting
no matter what!
Help us, Lux!
[gasps]
Hey... Is that...?
It's Megaera's key.
[gasps]
Incredible... I didn't
think I would ever see it.
The Erinius Regalia's true form!
Thank you for fighting
beside me, Rena.
You, too, Lux.
[gasps]
Can you feel it?
[gasps] The power
of light is overflowing!
[YUI]
Sara...
Tia...
Kei...
Ingrid...
Please, my friends, fight beside
me and lend me your strength.
And together, we'll all
save the future!
Of course! You got it!
We're in!
So are we!
Definitely. We're happy
to help any way we can.
Ready to do this?
Yeah!
Lux?
[YUI]
Please give up, Johann.
[growls]
Stop this, or we'll use our
combined power to stop you!
[JOHANN] You wanna stop me?
Go ahead and try.
Use all your power.
Use Lux's power.
Come at me with
everything you've got!
You puny humans can
band together all you want!
There's still no way
you can defeat me!
[YUI]
We've already banded together.
That's how humanity survives--
By taking care of one another.
[JOHANN]
Don't be so foolish!
If you tie your fate
to the fate of others,
you'll all end up dead!
And then what?!
Once you die, your lives
amount to nothing!
But for my soulless dolls,
life and death don't matter.
They go on forever!
[YUI]
But they don't live!
And they give nothing
to future generations.
We will hand down
something precious:
Hope!
They'll keep it alive,
long after we're gone!
[growls]
[INGRID] Yui and her mother
taught me to hold on
to the lessons of the past
while looking to the future.
I'll ensure the values and
traditions of Rimgarde
are never forgotten!
They will live on through me!
We won't just survive!
Tia and I are going to live
our lives to the fullest!
That's right, we are!
[SARA] With the ones
we love by our side!
[gasps]
[RENA] We'll laugh and cry
and love as one!
[YUI] And as long as what we
pass on surives, so will we!
On and on forever!
I wouldn't bet on it
if I were you!
I'll put an end
to that right now!
[RENA, YUI]
In the name of Erinius,
Alecto shall become
the enforcer!
[BOTH]
Trinity Power Strike!
[chuckles]
[ALL yelling]
[gasps]
Kill me.
[BOTH gasp]
[JOHANN] I'm finished.
So is Lux Ex Machina.
I have nothing left.
[YUI]
Johann...
[JOHANN]
I don't need your sympathy.
I was born alone and
I lived my life alone.
I'm going to die alone.
Why should it be any different?
[gasps]
What're you doing?
--She's leaving us.
--What?
Lux, wait!
Take this. I want
you to have it.
It means we're family,
and no matter where we are,
we're always together.
[JOHANN] Huh.
What are you doing here?
It's too late
to change anything.
[JOHANN]
Just let me die...
What's going on?
[JOHANN]
I don't understand.
Does this mean you're
coming with me?
[JOHANN]
Goodbye, Yuinshiel Asteria.
I might have been
a better man...
...if someone like you
had been the one who made me.
[gasps]
Look at the sky.
We made it home, Kei!
[giggles]
[BOTH laugh]
[BOTH giggle]
[laughs]
[RENA] What do you plan
to do after all this?
[YUI]
Hmm...
Well, first, I'm
going to go home.
Then, I'm going to take a bath,
and eat a big, hot meal!
And after that...
I think I'll sleep for a while.
That's not what I meant
and you know it!
Just kidding.
After dinner, I thought
we could all get together
and talk about it.
Sound okay?
Okay.
[YUI]
Good.
Don't worry.
We'll figure it out.
I know it.
[giggles]
[laughs]
Heh.
[giggles]
[sighs]
Yes!
[gasps]
Whatever's next,
we'll face it together!
Yeah!