Hey, are you gonna come or not?
[SARA]
Yeah, just a sec.
You're coming, too!
You sure it's not weird or
anything for me to be here?
Of course!
Sara and Tia specifically
asked me to invite you,
so don't worry about it.
And besides, it's been way
too long since you and I've
gotten the chance
to have a good chat.
[laughs] Oh! You little
sweetie pie!
Aw, come on, you're
embarrassing me!
[splash]
[gasps]
[TIA, SARA laugh]
[SARA]
You did it!
I told you not to push me!
[SARA, TIA]
Cannonball!
[RENA]
Hey, wait a minute!
[SARA, TIA laugh]
Weirdos.
I can't believe a soft, sweet
little marshmallow like you
can turn into a massive,
armored giant. It's crazy!
[SARA]
Hey, me, too! Lemme in there!
So, what in the world
are you guys, anyway?
[gasps]
We are Regalia!
[RETSU]
And what's that?
I have no idea!
Yep, we don't have a clue!
[RETSU]
Wait, what? You don't know?
Okay, well, what were you
doing before you came here?
We were out looking
for Rena and Kei!
Kei? Is it possible
there's another of these
little cuties out there?
Well, I... uh.
[TIA] Yeah! Kei's really
pretty and super sweet.
You should meet her someday.
Exactly how long did
you look for Rena?
For a long time!
Rena and Kei are the best at
hide and seek, aren't they?
[TIA]
Yeah!
I'd guess it was
about 2,000 years.
[gasps]
Well, you're adorable and
that's all that matters!
[SARA, TIA laugh]
[sighs]
[INGRID]
Let's go.
I think I could get used to this
kind of life pretty quickly.
Today has been so relaxing.
It makes last night
seem like a weird dream.
But it wasn't. All of
it actually happened.
It did.
[SARA] Hey! What've you two
been up to over here?
Aren't you gonna
get in the water?
We're just taking our time.
Trying to enjoy
the beautiful view!
There's a view?
[BOTH]
Uh?
Yeah, it's pretty.
But the world is full of fun
places to go and things to see!
Well, isn't it?
[SARA] Mm-hm! We saw some
really amazing things
when we were looking
for the others!
Could you tell us more about
the time you spent traveling?
[TIA, SARA]
Uh?
[MARGARET] Tisis. So,
we're looking at another
Regalia and the
person bound to it?
That's right,
but according to the empress,
these two are not our enemies.
[BOTH]
Uh! Hi, Yui! [laugh]
I'm so glad you're here!
I can't get over how
huge your house is!
It's enormous!
Well, it's not actually my
house, you know. Not really.
I'm surprised at how comfortable
they are with her already.
There's a foreign official
requesting a meeting
with the Empress.
There always is.
If we grant that type of
access to one country,
we may be setting a
precedent for others.
Well, to be fair, this
request is a bit unusual.
[THEODORE, AOI]
Hm?
[RETSU hums]
It's so incredible, it's
almost hard to believe.
You looked for Rena
for 2,000 years?
[TIA]
Mm-hm!
See, the secret is,
we never get any older!
[TIA]
Nope!
So, I guess we won't either.
It's okay.
[RETSU] Sara, Tia!
Give me a hand in here!
[SARA, TIA]
Uh? Coming!
[YUI]
There you are.
[RENA]
I was lonely for a long time.
Uh.
I always wanted
to have a partner.
Tia had Sara,
but I never had anyone.
I just wanted someone around
who could keep me company,
and for the longest time,
it seemed like no matter
where I went or
how hard I looked,
I always ended up alone.
That's why meeting your mom
and dad meant so much to me.
It changed my life.
They made me feel like I
was part of a real family.
I used to think
that I was cursed.
Always wondering why I was
stuck inside this body.
But now, I'm incredibly
grateful to be a Regalia.
Because if I wasn't, then
we never would have met.
It's true.
[TIA]
Hey!
Dinner's ready,
so come and get it!,
[RENA]
You hungry?
[YUI]
Mm.
[phone vibrates]
[YUI]
Uh?
Hey, Aoi!
Yeah, we're just about to
have dinner. Why, what's up?
[gasps]
[RENA]
Uh?
[BOTH]
Uh!
[TIA]
What was that all about?
Apparently there's a
Regalia in another country
who's interested in
meeting with us.
[TIA]
Oh, wow! For real?!
[SARA]
Can we come, too?!
Is it that Kei person
you mentioned before?
It doesn't sound like it is.
[RETSU] Huh! So, there are
others out there besides her?
Yup. You bet!
But this is gonna
be the first time
we've gotten to meet one
besides Rena and Kei.
[RETSU]
You traveled for 2,000 years
and never met a single one?
Wow, you're right.
That's so weird!
Totally!
Uh... Ha, ha... [sighs]
I've decided that I should
agree to the meeting.
[gasps]
Yay! We get to
make a new friend!
I love new friends!
So you're gonna take them
on an official state visit?
I'll give you the time off,
but you've still got a pretty
big tab, so you'll have to
put in some extra hours
when you get back, okay?
[SARA, TIA]
Aww.
Well, let's take
a seat, everyone.
If you're going on an adventure,
you should have a
proper send-off!
[SARA, TIA]
Wow!
These are some fancy eats!
It looks so delicious!
[RETSU] What? It's always fancy!
What're you talking about?
[SARA] Oh no, this is
definitely better!
[RETSU]
Hey!
[gasps]
[AOI] It's hard enough just
getting out of the palace.
I certainly never would've
thought we'd leave
the country at a time like this!
[YUI] I know, but it
can't be helped, Aoi.
[AOI]
No, of course. I understand.
It's my job to worry, remember?
I have no doubt you're making
the best decision for everyone.
This meeting could
give us answers
to some of the
questions we have.
Making contact with
another Regalia
is far too important an
opportunity to pass up.
Hey, is that it up there?
[AOI] All right,
looks like we're here.
[TALAQY] Welcome! We've been
looking forward to your arrival.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I am Karim Al Talaqy,
the President of Afmaraldo.
Thank you.
It's a great honor to
meet you, Mr. President.
The honor is mine,
Your Highness.
Now, if you would
please come with me.
Of course!
[TALAQY] This area has been
revered as hallowed ground
for as long as anyone
can remember.
Our people have lived beside
them for many generations.
They're part of our history.
[YUI]
I'm sorry, "they"?
[TALAQY] I'm afraid I must ask
your aides to wait here.
Only those called by the
Regalia may go inside,
but I assure you,
there is nothing to fear.
Yes, I understand.
We'll be back soon.
I hope so.
Please be careful.
[SARA] This seems like
the kind of place
where a monster would live,
don't you think?
One with big fangs!
[TIA]
Ohh... Wow...
Incredible!
These are all Regalia?
[SARA]
Are they stuck like this?
[TIA]
Aww, I hope not.
[RENA]
Come on.
[YUI] You'd never guess
something so pretty
would be on the other
side of that cave!
[SARA] Whoa! That's crazy! I'm
gonna go and get a closer look!
[TIA]
Right behind ya!
[YUI] I'm feeling nervous and
excited at the same time.
I wonder what they'll be like.
Me too. I've never met
another one besides us.
So I don't know what to expect.
[SARA]
Hey! Hurry up you guys!
You gotta come check this out!
[TIA] I wonder if this
one is stuck, too?
[SARA, TIA scream]
[YUI]
Sara! Tia!
[RENA grunts]
[VOICE] You mustn't take them
by surprise like that, Lowe.
They're our welcome guests.
[ALL gasp]
[RYU]
My name is Ryu.
It's very good to meet you
at last, Regalia of Erinius.
[YUI]
Erinius...?
Oh, Lowe.
Can you believe we've
finally met them?
[RYU] Lowe is Enki's Regalia.
I am bound to them.
[TIA] Whoa! We've never met
another Regalia before!
My name is Sara!
And I'm Tia!
I'm Rena Asteria. Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yui.
Hello! Pleased to meet you.
I can hardly believe it!
[YUI] Oh. Is she a little
on the shy side?
Hi, Lowe!
[RYU laughs]
Sorry, Lowe is actually a man.
[YUI]
Huh?
As a matter of fact,
he and I are engaged.
[YUI] I'm so sorry!
I guess I just assumed!
[SARA, TIA]
Huh?
[SARA, TIA laughing]
[YUI]
This place is truly beautiful.
It's so tranquil and relaxing.
[RYU]
Thank you very much.
It's surprising, though.
You're surrounded by desert
as far as you can see,
but there's a bountiful
spring here.
That's because of the power
granted to Enki's Regalia.
[SARA, TIA laughing]
[RYU] Lowe can manifest the
blessing of water at any time,
no matter where he is.
People who are chosen as
the core of a Regalia,
and those bound to them, who
bring out their true power,
have brought great
blessings to mankind.
[RYU] Delivering the power
of the gods to this world.
That is what it means
to be a Regalia.
Does that include
Rena and the others?
[RYU]
Erinius.
Three Regalia whose
purpose it is
to channel the
power of revenge.
Why revenge?
[RYU]
You have to understand.
Erinius is a Regalia that
was created for combat.
[gasps]
There's a reason for
its massive power.
Because it was originally
intended to seal away
something very dangerous.
[YUI]
What?
It's called Lux Ex Machina.
[TIA, SARA]
Uh...? Uh?
[JOHAN] The same image,
over and over. How boring.
Hey, why don't we just go
and attack the castle?
You know that Tisis
is probably with them,
and Alecto's right
arm came back,
so I don't see why we can't
get the show on the road
instead of waiting around
here twiddling our thumbs.
I don't believe that they're
at the castle anymore.
How about if we throw a
little fit in the city, then?
That would make the soft-hearted
empress come running.
Don't worry your
pretty little head.
It'll be over in no time
at all with your Regalia.
[gasps]
[JOHAN] Oh, well,
if you don't want to go...
Binding darkness born in light,
arbiter of eternal truth...
[INGRID]
Stop that right now!
Whatever you want.
I'm going, though.
[JOHAN]
I've got a new Gear now.
You don't mind if I look
for her myself, do you?
What happened, Ingrid?
[RYU] Lux Ex Machina's
power was devastating.
It swallowed up my
family and friends.
It nearly destroyed
the entire world.
[gasping]
[RYU] Regalia from all across
the globe sought out its domain
in hopes of stopping it,
but their efforts came
to nothing in the end.
Not a single one who
went ever returned.
Lowe and I saved who we could
and brought them here.
Thankfully, Lux Ex Machina was
sealed away before it could
swallow everything, or none
of us would be here now.
Sealed by what?
[SARA, TIA]
Huh?
Mankind was able to find a
way to harness the power
of Erinius, the god of revenge.
They entrusted it to the last
three people who had been
accepted by the Regalia.
It was they who were sent
to seal away Lux Ex Machina.
They did. That was an
incredibly long time ago.
[RYU] And in all those years,
we hadn't felt the presence
of a single other Regalia.
So, then, imagine
our surprise when
after waiting thousands of
years, we felt your power.
[BOTH gasp]
It must have been the
fight at Fostarosa Pier.
We immediately assumed that
it was Erinius' Regalia.
We pleaded with President Talaqy
to do everything in his power
to convince you to come
here and meet with us.
I know we should have come
to you, but, unfortunately
Lowe can't move anymore.
[YUI]
So, why did you wanna meet us?
To say I'm sorry that you've had
to carry this burden
on your own.
I know how difficult
it must be for you.
And I wanted to tell
you how grateful I am,
because if it wasn't for you,
we wouldn't be alive at all.
Thank you for fighting. Thank
you for being so courageous.
[TIA, SARA laugh]
[YUI] So, what about
all the others here?
[SARA]
Yeah, there are so many!
What's their story?
How come they don't move?
[TIA]
Are they sleeping?
[RYU]
No. They have left this world.
[TIA]
Huh?
I thought Regalia didn't die.
[RYU] They fulfilled their roles
and quietly slipped away,
just as we all do.
Even in their absence,
Lowe was happy to continue
providing water to the
place they left behind.
Sady, he has very
little power left.
He hasn't been able to
return to his original form
for a while now.
Does this mean the same thing
is gonna happen to us?
[RYU] We had always
hoped to revive this land
to its former lushness,
and we clung to that wish
for a very long time.
But unfortunately we
couldn't do it with
the limited power
that remained.
The people here are strong.
They love this land
passionately,
with all their hearts,
and would never leave it.
If Lowe has so
little power left,
don't you think you should
be conserving it?
This place is proof that
Regalia once lived.
Proof that we were
a part of this world.
Protecting this land and
watching over its people,
that has made Lowe and me
very happy over the years.
We plan to let the water keep
on flowing until we go the way
of the others and are
reunited with our friends.
Nurturing this land is
what brings happiness
to me and Lowe.
But everyone's path is unique,
as is everyone's journey.
[gasps]
So, to find your own
path in this world,
you must listen to your heart
and do whatever
feels right to you.
You have already
sacrificed so much
so that we could find
our happiness.
Now, we want you to find your
own. That's our final wish.
I want a piece of
that cuddle pie!
[TIA]
Yeah!
[TIA, SARA laugh]
Wow.
It's so beautiful!
[gasping]
[snores]
What is it?
I was just thinking I wish
I could see for myself
everything that happened
in Rimgarde that day.
Including all that
happened with you.
If I could do that, I feel like
I might be able to understand
what it is Ingrid's
trying accomplish.
We'll be landing in
Rimgarde shortly.
--Okay, thanks.
--[alarm blares]
[ALL gasp]
[AOI]
Hm?
[gasps]
[ALL scream]
Well, looky there, I found you!
[CAPTAIN 6A] What the hell
is traffic control doing?
[CO-PILOT 6A] They said it
just showed up on radar!
Someone tell me what's
going on here!
What does that warning mean?
It means that somebody
opened up the loading hatch!
[gasps] Seriously?
Do you really think
we should do this?
Don't worry, it's
gonna be just fine!
This is higher than
the diving board!
You sure?
It's our only choice!
Okay, then.
Are you two ready
to take the plunge?
[TIA]
Mm-hm!
We're at your service!
[JOHAN gasps]
Well, well.
This just keeps getting more
and more entertaining.