[glitches]
-Switch on approach guidance. -Roger that. Approach guidance.
[clicking]
It's not responding.
What?
And the autopilot too. Well, all right, then.
We'll do it the old-fashioned way.
[co-pilot] Roger.
-Huh? -[alarm beeps]
Instrumentation's going haywire.
[pilot] Can we work around it?
[co-pilot] No time.
[pilot] Well then, we'll just have to wing it.
[screeching]
Lefchitose flight 502 made an emergency landing today,
due to an electrical malfunction,
thankfully without any major damage or injury.
The problem seems to have originated
in the plane's systems control circuit.
Investigators say there appears to be no risk of fire,
but as a precaution, similar aircraft have been grounded.
There's also been a report of another system failure
on flight 460.
[Daigo] Is this whole mess all because of Meicoomon?
Most likely.
Why didn't you tell me this right from the start?
Why didn't you let me know that Meicoomon was their target?
-[phone rings] -Yes.
Roger. I'm on my way.
Professor Mochizuki just arrived.
If you'd told me about Meicoomon,
I might have been able to help
a lot more back there at the school.
We have to focus on our next step to counter Meicoomon.
[groans]
[girl] It's absolutely the best...
[boy over PA] That's it.
Our school festival is officially over.
CHAPTER 3: \"CONFESSION\"
A big thanks goes out to all of you who worked so hard on it
and a little thanks to those who didn't. [laughs]
We'll have a closing ceremony at 6:00 PM, so don't miss it.
Huh?
You're dancing brought in a whole bunch of people.
We did well because of you.
Oh, thanks, but...
it was all of us together.
[girl] I wish I'd worn that uniform Mimi and Meiko made.
-Next year for sure. -Yeah.
That's true. I can always wear it the next time around.
[chuckles]
Thank you.
[girl 1] Where did Meiko go anyway?
-She went to take the trash out. -That was a long time ago.
[girl 2] She seemed so out of sorts all day.
But when I asked her about it, she said she was okay.
I'll go check on her.
[boy 1] They put this 'keep out' sign up yesterday
and started guarding the area.
-What's going on? -[boy 2] I don't know.
[boy 1] Wow, skillful analysis.
-[Mimi] Meimei! -Huh?
Hey, are you okay?
Oh! Oh!
Meimei? Wait!
Where're you going?
Stop!
[sobs]
[panting]
[gasps]
-Talk to me. -Oh, Mei!
Meicoomon...
was Leomon.
What did Meicoomon do?
[cries out] Mei!
I know this is hard but....
we're here for you.
We're in this together.
[doorbell rings]
Ken's not home.
Hey, did anyone text you back?
Uh-huh. Not yet.
Was that really him?
[TK] It'll be okay. I know it.
-Huh? -Let's just focus on the facts.
Come on.
[sighs]
[Kari] Wow, TK's really grown up.
-Huh? What's that? -Oh, um, nothing.
-Okay. -[chuckles nervously]
[message tone]
-No one was home. -Too bad.
[Agumon] Apparently no one's home here either.
At least no one who'll feed us.
-Hurry up, Tentomon! -I am hurrying.
Just slowly. One, two, three, four...
Well, I guess we just need to make eight
since Meicoomon isn't here.
[all sighing]
Make us food, not sad.
Sorry, guess I shouldn't have mentioned Meicoomon.
Too soon, Tentomon.
You guys... for now, just stay put.
-But do I have to stay hungry? -Oh, I can't take it.
Then take these!
[Izzy] We have to figure out what's causing this infection.
And fast. Or it could lead to a mutation.
What's happening, Izzy?
These infections... aren't only happening in the digital world.
[chewing appreciatively]
I don't understand.
Meicoomon was so gentle.
Before... did she act... strange?
I don't think there were signs. It was like an outbreak.
[Izzy] We called this an infection.
I don't think we realized how right we were.
[beep]
[Izzy] It's way beyond anything we could have hypothesized.
[keyboard keys clicking]
[groans in frustration]
Sorry, we're late. We were busy cleaning.
-Are you okay? -[Meimei] Ye-- Yes.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
[Izzy] We have to put together some kind of a plan.
Meiko, I need you to answer some questions.
[Meiko] Okay...
Are we sure Meicoomon's infected?
Were there any symptoms,
or anything out of the ordinary beforehand?
If so, when did it all start?
Anything you can tell us,
no matter how insignificant could help.
Don't overlook anything.
-Come on, Meiko, think! -[beeping]
-[sobs] -That's enough, Izzy.
There is no need for the third degree.
Think before you speak, would you?
I'm sorry but we need this information and we need it now!
The bad cop routine won't help!
There's no time to waste!
The infection could be spreading...
or mutating, feelings are trivial!
Trivial? Come on!
Knock it off, both of you!
[Mimi] Humph.
Huh? Meimei!
[Meimei] It's all my fault [sobs]
Mei!
[sobs] I should have...
I'm so sorry!
[Joe] All right, everybody. Gotta go.
Later.
Yeah.
Mega level, huh. Not bad.
Yeah. Pretty cool.
Izzy said this might have predicted that.
Huh?
[TK] \"Those who crave true power
must seek the darkness but move past it.\"
So what does that mean?
Don't look at me. I don't know.
Eeh.
But if more of our digimon reach mega level,
we won't have to rely on Omnimon.
It'd be... easier on you.
Anyway... see ya.
[door opens]
[Meiko] I'm home.
Meiko! The school festival was amazing. Great job!
So, to celebrate, I made your favorite.
Ta-da! Tempura.
-Where is dad? -Uh, working.
He might have to pull an all-nighter again.
He has so many meetings these days.
It's because of Meicoomon... isn't it?
Hmm.
Officer Himekawa has the damage report.
[Himekawa] Thank you.
So far...
we have identified 13 spots around the city
and 52 across the country.
And we're having problems
with feedback affecting electronic transmissions,
especially at the airport,
which is close enough to the disturbances
for flights to be affected.
There were four emergency landings there this week alone.
One place nearly crashed into another.
It's currently under surveillance
and we're watching other runways as well.
[chair] Thoughts, Dr. Mochizuki?
All right, well, before this outbreak occurred,
there was an unconfirmed sighting
of an unidentified digimon at the high school.
[chair] And you believe that's related to this situation?
I can't conclusively confirm that yet.
But... it certainly does seem possible
given the circumstance we find ourselves in now.
[sighs]
This is worse than I thought.
Yes, it sounds like it's going to happen again.
Even more victims.
I really don't want to put those kids through... all of that.
I know.
Dr. Mochizuki?
-What is it? -Well, it's...
-It's about your daughter, sir. -What, Meiko?
[Daigo] It's just that she's very upset, sir.
That's all.
[Dr. Mochizuki] I'm sorry if it's caused you distress.
I'll speak with her when I return home.
[car coming]
[Daigo] Huh?
[car door closes]
Matt?
-What's wrong? -I need information.
We're in a tight spot right now.
I'll take all I can get.
Please help us.
[Himekawa] This is highly irregular.
You're asking us to break protocol.
All right.
I mean, you are involved, after all.
So I suppose you ought to know.
What you're reading is called the fifth interim report.
Only speak of it to the other digi-destined. For now, anyway.
That covers everything we know happened
during the school festival.
Lots of facts to analyze.
We'll have to tell the media soon.
It'll be a circus.
But eventually, everything is going to come out.
Can you give me any information about Ken?
Yes, of course, we always keep tabs
on all of the digi-destined.
[Himekawa] Don't worry about Ken.
[sighs] I was only worried
because I couldn't get ahold of him.
[Himekawa] Let the others know.
The Meicoomon investigation will start immediately.
We'll do our best to collaborate as much as possible.
We'll let you know if anything changes.
Are we good?
Thank you very much.
See you tomorrow, right?
-Himekawa, you crossed the line. -Why is that?
You straight up lied to him.
You think I should be honest all the time?
Don't you realize they would panic
if they knew how many digi-destined are missing.
My job is to partly to shield them from things.
That requires deception from time to time.
What about the fact that
Meicoomon is the root of all of this?
But if they knew that,
how do you think it would affect their relationship with Meiko?
Preserve their innocence at least for a while.
They'll figure it out soon enough anyway.
[groans]
[Daigo] But why?
Why keep the truth from me too?
Do you think that I'm untrustworthy?
Sometimes ignorance is bliss.
[sighs]
-[Dr. Mochizuki] Meiko. -Huh?
Father, I brought you a change of clothes.
Thank you, Meiko.
Please let your mother know
that I won't be coming home until late.
-Yes... -Get home safely.
But, um... About Meicoomon....
Sorry, my meeting's about to start.
Father...
I'm so sorry.
Just leave it to us. We'll handle this, Meiko.
[sneezes]
[phone buzzes]
\"Are you okay? Mimi.\"
Reboot, huh?
[keyboard keys clicking]
-[alarm buzzes] -[groans]
Oh, come on!
I just can't crack this thing.
[all] Oh!
Meiko, your friend's here.
Uh?
[Sora] I stopped by to bring you the homework
we were given for summer vacation.
Oh, thank you.
-[Sora] Are you eating? -Huh?
You have to try to pull it together.
-Oh... -You need to...
eat and get some sleep.
[giggles] You're like a mother hen.
-[Meiko giggles] -What, no way!
Tai said the same thing.
-Boy, you try to be nice... -I'm sorry.
Oh, now it's okay.
Tai had trouble before too.
He did?
There was a time awhile back when Agumon dark-digivolved.
[gasps]
I know. But Agumon is totally fine again, you see?
Just remember that we and our digimon are outliers.
Different than the others.
We're always connected.
[sobs]
[Sora] I truly believe that.
It's okay to let it out.
That's the whole reason why I came.
[sobs and cries]
[Joe] Oh! It looks like a tornado hit...
after a hurricane and a typhoon.
-[Izzy groans] -Huh? [screams]
Black tea... Please.
[Joe] You don't have to finish it all in one gulp,
you know.
And how long have you been awake?
How long ago was the school festival?
[cries out] What?
That is really not good.
Izzy, if you're too tired, then you can't get anything done.
Studying taught me that.
Honestly, it's about the only thing it taught me.
You know, you seem more upbeat than usual.
Oh, yeah? Do I?
Is it really that obvious?
What should I call it?
Maybe awakening or insight.
Or maybe just being tired of being tired of studying.
It's like I Joe-volved to mega level.
[chuckles]
Uh, anyway, where are the digimon?
They're in the server now.
It's the safest place for them to be to avoid the infection.
[all saying hello]
I gotta be honest.
I actually found some coding errors even inside our PC.
-And our server too. -Huh?
Don't worry. I fixed them.
It's all fine now.
That's good I guess.
When I cross-referenced the data,
it matched up with when Meicoomon
was infected at the school festival.
-The same thing that caused 'em. -I don't know yet.
It'll take time to figure out and find countermeasures.
How about you find your way to bed?
You need to sleep.
And I'm willing to bet
a shower would do you a world of good too.
Well, I know it would certainly do my nose good.
[laughs] I mean if I had one.
All work and no shower makes Izzy a lonely boy.
[Tentomon] Oh, the smell-manity!
-Hey, Joe. -TK, what's up?
Where's Izzy?
[Joe] He preferred the sleeping bag to the couch.
-Out cold. -Finally got him to take a nap.
He's been working so hard. It isn't healthy.
Do you think he feels responsible?
Think so. He's on a mission.
I mean since Meicoomon has become infected.
Just look at the really awful stuff that's happened.
But it'll be okay.
The infection won't spread to the other digimon so easily.
Thinking positive, huh?
Well, if you focus on the negative,
it's more likely to happen.
[Patamon] TK!
You're back! Wow!
-Patamon! -It's time you came to visit.
[Gomamon] And about time we came out!
Oh, yeah!
[Tentomon] Count me in too!
Or is it count me out? I'm so confused.
Whee!
-You've been waiting all along? -[Patamon] And bored too.
We were trying to stay out of Izzy's hair.
Well... all of his parts, really.
-Except the part that feeds us. -Get cracking with the snacking.
Sure feels like a long time since I've seen this little guy.
[Patamon] Aww.
Hey, stop. That tickles.
-Patamon... -Hmm?
[TK] No!
No, this can't happen.
[Patamon growling]
Patamon!
Please just calm down. It's gonna be okay.
[TK groans]
TK?
[TK] Patamon, please.
[Patamon gasping]
-[Joe] What's the matter? -[TK] Uh, nothing.
Patamon?
[Patamon snarling]
[TK] Come on, buddy. You gotta fight it.
[Patamon groaning]
Huh?
[Patamon] TK, you're kinda smushing me!
Oh, sorry about that.
What's going on, TK?
We're just hugging it out, you know.
Don't get carried away.
Izzy's gonna be upset if you break your digimon.
Right.
TK?
Uh, oh, uh...
Don't worry. It's just a scratch, see?
Oh!
[Patamon] Must have been some serious hugging.
I'm starting to think, you're trying to smush me.
Seeing Izzy wrapped up like that
makes me want some chips and salsa.
[Gomamon] You're right. He looks like a bean and cheese burrito.
-[Tentomon] Ooh, burritos! -Hey, Joe.
What if our digimon...
[chomping]
What if our digimon get infected?
-[Joe] What do you mean? -[sighing]
[TK] Just what if? What would we do?
-[Joe] We'd have to fight them. -We all need a takeout.
Huh?
Doesn't Izzy research that kind of thing so we don't have to?
[TK] Yeah. I guess.
[TK] I'm gonna head home.
Right. Hey.
Hold on, you're taking Patamon?
That a problem?
Of course it is.
But, uh... isn't it unwise to have them all in one place?
I mean, what if something bad happened?
-Hmm. -For example, as a worst case...
if one got infected, we could have an outbreak.
Don't say that!
[all] Huh?
[TK] Right. Sorry.
It's just...
Look, Joe, I just really want to spend
a little quality time with Patamon.
I'm sure we all feel that way.
[Patamon] I wanna go with TK!
I wanna go with TK! I wanna go with TK!
I wanna go!
Sorry, but you can't...
[Patamon] No, no, no! And I mean no for real!
I'm going with TK and that's that!
[snoring]
[Patamon] This is kind of fun, isn't it?
[laughs]
Yeah, kinda.
I did what you wanted, right? You looked so worried.
I just knew that I had to come home with you.
[giggles]
-[TK] Let's go. -[Patamon] Okay.
[TV] This high pressure front
means sunny skies in the East.
[Mom] How are you doing?
[Meiko] I just need to get my shoes on.
[Mom] You sure you want to go to school, honey?
-I'm fine, Mom. -See you later.
Okay, see ya.
Oh, Meicoomon...
Stop it.
[students talking]
-Hi, Meiko. -Oh, good morning.
I was just looking for you.
I slept so soundly I barely had time to finish breakfast.
Wanna have lunch together?
Uh... Awesome.
[Mimi] Meimei!
-Good morning, Mimi. -[Mimi squeals]
I'm sorry. I really should've--
Hey, hey, hey, it's nothing. Forget it.
Not quite.
[all gasping]
-It's like you just disappeared. -I didn't mean to.
Now, just relax.
Matt only meant that he was worried about you.
-Can't you tell by his face? -You're a tandura.
Now you're just making up words!
-[Mimi] Matt's a stinky tandura! -[Tai] But, seriously...
Uh, yes?
Izzy's really trying hard.
He spends all his time in his office now.
He's gonna figure this whole infected thing out.
If anyone can find a solution, he can.
-Right, Mimi? -[Mimi] Enough.
She gets the point already. She's a smart girl.
Or are you saying otherwise?
Oh, I'm sorry.
[Meiko] But I want to know what's happening.
And I really should apologize to Izzy.
Then we'll go together.
Please don't make things more complicated and dramatic.
-I'm not dramatic. -Don't pay any attention to him.
I'm sure Izzy will figure it out.
He'll save everyone and Meicoomon.
I hope.
[Joe] So you just took Patamon home with you?
Uh-huh.
Izzy was really upset.
Patamon was just homesick. He misses me.
-Don't be selfish. -Look, everything's fine.
If anything goes wrong, I'll send him straight back to Izzy.
[Kari] Wow! Meiko's actually here?
[Meiko] Good to see you.
Why does only Patamon get to go home?
All of us miss our digimon, you know?
-[TK] I know. -Well, it's not just Patamon.
They've all been complaining
about being stuck inside the server.
Do you think it's wise to take your digimon home?
-Or stupid? -[all] Hmm?
I don’t know. I'd love to have Biyomon at home but is it safe?
It's too risky. What if they get infected?
We'd have to fight them.
Don't say things like that.
How could we?
We're partners.
-What a mess. -I know.
TK... You see now
why we can't really take them out of where they're safe.
[TK gasps]
-What's wrong, TK? -Oh...
[TK] It's nothing.
-TK? -[TK] Patamon's fine.
I just want more time with him.
-Oh... -I'm sure... they'll be okay.
Come on.
It's still not fair. They should all come home then.
Well, why don't they? Once in a while can't hurt, right?
We can have them hang out at Izzy's while we're in school,
-and pick them up our way home. -That's right.
And if we're all watching them,
we'll notice if anything changes.
We'll be more informed and can alert everyone in the group.
It's just like taking a kid to daycare.
Yeah, they're practically our kids anyway.
I say Sora's right about Joe being right.
Guys, this is serious. We need to keep an eye on the situation.
Yep, we will when we get 'em.
[Mimi] Get 'em? Can't Izzy just email them to us?
[Joe] You must have a great data plan.
Truth is the Internet may not be secure.
We have to pick them up to stay safe.
[Mimi] Haste makes you knock on wood.
[Sora] Uh, yeah. Or something like that.
[Mimi] Matt, what do you think?
You still say it's too risky?
[Matt] Well, Gabumon's sure gonna be upset
if he's the only one left behind.
[Mimi] You say that like you have no choice.
But you can't hide that smile.
-Tandura! Tandura! -[Matt] Stop making up words.
All right. So we agree. Let's try it.
-You guys... -[all] Oh!
Sorry, Meimei.
We just got caught up in the moment.
Oh! It's fine. Don't feel bad because of me.
Well, I should get home.
Go pick up your digimon.
I bet they'll be happy to go home with you.
Thanks.
[Joe] Let's get 'em and see how it goes.
Hopefully better than usual.
-[Mimi] Bye, guys. -[Sora] See you soon.
-[Mimi] Go have fun. -Do something, Meimei. Text me.
I'm sorry.
None of that made you feel any better.
It's okay.
I've got homework to do.
-See you, TK. -Meiko!
Can we talk somewhere before you go home?
[Meiko] Are you really saying that Patamon's already...
I'm a horrible person.
I told them all that their digimon would be okay.
Like Patamon.
I lied.
I couldn't be honest.
It was too hard.
I get it.
It hurts.
[TK] What do I do?
What if I can't save Patamon?
I mean, what if Patamon...
What if Patamon starts acting...
-[Meiko] TK... -[TK sobs]
[Meiko] You poor thing.
[TK] The whole thing sucks.
-[TK] Sorry. -[Meiko] No, I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
This is all my fault.
Uh, no. Really.
I didn't mean for that to sound...
like I was trying to blame you. Forget it.
After all that's happened, I should be comforting you.
I'm just a selfish idiot.
[Meiko] You're wrong.
It is my fault.
[TK] All right. Put on a good face.
-I'm home. -Welcome back, TK!
[both giggling]
I didn't bring you anything.
Don't worry. It's okay.
Although, I mean, a candy bar would be kinda nice. [giggles]
Aha. Again with the smushing.
It's been happening all day long. Pretty weird.
Listen, TK.
This means I'm infected, doesn't it?
[chuckles] Thought so.
[TK] Patamon, I...
That's why you took me away from the others, right?
Because I might end up like Meicoomon?
[TK] No! You're gonna be okay!
[Patamon] TK...
If I start to go berserk...
you'll have to take me down.
[TK] Don't ever say that!
But I don't want to make everyone sad, TK.
[TK] I could never...
Just listen. I'm okay with it.
Whatever happens, it was worth meeting you.
It'll be all right.
I'm sorry. I know it will make you sad but you'll have to.
Patamon...
Don't cry, okay.
[both sobbing]
Patamon...
TK...
[doorbell rings]
[Patamon] Someone's at the door.
-Oh, hey, Matt. -Gabumon!
-So they tell me. -Let's get down to it.
Eh, what do you mean?
[Matt] First, can you turn on a light.
[TK] Oh, I hadn't noticed.
[Matt] It's too dark to notice anything.
I see snacks.
So what brings you here?
[Matt] Well, uh...
did you have a fight with Tai in the past hour?
-[TK] No. -[Matt] Sora?
[TK] Why on earth would I fight with Sora?
-So, Joe? Mimi? -What's your deal?
Do I always have to be fighting with somebody?
-It's kinda your thing. -He has a point.
You're not helping, you know.
Look, this isn't about me.
Huh?
Something's up with you.
[both] Ooh...
[Matt] Well, what is it?
I'm not leaving till you level with me.
So, start talking.
I'm scared...
Huh?
...that everyone's gonna finally realize
you're a terrible guitarist.
[Matt] Huh?
Eh, you little...
You really had me going there for a minute!
-[TK] Sucker. -[Matt] Not funny.
Okay. Kinda.
[phone ringing]
Sora?
What would she be calling me about?
-Go on. Answer. -I'm gonna.
Hello.
Just making Matt mad. You know, the usual. You okay?
Um-hmm. Yeah.
Just thought I'd call and check.
Okay, talk to you later.
Well, that's done. Next?
-Looks like Izzy. -Izzy it is.
Hey, Izzy. Just wanted to say thanks
for all your hard work yesterday.
Of course, and today too.
Right, and the day before. Sure.
Listen, don't forget to eat. And sleep.
But not at the same time. [laughs]
Okay, that's it from me. Goodbye, Izzy.
[Sora sighs]
Sora, you always do a good job of taking care of everyone else.
-Well, we're friends. -It's just...
With everything that's going on,
I get worried about everyone.
It really is nice that you're so thoughtful.
Thanks so much.
That's why they call me a mother hen.
-But what about you? -Huh?
You need to take care of yourself too, don't you?
Myself?
Not an option?
Well, selflessness is one of your best treats.
All right, since you're my favorite person,
I'll take care of you.
Sound good?
[giggles]
[Sora] Thanks, Biyomon. That means a lot.
[man 1] Flight 194, proceed to....
[man 2] Whoa!
[man 1] It's a blackout! Start the generator!
[man 2] It's not working.
[man 3] There's no power. But the planes...
[computer] The time has come.
The era of destruction is at hand.
Digimon shall roam free again
because your world is completely reliant
on its digital infrastructure,
it is fragile, extremely fragile.
It is a house of cards...
Breaking News: Massive blackout in part of the Kanto region.
...ever teetering on the brink of complete collapse.
It must be acknowledged.
The era of complete catastrophe is upon us.
[TV] The waterfront area was left
completely without power yesterday evening.
It's now been restored
but the reason for the outage remains unknown.
It's suspected to be related to the mysterious messages
seen all over the Internet.
Massive Blackout again in the Kanto region.
Across the region, nervous residents are scooping up
emergency supplies
in case of another power loss.
\"Digimon shall roam free.\"
What does that mean?
Wait, you guys are still here?
You're gonna be late.
Right.
Oh, can you pick up ice cream for dessert on the way home.
-And milk, too? -Got it.
Everybody else in the world's worried about a catastrophe.
And mom's just worried about dairy products.
[giggles]
-I knew I loved your mom. -Your priorities are a mess.
Glad you still have your appetite.
[chuckles]
[Agumon] He's still ignoring us.
[Palmon] It's like he's been hypnotized.
[Palmon] How long do you think he can stay like this?
It's gonna be a long night.
[Gabumon] Say something to him, Agumon. He's freaking me out.
Hey, there, Izzy. Trouble with anything?
-Like your hearing? -Oh, relax.
Izzy gets this way sometimes because, well, he's Izzy.
-Less talk-- -More snacks, I know.
-[buzzing sound] -[Izzy gasps]
-So he can move. -Well, that's a start.
Shh, come on, you guys. We have to let Izzy do his work.
Otherwise he won't get it done. And if he doesn't get it done,
the longer he'll be doing it.
[squeaking]
-Huh? -Uh-huh.
[thumping]
[Izzy typing]
Ma'am, the digimon. They've all been departing Izzy's building.
What's our next move?
Just follow them.
[boy] Man, I'm hungry.
[boy 2] Who wants some snacks?
[girl] How did you handle the blackout?
[girl 2] Same way I handle everything. Bad.
[Boy 3] They should have given us the day off.
[Boy 4] Yeah, an early summer vacation.
-[phone rings] -Huh?
[Kari] Huh, I thought I turned this thing off.
-[ringing continues] -Uh...
Hello?
The time...
has arrived.
[Gatomon] Do you think it was okay to leave Izzy's place
without asking first?
Well, we already left so we can't really ask second.
Oh, I don't know, I always ask for seconds.
Well, I just didn't want to bother bothering Izzy.
So what are we gonna do?
I think we've already proven we can stand around doing nothing.
But guys,
we have to make sure we don't expose ourselves to infection.
[Patamon] Funny you should say that.
[Gabumon] What's up?
It's, um... Thing is...
Well, I'm infected.
[all scream]
[Gomamon] That is so not good. Are you sure?
[Patamon] Yeah, I'm sure it's not good.
-Does being infected hurt? -No, it's just a little scary.
Does he know yet, TK?
Uh-huh, but he said not to tell anyone.
I guess I didn't do that too well.
But shouldn't we let all the others know?
No, not yet. Please, guys.
If you're infected there's no point in us staying at Izzy's.
But we should at least tell him
so he can help figure out your options.
[Tentomon] Maybe he can digivaccinate you.
Please don't. Listen, guys,
I'm just going to leave so I don't infect anybody else.
But where will you go?
[Patamon sighs]
Sora's gonna freak out if there are any more problems.
Mimi too.
I don't want to upset anyone but if you--
You have to promise me that if I start to go berserk...
you'll take me down.
-No! No way! -Don't say that.
[Patamon] Look, you're like my family.
[all] Aww.
I just couldn't bear it if I infected you.
I couldn't.
-[Agumon] Oh, Patamon! -I know.
[all gasp]
[Palmon] Kari? What're you doing here?
[Agumon] Not that we have a reason to be here.
It's not like one of us is infected or anything.
-[Agumon giggles nervously] -Listen to me.
[all] Wha...
-Not sure I like the new look. -[whimpers]
You're right.
-That's not Kari. -Then who is it.
[fake Kari] I am... the one who longs for stability.
I borrowed this body so that I could talk to you.
Is that... Kari?
You see... this world's in serious danger.
And the same goes for the digital world.
[all gasp in horror]
Those digimon who've become infected
are causing major problems.
They're continually terrorizing the quantized world
and disrupting its continuity.
-Quantized world? -Continuity?
[fake Kari] The digital devices of your world
and the surrounding sphere of the Internet
that was created from them
bred the digital world.
In essence, it emerged from the quantum sea.
More worlds than you can imagine have come into being this way.
Some worlds are as different as night and day
and yet they still exist side by side.
However, if these so called infected digimon
are able to breach the quantized world,
then in all likelihood,
they will destroy the digital world in the process.
It will cease to exist.
And humanity's electronic devices will fail as well.
[Tentomon] Wait, let me get this straight,
the digital world would be destroyed?
And this one would be too?
Sadly, yes.
And it is also likely...
that all of you would perish with the digital world too.
-That can't be true! -[all digimon] Oh, no!
Isn't there anything we can do?
There is only one way to avoid this grave fate.
Just one.
[all] One way? What?
A tremendous sacrifice.
When Meicoomon next emerges, time will run out
[sighs] and then...
Uh, Kari!
-Uh, Himekawa! -I think she's okay.
It seems she just fainted.
No, she's not okay.
What even happened to her, anyway?
Oh, I'm not entirely sure yet but...
it appears that someone used her
as a conduit in order to deliver a message to you.
What do you think she meant by \"a sacrifice\"?
[Himekawa] Perhaps... a reboot.
What, a reboot?
Please tell me that's something you can eat.
Agumon, stop obsessing about food!
We believe that the digital world
is one of the many worlds that exists
side by side with our own, a sort of parallel universe.
As long as our world exists,
it's possible to restart the digital one.
-That's a reboot. -And what happens if we do that?
[Himekawa] Well, infected digimon
weren't originally part of the digital world.
So after a reboot, the infection would be gone.
If that's true, what are you waiting for already?
Rebooting's only a last resort.
[all] A last resort?
The quantum sea has created uncountable other worlds.
At the same time, it's different than all of them.
It's the primal world.
The progenitor.
An unplanned, uncontrolled reboot
could leave gaps in evolutions.
Or even destroy the entire digital world.
But...
[Gatomon] But we're already out of time.
[Himekawa] Yes.
If we just stand around and wait,
all the other worlds would be destroyed too.
In order to avoid that,
we must reboot.
[Gabumon] If we do this,
will Matt's world be okay?
[Himekawa] Only if every trace of infection has vanished
from this world when the reboot is initiated.
How do you know that?
I'm a high-ranking officer, that's how.
You're saying that this sacrifice
is basically turning back time in the digital world?
That's right. More or less.
How's it work?
This whole reboot thing?
I don't know exactly
but it all rests on one thing.
Homeostasis,
and if it truly wants stability across worlds.
Homeostasis?
I'm almost positive.
That's who just talked to you through Kari.
Maybe it's easiest to think of it
as a super being from the digital world.
[Agumon] There's nothing easy about that.
[Himekawa] In any event,
we believe it is seeking stability across worlds.
But Meicoomon's next appearance
could trigger a dangerous reboot.
[all gasp in fear]
Well, regardless of that,
I can't leave Kari here like this.
I'm driving her to the hospital.
What're you going to do?
-Huh-oh, we're coming along. -Hold on.
Are you... trustworthy?
Gatomon, what's wrong?
[Gatomon] We need to talk.
[sighs]
Ah!
[Agumon] So to talk,
don't we have to actually, you know, talk?
[Gatomon] Right, so about this reboot thing.
It would let us help out a lot of worlds right?
[Gatomon] You don't really understand
what would happen
if we turned back time in the digital world, do you?
[all] Not at all.
It isn't only the digital world that would get rebooted,
we would as well.
-Get it? -[all] Not even a bit.
It means... that we would lose all of our memories.
Our memories?
-What are those again? -Agumon, not time for jokes.
Hold on. Are you really saying
we'd forget everything that's happened to us?
-[Gatomon] That's right. -[all] Oh!
Everything?
You're telling me I'd even forget Mimi?
No way.
-But I don't wanna. -Me neither.
I can't forget TK!
Just the thought of it's even scarier than being erased!
This is a bad idea.
[Tentomon] Even worse than all our other bad ideas.
[Gatomon] Yes.
Losing our memories would be truly scary.
But really, the scariest thing
is that we wouldn't even know it happened
'cause we wouldn't be able to remember that we forgot.
[Tentomon] Is there anything we can do?
You heard Himekawa.
If Meicoomon shows up, she could trigger an uncontrolled reboot.
And that's the bad kind of bad.
Not the slightly better kind of bad she talked about.
Wait, if we caught Meicoomon, could we stop the reboot?
Yeah, I bet that we can if we can all just work together.
But what if we can't?
[all groan]
[Gatomon] Listen, no more feeling sorry for ourselves.
We wanna protect our partners and their world, right?
Then, this is how it's gotta be.
We've to prepare for the worst.
Great. Now I'm feeling sorry for myself again.
[Palmon] Gatomon...
Come on, guys. Let's not give up hope yet.
[all moan]
Izzy's trying everything he can.
I know, but if he can't figure it all out then...
He will. He has to.
He's working on it.
And Izzy won't stop until he finds the solution!
That's why... eeyeah...
Tentomon!
I know he can do it.
It's his only option.
I believe in him too.
But what if it's too late by the time he figures it out?
[all groan]
[Himekawa] Well, that's a relief.
Seems you're just a little anemic.
Yeah, but...
I still don't understand what happened to me.
Last thing I remember, I was walking down the hall at school,
and next thing I know, I'm in the hospital.
Well, I don't really know.
I only found you after you fainted.
With all that's been going on lately,
you probably haven't been taking proper care of yourself.
-[Kari] I guess... -I should drive you home.
Oh, no! I'm okay, really.
I left my bag at school.
I gotta go back and get it.
All right, well, see you soon.
Thank you so much for all your help.
Hmm.
[Himekawa sighs]
We're all out of time.
-[Gatomon] Kari! -Huh?
Gatomon?
Gatomon, something wrong?
Aren't you supposed to be at Izzy's?
No, it's okay.
What do you mean, \"okay\"?
Let's go do some shopping before we go home.
Uh, shopping? What's going on? Are you all right?
Don't worry about it.
I-- I just want to spend some time with you.
Sounds great.
Huh?
Gabumon, what're you doing here? .
I'm just saying hi.
-[Gabumon] Hey, Matt. -Hmm?
Could you play the harmonica for me?
Harmonica?
-Please. -Well, Gabumon...
-I'm kinda practicing here. -[sighs] All right.
-Is everything okay? -Oh, uh... yeah. Never mind.
Gabumon?
Just keep on practicing.
Why'd you stop playing? Is something wrong?
Are you done?
I just thought I'd switch up the pace a little.
[plays harmonica]
[Sora] What is it?
It's just... Sora,
what do you want to do when you get older?
[Sora] Huh? Where'd that come from?
[Piyomon] I'm just curious about your future.
There's way too much going on and now to worry about that.
I mean, there's Izzy's health, the infected digimon...
I want to hear about your secret hopes and dreams.
Nah, I'll take a pass. That's way too grown up for me.
Come on, please tell me.
-Hmm, what do I dream of? -Yeah, yeah.
[Sora] Nah, it's too embarrassing.
[Piyomon] Oh, come on!
You want me to meet your girlfriend?
Oh, yeah. We're partners.
So I want to make sure that you get a proper introduction.
Partners, huh?
Yeah, well, that's what we are.
I gotta make sure my partners get to know each other, don't I?
I mean, she might even become my life partner someday.
[whimpers quietly]
Okay. So what shall I wear? Something special like a suit?
-My formal fur? -Formal fur?
No, just be yourself.
Don't change a thing. You got me?
All right, sure.
But for the record, I wanna know one thing.
Yeah, sure. Like what?
How we met? Or how we fell in love?
Or how she fills my heart with pure joy--
Can other people actually see her?
[Joe] Hey, she's really real.
For real.
-Kari! -Hm?
Kari! Look at that.
[Gatomon] So many types of ice cream.
You want some?
Uh-huh.
[Gatomon] Hey, don't forget me. Pass it.
[Kari giggles]
[Gatomon] Now that's good ice cream.
I mean, is it ever bad?
-Hey, Kari? -Hmm?
[Gatomon] Look, a photo booth.
-Can we take pictures? -Okay, if you want.
You don't?
No, come on, let’s go do it.
[Gatomon] Great one. That one, too.
That could be better. There, better.
[Gatomon giggles]
So she says, \"I got this beautiful pot of flowers, right?
And I have been watering them every day.
Two times a day.
But they're not growing.\"
Well, get this, Palmon, they are plastic!
-Huh? -Uh...
I thought that was... funny, right?
Oh! Yeah, totally. Really great story.
In fact, it was hysterical!
-Wait, what happened? -Uh?
[Mimi] Oh, good one, Palmon. You are so funny. [chuckles]
[Palmon] Hysterical, right?
[Agumon] Come on, Tai, let's go play soccer.
-Soccer? -And then video games.
And then lunch, and then some more lunch
and then lunch on the side, I love lunch.
-Do you like lunch? -[Tai] What's up with you?
Oh, nothing. Can't I just be excited for no reason?
[Tai] Did you get into the coffee again?
Oh, come on, Tai.
Let's hang out.
Seriously, are you okay?
All I want is to spend some time with you.
Agumon?
It's not like it's the end of the world or anything.
Um, forget I said that.
[Tai] You're acting weird. Well, weirder.
[Agumon] I don't know the meaning of the word.
[Tai] You don't have to know it to be it.
Just tell me what's going on.
You're making me more nervous than normal.
Um, it's nothing.
Come on.
Huh?
I just wanna play.
[TK] Oh, Patamon.
I just wish there was something I could do.
[Patamon whining]
[sighs]
[Patamon] Just being with you helps me.
You can squish me all you want.
Don't tell anyone I told you.
A reboot?
Don't worry, Tai.
Everything's gonna be okay once we stop Meicoomon.
We'll be just the way we used to be. Right Tai?
Tai?
[Tai] No, Agumon.
So, Matt, what're you thinking about?
I'd like to go back in time.
[Gabumon] Uh?
I know. I rarely think like this.
But I just wonder...
What if... my memories are all wrong, huh?
I was so young.
I could've made things up.
What if...
nothing happened like I thought.
Everything happened.
It was all real.
[sighs]
[plays harmonica]
[Izzy] These errors keep popping up in the code.
They seem to be the root of all this.
[Tentomon] Did you find something?
[Izzy] Well, our world's digital devices work on a binary code
or with other systems that can be converted to binary.
But somehow some got hacked
and overwritten in an unknown numerical system.
So computers around the world are getting viruses.
[Tentomon] Oh, no!
[Izzy] This new code
doesn't seem to be based in a binary system,
a decimal system or even a hexadecimal system.
Our electronic devices can't recognize it.
That's why we can't see it with our goggles.
If I'd known this sooner,
I could have come up with a plan to decode it. But...
without the base, there's nothing I can do.
Maybe it's possible to convert
the data into something readable.
But one mistake could cause
every computer and electronic device
worldwide to shut down.
And even if I knew the code's base,
what could I do about it now?
My own computer, one that I programmed myself,
is being overwritten.
This is pointless.
I'm just staring at the screen.
Not getting anywhere.
-I feel so useless! Aargh! -[electronic beeping]
I'm a fool. A useless fool!
All the time I've spent working on this...
And for what?
I'm just... useless. Useless...
[sobs]
Izzy, I don't mean to interrupt your meltdown but
you shouldn't feel so bad that you haven't found the solution.
But, this is a disaster.
And I can't figure a way out.
[Tentomon] Well, one thing I know about you is that
you are able to achieve great things
because of your great persistence.
You're driven by the opportunity to make things better.
I even think you're happiest
when you're learning something new.
Because you have the ability to see not only what something is,
but how great it can be.
But since you've become focused
on what's bad instead of what's good,
your work doesn't make you happy anymore.
Of course it doesn't.
I feel like I've been going in circles.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I hate to see you so miserable.
It must be hard to keep starting over.
-Tentomon, you... -[sighs]
Looks like there's only one thing to do.
[Izzy] What?
A reboot?
[Tentomon] We digimon can't do it on our own.
But if it comes to that,
then we're prepared to do what needs to be done.
[Izzy] A reboot would fix all our issues.
Okay, I've got a plan.
Now, I just have to get it done.
All right. I gotta work fast.
I can solve this.
I know you can, Izzy.
I believe in you.
I guess you believe in you too.
Just look at you go.
Now that's my Izzy.
Always full of hope
and everything's going to be okay now. Oh!
[electronic disturbance]
[Daigo] \"The ties that bind.\"
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
There's a distortion.
The data is clustering.
It's becoming denser at an increasing rate.
They're coming.
[thunder and electricity crackling]
[Meicoomon roars]
[Izzy]Oh, no! A distortion!
[policeman] Roger that. Just hang tight,
I'm heading toward the blockade right now.
[Tai gasps]
Wow!
Something big's about to go down, Agumon.
-Looks crazy. -You ready?
Oh yeah. Let's go.
[Tai] All right.
[Meiko's Mom] Meiko, wait!
[Meiko] I can't. I gotta go.
[explosive noise]
[Joe] Tai!
[Tai] Joe!
Glad you're back in action. Let's do this.
Agumon digivolve to!
Gomamon digivolve to!
[roaring]
-Greymon! -Ikkayumon!
-They'll wreck this place again! -Greymon!
Push Meicoomon back through the distortion!
[roaring]
[Meiko] Meicoomon's at the pavilion.
Oh, Mei!
[roaring]
Meteor away!
Needle spray!
Tai!
Man, what an epic fight!
Keep it up, Togemon.
You can stop Meicoomon!
[Meiko] No! Stop fighting!
-Is she serious? -Let her try to help.
-Meimei! -Meicoomon, you have to stop!
-[screeching] -[roaring]
[Meiko] Mei!
-He digivolved! -Mei, no!
Look out!
[Joe] Matt! Meiko!
Meiko, are you okay?
-Mei! -Wait, are you crazy?
I gotta stop Meicoomon. Please let go.
The digimon are trying to stop her
and they're the best chance we've got.
What happens if you run in there and get hurt?
Meicoomon might go berserk.
We've got to get to safety.
-Kari. -Yeah?
We can't just watch anymore. We gotta help.
[Kari] You're right.
Okay, go!
[Patamon] Wait for me, Gatomon!
Please, TK!
Gatomon digivolve to!
Angewomon!
-[roaring] -[screaming]
Yes, nice one.
Keep her in there.
Yeah, but... even if Meicoomon's there
what about after the next distortion?
[screaming and groaning]
That's not good.
[Patamon] TK, they need me.
-I gotta go. -No!
But, TK...
Patamon, if you go,
then you're gonna...
Are you kidding?
It's okay.
[TK] No, you have to stay here with me!
[Patamon] But I gotta and you know it!
We digimon have to protect your world.
[TK] Patamon...
And that's why I came here in the first place, you know.
But I... I can't...
[Patamon] TK.
See you soon.
[yells] Patamon!
Patamon digivolve to!
Angemon!
Mei, I'm here for you!
Please listen to me! Please!
[roaring and screaming with rage]
What can I do?
It's hopeless! Oh, Mei!
What's this energy spike?
It's totally different
than the data from the other distortions.
Why did it appear with Meicoomon?
Unbelievable!
You find something?
All of these strange events began
when Meiko and Meicoomon moved to town.
Of course! What's that mean exactly?
[Izzy] Maybe Meicoomon
didn't catch the infection from another digimon,
Maybe it was caused by Meiko.
[Tentomon] Meiko? Seriously?
I'm not entirely certain
but it does fit the observed data.
Listen, Izzy, we gotta get down there and help out right now.
I know. I'm just about done.
I just gotta load this on to my laptop.
[Meicoomon screaming]
Angemon!
[Angemon groans]
-Angemon! -It's too dangerous.
-But he might be hurt! -Did you see that?
Yeah, I did. He's infected.
-Angemon! -I knew it.
He's infected.
No, you don't!
Nice!
[Kari] Angemon and Angewomon are fighting each other?
I can't believe this is happening!
Why would they do that?
They've always been on the same side.
But, that means, Togemon could be in trouble too.
What if she gets infected next?
Oh, no! Togemon!
[screaming]
[Kari] TK.
Angemon...
-You guys! -Izzy!
Where's Meicoomon?
Our digimon are trying to push her through the distortion.
Rain!
[screaming in pain]
Oh, no! Birdramon!
-Garurumon! -Togemon!
Oh, no! They've all got it!
Angewomon too?
The infection is spreading faster
and at this rate,
the number of digimon getting compromised might multiply.
If that happens...
Greymon digivolve to!
MetalGreymon!
[screaming and groaning]
-What's happening? -Some kind of countdown.
To what?
The reboot!
[all] The reboot?
What's that mean? What's going on?
Gatomon never talked about anything like that.
That would mean our digimon'd have their memories erased.
[Joe] You mean they'll even forget us?
-Yeah. -No way! Try something else!
Actually I do have a plan B.
You do?
[roaring]
-Izzy, I need to fight too. -Hold on.
[Izzy] I can get data for a backup
if our digimon go into that cube.
What do you mean 'backup'?
I mean, copies of the original file
and if I have them
I can sort out the data corrupted by the infection.
Tentomon, go and help MetalGreymon
get everyone pushed into the backup field.
You got it!
Tentomon digivolve to!
Kabuterimon!
[Sora] Come on, you guys!
You have to save everyone! You can!
MetalGreymon!
[groaning]
[Izzy] Tentomon!
[gasp in shock]
Tentomon, you gotta get into that backup field.
-Alone if you have to. -[Tentomon] No can do.
What's the matter with you!
I'm sorry, Izzy, but I can't.
The other digimon are already out there
risking their hides to stop Meicoomon.
I can't stay in here doing nothing just to save myself!
Tentomon...
[Tentomon] Izzy, when we first met,
I didn't know you from Adam,
and I still don't know who that is,
but getting to know you over the years
has been the greatest thing that's ever happened to me.
If my memories get erased,
we'll just have to make new ones together, right?
-Wait... -No matter what happens...
promise me, you'll hold on to your love of learning, okay?
Stop this.
[Tentomon] Sorry I couldn't give you more of a heads up!
Tentomon!
Goodbye, Izzy!
It's been a pleasure.
Kabuterimon digivolve to!
MegaKabuterimon!
Once I get a hold of you,
I'm not going to let go!
[grunting]
Listen up!
MegaKabuterimon digivolve to!
HerculesKabuterimon!
[screaming]
Is this it?
Is it really time for me to say goodbye?
Everyone is going to be so very sad!
Open your eyes!
Thank you!
[electronic ticking]
[continuous beep]
[Patamon] Don't forget me, TK!
[TK] I think Patamon...
was the first one to catch it.
But...
I just couldn't bring myself to tell you guys.
Because...
I was so afraid.
Good morning, everybody.
Summer is upon us and the season started with
record breaking turnouts at our amusement parks.
There's been a steady flow of students and families
coming in since early this morning.
The forecast calls for nothing but blue skies
and unusually warm weather.
So this should be a very pleasant day.
I hope that everyone's able to enjoy it.
We certainly intend to.
-[children laughing] -[child 1] Take that!
[lifeguard] No splashing.
[Himekawa] It's been a whole week now.
And we've yet to see any signs of disturbance
in the digital world from the quantum sea.
[man] Seems so.
But there's a very good reason for that, you know.
[Himekawa] I know.
[Himekawa] The kids are just going to have to move on
and put all this behind them.
It had to happen eventually.
[Himekawa] Before we know it,
there will be new buildings sprouting up.
In six months from now,
this place will look just like it did before all this started.
Within a year,
everyone will have forgotten that it happened at all.
No one will give a second thought
to anything about digimon.
If they even remember what they are.
[man] What about the kids?
[Himekawa] They'll just...
have to say goodbye to that part of their childhood.
[Izzy] Any news on the digital world?
Have the digidevices rebooted?
When the digital world rebooted,
it was supposed to revert to its state
prior to the distortions
and the digidevices should have followed suit.
We're gonna have to find another way.
-[TK] What's plan B then? -What do you mean?
Even if find our digimon...
they won't remember us.
And what do we say?
When it came down to it,
I couldn't even protect my own partner.
I was helpless to save Patamon.
[Izzy] So what do you think we should do, TK?
Mope around and try to forget them?
This isn't about what you couldn't do in the past,
this is about what you're going to do now.
[Izzy typing]
[Himekawa] Izumi?
[Meiko] It's Mimi.
Got caught in the rain again.
[Izzy] Don't you want to see them again?
Yeah, of course.
They're our partners.
Maybe someday...
[whistle]
Agumon...
Hey! Tai!
[Tai] You know, you guys...
if we keep waiting for this mythical someday,
we'll be old and grey before we see our partners again.
[Izzy] Exactly.
Then let's go.
[doorbell peals]
[Meiko] TK...
-Are you serious? -[Tai] Absolutely.
You'd better be sure.
Once we open the gate, it could be unstable.
You may not be able to come back.
[Daigo] It's too dangerous.
You guys, don't be foolish. We have to discuss this.
-I'm going. -But Matt...
Look, there's no point in freaking out about it.
I mean we did the same thing
when we were back in elementary school.
That's right.
We're older now. We know the risks.
All right, then.
I'll set up where the reboot occurred.
Hime...
Nishijima, take them to the site.
I'll contact security and distract them.
[Daigo] Are you guys really sure this is what you want.
[all] Uh-huh.
[Meiko] You know that I can't join you.
[TK] Why not?
Because I don't have the right to go.
-What's that supposed to mean? -This was Mei's fault.
Well, Mei's and mine I guess.
How is it Meicoomon's fault?
Because Mei was the source of the infection.
[Mei] Mei... Mei... co...
Meiko...
[giggles]
And that is how I first met Mei.
My dad was working as a digimon researcher then.
He told me that Mei was an extra special digimon.
I heard some rumors,
but I never knew exactly why she was special.
I never expected things to turn out like this.
I wanted to say something,
but I... I just...
I... couldn't bring myself
to actually do it.
I... I...
But TK,
I don't want to make everyone sad, you know.
I know how hard all of this has been for you.
Forget about blame.
What's done is done.
It's what we do next that matters.
And I say what we should do is...
-go find our partners so we-- -Stop being nice to me!
I can't handle it. Don't sugarcoat it.
Just be honest and blame me!
Be angry, I deserve it!
Meiko! Stop!
[Meiko] I'm sorry but this isn't just hard for me...
it's all just so...
horrible.
At least, it does feel good
to finally say it out loud to someone.
It's true. [sobs]
I feel relieved,
now that I've confessed.
I have no right to see the digimon, none at all!
Just... Just leave me alone. [sobbing]
[TK] I'm sorry, Meiko.
I can't do that.
We're in this together.
I mean... you're Meicoomon's partner.
But more than that...
you're one of us.
When you're ready...
we'll be waiting.
[sobbing]
So you're saying that all along
[Joe] Meicoomon was the source of the infection?
Did your agency know?
I didn't. I would have told you.
Oh, Meimei, it's awful.
Well, maybe if she'd clued us in earlier...
You think you could've done it, Joe?
'Cause I know...
that I couldn't.
It's harder than you think.
Much harder.
I knew Patamon was infected but I couldn't tell you.
[Joe] You have a point.
Are those coordinates where
our partners are in the digital world?
I think so. I scrubbed the data
and got intel from Agent Himekawa.
[quiet whirring]
Uh-huh.
Agent Himekawa, what's she doing here?
[Sora] A D-three?
This is all theoretical
which is scientist talk for 'don't have a clue'.
But if the data that's on this D-three,
can be synced up with your own power,
it very well might be possible to open a gateway.
What power is that?
[Himekawa] The power that exists
within each of your digital crests.
[TK] I guess this is it.
[Daigo] Be careful, guys.
What's wrong?
[Sora] Well, it's sort of scary.
[Joe] You know, I've been thinking about this moment
since the first time I saw Gomamon.
I've got to be brave,
or else he'll never stop making fun of me.
[Matt] It'll be okay.
[Meiko gasps]
[glass shatters]
[Mei] I'm sorry, Meiko.
[Meiko] Don't touch the glass, it's dangerous.
You don't want to get cut, do you?
[gasps in pain]
Oh, no! Meiko, you're hurt!
It's okay. It's just a scratch.
You see, it's all better already.
[Mei] Does it hurt?
Not at all. It's totally fine.
[Mei] I'm so sorry, Meiko. I didn't mean to do it.
You got hurt because of me.
No big deal. Besides I'm pretty tough.
Thanks. I love you, Meiko.
Mei...
[buzzer]
[Meiko panting]
Uh...
[Tai] It all looks exactly the same.
[Mimi] Yeah, that thingy is just like that thingy.
[Izzy] Well, the digital world may have been rebooted,
but it's fundamental structure remains the same.
-Although... -What's wrong?
Something... just feels off.
-How so? -I'm not sure.
-But something is different. -I agree.
[Matt] Different how?
I don't know. It feels weird.
[all sighing]
[Matt] Well, let's go see what we can find out.
[Sora] So far...
all we've found out is that we're out of shape.
[Matt] Speak for yourself.
'Cause I'm too out of breath to speak for myself.
[Joe] At least we didn't find what we usually find.
Trouble, pain and terror.
-[lightning] -[Joe] Or maybe we did!
[loud explosion]
[roars]
Alphamon!
[Matt] There's another one.
Who is that guy? I've never seen him before.
[Joe] Just like old times!
[all screaming]
[TK] Well, we got through that like we always do, barely.
Did you see that new digimon?
I wonder who he is?
Pretty sure he's Alphamon's enemy.
I need more than that.
-[computer beeps] -Aha, Jesmon.
What're you thinking?
Just that both of those guys appear to be ultimate level.
Yeah, they did.
I thought that all the digimon would have reverted to
digieggs after the reboot?
Is it possible they escaped the reboot?
And then they somehow managed to digivolve to ultimate level?
Well, what are we supposed to do
if one of those digimon comes after us next time?
-Palmon and the others aren't-- -[muted whistling]
Shh.
What's up?
-You hear that? -Huh?
[whistling]
Sounds like a whistle.
[all sigh]
[Matt] Ah, why are we running again?
-[whistling] -[Matt] Just up ahead.
[all panting]
[whistling continues]
[TK] Togemon...
[childish sounds]
[Tai] Gomamon...
Who are you?
[both] Uh?
[all gasping]
[whistling]
Come on, give it back.
I'll give it back later when I'm done playing with it.
Awesome, but what's the deal with the whistle?
I wanna play! I wanna play!
It sounds pretty.
Just let me play with it a little while longer.
[whistling]
-[Sora] Yokomon! -[digimon squeal in fear]
Who are you?
[whimpers quietly]
Hello there.
And what's your name? I'm new around here.
I'd love to learn more about your world'
'cause it's really prodigious.
Would you tell me about it please?
[stranger] What a touching reunion!
[Himekawa smirks]
[Tai] Look at all of you.
It's great to see you again.
Meiko...