[MIIA]
If you're not sure how to
season your cooking...
"S" is the magic letter!
[MIIA]
Sugar! Salt!
Vinegar! Soy sauce!
[MIIA]
Woo!
Vinegar starts with V,
but yeah, sure.
[MIIA]
And of course, we can't
forget the secret
ingredient...
It's my burning hot..
love.. for.. you!
[MIIA]
(giggle)
Uh‐oh...
Nope, that's fire!
(panic) Are you sure
I can't help you, Miia?!
It's okay! I have to beat
out the competition to
become your bride, right?
And right now,
I am on FIRE!
[KIMIHITO]
If you're not careful,
we'll all be on fire.
Starting today, I'm gonna
cook all of our meals.
They say the best way to
a man's heart is through his
stomach!
I can see it now...
[KIMIHITO]
I'm home from work, Miia.
[MIIA]
Welcome back, Darling!
[KIMIHITO] (hm?)
[MIIA]
Would you like dinner...
or a hot bath? Or maybe...
you.. want.. me!
[KIMIHITO]
I'll have YOU for dinner
in the bath!
Ooooh, you're so greedy,
Darling!
Ah, I can't wait...
This has very little
to do with cooking...
[MIIA]
(spacing out)
[KIMIHITO]
Where is everybody?
I guess they're still
asleep. (surprised)
[KIMIHITO]
The pot's boiling over!
[MIIA]
(huh?) (panic)
(breath) (pained cry)
[KIMIHITO]
(startled) Miia!
Miia... Everyone makes
mistakes sometimes...
If you just keep trying‐
[MIIA]
I‐it's fine! I'm not upset
about the cooking anymore!
So, um... if you don't
mind, could you leave me
alone for a little while?
[KIMIHITO]
(notice) (huh?)
[MIIA]
Why is this happening
This is bad...
Oh no... What should I do?
I can't do it
without hands.
[KIMIHITO]
Is this some kind of paper?
[MIIA]
(surprised) Don't!
Ow...
[KIMIHITO]
(groan) (notice)
[MIIA]
(look up)
[KIMIHITO]
You're molting?
[MIIA]
(sob) (cry)
[KIMIHITO]
Well... I didn't know lamias
molted just like snakes.
[KIMIHITO]
So is that why you were
spacing out?
I was hoping you would never
have to see me while I'm
shedding my skin, Darling...
But now that I've burned my
hands, I'm gonna need some
help with the stripping.
[KIMIHITO]
(shocked)
The skin, I mean.
[KIMIHITO]
Oh.. yeah, that!
[MIIA]
Uh‐huh...
(clear throat) Nothing.
You shouldn't stress
out over it...
I mean... I can always
see your tail, so‐
[MIIA]
You don't understand‐
For lamias, being seen
molting
is way worse than
being seen naked!
This stinks...
I can't cook, I can't clean
or do laundry...
And if that wasn't bad
enough...
I can't even
shed my skin right.
[MIIA]
I can't marry you...
not if I can't live up to
your expectations
as your bride!
After you finally said
you'd consider marriage!
I've never messed up
molting before!
What's wrong with me?!
(crying)
[KIMIHITO]
That's called an
unsuccessful molting, right?
[KIMIHITO]
It happens to snakes
when they're stressed out.
[MIIA]
(huh?)
It could be that you're
feeling a little tense
because you're adapting to
a new living environment.
But you might get a skin
disease if you leave it
like that.
[MIIA]
(huh?)
How do you know so much
about this, Darling?
[KIMIHITO]
Oh, I've been doing some
studying...
Smith actually gave me some
helpful advice too.
[SMITH]
Lamias are biologically
similar to snakes...
Here you go,
educate yourself.
[MIIA]
(surprised)
If I'm gonna live with
all of you...
I should know these things.
[MIIA]
Darling!
Don't worry, I'll be happy
to help with your molting.
But in exchange... I want you
to help me when I molt.
[MIIA]
(huh?) But I thought
humans didn't molt.
[KIMIHITO] We do.
[MIIA] (surprised)
[KIMIHITO]
But it only happens
when we get sunburned.
[KIMIHITO]
Well... Here goes nothing!
[MIIA]
(reluctant nod)
Let me know if I'm
hurting you.
[MIIA]
(gasp)
(extended flustered panting)
[KIMIHITO]
Wow...
It comes right off,
doesn't it?
I guess this means all that
studying paid off
after all.
[KIMIHITO]
Um...
[MIIA]
(panting) (wince)
(pant) (muffled flusterment)
[KIMIHITO]
(gulp)
[MIIA]
Aaah! (overwhelmed)
(gasp) (overwhelmed)
(extended panting)
[KIMIHITO]
(panting)
Just do it...
Don't think about it!
[MIIA]
(gasp)
(startled)
[MIIA]
D‐Darling...
The t‐tip of my tail
is, um...
[KIMIHITO]
I‐it's sensitive, right?
You'll just have to be patient
for a sec, okay, Miia?
[MIIA]
(startled)
(squeal, into panting)
[KIMIHITO]
(surprised) (choking)
[MIIA]
Please, Darling,
we have to stop!
I just can't take it
anymore!
[MIIA]
If you don't stop
touching me there,
I'm gonna go crazy!
[KIMIHITO]
Come on, hang in there
a little longer!
It's just the tip, okay?
Just the tip!
[MIIA]
(scream) (extended panting)
[KIMIHITO]
Okay... I got it!
(panting)
[KIMIHITO]
That.. wasn't so bad...
Why don't we take the rest
off your stomach now, huh?
Flip on over to your back.
[MIIA]
Okay...
[KIMIHITO]
We're done with the tip of
your tail,
so you should be able to
rela‐ huh? (panic)
[MIIA]
Um, Darling?
Don't look at me, okay?
I'm taking it off now...
[KIMIHITO]
W‐wait a minute, Miia!
Don't you think it's better if
you do that part yourself?!
[MIIA]
But, this is the most
sensitive area...
If I leave any of the old skin
on it... I‐I'll get all
itchy...
So... please, Darling...
could you...?
[KIMIHITO]
(gulp) Y‐yeah...
Okay, now where's the rest
of the skin? (react)
[MIIA]
Um, n‐not there.
A little to the right.
[KIMIHITO]
Right, the right!
Uh, wait, it that your
right or my right?
[MIIA]
Oh, I'm sorry...
I meant more to my right.
(gasp)
[KIMIHITO] (horny)
Being blinded is making me
focus on my hands even more...
I can feel how warm she is.
[MIIA] (extended gasping)
[KIMIHITO] Wow, she's soft...
[KIMIHITO]
Ah, and smooth and silky
and squishy...
[MII]
(flustered) (gasp)
[KIMIHITO]
This is a lot different
from the scaly parts.
[MIIA]
(pant) (gasp)
Darling... I'm really sensitive
right there... (flustered)
[KIMIHITO]
I can't wait to touch her
delicate skin...
[MIIA]
(scream, into panting)
I‐I'm sorry, Darling...
I'm alright now...
I can take it... There's only a
little bit left!
[MIIA]
(panting)
[KIMIHITO]
I got a little carried away.
Aw man, if this keeps up...
then I'm probably gonna start
coming outta my own skin too!
I gotta finish this quick!
M‐Miia, tell me where the
rest of the skin is!
[MIIA]
T‐to the right...
(panting under)
[KIMIHITO]
Okay, I got it!
A little to my right!
It'll be fine as long
as your hand is there!
[MIIA]
(huh?)
[KIMIHITO]
Alright, Miia, here I goooo!
[MIIA]
(gasp) D‐Darling,
I didn't mean YOUR right!
[GOOFY SNAKE A]
Comin' in!
[KIMIHITO]
Something feels we‐
(scream) (pass out)
[MIIA]
(gasp) No! Darliiiiiing!
[SHRIEK A]
(horror scream)
[MIIA]
Here you go, Darling!
Hope you enjoy!
[KIMIHITO]
(disgusted)
Bon apetit! This is to say
thank you.
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?)
The hell is that stuff?
Is it some kind of traditional
lamia cuisine? Eugh...
[MIIA]
(giggle)
[KIMIHITO]
(nauseous)
(more nauseous)
[MIIA]
(giggle)
[KIMIHITO]
Looks delicious...
(forced eating)
(crash to table)
[KIMIHITO]
Wow, couldn't eat another bite,
thank you Miia...
[MIIA]
(happy) I can't believe
you ate all of it!
[KIMIHITO]
I've never tasted anything
like that,
and I might not live to taste
anything else again.
[KIMIHITO]
(notices door)
[PAPI/MERO] (nauseous)
[CEREA] No... we're too late.
[KIMIHITO]
What happened to you guys?
I haven't seen you since
breakfast!
[CEREA]
Ugh.. What is that smell?
[MIIA]
Oh! Let's see...
Curry, meat and potatoes,
hamburger steak,
fried rice, pork soup...
Ooh, and pudding!
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, Miia?
Did you follow a recipe?
[MIIA]
(mm‐mm!) I learned by watching
you!
[CEREA/PAPI/SUU/MERO]
(long nauseous)
[MIIA]
But I had everybody taste it,
so it should be okay!
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, why didn't you taste it
yourself?
[MIIA]
'Cause I always lose my
appetite when I start molting!
[KIMIHITO]
(long nauseous)
[MIIA]
MonMusu!
[MIIA/CEREA/SUU/PAPI]
[KIMIHITO]
I'm home.
[MIIA]
Welcome back!
Good to see you, Darling.
[PAPI]
Hey, Master?
[MERO]
Did you stop by the supermarket
today?
[KIMIHITO]
Yeah, they were having
a big sale there...
Vegetables and eggs
were dirt cheap.
[PAPI]
Uh, Master?
[MIIA/MERO]
(annoyed)
[SUU]
Master! Master, Master!
[PAPI]
I need to tell y‐
[CEREA]
Stop that, Suu!
Give Master some space;
he's exhausted!
[PAPI]
Master, I have something
to tell you!
Okay, I'm listening, Papi;
what's the matter?
[PAPI]
So you know,
I'm gonna lay an egg soon.
[CEREA/MIIA/MERO]
(shock)
[SUU]
(hm?)
[MIIA]
Oh wait, it's unfertilized.
That doesn't necessarily mean
you guys did it! My bad!
[MERO]
You frightened me for a moment!
[CEREA]
Oh Papi... You little
troublemaker!
[SUU]
(dazed) (play‐swinging)
How's it work?
Do you lay eggs every day
like a chicken or what?
[PAPI]
I'm not a chicken! I haven't
laid an egg in a long time!
But this WILL be the first time
I've done it since I came to
Japan, so I'm a little nervous.
[SUU]
(playing)
[MIIA]
Aw.. maybe it's because
you're stressed out?
Well... I think we'd better
talk to Ms. Smith about it.
[ALL]
(surprised at doorbell)
[KIMIHITO]
Um, can I help you, sir?
[KASEGI]
I believe you can!
Is there a young harpy
living in this household
who's getting ready to
lay an egg, by any chance?
[KIMIHITO]
Huh?
Wait how would you know that?
[KASEGI]
I was tapping your...
I mean, just a hunch!
Filmmakers know these things.
[KIMIHITO]
Filmmaker?
Ah, how rude of me! My
name's Kasegi;
I'm an experimental
film director.
My current project is
a documentary about the
Interspecies Exchange.
I was hoping you'd be
available for an interview.
[KASEGI]
(excited laughter)
Look at this wide hallway!
[KASEGI] (growing amusement)
[KIMIHITO] I'm kinda concerned.
So am I, but we DID come here
for an interspecies exchange.
[CEREA]
We should do what we can
to promote understanding.
[MIIA]
Does my hair look okay?
Don't worry... It's not any
different than usual.
[KASEGI]
Alright, why don't we start
with our little expectant harpy
friend?
[SUU]
(playing)
Beautiful... Is it time yet?
[PAPI]
(shaking head)
Then I'll get some footage of
the other girls' rooms
while we're waiting
for the main event!
[MERO/CEREA/MIIA/KIMIHITO]
(confused)
It's for the good of society!
You don't mind, right?
When you put it that way, I
suppose we don't have a choice.
[KASEGI]
(grin)
[MERO]
These are my living quarters,
Sir Kasegi.
[KASEGI]
Ah, that's why you're in a
swimsuit!
So you like gothic Lolita
fashion?
[MERO]
Yes, I do.
[KASEGI]
By the way...
Are you wearing underwear?
[MERO]
(shocked)
[KASEGI]
I'm curious to see what's
under that cute skirt...
[MIIA]
What's wrong with you?!
You can't just ask a girl that!
(fuming)
It's all for educational
purposes, I swear! Nothing
sketchy here.
Can you show me how
you get out of the pool?
[MERO]
Certainly, but it's very
simple.
I just build up momentum
and leap!
[KASEGI]
(grunt)
[MERO]
Did you get a good shot?
[KASEGI]
Oh, yeah.
[MERO]
(gasp, into shriek)
[KASEGI]
(snickering)
[KIMIHITO]
Hey that's not cool!
Don't worry about that,
we'll cut it in post.
Now let's keep the ball rolling
and see what we can
discover in Centorea's room!
[CEREA] (surprised)
[KIMIHITO] Listen, buddy...
Look. There is no reason
to fear, Master...
Now that I've seen what
happened to Mero,
I'll be on my guard.
A noble Centaur like me
is courageous through any
adversity!
[KASEGI]
Ooh, a Japanese‐style room!
Classy!
[CEREA]
Yes, I prefer tatami mats.
The nice texture...
and the grassy smell...
You see, my people don't
traditionally sleep on beds or
futons...
Tatami mats are better for
beings of my size‐
Yeah, yeah, that's great.
Anyway, are you wearing
underwear?
[CEREA]
What?! Where did that question
come from?!
That's got nothing to do with
this!
[KASEGI]
You don't wear bras either?
Um‐if you must know,
it's not customary for
Centaurs to wear underwear!
[KASEGI] I'll have to
investigate further!
[CEREA] (gasp)
[KASEGI]
Damn, these are massive!
Do they hurt your back?
[CEREA]
(uncomfortable) (angry)
You've taken this indecency
too far!
I won't tolerate
any more of this!
[KASEGI]
Who cares if it bugs you?
[CEREA]
(huh?!) (pushed back)
[KASEGI]
Asking the hard‐hitting
questions is what I do!
Even if you and all the other
monsters in the world hate my
guts for it..
this is my one true calling!
[CEREA] (pushed) (startled)
[KASEGI]
I can promise you... I will
fight for unity of all species!
[CEREA]
(fuming)
[KASEGI]
Now let's go check out Miia's
bedroom!
[MIIA]
(surprised) (sigh)
Well, here's my room, happy
now?
[KASEGI]
So, are you wearing underwear?
[MIIA]
That's all you wanna know?!
Yes, I am, okay?!
[KASEGI]
Would you mind
showing us, please?
[MIIA]
(annoyed)
I don't think so!
[KASEGI]
(gasp)
What's this?!
[MIIA]
(shriek) (clutch)
[KASEGI]
Hmmm!
[KIMIHITO]
Is that your molted skin?
Why didn't you trash it?
[KASEGI]
Skin?!
I was afraid if I threw it out,
the birds would get into it!
That would be way too
embarrassing!
[KASEGI]
No, you can't throw that away!
A rare item like that
would drive people crazy!
The Japanese have always
considered snake skins
to be lucky charms!
We've even built holy shrines
for worshipping
snakes as gods!
And snake skins have been
used in traditional Chinese
medicine for years!
But if you're just going
to throw out such a
valuable artifact,
I'd be more than happy
to take it off your hands!
[MIIA]
Ew, forget it,
I'm not giving you that!
Only a sicko would want to
keep somebody else's skin!
[KIMIHITO]
She does have a point...
[KASEGI]
Alright, then instead of snake
lovers,
I can give it to a
research lab...
Maybe they can make some
scientific discoveries with it.
[MIIA]
You mean it?
[KASEGI]
It might help us understand
each other on a deeper level!
[MIIA]
Uh, deeper? (hm?)
Might even lead to you getting
hitched to Darli‐er, that guy.
[MIIA]
Wait a minute...
Well, I guess if it's to better
society,
I would be a bad person
if I said no, now wouldn't I?
(conniving laughter)
[KASEGI] (tch)
[KIMIHITO] (hm?)
[KASEGI]
This could be better...
I'd be rolling in cash if I had
a video of the molting...
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?) (startled)
[MERO]
Master, help, it's Papi!
[KIMIHITO]
(surprised)
Papi!
[PAPI]
Um... I think... it's...
coming...
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, try to relax, okay?!
[MIIA]
Yeah, try Lamaze breathing!
Hee, hee hee, hoo!
Breathe in two times
and then hoo, let all the air
out at once okay!
[MERO]
You know a great deal
about childbirth...
[KIMIHITO]
Do you really have to
record the whole thing?!
[KASEGI]
This is for cultural
awareness, remember?!
Now then, Miss Papi, go ahead
and pull up that skirt for me!
[KIMIHITO]
Dude!
[PAPI]
(pull)
[KASEGI]
Whoo!
Aren't you taking this too far?
[KASEGI]
So give her a hand..
After all, the sooner
she lays the egg,
the sooner I'll be
out of your hair, right?
[KIMIHITO]
(stunned)
[PAPI]
(extended panting)
[KASEGI]
Nice moves there, "Master".
[KIMIHITO]
Shut up!
Oh, by the way, what do you
plan on doing with the egg
after it comes out?
I'm just curious.
[KIMIHITO]
Would you just be quiet
for five seconds?!
[KASEGI]
(chuckle)
[PAPI]
M‐Master...
just a little...
[KIMIHITO]
Sorry, was I being too rough?
[PAPI]
(panting) No, just go a little
lower... (flustered)
[KIMIHITO]
Lower?!
[PAPI]
(mmmfff!) (panting)
[KIMIHITO]
(ggh!)
I feel something hard...
Is that the egg, or...?
[PAPI]
(squeal) Ah... Master...
I can... feel... the egg...
It's gonna.. come out!
[KIMIHITO]
Y‐you can do it, Papi!
Okay! That looks excellent,
now take her panties off!
[KIMIHITO]
(shocked)
[KASEGI]
You want to make the world
a better place, don't you?!
[KIMIHITO]
Oh, come on, man!
[PAPI]
It's okay... Master...
(panting)
[KIMIHITO]
But... (nervous)
[KASEGI]
That's it! Time for the
uncensored egg‐laying scene.
[KASEGI]
Harpy eggs are so rare, I can
easily get 3 million for one.
[KASEGI]
And if I packaged the
footage along with it...
it'd be worth 4, no, 5 million!
[KASEGI]
These freaks of nature
bring in a pretty penny!
[KASEGI/SUU]
It's a good thing they're so
stupid; they fall for almost
anything!
[KIMIHITO/MIIA/CEREA/MERO]
(surprised)
[KASEGI] (startled)
[SUU]
Now we're getting to the
sexiest part.
Man, I can't wait to whack off
to this thing before I sell it!
[KASEGI]
(scream)
[MIIA]
So that's what this was all
about, huh?
[CEREA]
Unity? World peace? Ridiculous!
[MERO]
You insolent mongrel!
How despicable!
[MIIA]
You were just trying to make a
quick buck off us! How dare
you?!
[CEREA]
Give us back Miia's skin, now!
[MERO]
Yes, and surrender the camera!
[KASEGI]
I'm not afraid of you!
Monsters like you aren't
allowed to hurt humans,
remember?
This camera is my property
and mine alone!
I won't let you lay hands,
hooves, or fins on it,
do you hear me?!
[KIMIHITO]
Hey, hotshot.
You wanted Papi's egg too,
didn't you?
[KASEGI]
Ah! The egg! My precious 3
million yen! (happy)
[KASEGI]
(punched)
[KIMIHITO]
Get your eggs from the
supermarket; they're having a
sale.
[KASEGI]
(weak)
[PAPI]
(touched)
[ALL]
You're so brave, Master.
Oh, wait, did you
seriously smash Papi's egg?!
[CEREA/MERO/SUU]
(concerned)
Course not!
That was just a regular egg
I picked up when I
went shopping today.
[CEREA/SUU]
Clever!
[KIMIHITO]
You did good too, Suu.
Yeah, I had no idea
you could do that!
[CEREA]
A slime who can read minds?
Quite impressive.
[SUU]
(happy)
[MERO]
Pardon me, everyone!
I believe the real egg
is on its way now!
[PAPI]
(panting) (small push)
[CEREA]
You can do this, Papi!
[MERO]
Just a little further!
Your breathing!
Don't forget your breathing!
Hee, hee, hoo! Hee, hee, hoo!
[KIMIHITO]
(grabbed) Miia! Come on!
[MIIA]
I'm not letting you see this!
Whoa, it's coming out!
[CEREA]
Goodness, it's quite large.
[MERO]
Wow, it's really stretched...
[KIMIHITO]
Stop making such graphic
commentary!
[PAPI]
(scream)
[KIMIHITO/MIIA/CEREA/MERO/SUU]
(amazed)
So... what are we going to do
with Papi's egg?
[MERO] Yes, I wasn't aware such
a thing was so valuable... How
perplexing.
[KIMIHITO]
Hmm... Well, what do you
think, Ms. Smith?
[SMITH]
Don't ask me! You know I don't
get paid enough to get involved
in this!
[SMITH]
Oh, by the way, Darling...
[KIMIHITO]
Yeah?
[SMITH]
About that director.
The name and address on his
card were both fake.
But his M. O. was sophisticated,
so he might be a repeat
offender.
I'll look into it.
[KIMIHITO]
Uh‐huh...
Well anyway...
what are we having
for dinner tonight?
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, actually, Miia's cooking,
so join us at your own risk...
By the way, where's your egg?
[PAPI]
It's in the fridge.
[KIMIHITO]
That's a silly place for it.
What if someone mistakes
it for a‐(realize)
[ALL]
(mortified)
[SUU]
(huh?)
Tonight's dinner is my
specialty!
I hope everyone likes
boiled eggs!
[KASEGI]
That damn kid!
He destroyed the harpy egg,
my camera, AND the rare
footage!
[KASEGI]
I better collect some more
thread before I go broke.
(frustrated under)
[RACHNELA]
Somebody's busy. Shall I lend a
hand? I have several.
[KASEGI]
Shut your yap!
Don't go getting cocky
just because your thread's
a hot seller!
And stop spinning webs
everywhere!
Can't you keep 'em in one
place, huh?!
[RACHNELA]
Keep them in one place?
(chuckle)
[KASEGI]
(mmff!) (muffled struggles)
[RACHNELA]
You mean like this?
Anyone who'd throw away
3 million is either too
kind or up to something.
Which makes me
a little bit concerned...
not to mention intrigued.
[RACHNELA]
(giggle)
Now I will have to investigate.
[SMITH]
Say hello to a special force
made of exclusively non‐human
species
to punish non‐human criminals
in accordance with the
Interspecies Exchange Bill.
[SMITH]
We are... MONster's New Law!