[KIMIHITO]
Whoa! W‐wait a second! Time out!
[MIIA/PAPI]
Gotcha!
[KIMIHITO]
(pain)
[MIIA]
I'll never let you go,
Darling...
We're going to get married and
live happily ever after!
[PAPI]
Don't think so‐! Master's gonna
marry ME!
[CEREA]
No, the only proper wife for my
Master is ME!
[MIIA/PAPI/CEREA]
(glare)
[MIIA] Darling!
[CEREA/PAPI] Master!
[KIMIHITO]
Uh (stammering)...
How did we get to marriage
all of a sudden?!
[MIIA]
Right. Now let's review the
Inter‐species Exchange Bill.
[MIIA]
Rule number one is...
humans and demi‐humans can never
do harm to each other.
[MIIA]
And rule number two...
You're not allowed to go out
unless your host family's with
you.
[MIIA]
And most importantly, rule
number three is
whoever has resided with the
host the longest has ultimate
authority!
[MIIA]
So you two better listen to
everything I say!
[CEREA]
You made that last rule up,
didn't you?
[PAPI]
Fascinating!
[CEREA]
Don't listen to her, Papi!
[MIIA]
Did you get all of that,
Centorea...?
Pay attention please!
[CEREA]
How dare you...?
I've read the Bill; it says
nothing of the sort!
[KIMIHITO]
Cerea...? Ms. Smith wants you to
fill out your home‐stay
application forms when you get a
chance to uh...
[MIIA] (anger)
[CEREA] (awkward)
[MIIA] If you know the rules,
why is there a horseshoe
mark on his face?
[CEREA] Um, well...
[KIMIHITO]
No wait, Miia!
I can explain...
[KIMIHITO]
Better get a bath started‐
[CEREA]
(surprised)
(quiet shock)
[KIMIHITO]
(quiet panic)
[CEREA]
(kick)
[KIMIHITO]
(scream)
I didn't think anybody was in
there...
I promise.
It was all my fault, okay?
[CEREA]
N‐no it isn't!
I was sweaty after my
morning run, so I
decided to take a bath.
I should have locked the door,
I'm sorry.
[KIMIHITO]
Nah, you don't have to
apologize.‐ I should've knocked.
[MIIA]
What's wrong with you‐?!
You are way too nice to her‐!
And you‐!
Those application forms aren't
gonna sign themselves!
[CEREA]
Ah.. right!
[MIIA]
All he did was see you naked‐!
You Centaurs can be so violent!
[CEREA]
Uh...What?!
You don't have any room to talk,
serpent!
Smith said you dislocated his
shoulder not long ago‐!
How is
that any different?!
W‐well, I just couldn't contain
my joy after he protected me...
[CEREA]
That's nothing,
I'll have you know
my Master took a villain's
blade to protect ME‐! so there!
[MIIA]
That's where you're wrong‐!
Darling defended my honor by
punching someone in the FACE‐!
So there!
[KIMIHITO] This isn't
gonna end well.
[CEREA] Any thug could do that!
[KIMIHITO] This isn't
gonna end well.
What Master did for ME
was heroic!
[MIIA]
It was a fake sword!
It's not like that guy could've
even hurt you!
[KIMIHITO] Papi!
(Miia and Cerea arguing under)
[PAPI]
Oh man...
This Inter‐skeezy whatever's
got way too many big words...
My head's all hot now.
I want a bath...
[CEREA]
My name is Centorea, and I'll
thank you to address me as such!
[KIMIHITO]
Uh.. then go ahead and take one.
[PAPI]
Master... I can't take a bath by
myself!
[KIMIHITO]
Huh...? Then why don't you ask
one of those two‐
[MIIA]
Yeah, well Darling and I have
taken a bath together!
[CEREA]
That may be so, but Master's
already touched me physically!
[MIIA]
Oh whatever he had no idea
what he was doing!
[PAPI]
(happy humming)
[KIMIHITO]
It's cold.
[PAPI]
Okay, let's go!
(happy)
[KIMIHITO]
Whoa, wait a minute!
You need to put on the swimsuit
Ms. Smith got for you first.
[KIMIHITO]
Though I'm not sure why it's a
SCHOOL swimsuit...
[SMITH]
It's the only style
that would fit her!
[PAPI]
But... I don't have hands‐
so I can't put it on myself.
[KIMIHITO]
Okay, wh‐where's the hole?
[PAPI]
I'm ready, Master...
[KIMIHITO]
It's my first time,
so I don't
really know how to do this...
[PAPI]
Is it going in?
[KIMIHITO]
Yeah, all the way...
[PAPI]
Ahh... it sure is!
[KIMIHITO]
Wow, it's really tight...
[PAPI]
Y‐yeah...
[KIMIHITO]
Okay now you just have to put it
into the other hole.
[PAPI]
Like this?
[KIMIHITO]
Well, I can't see,
so I'm not sure.
[PAPI]
(small exert)
(gasp) Master...
don't tickle me like that!
[KIMIHITO]
(ggh...)
Uh... now you need to use some
pressure
and just push it
through...
[PAPI]
Mmm... but my feathers are
getting in the way.
[KIMIHITO]
I‐it's okay, it should stretch.
[PAPI]
(surprised)
[KIMIHITO]
(fighting a boner)
[PAPI]
(shy)
Master...
[KIMIHITO]
You know what...? I think I need
to cool off for a little bit...
Go ahead and play, alright?
[PAPI]
Okay, I'll cool off with you!
(giggle)
[PAPI]
The water's so nice!
[KIMIHITO]
I'm like an otter with its baby.
[PAPI]
More like brother and sister!
If I had an older brother,
I'd want him to be just
like you, Master!
Me?
Yup! I really like the way
you always play with me...
and how you never get mad at me
when I do bad things...
You're the best ever!
[PAPI]
There aren't any boy harpies...
so I don't know what it would be
like to have a brother...
[PAPI]
But still...
I've always WANTED a brother...
so I'm really happy
that I met you!
[KIMIHITO] (surprised)
Oh... well I..
I guess there's nothing wrong
with being your big brother...
[PAPI]
(stand up)
Okay, let's get even closer...
[KIMIHITO]
(shocked)
Ah‐what are you...?!
It felt really nice when you
touched me here before...
My heart was beating really
fast!
I want to do it some more,
if that's okay with you?
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, not if we're brother and
sister!
[PAPI]
Hey, don't push me away!
Rggh, fine!
If that's how you're
gonna beeee!
[KIMIHITO]
(fear)
[PAPI]
(scream)
(shocked)
[CEREA]
Honestly! I'd expect this
behavior from a child...
but now that I know that you're
my age...
[CEREA]
Well, I simply cannot tolerate
it!
[PAPI]
(fret)
Let me down from here!
[KIMIHITO]
Cerea...
[CEREA]
Now then, Master...
P‐please mount me...
[KIMIHITO]
Huh...? What?
[MIIA]
I don't think so!
Did you think you could
hide from me?...!
Ms. Smith'll be here to get your
homestay paperwork soon.
[MIIA]
Now hurry up!
Get your hooves off Darling and‐
[MIIA]
Jackass...
[CEREA]
Papi should cool down shortly...
We just need to give her some
time.
[KIMIHITO]
(almost fall)
[SATSUKE]
(bored humming)
[CEREA]
Are you alright, Master?
[KIMIHITO]
Oh, yeah, I'm okay...
And my clothes are all dry now
from riding on your back too.
[CEREA]
I see... Then..
would you mind moving your
hands?
[KIMIHITO]
(horrified)
Ah...! Sorry!
[CEREA]
(released)
I‐I didn't mean to!
[CEREA]
Ah.. no.. That's alright...
I am my master's servant, after
all, so it's not a problem.
[KIMIHITO]
Come on, "servant"?
Isn't that a bit much?
[CEREA]
No, not at all!
I am a Centaur...
My people are proud warriors
who carry the ultimate loyalty
for our masters!
[WALLA: Men]
(battle charging)
For that reason...
I am honored to have a
master to serve!
Just like my father,
my grandfather, and
great‐grandfather before me!
I am a knight before
I am a woman!
This is the way Centaur‐kind
operates...
So no, it is not too much.
[Men] Hear, hear!
[KIMIHITO]
What is that, your Stand?!
Whatever, I get it!
[KNIGHT]
K, see ya.
[KIMIHITO]
But hey...
You're in Japan now, remember?
Now I know that your culture's
important to you, but...
[KIMIHITO]
... but you're allowed to relax
your shoulders a bit.
[CEREA]
I don't know...
You came here because of
cultural exchange, didn't you?
So why not take advantage of it.
[KIMIHITO]
Can't you think of anything new
out there you want to do?
[CEREA]
Something new...? Well, I...
[GIRLFRIEND]
(giggle)
[BOYFRIEND]
Where should we go for lunch?
[GIRLFRIEND]
I dunno, you pick!
[BOYFRIEND]
Aw, you always make me pick.
[CEREA]
Um I...
N‐no... nevermind...
[KIMIHITO]
You can tell me.
[CEREA] Your hand...
[KIMIHITO] (huh?)
[CEREA]
I‐I think I'd like to hold...
your... hand...
Well... I've only ever held
swords and bows...
so I thought maybe it might be
kinda nice... because...
[CEREA]
Th... that's what human girls
do...
I... it wouldn't mean
anything...
unless you wanted it to...
Oh no.. wait... That wasn't
proper of me at all...
I can't say such things
to my master‐!
Please forget I mentioned it!
[CEREA]
(gasp)
[KIMIHITO]
You mean like this?
[CEREA]
(shy)
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, Cerea?
(look)
[CEREA]
(giddy smiling)
[KIMIHITO]
You okay?
[CEREA]
(awkward)
Don't look at me!
I‐I must look like
such an idiot,
turning all red like this!
[KIMIHITO]
But... I, uh...
[CEREA]
Please avert your eyes, Master!
[MIIA]
(scream)
(impact)
[CEREA]
(react)
[PAPI]
(land)
[MIIA]
What did you do that for?!
[PAPI]
You told me to let you down.
[MIIA]
You could've let me down gently!
[CEREA]
What are you two doing here?!
The law clearly states
that you mustn't go out alone!
[MIIA]
Well it's fine if nobody
finds out!
[CEREA]
That's terrible!
[MIIA/PAPI]
(notice)
[CEREA]
(confused)
[KIMIHITO]
(muffled struggle)
[MIIA]
CEEENNTTTOOORRRREEEEAAAA...
[CEREA]
Ah! No...! This isn't‐
[MIIA]
Shut up! First you
kidnap my Darling,
then you take him off somewhere
to make out with him‐?
I thought Centaurs were all
about honor!
[CEREA]
That is quite enough‐!
The last thing I need is a
lecture about honor
from a conniving viper...!
And why do you keep calling him
"Darling"‐?!
Don't tell me you believe
you're his wife?!
[PAPI]
If you're gonna fight, I'll take
him for me!
[MIIA/CEREA]
Stay out of this, chicken wing!
[SMITH]
Ah, I love this song...
(notice)
[PAPI]
(whining)
[SMITH]
Surprise, surprise...
[MIIA/PAPI/CEREA]
If you two won't leave him
alone,
then we'll just have to
solve this the hard way!
[KIMIHITO]
Agh!
[MIIA]
(roar)
[CEREA]
[PAPI]
(roar)
[KIMIHITO]
(speechless)
[SMITH]
(grunt)
[KIMIHITO]
Hey!.. Stop it‐
(shot)
[MIIA/CEREA/PAPI]
(shocked)
[SMITH]
(Uhh...)
[MIIA] Darling!
[CEREA/PAPI] Master!
[SMITH]
Well...!
That's funny; who knew I would
accidentally hit you instead...!
And 3 times at that...
No harm done they're only
tranquilizer darts.
[KIMIHITO]
That's easy for you to say.
[SMITH]
I don't wanna lose my job...
Our secret?
[KIMIHITO]
(annoyed)
Wait a second...
It's way too quiet;
where'd they go?
[SMITH]
(gesture)
[MIIA/CEREA/PAPI]
(worried)
[KIMIHITO]
(surprised)
Are... you guys okay?
[MIIA]
It's just... well, if we hadn't
been acting so selfish,
then none of this would've ever
happened to you...
[PAPI]
Uh‐huh... What she said!
[CEREA]
I'm a failure as your servant...
Please forgive me.
[SMITH]
(smile)
That's why we made a decision,
Darling...
From now on, we'll do whatever
we can to hold back
so we don't
cause you trouble!
[KIMIHITO]
Hold back?
[PAPI]
Uh.. right...!
I won't ask you to play with
me ever again, okay?
[CEREA]
I won't lose sight of my
position as your loyal steed!
[KIMIHITO]
Don't say that!
I know you tend to get carried
away sometimes...
and you shouldn't start fights.
[MIIA]
Darling!
[KIMIHITO]
But the one who's REALLY to
blame for all this is Ms. Smith!
[SMITH]
(long spit take)
[KIMIHITO]
Stuff happens. But the whole
point of this home‐stay thing
is to learn to get along with
each other, right?
And since we're all in this
thing together...
I'd say that kinda makes us a
family.
[CEREA/PAPI/MIIA]
Family...
[KIMIHITO]
So, no matter what complicated
junk gets in our way,
just keep being yourselves.
[CEREA/PAPI/MIIA]
(happy)
[MIIA]
Darling‐
[SMITH]
I couldn't agree more!
[KIMIHITO/MIIA/PAPI/CEREA]
(stunned)
[SMITH]
Family... of course.
(chuckle)
This is too perfect.
I knew I was right to ask
Darling to look after them.
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?)
[SMITH]
Speaking of which, there's been
a movement recently
to amend the
Inter‐species Exchange Bill.
Well... most of the proposed
changes are just boring legal
jargon...
but there IS an article that
would allow marriages between
humans and demi‐humans.
Unfortunately, it's difficult to
predict whether it'll actually
work in practice,
so I've been looking
for a test case.
[KIMIHITO]
Really?
[SMITH]
And that's why you're going to
marry either Miia, Papi, or
Cerea...
Have fun. Choose carefully.
[MIIA/PAPI/CEREA]
(surprised)
[KIMIHITO]
(shock)
Marry?!
[SMITH]
MonMusu.
[MIIA/PAPI/CEREA]
MonMusu!
[KIMIHITO]
Ms. Smith...
Why did you bring up marriage?
[SMITH]
Well, marriages between species
really are the next logical step
in our progression,
even if it causes a
few hiccups early on.
[SMITH]
And that's why
we're doing a test.
[KIMIHITO]
No! What I mean is,
you can't just tell
somebody to get married!
[KIMIHITO]
This isn't the way it's supposed
to work!
What do I do?!
[CEREA] (sad)
[PAPI/MIIA] (concerned)
Hmm... just go with your gut.
[KIMIHITO]
Is that supposed to help?...!
Hey.. hold it!
So that's it,
you're just gonna leave?!
[SMITH]
That's all I got...
My business is done here.
[KIMIHITO]
(stunned)
[SMITH]
Bye... Have a good night!
[KIMIHITO]
(big shock)
[SMITH]
Can't help but think...
That I left something out.
[SMITH]
Oh well.
[KIMIHITO]
I can't believe I'm being forced
to get married.
[KIMIHITO]
But if I touch them,
I'll go to jail?
[KIMIHITO]
Well... it's a good thing I
haven't tried to do anything...
Though they really aren't
making it very easy for me
with the way they act‐
Oh man I'm in trouble!
[KIMIHITO]
(thinking) Marriage, huh?
(knock)
[KIMIHITO]
(startled)
[MIIA]
Darling... are you awake?
[KIMIHITO]
Miia?
[MIIA]
Sorry to bother you, but you're
acting kind of strange...
I'm worried about you.
I guess... you're upset because
you don't want to marry
any of us, is that it?
[KIMIHITO]
Uh‐no... not exactly.
I was just taken aback 'cause
she was trying to force me...
It's not like I'm against
marriage, y'know.
[MIIA]
Really?
[KIMIHITO]
Well, that's not quite all.
I've never even had a girlfriend
before.
Plus I've never... you know...
"been" with a girl...
[MIIA]
I see.
So it's not that you
don't want to.
[KIMIHITO]
Miia...
[MIIA]
I knew you couldn't possibly be
having doubts about marrying me,
Darling.
[MIIA] You're so sweet.
[KIMIHITO] (startled)
[MIIA]
And you are so pure...
[KIMIHITO] (nervous)
[MIIA] A few of the many things
I love about you!
[MIIA]
Hey... you know something...?
When snakes copulate...
they do it all night long.
They wrap their entire bodies
around each other
from their heads to
the tips of their tails.
They get so close you can't
even see where one ends
and the other begins.
[MIIA]
Darling... I'm ready for you...
I want us to become one,
right now.
[KIMIHITO]
What is up with her?!
I mean, she's always really
clingy and lovey‐dovey...
But tonight she's... well...
she's being very aggressive!
[KIMIHITO]
M‐Miia! Wait!
(fall down)
Are you okay?!
[PAPI]
Uh‐huh...
[KIMIHITO]
What the‐?!
Wh‐why aren't you wearing
any underwear?!
[PAPI]
Oh... don't worry,
you can look at me...
We're gonna get married anyway,
so it's okay, right?
[KIMIHITO]
THERE IS NOTHING OKAY
ABOUT THIS.
Do you even know
what marriage IS?!
[PAPI]
(shift weight)
Yeah, it's when you mate
and lay eggs.
[MIIA]
(dazed pain)
[PAPI] First you insert your ‐
[KIMIHITO]
Don't be so graphic!
I know how it works, I promise!
[PAPI]
Graphic...? It's fine...
(unbuckling)
I'm a grown‐up too.
I can lay eggs.
[KIMIHITO] (react)
[PAPI]
I mean I'm old enough to mate.
I'm not some little kid okay.
[PAPI]
The two of us should make lots
of eggs, Master.
[KIMIHITO]
Now Papi's acting all weird too.
Dammit, Ms. Smith, why did you
have to bring up getting
married?! (galloping hooves)
[KIMIHITO]
(slammed)
[CEREA]
(shock)
[PAPI]
(weak collapse)
[CEREA]
I'm too late!
[MIIA/PAPI/KIMIHITO]
(pain)
[KIMIHITO]
Hey, good timing...
I dunno what's gotten into
those two tonight.
[CEREA]
I'm not surprised.
There's a full moon tonight.
It puts their beastly
instincts into overdrive.
[KIMIHITO]
A full moon?
[CEREA]
That, combined with all that
talk of marriage,
must have caused them to lose
their senses.
[KIMIHITO]
I had no idea...
So.. why aren't YOU like that?
[CEREA]
Don't be silly!
I wouldn't abandon all reason
over a full moon!
I've sworn eternal loyalty to
you, Master.
My body and soul
belong to you...
You can do anything
you wish to me!
[CEREA]
I mean that makes us practically
married anyway, right?!
Here! Please touch me to your
heart's content...
I insist!
[KIMIHITO]
I don't care what you say,
you're just as crazy
as the other two!
[CEREA]
(Oh!)
Perhaps you'd prefer this!
Ah?!
[KIMIHITO]
(nosebleed)
(straighten up)
[MIIA]
Darling...
Get closer!
[PAPI]
Forget her, Master.
You're mine!
[CEREA]
My master only has eyes
for his devoted servant!
[KIMIHITO]
She wasn't kidding, their animal
instincts
really are getting
the best of them.
They're out of control!
If I DID try to do something
with one of them...
I'd probably have a heart
attack!
(scream)
(pain)
[MIIA]
Not so fast!
You can't run from me, silly...!
We're destined to be together;
I'm never letting you go!
[PAPI]
But I want you to fertilize
my egg for me, Master!
[CEREA]
I'm going to be your wife,
and I will not surrender!
[MIIA] Darling!
[PAPI/CEREA] Master!
[KIMIHITO]
(startled at phone vibration)
[SMITH]
Hey, Darling, it's Smith.
[KIMIHITO]
What now?!
[SMITH]
I forgot to tell you,
it's a full moon tonight.
[KIMIHITO] (phone)
Gee, thanks for the info!
At the rate we're going
we're gonna have a funeral
instead of a wedding.
[SMITH] (phone)
Which one did you bang?
[KIMIHITO]
Didn't 'bang' anyone...!
Oh... and thanks, by the way...
You just HAD to say
"marriage"...
Now they've lost their minds!
[SMITH]
Hmm...
So... I take it that means you
haven't made your decision yet?
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?)
[SMITH]
You don't know who you want
to marry?
[KIMIHITO] (phone)
Uh, I've been a little busy!
[SMITH]
Please tell me you at least
talked to them...
You need to keep them
in the loop.
But no... after I left,
you ran to your room and locked
yourself in, didn't you?
[KIMIHITO]
(awkward)
[SMITH] (phone)
If you don't tell them
how you feel,
they'll get insecure.
That's why they're acting
so desperate.
[SMITH]
Well... best I can say is...
just try to cool them off.
[KIMIHITO]
(phone)
How am I gonna do that?
[SMITH]
You've got a fridge, right?
[KIMIHITO]
Yeah...
[SMITH] (phone)
Try using ice cubes.
[KIMIHITO]
Seriously?!
[SMITH]
(splash; distortion)
Ah!
Crap I dropped my phone
in the tub...!
[KIMIHITO]
Hello...?!
Please, you can't ditch me now,
I need your help!
[MIIA/PAPI/CEREA]
So this is where you've been!
[KIMIHITO]
(shock)
[PAPI]
That was so close!
[CEREA]
I'll never let you out of my
sight again, Master.
[MIIA]
Darling, what have you been
doing in here?
You're soaking we‐
[CEREA]
(gasp)
[PAPI]
[MIIA]
(gasp)
[MIIA] Darling!
[CEREA/PAPI] Master!
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?)
Yeah, I'm here.
[KIMIHITO]
(look around)
Ohhh, it's ketchup.
I hope I can get this out
of my clothes.
[MIIA] Darling...
[CEREA/PAPI] Master...
[KIMIHITO]
Hey, you aren't freaking out.
You guys must be feeling better.
[KIMIHITO]
Miia, wake up... It's morning.
[MIIA]
(stir)
[PAPI]
(light snore)
[KIMIHITO]
Papi, Cerea, you too.
[MIIA]
(yawn)
Oh... g‐good morning...
Darling...
(gasp)
[KIMIHITO]
Is it though?
[MIIA]
Ah...! What happened to you?
[PAPI]
Master... did you get
into a fight?
[CEREA]
I do hope you're alright...
[KIMIHITO]
Of course I am...!
Well, Not really...
[KIMIHITO]
But I was indecisive.
So when it comes to last night
there's no one to blame but me!
[CEREA/PAPI/MIIA]
(confused)
[KIMIHITO]
I shouldn't have made you guys
feel insecure...
I'm gonna try to
make a decision soon!
[CEREA]
A decision?
[KIMIHITO]
(clear throat)
I'm going to date
all three of you
and figure out
who I want to marry!
I mean... you know, if that's
alright...
[CEREA/PAPI/MIIA]
(surprised)
[KIMIHITO]
And that being said!
[CEREA/MIIA/PAPI]
(eager)
[CEREA/PAPI/MIIA]
(worried)
[CEREA/PAPI] Master!
[MIIA] Darling!
[KIMIHITO]
Could you three please
try to go to bed early
when there's a full moon?
[SUU]
(extended scrubbing exerts)