[KIMIHITO]
(happy sigh)Well, This is a nice
change of pace, huh?
At least that's what I'd LIKE to
say.
[KIMIHITO]
Ugh... Why'd you say you wanted
to come here again?
[PAPI]
Me?... I never said anything
like that.
[KIMIHITO]
What?! You don't remember?!
[PAPI]
(hmm...)
Uh‐oh...
Now that you say that,
I feel
like I forgot something
important...
[ZOMBINA]
This is so good!(gross eating
under)
[KIMIHITO]
What are you doing?!... Stop
chowing down!
You're supposed
to be our bodyguard, aren't
you?!
[ZOMBINA]
Man, I love meat!
[KIMIHITO]
This was your idea!
You said if we make it look like
I'm alone with the girls in the
woods,
we might draw out the guy
who wrote the letter!
But he's not gonna come out if
he knows we have you here to
protect us!
[ZOMBINA]
It's nothing to freak out about.
[KIMIHITO]
Why not?!
[ZOMBINA]
Oh... by the way, I heard
somebody dumped some industrial
waste
around here somewhere...
Be careful.(gulp)
[KIMIHITO]
Whoa, industrial waste?
[ZOMBINA]
What if you get infected by
radioactive sludge and turn into
a zombie?
[KIMIHITO]
Not sure how to respond to
that...
[ZOMBINA]
I wonder if your face will melt
off.(laughing)
[ZOMBINA/KIMIHITO]
(surprised)
[PAPI/SUU] (huh?)
[KIMIHITO/ZOMBINA]
(staring)
[BIG KII]]
(roar)
[ZOMBINA]
Uhhmm... okay... that's a tree
monster...
[KIMIHITO]
(freaking out)
[BIG KII]]
(rage)
[KIMIHITO]
(panicking)
Can somebody please tell me what
that crazy thing is, 'cause it's
a WHOLE LOT
more terrifying than
a zombie!
Is that another non‐human
species
or just a nuked‐out
tree?!
[PAPI]
(gasp)Kii!
[BIG KII]
Papi... Papi!
[PAPI]
(panic)(grabbed)
I REMEMBER NOW!
[KIMIHITO]
PAPIIIII!(running)
[SUU]
(gasp)
[KIMIHITO] (fumble)(dig heels
in)
[SUU]
(groan)Ah.. Master...?
[KIMIHITO]
Run away, Suu!
You have to go let Smith know
what's going on!
[SUU]
But...
[KIMIHITO]
OH GOD IT'S DIGGING INTO MY
CROTCH AAAAAAAAH!
[SUU]
Master!(huh?)
(squeal)(bounce x3)
[KII]
Stand down... human... I will
not allow you to harm me.
I am a Dryad... Keeper of plants
and protector of the forest.
And I despise you human beings.
[KIMIHITO]
(surprised)A Dryad?
That can't be right...
They're in the
book Smith gave me
but they're
not this massive.
[KIMIHITO]
(pain)
[PAPI]
No!... Don't do it, Kii!...
Please don't hurt my master!...
Stop!
[KII]
Papi...
[KIMIHITO]
(struggling)(huh?)
[PAPI]
Guess Kii's mad... You okay?
[KIMIHITO]
Huh?... Kii?... Are you telling
me you two know each other?
[PAPI]
She's my friend... I forgot
about her for a long time.
One day I was out flying around
and I saw Smith ince‐ I mean,
arresting somebody for
kidnapping a non‐human.
That's when I saw Kii, all alone
and scared.
[KIMIHITO]
Why'd you call her Kii?
[PAPI]
Rhymes with tree.
[KIMIHITO]
Wow, clever...
[KII](huh?)
[PAPI](Under)
(look)(smile)
[PAPI]
She was weak and her roots were
all dried out...
so I decided to
plant her here in the woods.
[PAPI](Under)
(giggle)(smile)
[PAPI]
Gotta go!... Bye!... I'll be
back soon!
[KII]
Papi...
[KIMIHITO]
So, how did she get so big?
[PAPI]
Beats me, I forgot all about her
after that!
[KIMIHITO]
What is wrong with you?!
[PAPI]
Kii!.. I promise my master isn't
a bad person!... Let him go,
okay?
[KII]
Papi...
[PAPI] (huh?)
[KII]
Humans are the ones who brought
me to this place...
You may be
my friend... but I still hate
humans!
[KIMIHITO]
(scream)
[PAPI] Don't hurt him
[KIMIHITO]
Wait a minute... "Dryad" starts
with D!
Maybe she sent me that
death threat!
[PAPI]
(straining)Stop this, Kii!
(slapped)
[KIMIHITO]
Stay back, Papi!
[PAPI]
But this whole thing is all my
fault!
If hadn't forgotten about her...
she wouldn't be so angry!
That means I have to be the one
to stop her!(slapped)
[KIMIHITO]
Papi!
[PAPI]
(impact)(confused)
[KIMIHITO]
S‐Suu?! Now you're a big scary
giant too?!
[KIMIHITO]
(scream)
[SUU]
Master!... I believe Kii
ingested some of those toxic
nutrients... It's just a guess,
but that could be the reason for
her extreme increase in size.
[KIMIHITO]
Good guess...
[SUU]
If we can extract those
nutrients from her body,
it should be enough to stabilize
her.
[KIMIHITO]
So getting bigger made you
smarter too, huh?
[SUU]
(dodge)(punch)
[PAPI/KIMIHITO]
(hanging on)
[KIMIHITO]
How are we supposed to get that
stuff out of her?!
[PAPI]
Ugh... all this bouncing is
making me queasy...
[KIMIHITO/PAPI]
(bounce off)(scream)
[PAPI]
(falling)
[KII] (gasp)
[PAPI]
(mmmff...)Okay, let's see...
will this work?
[KII]
(startled)
[PAPI] (suckling)
[KIMIHITO]
Okay, that's a weird method...
but it looks like it's gonna
work at least!
[PAPI]
(gasp)(smooch exert x2)
Aw darn it, I can't quite reach
her!
Hey!... You'll have to take over
from here!
[KIMIHITO]
(shocked)
[PAPI]
(yelp)
Hurry!... I can't move,
and this
is kind of a bad position!
[SUU]
Master!
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, do I really have to?!
[PAPI]
Please, we need you!... Only you
can save her!
[KIMIHITO]
But‐!
[SUU] Quickly!... I can only
keep her restrained for a little
longer!
[KII/KIMIHITO]
(shy)
[KIMIHITO]
(determined)(reach)
(tongue‐out reach)(sucking)
[KII]
(moaning)(determined)
[SUU]
(huh? x2)(straining)
[ZOMBINA]
Jeez, I thought I was double
dead! I sure hope they're okay.
[ZOMBINA]
WHAT THE HELL?!
[KII/PAPI/SUU] (sex noises)
[PAPI]
Let me go...
[SUU] That's enough;
you're sucking me
dry...
[KII]
N‐no more...
[ZOMBINA]
(huh?)
[SMITH]
Well, that was quite an ordeal!
But it could have been worse.
Luckily there was no chance
of casualties out here in the
middle of the sticks anyway.
[SMITH]
Now then... This must be the
girl.
[PAPI/SUU]
(startled)
[KIMIHITO]
Wait a second!
[SMITH] (huh?)
[KIMIHITO]
It wasn't her fault... This all
happened
because of that illegal
waste, didn't it?
I think you
should punish the people who
dumped it,
not her!... She
couldn't help what she did!
[SMITH]
Oh, don't be so dramatic... I
have no intention to punish her.
[KIMIHITO]
(confused)
[SMITH]
She obviously wasn't
the person
who sent you that letter
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?)
[SMITH]
I saw her paperwork.
She can't write.
[KIMIHITO]
Ohhhh...
[SMITH]
Starting today,
Kii will live
here in this forest...
Don't worry, we'll take
care of that garbage that made
you mutate, okay?
[KII]
Thanks.
[SMITH]
Of course if you'd rather just
go back to your homeland, I'm
sure
we can arrange that...
How's that sound?
[PAPI/KII/SUU]
(listening)
[KII]
As long as Papi and Suu can come
and play with me,
I don't mind
staying here.
[PAPI]
(happy)
[SUU] (stare)
[KII]
But that guy doesn't have to
come.
[KIMIHITO]
Me?!
[SMITH]
What did you do?, Out with it.
[KIMIHITO]
(awkward)
[KII]
On the other hand,
you guys seem to really
like that human for some
reason...
[KIMIHITO]
But I didn't really have a
choice,
I mean, she was gonna...
What makes him so special?
[PAPI/SUU]
Um...
... because he's nice!
[KII]
That's true, I guess the way he
sucked on my boobs was nice and
gentle...
[KIMIHITO]Did you really have
to bring that up?!
[SMITH]
Wow, Darling, you disgust
me sometimes.
[KIMIHITO](Under)
Look, it's not what you think,
okay?
[ZOMBINA]
Always wondered what it'd be
like to be buried alive alive!
Well, except I'm dead...get me
outta here!
[CEREA]
Master, it's dangerous to walk
on the street side. Please stay
to my left if you don't mind.
[KIMIHITO]
Uh‐huh...
[GAL 10A]
Would you like to donate?
[CEREA]
I'll contribute something,
just stay
away from my Master!
[GAL 10A/GAL 10B]
(amazed)
[SHADY GUY 10A]
Hey buddy, you got a minute?
We've got the best girls in
town, you know‐(startled)
[CEREA]
He's not interested!
[KIMIHITO]
Hey!
(notice)
[CEREA]
Wait, Master, it could be
another threat. Allow me.
[CEREA] Who's there?!
[MANAKO]
(startled)Th‐this is Manako,
I'm the surveillance agent.
I'm watching you two from on top
of a tall building, and um...
[CEREA]
Do you see danger?!
[MANAKO]
Well, it's nothing dangerous
exactly... But.. I should bring
it to your attention‐
[CEREA]
What?! Is there an enemy?! I'll
strike it down immediately!
[MANAKO]
It's just, you're supposed to be
staging a date to draw out the
culprit... but... that armor
you're wearing doesn't really
scream "romantic outing"...
[CEREA]
Don't be absurd!
We still don't know anything
about this "D" character!
I HAVE to be in full armor to
keep Master safe!
For all we know, the letter "D"
could stand for Dastardly Devil
of Death!
[MANAKO]
I don't think an evil overlord
like that would hang out in
Japan... (shriek)
[CEREA]
It's just an example!
And besides, I'm PROUD to go out
in full armor!
[KIMIHITO]
Um... okay but..
at least
take off your helmet.
I think it's making some people
concerned.
[CEREA]
I can't decline a request from
my Master... Still!
For as long as I am by your side
today,
I swear to you, I will
never allow
anyone to harm a
single hair upon your noble
head!
[KIMIHITO]
Wow, what's got Cerea so fired
up?
I mean, she always talks
like that, but today she seems
especially... intense.
[MANAKO]
I sure hope this works...
[LILITH]
Hey, there.
[MANAKO] (shriek)
[LILITH]
What are you doing up on the
roof all by yourself, lady?
[LILITH]
Whoa, you're packing heat!
[MANAKO]
H‐hello there... What brings you
up here, young la‐ (OM gasp)
[MANAKO/LILITH]
(shriek)
[LILITH]
One‐eyed monster!
[MANAKO]
Children are always afraid of
me.
There's no place for
monoeyes in this world.
[LILITH]
Other non‐humans are so easy to
play with.
I can't have her getting in the
way of my playdate
with my favorite
goofy Centaur, now can I?
(giggle)
'Cause For Lilith the adorable
Devil girl..
humans and
non‐humans alike are nothing but
helpless playthings!
Now then, what kind of game
should we play together first?
[CEREA]
(exert)(extended struggle)
[KIMIHITO]
(panic)Don't hurt yourself,
okay?!
[CEREA]
I must!... I can't leave you
unsupervised, Master!
[KIMIHITO]
Uh... Let's just do outdoor
stuff then.
[CEREA]
(awkward)I'm so sorry...
[KIMIHITO/SALESGIRL10A
(stunned)
[CEREA]
Ah!... How terrible!(fretting)
[KIMIHITO]
Cerea! You okay?
[CEREA] I‐I'm fine!(wince)
[KIMIHITO] (knocked aside)
[KIMIHITO]
Balls
POLT
(running)(sigh)
(pant x2)Ahhh...
[CEREA]
I apologize for earlier.
[KIMIHITO]
Eh, don't mention it... Anyway,
I'm getting hungry now... Did
you say you made lunch?
[CEREA]
It's nothing special, but I did
prepare something.
[KIMIHITO]
Wow, that looks great!
[CEREA]
Ooh..umm..well. You always cook
for me,
so I thought I'd make
something to show my thanks,
despite not being much of a
cook.
[KIMIHITO]
Oh, they're tuna sandwiches.
Alright, let's dig in! (chewing)
[CEREA]
I hope they taste good...
I don't use bizarre ingredients
like Miia does.
[CEREA]
How is it, Master?
[KIMIHITO]
Oh! Uhhh, it's pretty good!
I.. It has kind of a subtle
flavor to it...
I bet they're good for you!
[CEREA]
Y‐yes they are! I try to be
conscious about what I eat, so
I'm glad you like them!
[RACHNELA]
My, Centorea... Did you taste
them?
[CEREA] You!
[KIMIHITO] Rachne... Why are you
here?
[RACHNELA]
These don't taste like anything,
dear.
[CEREA]
(gasp)
[KIMIHITO] (awkward)
[RACHNELA]
Honey was just trying not to
hurt your feelings.
[CEREA]
Is that true?
[KIMIHITO]
N‐no! Uh...
I‐I don't think it
tastes BAD or anything.
[RACHNELA]
If you enjoy eating paper bags.
[CEREA]
Well... You see, Centaurs can
only eat vegetables,
so... I‐I
couldn't sample the whole
sandwich before serving it.
[CEREA]
I failed.
[RACHNELA]
Here, have some salt.
[KIMIHITO]
Why do you have that?
[CEREA]
I'm sorry, I need to go clear my
head.
[KIMIHITO/RACHNELA]
(concerned)
[CEREA]
(troubled)(sigh)
[LILITH]
Hey! Pony girl!
[CEREA]
(surprised)
[LILITH]
You're one of those Centaur
things, aren't you? So what
are you up to out here?
[CEREA]
To tell the truth... I don't
know what I'm doing. (sad)
I simply wanted to repay my
Master for everything he does
for me, but all I can do is ruin
everything I touch.
No matter what I do, I'm useless
to him...
I'm not worthy to
stand by his side.
Oh.. I'm so sorry, that was
inappropriate...
Just forget
it... I was‐(surprised, into
gasp)
[CEREA] (confused)
[LILITH] I'm sure that's not
true?
[LILITH]
Think about it a little harder..
I'm sure there's SOMETHING you
can do to make your master
happy,
isn't there, my little
horsey friend?
[KIMIHITO]
Cerea? Hey!
Where did you disappear
to?(notice)
There you are. Uh... what's
wrong?
That hurt... What's up with you?
Uh... please say something.
[KIMIHITO]
(freak out)(stammering
under)
[CEREA]
I've heard that human males
prefer females with larger
breasts, so I thought you might
take pleasure in fondling mine.‐
Though I hope they aren't TOO
large for you, Master...
[KIMIHITO]
Ah!.. Well I mean, no, they're
not too big,
but that's not
really the problem here!
[CEREA]
Right, I apologize...
I shouldn't have withheld myself
from you...
Forgive me;
I was too proper.
[KIMIHITO]
This is like seven different
kinds of problematic
I‐I can't get away!
[CEREA]
Yes, that's it, Master...
Touch my body
in any manner you please.
[KIMIHITO]
(freak out)
[CEREA]
(panting)
[KIMIHITO]
Uh‐oh, they're so soft, I'm
starting to lose
consciousness... My hands are
moving on their own now!
[LILITH]
(giggle)
What a riot!...
I only hypnotized
her a little bit, and now she's
throwing herself at him!
(giggle)
Oh man, I bet they'll go all the
way right here in the park!
(hm?)
Hey, who's back there?... Don't
be so loud!
If they see me‐(stunned)
[LILITH]
(shriek)
[KIMIHITO]
(OM dazed sit up)
[CEREA/KIMIHITO]
(huh?)(OM startled)
BOAR(Under)
(running)
[LILITH]
W‐why would there be a wild boar
in a place like this?!
[KIMIHITO]
Hey, you big pig!... Slow down!
BOAR
(running)(OM enraged)
(impact)
[KIMIHITO]
Sorry, pal...
BOAR
(angry)
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?)
BOAR
(preparing)(charge)
[KIMIHITO]
Dammit, now it's after ME!
POLT
(running)
[KIMIHITO]
Whooooaaa!... You were awesome
back there, Cerea!...
Thank you.. You saved me.
[CEREA]
There's nothing to be impressed
about.
[KIMIHITO] You don't have to be
so humble about it
[CEREA] Yes I do!
[CEREA]
Master... all I want is to be of
use to you but... I'm
constantly causing you more
trouble.
The only time I can aid you is
when I'm cleaning up a mess that
I made.
I'm just not worthy to stand by
your side and call myself your
servant
but I want you to be
able to depend on me... no
matter what you may need.
I'm so sorry I failed you,
Master.
[KIMIHITO] Okay.
[CEREA]
(surprised)W... what are you...?
[KIMIHITO]
Well, it turns out I was so
surprised by that boar
that I twisted my ankle... I
hate to bug you, but could you
give me a ride home?
[CEREA]
Mmm... well um... I could...
it's just...
I told you... I'm only useful
when I've already inconvenienced
you...
[KIMIHITO]
That's not true.
[CEREA] (panic)
[KIMIHITO]
I count on you more than you
know... All the time.
[CEREA]
Oh, Master...
[SATSUKE]
Hey, uh, we got a call about a
loose animal around
here...(surprised)
[SATSUKE]
What the hell?! Why is this...
[RACHNELA]
Let's see now... Whatever am I
to do with you, my sweet
little... what was it?...
Lilith?
[RACHNELA]
I can't let you go in case
you're the culprit
Oh dear,
you seem frightened!... How
adorable.
[LILITH]
Oh, you think I'm scared?...
Kinda seems like you're the one
who's scared around here.
You act like some kind of tough
black widow chick
who's got
everybody wrapped up in your
web...
But the truth is, you're too
afraid to open up and show
people who you really are.
Sure you can act like you don't
care,
but you really just can't
handle rejection. That sound
about right
You're worried about what
humans are gonna think when they
see that creepy spider bottom
half of yours... aren't you?
All those eyes and you
can't see that you're the one
tangled up in a web of fear
(giggle)(surprised)
[RACHNELA]
Oh I see.
At first glance I thought you
were nothing but a loud‐mouthed
child... but you're a grown
woman.
[LILITH]
(scared)
[RACHNELA]
So that means I can give you an
adult punishment,
right?(laughs)(lick lips)
[LILITH]
(scream)
[CEREA]
I've found a way to reduce
Master's responsibilities.
Starting today, I'll be in
charge of preparing salad.
I want you all to clean your
plates, and don't be picky.
[MIIA]
Hey, not everybody's a herbivore
in this house, you know!
[PAPI]
Yeah, this is boring! I want some
meat! Come on!
[CEREA]
Don't bother!... I will be as
strict as the Master was
generous.. From this day
forward, you won't get a scrap
of meat until you finish every
bite of your vegetables!
[PAPI/MIIA]
No fair!
[MERO]
Well, I don't mind the change;
salads are quite healthy!
[KIMIHITO]
Thank you, Cerea... I can
never
get these ladies to eat their
vegetables.
[CEREA]
No... this is the least I can
do.
I always carried the weight of
the world on my shoulders.
I didn't want to accept that
there are some things I can't
handle.
[CEREA]
Therefore... from now on, I
promise to do whatever I CAN
do to the fullest!
Thank you, strange girl! Though
I can't quite remember all of
what you said...
[LILITH]
There's SOMETHING you can do...
[CEREA]
And in return.. I‐I'll ask for
help whenever I need it, Master.
Is that alright with you?
[KIMIHITO]
Sure thing. Anytime you want.
[CEREA]
(happy)(smile)
[LILITH]
(sexy panting)
[RACHNELA]
So then... you're not "D" after
all...
Tell me, little imp... is
there anything else you're
hiding?...
Or perhaps you've
been lying to me?
[LILITH]
Oh no, mistress, I wouldn't
dream of
keeping anything from
you!
So could you please let
me have my reward now?!
[RACHNELA]
(chuckle)
[LILITH] (pleasured squeal)
[CEREA]
What do you think you're
doing?!...
You have to eat it
yourselves!
[PAPI]
Finish every bite!
[ZOMBINA]
Oh, by the way......
you're going on a hot
date with us today.
[KIMIHITO]
Huh?
[ZOMBINA]
Check this out.
[KIMIHITO]
Oh great, another creepy letter.
[LALA]
It's you. You're going to die...
very soon.