[Women]
Welcome home, Master!
It's great to see you!
(cafe chatter)
[SMITH]
Darling!
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, hey Smith. Why are we
meeting at a maid cafe?
[SMITH]
Why not? I've always wanted to
check these things out.
[KIMIHITO]
Uh‐huh...
[SMITH]
Aw, what's wrong?... Not a fan?
[KIMIHITO] (surprised)
N‐no... it's okay.
[SMITH] (giggle)
MAID 9A
Just let me know when you're
ready to order, okay, Master?
[SMITH]
Excuse me, miss, could we get
two coffees over here?
[SATSUKE]
Ahhh... I'm so glad I'm finally
off duty today‐
[MIIA]
(fuming)
[SATSUKE]
(startled)
Not again!
[MIIA]
Is he on a date with Smith?!
How dare he cheat on me?!
[CEREA]
We can't tell anything for
certain yet.
[MERO]
We need to go in and find out
for ourselves.
That's the only
way to be sure.
[CEREA]
Yes, you're right... but I think
it's fair to say none of us
exactly blend in.
[MIIA]
What if we wore disguises?
[CEREA]
We don't have anything on hand.
Then again I suppose Suu
is kind
of a walking disguise.
[MIIA/MERO/CEREA]
(realize)
[PAPI] (huh?)
[SMITH]
Ugh, great... This is cheap
instant coffee.
[KIMIHITO]
I'm sure, but maybe you
shouldn't say it so loud.
MAN 9A/MAN 9B
Whoaaaa!(OM goofy mesmerized,
laughing)
[MERO]
Thank you for your order,
Masters, I'll bring that right
out.
[MERO]
It'll just be a moment.
[KIMIHITO]
Mero?
[MERO]
Oh? Is there a maid
you'd
like to request?
[KIMIHITO]
Uh... no... Sorry...
I thought
you were, uh...
[SMITH]
Oh, don't be ridiculous,
Darling.
Mero has a fish tail.
[KIMIHITO]
Yeah... I just thought it might
be...
[SMITH]
Under the dress?(laugh)
[MERO]
I succeeded!... They didn't
find me out.
[CEREA]
Hey!.. Quiet!
[MIIA]
Keep your voice down
or they
might catch you!
[CEREA]
(troubled)Anyway,
I think it's
going well so far.
[MIIA]
This would probably be a lot
more effective if we let Suu
take over.
Okay, Mero, see if you can get
some incriminating evidence on
those two!
[MERO]
I'll see what I can
do.(startled, into trip)
[MAN 9C]
(startled)(Foley)Careful!...
Watch where you're‐
[MERO]
Oh dear... I hope you'll excuse
my clumsiness, Master...
[MAN 9C]
Eheheh... sure thing,
baby.
[MIIA]
Uh, Mero? You can drop the maid
act now.
[MERO]
But I've already got a
backstory!
A noble stripped of her title...
who disguises herself as a
housemaid just so she can be
closer to her forbidden love!
[MIIA]
That's not what we're here for,
tragedy addict!
[MERO]
Tragedy addict?... Well, you
don't have to be so harsh..
[MIIA]
just keep a close eye on
Darling, alright?!
[SMITH]
That was nice. Perfect start for
our date... What's next?
[MERO]
(shocked) It IS a date!
[SMITH](Under)
I'm open to suggestions...
[MERO]
N‐no, perhaps Miss Smith is just
forcing him to go with her. Yes,
of course!
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, you're making me kinda
nervous.
[MERO]
He's not objecting to it!
[MIIA] Mero? What's going on?
[SMITH] Don't worry, I'll show
you what to do.
[MERO]
Well, actually...
(surprised)(gasp)
[SMITH/KIMIHITO]
(hm?)
[MERO]
S‐Suu, what are you doing?
(bothered noises)( panting)
[MERO]
Oh, it's my sweat!... I forgot,
when Suu gets dehydrated, she'll
attack anything for water!
This isn't good... If I make too
much noise, the master will
surely hear me!
Oh? I'm not sweating anymore,
now it's just...
(startled)I‐I lost control...
ah.. ah.. aaaahhhh!
MAID 9A
Here's your receipt, thank you!
[SMITH]
Thanks.
You ready to go now, Darling?
[KIMIHITO]
Oh... Y‐yeah!
MAID 9A/MAID 9B/MAID 9C/MAID
Have a wonderful day, Master!
[WALLA:General]
(cosplay event chatter)
[COSPLAY GIRL 9A]
You'll love this game!
[COSPLAY GIRL 9B]
Yeah, pick up your copy today!
[SMITH]
It must be some kind of costume
party.
[KIMIHITO]
It's an event for a new game, I
think. (hm?)
[SMITH]
Hey Darling... Mind if we stop
in here for a sec?
I'll show you how great I am at
crane games.
[KIMIHITO]
Hmm...She's got hands and big
boobs... Can't be her.
[SMITH]
Are you coming?
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, yeah!
[MIIA]
That was close!... I don't think
they're onto us though.
[CEREA]
I have to admit, it's strange to
see Papi with arms and breasts.
[MIIA]
Oh no! Where'd he go?
WALLA: General
(arcade chatter)
[KIMIHITO]
Wow, you're a pro at that!
[SMITH]
What did I tell you?(OM look)
I think we should find someplace
quieter.
[PAPI]
(startled)Where's the phone?‐ I
need to tell Miia!
I dropped it!
Come on, Suu, help me get it
out!
MAN 9E
(huh?)(shock)
[PAPI]
Come on... I need it...(OM exert
x2)
Okay, almost got it...(exert)
MAN 9FMAN 9GMAN 9HMAN 9E
(surprised)
[PAPI]
Ah... I have to call the others
before it's too late!
Suu... It's moving... Stop it
before it comes out!
(squeal)Suu... it's close to my
butt...
(gasp)
How deep is it gonna go?...
I don't know how far I can
reach...
Just a... little more... ah!
Hurry up... I don't have much
time!(fidgeting)
Oh no! Nooo!
[PAPI]
(gasping)
[CEREA]
What's taking her?... I should
give her a call.
[PAPI]
(OM gasp)(OM scream)
[SMITH]
That wasn't a smart move.
I can't really call crane games
a work expense.
We should head out.
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, yeah... Huh.
[SMITH]
(sigh)It's good to sit down.
[KIMIHITO]
I've got an idea..
I'll go get
us some ice cream.
[SMITH]
I'll take coffee flavor!
[KIMIHITO]
You love your coffee, don't you?
Hey uh... one vanilla... and one
coffee flavor please. (hm?)
[MIIA/CEREA]
Coming right up, sir!
[KIMIHITO]
Oh man... everybody looks
familiar today.
[MIIA/CEREA]
Thank you for your business!
[MIIA]
We did it!.. He's clueless!
[CEREA]
We were lucky to find this
unattended truck.
[SALESMAN 9A]
Agh, my stomach! I'm gonna be in
here for a while...
[MIIA]
And no one can see our bottom
halves!
[CEREA]
Yeah well these clothes are a
little tight though.
[MIIA]
Sorry, there's not enough Suu to
make two outfits.
[CEREA] So we're stuck being
tied together. [SATSUKE](Under)
Dude, get down here...
[MIIA]
It's all up to you and me now.
[KIMIHITO]
Here you go.
[SMITH]
That's so sweet of you, Darling.
[KIMIHITO] No trouble.
[MAN 9J]
Is this it?
MAN 9K
The ice cream truck with the hot
chicks?!
[MIIA][CEREA]
(startled)
WALLA: Men
Milk Flavor! Milk Flavor!
[SMITH] (annoyed)That's it...
I've had it.
[SMITH] Let's go, Darling!
[WALLA: Men] Milk Flavor! Milk
Flavor!
[MIIA]
They're on the move!(realize)
Are they gonna...?!
I'm sorry... but I'm leaving
this to you. Come on, Suu!
[CEREA]
(huh)Miia, wait!
Our clothes are connected!... If
you pull too hard it'll come
off!
Miia stop!
WALLA: Men
(big cheer)
[MIIA] (sigh)
Kept you waiting, huh?... I've
arrived at the sneak point.
I kill me...(surprised)
[RACHNELA]
Looks like age...
hasn't slowed you down one bit.
[RACHNELA]
That was fun.
[MIIA]
(gasp)Rachnela?! Why are you
here?!
[RACHNELA]
I've been following you, of
course.
A love hotel in the daytime.
Smith sure has a lot of energy.
[RACHNELA]
(giggle)
[SMITH]
Don't worry, Darling... Just
leave everything to me, okay?
[RACHNELA]
Found them.
[MIIA]
So?... What's your deal?... Here
to watch?
[RACHNELA]
I'm here to get something.
[MIIA]
Yeah?‐ What's that?
[RACHNELA]
Not much... just blackmail
material.
If he's schtupping her...then
there's going to be a serious
conflict of interest for us...
I'm just looking out for our
well‐being.
Now then...
[MIIA] (surprised)Wait a sec!
[MIIA]
There's no way Darling would
cheat on me!
There has to be a good
explanation!
[RACHNELA]
You're choking me!
[MIIA]
He's not doing anything, so you
don't need to go in there,
okay?!
[RACHNELA]
(choking)that doesn't make
any sense at all!
Stop screaming or we'll get
caught!
[MIIA]
Whatever, take me up there!
[RACHNELA/MIIA] (huh?)(shriek)
[RACHNELA/MIIA]
(confused x2)
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, hey guys... This is
awkward... What's going on?
[MIIA/RACHNELA]
uhh huh?
[SMITH]
Sorry I didn't tell you.
[MIIA]
You've got some explaining to
do!
[CEREA]
Start from the beginning!
[SMITH]
If you say so...
Take a
look at this.
[SMITH]
Darling received an interesting
letter.
[CEREA/RACHNELA/MERO/PAPI]
(hm?)
[CEREA/MIIA/MERO/PAPI]
(surprised)
[RACHNELA]
Looks like a murder threat!
[SMITH]
Exactly... So we decided to
stage a date, thinking that
might help lure out the
culprit... I guess they weren't
convinced.
[CEREA]
Oh, dear.
[SMITH]
So...I have a favor to ask of
you girls.
[KIMIHITO]
(hm?)
[MIIA]
What's that?
[SMITH]
Until we find who did this...
would you mind going on a few
dates?
[CEREA/PAPI/MIIA/MERO/KIMIHITO]
(surprised)What?!
[SMITH]
(smile)
[MIIA]
(happy humming)I can't believe
I'm on a date with Darling!...
Just the two of us!
At least I THOUGHT it was. Why
did Mero have to come with us
again?
[KIMIHITO]
Miia, calm down.
[MIIA]
(squeal)But it's supposed to be
a date! She can't come!
[MIIA/Under)
(sobbing)
[MERO]
Please don't cry, Miia!
[MIIA]
(hm?)
[MERO]
I only want to be Master's
mistress, remember?
I'm more
than happy to support you in
becoming his REAL lover!
[MIIA]
A... are you sure?
[MERO]
Leave it all to me!... I'll do
everything I can to make sure
you two live happily ever after!
[MIIA]
Well, it's not like I'm gonna
say no to that.
[KIMIHITO]
Be serious, you guys...
We're
here to catch the person who
wrote that letter.
[KIMIHITO]
Don't lose focus‐(huh?)
[TIO]
(giggle)(surprised)
Oops! Pretend I don't know
them...
[KIMIHITO]
I appreciate them giving us a
bodyguard...
but she
kinda stands out.
WALLA: General
Lady Mero... let us welcome
you.
Thank you for your
patronage. Have a great day.
[MERO]
Thank you for having us.
[MAN 9L]
Of course!
[MIIA]
They just let her in on sight?!
Is it because she's a mermaid?!
[KIMIHITO]
Now we stand out even MORE.
[MERO]
Be sure to use this,
alright?
It'll get you in free
anywhere.
[MIIA]
Wow, thank you.
[MERO]
I think I'll go visit the
freshwater fish display.
You two enjoy the
aquarium on your own. Farewell!
[KIMIHITO]
Bye, be careful.
[MIIA]
I think she might've done that
just to be nice.
A free pass for every aquarium
in the world?!
Darling! Look over here!
[KIMIHITO]
(hm?)
[MIIA]
Those fish look like they're
kissing, don't they?
[KIMIHITO]
Mhmm... Wonder what that is...
Are they courting?
[MIIA]
Maybe they're boyfriend and
girlfriend! It's cute!
[MIIA]
(realize)
[KIMIHITO] (realize)(look)
[MERO]
Of course not!
Both of them are male!
[MIIA/KIMIHITO]
(startled)
[MERO]
When two of them fight over
territory...
they look like
they're kissing. That's why
they're called Kissing Gourami‐
[MIIA] (angry)
Mero!... You just ruined the
moment!‐
You were
supposed to be helping me!
[MERO]
Oh, I'm sorry! Sometimes I can't
help but recite fish trivia!
I know some interesting facts
about sea snakes!
[MIIA]
Just save it.
[MERO] For example, there are 62
species of sea snake, starting
with‐
[MIIA]
NOBODY CARES!
(pant x2)Jeez, Mero... why'd you
have to go and kill the mood
with your dumb fish facts...
[WOMAN 9A]
Thank you all for visiting the
aquarium!
[MIIA] Hey wait, where
did she go?
[WOMAN 9A]
For today's show we have a very
special guest!
[KIMIHITO]
The dolphin show's getting ready
to start now.
[WOMAN 9A]
Why don't you come on out and
say hi?
[MERO]
Thank you!
Hello there!
[KIMIHITO/MIIA]
She's on stage?!
[WOMAN 9A]
Meet Lady
Meroune... She's a real live
mermaid... and she's swimming
with our dolphins today!
[LIL GIRL 9A] They have mermaids
here? [LIL GIRL 9B] I've never
seen one!
[MIIA]
(realize)Wait... If the perp is
watching,
she shouldn't draw
attention to herself!
[MERO]
Miia!
I hope you both enjoy the
show...
I promise I won't ruin
the mood now!
[MIIA/KIMIHITO]
(shocked)
WALLA: General
(cheers, amazed)
[KIMIHITO/MIIA]
(amazed)
WALLA: General
(cheering, happy)
[WOMAN 9A]
Thanks for watching the show!
Come on down and see the
dolphins up close!
[KIMIHITO]
(hm?)
Miia?... She's gone.
[MAN 9M]
I heard there's a mermaid here.
[MIIA]
He just can't stop staring at
her.
Ugh! It's all her fault!
[MIIA]
Here to help.. yeah, my tail!
(surprised)
[DRACO]
(gyaaah!)(frantic fixing)
[MIIA]
I'm so sorry! Huh? A tail?
[DRACO]
No, it's okay... Oh.
It's rare to see a non‐human
girl...
I'm sorry. I guess I was
a little distracted.
[MIIA]
I wonder what species he is. A
Lizardman maybe?
[DRACO]
It's cold in here.
My body temperature's kinda
low...
That must be why I'm so
out of it today.
[MIIA]
Yeah, I know what you mean!
Whenever the AC's on, I feel
like I could start hibernating
right there!
[DRACO]
I can't even go to the frozen
section at the grocery store.
[MIIA]
Me neither!
[DRACO]
Oh... here, take this. It'll
help warm you up.
[MIIA]
(surprised)
Wow, thank you.
[DRACO]
You seemed pretty upset.
Everything okay?
[MIIA]
Yeah.. I'm fine.
[DRACO]
Man... they keep this place so
cold.
You want to go out in
the sun for a while?
[MIIA]
Uh, sure.
[TIO]
Yeah, Miia just walked off with
some good‐looking guy...
WOMAN 9B(Under)
Ma'am? I'm sorry but you
[TIO]
Do you think I should follow
them?
I don't know, isn't it
more important to make sure
Darling doesn't get left alone
while the culprit's on the
loose?
[WOMAN 9B]
It'll die. Please give it back
[TIO] Besides, I'm having fun.
[SMITH]
It's possible Darling's not the
one they're after.
[TIO] Huh?
[SMITH] It could be he's got his
eye on those girls...
He probably sees
Darling as competition for their
love.
[TIO]
Uh‐oh...
[MIIA]
The wind's a little chilly
today.
[DRACO]
Take my jacket.
[MIIA]
Oh, thanks a lot.
[DRACO]
I can't believe what a jerk that
guy is.
He should know better than to
bring another girl on a date
with you.
[MIIA]
(surprised)
No, Darling's not a jerk at all.
[DRACO] (hm?)
[MIIA]
He's a really sweet person;
he just wants
to take good care of ALL of us.
[DRACO]
But if he really cared about
you,
why would he leave you
alone like that?
[MIIA]
No, Mero's the one to blame
here!
She said she wanted to
help me out, but all she did was
show off!
[MIIA]
But Darling's so nice.
He didn't want to abandon
someone who needed him.
That's
one of the things I love about
him.
[DRACO]
(annoyed)Stop talking about
that scumbag!
[MIIA]
W‐what?!
[DRACO]
What's
so great about that loser?
He has
everything he could ever want
and he doesn't even care!
[MIIA] Don't yell...
[DRACO] I think you should be
with me instead.
[MIIA]
Umm huh?
[DRACO]
We have a lot more in
common anyway.
I think we would
be great together.
As for your friend... it'll be
easy to get him out of the way.
[MIIA] (gasp)
[DRACO]
Who better to understand you
than someone of your own kind
right?
[MIIA]
Wait a second, Lamias and
Lizardmen
are kind of similar,
but I don't know if‐
[DRACO]
You think I'm a Lizardman? No,
I'm something much better!
[MIIA]
(gasp)
[DRACO]
I'm the greatest...
no...... I'm
the KING of all species!
A proud royal descendant of
the dragons themselves...Bow
before Draco the Dragonewt!
[MIIA]
Dragonewt... D! He must be the
one who send that letter!
[DRACO]
Now just be still and do
everything I say!
[MIIA]
(gasp)(shoved)
[DRACO]
I've been watching you, you
know.
[MIIA](Under)
(trembling)
[DRACO]
And now...I can finally make you
mine.
[MIIA]
Darling... please, I need you!
[DRACO]
(gasp)
Huh?... Who's there?!
[MIIA]
(muffled surprised)
[KIMIHITO]
(battle cry)GET AWAY FROM
MIIAAAA!
[MIIA]
It's Darling!
[DRACO]
What is that idiot doing?
Is he
trying to crash that thing right
into us?!
Agh... I better dodge him
quick! Wait, what?!
Where'd the oars go?!(gasp)
[MERO](Under)
(laugh)
[KIMIHITO]
(big scream)
Are you okay, Miia?
[MIIA]
Uh‐huh...
(sneeze)(shiver)
[KIMIHITO]
Take this.
[MIIA]
(look)Oh, thank you, Darling.
[KIMIHITO/MIIA]
(look) (laughing)
[DRACO]
YOU LITTLE!
Get your filthy hands off my
bride this minute,
you pitiful
human!... You're nothing but
trash!‐
You could never compare
to‐
[MIIA]
Give it a rest, would ya?!
[DRACO]
That was my face (sneeze)
[KIMIHITO]
Come on now.
If you keep those wet clothes
on, you might accidentally
hibernate.
You should take them off and
warm up in the sun.
[DRACO]
Go away!... Don't touch me!...
What's wrong with you?!
[KIMIHITO]
Wait... There.
[DRACO]
(freak out)
[KIMIHITO] (shocked)
[MIIA] (shocked)So you're a
girl?!
[DRACO]
How could you?!
All I wanted was a friend...
Somebody who's a reptile species
just like me!
[MIIA]
Then why did you call me your
bride?
[KIMIHITO]
Do you always take your friends'
clothes off?
[DRACO]
Men are such savages!‐ This is
why I hate them!
[KIMIHITO] Whoa...
[MIIA] Is that why you sent
Darling that nasty letter?
[DRACO]
What nasty letter?! What are you
talking about?!
[MIIA]
(hm?)
[KIMIHITO] (huh?)
[DRACO]
You disgust me! YOU
FILTHY HUMAAAAAN!
[MIIA]
(shudder)(notice)
What's in here?
[KIMIHITO]
(surprised)Uh, wait, don't open
it!
(uncertain)Let me see.
[MIIA] (hm?)
[KIMIHITO]
Turn around for a second.
[MIIA]
(surprised)Okay.
Darling! It's gorgeous... For
me?
[KIMIHITO]
Well, I saw it at the gift shop
and... uh...
I just thought it would look
pretty on you, that's all.
But then, I couldn't find the
right moment to...
(surprised)What's that for?
[MIIA]
(giggle)
You're always so sweet to me.
Thank you so much, Darling! I
love you!
[KIMIHITO]
(hm?)(scream)
[WOMAN 9B] I'm so sorry,
dolphins...
[SMITH] I see
someone went out without their
host family.
I'm letting you off easy
today...
But this is the last
time. Understand?
[DRACO]
You have not heard the last of
me! (struggling)
[SMITH]
So she isn't the culprit after
all. Who could it be?
[KIMIHITO]
Ugh... Why'd you say you wanted
to come here again?
[PAPI]
Me?... I never said anything
like that.
[CEREA]
For as long as I am by your side
today, I swear to you, I will
never allow anyone to harm a
single hair upon your noble
head!