[KIMIHITO]
(shocked)I‐I'm gonna die?
Come on... That's crazy talk.
[LALA]
No.Think of how many times
you've narrowly escaped your
death.
[KIMIHITO]
Well, yeah but‐
[LALA]
Don't waste your breath. My evil
eye of Balor sees the
fate of every man.
I am a Dullahan, a knight
of the underworld.
I've come to reap
your soul and take it
to‐(caught)
[RACHNELA]
No one's laying a finger on my
Honey... except for me, of
course.
[LALA]
(grunt)I am death incarnate!
This mortal thread of yours will
never stop his fate‐
[RACHNELA]
I'll handle her... You girls
protect Honey.
[CEREA]
Ah... Yes, of course! Papi! Take
the master somewhere safe!
[PAPI
Okay!(hup!)
[KIMIHITO]
(grabbed)(panicking)
(scream)Papi! You need to fly
higher!
[PAPI
(gasp)
[KIMIHITO]
Focus on what's in front of you!
[PAPI(Under)
(nervousness)(impact)
[KIMIHITO]
Keep your eyes on the
sky!(scream)
[SUU]
(catch)(smile)
[KIMIHITO]
(guhhh...)
[MIIA]
Nice one, Suu!
Keep saving him... We need your
help more than ever!(panting)
[SUU]
More than ever?
[KIMIHITO]
Yeah, thanks again,
Suu‐(drowning)
[MIIA]
Darling!
[PAPI]
Owwie.‐ I forgot I can't see so
well at night [time].
[CEREA]
Look what you're doing to him!
[MERO]
Oh, I do hope you're alright,
Master!
[KIMIHITO]
(OM pant x4)
[MIIA][CEREA][MERO]
She was right...
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?)
[WALLA: General]
(screams, terror)
[KIMIHITO]
(aagh!)(OM scream)
[MIIA/CEREA/MERO]
He really is at death's door!
[KIMIHITO]
Would you guys just relax?...
You're imagining things.
[CEREA]
I'll protect you from anything,
even fate!
I thought this might happen, so
I've prepared a saddle for
traveling long distances.
[CEREA]
This way, Master and I can run
as far away as necessary!
Traditionally, it's a great
dishonor for a knight to flee in
the face of danger...
... but a true knight knows
today's dishonor is tomorrow's
victory!
And if it ensures my Master's
safety, I'll pay the price!
[MIIA]
Wow, Centorea!
[KIMIHITO]
Uhhh...
[MERO]
Running off into the sunset
together is very romantic!...
How touching!
[CEREA]
(startled) Well, I'll leave the
rest to you, Miia!
[MIIA]
(huh?) Hey!... That's no fair!
[RACIST GUY] (laughing)Yeeha!
[RACIST GIRL] See how fast we
can go!
[RACIST GUY]
Good thing this baby's insured!
Whoa, what the hell?!
[CEREA]
You won't die, especially at
THEIR hands!
[KIMIHITO]
(holding on)(land)
[CEREA]
Tarnishing my proud name...
leaving my home...
All to preserve my Master's
life! It's honor through
dishonor!
This is legendary!
The knight and her master travel
far and wide to elude their
pursuers...
in search of a place
where they can live in peace...
forever and ever!
Then one day...... they realize
an unbreakable bond of love has
been forged between them!
(happy)Goodness, I've let myself
get carried away!
[KIMIHITO]
(struggling)
[CEREA]
Oh no, I'm sorry, Master!
[KIMIHITO]
(scream)(impact)
[CEREA]
Are... you alright?
[KIMIHITO]
Never been better...
[CEREA]
I don't believe this...
Normally,
I'd never make a
mistake like that. This means
not even I can protect him!
[LALA]
You're right; nobody can.
[CEREA]
(scream)You! How long have you
been...?!
[LALA]
Such a foolish mortal.‐ Just as
you can never escape
the call of
death, neither can you escape
from my sights.
[CEREA]
Quick, Master, you must run
away!... Leave this to me!
[KIMIHITO]
Listen, can't we talk about
this?(OM yanked, scream)
[CEREA]
Mero! Well then, I suppose I can
give you my full attention!
[LALA]
(surprise)
[KIMIHITO]
Agh!... Mero, wait!...
Are you trying to
drown me?!‐ I don't have gills
like you do, remember?(hit)
[MERO]
Oh, Master!
[KIMIHITO]
(gasp for air)That was a close
one...
[MERO]
Master? I'd like to request
something of you.
I was thinking, since you're
going to pass away any time now
and there's nothing we can do to
stop it...
[KIMIHITO]
You accepted that awful
quickly...
[MERO]
I want you to leave behind a
token of our tragic love that I
can treasure forever!
[KIMIHITO]
A token?
[MERO]
Yes!
So I can remember you... every
day.
[KIMIHITO]
Wait... you mean... OH, haha..
for a second I thought you
wanted me to, uh... I dunno,
make a baby with you or
something
weird like that... But
that would be insane‐
[MERO]
Yes, that's exactly what I want.
[KIMIHITO]
(floored)
[MERO]
Ah.. a child born after your
death...
Think of it; the idea
is so terribly heartbreaking and
yet it's so inspirational at the
same time!
[KIMIHITO]
Stop assuming I'm gonna
die!(startled)
[MERO]
Please, Master!.. I need you to
fertilize my eggs as soon as
possible!
I'll help you create a legacy
that will live on forever!
[KIMIHITO]
Pull yourself together, tragedy
addict!
Listen, Mero! Just because that
girl SAYS I'm at death's door
doesn't mean I‐
[MERO]
It's alright, no one can see us
underwater... Are you ready?
[KIMIHITO]
Do I LOOK ready to you?!
[MERO]
Master... it's time to do it.
I'm new at this, so please be
patient with me.
[KIMIHITO]
Oh god... I‐I'm blacking
out...(OM look)
[MERO]
P‐pardon me... It's true that
I'm a mermaid...
but I can't
breathe underwater... Please let
go...
[MIIA]
Hey!.. Darling!.. Are you okay?
You need to cough up the water!
[KIMIHITO]
(dazed)(choke)
[MIIA]
That's not gonna work!
[KIMIHITO]
(thrown down)
[MIIA]
This is bad... This is really
REALLY bad!
No matter what we do
to help him, we keep putting
Darling's life in danger!
[MIIA]
(surprised, into shriek)
(stunned)
[MIIA]
Rachne?! Don't tell me you're on
her side!
[RACHNELA]
You girls just don't get it, do
you?
[MIIA]
(huh?)
[RACHNELA]
Try as we might, we'll never
save Honey from his fate...
Knowing that...
... wouldn't it be best to go
ahead and put him out of his
misery now?
there's no need to delay the
inevitable
Dullahan... use that scythe to
do what must be done.
[MIIA]
Wait!
[RACHNELA]
(hm?)
[MIIA]
Don't take him away from me!
If you're gonna kill him now...
then you'll just have to kill me
too!
[RACHNELA]
I can tell you're trying your
best to be tough,
but you're
shaking like a fly in a web.
[MIIA]
Sh‐shut up!
I mean, do you guys honestly
expect me to let you do this?...
This person just showed up out
of nowhere and now she's going
to take my Darling's life!
And there's nothing I can do!
At least let me die too, so we
can be together in heaven.
[RACHNELA][LALA]
(troubled)
[KIMIHITO]
(coughing)
[MIIA]
Darling!
[KIMIHITO]
Come on...
You seriously believe
I'm gonna die?
[KIMIHITO]
Just because this random girl
said so?
[LALA]
(pout)
[RACHNELA]
(hm?)
[KIMIHITO]
(think)(think harder)
Miia.
[MIIA]
(huh?)
[KIMIHITO]
I'll come back...
and when I
do... I'll get married!
[MIIA]
(blush)Don't say that!
That's a death flag!
[KIMIHITO]
Let's split up; we can cover
more ground that way.
[MIIA]
Another one?!
[KIMIHITO]
Is it alright if I cross the
finish line now?
[MIIA]
When people say that stuff...
[KIMIHITO]
You mean stuff like, "You don't
mind
if I beat that thing,
right?"
[MIIA]
Yeah, they always die
afterwards!
[KIMIHITO] No problem.
Everything's fine. [MIIA] Stop
it!
I'm not afraid of anything
anymore.
Ow.
SATSUKE
My bad!
[KIMIHITO]
Are you satisfied now?
[RACHNELA][MIIA]
(confused)
[KIMIHITO]
I'm not about to die.
[RACHNELA]
So...
[MIIA]
She's not death incarnate?
[SMITH]
(laugh) What do you think this
is, a horror movie?... She's not
the grim reaper.
[KIMIHITO]
The detachable head's pretty
horrific...
[SMITH]
And you! You're never going to
run away like that again...
right...
... Lala?
[LALA]
Agh... How dare you address me
by my worldly name?
[RACHNELA][MERO][MIIA][CEREA]
Lala?
[SMITH]
I've been looking all over for
you.
[LALA]
I told you, I am death
incarnate...
Therefore, I am as
uncontrollable as death itself.
[SMITH]
Now why did you send Darling
that nasty letter?
[MIIA]
Don't tell me I have ANOTHER
rival to compete with!
[LALA]
It is impossible for the living
to escape death...
and, well...
being an executioner
aboveground,
I understand that
concept better than anyone else.
That being said... if a mortal
being was entitled to extra
territorial righ‐
[SMITH]
Just tell me what it is you came
here to do.
[LALA]
Mm... uh... Well, you see...
When I saw that man... I thought
it was so strange
how he was
always so close to death but
never died.
[MIIA]
Is that really your reason? I
don't get it.
[LALA]
What kind of harvester of souls
would I be if I were to overlook
something like that? His soul
was poised on the brink of
death;
I needed to ensure that
the job was done...
[SMITH]
Ensure the job was done? You're
lucky you didn't hurt Darling,
or there'd have been hell to
pay!
[KIMIHITO]
Why doesn't that make me feel
safe...?
[SMITH]
Every time we find a place for
you, you wind up missing.
[LALA]
Of course... Because no one
there is at death's door.
[SMITH]
You seriously think I'd let you
move in with someone who's about
to die?
[LALA]
It appears this agent from the
organization sees me as a
threat.
[KIMIHITO]
Oh, so the organization is Smith
and her crew.
[LALA]
Well then... I'm going to
stay right
here and observe this
human for a little longer.
[KIMIHITO] (huh?!)
[LALA] It shouldn't be a problem
if I move in with all of you.
[SMITH]
I'm fine with it!
[KIMIHITO]
Don't I get a say in this?!
[MIIA]
As long as she's not after
Darling.. sure.
[CEREA]
As long as she isn't really the
grim reaper after all.
[RACHNELA]
As long as I can tie her up
every once in a while.
[KIMIHITO]
Is that all it takes for you
guys?!
[SMITH]
I'm impressed, Darling. You were
able to see that it was all an
act.
Most people make up their minds
as soon as they take one look at
her.
[KIMIHITO]
Not me... I've gotten used to my
life being in danger.
Hm... You've got a point.
[KIMIHITO]
You know...She's just like
middle‐school me.
[LALA](Under)
I may not be the exact form of
death you perceived me to be...
[SMITH] Hold on...
[LALA] However, the Dullahans
Were you one of those weird kids
who pretended they had powers?
[LALA]
and that's much more terrifying!
[KIMIHITO] What? I have no idea
what you're talking about!
[LALA](Under)
But do not be afraid, mortals...
For death is only the beginning!
[KIMIHITO](14 y/o)
So, the final battle is
beginning.
Yes, it's me.It appears Ohama
would like to challenge our
power.
Oh, I already know... It's just
the kind of thing he'd do.
La... jodaso steana.
[KIMIHITO]
(sigh)
We're spending a fortune on
food.
These girls are eating me
out of house and home!
I was barely making ends meet
before...
... but with Lala here I don't
stand a chance.
It's gonna be tight this month.
I'll just have to make do with
what we've got.
Awesome...Hey Miia, any idea
what happened to all the
groceries?
[RACHNELA]
My goodness!‐ You were cooking
without tasting the food again,
weren't you, dear?...
Look what
you've done to poor Lala.
[MIIA]
I tasted it!
[KIMIHITO]
(sigh)Well... I think they're
having a sale at the
supermarket.
[KIMIHITO]
Of course. Today of all days.
[MIIA]
I wanted to go shopping with
Darling too!
[RACHNELA] Well somebody had to
finish the dishes,
and you did
make the mess! [MIIA](Under)
it's not fair!
[CEREA]
There's no helping it. We'll
have to go elsewhere.
(street/market chatter)
[MEAT SALESMAN]
Come on over! (ad‐libbed
meat‐selling under)
[MERO]
What a lively place this is!
[CEREA]
I've never been to an outdoor
market.
[KIMIHITO]
Eh, it's not all that exciting.
(hm??)
[FISH SALESMAN]
CLOSE UP THE SHOP, HURRY!
That
girl's a mermaid!‐ What if she
sees us selling fish?!
[MEAT SALESMAN]
There's a bird girl too! We have
to put away all this chicken!
[MEAT SALESMAN] Get rid of the
duck, honey!
[MEAT WIFE] Should
I do something about the horse
meat?!
MEAT SALESMAN/MEAT WIFE(Under)
(flailing, panicking)
[KIMIHITO]
It's okay, everybody! They eat
fish and poultry all the time!‐
Don't worry! It's fine
[MEAT SALESMAN]
(huh?!) Oh, well I had no idea.
[CEREA]
Well, I only eat vegetables...
[KIMIHITO]
(hm?)Mero?
FISH SALESMAN
Uhh hey...
[MERO]
My, the fish you sell here seem
to be very fresh.
They're so healthy. Not one of
them is too bony or dry.
Such exquisite fish... What a
rare and pleasant sight.
You may live on the land... but
you certainly have impeccable
judgement of aquatic creatures,
don't you?
As an ocean‐dweller, it touches
my heart that you possess such
an intricate understanding of my
world.
[MERO]
I just had to express my
gratitude.
FISH SALESMAN
THANK YOU SO MUCH, MISS
This is one of our top‐quality
yellowtail.
I'd really like you
to have it.
[MERO]
(happy)Awww
[KIMIHITO]
(freak out) We can't accept
something like that!
[KIDS]
(playing)(laughing)
[LITTLE GIRL A]
I wanna fly too, bird lady!
[LIL BOY E]
Let me go next!
[LITTLE GIRL A]
No way, wait your turn!
[KIMIHITO]
He ended up giving us a bunch of
extra stuff.
[MERO]
Yes, he was quite a generous
man.
[VEGGIE LADY]
I'm glad you like our
vegetables.
[KIMIHITO]
(hm?)(awkward)
[VEGGIE LADY]
Don't be shy, dear, have some
more!
[CEREA]
Oh no, I couldn't take any
more...
[VEGGIE LADY]
What are you talking about?
I'm sure a good strong girl like
you can eat plenty!
I highly recommend the carrots.
[CEREA]
Ca... carrots...
(serious)
[CEREA]
(happy yell)
These are incredible! So fresh
and sweet!
No... sweet doesn't
cover it! There's so much depth
to the flavor!
These carrots are the gods of
all vegetables!
Herbivores' taste buds are two
to four times more sensitive
than humans'.
That's why I can appreciate all
the complex flavor sensations in
these glorious carrots!
While we're on the subject,
carnivore species only have a
tiny fraction of the taste buds
humans have.
Might explains why Miia's such a
terrible cook.
[MIIA]
Actually, that's only one
reason.
[RACHNELA]
Who are you talking to?
[VEGGIE LADY]
Well! I'm happy to see you enjoy
them so much!
[CEREA]
(thrilled)
[VEGGIE LADY]
My sweet grandmother put her
heart and soul into growing
those carrots.
If you go ahead and stock up;
I'll give you a discount!
Plus a few extra!
[KIMIHITO]
That's nice of you, ma'am, but
we can't really
afford that
much... Money's kinda tight
so...
[VEGGIE LADY]
Oh, you're broke, are you? You
better feed this girl!
Here, you can take these with
you... Those are the
funny‐shaped
vegetables people
never want to buy... They still
taste delicious though!
[TOFU LADY]
Excuse me!
You can have this tofu pulp if
you like.
[EGG LADY]
That little bird friend of yours
has been a big help
playing with
the kids today, so I wanted to
thank her somehow.
These eggs are all grade B, but
you're welcome to take them.
BAKER MAN
Here, have some bread crusts!
[KIMIHITO]
Wow... You guys are so generous!
[PAPI
Look at all the food!
[KIMIHITO]
How are we gonna carry it?
[MERO]
Couldn't you take it on your
back, Lady Centorea?
[CEREA]
Do I look like a pack mule?!
[KIMIHITO]
Sorry to put you out, Cerea; do
you mind?
[CEREA]
My pleasure, Master!
[MERO]
That hardly seems right.
[CEREA]
I'm sorry...
[KIMIHITO]
Thanks again!
[SUU]
You're not going home yet,
Master?
[KIMIHITO]
Mmm... I think I'll get a little
more, just to be safe.
It takes a lot of groceries to
keep everybody fed...
[SUU]
Don't worry about me; I don't
need food.
I can always get my nutrients
from anything that's
digestible...
So you don't have to buy any
groceries for me, okay?
[KIMIHITO]
Thank you, Suu... but... I still
want everybody to eat the same
nice dinner at the same table.
I mean... we're family, right?
(surprised)Whoa, hey!
[SUU]
Come with me, Master!
[KIMIHITO]
W‐wait a second! GAH! MY AAAARM!
[KII]
I understand perfectly.
You've come into these woods to
collect some edible plants for
your dinner table, is that it?
[KIMIHITO]
Is that... okay?
[KII]
I'm the guardian of this
forest.
What makes you think I
would allow you to ravage it in
such a way?
[KIMIHITO]
Fair enough.
[KII]
(startled)Suu... what are
you‐?!‐ (gasp)
[SUU]
(start to suck)(extended
sucking)
[KII]
(extended moaning/gasping)
[KIMIHITO]
(panic) What the hell, Suu?!
[SUU]
She said no, so I thought I
should give her something in
return.
She seemed to like it when YOU
sucked on her like that last
time, Master.
[KII]
But I wasn't going to tell you
no.
[KIMIHITO]
Huh?
[KII]
Papi taught me that friends
should help each other.
[KII]
So, I will permit you to gather
a small amount.
Follow me; I'll take you there.
[KIMIHITO]
That's perfect... Thanks, Kii.
So that stump thing moves with
her?
Wow, check this place out!
[SUU]
Pretty!
[KII]
Feel free to pick some plants.‐
Those ones over there should be
edible.
[KIMIHITO]
Um... some of these are
definitely poisonous mushrooms.
[KII]
All I did was direct you to an
area with plants that
are ripe
and firm enough to be
ingested...
[KII]
Whether or not those plants are
poisonous...
I have no idea.
[KIMIHITO]
(stunned)
I don't know enough about plants
to figure out which ones are
safe to eat.
Sorry, Suu, but I
think we should call it a day.
[SUU]
Ding ding!(eating)
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?)
[SUU]
Bzzz!
[KIMIHITO]
No way!...
You can tell if
they're poisonous?!
[SUU]
This kind here is okay to eat.
But this one's not.
[KII]
(impressed(I didn't know you
could do that.
[KIMIHITO]
I hope she doesn't get sick from
eating that stuff...
[KIMIHITO]
(sigh)
We ended up taking a lot more
than I thought we would...
Sorry, Kii.
[KII]
That's alright... The forest has
plenty more to give.
Tell Papi to come visit me when
she has a chance.
[KIMIHITO]
Yeah, we'll come back.
[KII]
Not you.
[KIMIHITO]
(awkward)
Suu... you sure you're okay?
[SUU]
Yep, I'm perfectly fine!‐ But we
should hurry home, Master;
those
freeloaders are probably hungry
by now.
[KIMIHITO]
That was kinda harsh. Is that
the poison talking?
[DRACO]
THERE YOU ARE!
[KIMIHITO]
(uhh)
[DRACO]
Miia WILL be my bride!
Now hand
her over, you filthy human!
[SUU]
(spit)
[DRACO]
I‐I can't move! What'd you do to
me?!
[KIMIHITO]
So she IS poison.
[DRACO]
(gasp)
N‐no, wait! I'll leave him
alone,
I swear! Just let me go
and I won't lay a claw on him!
[DRACO]
(scream)
(panting)
[KIMIHITO]
Sorry for the wait!
Ladies...Bon appetit!
MIIA/CEREA/PAPI/MERO/LALA/RACHNE
L A] (amazed)
L A] Thanks for the food!
[KIMIHITO]
(sigh)And we've got lots to
spare too!...
We should be good
for a while.
And it's all thanks to you,
Suu.Great job.
[SUU](Under)
(happy sounds)
[KIMIHITO]
(annoyed)
[SMITH]
Well, good evening, Darling!...
We were in the neighborhood, so
we thought
we might join you all
for dinner.
[ZOMBINA]
Ooh!.. Smells good!
[TIO]
Yeah, I'm really hungry!
[MANAKO]
Sorry to interrupt.
[DOPPEL]
I tried to tell them not to, but
here we are.
[SMITH]
That looks good!
[TIO]
I don't think this'll be enough
food...
[SMITH]
You're right.
Whip up a few more
helpings,
would you, Darling?
[KIMIHITO]
(weak laugh)
Okay! Keep those orders coming,
everybody!
I'll make you as much food as
you can eat!
[SMITH] More tempura, please!
[KIMIHITO] Here!
[CEREA]
Would you mind making us another
salad?
[KIMIHITO]
More salad, coming up!
[TIO]
I want more bread pudding!
[KIMIHITO]
I'll get that right away!
[MIIA]
Aww, I didn't get to try any
yet!
[KIMIHITO]
(power up)YOUR WISH IS MY
COMMAND!
[MIIA]
That was delicious!
[CEREA/MANAKO]
Thank you for dinner.
[PAPI
(burp)
ZOMBINA
I'm so full I could die...
DOPPEL
It's a little late for that.
[SMITH]
What is it, Darling?
[KIMIHITO]
What?!‐ What are you talking
about?‐ Everything's peachy!
[SUU]
Actually, Master's devastated
because those
freeloaders just
went through all the groceries
in one meal
and now we have no
[more] food left.
[KIMIHITO]
A‐AH, SUU, I SEE YOU'RE STILL
FULL OF POISON.
[SMITH]
Darling...
[KIMIHITO]
Uh, don't listen to Suu; she's
not herself today!
[SMITH]
You do know you can expense
groceries, right?
[KIMIHITO]
(stunned)
[SMITH]
Didn't I tell you that?...
All
you have to do is keep your
receipts and we'll reimburse you
in full.
[KIMIHITO]
(rage‐drowning)
[SMITH]
Now what are you doing, Darling?
[KIMIHITO]
Sometimes it's difficult, and
things can get pretty crazy...
But I gotta admit, it's always
an adventure.
And that...
is Everyday Life
with Monster Girls.
[KIMIHITO]
(chuckle)