[KIMIHITO]
(sleepy breathing)(groan)
(confused groan)(look)
[CEREA]
Good morning to you... Master.
[KIMIHITO]
(freak out)Whoa!.. What are you
doing here?!
[KIMIHITO]
Miia would do this... but you...
[PAPI]
That was yummy!
[SUU]
Mhm!
[RACHNELA]
Breakfast was wonderful.. Honey.
[KIMIHITO]
Glad you enjoyed it.
[MIIA]
Wait a minute, bug breath!...
I heard that!...
What the heck do you
think you're doing by
calling my future husband
Honey?!
[RACHNELA]
Oh... Would you rather I call
him "Darling" the way you do?
[MIIA]
(angry)(raging)
You better watch it!... you
skanky spiderrrr!
[RACHNELA]
Oh no, dear, you can call me
Rachnera...
We're all friends
here, aren't we?
[MIIA]
(grunt)Get her, Papi‐
[PAPI]
Wow, you're so fun!‐ I want you
to be my big sister!
[RACHNELA]
There's the greeting I was
hoping for.
[MIIA]
Thanks a lot, Papi, you're a big
help!
[MERO]
Tell me, which ocean did you
come from?
[RACHNELA]
(laugh)Well, I'm a spider, not a
crab.
[MIIA]
Whatever, who needs them?
Centorea should take my side!
[MIIA]
(stunned)
[CEREA]
I don't have any objections to
Lady Rachnela staying here with
us.
[MIIA]
Huh?!
[CEREA]
She doesn't make me suspicious
the way Lady Meroune does.
[KIMIHITO]
Hey... Cerea!(ahhh...)
[CEREA]
(surprised)Pardon me!
Please ride on my back!... Go
on!
[KIMIHITO]
No thanks, it's okay...
Something wrong?... You're being
kinda pushy.
Why are you sticking so close to
me?
[CEREA]
What do you mean?... You're my
great master!...
It's my duty to
accompany you... Please allow me
to stay at your side always!
[KIMIHITO]
It's just... I gotta pee so...
[CEREA]
P‐please excuse me then!
[MIIA]
So you really don't mind her?
[CEREA] I don't.
[MIIA] That spider's gotta be up
to no good,
don't you think?... I
mean, she even LOOKS dangerous.
[CEREA] Miia.
[MIIA] (surprised)
[CEREA]
No matter how she looks...
don't judge
someone by appearance,
It's not honorable.
[CEREA]
As non‐human species,
we should
know that better than anyone.
[MIIA]
Y... yeah, I know that but
still‐
[CEREA]
(grunt)
[MIIA/CEREA] (startled)(look)
[CEREA]
(kick)
[CEREA/ MIIA]
(fuming) (angry)
[RACHNELA]
(clear throat)
Whoops.. Sorry!... Silly Honey
just came rushing into the
bathroom!... I was so startled I
trapped him!(giggle)
[MIIA]
That's a lie!... You were
waiting for Darling
to‐(surprised)
[CEREA]
That's alright... But if you
wouldn't mind... please lock the
door from now on.
[MIIA]
(shocked)
[KIMIHITO]
(sigh)I'm so tired...
What's up with Cerea today? And
Rachne...
(startled)What the hell?!
[RACHNELA]
I see we're finally alone.
[KIMIHITO]
Rachne!
[RACHNELA]
Oh and you've shortened my name
too?
I quite like it.
[KIMIHITO]
What are you doing in my
bedroom?!
[RACHNELA]
I'm here to make you mine.
Head.. to.. toe.
[KIMIHITO]
(panic)
[RACHNELA]
You're looking for a marriage
partner, right, Honey?
And yet you haven't laid a
finger on them.
Are you
lacking experience?
[KIMIHITO]
(freak out)
[RACHNELA]
In that case, I'll teach you
everything you need to know,
Honey.(giggle)
I'm promise it'll be fun...
Those other girls won't get in
our way.
Ooh! You're already so hard!
[RACHNELA]
(surprised)Oh my... Was that
really necessary?
[KIMIHITO]
I thought that was a fake sword.
[CEREA]
(determined)
[KIMIHITO]
(scream)
[RACHNELA]
How about that...She might be
more deadly than me.
[KIMIHITO]
Cerea, stop running!
I'll fall off!... Where are you
taking me?
[CEREA]
Somewhere you'll be safe!
If she means to sink her fangs
into my Master, then...
then...
we'll just have to run away!
[CEREA] Have a nice day!
[KIMIHITO] You too hun!
[CEREA] It's kicking!
[KIMIHITO] Let me feel!
[CEREA]
(troubled)They're staring.
[KIMIHITO]
(huh?)
[CEREA]
Those are the stares we
non‐humans always get.
I'm sure
most of them don't mean any
harm.
Still... the stares people give
you just because you're
different...
They're so severe... they pierce
through you.
[KIMIHITO]
I think they're probably staring
at something else...
[CEREA]
Those looks are painful... We
know that all too well.
SATSUKE
(ogling)
[KIMIHITO]
I still don't think that's the
reason‐
[CEREA]
I hate the way it makes me
feel... and yet...
I'm no better...
I judged Lady
Rachnela by her appearance.
[KIMIHITO]
Well... you turned out to be
right...
[CEREA]
That's not the point! Making
assumptions about her was still
unforgivable!
I'm ashamed... I came here to be
an ambassador
of the proud
Centaur species, and yet... look
at me.
I can't represent my kind... I'm
not worthy.
[KIMIHITO]
(concerned)
[RACIST GUY]
Well, well, well!
Check out that massive rack!...
But that horse's ass... that's
freakin' gross.
[RACIST GIRL]
Isn't that a Centaur?... Can you
even screw one of those things?
[KIMIHITO]
Not these jerks again... They
even brought friends.
[CEREA] (hmph!)
[RACIST GUY] She's more like a
cow with those tits!
[RACIST GIRL]
No kidding! I wanna milk 'em!
[RACIST GUY]
Yeah, that sounds good. I'll do
that!
[KIMIHITO]
Hey, that's enough‐
[CEREA]
Wait, Master... I don't
understand anything
they're
saying, but this isn't worth it.
We should get out of here‐
[RACIST GIRL]
Is that her boyfriend?
[RACIST GUY]
There's no way a wussy boy like
him can keep her satisfied!
[THUG 8A]
Yeah, I bet he's a virgin with a
little baby wiener!
[RACIST GIRL]
Ha, she needs a stallion!
[CEREA]
(screams)I'll cut you to
pieces!... Now begone!
[KIMIHITO]
Whoa... Cerea!
[RACIST GUY]
Uh‐oh... Be careful...
You monsters aren't
allowed to attack people,
remember?
[CEREA] (unsure)
[RACIST GUY] You don't wanna get
deported, now do you?
[THUG 8A]
Where you goin', virgin boy?
[CEREA] Master, no!
[THUG 8B/THUG 8C]
(reach out)
[RACIST GUY]
We can forget about the bottom
half anyway.
Those titties'll be
enough for all of us.
[RACIST GUY]
(laughter)(huh?)
What the hell...
[RACHNELA]
Well what do we have here?
[RACIST GUY]
(surprised)(look)
[RACHNELA]
have you been playing naughty
games without me?
[RACIST GUY MenTHUG 8A/THUG
8B/THUG 8CRACIST GIRL]
(panicking)
[RACIST GUY]
You know the law; you're not
allowed to hurt me!
I‐if I go
to the authorities, you...!
[RACHNELA]
Do you really think you're going
to get that chance, my friend?
[RACIST GUY]
(faint)
[RACHNELA]
(sigh)Honestly... Why were you
letting that
sniveling gaggle of
vermin have their way with you?
[CEREA]
I had to... causing harm to
humans is illegal.
[RACHNELA]
Only if you get caught.
[CEREA]
(clear throat)Well.. anyway,
thank you for that.
If not for you, Master and I
would‐
[RACHNELA]
Only I can torment you...
On.. ly.. me!... Understand,
Honey?
[RACHNELA] Now let's get a nice
room somewhere, shall we?
[RACHNELA]
(pained)
Ouch... That wasn't funny,
dear... You could've killed me
with those hard hooves!
[CEREA]
I‐I am grateful to you, and I
don't mean to discriminate...
[CEREA]
... but even so, I still hate
you!
[KIMIHITO/RACHNELA]
(huh?)
[CEREA]
You mustn't toy with him!...
He's not some plaything; he's my
Master!
And as his servant, I can't
watch him endure this!(squeeze)
[KIMIHITO]
(squeezed)(long weak)
[CEREA]
(gasp)Ah.. what have I done
now?!
And after she rescued me too...
I should
return to my homeland. Thank you
for everything, Master...
[KIMIHITO]
Whoa, calm down!
[RACHNELA] (laughter)
[KIMIHITO/CEREA] (huh?)
[RACHNELA]
I see you're finally speaking
your mind...
You're much too
serious... you know that?
It bothers me when people try to
put up a good front.
Like the way
you said you had no objections
even though you were
afraid of me. Just be honest!
I know, I'm a giant spider. I'm
dangerous enough to do THIS.
It's natural to be wary, but is
it discriminating?
You can like and dislike what
you want...
If you find you
dislike me... well, that's
normal.
Pretending to get along just
makes you a hypocrite.
It's
alright for you not to like
me.(smile)
[CEREA]
(surprised)
[RACHNELA]
Now then... why don't we head
back home?
Spinning all that
thread made me hungry.
[KIMIHITO]
Oh...okay, I'll make something
for dinner.
[CEREA]
Goodness...I didn't know what
to say.
It may be true that I dislike
her, but...
[KIMIHITO]
You're gonna
make me fall down.
[CEREA]But perhaps I can
at least trust her.
[RACHNELA](Under)
You're so warm, Honey...(giggle)
[CEREA]
Lady Rachnela, please allow me
to repay you for saving me.
I feel just
terrible for my ingratitude.
[RACHNELA]
Hmm... In that case...
[MIIA]
(amazed)
[KIMIHITO]
Um... what's happening?
[RACHNELA]
Oh... I just wanted to try tying
her up... Nice, isn't it?
[CEREA]
Endure it, Centorea, you deserve
this!
Perhaps this punishment
will cleanse your impure heart!
[RACHNELA]
Oooh!... Wouldn't it be fun if I
tied your hands behind your
back?(giggle)
[CEREA]
I really do hate
her!(struggling)
[RACHNELA]
MonMusu!
[KIMIHITO/SUU]
MonMusu.
[MIIA]
Oh no! You caught a cold?!
[KIMIHITO]
Uh‐huh...(cough)
[KIMIHITO] Ugh...
[MIIA] No... Please don't die on
me, Darling!
[PAPI]
Wow, Master... You look bad.
[MIIA]
Don't you worry!... You can
just leave everything to Nurse
Lamia, okay?‐ I'll have you back
to perfect health in no time!
Oh my gosh, Darling, you're
getting really sweaty!
Maybe we'd better take all your
clothes off!...
Or maybe you
want to give ME a shot.‐
What do you
think of that?(thirsty laughter)
[CEREA]
Miia!... Get a hold of yourself!
MIIA/CEREA/PAPI/SUU/MERO/RACHNEL
A] (startled)
[SMITH]
Stop right there! Ladies... you
must evacuate quickly!
Darling may be contaminated. We
have to quarantine him.
We're responding to a severe
threat of virus mutation.
If a new virus from a human
mutates and is transmitted to
non‐human species...
It could lead to a
pandemic that threatens the
existence of all non‐humans!
[CEREA]
So, what do you propose we do
about Master?
[SMITH]
Don't worry... You ladies let me
take care of him instead.
[MIIA]
Aren't you busy?
[SMITH]
Well yes... I've got more
paperwork
than I can manage...
but preventing your extinction
is first priority!
[ZOMBINA]
You're the worst!... Don't bail
out when we're busy!
[RACHNELA/MIIA/CEREA]
She just wants to skip out of
work!
[SMITH]
(snoring)
[RACHNELA/MIIA/CEREA/PAPI/MERO]
Of course.
[MIIA]
Okay, looks like it's up to us
to get Darling well again!
[PAPI]
Yay!
[CEREA]
Wait. Smith is right;
there'd be
serious trouble if we got
infected.
[MERO]
Ah, I can picture the tragedy
now!
[KIMIHITO](Cool)
Mero... I got you sick; it's all
my fault!
[MERO]]
You mustn't weep for me...
But please...
you must live on... for my..
sake now...
[KIMIHITO]
(worried)Noooo!
[MERO] (cheeky laughter)
[MIIA] (angry)
[CEREA]
If only one of us was resistant
to infection...
[SUU]
(hm?)
[KIMIHITO]
(coughing)
[CEREA]
Master? May I come in?
[KIMIHITO]
(hm?)Cerea...
Oh, Suu. You sounded like Cerea.
[CEREA](As SUU)
Master!... Can you hear my
voice?!
[KIMIHITO] (huh?)
[CEREA](As SUU)
We were instructed to keep our
distance to avoid
contamination... Therefore...
We have decided to have Suu take
care of you on our behalf!
[CEREA]
Well done Suu... Good!
[CEREA](As SUU)
Suu will be acting as a proxy
nurse,
so please ask her for
anything you need!
[MERO]
What a wonderful idea!... You're
quite resourceful, Centorea!
[CEREA]
Maybe so... but the real
obstacle is how
to teach Suu to
be a good caretaker... right?
[MERO/RACHNE/PAPI/MIIA]
(hmm...)
[SUU] (smile)
[MERO] (happy)Alright!
[MERO]
Here's something...Why don't we
have Suu play the part of the
Master? That way she can
learn how from experience!
[CEREA]
Good!... Let's teach her to take
his temperatu‐oh!
[MERO/RACHNELA/MIIA/PAPI]
(surprised)
[MIIA]
Whoa, is that her?!
[CEREA]
I didn't know she could do that!
[PAPI]
You're so cool, Suu!
[CEREA]
A.. Alright, Suu... P‐pay close
attention.
Put your forehead up against his
like this...
And feel his...
temperature...(gasp)
O‐oh dear... so hot...
That was intense! One of us has
a serious fever...
[KIMIHITO]
(surprised)Oh... that's nice and
cool, thank y‐
(splutter)No wait, Suu!... I
know this is kind of your thing
and all, but when I'm this sick
it might just kill me!
[KIMIHITO]
(gasp for air)
[CEREA](As SUU)
Your fever's over 100!
[KIMIHITO]
I almost drowned!
[MERO](As SUU)
Hello Master...
Please allow me
to take care of you for a little
while.
[KIMIHITO] What?
[MERO](As SUU) When we mermaids
are feeling sick...
The traditional cure...
is to take a long bath in a pool
with a blend of medicinal herbs.
If you soak long enough, any
ailment can be healed this way.
[KIMIHITO](Under)
(shivering)So cold... How long
do I have to sit here like this?
[MERO](As SUU)
You should recover in about a
week's time!
[KIMIHITO]
Are you kidding?!‐ I'll be dead
by then!
[MIIA](As SUU)
(smile)I knew the rest of you
guys would suck at this.
It's my turn to shine... At a
time like this, he needs his
nutrients!
[KIMIHITO]
(nervous)This isn't good...
[MIIA] Voila!‐ It's Miia's
special white rice porridge!
[RACHNELA/CEREA/PAPI](horrified)
[CEREA]
Actually, it looks pretty
decent.
[MIIA]
I've been practicing every day!
[MERO]
Rice porridge! I've never seen
it before.
[MIIA]
Want to try it?
[MERO]
May I?
Thank you very much!(bite)
[SEA WITCH 8A]
(chuckle)This potion will grant
you human legs, Little
Mermaid...
But in return, you will suffer
the agony of your fins being
torn to shreds and experience
every torture of hell.
[MERO]
(dazed sigh)
[MIIA]
I used all the best ingredients
too...
White rice, white onions,
white sesame, white cabbage,
white peaches, white icefish,
white roe, white swan, white
egret
and just a little bit of
white chocolate to top it all
off!
[CEREA]
You thought white rice porridge
is just porridge with [all]
white ingredients?!
[MIIA](As SUU)
... bit of white chocolate to
top it all off!
[KIMIHITO]
(scared)Can I really eat this
stuff?...
I‐I feel like it might
actually kill me...
Huh?... Did you eat it already?
[SUU]
(nod)(huh?)
[KIMIHITO]
Aw... I REALLY appreciate that.
[PAPI](As SUU)
Ready, Master?... It's my turn
to play!
[KIMIHITO]
Can't I just go to bed?
[PAPI](As SUU)
My wings are soft...and they're
so warm too!
I bet you'll
feel better if we snuggle!
[KIMIHITO]
You know... that sounds pretty
good, actually.
[PAPI](As SUU)
You heard him, Suu! Sleep next
to Master for me, would ya?
[KIMIHITO]
(shocked)
[SUU]
Suu... sleep next to... Suu...
Master...
[KIMIHITO](Under)
You're just gonna sleep next to
me?
'Cause It kinda feels like
you're gonna eat my soul!
(freaking out)What's
happening?!.. I'm scared!‐
(freaking out)
[MIIA]
Get your claws off him!
[PAPI]
Why are you so mad?
[MIIA]
Oh, I think you know why!
[CEREA/MIIA]
Don't you realize what that
looks like?!
[PAPI]
So?... It's Suu.
[CEREA]
I know that!... But it looks
wrong!
[MIIA]
Oh yeah?! Well if you can do
that, so can I!
[CEREA](Under)
What are you doing?!
[MIIA]
If you're drenched in sweat...
it's gonna make you cold...
Don't worry.
I'll use my body to wipe off the
sweat for you.
You like it?... Huh?(startled)
[CEREA]
That's so indecent! The best
remedy...
is to warm him up using your
own body heat.
Keeping a man warm in this
manner has been
a woman's job
since the beginning of time, you
know.
(surprised)
Ah... th‐therefore...
there's
nothing untoward about this in
the slightest!
C‐Centaurs have a higher body
temperature than humans,
after all...
It's 100 degrees,
just like horses.
So that makes us... the.. the
perfect species... for um...
warming up...
That said, my body temperature
is so high at the moment,
I'm afraid I'm more likely to
burn you, so I'm awfully sorry,
but it's probably best if you
let me recuse myself from this
one.‐ Forget I said anything,
Master...
[MIIA]
Then why don't you let me‐agh!
[PAPI]
(shove)No, me!
[MERO]
No! I'll do it!
[CEREA]
No wait... I'll do it.
[RACHNELA]
Honestly... I think that's quite
enough...
If Suu learns
something strange.. it's your
fault... Now‐(surprised)
[KIMIHITO]
Suu, what are you doing?
Whoa... hey! What the heck were
those other girls teaching you?!
[KIMIHITO]
I... think I'm at my...
limit...(ggh...)
[KIMIHITO]
(fevered panting)
[SUU]
(huh?) (focus)
[KIMIHITO]
Suu! Suu!
[SUU]
(hm.. huh?)
[KIMIHITO]
Come on now... Don't go out by
yourself... We've been worried
about you.
I guess you got stuck because of
all the rain, huh?
[SUU]
(nod)(huh?)
[KIMIHITO]
Here, take my umbrella.
Brrr!.. It's cold out here
though.. Let's go home. (
sneeze)
(sniffle) Well... anyway, don't
run off on your own.
I was afraid something happened
to you.
[KIMIHITO]
(coughing)
(panting)
[SUU]
(determined)
[KIMIHITO]
(drinking)W‐water?
(realize)(freak out)
[KIMIHITO]
Suu.. what are you doing?!
Wait... I feel better now.
(surprised) It's dark out. Were
you watching over me this whole
time?
Thanks for your help... Suu.
[SUU]
(happy)
[MIIA/CEREA/PAPI/MERO/RACHNELA]
(fall in)
[KIMIHITO]
Uh... Do I wanna know?
[MIIA]
Darling... you're up.
[PAPI]
Are you okay?
[KIMIHITO]
Yeah, thanks to Suu, I'm much
better.
[MIIA/CEREA/PAPI/MERO/RACHNELA]
(surprised)
[PAPI] Wow, good job, Suu!
[SUU]
Oh no... I was the one who made
him sick in the first place...
I'm sorry I ran off.
But I'm glad I could make
everything better...
because now
I know I love my Master!
[KIMIHITO]
(speechless)
[MIIA]
Suu... did you... say...?
[MERO] Are you sure?
[PAPI] We must have taught her a
bunch of words today.
[CEREA]
Or Miia's food made her
delusional.
[MIIA]
What do you mean you love him?‐
You mean, you LOVE HIM, love
him?!‐ I need to know!
[SUU]
I need to know?
[MIIA]
Not talking anymore?!
[SMITH]
What's all this noise?
Darling's room is quarantined,
remember?‐
You girls aren't
supposed to be in here.
[MERO]
Ooh, Miss Smith,
what a pleasant surprise...
We were just here to see...
[SMITH]
(sneeze)(sniffle)
[SMITH] Uh‐oh.
[SMITH]
Uh... it turns out I've got a
bit of a cold...
If you girls
could come over and nurse me
back to health,
I would really
appreciate it. (cough)
ZOMBINA
Aw, too bad!... Don't get me
wrong, we'd LOVE to...
But we wouldn't want to start up
a pandemic or anything like
that;
you understand, don't you,
Boss?
[SMITH]
(sneeze)Ughhh...
[MIIA]
Is he on a date with Smith?!
How dare he cheat on me?!
[CEREA]
We can't tell anything for
certain yet.
[MERO]
We need to go in and find out
for ourselves.
That's the only
way to be sure.
[MIIA]
Oh no! Where'd he go?