[ZEMUNN]
I'll be honest with you.
You've been a real thorn
in Urmun's side lately,
Viscount Remedius.
[NAJIK]
More than that, Zemunn.
He's a Rahzel.
His family's company's been
selling Juhshiki weapons
to Dochetta.
The people of Urmun
are suffering
because of his inventions!
I say we kill him
in the name of Zhuo Lu!
That's right!
He deserves to die!
You idiots!
You captured him without a plan!
Do you want the Dragon
Empire against us, too?
Then what?
Should we free him?
We can't!
Navarro, Stop it!
You too, Najik!
Back off, Naricia!
This is for our people!
Pardon.
You shouldn't fire
that Majouken.
It'll explode and then
we'll all be dead.
D'you think I'm stupid?
[NAJIK grunts]
[gasps]
A bit of dust found its way
into the contact terminal.
Urmun's a dry place.
You should change these
every three months.
[MEN gasp]
--Will you check my weapon?
--Yeah, and mine, too?
[MEN chattering]
All right, all right.
One at a time please.
See that?
Remedius is really incredible!
[LARGONKIN] There,
another Magatsushiki down.
Soon as we kill one,
another pops up.
It's starting to feel like
these attacks are endless.
[GAYUS]
Apparently Largonkin's people
already took care of
the Magatsushiki
that was found in the subway.
What's wrong?
Oh, that girl.
[GIGINA]
Premelena doesn't concern me.
[GAYUS]
That's harsh.
I gave her a merciful death, as
is the way of a Draken warrior.
That's it.
Ah, you're on time. Perfect.
[GAYUS]
What about them?
It would appear
they've arrived early.
They're ready for us.
Be careful.
Of course.
[GAYUS] So this is the
Aurora Hammer, the group that's
trying to remove Urmun's
twisted head of state, Dochetta,
from power.
[ZHUO LU]
That's far enough.
[ZHUO LU] I see Calpulnia
herself is here, as agreed.
Where is Party Leader Zemunn?
[ZHUO LU]
Zemunn is no longer in charge.
[CALPULNIA] Then, with
whom should I negotiate?
You'll speak with me.
I lead the Aurora Hammer now.
My subordinates call me Zhuo Lu,
Man-Eating Sand Dragon.
Gigina!
Don't you start anything!
He's dangerous.
Possibly even deadlier
than the Cardinal's
Twelve Winged Generals are.
This is serious.
[ZHUO LU]
Do you have the ransom money?
First, I want to
see the hostage.
[ZHUO LU] I'm afraid that's
simply not the way I operate.
There, you had a good look.
Now bring out my
nephew right now!
Ready to complete the trade?
Not so fast.
For all we know, he's a fake
who's been given
plastic surgery.
We need proof that it's him.
A Jushiki wavelength reader?
Fair enough.
[VOICE 7A]
Match confirmed.
Accuracy guaranteed with
99.9988 percent certainty.
I'll accept it.
[coughs]
[gasps]
[MAN 7G gasps, groans]
Stop him!
[GAYUS grunts]
Gigina!
[CALPULNIA coughs]
[gasps]
[MAN 7I grunts]
Whose side are those men on?
Beats me! We need
to get outta here!
[gasps]
How could any human generate a
Jushiki barrier that powerful?
Who is he?
Farewell.
[gasps]
[MEN screaming]
[GAYUS] Sixth-order numerical
quantum Jushiki, Sui Tori.
It converts the
body's amino acids
using quantum interference.
It's a demon's curse.
Good thing you
healed us with O Se.
That and my shielding curse
Phoenic just saved our lives.
[CALPULNIA pants]
[GAYUS]
Sand Dragon, huh?
It's almost as if the
victims have been chewed up
from the inside out.
[gasps] Wait a minute.
Where is Remedius?
Looks like he's gone.
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
I'm not sure
which group it's from,
but somebody left us
a little parting gift!
[GAYUS]
Huh?
[GIGINA grunts]
[MEN chattering]
[gasps]
Hey. Drink up, buddy!
Ah, thank you.
But.... I'm still
your hostage, aren't I?
Ahem. We owe you one.
You did save our lives.
Good thing you
know your weapons.
Mine's workin' like a dream!
Yeah, mine too!
[MAN 7B]
Thanks, pal!
Really... all I did was
lend you a small hand.
If you save someone's life,
then they owe you--big.
That's how things work here.
I'll die for you.
Same goes for me.
In the name of Zhuo Lu!
Thank you both.
Truly.
[NARICIA] A long time ago,
the people of Urmun
were under the control
of a terrible king.
Cries of pain and sorrow
echoed across the land.
The people prayed to God,
but nobody answered.
One woman's husband and children
were slain by the king.
Riddled with despair,
she climbed to the
highest peak of Derilla,
the northern Urmun
Mountains of Hell,
with the intention
of taking her own life.
She walked seven days and nights
through the hot, dry climate,
not a blade of grass in sight.
Despite all of this,
though screaming
with every ragged step,
she still couldn't die.
After fainting from exhaustion,
she woke to see the Sand Dragon
Zhuo Lu before her.
She begged the dragon
to aid her in her plight.
But as punishment for
the crime of eating people,
Zhuo Lu had been
bound to the mountain
and stripped of
his former powers.
"Please, eat me,"
the woman pleaded.
"Let my blood and flesh
restore your dragon strength
so that you can defeat
the evil king for us."
She closed her eyes and
dove into the dragon's mouth.
[NARICIA]
Imbued with newfound power,
Zhuo Lu broke free
of the mountain
and descended upon the palace,
where he tore the corrupt king
and his henchmen to shreds.
That's when Zhuo Lu
told the people,
"Give your flesh and blood and
I will appear to devour any foe
who dares threaten
any harm to Urmun."
Finally, with a mournful howl,
Zhuo Lu vanished
into the distant sky.
To this day,
the Sand Dragon slumbers
somewhere deep within Derilla,
the Mountains of Hell,
waiting to be offered another
sacrifice of flesh and blood.
[REMEDIUS]
That was an awfully sad tale.
From what it sounds like, your
people were never really saved.
Right. So we put our
faith in a fairy tale.
It's less depressing that way.
One of these days
I will become Zhuo Lu
and then I can
devour Dochetta myself.
--[explosion]
--[gasps]
[SOLDIER 7A]
His Highness Dochetta
didn't give you permission
to open a shop here.
You're just a
fourth-rank citizen!
Please, sir!
You insect.
[SHOPKEEP 7A screams]
[gasps]
[REMEDIUS]
That's...!
What are you doing? Let's go!
I was told they'd be used
to protect peace, but--
A sword's a sword!
[NARICIA shrieks]
[gasps]
Naricia!
[SOLDIER 7A]
Hm?
[REMEDIUS]
Die.
[ZHUO LU sighs]
[CALPULNIA] Yesterday's
exchange was a failure.
They killed all the guards,
got away with the
two billion yen ransom,
and I lost my
dear nephew Remedius.
I'm lost.
Who am I to hold accountable
for everything that's
taken place here?
I'm sorry.
There might've been things
we could've done better...
...but still, our assignment
was to protect you.
I'd say we managed
to do that much.
So, who were
those other attackers
and what was their motive?
I don't know.
The police didn't learn
anything else about them
from the scene, either.
Another thing.
I haven't seen Egurrd
since the incident.
Well, do you think that
he had anything to do
with what happened?
I couldn't say.
What's that?
This is a piece
from a chells set.
The board is arranged
to recreate
the exact same play
Remedius used
in the game that earned him the
title of continental champion.
It's weird that the pieces
are birds and elephants.
Indeed.
But apparently that used
to be the standard design.
These days,
the elephants are bishops.
And at some point, the birds
and boats were changed to rooks.
Anyway, I've come to realize
that I treated
Remedius unfairly.
I forced him to give up chells
and devote his life
to company research,
but he loved this game.
He had such solid ethics.
The boy must've been
so devastated to learn
how his inventions
were being used in Urmun.
Oh, I can't bear to think of it.
[CALPULNIA sighs]
[CALPULNIA]
Now then.
I have one more request
I'd like to make of you.
Go track down the Aurora
Hammer and get Remedius.
Bring him back
no matter the cost.
That's the only way
for the two of you
to set things right with me.
I know it's a security thing,
but it's such a pain in the ass
that they confiscate
our weapons before we land.
[GIGINA]
Hm?
Don't move.
Just listen.
Someone's watching us.
They're at our 3:16.
Six-point-one degree pitch,
about 550 meters away.
[GAYUS]
I'm looking.
[GIGINA]
Too late. They're gone now.
Who was it?
One of my many secret admirers?
We both know
that isn't possible.
No, this smells like
the last encounter.
There's no way this
could be Mouldeen's work.
We'll talk to Vinnel.
He can help us find
the Aurora Hammer.
[GIGINA] I'm beginning
to think we should have
turned this entire mission down.
[GAYUS]
No getting out of it now.
We're already
a part of the mess.
This is Tarelk. Isn't he grand?
[GAYUS]
A grand waste of space.
And please stop
naming the furniture.
[GIGINA] My son has room
to store items of any size.
Or perhaps, an entire person.
Sure, as long as it's not you.
Nonsense.
There's nothing my son can't do.
This cabinet's potential
is never-ending.
Prove it, then.
I'll bet you a hundred yen.
[GIGINA]
Aha, perfect fit!
Who's laughing now, Gayus?
[GAYUS]
You're right.
Laugh at me all you want.
[GAYUS hums]
[GIGINA]
Good work, son.
Now release your father.
Gayus.
Open the door at once.
I'm sorry, sir,
but we have a fee for escaping.
I hope you have a hundred yen.
[GIGINA]
Let me out, or I swear
I'll separate your
neck from your torso.
Go right ahead.
Of course,
you'll need to find a way
to break out of
your precious cabinet
before you can do anything.
[GIGINA]
There's your fee.
Open it.
Oops, I forgot.
The door-opening fee
recently changed
from a hundred yen
to a thousand.
Plus, there's the mandatory
10,000 yen gratuity
on top of that.
[GIGINA]
Release me!
[gasps]
Wow, Gigina.
I gotta say, you've
never looked so good.
[GIGINA] You will atone
for Tarelk's dismemberment
with your life!
[GIGINA yells]
[GAYUS grunts]
All right! I take it back!
Your son's cool!
[phone rings]
[GAYUS]
What's up, Largonkin?
Yeah, sure.
Be right there.
[LARGONKIN]
Hm?
Hey! You made it!
Allow me to introduce you
to our top people here.
That's Iegie and Jabeira.
They're both 12th-rank.
You must've heard of
Vice President Yahkto.
'Sup. You must be
the sword dancer.
Hey, Old Man Largonkin.
What's so special
about this guy?
Just what I expected
from Mr. Draken Warrior.
Your kind's always crazy.
And you look like an Alurian,
meaning you're inferior.
[IEGIE, GIGINA grunting]
Cut it out, you two.
[JABEIRA]
That's Iryu.
12th-order electromagnetic
optics curse.
Were you scared?
Just ignore him.
He can't contain his
jealousy over your title
as the top Jushiki swordsman
in Eridana, that's all.
[IEGIE scoffs]
Anyway.
I shouldn't ask, but...
[gasps]
...you're not seeing
anybody, are you?
Uh, sorry. Yeah.
[JABEIRA grunts, groans]
Damn, so you're somebody's pet!
I hope she puts you down,
you flea-bitten dog!
[thud]
When her mood changes,
she becomes a completely
different person.
I swear, there are normal
people working here.
[YAHKTO] We still don't
know what Magatsushki is.
Some people believe
they are information
manifested as creatures
that exist in the same phase.
Yet another common
theory postulates
their very existence
is a type of Jushiki.
Therefore,
in order for Magatsushki
to form their bodies,
it is necessary for
them to absorb matter
from the world around
them and rearrange it--
Boring.
Give us the abridged version?
In short,
Magatsushki have a completely
different makeup than humans do.
So, their minds and motives
can be difficult to understand.
There's one thing that's
pretty clear, though.
They're getting closer
to the center of the city.
Yeah, that's true.
Not sure what the
reason is behind it yet,
but... the pattern's there.
We'll have to keep
investigating.
[WOMAN 7A]
Wait, sir!
You can't just--
[LARGONKIN]
Can we help you?
Mr. Largonkin.
Pardon my intrusion.
I'm honored to meet you.
My name is Deacon Sarvey.
I came here to
give you something.
Please enjoy this
token of our esteem.
And now, let us continue
with our happy play.
Settle in for act two.
This one's a tragedy.
[MAN 7M screams]
[SARVEY laughs]
[GAYUS]
Deacon Sarvey!
[SARVEY] Ah! Ooh!
Disrespect the father of death?
Fools, all of you! [laughs]
Did he just...
eat his Jushiki power?
[chuckles] And he promoted
himself from Deacon to Father.
Now! Attack him with Fel Fu!
That little toy castle
was a Magatsushiki, too!
The father attacks
while the box defends him.
So even the Magatsushiki
are learning the art of combat.
[SARVEY laughs]
Iegie!
Jabeira!
Get ready!
Right!
[grunts]
[SARVEY yells]
[LARGONKIN yells]
My, you're impudent!
We're not done! Get back here!
[SARVEY groans]
Ha, ha. Never underestimate
Gaft poison, gramps!
[SARVEY yells]
[yells]
[SARVEY screams]
[GIGINA grunts]
Y'know, I'm thinking this
could use a woman's touch.
[SARVEY screams]
[SARVEY laughs]
That was weird.
[clapping]
What a talented cast.
Give us a bow!
Oh, don't take it too seriously.
It's only showbusiness!
I'm just here to
introduce myself for today.
Well, unless... you feel you
haven't spilled enough blood.
Screw you!
Calm down.
[LARGONKIN] You're not
ordinary Magatsushiki, are you?
[AMUPURA]
Well, aren't you astute!
I am type number 498,
although many have called me
"the grave crawler."
The illustrious entertainer,
Viscount Amupura.
I am Baron Janahn Ghalan--
type 502,
or "the weaver of war."
So you're numbered.
Does that mean you're...
Great Magatsushiki?
Correct again!
And all you lucky ducks
have been selected
to serve on the committee
for our little evening party.
You should be quite honored.
Amupura.
Look at his right hand.
How about that!
Our friend sporting
an Eye of the Cosmos,
taken from the Vaisen!
[GAYUS gasps]
How did an insignificant
wretch like you
get a hold of such a thing?
Don't lie to me, boy.
[GAYUS gasps]
[AMUPURA]
Ooh, Baron Janahn Ghalan,
I'm having far too
much fun, aren't you?
Now, about the party.
What would you say
if we were to make
one teeny-tiny
modification to the rules?
Fine.
I propose, as a required
condition for victory,
we bet their heads
and that ring.
The curtain will be
coming down very soon now.
The final act is at
noon in three days.
If the game isn't won by then,
we will destroy the board.
What's in three days?
Damn those two.
They only speak in riddles.
[GAYUS] Countless tragedies
have been set in motion
by nothing more than a simple
inability to communicate.
Without understanding,
the world is an infinite desert,
where words and meaning
perish in the sand.