[SOLDIER 8A]
We're in position.
[yawns]
[SOLDIERS]
Cheers!
Here's to another win.
Nothin' can stop us!
We're undefeatable
with Remedius on our side!
[chuckles]
Y'know, I didn't expect you
to have so much talent
as a tactical commander.
Glad I surprise you.
Thanks, Zemunn.
But, my strategic thinking
is merely the result
of my fondness for chells.
I'm curious.
Why do you continue to
partake in this battle?
No one would hold it against you
if you went home to Tsevellen.
Maybe.
[REMEDIUS]
But I can't turn my back
on the truth I've learned
since coming here.
Jushiki was meant
to bring happiness,
but it's being used
for oppression.
I simply can't allow
such injustice.
Injustice, huh?
[REMEDIUS] Diplomacy will
change nothing at this point.
Action is the only
true means for reform.
Although, all of our actions
utilize force and violence.
That's right, but it's pure.
You use force for
the right reasons.
It's the only option
you've been given.
[YAHKTO] Father. I wholly
surrender myself unto your hand.
[FUNERAL ATTENDEES cry]
I am prepared for anything
and I accept it.
May your soul dwell in me
and may it reside within
all beings of your creation,
illuminating their lives
with solace and love.
[GAYUS]
Hm?
What's wrong?
[GIGINA]
I can't do this.
Participating in these rituals
would betray my homeland.
C'mon, dude.
[thud]
[GIGINA] You shall drench
your body of abundant dreams
in blood, weaving a heavenly
robe of moonlight and stardust.
Henceforth, idleness
and transience shall vanish,
as the pale messengers disperse
and forget the need to
compare their own ferocity.
[GIGINA] Even our most
joyous days are somehow sad.
Making a child's
dream come true...
...is still not enough
to end the loneliness.
I believe in love--
a love that is without
reason, without words,
with only an intense passion.
[GIGINA]
Youth was no more than a scar.
Naivety tumbles forward,
falling from immortality
to the ephemeral.
That fleeting eternity,
that smile of yours
perished so quietly.
[GIGINA] It is all that remains,
singing from within my heart.
That's just a silly song
Premelena would sing
for a night chat.
Seemed fitting for
such a somber occasion.
[sighs]
[GAYUS]
So we done here?
This all you got?
A river of useless tears
spilt over a dead coworker?
Lotta good that's gonna do him.
--Heartless creep!
--You wanna die?
Leave your arms
holstered, fools!
Gayus has a point.
We need to focus on
who killed our peer.
The damn Magatsushiki
and the Great Magatsushiki
who control them.
Amupura and Janahn Ghalan.
Am I wrong?
Right. We've shed enough tears.
Who's gonna kill the bastards so
our comrade can rest in peace?
[FUNERAL ATTENDEES]
We are!
[LARGONKIN] Then what the
hell're you waiting for?
Go to town!
Hunt down every single
last one of them!
Let's send the Magatsushiki
back to hell!
[FUNERAL ATTENDEES yell]
Thank you for that,
playin' the bad guy and all.
Only reason you
called me, isn't it?
You're a pain
in the ass, y'know.
So, I've been doing
some thinking.
Why don't you guys
join our agency?
What?
I'm being serious here.
I respect the two of you...
...more than you think I do.
Sorry, Largonkin, but no thanks.
We're comfortable with this
master-pet situation we've got.
I'm surprised to say it, but
I agree with what the pet says.
So, what then?
Am I just not good enough
to fill Diorg's shoes?
--Watch it, man.
--Largonkin!
[LARGONKIN]
My apologies.
Please forget I said that.
[LARGONKIN]
Oh, one more thing.
For what it's worth, a colleague
saw Cuello in Eridana.
[gasps]
[LARGONKIN] I thought it
only right to let you know.
What the hell's
Cuello doing here?
[VINNEL] Regarding the
Aurora Hammer research
you've requested.
We've uncovered some
rather perilous info
regarding a man named Parumuwei.
He's a former Rahzel employee,
but he makes his living selling
weapons in Eridana these days.
Our intel shows
that Aurora Hammer's
been in contact with him.
We just got the same info from
the police, so that confirms it.
Are they in Eridana
to obtain weapons?
Certainly looks
that way, at least.
[VINNEL] At the moment,
it's still hard to say.
I haven't been able to
pinpoint their hideout yet.
Seems as though someone from up
top is regulating information.
[GIGINA]
Hm?
Really? Are we talking
police or military?
[GIGINA]
Gayus.
Our missing man.
He's across the street.
That's him all right.
[CITIZENS chattering]
Sure took you two long
enough to notice me.
Heh. Well, thanks for
being so obvious about it.
We're really getting
surrounded a lot lately.
Yeah, everyone
wants a piece of me.
Guess the world's finally
taking note of my charms.
There are too many.
It's a pain, but should we?
Not just yet.
So, Egurrd.
You've got us trapped,
but you haven't actually
bothered attacking us.
Am I wrong in assuming you
don't actually want us dead?
Brass wants to meet you.
Follow me.
Hey, Egurrd.
There's a thousand
better ways to say that.
[EGURRD]
Hm?
And each one of them includes
a single common word. "Please."
I've brought them as requested.
Good work.
Welcome, Offensive Jushikiists.
Glad you're here.
I'm Lieutenant Colonel Gohhel.
I'm the head director
of Dragon's Jaw.
I assume that you're
familiar with our work?
Yeah, I know of Dragon's Jaw.
They're a strategic
special ops task force
that were established at the
behest of Queen Xenobia of Ilm.
I knew Eggurd had the stench
of a military man on him.
[EGURRD]
Excuse me?
I noticed you opened your
cigarette pack from the bottom.
The unique habit of
a man who's seen combat.
You could've shared that
observation with me, y'know.
Not my fault you're
too dumb to use your eyes.
Ahem. Shall we talk?
I imagine you'd like to know
the reason we revealed our hand.
We would like you to refrain
from any further investigation
into the Rahzel Company
or the Aurora Hammer.
Our mission is to eliminate
all hostile forces
plotting against
the Dragon Empire.
We can't risk the involvement
of amateurs complicating things.
I hope you understand.
[GAYUS]
Can't say I do.
The Aurora Hammer is unwavering
in their intent to overturn
the dictatorship in Urmun.
And we both know
Dochetta's a thorn
in the side of
the Dragon Empire.
I could understand if you were
maneuvering to assist them,
but defeating them
doesn't make any sense.
It does sound like a
backwards plan of action.
[GAYUS] The only logical
reason I can conjure up...
...is that you've
got tracks to cover.
Like Viscount Remedius
joining the Aurora Hammer.
[EGURRD gasps]
[GOHHEL]
Stand down.
I'm afraid you're right.
After witnessing
the misery in Urmun
while being held as a hostage,
the Viscount came to sympathize
with the Aurora Front.
And to make matters
even worse...
Colonel, sir!
[GOHHEL]
Party Leader Zemunn's followers
didn't care for his planned
reconciliation with Dochetta.
So they joined up with a man
named Zhuo Lu and ousted Zemunn.
From there, they formed an
even more extreme organization
known as Aurora Hammer.
You're telling me a hostage took
over an anti-government outfit?
[GOHHEL]
The Viscount is Tsevellen.
With this turn of events,
it could be perceived
the Dragon Empire is meddling
in the affairs of Urmun.
Yes, it could.
So that raid during the hostage
exchange was a distraction.
Your real objective there...
...was to assassinate
Viscount Remedius.
That exchange was a farce.
Nothing more than a
show by the Viscount
to secure funds for his group.
We simply played along
to take advantage.
So the poison in the
identifier device--
that was your nasty
handiwork, wasn't it?
We had all of Aurora
Hammer right there.
It's not like we could pass up
the opportunity
to eradicate them.
You understand now, don't you?
We'll take it from here
with no further interference.
And this isn't
a request, gentlemen.
It's an order.
To be perfectly clear,
even if Calpulnia comes begging
tearfully on her hands and knees
for you to help her,
you firmly turn her down.
That's all I have to tell you.
And please try not to forget
that this order is coming
from the government.
[creaking, clattering]
That all adds up to
1,023,420,000 yen.
Gotta say, it's a pleasure
doing business with you.
I'm impressed that you
hid all of this, Parumuwei.
Quite crafty.
I was informed you're
a former Rahzel employee.
Yeah, I am.
I'm curious.
How in the world
do you intend to
covertly transport all of this?
[ZHUO LU] I don't see how
that's any of your concern.
Say... are you, um...
Are you actually serious
about purchasing that?
I feel like I should be
more upfront with you.
The thing was
never even completed.
Rahzel and the military
only got so far with the project
before abandoning it.
[ZHUO LU]
I couldn't care less.
You don't plan on
actually using it?
It was only intended
as deterrence.
And besides, one would
need to complete
the entire composition
shiki in order to use it.
[gasps]
No way.
Impossible.
You can't be--!
[chuckles]
You look a little
surprised and perplexed
as to why we've captured you,
Viscount Remedius Levvi Rahzel.
[REMEDIUS groans]
[gasps] You filthy murderer!
Hah. This one's got some
piss and vinegar in her.
Seems as though the royalty
of the Dragon Empire
has a taste for wild kittens
that like to scratch and claw.
Dochetta!
What you're doing is wrong!
[DOCHETTA scoffs]
Is it?
And just what have you seen
with your own eyes, Viscount?
Naive fool.
This nation can't be saved
by ideals or justice.
It's far too late for
that fairy tale ending.
Let me explain
why we've captured you.
The truth is, Remedius, you're
a walking, talking pestilence.
And trust me, I'm not the
only one who feels that way.
[REMEDIUS gasps]
You're deserving of a truly
special punishment, Viscount.
I'll make sure you die
in the worst pain imaginable.
And every second of your death
will be wracked with despair.
[ZHUO LU] The Viscount
Remedius... no longer exists.
[JIV] Just shut up and
take a seat, will you?
First, accounting.
It looks like a child's
in charge of your expenses.
You're wasting money
on frivolous junk.
Second, you're both
adult men, aren't you?
You can at least pretend
to be on good terms
while you're working together.
Jeez.
C'mon, there must've
been one time
where you two saw
eye to eye on something.
Nope.
Will you just shake hands
and bury the hatchet?
What? But I haven't even
argued with Gigina today.
[JIV] You have
every other day, though.
Do it properly, damn it.
This is proper.
It's a Draken handshake.
Yeah, he's right.
Every once in a while,
he manages to say something
that's not utter crap.
That is not the thing
you should be agreeing on!
Well done!
I'm proud of you guys.
Oh, no! I lost track of time.
I have to get to work.
Wait.
I thought you told me
you had the day off.
My boss and I are
scheduled to visit
the Rahzel Company
campus tomorrow,
so we need to prepare for that.
I'll be back in time
for lunch, though.
[GAYUS]
Rahzel?
You're going out
to their island?
Yup. I'm really kind of excited.
I'll see you at our usual
spot at the park, okay?
[GAYUS]
Uh, sure.
And Gigina, you're invited
to come along, too.
Bye.
Huh.
I almost feel sorry for
how rough your life must be.
[GAYUS] Rahzel Company's
gem supplement ring,
the Remetogen IV!
[GAYUS whines]
[JABEIRA]
I said no, damn it!
You don't need it in battle
and our work expenses
won't cover it.
I'm not gonna let you waste any
more money on an impulse buy!
[GAYUS]
Is that you, Jabeira?
[JABEIRA] Hm? Well, well,
if it isn't Gayus.
What a nice surprise.
You know what would
make it better, though?
If you choked to death,
you bastard.
Jabeira.
Your personality
managed to switch gears
smackdab in the
middle of a sentence.
[JABEIRA scoffs]
Quit analyzing me, Iegie.
And I ain't allowing you
to make that purchase,
so put it back!
[GIGINA]
Hm?
Is that guard ornament
you're holding
Furniture Craftsman
Toldam's Lion Tooth?
For an uncultured Draken, you're
actually pretty well-versed.
But can you tell me
which period it's from?
[GIGINA]
Hm. Middle.
If you want me to
be more specific,
it's from when he was working
with painter Iem Adder.
It's an exceptionally
rare piece.
Looks like you and I share
more than a few hardships.
I guess that's true.
But you two seem like
you work well together.
You're happy, at least.
[JABEIRA]
What? You're not happy?
Here's the thing.
Our agency? We're all
basically family.
I was a mess before
Largonkin took me in.
I was reeling from a recent
divorce, just lost my job,
and had nowhere to go.
Same with Iegie.
He's got a similar story.
He's come to adore
Chief Largonkin like a father.
Family, huh?
Don't say it like a bad thing!
[gasps]
[JABEIRA] Iegie,
don't trade that with him!
You'll lose money!
[ROLCA] There ya go.
I'm all done with the repairs.
Damn, man, you went all out
with the seventh-order
Jushiki on this thing.
Talk about overkill.
No wonder it broke down.
You swapped the engine chamber
with a Rahzel one, huh?
[ROLCA]
Yeah.
That all right with you?
Sure!
Great job, as always.
Now then, go on and
hand over that Majouken.
[GAYUS gasps]
Wait, are you saying--
Yeah, well, you had a part
in that Magatsushki
incident, didn't you?
Consider this an
early investment.
A temporary rental.
Are you sure?
Just don't die on me.
Or at least pay your tab first.
And besides.
[GAYUS]
What?
Let's talk inside.
[ROLCA] Gayus, where exactly
did you come across this?
It was a rotten gift left behind
by a man I utterly despise.
It's called the
Eye of the Cosmos.
The Eye of the Cosmos, eh?
So? What were the
analysis results?
Well, I wasn't able to find
much, but I can tell you this.
The carving on it's engraved
from the scales of a dragon
that's been alive
for over 10,000 years.
Ten thousand?
As in nine more than a
1,000-year class Altar?
That's right.
We're talkin' about a dragon
that far outranks that.
And I've put this
through the ringer.
Ran it through
all kinds of equipment,
but it's unidentifiable.
Although I did get
one analysis report
that something was
pulsating within it.
[GAYUS]
And what does that mean?
[ROLCA] Well, simply put, this
ring of yours is somehow alive.
Alive?
I hope you take my advice here.
Best thing you can do is give
that back to the man you hate.
[BOTH giggling]
Did you have fun?
[GIRL 8C]
Uh-huh!
[JIV]
It's so peaceful here.
[GAYUS]
Yeah.
I feel bad.
I don't know why I didn't think
to buy some for Gigina, too.
[GAYUS] Trust me,
it would've just gone to waste.
Don't mind him.
I know, it's just...
Jiv?
[LARGONKIN]
Gayus. What a coincidence.
[GAYUS]
Largonkin?
[LARGONKIN]
Jivenya, was it?
She seems nice.
That she is.
She's an amazing woman.
You better hurry up and
start a family with her.
Trust me, you won't regret it.
You might think that, but
you and I are nothing alike.
[LARGONKIN]
Hm?
I could die at any time
in my line of work.
I live life on the
edge at all times.
A happy life sounds
like nothing more than
some make-believe
fairy tale to me.
You're so young.
You need to clear your head.
Forget Cuello and move on.
That's enough!
[gasps]
Diorg is dead and gone.
Stratos is left to suffer
and rot without a soul.
And then there's Cuello...
Gigina and I are the only
ones left with the agency.
That's all.
[phone rings]
[sighs]
Another Magatsushiki
has surfaced.
Gigina.
No, we don't need you.
You won't be any use to us
in your current state.
You smell lovely tonight.
Is that Desire
No. 9 by Algamon?
[gasps]
It's tough to trust a man who
recognizes a perfume by scent,
especially one I've never worn.
Observation's the mark
of a kind man, that's all.
[GAYUS]
Oh, I see.
I'm...
[WOMAN 8E giggles]
I was just thinking
about the past.
Huh?
[GIGINA]
There was a time in my life
when I considered myself happy.
A time when I had people
I could call my friends.
I'd forgotten until today.
No.
The truth is,
I wanted to forget.
Oh. But why?
I don't answer questions
from my prey.
[WOMAN 8E]
Oh?
[GAYUS, GIGINA]
Cuello.
Where the hell did we go wrong?
What's wrong? Talk to me.
[JIV]
Earlier today,
what exactly did
Largonkin say to you?
Uh... It was nothing.
Just some silly stuff
from the past.
[JIV]
Was it about that Cuello person?
The one who wore Desire
No. 9 before you met me?
God, Gayus.
You actually called me
Cuello in your sleep.
Jiv, look.
It's just...
Tell me why!
Why won't you look
at the here and now?
Why won't you look at me?
Just what the hell are you
actually looking at?
Is it something that
you can't share with me?
Can you share it with Gigina?
Or only... with this Cuello?
Listen.
[JIV]
Go home for the night.
Please leave.
[GAYUS]
Such a hard-ass.
You're a genuine
hard-ass, Gayus.
Someone goes and digs up a few
old scars and look at you now.
It doesn't matter
how hard I try to forget.
My past is right
where I left it.
Always questioning me...
...whispering in my ear
and asking if I
made the right choice.
Damn it.
Such a hard-ass.
You really wanna prove yourself?
Impossible.
You can't escape your past!
I see. Well done.
I swear.
I simply can't help but loathe
myself on nights like these.
[GAYUS]
A kind angel flies into the sky,
trying to save the earth.
It mistakenly flew at a height
the people could reach.
So the angel of salvation's
wings and flesh
became the people's desire,
until there wasn't a single
feather left to save them.