[ROLCA grunting]
[yawns]
[groans]
[ROLCA]
Hey. Quit slackin' off.
You just had to drop in
unannounced last night.
The least you can do is
work to earn your keep.
I'm just not used to
making money this early.
Ugh, you still
smell like a sewer.
--[GAYUS sniffs]
--[GIGINA yawns]
[phone rings]
Dammit, Soleil,
get over here right now!
Sorry, but the number you have
dialed is not in service--
Somebody raided
the evidence storage
at our community safety
division and managed to
steal some information
about the heads of
black and fire dragons.
[GAYUS]
That's not good.
Since the proof is gone,
I'm cutting your reward!
Also, I spilled milk on my shirt
this morning, I broke a plate,
and my daughter
ran away from home,
so you're gonna pay
for all those things too.
What kinda crap is that?
Sounds like a shrewd guy.
[GAYUS]
Nah, he's just a jerk.
Anyway, do you know
anything about this?
Huh. Not sure.
It's a shred of clothing
from that witch we ran off.
Never seen fabric
like this before.
It might be a good idea
to get a second opinion
from a specialist.
[GAYUS]
Please. As soon as you can.
Happy to help out.
Always nice to do
real Jushiki shop work.
[GIGINA]
This is a great gem.
It is! You're lookin' at one of
the immaculate masterpieces
by legendary gemstone craftsman
Fleggun of late-age Damascus!
Thanks to a few
specialized equations,
it's top-notch at
Jushiki-disabling.
So it's a good choice
for the front line.
Good to know--
Not so fast.
Even this idiot knows
not to make major purchases
without running it by
his accountant first.
[GAYUS gasps]
I tell you literally
every day how broke we are.
What the hell makes you think
you can buy Jushiki equipment
worth as much as a house?
I needed it. Mine was
getting worn out.
[sighs] "Was," huh?
[GIGINA] And I've already signed
a monthly payment contract.
Thanks for your business.
[GAYUS groans]
[CITIZENS chattering]
[doorbell rings]
Hello-- [gasps]
Gayus, you smell like a sewer!
[GAYUS] Better than another
girl's perfume, right?
If that happened, I wouldn't
let you into my house.
You really jumped into a sewer?
[GAYUS]
Yeah. It kinda had to be done.
Well, let's get you
out of those clothes.
The bath is all ready.
I'm pretty sure I can
take off my own pants.
But isn't it more fun
if I give you a hand?
Jivenya!
I gotta have you right now.
Sorry, babe, we can't!
Aren't you supposed to go
to work this afternoon?
Who needs work?
Not a good idea.
You really need to keep
your head in the game, Gayus.
Your job is dangerous enough
without me distracting you
before you head off to work.
What you do bothers me
sometimes. It's so risky.
[GAYUS]
I know.
I'm sorry I couldn't
take you to the festival.
[JIV]
It's fine.
--But we still can't do it.
--[GAYUS] Eh?
You smell so gross
I think I might puke.
We now bring you an update
regarding the Serial
Jushikiist Murders.
Earlier today on Wella Street
near the middle of Eridana City,
this man, a Jushiki engineer
named Lolorf Iscafendler.
was attacked with
offensive Jushiki.
The suspect is still at large.
[CITIZENS chattering]
[VINNEL]
Gayus.
You got a second, Vinnel?
[VINNEL]
What would you like to know?
I met this weird woman.
Gimme all you got on
somebody named Nidvork.
Green eyes and dark hair.
Either Alurian or from
the eastern Seg region.
From what I can tell,
she's a gravity Jushikiist
working at the Enlightened
level, or possibly even higher.
Oh, and she kept going
on about her husband.
I think she said his
name was Eninguluud.
[VINNEL] That's more
than enough to find her.
[VINNEL]
Hmm, nothing.
Yeah, I didn't find a thing
when I looked her up.
[VINNEL] Many people withhold
their personal information
from public records,
even members of
the Jushikiist Guild.
It might be helpful to try
hacking into the guild's or
the government's data stores.
You're the information broker.
Don't you think you
should handle that?
[VINNEL]
Of course. I'll do what I can.
Yo.
[ARZEL]
Oh, hey, Gayus.
Ten pollock
'n ten orders of bread.
Throw in some of today's
special while you're at it.
Wow, somebody's got an appetite.
Believe it or not,
it's all Gigina.
Front-line Jushikiists like him
can be notorious
for eating like pigs.
What's up, Arzel?
You made a big splash
yesterday, didn't you?
Oh, you saw that?
Sorta.
Ha! Look here!
The paper published my article
and all my photographs.
It's under my
boss's name, though.
"Tienlun Accord Resistance
Movement Sweeps Eridana City.
Protesters are adamant that
humans and dragons
can never reconcile."
You have to read the
whole thing, though, okay?
I put some serious
work into that!
There's info about
why the other side
is in favor of the accord, too.
They're saying without it,
we'd be at war right now!
So, I assume you're a "yes"
on the Seven-City Alliance
ratifying the Tienlun Accord?
It makes sense to me,
but I can understand
how both parties must feel.
A lot of people have lost their
friends and family members
because of conflicts
with the dragons.
But, anyway,
I told you about the
Jushikiist murders, right?
Have you heard
anything else yet?
Not a thing.
You do realize you're
a prime target, though.
Hey, this looks like
a job for Horton!
Ha-ho!
It's time for Horton's
Spicy Fortune Telling
to reveal your future!
[GAYUS] It's time for you
to go jump off a bridge.
Voila!
--[screeching, bang]
--Steer clear of runaway cars!
I took a photo out of habit,
but this doesn't seem
very newsworthy.
[GAYUS groans]
Look, man.
I still don't get why you're
fine with riding a bike,
but you're hopeless
when it comes to cars.
Because bikes are
basically like horses.
Cars are a mystery to me.
They are the vehicles of demons.
Catch up to civilization,
already.
Let's get this over with.
After today,
no more bodyguard duty.
[elevator dings]
I'm sorry for the early start.
Actually, I seem
to be a bit late.
To think His Eminence
Cardinal Mouldeen of all people
is 30 minutes late
to an appointment.
Forgive me, sir, but
have you never heard of
the ancient piece of
Draken wisdom that tells us,
"No one can swing their blade
without their head"?
Obviously I'm stealing
Gigina's line here,
but my impression of him is
pretty spot-on, don't you think?
Well, as much as I'd like to do
my impression of you, Gayus,
I doubt the Cardinal
would appreciate
seeing me make a drunken fool
of myself in the streets.
That's some big talk
there, Draken-boy.
How about we discuss
your diary instead?
I should mention
all your entries
sound like a
five-year-old wrote them.
How dare you!
You broke into
the office cabinet?
It wasn't hard to unlock
it with that technique
we learned from our old bounty.
You should probably
be more careful
where you hide your stuff.
Oh, like you?
As I recall, you make it a point
to choose your storage devices
for lewd images more carefully
than you'd choose a wife.
[gasps] I know damn well
I didn't say that to you!
You didn't have to. I heard
you muttering to yourself
while I was repairing
the inside of the dresser.
"Repairing" it, huh?
I hope it comes to
life and eats you!
That'd be the greatest
piece of furniture ever made.
Uck.
[clapping]
[MOULDEEN]
You put on quite a show.
Staying here to
watch your antics
might be even more entertaining
than all the sightseeing
I had scheduled.
Gayus Levina Soleil
versus Gigina Jardi Doruk
Meleios Ashley-Bufh, eh?
I'm surprised you
remember our names.
We're supposed to
just be temporary help.
Whenever I become
involved with anyone,
the least I can do is remember
names, wouldn't you agree?
Yeah, maybe.
Anyway, what sights would
His Eminence the Cardinal
like to see on his final day
in our beautiful city?
Ah, that's right.
The first engagement for today
is the tea party I've arranged
with another visitor from afar.
If my expectations are correct,
it's sure to be an
interesting event.
You aren't praying.
Do you not believe in God?
That's a difficult question.
Judging by the state
of the world these days,
it's hard for me to believe
He exists in any physical way.
I assume you don't
need me to tell you
those are blasphemous
words to utter
in front of the faith's
guardian... and in church.
Helodel's late fiancée, Shifaka,
she died because of a dispute
between the Dragon Empire
and the Seven-City Alliance.
If there really are
such things as "gods,"
then why do they
let so many people die
because of things like
accidents, disease, and wars?
And what possible reason
could they have had
to take my
innocent sister Aleciel?
You think it's blasphemous
of me to ask that question?
[MOULDEEN]
Well, perhaps.
Either God does not exist or
He is exceedingly merciless.
Huh?
But how painful would
life be without Him?
The dead cannot return to us.
Miracles aren't real.
Religion exists to give people a
sense of purpose and direction.
That's why the
majority of society
has no choice but
to shut their eyes
and pretend in order
to go on living.
You should be careful not to
search too hard for reasons.
You tend--well, all Jushikiists
tend to be desperate
to find some greater
meaning in all this.
But that's being arrogant.
We can never hope to achieve
that level of wisdom.
What do you mean? I don't--
[MOULDEEN]
Gayus.
I'm sorry, but I've
given you my answer.
I suggest you find
some of your own.
And some questions as well.
After all, my boy,
facing questions
that have yet to be
answered is the inspiration
that drives humankind
above all else, is it not?
And of the countless paths we
human beings can take in life,
it is also the most
honorable and rewarding.
[GIGINA yawns]
Are we finished waxing
poetic yet, sir?
You know, appearances aside,
you two seem
incredibly well-matched.
Oh, yeah, I totally
agree with you.
When you take away his
stupidity, his furniture fetish,
and his complete lack of
financial responsibility
and common courtesy,
the guy's not a bad partner.
Flawed though he is,
you're no better.
Your weakness is your
inability to accept things
for what they are.
Do not let yourself
be limited by that.
Huh?
Our visitor's arrived,
Your Eminence.
Greetings! I've been
so eager to meet with you!
And I with you.
This way, if you don't mind.
[footsteps]
I'm probably gonna
regret asking you this,
but what are some qualities you
look for in your ideal chair?
That one is easy.
It needs the quintessence
of a chair--
noble and beautiful
in equal measure.
The pews here must have
a respectable lineage.
You can tell that much
by their pious expressions.
So, you know who
that was, right, Gayus?
He's from the Lapetodes
Seven-City Alliance.
His name is Azu Bita.
Yeah, I know.
Azu Bita's one of
the right-hand men
of the Alliance House's
Supreme Chairman Kai Kuyou
and the executive in charge
of the Democratic Liberal Party.
If you knew that,
why didn't you speak up?
Well, "The man who
avoids danger...
...will survive
to see another day."
That's what dad told me--
Hey!
Huh?
[gasps]
[GAYUS gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
Are they with--?
[GIGINA yells]
[SOLDIER 3A groans]
[GAYUS grunts]
--Gigina!
--[GIGINA] Right!
[groans]
[sighs]
[gasps]
Watch out!
I'll take it from here.
[GAYUS]
Good!
What's happening?
Suffice it to say these
guys aren't our friends!
All of your other guards
have been killed, Cardinal.
Prepare to run.
How are we supposed
to make it out?
Damn it, you'd think
a church building
that deals with
royalty all the time
would have at least
one escape route!
We've picked off a few of them,
but I guarantee you
there'll be more.
If Gigina and I can
stop them, we will.
If not, we'll at least
buy some time trying.
Compared to you,
we're expendable.
But if you were to die,
a war would break out
between the Dragon Empire
and the Seven-City Alliance.
We don't want to see
history repeat itself.
[gasps]
[MOULDEEN]
Yes, you may be right.
I applaud your willingness to
give your life for someone else,
and I believe
such acts of courage
should be generously rewarded.
In that case, there's
something that matters to me
a lot more than money or medals.
If I manage to
leave here with my life
then I will consider
no payment too great.
All I want from you
is the truth, sir.
[MOULDEEN] Hmm. As much
as you'd like to hear.
Heads up!
Let us now share in
the banquet of battle!
[GIGINA] Sparks fly as the
blades of two separate lives
meet in combat.
And for a single moment,
the world and I
share the same pulse.
This is your chance
to demonstrate
the extent of your power!
Show me what you can do!
[yells]
[gasps, pants]
[gasps]
[SOLDIER 3B groans]
I guess that about does it.
[GIGINA grunts]
[GAYUS groans]
That's quite impressive.
I had no idea there was
an assassin in the world
skilled enough to challenge
a Draken warrior.
Leave your name as you die.
[CURACAO]
No. All I can tell you
is that I'm a ninja who
protects the Kouga clan.
[GIGINA grunts]
What's that?
Nothing good.
It's a third-order chemical
alchemy Jushiki called Chilliat.
[GAYUS] It generates
hundreds of millions
of monomolecular needles.
And they can pierce through
almost anything.
[GIGINA]
I noticed that.
[GIGINA grunts]
[GIGINA groans]
[yells]
[CURACAO panting]
[CURACAO]
The Kouga...
...complete every mission!
[gasps]
[GAYUS grunts]
[GAYUS gasps]
Aleciel! Aleciel!
[gasps]
[inaudible]
[GAYUS]
I wish I could've died, too.
But this is how
it's supposed to be.
[GAYUS gasps]
Let me go!
Please, let me go!
[GAYUS gasps]
[GAYUS]
Hey there.
[gasps]
Oh. You're awake.
Am I in a hospital bed?
[JIV]
Um, yes.
You've been admitted to
Eridana Private Hospital.
At least I have a beautiful
nurse watching over me.
--[GAYUS gasps]
--[JIV sobs]
[JIV]
My Gayus came back to life!
[GAYUS]
Uh... You're hurting me.
You're okay.
Oh, Gayus, I was so afraid.
I thought I'd lost you forever!
[JIV cries]
[NIDVORK panting]
It would seem even for
someone of my fortitude,
a spell that strong
is difficult to endure.
[cat meows]
[NIDVORK]
Do you disagree with me, feline?
[meows]
[cat meowing]
You don't seem to
fear me in the least.
[NIDVORK] I swear,
darling, these hands of mine
will do everything in
their power to avenge you.
[GAYUS] There are certain
things that are even deadlier
than pure, unadulterated malice.
Nothing is more dangerous
than benevolence to
the point of foolishness.
After all, how can you stop
a disaster caused by goodwill?