[GAYUS groaning]
Agh, damn.
I can't believe that bastard
used me as a meat shield.
[groans]
I'm a powerless,
low-level Jushikiist
without a penny to my name.
They used me up
and now they'll let me die.
What a pain.
[GAYUS, GIGINA]
This is a load of crap.
[GIGINA] A victory
that's less than triumphant
is an insult to the
proud Draken people.
[DIORG] Yeah. And it's a shame
we lost one of the rearguard.
Man. If only we
could find a good,
capable Jushikiist
lying around somewhere.
Forget it, Chief Diorg.
If they were worth anything,
they'd be snapped up
by another agency.
We should all just die now.
We've lost one man, Stratos.
We can't afford more casualties.
Too bad.
I guess that means I'll have to
come up with another way to die.
Look, Diorg.
There's garbage in the road.
Straight ahead.
I thought it was
dead already,
but it's putting up
a fight against my shoe.
[GAYUS groans]
Who are you calling garbage,
you big stupid ox?
[GAYUS]
This is a story from back when
my aspirations as a Jushikiist
were slightly higher.
[GAYUS pants]
I got him!
[GIGINA]
You idiot!
If you keep putting
the front line at risk,
you're a worse threat than him!
You fight like a damn amateur!
Hey!
It's not my fault if you're
too slow to dodge an attack!
If that's how you feel...
[gasps]
...then you're of no use to me!
Begone!
[GAYUS gasps]
Wow, thanks.
You're standing in the way
of a Draken sword.
You must not
value your life much.
I do value my life.
I just have a policy
not to allow unnecessary
killing, that's all.
So back off!
Are you suggesting it's
pointless to clear the street
of useless pieces of trash?
We both know that's
Chief Diorg's decision.
And since I'm the deputy chief,
I call the shots
when he's not around.
Your ideals are just as
disagreeable as you are.
What a nice compliment.
Thanks, Gigina.
Hold on, where are you going?
[GIGINA]
The furniture shop.
I need a break.
[sighs]
You jerk.
You're the one who
picked him up, you know.
[scoffs] I don't care if
the guy is a Draken swordsman.
Combat junkies like him can
take their shiny toy weapons
and go to hell.
Take a look at what
you've done here, Gayus.
[GIRL 12A crying]
[CUELLO]
Your bullheaded arrogance...
...is what caused
this devastation.
[GAYUS] Gigina and I
are just incompatible.
I hate that guy!
Well then, you'd better
get compatible, and fast.
Just like in that fight earlier.
You couldn't have done it alone.
You should have waited
for Gigina's help,
or for me to use
my electricity Jushiki.
[CUELLO] Plus, the curse you
used was excessively large.
What were you doing?
Trying to show off for someone?
Hey, are you even listening?
--Oh, Cuello.
--[CUELLO] Huh?
I'm sorry. I know my
lack of experience
probably causes you
nothing but grief.
I wouldn't say that, exactly.
[GAYUS]
I'm just nervous!
I have to stop dragging
everybody else down out there.
Because if I don't,
I'll get abandoned
all over again.
That's absurd!
We would never
abandon a teammate!
Cuello! Please promise
you don't hate me!
What? Of course
I don't hate you.
[GAYUS]
Okay, then.
[CUELLO gasps]
There's something I want to do.
Just be still.
[GAYUS] It's always been
kind of a fantasy of mine
to do it with a self-righteous
ice queen like you
and then throw her away like
a used piece of scrap paper.
[GAYUS gasps]
What d'you think you're doing?
Uh... Okay, I get it now.
You hate guys.
No, I'm pretty fond of most men.
They usually make
pretty good Jushikiists,
especially if they're
not the type
who likes to act all pitiful
just to gain sympathy
from a woman.
[sighs]
That's fine. I wouldn't want
to sleep with you anyway.
Glad we're agreed.
The truth is,
well, I don't really care for
men who are weaker than me.
[phone rings]
[CUELLO]
Hello?
Yes.
Right.
I understand.
This isn't good.
Stratos and Chief Diorg
have gone out on business.
Gigina's off being moody.
Who's left?
What a cheap routine.
I know you didn't
forget about me.
Oh well, at least you
recover quickly.
So, do you think you got
the guts for a mission, Gayus?
[CUELLO] Our target today
is Maslow Gossum.
[GAYUS]
Handsome guy.
Marriage fraud, right?
Actually, he attacked a
jewelry store about a month ago
and murdered two
security Jushikiists.
The losses added up to
a hundred million yen.
Later Maslow was apprehended
by the Largonkin Company's men.
But he escaped while
waiting for trial
and never revealed
the whereabouts
of the stolen jewelry.
So he was out on bail
after killing two people?
Yeah, and in order to come up
with enough to pay that bail,
Maslow had to borrow an
incredibly large amount of money
from a bail bond agent.
But that doesn't
make any sense.
If you run away,
then doesn't the court get
to pocket your bail money?
What's his endgame here?
That's exactly what we're
supposed to figure out.
The bail bondsman
is who hired us.
Wants us to capture him
in time for his trial
before the police do.
And, of course,
we can't kill the guy.
Plus, there's this.
[GAYUS]
Claymore.
He's a chemical
manipulation type.
And a tenth-grade
Jushikiist at that.
Are you scared?
Of course not!
Now, what's the plan?
First, we need to
dig up his past
and try to figure out
where he's hiding.
Till then, we lay low.
[GAYUS] Sure was easy to get
that informant to sell him out.
These are tough times.
Just goes to show you
humans are selfish creatures
and everyone's got a price.
Well, if it hadn't
been for that,
we might've never
found his exact location.
So, I guess I can't complain.
Now all we have
to do is catch him
and bring him back,
dead or alive.
[CUELLO]
I told you, no killing.
Can we skip past the
self-righteous talk, Cuello?
Killing is part of the job.
Sometimes we-- What?
[CUELLO] I'm going to go in
first and neutralize the target.
You're only here to serve as my
backup, are we clear about that?
Yeah, I know.
[knocking]
[CUELLO]
Hello?
It's the power company.
Routine inspection.
Anybody home?
[clattering]
[gasps] He's running!
Say goodbye!
[GAYUS]
Crap!
[gasps]
[CUELLO yells]
[MASLOW grunts, yells]
[MASLOW groans]
[gasps] Get him!
[CUELLO groans]
Almost.
[gasps]
[CUELLO]
Hey!
Gayus!
This looks bad. Hang on!
I'm sorry.
I am nothing but... trouble...
Let's save the self-deprecating
comments for later!
[GAYUS]
Oh, god. I'm...
[CUELLO]
Try to stay calm!
[GAYUS]
...gonna die.
Hold on!
[CUELLO humming]
[gasps] You're awake!
Stop looking!
Uh... sorry!
Uh-- wait, did you
do stuff to me in my sleep?
[CUELLO]
Ugh. You wish I did!
Why did you save me back there?
What?
[GAYUS]
I disobeyed your orders.
If that Maslow guy
had killed me,
it would've been my own fault.
So, there was no reason
for you to put your life at risk
to protect me.
I'm a sixth-grade.
You're five grades higher.
Your life is worth
more than mine.
[sighs]
Oh, Gayus. Listen.
I don't know what
you've been through,
but that's not how we
view things here.
It's normal to put
your life on the line
to help out a teammate.
That's just the way the Diorg
Jushikiist Agency operates...
...and it's my
own personal code.
You won't get far
in this business
without learning to lean
on people, okay, rookie?
There's no need
to be embarrassed.
It's natural.
I slowed everyone down
when I was new, too.
I used to get cocky
and ruin everything,
then cry at how useless I was.
Just take it slow.
As long as you keep on learning,
then... you'll be fine.
Hey, Cuello.
[CUELLO]
Yes?
Uh... thanks for saying that.
Now then.
I'm not gonna let you
stay in bed forever.
I had the Chief call
for Gigina to help us.
Once we all meet up,
it's time for a rematch.
I've already set up
a trap for him.
You're pretty strong.
[CUELLO]
No, not really.
It still scares me
that my enemies and I
won't stop until
we kill each other.
But still.
What's stronger than my fear...
...is my hatred for
anyone who hurts others.
That's what drives me.
I want to do
everything in my power
to keep the people I love
safe from danger.
[CUELLO]
And if possible,
I'd like to avoid killing.
I know it sounds like
self-righteous hypocrisy to you,
but...
...even if you laugh
or people mock me,
it will not change my resolve.
I'll still believe.
Oh, Cuello.
The way you're
making me feel is--
[doorbell buzzing]
That must be Gigina.
Come on in.
Well, lookie here.
Didn't think you'd survive.
That's too bad.
[scoffs]
Get outta the way or
die, you damn slowpokes!
Come on!
Put the pedal to the metal!
I'm Cuello,
the queen of the highway!
Hey, Gigina!
Why the hell did you
have to let her drive us?
Easy now, Cuello.
Hold on tight.
Mama's got a serious
need for speed, baby.
Let's race!
[GAYUS] All right, we still
haven't captured Maslow.
So, what's our next move?
[CUELLO]
This part's simple.
He's probably on edge
since our run-in yesterday.
And even if he isn't,
it's hard to sell high-value
gemstones in this nation.
Either way, his best strategy
at this point in time...
...is to leave the country.
But, this Maslow is
a high-profile criminal.
For him to get through
border security,
he would need a fake passport.
Yes, exactly.
Hence the trap I told you about.
If you use the right bait,
your quarry will catch itself
without you having
to do a thing.
I know you're here.
I've got the cash
for the passport.
What kind of moron
doesn't pay the forger
some hush money first?
[MASLOW groans]
Don't bother resisting.
I think you're outnumbered here.
Think again!
[GAYUS groans]
[gasps]
[MASLOW yells]
[BOTH grunt]
[yells]
[BOTH grunting]
[GAYUS yells]
[CUELLO]
Gayus!
[GIGINA groans]
Nice try, for a wimp!
You're in way
over your head, buddy!
Huh?
Are you trying to kill me?
[CUELLO]
Look out!
[MASLOW]
Heh.
[GIGINA groans]
[CUELLO yells, groans]
[groans]
[CUELLO yells]
[gasps]
[yells]
[CUELLO]
There we go.
Let's get this jerk
tied up, huh.
What now?
[GAYUS]
Wait, Gigina!
I told you already.
No one who values their life
stands against a Draken sword.
I have no choice but to
kill someone who does that.
You're not the only one
with personal rules, Gigina.
I'll say this again.
You're not killing anybody
as long as I'm around!
Those are just some
pretty words and nothing more!
If they are, then at least
I've still got my pride,
the same as you have yours!
If you haven't spilled
enough blood, here's mine!
[GIGINA]
Save it.
What would I gain
from taking your blood?
[groans, pants]
[GIGINA]
Cuello, hold out your arm.
[GAYUS]
That's pretty impressive.
Gigina's mastered the art
of healing-type Jushiki.
That's much better.
Thanks a lot.
You're an excellent
warrior, Cuello.
I truly admire your intensity.
Someday, I hope we get the
chance to fight to the death.
[chuckles]
I'm just doing the best
I can, one day at a time.
I refuse to be
a heartless killer.
There's always another way.
[DIORG] All right,
all together now, team!
Let's smile big.
This photo will commemorate
our newest member!
Hey.
Why does the chief look
like he just got beat up?
Thought he was at a meeting.
It was a meeting.
He said he got injured in of one
of Stratos's suicide bombings.
I almost had me this time.
Can we just take this picture
and get it over with?
[DIORG]
Sorry, Gigina.
Scoot a little to the
left for me, would ya?
Lift your head up, Stratos.
You're not dead yet.
Good!
We're ready!
[gasps]
Come on. Look at
the camera and smile.
Learn how to lean on us, Gayus.
We're your teammates.
And, here we go!
[GIGINA]
You could really use a shelf.
[GAYUS gasps]
Sorry, what did you say?
I said you ought
to have a shelf
to organize all those
dusty old things.
I suppose that I could
build one for you.
Well, if it's gonna
look anything like
that other piece of junk
you made recently...
...no thanks.
What's that?
You dare show disdain
for my beloved son Tarelk?
Yeah!
The trash apple doesn't fall
far from the garbage tree!
[GIGINA] If I'm garbage,
you're toxic waste!
--Huh?!
--[GIGINA] Yeah!
[BOTH groan]
I don't have time for this.
If we keep fighting,
I won't finish.
[scoffs] Maybe you would if
you'd stop getting caught up
in your silly memories.
[GIGINA]
Did you see that Remedius died?
[GAYUS]
Yeah.
Interesting.
[GAYUS]
Following the death of Dochetta,
Urmun descended
into a nasty civil war.
The Dragon Empire
deployed the military
in the name of peace, but...
...I doubt Mouldeen
will do anything else
to try and fix things.
[GAYUS] As long as Urmun is
consumed by political turmoil,
the Dragon Empire's economy
can continue to thrive.
I don't see why he'd
want to upset that.
In the end, most of
the people of Urmun
failed to respond
to the rallying cries
of the Aurora Hammer.
After a few sporadic
revolts and resistances,
the organization disintegrated,
and Remedius eventually
met his death,
still inhabiting
the identity of Zhuo Lu,
the Man-Eating
Dragon of the Sand.
His headless corpse
was found outside the city.
Most people presume
he must have been assassinated.
--[sighs]
--[knocking]
[JIV]
You there, Gayus?
Hurry up!
Jivenya,
where are you taking me?
The seabird shop!
I got all of us an invite
to Largonkin's big
welcome-home-from-
the-hospital party!
Jabeira and Iegie are
supposed to be there, too!
Wait, we're not about to have
a repeat of last time, are we?
Oh, probably.
The two of you never learn
from your past mistakes.
Sorry.
I didn't hear that.
But guess what?
Crab dinner!
Let's go feast on some crab!
[GIGINA]
What the--? Unhand me, woman!
[JIV]
Not happening!
[GAYUS]
The golden age is over.
[GAYUS] The sky that I saw
before has faded away.
But still...
I promise you'll have fun!
You'll never force me to say...
[GAYUS] ...I've got the
woman I love by my side...
...and a partner who
always has my back.
[GAYUS]
Beneath this new sky is a world
that I somehow both
despise and adore.
And that means...
[JIV]
Gayus!
Hurry up or we'll be late!
Okay.
Be right there.
[GAYUS]
...I have everything I need...
...right?