[GAYUS]
Tsevellen Year 223.
Using the Event
Induction Computer,
humanity successfully creates
its first space-time bubble.
The fundamental rules of physics
within the bubble are altered,
breaking the law of
conservation of energy,
including the Planck constant,
causing the emergence
of matter derived from
quantum field instructions.
The hyper-physical phenomenon
that allows matter to be
extracted at will
from vacuum fluctuations
forms the basis of
the system of technology
that will soon come
to be known as Jushiki.
[GAYUS] And now, we find
ourselves in Imperial Year 497.
[GAYUS] What was once called
"magic," and thought of as
the domain of dragons and
other abhorrent creatures,
has been correctly
identified as the power
that humans have gained
through Jushiki.
[GAYUS] Therefore,
dragons and the abhorrent
are no longer the subject
of awe and fear,
but enemies to be hunted down
and slain by humankind.
[growls]
[GAYUS] Those who specialize
in eliminating these foes
by weaving attack Jushiki
are referred to as
Offensive Jushikiists.
[GAYUS sighs]
Don't look at me like that.
This might be the buffer zone
between us and the dragons...
...but if you're
gonna eat people,
then you leave us with
no choice but to kill you.
So...
[GIGINA]
Bit late for apologies.
This is our job.
We are Offensive Jushikiists.
[GAYUS]
It still sucks.
[GIGINA]
But fighting the dragons
is the highest honor there is.
I'm okay with it.
Well, sure, honor's
really important to you.
I mean, you're one
of the fighting race.
But not all of us are
the noble Gigina Jardi
Doruk Meleios Ashley-Bufh.
If you're so smart, then what
was that sad excuse for an Aini?
[GAYUS]
What do you mean?
[GIGINA] You didn't generate
enough to cover the distance
between you and the target.
If I'd gotten there a
fraction of a second later,
you'd be dead right now.
[GAYUS]
Yeah, but--
I just figured
it'd be a good idea
to buy us a little
time, that's all.
I totally knew you'd
be there to back me up.
Come on, Gigina.
Any dragon killer
with half a brain
would expect his
loyal Draken to--
[GAYUS gasps]
Don't speak of my kind.
You aren't worthy.
[GIGINA]
I mean it.
[sighs] All right already!
You're such a pain in the ass.
Are all your people this touchy?
[GAYUS] I knew we
wouldn't get off that easy.
The report said we were
looking for a pair of dragons.
And they're 500-year class,
so they're gonna
put up a good fight.
Well, at least we know
what we'll be up against.
[dragon growls]
[GAYUS]
A black dragon!
Looks like an 800--
no, 900-year class!
An Altar!
--This is excellent!
--This is bad news!
Arsh Modai, huh?
Let's break through!
[yells]
[GIGINA grunts]
[growls]
[GIGINA]
Gayus!
[gasps, grunts]
Wait, is that Proke?
[groans]
It's even stronger
than we were expecting.
[GAYUS]
Healing Jushiki.
This is my first Altar.
You think we can win?
How should I know?
I've never fought
one of these either.
[chuckles]
Should be fun though--
Your kind is so messed up.
Either way, we can't breach
that barrier head-on.
[GAYUS]
We need a plan.
[clinking]
Okay. Let's go!
What part of "we need
a plan" don't you get?
[GIGINA yells]
[GIGINA grunting]
[GIGINA groans]
[GIGINA grunts]
[dragon roars]
[yells]
[roaring]
[yelling]
It's dead... right?
[exhales]
[groans]
So typical.
You had to make sure you were
the last one standing, huh?
If I was weak enough
to fall before you do,
I'd kill myself.
[cars honking]
[CIVILIANS chattering]
[SAZARAN]
You're supposed to be
the Viscount
Gayus Levina Soleil!
Now start acting like it!
Or is that big title
just for decoration?
[GAYUS]
Sorry, Chief Sutherland,
but as the third son, I'm
technically a Vice Viscount.
So, yeah, it is.
Well, after this catastrophe,
I don't need to tell you
that you won't be getting
the compensation you requested.
Huh? [gasps]
What the hell?
It was an 800-year!
A black dragon like that
could turn into an Altar!
[SAZARAN]
You're wasting public funds!
Listen, Chief!
[SAZARAN]
I've heard enough, boy!
Go learn how to be
decent human beings.
Till then, I want you
out of my office!
[GAYUS] I should see
if there's a Jushiki
to make his hair fall out.
That'll teach that old windbag.
People like him only
care about protocol,
and, of course,
covering their own asses.
But still...
I'm glad I beat that thing...
even if it was a semi-Altar.
Makes me think I can
slay a real one next time.
I think that blow to the head
might've rattled your brain.
'Cause next time,
you're dead.
As long as you and I are
partners, we can never lose.
Uh... I mean, yeah,
sure. You're right.
Most of the time we're
unstoppable. I'm just saying...
[GIGINA]
Hm.
May the sword and
the moon bless you.
[GAYUS sighs]
[OFFICIAL 1A]
As I said,
the Alsok territory
is not our main concern.
We must keep coexisting
with the Seven-City
Alliance of Lapetodes!
You mean surrender
our territory?
And to that pathetic nation?
[OFFICIAL 1A] Lapetodes
would say the same of us.
It's better to avoid conflict.
[OFFICIAL 1C] Give them an inch,
and they'll walk all over us!
[OFFICIAL 1B]
I agree!
Compromise is out
of the question!
It seems like this quarreling
will never end.
[XENOBIA] How impudent
of you, Cardinal Mouldeen.
Quite unfitting of the
Oujes Emperor's proxy.
In that case, what do you think?
Enlighten us,
Queen Xenobia of Ilm.
I think between the fight
for the Alsok territory,
and the prevailing dragonkind
Vaisen, as well as the Kenryu,
we've got multiple headaches
to contend with.
I understand that
you're taking action,
but there's one strategy
that'll solve all our problems
in one fell swoop.
Although not everyone
will be fond of it.
[MOULDEEN]
Assistant Administrator Guzreg
of Joint Staff Headquarters?
Not so fast, dear cousin.
Tread more carefully.
There are rumors one of
the military factions
has gotten in bed with the
hardliners from the church.
[XENOBIA chuckles]
They must really hate us.
I'm reluctant to say whether
or not the feeling is mutual.
[CURACAO]
Your Grace. I have news.
The Wise One wants to speak
with you, quick as you can.
Pardon me.
[MOULDEEN]
Hello there, Jokanne.
You're wearing an
adorable outfit today.
I look adorable everyday.
Anyway, listen close.
Something fun's happening.
[MOULDEEN] Such nerve, to bring
that up at a time like this.
Send word that our
meeting location has changed.
[CURACAO]
Changed?
Where to, sir?
[MOULDEEN] I think I know
the perfect place.
The far city of Eridana, where
Jushiki and the conspiracies
of countless nations run wild.
[NIDVOLK] Once again,
it's the wrong person.
[NEWS WOMAN 1A]
Now for more on the matter
of the Ninth Holy Land War.
The Seven-City Alliance
is still in talks
regarding the Alsok territory.
However, the discussion
appears to be deteriorating,
with hardliners and moderates
still unable to find common
ground on the subject.
Elder Orkentius, the hard-liner
official from the church,
is expected to call
for the deployment
of the imperial
military any day now.
Meanwhile, Cardinal Mouldeen,
the moderate representative
in the assembly,
doesn't seem to be
offering up any response.
[GAYUS] Guess it's time
to head off to work.
What's up, Horton?
Business as usual?
Gayus! Long time no see!
Yeah, we're slow as ever.
How 'bout you?
You really think I
would be having breakfast
at a dump like this
if things were going well?
Hey now!
Our fried pollock is Eridana's
best, I'll have you know!
Oh, and...
...since you're a regular here,
you get the special service!
Sit back and enjoy
Horton's Spicy Fortune Telling!
[GAYUS chuckles]
No, thanks.
This week says your
death will be by hanging.
Ha, ha! Nice.
No luck with money at all, or
the ladies, for that matter.
Also, you should beware the
clergy, as well as reptiles!
Don't tell me you actually
believe that crap.
[GAYUS]
Arzel? Why are you doing that?
I'm impressed!
I heard you took down an Altar!
Whoa! That is incredible!
[GAYUS] Well, to be fair,
it was a semi-Altar.
Hold up. Are those
shots for the paper?
You should at least
try to get my good side.
Nah, I'm not interested.
I took your photo out of habit.
If I was doing an article, I'd
use a photo of your hot partner.
We could sell a lot more
newspapers that way.
Besides, I'm following
a different incident.
I just got back
from investigating!
What incident is that?
I call it the Jushikiist
Murder Spree!
The story hasn't gotten much
attention in the media so far,
but three Offensive Jushikiists
have been assassinated recently!
All three were pretty strong,
but the perp eighty-sixed
each one with a single blow!
I think the murders are
connected. And if I'm right,
that means we've got a seriously
nasty killer on our hands!
What's really creepy is that
each time this guy
offs another victim,
he gets a little bit closer
to the center of town.
I'm guessing from the M.O.
that he's hunting Jushikiists
'cause he wants to zero in
on a specific target.
Well, in my line of work,
sometimes it's necessary
to kill our own guys.
That could be
what happened to 'em.
Infomation comes at a price!
Welp. I'll see ya.
Be careful out there!
Huh?
How 'bout, uh, one more fortune?
[GAYUS]
Morning, princess.
Want a snack?
Of course not.
You're a finicky
little thing, huh?
Where do you get
that from, I wonder?
Hey, Gigina.
He must be up there again.
[GAYUS]
Huh. It's kinda... beautiful
when you're just watching.
[GIGINA] Hmm. I'm picking up the
aura of an impoverished scumbag.
It's too early
for for that crap,
especially during your morning
prayers, mister god-lover.
[GIGINA]
The Kudu is a ritual
in which one wishes for
good fortune in battle
as well as respect and
admiration for the dragon
and our ancestors.
It's nothing like the
petty god you know.
Yeah, whatever.
I just came up here to tell you
to get all those chairs and
cabinets out of our office.
Or at least use 'em
to store some stuff.
It's a waste of space!
Don't be ridiculous, Gayus.
I would never dream of
doing anything like that.
Putting things on top of
chairs or inside of drawers
would rob the furniture
of its functional beauty.
Come downstairs.
We need to talk.
[GIGINA]
Hm? What is this nonsense?
[GAYUS] Three-hundred fifteen
thousand from Rolca's shop,
850,000 from Czahn,
that quack doctor...
What are we supposed
to do with all these?
Nothing.
The Draken people have
a saying about money.
"A hard-working person
will never be poor."
Oh, is that right?
Then how come I'm busting
my ass teaching on the side
and I'm still broke?
I try to make ends meet,
but how the hell I'm gonna
get through this month
might as well be
quantum mechanics.
Oh, hey, Gigina.
What are those crazy-
expensive-looking gemstones
I see in there?
I don't think I've ever
noticed them before.
Huh? Ah, you like them?
These are the ZAM-496 Mk. IV,
engineered specifically for
use by Offensive Jushkiists.
And they're even
more spectacular
than the previous model!
Oh, the receipt! Here.
[GAYUS groans]
[GAYUS yells]
--[footsteps]
--Hey, where are you going?
Anywhere!
[GIGINA]
Wait, Gayus.
Pick up the Jushiki bombs
I ordered from Rolca's shop.
But don't worry. The payment's
already been sent to the office.
[door slams shut]
Is he sick? He doesn't
seem very happy.
[ROLCA] All right, pleasure
doin' business with ya.
Huh?
You're extra smiley
today, Rolca.
What's with you?
Oh, don't give me that.
You wiped out a
semi-Altar black dragon.
I'm guessin' you made a
killin' on a job like that.
Sorry, things are a
little messy right now.
You mind if I pay my tab
at the end of the month?
It's startin' to add up, kid.
I know.
By the way,
where did you find out
about me slaying that dragon?
[ROLCA]
Everybody's heard.
You've been advertising
it all over town.
I've never seen this ad!
[ROLCA] They were
postin' 'em everywhere.
Even handin' 'em out
at city hall.
[GAYUS] Is Chief Sutherland
trying to pull something?
[ROLCA]
Hey, it's free buzz!
--[CITIZENS cheering]
--I'd be grateful if I were you.
--[popping]
You have any idea why it's
so lively out there today?
You gotta be kiddin'.
Tomorrow's the annual
Eridana festival, remember?
Is it really that time already?
Oh, no.
[CITIZENS chattering]
You're telling me you actually
remembered it this year?
Uh, yeah. Why wouldn't I?
I mean, I had to stand you up
last year 'cause of my job.
So this time I decided
to make arrangements
a whole month in
advance, just for you!
Why would I lie to you?
Fine, I believe you.
Now! Eat up, darling!
It's a traditional Alurian dish,
pigeon falusi with
cranberry sauce!
Uh, Jiv?
Question.
Is Alurian food always this
purple and poisonous-looking?
[JIV]
Mmm, delicious!
Go ahead and dig in
before it gets cold, okay?
--[JIV chewing]
--Um... thanks, honey.
[footsteps]
[MAN 1A]
Excuse me.
[MOULDEEN]
Hm? There you are.
Tell me, have we
selected our guards yet?
Yes, sir.
I think they'll do quite well.
[MOULDEEN]
Hmm. Interesting.
He went to Lyunerg
Imperial University.
It's too bad he
quit graduate school.
Did the two of you attend
at the same time, by chance?
[MAN 1A]
Yes. We were friends, actually.
In fact, he was one of
the elite students
in the research facility.
[MOULDEEN] So he could have
made his career in research.
[MOULDEEN] Were they the ones
who defeated that black dragon?
[MAN 1A]
Yes, sir.
[MOULDEEN]
I see.
That's excellent.
[VICTIM 1A panting]
Hey, leave me alone!
[footsteps]
[VICTIM 1A gasps]
[screams]
[gasps]
What's the matter?
[GAYUS] Uh, nothing.
I was just lost in thought.
You're always thinking about
something, aren't you, Gayus?
I guess so.
I'm a science-oriented
Jushikiist.
The gears are
constantly turning.
I don't mean that.
What I'm saying is, I never know
what you're thinking about.
But your mind always seems like
it's somewhere far away from me.
You wanna know what
I was thinking about?
I was sitting here watching
my beautiful girlfriend Jivenya
making some coffee,
and I thought, "Wow,
look at that sexy little ass.
How lucky am I to have her?"
You perv.
--[JIV gasps]
--[GAYUS] Yup.
There's nothing better
than being with you.
Nothing.
[NIDVOLK]
How unfortunate.
What would possess this man
to try and do me harm?
[NIDVOLK]
Alas, regardless of the reason,
I was wrong again.
My enemies will soon pay.
[GAYUS]
Screaming, we ask the question
in search of the
beautiful recitation,
until the heart within
my chest is adorned.
Tell me the lies and
roses within the truth.