[DOCTOR 4A] You gave us
quite a scare, Mr. Soleil.
Your heart stopped for a
moment and we were worried
because we couldn't
detect your brain waves.
--[groans]
--I'm sorry, sir.
I'll try it again, okay?
Let me guess, you're
new here aren't you?
Yes, I am. My name's Nojé.
You were in a deep coma
and the staff and I were
prepared for the worst,
but you look
perfectly healthy now.
I must say, it's an
absolute miracle.
Miracle. Huh.
Kinda like the miracle of love.
[NOJÉ]
Hm?
Anyway, it seems
like you've recovered,
so I'm discharging
you, Mr. Soleil.
I guess my vacation's over.
[GAYUS] It's almost like
that black claw swooped in
and pulled me back
from the dead.
[NOJÉ]
Mr. Soleil, did I hear correctly
that you're an
Offensive Jushikiist?
I am. Why?
Well, sir, I may need
your help with something.
[GAYUS] Great, I can
always use some work.
You'll have to
give me your number.
I give a discount
for pretty girls.
[NOJÉ giggles]
Uh?
We've received reports
that Elder Orkentius
has been called upon
to give testimony
regarding a botched
assassination attempt
on Cardinal Mouldeen
and Seven-City Alliance
Representative Azu Bita.
Orkentius is
challenging investigators
to provide evidence
of his involvement.
Next, new developments
concerning the Tienlun Accord.
Senator Yah Wen of
the Seven-City Alliance
has begun negotiations
with the Vaisen
to open dialogue
with the dragons.
How about that.
Apparently the moderates
are calling the shots now.
[MOULDEEN] Would that
it was as easy as that.
[GAYUS]
Hm?
Cardinal Mouldeen, it's you.
[HELODEL]
Gayus! I'm so glad you're--
[HELODEL groans]
Ow... That hurt.
If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't be caught up
in all this nonsense.
You owe me one, buddy.
You seem better.
Now, Helodel.
I'm going to have a
word with Gayus alone.
Please bring the car
around to the parking lot
if you don't mind.
Sir!
[GAYUS]
What an honor.
To think I'm meeting
Cardinal Mouldeen...
...from the proud
royal dragon family.
That's an unusual
choice of greeting.
I don't think so. This is the
first time I've spoken to you.
The Mouldeen I escorted around
was Genon Kal Darius,
one of the
Twelve Winged Generals
and infamous master of disguise.
Correct.
Tell me, when did you
realize that was the case?
I wasn't a hundred percent sure,
but the moment
I became suspicious...
...was when the other you
mentioned liking Urk cuisine.
You and Genon are
right-handed, aren't you?
Typically, when a
right-handed person
recalls a familiar location,
their eyes go to the upper left.
And when the memory
is something auditory,
it is said that the eyes
will move to the bottom left.
When you, or the copy of you,
brought up Urk food,
he looked down and to the left.
If I had to guess,
I'd say he was remembering
what someone had
told him to say.
I see. So how do you know that
this Mouldeen is the real one?
Because, back at the church,
Genon promised me he
would tell me the truth.
[MOULDEEN] Yes, but what
good is the word of someone
who aims to deceive by
masquerading as another person?
I haven't gotten to the
main point of my argument.
Look, Your Eminence.
I know you attempted to get
yourself assassinated, but why?
[MOULDEEN]
Aren't you insightful.
I'm just saying, you're
cautious enough to have
seven body doubles,
and your attackers
still knew where to find you.
Someone has to be a traitor.
My theory is you purposefully
leaked that info yourself
and it led them to that
well-guarded meeting.
--[engine starts]
--[MOULDEEN] What a shame.
You were close,
but not quite right.
Helodel is the real traitor.
[gasps]
[MOULDEEN]
The basket of flowers and fruit
that Helodel brought for you
must have exploded
in the car just now.
No way. Helodel did it?
He's the traitor
and now... he's dead?
The truth always turns out
to be so mundane, doesn't it?
[GAYUS gasps]
As a general rule I try
to avoid consuming fruit
that contains high-performance
explosives, don't you?
Tell me why!
Why would he betray you?
And then turn against me
at the same time?
[gasps]
[MOULDEEN]
It's simple, really.
Helodel could never
come to terms
with the death of his fiancée.
By the time he
joined the military,
he had already become a
loyal lapdog to the hardliners.
[GAYUS] Maybe, but you
didn't have to kill him!
You could have just
brought him to justice!
[MOULDEEN] You mustn't become
detached from reality, Gayus.
Don't forget,
I just saved your life.
Besides, Helodel isn't the
only one who was manipulated.
[GAYUS]
Wait a minute.
You called in the
assassins too, didn't you?
Precisely.
Every single one of those
ninjas is my servant.
I ordered their leader,
Curacao Opte Kouga
of the Twelve Winged Generals,
to pretend to be one of the
hardliners and mount an assault.
Every move of that assassination
attempt from start to finish
was pre-planned to
result in a safe failure.
[GAYUS gasps]
[MOULDEEN] However,
the meeting itself was real,
and responsibility for the
fallen ninjas and guards
is all mine.
Though the ultimate purpose
was to save lives,
I recognize that it was
an unforgivable act.
This is war.
The war before the war.
Or rather, the war
to prevent the war.
As long as I live, I'll never
run from such a fight.
It's the war to prevent a war.
So that meeting must've
been about Alsok...
...and the Ninth
Holy Land War, right?
[MOULDEEN] Yes, it's a feud
between the Dragon Empire
and the Seven-City Alliance.
I'll ask the Alliance's
occupational forces
to retreat to the
Daef Front in Alsok.
Why would you do
something like that?
It's only gonna help
the Dragon Empire!
How do you gain from this?
Why did you bother
toying with us like that?
If you must know,
our primary directive
was to ensure that
the traitor Helodel
believed his nasty little scheme
would play out
according to plan.
Secondly, we wanted to make
the incident more believable
by involving outsiders.
Third, we knew that you
would be neither foolish
nor heroic enough to
stand up to the Empire.
Lastly, you'll see what
price the Dragon Empire
will be paying to
the Alliance for this,
but you'll have to be patient.
Wait, you mean you're...?
I like to think I have not
only our land, but all things,
even this entire planet,
in my sights.
[GAYUS] I still believe
that you're a hero and all.
But, now...
It's interesting, Gayus. In
many ways you and I think alike,
while in others
we differ completely.
I am somewhat
fond of you, though.
Perhaps that fondness
is what inspired me
to choose you as an observer
for my little project.
I'm eager to try your
home cooking, Curacao.
Have you got it all prepared?
[CURACAO]
I believe we're all set, sir.
You'll be happy to know
I've brought the full barrel.
[CURACAO gasps]
That idiot had a bad feeling
about you from the beginning
and still turned a
blind eye to your scheme.
I guess he's even more
dense than he looks.
He just wanted to believe
the lie your decoy told him--
that you strive to protect
the smiles of children
as they play and eat candy.
He has my eternal gratitude.
[GIGINA] We don't accept
gratitude as payment.
There's a part of me that
believes you're a threat.
That's why I'll take
half your head!
[GIGINA] A high-order
Jushiki-proof barrier?
How strange.
Though I'm protected
by Jushiki master
Jokanne's handiwork,
I'm still quite terrified.
Two people now
think me dangerous.
However, you were the only one
who actually decided
to do something about it.
It's easy to deceive people
who spend their time thinking,
but difficult to trick someone
who acts on instinct.
You're just like Gayus.
Both of you place
your lives on a scale
to test your effectiveness.
Now go to hell and take
your word games with you.
Well, now.
I think it's about time for our
rambunctious cohorts to arrive.
[BELDRITT yawns]
That sure took forever,
didn't it, Bro?
I'm gonna go on ahead.
Catch you later!
[laughs]
It's so rude just to
take off like that.
Oh, Gayus. I was so frightened.
I know.
I'm so sick of you almost
getting yourself killed...
...and the hospital trips.
I'm sorry.
I'm not... just some
scared little girl.
I had all these plans
to put on a brave face
and welcome you home like a
real woman would, but then...
[sighs]
From now on, when you're
setting off for battle,
you have to warn me
gently before you go.
Because that way,
when someone comes back
to me holding your body,
at least it could possibly
spare me half of the tears.
Can you do that? Promise me.
[JIV]
Gah, I'm already embarrassed
for saying something like that!
Uh, Gayus!
I want you to drink
till you forget what I said!
[chuckles] Fine by me.
Several things have changed in
Eridana while you slept, Gayus.
[GAYUS]
Yeah.
I got the gist of it.
[GAYUS]
Hm? What's this?
"Still No Agreement"?
"Dragons failed to
attend Tienlun Accord
negotiation meeting
set by Alliance.
Senator Yah Wen,
who proposed the summit,
is sure to suffer
a considerable hit
to his reputation
after this failure."
Huh. Wait a sec.
Senator Yah Wen is
Representative Azu Bita's
political opponent, right?
[GIGINA] It's possible
Cardinal Mouldeen interceded
on behalf of the dragons.
[gasps]
[MOULDEEN] Lastly, you'll see
what price the Dragon Empire
will be paying to
the Alliance for this,
but you will have to be patient.
[GAYUS]
That's crazy.
The Dragon Empire's
got no bargaining chips.
Have you gotten any word
from Rolca or Vinnel recently?
[GIGINA] Who knows.
I turned off communications.
Damn, Gigina. How you manage
to survive in modern society
is a mystery to me.
Anyway, we got some
solid info from Vinnel.
There's no gravity
Jushikiist in existence
by the name of Nidvork.
So, then, who was that woman
we fought with that night?
[GAYUS]
No clue.
Hello?
[ROLCA] Glad to hear
you pulled through, kid!
Well, are you glad
enough to let me slide
on this month's payment?
[ROLCA] Yeah, sorry,
you're breakin' up. What?
[sighs]
So, you find anything out
about that strange cloth?
[ROLCA]
Yeah.
It's biological tissue
that's been modified
by gravity Jushiki.
Sending you the analysis.
It's tissue?
[ROLCA]
What do you two think? What's...
Thanks, Rolca. See ya.
[ROLCA]
Wait, Gayus!
[GAYUS sighs]
[GAYUS] Jushikiist
Supreme Advisory Court?
Hm.
They say they wanna make me a
13th-grade Jushikiist like you.
[panting]
Gayus. Do you think
we'll see her here?
Yeah.
[GIGINA] We could ask other
Offensive Jushikiists for help.
There's always
the mighty Largonkin,
or the terrible
scarlet Panhaima,
or the hermit wizard, Imhotep.
Any would be a wise option.
Why would we work with them?
Most likely they'd just
end up killing us instead!
[GIGINA]
Why don't we find Cuello?
[GAYUS] We don't have
the money to hire anyone.
And we're not on
good enough terms
to go asking people for favors.
[GIGINA] We'll have to
fend for ourselves...
...which is pretty much
how it's always been.
[GAYUS]
Well, at least I came prepared.
The most immediate concern
is that it's going
to take too long.
Plus there's the focusing ratio.
[GAYUS]
Yeah.
Our best bet is
to draw her out here
and then use Jushiki
to trap her.
[GIGINA]
Same one again?
[GAYUS]
Well, it's better than nothing.
[phone rings]
[NOJÉ]
Please, help me!
[gasps]
Woman. What's this all about?
I apologize.
You see, I saw some
hospital malpractice.
I informed the president, but
he made me keep quiet about it.
And now you've got bad people
chasing you, right?
[NOJÉ]
Mm-hm.
[NOJÉ] I'll take you two to
where I'm hiding the evidence.
Quick question, Genon.
[gasps]
What, did you think I didn't
know this was all a trap?
[GENON]
What gave it away?
[GAYUS] Your disguise and
your acting are perfect, but...
...as much as I
hate to admit it,
a beautiful nurse
taking a liking to me
and pleading for my help?
Come on now. That isn't
believable in the least.
Besides--
[BELDRITT]
You know Gayus actually has
a pretty good point, Genon.
And "Nojé" sounds
like a faké name.
Pick something more
realistic next time!
[JESPER]
Your job is complete.
We'll finish things up here.
You mind introducing yourselves?
We work for that old guy.
You can call us--
Shut it. We work
for Cardinal Mouldeen.
[groans] That hurt!
You're being so mean!
I'm Beldritt Livet Raki.
Clearly I'm the lovable one!
And my grumpy big bro
is Jesper Livet Raki.
Well, actually,
we're fraternal twins.
I know them!
I hear they're 14th-grade.
There's no way you're brothers.
I thought you were his son.
Does that matter?
Hey, if you knew this was a
setup, why'd you come here?
[GAYUS] Better than getting
attacked in my sleep.
'Kay, I'm gonna
come kill ya then.
Put up a good fight for me!
[gasps]
[roars]
I want you to meet my
good friend and servant.
Picked this one
just for you. Heh.
[BELDRITT laughs]
[BELDRITT] So I'm sure
you'll have tons of fun!
[GIGINA grunts]
A sword, huh?
[GIGINA grunting]
You're quite rude.
I'm returning the disrespect
you showed His Eminence.
You wield your blade
with Jushiki.
[JESPER]
And you're about to die by it.
[GIGINA]
Hmm.
Take care of him for me.
[panting]
[GENON]
There you are.
[GAYUS]
Huh?
[GAYUS grunts]
[GAYUS gasps]
[GENON] Now, look closely
and see through my disguise!
[BOTH grunt]
What an excellent battle.
You'd better have faith
in that weapon.
Like my partner,
you appear to be the type
who relies on reason.
I have no use for such things
when it comes to combat.
Either way, it'll take more than
that brittle sword to defeat us.
Now embrace your death,
but not before you witness
the unspeakable devastation
of the Nine-Headed
Dragon Fang Blade!
[GIGINA chuckles]
[yells]
[GIGINA grunting]
[GIGINA]
Hmm...
[GIGINA grunting]
[JESPER groans]
[GIGINA]
Heh.
[GENON chuckles]
Let's do this!
[GENON gasps]
[roars]
[sighs]
Hey, that was pretty smart.
You guessed my next move!
Well, I'm going to go
meet up with my brother.
[GAYUS sighs]
Either they want to separate
me and Gigina, or else...
[MOULDEEN] So, what exactly
caused Genon's undoing, Curacao?
[CURACAO] He most likely fell to
a sixth-order chemical alchemy
by the name of Astarte.
Simply put, it's a deadly
Jushiki that emits an odorless,
tasteless poison gas
over a limited range.
It's prohibited
around the world.
[MOULDEEN]
I didn't expect Soleil to have
such a trick up his sleeve.
I see Jesper's also having
some trouble with Gigina.
[panting]
You charged the blades of
the Dragon Fang head-on.
You're mad!
I noticed that your Jushiki
doesn't increase in mass.
All it does is
manipulate metals.
Each of your nine blades only
does a ninth of the damage.
So, unless one hits a
vital spot, it can't kill me.
[BELDRITT]
I'm back! Miss me?
[gasps] Oh, no! You're hurt!
I'll be fine.
[sighs]
Hey! You should probably
take a break, Genon.
[GENON] No! It'll take
more than that to best me.
Much more!
His Eminence Cardinal Mouldeen
specifically instructed us
to take our time and
not end this quickly.
What do you say
to two Dragon Fangs?
Oh?
I like that even better.
Perhaps now it'll
actually be a challenge.
Hey!
Where have you been, Gigina?
I thought you died!
Course not.
Your ugliness may be enough
to kill most people on the spot,
but I'm pretty tough.
Time for round two.
[MOULDEEN]
What an exciting spectacle.
And now, the final actor
is waiting in the wings
to make a dramatic entrance.
The moment of rebirth
is drawing near.
When I posted those
flyers all over town,
I was certain the audience would
be ready to watch it unfold.
At last our
glorious stage is set.
The thrilling climax
is about to begin,
leading up to the
long-awaited grand finale.
[GAYUS] Humanity never
learns to love wisdom.
We've always been prone
to choose foolishness.
[GAYUS] And the truth is, we're
predestined to behave that way.