[JIV]
Morning already?
[JIV sighs]
Right.
I have to go to work.
Your appetite is impressive for
it being so early in the day.
Anyone who can't
eat this much food
has no business being
an Offensive Jushikiist.
I like your style.
I ate like that in my day.
Sure brings back memories.
All right.
You and I both know you
didn't just ask us here
to have a nice breakfast.
Right. It's been three days now.
Which means it's time
for this "evening party."
This map illustrates all
the places the Magatsushiki
have emerged
during the past month.
Wow, they're really scattered.
Yes. So we decided to expand
our investigation to include
any similar incidents that
occurred in the past six months.
[GAYUS]
That's a lot!
They may not all be connected,
but it's safe to assume
preparations for
the "evening party"
have been underway for a while.
Either way, we're sure
to end up trading blows
with those Great
Magatsushiki somehow.
[GAYUS]
Yeah, but without knowing
what the "evening party" is or
what Jushiki they'll be using,
we can't really
make any solid plans.
Magatsushiki are wildcards.
Every one of them is unique,
with its own skills and quirks.
We'll just have to wait.
[YAHKTO]
We hypothesized in the past
that the Magatsushiki's
very existence
was in itself a form of Jushiki,
which appears to be correct.
The Magatsushiki
seem to have originated
from somewhere in
high-dimensional phase space,
which also happens to be
the fundamental
qualifier of Jushiki.
So they're creatures
from some other dimension?
Indeed.
That's what we've
come to understand.
But they need a medium in
order to appear in this world,
so they have to latch onto
something or someone
that already exists.
Uh-huh.
In other words,
those things are only here
because something
is hosting them.
So this is called "food," eh?
It's a fascinating concept.
Don't you agree,
Baron Janahn Ghalan?
It tastes no different
than steel to me.
My.
I do believe our neighbors here
have forgotten
their table manners.
You should have a seat.
I assure you we didn't come
to pick a fight with anyone.
Now that the evening
party is underway,
we're going to
play by the rules.
They're entities of information,
so rules mean
everything to them.
Got it.
[AMUPURA]
Forgive my eavesdropping,
but I heard every word of that.
Clearly, you still
don't understand
the purpose behind this
little soiree of ours.
So, allow me to
give you a little clue.
The "evening party" is actually
one big, bad Jushiki curse.
If you want to
stop the festivities,
you'll have to
defeat the caller.
The caller?
Are you saying
somebody summoned you?
Tell me!
Sorry, that's
privileged information.
[JANAHN] We haven't yet
become the masters
of our own destinies,
you understand.
[AMUPURA] If you want
my advice, your first move
should be to study the board
with extreme precision.
Although, if I'm being
honest with you,
you're not going to
like what you find out.
Oh, and about that Eye of
the Cosmos you've got there.
I would hold on tightly to it.
Damn.
[phone rings]
Hey, Iegie.
Go get Jabeira.
Those two clowns are back.
We need the team.
Shall we go with them?
No.
[phone rings]
[VINNEL]
I have some intel, for a price.
[VINNEL] Here's the location
of the Aurora Hammer's hideout.
The weapons dealer
Parumuwei tipped me off.
Of course, he died not long
after sharing that information.
[GAYUS]
This is it.
[GIGINA inhales]
Careful! What if there's a trap?
[GIGINA]
I already used Agane.
We'll be fine.
Look, that's a smart move,
but not even dogs can
sniff out sealed bombs.
Well, I don't smell any humans
on the other side, at least.
That's good enough for me.
[GIGINA] Hurry up, Gayus.
In the wise words of my people,
"Last one there has dragons
feast on his flesh."
You should talk.
Your fiancée probably says
your sense of urgency
conveniently comes and goes--
Less talking, more walking.
[gasps] Egurrd?
[gasps]
[GOHHEL]
What are you two doing in here?
You were told to wash
your hands of this matter.
I made myself perfectly clear!
Yeah, well,
last time I checked,
we don't answer to Dragon's Jaw.
This isn't a coincidence.
[gasps]
The hell is that?
[GIGINA]
Viscount Remedius.
[ZHUO LU]
How kind.
I didn't expect
such a warm welcome.
[gasps]
[EGURRD]
Zhuo Lu!
[ZHUO LU] I don't see what
you would gain from attacking
a three-dimensional
holographic display.
[groans]
[ZHUO LU]
I pity you, Remedius.
You were closer to me
than anyone in this world.
I've called you all here
to tell you something.
It's a message from the
late Viscount Remedius.
[EGURRD]
What did he say?
His death couldn't
have been avoided.
And I think you know
the reason why.
[GOHHEL grunts]
But it's the truth.
The Dragon Empire created the
anti-government organization
known as Aurora Front.
It was later re-named
Aurora Hammer,
but there's no
denying its origins.
That is some serious
foreign interference.
Then, what happened
at the hostage exchange--
that was meant to be a cover-up
for the Dragon Empire's
own scandal.
No. That can't be right.
[GIGINA]
Hm?
If the Dragon Empire wanted to
take out the
Dochetta administration,
then the Aurora Hammer
would be very helpful to have.
And so would the
Viscount, of course.
Remedius was a civilian,
which is why nobody picked up
on the Empire's scent.
There would have been no
obvious incentive to kill him.
[ZHUO LU chuckles]
The one part that
doesn't make sense
is why Remedius hated
Rahzel and the Empire
enough to risk his own life.
Why doesn't your organization
have a way of
explaining that, I wonder.
Dragon's Jaw should know.
That's the thing you
ought to be investigating.
Now, you must listen
to Remedius's words.
You're about to be
filled with more hatred
than you've ever known.
By the time anyone sees
this video recording,
I will have already passed on.
But if it serves to gain control
of the twin Jushiki warheads,
my life will not have
been sacrificed in vain.
I speak of the Jushiki
born from my research,
sealed away before anyone
had a chance to initialize it.
The one called Ava Dorn.
[gasps]
[REMEDIUS]
I built an initialization curse
that was never finished.
To use it requires the Jushiki
power of several dozen people.
That, and the
computational power,
need to be akin to an Altar's.
Now, the time has come.
Ava Dorn... is a
devastating weapon
that joins this
world to the other.
Both of the Jushiki
warheads will be detonated
at high noon today, and
their target is Rahzel Island.
[ALL gasp]
This is your warning.
The Dragon Empire will cease
all exports of Jushiki weapons.
This message is being sent to
Eridana City and the Empire.
Should even one person
attempt to escape the island,
the two warheads
will instantly detonate.
The Rahzel Company
has betrayed me
in the most despicable
way imaginable.
So, to them, I happily say...
...die.
Die.
Die. Die. Die.
Die. Die. Die. Die.
Die. Die. Die. Die. Die.
Die. Die. Die.
Die. Die. Die. Die.
Die. Die. Die. Die. Die.
Die. Die. Die.
All of you, die!
That is my one and only
desire-- that you be
forced to taste the hell
that I've passed on to Zhuo Lu!
Every member of Rahzel
deserves to face
the same despair and
suffering Naricia endured!
[laughs]
What will you do?
It's almost high noon.
Before long, Remedius's curse
will decimate the island. Well?
Let's go.
Gigina.
[GAYUS] Jiv is on
Rahzel Island... right now!
[JIV]
Hey, it's Jivenya!
Sorry, but I'm currently
at the Rahzel Company.
Feel free to leave a message--
You can call her all you want,
but if your woman is there,
no phone message will
get her out of danger.
I know that!
Everyone on that island
is being held hostage.
Damn it!
Why is this happening?
Why's everything so hard?
Stop it, Gayus.
What am I, cursed or something?
Everywhere I go,
bad things always follow me!
No matter how hard I try
to do what's right,
it blows up in my face!
Gayus!
[GAYUS gasps]
[GIGINA] I'm not as good at
expressing myself as you are,
but my past, every
decision I've ever made,
for better or worse,
is a part of who I am today.
I can't pretend
any of it didn't happen.
That doesn't help.
[GIGINA]
I know.
Gigina.
What would you do?
Speaking as a Draken,
I gladly face any battle
that's in front of me.
But if I'm speaking
as an individual,
I pay my debts.
That's all.
[GAYUS]
Okay, then let's pay our debts.
[YAHKTO] On the screen
is a top-secret experiment
on the seventh-order metatheorem
Jushiki conducted 13 years ago.
It's known as Ava Dorn.
Whoa!
They made a
dimensional hole, huh?
What's next is the issue.
This is the world
of Magatsushiki.
Because of the enormous
computational capacity
in their environment,
a multitude of wretched
plague demons were summoned
from deep within
the pits of chaos.
They're simple beings that can't
even be defined as Magatsushiki,
but that makes them
all the more--
Hey. What's going on?
[gasping]
[chokes]
[gags]
[YAHKTO]
Fifty-eight seconds
following the initial
plague demon infection,
its Jushiki causes
mass cell death.
At 113 seconds, victims
bleed from every orifice...
...then fall into a coma.
Finally, 137 seconds from
contact, the infected die.
There is no cure.
The fatality rate
is 100 percent.
Ava Dorn has a large radius--
about 600 meters wide.
If it were to be activated
above Rahzel Island...
Just say it.
Then all 1,205 people
on the island
would suffer through hell,
followed by death.
The Rahzel Company's
taking action right now.
They're evacuating
non-island staff members
to outside the city.
Everyone thinks it's
just a training drill.
[GAYUS]
But everyone else!
Can't we at least contact
the island and make a plan?
No, all communication and
transportation's been cut off.
This was the mayor's call.
The police's hands are now tied.
[gasps]
So we're just gonna
let them all die?
We could stop this if we
disarm the two warheads
before they detonate, though.
Yeah, but if we knew
where they were,
we wouldn't be sitting here.
Course not.
But finding 'em
is our only hope.
We have two hours.
Let's think.
[GAYUS]
This is a crisis, Gigina.
How can you sit in a chair
relaxing like that?
I'm enjoying this chair
because there's a crisis.
[GAYUS] Well, it looks
like the staff evacuation
is going smoothly, at least.
Imagine how much we could
smuggle during this.
[beeping]
There's obviously an
electromagnetics Jushikiist
jamming it.
You can't get through.
[GAYUS gasps]
[JIV] What's going on?
I've got tons of messages--
Listen!
Where are you?
I'm at work,
like I'm supposed to be.
Gayus, what's the matter?
Oh, right.
I did hear a few people say
they were having trouble
getting a good signal--
[GAYUS]
Jiv.
What?
I'm sorry... about last night.
I should have
trusted you, Gayus.
[GAYUS]
No, it's--
[JIV]
What's gotten into you?
[GAYUS]
Jiv...
Just gimme a second, okay?
Gigina.
Your flight Jushiki...
Couldn't that save her?
It is possible.
But, then...
Please!
You're serious?
Yeah.
Let me tell you one of the
wisest of Draken sayings.
"Whether you speak from
your mouth or from your ass,
the results can often
be quite similar."
You shouldn't resign yourself
to the curse of a deceased man.
His murderous ambitions
are dog feces
on the side of the road to us.
And you should never accept
the death of your woman,
especially without
so much as a fight.
[GAYUS]
Jiv.
I want to apologize in person.
[JIV]
What's wrong with you?
You're acting weird today.
[GAYUS] We should
go out to eat next Sunday.
I know a restaurant
that has amazing crab.
You'll love it.
Let's go, Jiv.
Promise me.
That's fine, Gayus.
But why...?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
No matter what happens,
I swear I'm gonna
win this fight!
[GAYUS]
Okay.
So, let's assume our famous
chells prodigy Remedius
put together a perfect
game board for us.
There are two
Jushiki warheads...
...but how are they set off?
[GAYUS] The Jushiki power
of several people combined,
which is comparable
to that of an Altar.
And that's the core
of alchemy Jushiki.
So what are the two keys
that unlock the two warheads?
And what's the equation for
the plague demon's Jushiki?
Wait! I've got it!
It's so clear.
Hey, Gigina!
I figured out how this "evening
party" is gonna go down.
[GAYUS]
It was Remedius who summoned
those two Great Magatsushiki.
With the power they hold,
plus the Jushiki gathered
from all those people,
the two warheads can activate.
For the grand finale,
Amupura and Janahn Ghalan
will become the core,
fulfilling the
detonation conditions.
That's the "evening party"
they kept talking about.
So, that means Ava Dorn
is actually...
If we aren't able to
destroy those warheads,
they will initialize.
Remedius is a genius,
but there's one thing
he couldn't stop.
And that's the will of
the Great Magatsushiki.
They want to fight us
during the evening party,
but not because of the plan.
They're provoking us for
their own entertainment,
which is why they decided to
draw us in by leaving us a hint.
The Magatsushiki locations?
How's that gonna help?
The ones at Boshor Point
had human-like faces.
Giant fangs at
the dental clinic,
then Deacon Sarvey and a model
castle at Largonkin's office.
Elephant at the zoo.
Large bird at the storage place.
You're right!
I get it now.
It all makes perfect sense!
Yeah.
The appearances
might've seemed random,
but they were abiding
by a set of rules.
[IEGIE]
Rules? You're confusing me.
[gasps]
When the pawn gets over there,
it turns into a dragon.
If you're trying to
win a game of chells,
you need to make your
dragon the strongest.
I've heard rumors
that you've memorized
every move of every chells
game you've ever played.
Is that the truth?
Yes!
I remember it all, actually.
Everything I've seen, or heard,
or felt since I was born.
Every last detail.
That's quite a tragedy.
Huh?
[MOULDEEN]
Indeed.
What a sad existence.
Once human, now a dragon.
You've lost yourself.
[GAYUS] The chells pieces
that you typically see nowadays
have changed a lot from
the original designs.
For instance, the bishops
were once elephants.
Sometimes fangs, too.
And the castles used to be
ships or large birds.
Okay, I'm with you when you say
the Magatsushiki
are chells pieces.
But how does that
tell us the locations
of the damn Jushiki warheads?
[GAYUS] The "evening party"
is a chells match,
and the board is Eridana.
So, the Magatsushiki appeared
according to the
rules of the game.
And I know exactly
what the last move is.
It's going to be identical to
Remedius's famous winning play--
the one from the
continental championship.
Are you saying that you've
figured out where they are?
There's a white king that's
gonna lose the battle.
It's here-- Rahzel Island.
And the black dragon piece
that's going to put
the king in check...
...is Osedek Clock Tower!
[REMEDIUS]
Both of the Jushiki warheads
will be detonated
at high noon today
and their target
is Rahzel Island.
[GAYUS]
Take it from me, friend,
you shouldn't waste time
seeking eternal paradise.
Drink in the possibilities
of this realm
and set sail into
the sea of stars.
For your opportunities are
as infinite as the night sky.