[clock chimes]
[GIGINA]
The sky looks beautiful.
[GAYUS]
Uh, yeah, I guess so.
What kind of person
can talk about the sky
at a time like this?
Are you afraid?
No way, don't be stupid--
Yup, super afraid.
Since we're probably gonna die.
[IEGIE] Let me guess, "Draken
warriors don't feel fear."
More accurately, we're not
as disposed to fear death.
But still.
Even if I were to feel afraid,
I would never let it
influence my judgement.
If I'm to die, it'll be
due to my own choices.
A decision is a noble thing.
Every move a person makes
can modify their entire
existence for years to come.
[LARGONKIN]
Agreed.
Just like how the lives of all
1,200 people on Rahzel Island
are hinging on this one battle.
We've gathered you all here
to fight the Great Magatsushiki.
You can flee now if you'd like.
You won't be blamed.
We won't run, Chief.
We're Offensive Jushikiists!
Good answer.
Now then!
Let's show those monsters
what we're made of!
We'll send them back
where they came from--
into the darkest depths of hell!
[growls]
[LARGONKIN]
Here they come!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Eat this, you creepy slimeballs!
[SOLDIER 10B, 10C groan]
[GAYUS] Heh. Okay, time to knock
this guy off his high horse.
Stop with the one-liners
and kill him already!
[IEGIE yells]
And just like that,
it looks like the party's over.
[GAYUS]
Well played.
[IEGIE]
Hm?
[IEGIE chuckles]
--[rumbling]
--[BOTH gasp]
[IEGIE]
What the hell is that thing?
[GAYUS]
That would be the bishop.
This has gotta be
cheating somehow!
[LARGONKIN groaning]
[yelling]
[GIGINA yells]
[LARGONKIN yells]
Weren't expecting a group
tactic, were you, Magatsushiki?
[MOULDEEN]
Shame about Remedius.
That boy was truly a genius.
[CURACAO] I didn't realize
you knew each other.
[MOULDEEN]
It was years ago.
I challenged him on
this very chells board,
but he bested me, of course.
You lost?
[MOULDEEN]
Yes. Remedius was one of a kind.
If he hadn't been the one
to inherit Rahzel...
[MOULDEEN]
The play has already been made.
But even now,
Remedius's choice is...
[slicing]
Damn it, they got Weitos!
You're gonna pay for that!
[JANAHN] So, you finally
solved the riddle
and found your way to us.
But this wouldn't be much of
an ending to the evening party.
The air is much too stale.
Allow me to dust things
off for our guests.
[gasps] Fall back, now!
[pants]
[LARGONKIN]
He just used Par Ee Mon!
[GAYUS] And wove it
together in an instant!
That computational power
is off the charts!
Not coming?
Then perhaps you'd like
to taste this pain again.
Nah.
[GIGINA yells]
[JANAHN]
Interesting.
I've been waiting for someone
like you to challenge my skills.
[GIGINA gasps, groans]
[GAYUS]
Gigina!
[panting]
[GAYUS]
Hey! Are you okay?
[JANAHN] I welcome you
to our humble arena.
Without further ado,
let us now partake
in the day's festivities.
[JANAHN groaning]
[JANAHN] Which of you
dares battle me first?
[BAYLICK]
What's going on in there?
Look. Do you think
they can win this fight?
Yes or no?
[YAHKTO] Hmm.
The probability of success is--
Eh, forget it.
[BAYLICK] Please don't let
there be any more casualties.
[IEGIE screams]
No, Iegie!
So much for dual-wielding.
Now I'm "One-Sword Iegie."
Sounds pretty lame, huh?
Stop talking.
You might make
the bleeding worse.
[pants]
[JANAHN]
What a joyous occasion this is!
I'm so pleased we invited you
to our little party!
How does his
swordsmanship stack up?
Let's just say,
if we were in ancient times,
he would be revered
as a god of war.
I think I've got an idea.
You in?
I have my doubts about you,
but seeing as how there
aren't many options here,
I'm willing to listen.
[GAYUS]
Largonkin!
Your cigars!
Throw 'em over here!
[JANAHN] You've resorted
to parlor tricks.
[JANAHN coughs]
Look, there's 1,200
lives on the line,
including my girlfriend's.
Do you think we could
cut to the chase, bug brain?
[JANAHN] How dare you make
light of the evening party!
This is a sacred place
of judgement by combat!
[GAYUS grunts]
[LARGONKIN yells]
Let's hit him with everything!
[IEGIE yells]
[JANAHN groans]
--[JABEIRA yells]
--[JANAHN groans]
[GIGINA yells]
[JANAHN screams]
[JANAHN]
That was impressive...
[JANAHN groans]
[JANAHN]
...for your kind.
I do not like you in the least,
but in terms of your fighting
prowess, I must commend you.
[gunshots]
That wasn't the most
beautiful victory.
A win's a win, dude.
Wait just a minute.
What did you actually
use to do him in?
A poison gas Jushiki?
Wait, no.
His barrier would be able to
block something
like that attack.
Cigars. Now I get it!
[GAYUS]
Yup, bingo.
Some of the chemicals that were
commonly found in tobacco
were used to create a natural
insecticide back in the day.
Looks like Janahn Ghalan's
summon mediums
were a human and a spider.
A spider's respiratory system
isn't good at
filtering out toxins.
And since he was new to
having a physical body,
he didn't know he shouldn't
inhale the smoke.
Burning the tobacco
was a chemical reaction.
His barrier couldn't
respond to it.
Figured I'd take a gamble.
Jeez, man.
Do you think this hard about
every fight you get into?
[groans]
I told you not
to talk, remember?
You two should stay here
for a little while.
The rest of us can go--
[IEGIE] No! I want to
fight till the bitter end--
[thud]
You're always a
handful, aren't you?
Keep him safe, Jabeira.
You two are gonna
turn my hair gray!
I'm tired. Let them
handle the rest.
[chuckles]
Get ready, Gayus.
There's another freak upstairs.
We should hurry.
[NARICIA panting]
Remedius.
If I die, you have to...
eat me, okay?
Because that way,
at least you can survive.
Don't be absurd.
Naricia.
We're both going home.
We have to kill Dochetta...
[coughing] ...so that
Urmun can be at peace.
Look. Remedius.
I need you to promise me
that you'll save Urmun,
no matter what happens.
I want it... to be a place
where no one has to suffer...
--[gasps]
--...like we did.
No, don't!
Please know that I love you,
more than anyone else ever!
[REMEDIUS]
Naricia!
[NAVARRO]
Hey! Where are you?
Hello?
Are you here?
[MAN 10A]
Hey, Naricia!
Come on, say something!
I know how you must feel,
but... it's no use.
They must be dead.
You're wrong, damn it!
[MAN 10B]
But it's freezing out here.
[MAN 10A]
Hey! I think I found someone!
[NAJIK gasps]
Is that him?
[NAJIK, NAVARRO gasp]
--[NAJIK] Remedius?
--[REMEDIUS panting]
Hey. Where's everyone else?
[REMEDIUS]
They're dead. All of them.
[gasps]
[REMEDIUS] Except... our dear
Naricia is inside of me.
What's that mean?
[REMEDIUS laughs]
[REMEDIUS]
I ate her.
She offered her body
to me and I accepted it.
[NAVARRO]
Ate her...?
No...
[REMEDIUS]
This... is all that's left.
Oh, god.
You didn't!
With this, I'll have
every bit of her in me.
So thank you, sweet Naricia.
[REMEDIUS] The weak Remedius
you once knew is now dead.
"Give me flesh and blood.
That's when I will appear
to devour any foe
who dares to threaten
harm to Urmun."
Yes. I am the
[REMEDIUS, ZHOU LU]
demon you sought.
I've come to avenge you.
[ZHOU LU]
Cower before Zhuo Lu,
the great Man-Eating
Dragon of the Sand.
[ZHUO LU]
Zemunn.
You set up the board
by sacrificing yourself
as the late Viscount Remedius.
This is the final move.
Let us cast Rahzel
into oblivion!
[GAYUS panting]
[GAYUS groans]
[GIGINA] I've had enough
of their surprises.
[LARGONKIN]
Heh. At least we're alive.
Salmak consumes your Jushiki
power and turns you to stone,
while Otis necrotizes
cells with venom.
So, I'm guessing that
Amupura's medium was a snake.
It was also using that
ability to teleport itself.
But still. Judging
by that explosion,
I'm guessing we're
rid of him for good now.
[AMUPURA]
Nope, guess again!
Voila!
I'm as good as new!
[BOTH yell]
[GIGINA coughs]
Oh, but wait, that's not all!
This model has 46 percent more
Amupura than the leading brand!
[LARGONKIN]
How did he regenerate
without me even noticing?
I can't figure this scumbag out.
[GAYUS]
Wait, hold on!
I think I understand it now!
All he's doing is
using Goarp continuously!
He's turning his body
into information
and converting that
to subatomic particles.
Then he transfers that as
waves and rebuilds himself
as soon as he reaches
his destination!
And even though the before
and after may look similar,
they are entirely different.
He switches his body out
--[clapping]
--each time.
[AMUPURA]
Correcto!
Now let's get on to the last
of this evening's events.
Oh, by the way.
The twin Jushiki warheads
are still here with us now.
[GAYUS]
Tell me, Gigina.
What's the Draken secret
for beating this guy?
You take a four-eyed redhead,
let him get eaten, and kill
the thing from the inside.
As the one four-eyed redhead
in the room, I vote no.
[GIGINA]
Then how do we win?
You know, there are plenty of
other important things in life.
I think it's time for society to
end this obsession with victory.
Well, that won't make
much difference to us
if we die right now.
Yeah, guess not.
[GAYUS coughs]
[GAYUS] If only we could
blow this place up
along with that damn warhead.
[GAYUS]
Hm?
Ah, look who we have here.
If it isn't the
Baron Janahn Ghalan!
[JANAHN]
I'm afraid it's... over for me.
You mean you don't have
enough Jushiki power left
to regenerate yourself?
My, my, isn't that humiliating?
[JANAHN] According to the
rules of the evening party,
I suppose it's only right
for you to eat me now.
If I must.
[GAYUS]
You ate your own comrade!
[AMUPURA]
Yes. To our species,
the protection
of our information
takes priority over the survival
of individual entities.
Speaking of which,
I must express my
admiration for Remedius.
By ingesting the little
ingénue he so adored,
his body was imbued
with her heroic spirit.
Anyway, the party's been fun,
but it's getting late.
It's the moment
you've been waiting for.
Now that the Baron and I
are one, the warheads can fire.
[ALL gasp]
[AMUPURA] Observe as the
gods of death take flight
and their catastrophic fury
is unleashed upon Rahzel Island!
[LARGONKIN]
Not today!
[LARGONKIN groans]
Eridana is my home!
I'm not letting
a single person die today!
[groans]
Your determination's inspiring,
but I'm as hellbent as you.
[LARGONKIN groans]
Gayus, do it now!
Right!
--No, Largonkin!
--[GIGINA] Largonkin!
[GAYUS] Looks like your evening
party's just been crashed!
[AMUPURA chuckles]
Do you honestly think Remedius
didn't plan for
things like this?
[AMUPURA groans]
--Hey!
--Got it!
[GIGINA]
I can't keep this up for long.
Can you stop that thing?
Here goes nothing--
[GAYUS groans]
I just told you.
I'm not playing around here.
[screaming]
My goodness. What a delicate
little lady-scream you have.
Farewell!
[GIGINA]
Gayus, are you all right?
Great. Think that kick
woke me right up!
[AMUPURA] The evening party
is now complete!
I fulfilled my agreement
with the Viscount Remedius!
At last, my family
can enter this world!
So he did this to
summon his kind here?
Nice try!
But now that I know how his
teleportation trick works,
it's not like
the guy's unstoppable.
This'll be easy!
Sorry, Amupura,
but you're just another
piece on the chells board
and this is checkmate!
[AMUPURA screams]
[AMUPURA growling]
[AMUPURA]
You insolent fools!
How dare you do such a thing
to the all-powerful ruler
of the Magatsushiki!
I mustn't allow myself
to be defeated yet!
The Eye of the Cosmos!
[AMUPURA screams]
It's over.
Uh-huh.
[sighs]
--[bang]
--[gasps]
[GAYUS]
What?
[GIGINA]
So Remedius even managed
to trick the Great Magatsushiki!
[GIGINA]
I'm sorry.
Oh, Jiv.
[BOTH groan]
[GIGINA]
Wait a minute.
Does this mean Largonkin
deployed Jushikiists over there?
[GIGINA]
Oh, I take back what I said.
Huh?
Don't remember, I guess.
Well, anyway...
my Jushiki is out.
[GAYUS] Would've been nice
if you'd mentioned that sooner!
[CROWD chattering]
[GAYUS groans]
[GIGINA]
Oh, good, you're still alive.
Yeah, and from the looks of it,
I don't think I've died
and gone to heaven.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
be here with me.
Unless you're my
eternal punishment.
Since I know how much
it'll hurt you to hear this,
today happens to be the luckiest
day of your life, Gayus.
It's all downhill
from here, huh?
[JIV]
Huh? Gayus?
Gayus?
[gasps]
Hey, Jiv.
I wanted to apologize
about last night--
[JIV]
No!
I don't care.
Forget that, okay?
But I... acted like such a jerk.
[exhales] Hey.
Welcome back. I missed you.
How about that?
I finally got to
say it that time.
I'm home now...
...Jiv.
[GAYUS]
The mind is a powerful weapon.
It can easily turn hell into
heaven and heaven into hell.
Because of that, there's
no way to know for certain
whether the world I see
and the world you see
are one and the same.
But that's exactly
the way it should be.