Here we are.
How'd she trick you
into showing up, Gigina?
She said that there was
a secret furniture shop here.
Damn, even a kid could
see through that lame excuse.
I wanted us all to have
a surprise get-together!
You know, to help
you all get along.
Sorry, but Gayus and I have
a gentlemen's arrangement
to never become friends
under any circumstances.
Yeah, what he said.
The only thing we agree about
is that we never agree
about anything ever.
Uh? But doesn't that mean
you are on good terms?
Or no?
I'm lost.
[JABEIRA]
Don't hurt yourself, Jivenya.
[JIV]
Jabeira! Hi!
Long time, no see.
[JIV]
Yeah, it's been forever!
[IEGIE]
Hm? Hey.
The four-eyed nerd and
the Draken dumbass are here.
Wait, what?
[yawns]
[JIV]
Jabeira's really great!
She helped me out a lot when I
first started with the company.
You're as adorable as ever.
Why'd you go and leave us, huh?
Damn, Gayus.
You landed a girl who's
totally out of your league.
Wanna run that by me again?
What about this guy with you?
I don't think I know him.
Is he your boyfriend, or...?
Of course not!
Just a fellow Jushikiist!
Aw, Iegie.
Come over here and give
an old woman some sugar!
[gasps] What the--
Could you please stop
talking like a grandma?
Ugh.
By the way.
How's Largonkin doing?
He'll be out of the hospital
soon, thanks to you guys.
Aw, yeah!
Takes more than some lame
Magatsushiki to beat my old man!
[CZAHN]
Oh? Is someone injured?
[JABEIRA]
Hey there, Czahn.
It's good to see ya.
How ya been?
Oh, great.
Are you BFFs
with the doctor, too?
Oh, no, Jabeira and I
are cousins.
[GAYUS] A hothead who
changes personalities
at the drop of a hat
and a quack with
an organ fetish.
Your family tree has
got serious root-rot.
Ha, ha. You're hilarious.
Ooh! I just had a great idea!
Since you're here, the six of us
can all party together!
[JIV giggles]
'Kay, 1, 2, 3!
Yeah, yeah, 4, 5, 6.
I don't understand how
this qualifies as a game.
Just roll with it,
all right, Doc?
Now, I say "7, 8, 9."
Okay, 10, 11...
[GAYUS] I'm sure Jiv
doesn't realize this,
but nothing good can come
from Offensive Jushikiists
drinking together.
That is to say,
it ends in bloodshed
about 80 percent of the time.
...22, 3, and 4 then.
[GAYUS]
So, in my infinite cleverness,
I came up with a fun
little drinking game.
The rules are simple.
Everyone counts
numbers in order.
If you have to say 100,
then you lose
and you're punished.
You can say one
to three numbers
and the game starts to
get really interesting
during the last few turns.
[JIV]
Um, let's see... 97?
Nice knowin' ya.
98 and 99.
I can't believe
I've lost already.
One... hundred.
[GAYUS] But, of course,
that's according to my plan!
The loser's punishment is chosen
by the player who
went right before them.
Naturally, as the night
goes on and people get drunker,
the game becomes more ruthless.
In other words, the person
who loses the starting round
will inevitably end up suffering
less than everyone else does.
[GAYUS screams]
Now, there's no need to
make a fuss, Patient 49707015.
I'm just going to put those
beautiful organs of yours
on display.
This is bad.
I guess I underestimated...
how much you... guys hate... me.
Come now, don't worry!
I'll be working
with my precious baby.
It slices through
skin like butter.
[JIV] What are you doing?
Get away from him!
Well, look at that.
She came back already.
[JIV] Gigina! I can't
believe you lied to me
about my neighbor's
house being on fire!
Sorry. I suppose I misheard.
[JIV]
This is my property!
Keep your dirty hands off it!
Oh, my.
Exactly what part of him
do you mean by "it"?
His pancreas?
That's a vital one.
I can certainly understand that.
Nope, I don't
think so, Czahn.
The part she cares about
is a little lower down.
[JIV gasps]
No, that isn't the only thing!
I was talking about the
total package, not just--
I think we're all talking
about a package, hon.
[IEGIE, JABEIRA gasp]
Uh, never mind, ladies.
Let's not get violent, 'kay?
Fine. Shall we play again?
[JIV]
Oh, you are so on!
No, wait, guys,
come back!
I... can't move.
[GAYUS]
Round two's about to start.
Time for me to get revenge.
...94--
[GAYUS coughs]
Are you all right?
Okay then.
I'll do... 95.
Then I think I'll go with 96.
[gasps]
Damn it!
That cough was a signal!
[GAYUS]
97, 98, 99!
Ha!
Looks like you lose!
[groans]
My... My... My, uh...
My, uh...
I can't hear you!
[groans]
My... My fiancée is...
an incredible woman.
And I... I... I, uh...
Yes?
I... love...
[gasps]
[GAYUS] The victim for the
third round was Doctor Czahn.
[IEGIE]
94.
[CZAHN]
95.
[GIGINA]
96.
[GAYUS]
97.
So, 98?
Don't worry.
I can handle punishment.
I'm saying 99, too.
--Yeah!
--No fair!
Blame your boyfriend.
He's the one who
made up this game.
Now, you say 100!
[whines]
[JIV]
Oink! Oink!
Oink! Oink...
[JABEIRA]
You're not convincing enough!
I've never seen a piglet with
a scrunched-up face like that.
Now be cuter!
Come on, she's
been through enough.
[JABEIRA]
Think so?
[gasps]
[JABEIRA]
Nope!
Ow!
Squeal some more!
What a shame.
Rest in peace, my love.
[laughs]
Hey. Gayus?
[GAYUS]
Don't say it.
[GAYUS] Offensive Jushikiists
can work together,
but it's impossible
for us to get along.
And so, the game continued.
Ahh, it's round ten!
This is the last one
of the night!
--Who's going first?
--Dude.
Should we stop?
I'm worried about your girl.
Seems like she's been
kind of off ever since--
Mind your own business.
Quit bothering me,
or your penalty's gonna be
jacking off in public.
He'll do it, too.
If you're afraid, you can
shove your head up your ass
and wait for the
end of the game.
I don't know if I'd call it
a game at this point.
It's more like we're shooting
dice on a battlefield in hell.
[sighs]
Albertacadabra,
and away we go, kiddos!
I'm the magical gabby
granny gal Jabby Jabeira!
With my dark,
decrepit Jushiki power,
I'll make all your worst
nightmares come true!
For a price, of course!
Mommy! [cries]
[MOM 11A]
I won't let her get you, dear.
Why was I cursed to be
born into this world!
Is this the glamorous
Offensive Jushikiist's life
I always dreamed of?
No! It can't be!
No. No!
--[JABEIRA crying]
--Well, that's depressing.
--Are we supposed to laugh now?
[JIV]
Jabeira.
It's you.
I think that's enough...
...of rehearsal.
--[JABEIRA screams]
--[JIV] Stop whining!
I say we get ready to take
"the magical granny girl show"
on the road...
[CZAHN] I assume they'll
need a doctor after this.
My fiancée's wicked,
but not like that.
Eh. I'm just happy she took
everybody else along, too.
Did you notice them?
Yes.
The incident's over now,
so why are they still
concerned with us?
[GAYUS] Man, this was a
last-minute invitation.
Lemme guess. A surprise party?
[XENOBIA] Are you the two
heroes who saved Eridana?
Oh yeah, I thought it was about
time for our fame and fortune,
Queen Xenobia.
Indeed it is a party...
...to thank you
for all you've done.
What an honor.
Couldn't have done it
without the information
you provided us with.
[XENOBIA]
Information?
Of course.
Someone told
Parumuwei the arms dealer
to spill the location of
the Aurora Hammer's hideout.
It was you, right?
And since he wasn't
useful anymore,
you had him killed and made it
look like Aurora Hammer's work,
didn't you?
My goodness, what an
intelligent young man you are!
I'm shocked.
No wonder Mouldeen
took a liking to you.
Listen.
There's one thing I've been
trying to wrap my head around
since we saw Zhuo Lu
at that hideout.
What's that?
Zhuo Lu was saying Aurora Hammer
was originally established
under the name "Aurora Front"
by none other than
the Dragon Empire itself.
If that's true,
why did you want to crush it?
You created the group in secret
to interfere with
Urmun's internal affairs.
Nothing would have been
more convenient for you
than having a civilian like
Remedius take the reins.
Is that your only question?
Not quite.
Why did Remedius
have such a big grudge
against Rahzel and
the Dragon Empire?
He said it was the
worst betrayal imaginable.
[GAYUS gasps]
[GAYUS]
No way. It... can't be!
I don't believe it!
[GAYUS]
The Dragon Empire is conspiring
with that monster
Dochetta, isn't it?
[XENOBIA] I'm sure you know
that this nation's economy
is highly dependent on
various Jushiki industries.
It's not an overstatement
to say that
cutting-edge Jushiki technology
is integral to our survival.
And to continue making those
products, we need resources.
I'll just cut to the chase.
Both the Seven-City Alliance
and the Dragon Empire
have fallen in line
with Dochetta's regime.
[BOTH gasp]
[XENOBIA] In return,
we share mining rights,
which means we have access
to Urmun's rare metals.
Then just join forces
with the Aurora Hammer!
That's not as sketchy as--
[XENOBIA]
We can't do that.
Because the
Aurora Hammer insists
that anything in Urmun's domain
belongs solely to Urmun.
We don't benefit
from that policy.
The Empire does not
make compromises.
Therefore, our only
remaining option
was for Remedius
to die as a hostage.
Wait, as a hostage?
What do you mean?
Well, I have to
protect our economy
and the everyday lives
of the people I rule over.
As royalty of the Dragon Empire,
I'll stop at nothing to
ensure that that happens.
I'll sink to any depth.
The suffering of other
nations is of no concern.
After all, why should I
have any sympathy for fools
who are unable to
create solutions
for their own
country's problems?
What kind of ruler--
[XENOBIA]
Don't be cross with me.
It was Mouldeen's decision.
He declared it
at the secret meeting
with the Seven-City Alliance
you happily escorted him to.
[GAYUS]
I should have known.
You and Mouldeen are so alike.
This whole royal family
is one big man-eating dragon!
Answer me one more thing.
What do you gain from revealing
that to us at this point?
Just pure amusement.
You two did survive
that madman's plot,
so I was curious to discover
what kind of interesting
people you might be.
But this wasn't nearly
as fun as I had hoped.
[XENOBIA]
My goodness.
They left me with
some harsh words.
Young people like those two
have no tact at all.
[MAN 11A]
It's time, Your Highness.
Understood.
[CROWD chattering]
What did you think
about Gayus and Gigina?
Well, to be honest,
I don't understand what
makes them so special to you.
You're as frank as
always, my dear cousin.
This is only a silly spectacle.
Did you have to
bring your Generals?
Of course.
--[music plays]
--[CROWD cheering]
It's time to begin.
I hear the ceremony
will be broadcast
to the Empire as well,
so be sure to smile.
[CROWD cheering]
[NEWS WOMAN 1A]
We're looking at clear skies
all day long tomorrow.
Great weather for doing laundry.
Why do I feel like
this is far from over?
We've done everything
within our power.
You must accept that.
Yeah, I know.
[gasps]
[GAYUS]
Zhuo Lu?
So he is alive!
We're broadcasting live
from the palace parade grounds
in the Urmun Republic,
where a celebration for
President Dochetta is underway.
[CROWD]
Dochetta! Dochetta!
Dochetta! Dochetta! Dochetta!
[DOCHETTA]
Hm?
[CROWD screams]
[XENOBIA gasps]
I trust you're unharmed, cousin.
[DOCHETTA] Do you think this
is the first assassination
I've avoided using Jushiki?
[CROWD cheers]
Dochetta and Urmun will not die!
[gasps]
[CROWD murmuring]
[ARZEL] What the heck's
going on over there?
I've never seen
Jushiki like that!
[chuckles]
Dochetta's going to
die a miserable death
befitting all the sorrow
he's responsible for.
That's the Ava Dorn Jushiki!
Why are you doing this?
I thought you just
wanted revenge
on Rahzel and the Dragon Empire!
The attack on the island was
always supposed to be a failure.
Those two warheads weren't
meant for the Rahzel Company.
They were a diversion
as I moved the vast arsenal
I got from Parumuwei into Urmun.
[BOTH gasp]
By making everyone believe
Remedius's chells board
was here in Eridana,
I was able to manipulate
the Great Magatsushki,
Dragon's Jaw, and the
two of you all at once.
But the real game board
was in Urmun from the start.
[CROWD screaming]
[gasping]
[ZHUO LU] The main objective
to winning a game of chells
is not capturing the queen,
but defeating the king.
By that logic, which would
you say is the prime target
for my vengeance--
Rahzel or Dochetta?
[ZHUO LU] Once that tyrant
is overthrown for good,
the people of Urmun will rise
and a new nation
will be born at last.
Whose idea is that, Zhuo Lu?
Oh wait, that's right.
You're Remedius, aren't you?
Remedius Levvi Rahzel
is who I used to be.
Now I am only Zhuo Lu, the
Man-Eating Dragon of the Sand.
Enough with the
self-righteous act!
Whoever you are, you had your
own people die in your place
at the hostage exchange!
You're just a
self-serving coward.
[ZHUO LU chuckles]
Do you think I would do
something that wasteful?
The corpse
presumed to be Remedius
was actually a traitor with
connections to the Empire.
That man was Zemunn, the former
leader of the Aurora Front.
[gasps]
But why would you do that?
You have to ask?
Are you suggesting
that there's another way
to stomp out the oppressors
and achieve peace and freedom
for the citizens of Urmun?
How can you talk about peace
when you've murdered
innocent Eridanians?
That's just as wrong!
Don't think for a second
that you aren't to blame.
Because of your very
existence as a Jushikiist,
countless people have been
exploited and put to death!
[GAYUS]
But that's--
[ZHUO LU]
Name one alternative.
How do you propose
I save the land of Urmun?
The men whose bowels
were ripped out
for opposing the establishment.
The women raped by soldiers.
The children claimed
by disease and famine!
And poor Naricia!
If none of us act,
what good are words?
Nothing changes!
After all I've seen, how do I
erase the horrible nightmares
burned into my memory?
[GAYUS] What you're doing
won't save anyone.
You're only creating more
dictators like Dochetta.
Well, then I'll assassinate
as many of them
as I deem necessary...
...for Naricia, and for
the citizens of Urmun.
[GIGINA]
Don't.
He's deploying an
Altar-level barrier.
You are a contemptible man.
You think this is your will,
but you're a puppet
like anyone else.
[ZHUO LU]
My will is Naricia's will.
That's the path
I've chosen to take.
Your criticism is sharp,
but you won't and can't
do anything to make a change.
I have no use
for men whose words
aren't supported by action.
So give up.
You will not defeat me.
I delivered you a gift
so you were able to contact her.
And because of that, you did
some truly excellent work.
I know that smell!
Something wrong?
Uh, no.
[GAYUS]
So...
...that electricity we saw...
[GIGINA]
Let's go.
[GAYUS]
Uh, right.
[CUELLO chuckles]
[NARICIA] If only there were
no more fighting in Urmun
or the whole world, ever again.
And there could be peace
and happiness everywhere.
No, that isn't possible.
No matter what, mankind
will always have conflict.
[NARICIA]
I understand.
But peace is something
you should pray for.
You have to wish hard, or else
nothing will ever change.
You may just be right.
But what I wish for
more than anything else
is that you'll always have
the ability to look at the world
in the same way as
you do tonight, Naricia.
You're weird.
It is extremely
important to me.
What I desire more than anything
else is that this wish...
...no, that this prayer
of mine reaches your heart,
even if I die and
am reduced to dust.
So let's speak our
wishes and prayers now,
while we're both still here.
[ZHUO LU]
Naricia.
Even if nothing that we pray or
wish for can ever come to be...
...still,
[ZHUO LU, NARICIA]
I'm with you.
[GAYUS]
At the end of the world,
our tears and blood
will surely be enough
to drench an entire desert.
None of us will ever
truly be complete.
We'll never have the chance
to walk through paradise.
But, even so, I wonder...