My name is Isabella York,
and this is my prison.
Here there are only sheltered girls who are well off
as well as their handmaids and teachers.
It's a girls' school separated
from the world by high walls.
All the students are from respectable families,
or will be marrying into one.
I am, no doubt, the latter.
She is free to go anywhere.
But not me.
May I introduce myself?
If it is your wish, I will travel
anywhere to meet your request.
Auto Memories Doll at your service.
Violet Evergarden.
What's a Doll doing here?
I was sent here by your family.
They instructed me to help you
achieve success as a debutante.
A debutante?
In only three months?
Yes. I'm to be your tutor in culture, conversation,
etiquette, and dance. Everything
that is befitting of a lady.
I will be serving in that capacity until your debut.
Dolls do that kind of work, too?
No. We normally just write letters for our clients.
If it wasn't for the royal Drossel
family's introduction, I would've declined.
Hmph. It sounds like you're a snob.
And people like that are the worst.
I heard you're prone to coughing fits.
Don't touch me!
Your hand...
It's a prosthetic.
I lost both of them in the war.
A Doll who serves the royal family?
No. I'm a civilian Doll. Our
company is in Leidenschaftlich.
Leiden...?
That's right. It's the southern-most nation.
It's about four days from here.
That is, if you only use local trains
on the trans-continental railroad.
So that means... you can go anywhere you want.
For a job, yes.
Must be nice.
Until I complete my duty,
I will remain with you.
I don't wanna be with friends with you. So keep
quiet unless it's absolutely necessary for my education.
You've got that grumpy look again.
Is the matter really that difficult?
Mm-hmm.
It's a request that was made for Violet.
They want her to tutor an aristocrat's daughter.
To tutor her?!
Apparently, it's for three months.
Can't say no to the royal family.
But three whole months?
Oh, I can go check on her every now and then.
It's at a girls' boarding
school, which means no men allowed.
A girls' boarding school, huh?
These public love letters are so dreamy.
I just made this the other day.
It's lovely!
Well, if you like it, you can have it.
Who is that?
Whoa... Who is she?
I've never seen her before.
Do you know her?
No, I've never seen her, either.
Good day to you, Miss York.
And who do we have here?
Ah... Well, um, she's...
I will be serving as Miss Isabella's handmaid.
My name is Violet. It's a pleasure.
Well, my name is...
Miss Lancaster, I presume.
I was already informed of your name.
That was such a perfect curtsy!
She looks more like a princess than a handmaid.
Please use the outer most knife.
Huh?
I'm sorry, Miss, but why have you stopped working?
It's important that you continue on with your lesson.
This is mandatory curriculum.
Later.
The correct phrase would be, "I wish to continue later."
Taylor?
Hmm?
Tee-hee! Sister!
Taylor!
Do you know that you've always
been my precious treasure, Taylor?
Miss York, which salon will you be entering?
Huh? Oh...
Well, of course, it will be Miss Lancaster's salon, right?
The prime minister's family, the Lancasters, and the
Yorks, the two titans of trade, have ties to the Drossels.
I'm terribly sorry.
Miss Isabella is quite frail, you see.
Before coming here, she had spent much of her life alone.
Now, she is trying to acclimate to living with others.
So, in knowing that, would you please allow her more time?
Ah, yes!
Oh, wow! She's just like a knight from a romance story!
Miss Isabella. I left your side earlier... I apologize.
Just being around you...
It really makes me miserable.
Taylor...
Good day to you, Miss York.
After this, we'll be holding a
tea party back at the dormitory.
If you would like to come...
Just go away.
Uh... I'm sorry, have I offended you?
My apologies, ma'am.
My master has instructed me to
limit her interactions with others.
At least until she becomes a debutante.
You truly are a princess knight. Very well.
Let us forget this ever happened.
Good day to you both.
They're only able to see me for who my family is.
It's like I'm trapped in that identity.
Is that so?
You're no different, you know.
This is simply a duty I must complete.
You really are perfect in every sense, aren't you?
So much so, you could even pass as royalty.
I'm an orphan.
Huh?
You're really gonna stay here for three months?
Are you?
You told me to keep quiet unless it's absolutely necessary
for your education. I'm following your instructions.
Forget that right now.
Our company has other dolls, so
business will continue as usual.
That's not what I meant.
Is there anyone that you'll miss? From back there?
So there is.
There is someone, but...
Unfortunately, we cannot see each other.
Really?
I hope you're doing all right, Violet...
Taylor...
I'm sorry, it's me, Violet.
Hmm? Uh!
How are you feeling this morning?
Were you up all night?
I've undergone endurance training in the past.
So a little missed sleep is...
It is not an issue.
Listen. Since we're close in age, I wanna talk to you.
You know, like normal.
Very well.
Although... what do you mean,
precisely, when you say, "like normal"?
Um. For example, I, uh... What's wrong?
It's time to get ready.
You're going to be late for school.
At this school, it is customary to learn
the dance as both the male and the female.
Miss Isabella, let's begin our lesson
by you learning the woman's part first.
And I will be the man.
But I've always been clumsy,
and I might step on your feet.
The secret to enhancing your performance is to
relax your body. Just try and follow the lead.
Miss Isabella.
Huh...?
Violet, why don't you come and join me?
No, thank you.
Friends are supposed to bathe together, though.
Is that really what they do?
Yes, it is, so come on!
What do you say? Huh? Get in!
I've never done this before.
Taken a bath with someone.
You haven't?
Come here.
Is this also what friends do?
I don't know. I slept like this with my little sister.
I see.
Wah!
Open wide, Taylor!
So is it good?
Sister!
Why don't...
You have the basic steps down nearly perfect.
For today, I was thinking we could add some new steps.
Mm-hmm.
I'm all done.
Thank you for doing that.
I just noticed something.
You always wear your hair the same, huh?
I do.
Miss Isabella?
Just relax.
We can't do this. You'll miss the morning lecture.
Don't worry so much.
I have a sister. I used to do her hair all the time.
Your hair is just like velvet.
Bet it's worth a lot.
You're going to sell it?
Of course I won't.
And done.
Like it?
It seems like it could block
my line of sight in an emergency.
Oh? But it's so cute.
Okay, then. How about this?
Ta-dah! Just like cinnamon buns.
Miss Isabella, it appears you're having fun.
That obvious?
Hey.
Let's forget about school. Can't we go somewhere else?
Where exactly do you want to go?
Anywhere is fine.
Just the two of us.
We can't do that.
I'm sorry, Miss Isabella.
Hmm?
Now, why don't we try that again?
Miss Isabella?
I can't do it.
I can't be a lady. I never could.
You've learned to dance, and now you're going to...
I don't need your flattery!
I'm not able to be a good at everything like you are.
I'm not... I'm not like you.
Like me?
Yes, that's right! I'm totally different!
It's not fair. Not at all.
You don't realize how lucky you are.
Sorry.
It's okay. It seems you're just a little tired.
What sorts of letters have you written?
I've written many different kinds before.
Letters from kids writing to parents,
from sisters to brothers, and even love letters.
Love letters? A strait-laced girl like you?
Yes. They were all well-received.
Really?
It's more common than you think.
Every one I wrote was filled with all kinds of love.
I think people request them because letters
let you express the things you normally can't say.
Hey, I was wondering...
I'm always so mean. But you're... still so nice to me.
You really think that I'm nice?
Yes, you are.
Thank you.
I guess I'm just doing what I've learned.
Miss Isabella, if you're unable to sleep,
I could always tell you about the constellations.
I learned all about them back when
I used to work at an observatory.
Mm.
Okay, I'll tell you a story about the stars.
The ones that shine this time of year.
What's all this?
It's from your father.
You're to wear this when you become a debutante.
This one is for you.
Huh? What's that?
It says, "Having fun?"
Who's that from?
It's a dress that was sent over by my company.
And, from the looks of it, it was most
likely delivered to me by one of my coworkers.
How nice. I bet it means he wants to see you soon.
You're leaving today, aren't you?
Yes. I'll be leaving tonight.
Okay.
Well then, let's have lots of fun at the ball.
Will you escort me?
I'd love to.
They're all looking at you, you know.
Is it because I've done something wrong?
No, silly.
It just means you look beautiful.
Everyone else is dressed up, though.
But you're the most beautiful.
Hey... Don't leave my side, okay?
Okay. I promise.
Miss Isabella.
I wanted to say... thank you, Violet.
Of course.
Are you tired?
I am, but...
That was fun.
I didn't even step on your feet.
Yes.
So what will you do now?
I'll go back home and start writing letters again.
I...
Hmm?
I want you... to write a letter for me.
Who is it for?
My little sister.
The truth is, I wasn't actually born into the York family.
Amy.
Hmm?
See that you do better next time around.
Yeah, well, it's tough out there with the war going on.
Huh?
Where's your mom?
Another abandoned child?
Well, even if we could sell
her, she's probably not worth much.
I've decided.
Hmm?
She'll be my little sister.
What? Don't be stupid.
How exactly do you think you're going to support a child?
I mean, you're still a kid yourself.
It's about revenge.
I was forced to live like this, too.
This child was about to suffer the same fate, but...
... I'll make sure she has a happy life.
I may have nothing, but I'll give her a fighting chance.
You call that "revenge"?
Well, it's not my fault if you two die.
You're going to be my little sister now. I'm Amy.
Hmm?
Uh... Let's see...
I'm sister.
Ah... Si... Si... Sister!
I'm home.
Sister!
Open wide, Taylor.
Mm!
Is it good?
Sister!
Our room was filthy.
And we pretty much had next to nothing.
But during that time...
... there was nothing more I could do.
Sister...
Huh?
Amy Bartlett, I presume?
How dare you barge in here? What is this?
So this is the child of that
woman from all those years ago.
The blood of the York family flows in her veins.
She is my daughter.
Hmm...
I want you to leave your name and
your past behind, and come with me.
Do that, and I'll see that the child is cared for.
It's in her best interest.
Did you truly think you could keep living like this?
Sister...?
I had nothing to offer her.
No dreams, no hope. The one true thing I had,
the best thing I had was...
Sister...!
Sister!
... my desire to protect her no matter the cost.
My desire to save her. It became my reason to keep living.
That was the day I sold my life to
the man who said he was my father.
And so ended Amy the homeless girl.
As for Taylor, I've been separated from her ever since.
We're not even allowed to meet.
In some ways, I can relate.
I never knew my parents. I was found
abandoned and was raised as a human weapon.
But then, someone new entered my life. He taught me to
write and he helped me to grow into the person I am today.
He always treated me kindly.
Because of him, I now... have a purpose in life.
I wasn't able to give anyone anything.
No. You're wrong about that.
What you did was give me my very first gift of friendship.
Also, you taught me something.
You taught me... that even the smallest
gesture like holding hands can warm the heart.
Miss Isabella, I believe you have given Taylor
more than you'll ever know.
Even if you can't see her,
you can write a letter. With a
letter, your feelings can reach anywhere.
Dear Taylor...
I'll pay you back someday.
Unfortunately, I have nothing to give you right now.
But I will repay your kindness.
There's no need.
Hmm? Why not?
You've done so much.
I don't know, I... I can't explain this feeling.
But I promise you don't have to.
Hey...
Will I ever see you again?
I don't know the answer to that.
But remember this... Miss Amy.
I am an Auto Memories Doll.
I go wherever I'm needed, if it is what you request.
So I see the Princess Knight is gone.
Now we can finally talk.
Uh, okay.
At the debutante ball, your waltz was beautiful.
Thank you, but... I couldn't have done it without Violet.
She helped me, Miss Lancaster.
Please, call me Ashley.
Huh?
Putting aside our ranks and our family names for a moment,
I was hoping that... That the two of us could talk alone.
Hey.
Hmm?
I have a couple letters here for you.
Me? For Taylor?
That's right, for you.
Oh, hey, you, over there!
Does she know how to read?
Nuh-uh.
Just my luck...
I guess I'll read them to you, then. Ready?
Taylor!
Okay, here goes.
Brother!
What? I'm not your brother.
All right. Listen up.
The first letter is from my co-worker, Violet Evergarden.
The gist is, "Come and see me
if you're ever in need of help
or want a shoulder to lean on."
This one doesn't have a name or address.
What is this? It's so short.
It says, "Here is a magic word that will protect you:
Amy. That's all you have to say."
Mean anything?
Hi, Taylor. I'm no longer known as Amy.
I had to abandon the name I've always had.
But I did it for you, because I love you.
Si... Sister...
But as long as you keep saying it like a magic word...
Si... ster...
... my hope that you'll have a better life someday...
... will never... fade away.
Sister!
So please, Taylor...
Amy.
Postal service.
Postal service!
Hmm? What's the matter?
Mr. Felitz... guess he isn't home again.
That's strange. He's always making such a racket
at nighttime. I could hold it for him if you'd like.
Uh... No, it's collect on delivery.
I'll come again this evening.
Hey, you three!
Hands off my bike!
Run!
What a beat-up bike!
Postal service.
Postal service?
Thank you.
You're welcome. Always happy to serve.
Where did that postman go?!
Postal service.
Hold on. One question.
Huh?
You see the tall building over there?
What on earth is that?
I told you before. It's a radio tower.
What's a radio, though? It's not something
that's going to give me headaches, is it?
It's nothing like that, no. War ended four years ago.
We're just rebuilding.
Lots of progress has been made since then.
Despite considerable growth worldwide,
the work of a mail carrier hasn't change. Not one bit.
It's the same thing every day.
What a boring job.
The same symbol...
Huh?
Bro...
Brother!
Huh?
What?
Brother!
Huh?
Oh, my! Are you lost?
Is that Benedict's little brother?
Or is it his lovechild?
Give me a break. She's just visiting.
Uh. My name's...
... Taylor! Taylor Bartlett!
What?! You're a girl?!
You said Taylor, is that right?
Mm! You're Wyalet Evergaldian?
That wasn't even close.
Look, this is the letter you wrote three years ago.
It said to come and see you if I'm ever in need.
That's why I'm here.
She's that kid?
Miss Taylor, does that mean you're in trouble?
I have a favor to ask you.
I want...
I want to work here!
Huh?!
Work here?
"If there ever comes a time when you leave
the orphanage, and you find that you need help,
please don't hesitate to come and find me.
From Violet Evergarden."
I see.
Taylor? Did you happen to... run away from your orphanage?
The letter is addressed to an
orphanage run by the kingdom of Drossel.
I can't imagine they'd let a
girl your age wander around alone.
Is that true?
Hmm?
Yeah.
I'm sorry. In order to work here,
I'm afraid you would have to be a
little bit older than you are now.
No, please! I'm all out of money!
I have nowhere else to go!
Nevertheless...
I ask that you allow her to stay.
Violet, you, too?
She's the little sister of... a friend of mine.
I promised I would help her.
I want to know! I want to know what...
... "I love you" means.
Well, I suppose it will take some time to
send her back. It'll require some looking in to.
So then...?
Mm-hmm. Until everything is all sorted
out, I suppose you can look after her.
Does that sound good to you?
Yay!
Great! You'll be helping the ghost writers, then.
Nuh-uh, no I won't!
Wanna know why? 'Cause I'm gonna deliver mail like you!
You are?
D-Deliver mail?!
Mm-hmm! Tee-hee.
You really don't want to help the ghost writers?
Are you sure?
Yeah! Before I even came here, I
decided I wanted to be a mail carrier!
There's no way! A little kid
couldn't do that sort of work.
Don't say that! Please, Brother, come on!
Just let me do it, please!
Quit it! I'm not your brother!
Won't you do this for her?
Seriously, guys?
I agree with her on this, Benedict.
She came all this way. Why
not at least show her the ropes?
So. It seems the boss has spoken.
Listen up. Just from looking at it, it may
seem easy, but delivering mail is really hard work.
So how about we have you start with delivering this mail.
Here you go.
Uh. Where's it go?
It goes to the addresses on the envelopes.
Take this. Read it.
Let's see...
Two... One...
It's in the Mill District, Leiden.
Alexander Street. The numbers 2125.
Hm? Don't tell me...
Oh, yeah! Mill District! I knew that.
Here?
Yeah.
Next address.
Uh.
Hey, there are no mailboxes here.
That means we have to go to each unit.
The fourth floor?
Next one.
What?!
There. Huh?
That's it for today. Let's head back.
Wow.
Huh?
You really deliver that much mail every day?
You never... You never even looked at a map! Not once!
That's amazing!
Well, yeah. Any decent mailman
has his entire route memorized.
Brother...
Hey! Can I call you "teacher"?
Huh? You kidding? No way.
It lit up all by itself!
They're really changing things around here.
They're switching to electric lights all over the city.
Really?
So why exactly do you want to be a mail carrier anyway?
That's a silly question.
It's 'cause mail carriers don't just
deliver mail, they deliver happiness.
Wow!
I can sleep here?!
Yes.
Where's your room, Wyalet?
At the bottom of the stairs. Across from it, actually.
So then, I have this whole room to myself!
Teacher!
Will you teach me again tomorrow?
Well, it's just... You don't know how to read yet, do you?
You... didn't read a single address today.
You were only able to read the numbers.
Mm...
Yeah... I can't read...
I want to, but...
I've always had trouble learning the alphabet.
Whenever I received a letter,
I would just have the nuns read them to me.
"Here is a magic word that will always protect you: Amy.
That's all you have to say."
Sister...
Hmm?
Read it... again?
I know I... wasn't honest.
I'm sorry...
Miss Taylor.
I'll teach you the alphabet if you want me to.
Huh? You will?
Yes. We'll start training together tomorrow.
Training?
No. What I meant to say was "study."
Study hard, and then,
we'll make you into a fine young mail carrier.
Wyalet!
It's Violet, actually.
Do you think that since I can't sleep by myself,
that makes me a baby?
No.
Hmm?
Is it looking outside?
The one I have is a bear.
Your sister always wanted to do this, too.
Sleep in the same bed together.
Is that true? You slept in the same bed?
Yes.
I see.
I wonder if I also used to
sleep in the same bed as Sister.
I wanna hear some more about Sister.
It's time to wake up, Miss Taylor.
I hope you slept well.
Ah!
They come undone if you only do
it with two strands, Miss Taylor.
By braiding three strands together,
it'll stay in place better.
Good morning.
Good morning, everyone!
Huh?
Well, good morning, you little apprentice.
Mr. Roland. I thought that you had retired already.
I just have so much free time,
I couldn't help myself. And what about you, Violet?
I hear that you're going to be
helping out with some deliveries today.
A is for the animals, and I is for the ice
U is for the umbrella, but the weather's so nice
Hah! E is for Err...
Violet?
Luculia.
It's been ages!
Wait, why're you dressed like that?
We're delivering mail!
You're delivering mail? With this girl?
She's an apprentice. I've been
helping her learn since she arrived.
Helping an apprentice... Is that part of the job?
Where are you headed?
To New Town.
Ah! It's just that way, right over the bridge.
Luculia!
Hmm?
I have to go, Violet. Good to see you.
... And you are...?
... My name's Taylor!
Well, then. Good luck with your job, Taylor.
Tee-hee.
Who was that lady?
She's a Doll, just like I am.
And that man with her?
That man? I don't know. I've never seen him before.
This place is New Town?
Yes. Try reading the address.
Okay, I'll try. L-E-I... Lei-den. Leiden.
And then... What's this one?
Rhetorica District. What's next?
Rhetorica District, 6, 7, 8, 9...
... 10, 11... It's 12!
Here it is!
Miss Taylor.
Hmm?
It's this way.
What's this?
This is a machine that's called an elevator.
It's a new device that's being introduced
at New Town's latest apartment buildings.
I... think it's for transportation.
So how does this thing work?
Well, let's see...
I believe you use this.
It didn't work...
Wow! It's moving!
Ah! That was our floor!
I'll bring it back down.
Wah!
Whew, we made it.
The stairs would've been faster.
Ah!
Oh, my!
Postal service!
Why, thank you, dear. Oh!
This is from my mother.
Marty! There's a gift from your grandma here!
Really?!
What is it?
Slow down.
Uh. Ooh! It's candy! Hooray! Hooray! Hooray! Hoo...
Uhh...
Hey, um... Was it that obvious I wanted some?
Yes.
Really? So Luculia is in Leiden now?
She is. She was there with a gentleman.
Do you think that... That it's
the man she's going to marry?
I guess marriage means her Doll days are over.
No way. She said she wasn't going to quit.
She wants to keep working even after she gets married.
Wait, seriously? Wow...
Times have changed.
Changed how?
Seems like there's now more to a Doll's life
than finding the man of your dreams and retiring.
Is that supposed to be the optimal life for a Doll?
Yeah. Until now, at least.
Do you two share that ideal? Finding a man and retiring?
Huh?
I wouldn't call it an ideal, exactly.
I think I'm more interested in
becoming the top Doll in the world.
Oh. I want to write novels.
I think that's always been my
dream more than anything else.
Writing novels?
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm really interested in it.
I already wrote and submitted a short story.
So there are many dreams and ideals, then.
Well, how about you?
You want to know... my ideal?
Ah! Teacher!
I'm not your teacher. Time for afternoon deliveries.
Miss Taylor!
Huh?
You sure it's okay?
Yes.
You know that no one's ever bought me clothes before?
Oh, is that true?
Yeah, at the orphanage, it's all hand-me-downs.
I love having something that's all my own.
I'll treasure it.
This, too! My teddy bear is also
my precious, precious treasure.
Having something to treasure... That feeling...
It's wonderful, isn't it?
I can't remember much from back then.
I wonder if Sister used to do this for me.
I forgot almost everything.
"Here is the magic word that will always protect you:
Amy. That's all you have to say."
Miss Taylor. Why is it that you
want to be a mail carrier so badly?
I wanna be like Teacher. 'Cause he's
the one who delivered Sister's letter.
I know that I forgot what it
was like when I lived with Sister,
but I still have this letter from her.
I've always kept it close to me. It reminds me of
her and her love for me. That's what Teacher delivered.
He delivered happiness.
Mail delivery is a great career.
I believe you've chosen well.
Mm-hmm.
Amy...
I also want to be able to deliver happiness.
I was thinking...
Why don't you write a letter to your sister?
Um. Yeah, but... I can't read.
I'm still learning. But even if
I could, I dunno what I'd write.
Miss Taylor. I am a Doll, you know.
So please, let me help you with this.
Will she like it? The letter?
I believe that your feelings will reach her.
Um... Dear Sister...
What is it? You know how early it is?
Is she going back to the orphanage?
No. We want to know if you can deliver a letter for us.
Hmm?
Did you write this yourself?
Mm!
I learned to read and write.
You're sending it to Amy Bartlett?
Where's the address, though?
We don't have it.
Huh?
Amy Bartlett is now called Isabella York.
She attended a girls' school as heir to the York family.
But her current whereabouts are unknown.
Isn't she a friend of yours, Violet?
Well, we did exchange letters for a period of time,
however... she stopped writing.
I imagine she was married off to an important aristocrat.
But we've no way of knowing who that is.
Wait, are you asking me to track her down?
But that's...
Please? Please, Teacher?
Will you?
I need it... I need it get to her.
No matter how difficult, every letter
deserves to be delivered. But listen up.
If I do it, I have one condition.
I thought you might be here.
Hmm?
Hard work is all fine and dandy,
but you also need your sleep.
Thanks.
Ah, that hit the spot!
Oh, I almost forgot. A letter arrived for you.
Huh?
I found it...
This was his condition?
Mm-hmm. Can't say I blame him.
His old bike was on its last legs.
You have to be careful out there. Promise me you will?
Mm-hmm!
Let's go.
Hmm.
Violet.
Yes.
Thanks a lot. For all that you've done.
Ah... Of course.
Good luck, Miss Taylor! I hope it goes well!
You worked so hard... I hope that...
I hope that your love is delivered.
It seems like the York family went to great
lengths to keep Isabella's true identity a secret.
But she's from one of the great houses with
ties to the royal Drossel family, so in reality,
there were only a few worthy suitors.
The rest was just process of elimination.
Whoa...
She lives here?
Yes. This is Count Neville's manor.
The local villagers say that
they see the count pretty often,
but, apparently, they've actually
never seen the lady of the manor.
However, merchants who visit here
say that, around this time of day,
they've managed to catch a glimpse
of her at the back of the mansion.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Um... I have a letter for you.
A letter? For me?
Yes, that's right. For Isabella...
Wait, make that "Amy Bartlett."
Here.
Taylor... Bartlett.
It can't be...
It says...
"Dear Sister"...
The nuns told me what happened.
They helped me understand everything better.
They said that the reason you went off
to somewhere far away was to protect me.
But you still sent me a letter.
You were thinking of me, even when we were so far apart.
That's why...
... I know that...
"I know that I'm Taylor Bartlett."
"I am Amy Bartlett's"...
... "little sister."
My sister...
My little sister...
Good morning, Taylor.
Sister...
Just so you know, Violet helped her write it.
Is... Is that true?
I'm so glad!
I'm so very glad!
Thank you for this.
Sister...
Huh?
Like peas in a pod.
So she's able to write now.
The last time I saw her, she was so little.
I think that... I'm going to write Taylor a letter.
And Violet, too.
Will you deliver them?
Of course.
But someday, it just might be someone else.
Huh?
Teacher, I saw you crying.
You were the one who was crying!
Yeah, but you were, too.
Enough!
So. You really okay with not meeting her?
Mm-hmm.
I don't wanna do it until I become a real mail carrier.
Once I do, I'll come back and deliver my letters myself!
Heh. Still haven't given up, huh?
Course not! 'Cause what mail carriers deliver...
What we deliver is...
... happiness.
Is that right?
Mm-hmm!
Amy.
Soon after, Taylor Bartlett ended up
being adopted by the Evergarden family.
And when she's old enough to work...
Wow!
So cool!
She'll become a mail carrier once again.
Postal service.
Excuse me, one moment.
Huh?
When is that big building going to be finished?
They're taking forever to finish it!
Someday...
Someday.
Taylor...!