‐ [Ranpha] Why do we
always get jobs like this?
Hey, are you listening, Vanilla?
(metal clangs)
(robotic arm whirs)
It must be God’s calling.
Maybe I’ll find a diamond
ring or something.
‐ Hey, is this trash burnable?
Do you have any idea, Ranpha?
‐ Don’t ask me, I don’t know.
‐ But it’s very important
to separate your trash.
(trash whooshes)
(Ranpha groans)
‐ What are you doing?
I can’t take this anymore.
(Milfeulle yells)
Shut up!
‐ [Milfeulle] No, please don’t.
(trash whooshing)
‐ [Ranpha] I’ve
had enough of you!
‐ [Milfeulle] Stop it!
No!
(Ranpha groans)
Hey, that’s not very nice.
Stop it!
Oh, ah, Ranpha!
(sirens blaring)
(ship whooshing)
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Ranpha] Vanilla Flavored
Asteroid Trash Stir‐Fry.
‐ [Forte] To think
that the secret mission
of the Angel Brigade of
the Transbaal Empire Force
is separating trash.
‐ No kidding, some mission.
‐ [Mint] Hard to believe
the lost technology
is in this dump.
‐ According to the
intelligence department report
that’s the case.
‐ [Mint] But they’re
always messing up.
You think they’re right?
‐ Well, now, I can’t say.
‐ If we don’t find anything here
we’ll just pack all this
trash into a missile
and send it to them.
‐ [Ranpha] Forte,
I think I’ve got the
perfect thing for that.
‐ Hmm?
‐ [Ranpha] Vanilla just
found it with the trash.
‐ It’s not even listed
in the weapons catalog.
‐ Huh, I’ve never seen a
missile like this before either.
‐ Maybe this is it,
the lost technology.
‐ Really?
This thing?
‐ No way, it’s just
a dud, garbage.
Let’s get rid of it.
‐ Do you wanna take it apart?
‐ Okay.
‐ [Dud Missile] You
people are awful.
Maybe I’ll just blow
myself up right here.
‐ Who’s that?
‐ [Dud Missile]
It’s me, right here!
‐ Who’s there?
Come out from where
you’re hiding.
‐ You just don’t get it, do you?
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am MA347612890GT4078579132RF24
00Z 17924398TZR
Two Thousand Modular Guided
Type 452963752391MQTO
Gold Launch System GLS‐equipped
Self‐Computing
Double‐O Three Seven
293165734285YGNKTIO1200YMCA41263
Normad.
That’s me.
It’s a pleasure to
make your acquaintance.
‐ And you too, Mr. Missile.
‐ I am not a missile.
I am MA34761‐‐
‐ We got that.
What’s your outfit?
Where are you from?
And why are you in this dump?
Answer me!
Well?
‐ I miss the old days.
Women back then were
so reserved and sweet
and warm and gentle,
they really cared.
‐ What’s that?
‐ I don’t know if
I can go on living.
Maybe I should just blow up.
(all yelling)
(Volcott stammers)
‐ Stop and think if you can!
‐ You think I can’t?
I can!
‐ Mr. Missile, I
mean, Mr. Normad,
how about we just
talk this over?
I apologize for my
insolent subordinates.
‐ Well then, are you
the one in charge here?
‐ [Volcott] I am.
‐ I think we can get along.
These subordinates
must frustrate you.
‐ Well, you know.
‐ No need to hide it.
I can tell.
‐ Just wait a minute.
‐ Ranpha.
‐ [Normad] Think twice before
you talk to me like that.
‐ Forgive me, I’m sorry.
‐ You need to understand,
as a women you should
make a point of learning
a few things from Vanilla.
‐ [Forte] Why Vanilla?
‐ [Normad] Can’t you tell?
She’s quiet, restrained,
a wonderful lady.
‐ [Forte] She’s
just a kid, a kid!
‐ [Normad] Sounds
like envy to me.
‐ [Forte] Yeah, well,
you’re just a missile.
‐ [Normad] I am MA3476‐‐
(Volcott coughs)
‐ I think we should
continue this discussion.
So, Normad, how did
you end up in the dump?
‐ [Normad] I was picked up
while having myself a sleep
during a long voyage.
‐ A voyage?
‐ Yes.
I wasn’t happy in
the military anymore
so I set off on my own.
All by myself.
‐ (scoffs) Quite a story.
So in other words, you’re AWOL?
What a coward.
‐ [Normad] I had a hard
time coming to grips with it
and understanding who I am.
‐ Huh, what’s that?
What do you mean by that?
‐ [Normad] I suppose a crude
and violent person like you
wouldn’t understand.
‐ What you say?
‐ [Normad] I’m a missile.
When I hit my target I
blow up, that means I die.
‐ But a missile’s destiny
is to hit the enemy
and go up in a blaze of glory.
‐ [Normad] You think
it’s that easy?
I’ve worked hard and
learned many things.
I thought there was a
bright future for me,
but in the end all I
could look forward to
is a violent explosion.
Don’t you think that’s cruel?
‐ Yeah, that’s what missiles
are for, aren’t they?
‐ [Normad] But I
don’t want that.
I don’t want to die
in an explosion.
There must be a better
purpose for me in life.
That’s what I wanna find.
‐ Oh, Mr. Normad,
that’s beautiful.
‐ [Normad] Thank you.
How’d you like to get together
later and talk about life?
‐ I’d love to, but I’m
not good at conversation.
‐ [Normad] I hate you.
‐ He talks enough for two.
‐ What now?
We can’t put him
back in the dump.
‐ Maybe not, but he is an
AWOL missile after all.
The military might
have something to say.
‐ This is an issue best
left to a higher command.
‐ [Normad] This is so cruel.
So cruel!
I miss the old days,
everyone was so
sincere and gentle.
I should self destruct!
(lid pops)
(all gasping)
Just kidding, it was a joke.
Just a little joke.
(all sighing)
I have a lot of
knowhow and experience.
You might find me
useful to have around.
‐ That might be very true, but.
‐ This thing’s just
way too dangerous
for us to have lying around.
‐ Wait a minute.
(machine beeps)
‐ [Forte] I get it.
Take him apart and just keep
the computer chip, right?
‐ [Ranpha] We’ll put the
rest of him back in the trash
and there won’t be any evidence.
‐ Oh, Milfeulle.
‐ Huh?
‐ Do you see that big
button in front of you?
‐ Big button.
Button.
Ah, there it is.
‐ Did you push it?
‐ Yes, what now?
(missile beeps)
‐ [Normad] Switching
to self destruct mode.
Self destructing in one minute.
(all screaming)
‐ Why would a missile have a
self destruct device anyway?
‐ [Normad] My name
is not missile.
It is MA347‐‐
‐ Yes, we know!
Can we disconnect this thing?
‐ We should be able to stop
the self destruct mechanism
by cutting either the
red or blue lines.
They’re shown on the monitor
that’s attached to Normad.
(monitor beeping)
‐ This is your fault Milfeulle.
You’d better do something.
‐ But, what if I
cut the wrong one?
‐ It’ll explode.
‐ No, I can’t do it!
I’d only be guessing.
‐ Our lives are at stake.
You have no choice but to try.
‐ But I, oh!
(girls grunting)
All right, I’ll try.
‐ [Normad] 30 seconds
to self destruct.
(Milfeulle whimpers)
(intense music)
20 seconds.
‐ Do it, luck’s on your side.
(Milfeulle whimpers)
‐ What are you doing?
Hurry!
‐ Okay.
(monitor beeping)
‐ Once you choose just
click with the trackball.
(Milfeulle whimpers)
(intense music)
‐ [Normad] 10 seconds.
‐ Come on!
Hurry up and press it.
‐ Right, but, I
can’t move my finger.
‐ What?
‐ Five.
‐ What are you doing?
‐ If you don’t push it now.
‐ Listen to me, Milfeulle.
‐ [Normad] Four.
‐ Close your eyes and
picture a flower‐‐
‐ [Ranpha And Forte]
Don’t be afraid.
(monitor beeps)
‐ Three.
‐ What are the chance?
‐ [Normad] Two.
‐ Come on.
(girls gasp)
‐ [Normad] One.
Just do it, push it!
(monitor beeps)
(energy whooshes)
‐ What happened?
(monitor beeping)
(Milfeulle gasps)
Vanilla.
(all sighing)
‐ [Normad] The self destruct
device has been stopped.
(light piano music)
Thank you, Vanilla.
Checkmate.
‐ 137 losses in a row.
‐ No point in playing again.
How many times you wanna lose?
I’m sorry for taking away
your only joy in life.
(chip whooshes)
‐ I’ve got a body for you.
Much better than doing
nothing, isn’t it?
(Ranpha grunts)
‐ [Normad] Workouts?
‐ Would you just
stop complaining?
(chip whooshes)
‐ Yeah, you’re lucky,
this’ll make it easier.
(Normad rattles)
‐ [Normad] I hate menial work.
(Mint laughs)
(chip whooshes)
‐ Have I got a body for you!
‐ [Normad] I’ll
pass on that one.
‐ [Forte] Well,
what do you think?
These are the only two body
types we have left for you.
‐ Although they’re
stuffed animals.
‐ [Forte] Well?
‐ [Normad] All
right, I’ve decided.
Thank you, Vanilla.
I really like this new body.
I knew right away
when we first met
that we could definitely
become good friends.
I hope we have a long
and happy friend.
(Normad grunts)
Oh, my, my.
Don’t worry that
didn’t hurt at all.
You truly are
wonderful, Vanilla.
You’re like Venus herself.
‐ [Milfeulle] I’ve
made some tea.
‐ [Ranpha] So you’re
telling us that your life‐‐
‐ [Milfeulle] I’ve
made some tea.
‐ [Ranpha] Oh no, they
slipped him poison.
‐ [Milfeulle] I’ve
made some tea.
‐ [Ranpha] It can only
be a test from God.
‐ I’ve made some tea.
‐ A rich husband!
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)