(engines roaring)
(alarm blaring)
("Galaxy Bang!
Bang!" by Angel‐tai)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Forte] Downtown
Soul food Oden.
(sirens blaring)
(melancholy music)
There’s a neighborhood,
about 10 kilometers south
of the center of town.
It’s called the Miles
district, Highland.
(sirens blaring)
But being overrun with crime,
the district has come
to be known as Deadtown.
‐ [Woman] Welcome.
‐ Hello, there.
‐ [Woman] Hello, again.
(slow, Japanese music)
You really are a night owl.
(Forte chuckles)
Coming to a rowdy spot
like this, almost
every night you can?
‐ I find it relaxes me.
‐ [Woman] You shouldn’t
be drinking so much.
No man’s going to
wanna marry you
if you’re a lush, you know.
(Forte chuckles)
‐ Can I have some oden
with some fish cake and potato?
‐ You pay first, Milly.
‐ What are you so worried about?
I’ve got lots of money.
‐ You pay me first.
‐ I have it, okay?
‐ (sighs) And how many
times have I fallen
for that story now?
You can’t pull that again.
‐ (growls) Just
never mind, then.
‐ My goodness!
‐ Hang on a second.
(Woman gasps)
‐ Hmm?
‐ Oden with fish
cake and potato.
‐ Hmm?
‐ You’re buying me dinner?
Wow, that’s great!
‐ Huh?
Alright, here you go.
‐ Yum, thanks a lot. (sighs)
Mmm, this smells great.
‐ 45 caliber, huh?
This is too big for a kid.
‐ (munches) Hmm, hmm? (gasps)
‐ Hmm?
‐ I’m not a kid!
‐ Milly!
‐ You do that again,
you’ll pay with your life.
‐ Hmm?
‐ And don’t forget it! (munches)
‐ Hey, wait!
Aren’t you even
gonna thank the lady
who paid for your meal?
Milly!
‐ (chuckles) She’s
from around here?
‐ (sighs) She’s not really
a bad kid, you know.
Her father was a big
shot in organized crime.
He’s in prison now
serving a life sentence.
Her mother is with another
man and has lost interest.
‐ It must be tough.
(melancholy music)
(sirens blaring)
(communication device beeping)
Yes?
Roger, I’ll return to base now.
‐ Hold it!
‐ Huh?
(Milly panting)
(Forte gasps)
(tires screeching)
(horn blares)
(Milly grunts)
‐ Oh, (pants) did you just
see a little girl run by here?
Ah!
M‐Milly, Milly!
(Milly sighs and giggles)
‐ Hey, you.
(Milly squeals)
‐ What do you want?
‐ You’re gonna return
what you stole.
‐ But I just ate it.
‐ Then, you’ll pay for it.
‐ I’ve got no money!
‐ Then, we’ll go to the police.
‐ (growls) You don’t understand!
Everyone who lives around
here is doing the same thing.
‐ So, you think
that makes it okay?
(Milly grunts)
(Forte yells)
Why you...
(groans) That,
that punk. (laughs)
Hmm?
Is this hers?
‐ There you are!
(grunts) I want you
to give me my gun!
‐ You’re back.
‐ It’s mine, give it back.
‐ Don’t you mean, may I please?
‐ What?!
I’m calling the cops!
‐ Go ahead, you’re the
one who’ll be arrested.
(Milly growling)
I’ll have the bill, please.
‐ Right away.
I want you to take me
and show me your home.
‐ Huh?
‐ If you want your gun back,
you’re gonna have
to do as I tell you.
‐ [Milly] But you’re
not coming in!
‐ [Forte] Milly, do you
like this neighborhood?
‐ [Milly] I don’t
know how anyone
could like this rotten place.
Well, here it is, my gun please?
‐ [Forte] One second inside.
‐ [Milly] I said I’m
not letting you in.
(grunts) Hey, you
can’t go in there!
(Forte gasps)
‐ What an untidy
room you’ve got here.
‐ Where’s my gun?
‐ You could at least
offer tea to your guest.
‐ (growls) Give me a break.
‐ Okay, I’ll leave.
‐ (growls) Alright,
alright, tea then!
What’s her problem anyway?
Why do I have to serve her tea‐‐
(Forte chuckles)
‐ In my home? (grunts)
‐ Hmm.
Hmm. (chuckles)
‐ (gasps) Hey, you get
out of there right now!
‐ This outfit is so cute.
‐ [Milly] Put that away!
‐ Please try it on?
‐ No way!
‐ You don’t wear
these clothes?
‐ No!
‐ [Forte] You never wear them?
‐ I told you, I don’t!
‐ Really, you don’t?
(Milly growling)
Wow!
You look pretty in that!
If you’d dress like that more
often, boys would notice you.
(sips) What?
‐ You promised me I
could have my gun back.
‐ Oh, yeah.
Here you go.
‐ But this is...
(Milly quivers)
‐ Your gun.
(Milly gasps)
Don’t you want it?
‐ Just shut up!
(door slams)
(footsteps pounding)
(Forte heavily breathes)
(gunshots banging)
‐ [Forte] I understand.
(footsteps tapping)
Milly.
(gun clicks)
I understand your feelings.
I know exactly what
you’re going through.
(melancholy music)
(Milly munching)
‐ Any good?
‐ Not really.
‐ Then, don’t eat it.
‐ But I’m hungry, though.
(Forte chuckles)
What is this?
‐ Just open it up.
(Milly gasps)
‐ But why, why are
you doing this?
You don’t know
anything about me.
‐ Afraid?
‐ [Milly] What’s this for?
‐ You can’t trust anyone
or anything, can you?
Hmm, can you?
‐ You only think
that you understand!
‐ Oh, yes I do, very well.
I’ve been through
the same thing.
‐ Huh?
‐ I was alone.
There was nobody there
who knew how to reach me.
When you live in that
kind of environment,
you just stop trusting people.
And then, you begin to believe
that you are so different
that no one will like you.
But, there are many ways out.
So sometimes, when you
hear a knock at the door,
take a chance and look.
(chuckles) This kind, old
man told me that years ago.
(Volcott sneezes)
Here then.
You can have this back, bye.
‐ [Woman] Thank you.
‐ Wait!
‐ Thank you for the tea.
It was very good.
‐ Huh?
(Milly giggles)
Hey, thank you, Forte! (laughs)
(sirens blaring)
‐ [Milefeulle] W‐w‐wait!
At this rate, Vanilla will‐‐
(gunshot explodes)
‐ [Forte] So why?
‐ [Normad] It’s been two weeks!
‐ What?
‐ But why?
‐ [Normad] It seems
Vanilla has lost
something very important.
‐ [Forte and Raphna] What?!
‐ [Raphna] Well, let’s
ask the fortune‐teller,
Mother Milky Way, about it.
("Horoscope Rhapsody")
(singing in foreign language)