(ship humming)
‐ [Mint] So it’s just
Vanilla and me this time?
‐ Yes, I’ve been trying
to get ahold of the others
but it seems they’re
both still on vacation.
‐ And so are we after all.
It’s just that when I was told
that somebody new was coming
I decided I should
stay near the base.
Right, Vanilla?
‐ Vanilla doesn’t seem
to be having a problem
with that at all.
‐ You know, Volcott, it’s
always the quiet types
like her that go completely
berserk out of the blue
with no warning.
‐ Really?
Hmm.
‐ Hey, Colonel, don’t you
think it would be good idea
to have Forte and Ranpha with us
before the new recruit arrives?
‐ I do,
but I have no idea
where they are,
or what they’re doing
with themselves.
‐ [Ranpha] Forte, I don’t
think this is a good idea.
‐ [Forte] Don’t
worry, leave it to me.
‐ But.
(dramatic percussive music)
But, Forte‐‐
‐ Shh, quiet, Ranpha.
‐ But I.
‐ That’s it!
(ball rattles)
‐ On black, number four.
‐ Yeah!
‐ That was sweet!
(sirens blaring)
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)
Gamble Milfeulle Sauce.
(ball rattles)
‐ Red, number seven.
‐ Wow, I can’t believe the
winning streak you’re having.
What luck!
It’s incredible.
‐ [Forte] This is nothing.
‐ Huh?
‐ You know, if this keeps
up we could spend the rest
of our lives on
this resort planet
and never have to worry
about anything ever again.
‐ Wow.
‐ All right, Ranpha Franboise,
are you ready to go on
a really long vacation?
‐ [Man] I’m impressed.
‐ Huh?
‐ It seems that luck
is on your side.
‐ (giggles) That’s right.
We seem to be on quite
the wild streak of luck.
You look like you just
might be the perfect one
to share it with.
‐ So, just who are you?
‐ My name is Green, and I’m
the owner of this casino.
Now, how would you like
a little excitement,
like some competitive betting?
‐ Hmm.
(patrons chattering)
‐ Well, let’s begin.
Bets, please.
(ball whooshing)
What will it be?
‐ Hmm, I’ll put
everything on red.
‐ Oh no, Forte!
‐ [Green] Well, I do
admire your courage.
(dramatic music)
(wheel whirs)
‐ Why thank you.
(Green laughs)
(Mint sighs)
(phone ringing)
‐ Ah, Ms. Mint, come here.
I’ve got Forte and
Ranpha on the line.
‐ Forte, Ranpha, what
are you two up to anyway?
We’ve been looking for you.
‐ [Both] Mint, we’re
having such a blast!
‐ Okay, something’s up.
‐ [Both] You’re on vacation too,
why don’t you come and join us?
‐ I don’t think that’s possible.
The new person will
be starting today
so I can’t leave here.
‐ Come on, spend a
little time with us.
We really need to
see you face to face
and we want to talk to about
something really important.
‐ We won’t take a
lot of your time.
You’ll be back to base
before you know it.
‐ I’m not lending
you money, sorry.
‐ [Both] Well, we tried.
(both gasp)
‐ All right, girls, shall we go?
(bell rings)
(luchador yells)
(kick thuds)
(luchador thuds)
‐ Ranpha!
‐ Yeah, I’m right here.
(Ranpha thuds)
(Forte grunts)
(both grunting)
(bones cracking)
(crowd cheering)
‐ Go get ’em, girls, come on!
That’s it, go get her!
‐ You know, I think this
is more fun than roulette.
‐ I couldn’t agree more,
but at the moment I’m
almost at my limit.
(Forte groaning)
Ranpha.
(bones cracking)
(Ranpha groaning)
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
‐ [Milfeulle] Don’t quit now!
‐ Huh?
‐ Just give him one.
Like this and like this.
‐ Huh?
‐ Come on, you’ve got it in you.
‐ [Both] It’s that lucky girl!
(bell rings)
‐ That was amazing to
see a comeback like that.
Wow, and what was that
last move you pulled?
You lifted her up and
dropped her on her head.
I’ve never seen
anything like it.
Honestly, you both are just
so awesome in that ring.
‐ Excuse me.
How much money do you
have with you right now?
‐ Huh?
‐ Okay, my friend, listen,
from your clothes I can see
that you’re in the military.
What would your commander say
if he knew you were out
this late at a casino?
‐ You know, you two sure
don’t look much like
professional wrestlers.
(both groaning)
‐ [Both] We need to know how
much money you have with you!
‐ Here.
I’m sorry, but it’s all I’ve
got left after shopping.
I found this great sale
on the best chocolate
I’ve ever tasted.
‐ Unbelievable.
‐ Okay, girls, time
to for the next match.
‐ Sorry, Green, but we’re
through wrestling for you.
That’s it.
‐ Oh?
Then you’ll be paying
cash for your debts
that you owe the casino?
‐ You bet.
(slot machine dinging)
‐ Forte,
I know that girl’s
got nothing but luck
but do you think we
should be trusting her
with the very last coin we have?
‐ I think we’re out
of options here.
The best thing we can do now
is bet on our friend’s
mysterious good fortune.
‐ Forte.
‐ I mean, do you really
wanna quit the Angel Brigade
and become a
professional wrestler?
‐ Hello.
‐ Will you please shut up?
Look, what I’m saying is
do we want to put our fates
into the hands of
a total stranger?
Our future rests with that coin.
We’ve only got one last
chance to make it or break it.
(lever creaks)
‐ Huh?
(slot machine dinging)
‐ Look, everything’s
going round and round.
This is so much fun.
‐ No wait!
‐ A minute!
(slot machine dining)
Luck or no luck, we
definitely need a miracle.
(slot machine dinging)
(coins clattering)
‐ Oh no!
What’s happening here?
What am I supposed to do?
Oh no, stop, stop!
‐ She is something else.
(upbeat music)
(ball rattles)
‐ Black again, number four.
‐ You won again.
Now we’re really
back in the game.
‐ Good one.
What are you going
to play next, huh?
‐ [Milfeulle] Let’s
see, I’m 17 years old,
so how about 17?
‐ Very impressive.
Have you girls broken even yet?
‐ Hey, back off, Green.
We’ll do a lot better than
that before the day’s out.
‐ Hey, hey!
I just won again!
‐ (laughs) Tell me, girls,
how can we make this
more interesting?
How about a game
of all or nothing?
Of course if you win
we can just forget about the
debt that you still owe me.
(Ranpha gasps)
Fair is fair.
‐ Really?
‐ On the other hand,
if I defeat you,
your beautiful friend
here must join you
in the wrestling ring.
I’m sure she’ll be more popular.
(Ranpha scoffs)
‐ [Forte] Fine, let’s play!
(upbeat music)
‐ Now we begin.
Place your bets.
(ball whooshes)
Well, my friends?
‐ What will you bet on?
‐ Hmm, I know, red
as in strawberries.
‐ Are you sure?
(upbeat music)
(wheel whirs)
Do you realize just
how serious this is?
(Green laughs)
(ball rattles)
(girls trilling)
(all gasping)
(Green laughs)
‐ [Green] It seems
like I’ve won, so.
‐ Look!
A shooting star!
(meteor whooshing)
(glass shatters)
‐ What the heck?
What’s going on‐‐
(metal thuds)
(glass shattering)
(wind whooshing)
‐ [Forte] How unbelievable.
‐ Whoa.
‐ [Milfeulle] Wow!
‐ [Both] Huh?
‐ Hey, it’s on the red.
Look, look, we’re on the red.
I think that this means that
we win again, doesn’t it?
(girls stammering)
‐ Is this really happening?
What?
She’s joining us?
She’s assigned to Angel Brigade?
‐ Yes, that’s correct.
Apparently she was a
very bright student
at officer training school.
Something about
having good luck.
‐ That’s nice but does
that make her very bright?
‐ Now, now, she’s
in the Brigade,
so you girls are going
to have to work together.
‐ Well, I don’t
approve of this at all.
We can’t rely on
happy accidents.
‐ Ranpha, do you want to go
back to wrestling or what?
After all, she was the one
that got us out of
our gambling debt.
(Ranpha groans)
Welcome to the Brigade.
And what was your name again?
(upbeat music)
Recruit, are you with us here?
‐ My name is Milfeulle Sakuraba.
And I look forward to
working with all of you.
(upbeat music)
‐ [Mint] Close your eyes
and picture a flower garden.
‐ [Forte] Doesn’t sound too bad.
‐ [Milfeulle] I think
that’s wonderful.
‐ [Man] No Kidding.
‐ [Forte] Have I
got a body for you.
‐ [Milfeulle] I think
that’s wonderful.
‐ [Mint] It doesn’t seem to go.
(upbeat pop music)
(singing in foreign language)