(engine revving)
(upbeat cheerful music)
(singing in a foreign language)
‐ [Narrator] Assorted angel
fruits shipped direct.
‐ [Ranpha] Yahoo!
Wooho.
Yahoo.
‐ Ranpha’s sure having
an awful lot of fun.
‐ Well, I’m not surprised.
‐ You know, the Kincaid Company
is one of the biggest
construction firms
in the entire Milky Way galaxy.
‐ And to think they’ve got
such a young president too.
‐ Hi, handsome!
(smooching)
‐ But why would the president
of a large construction firm
have someone threaten his life?
‐ Well, I’m sure there
much be a good reason.
‐ It can only be
a test from God.
(smooching)
‐ Well, whatever.
The most important thing here
is that we have been assigned
as his bodyguards, right?
‐ Oh, but if I could
just catch his eye
I know a great romance would
blossom, and maybe marriage!
Oh, my!
‐ So what’s the problem?
I got something on my face?
(gasping)
‐ You’re not the president of
the Kincaid Company, are you?
‐ Yes, Jim Kincaid, president
of the Kincaid Company.
‐ But, what about this?
‐ Oh, that’s a picture
from my younger days.
Hope, did you send
them the wrong picture?
‐ I’m very sorry
sir, my mistake.
‐ So much for that idea.
‐ Fallen out of love now?
‐ You’ve gotta be kidding.
I’m still an innocent young
girl with a very bright future.
‐ So, Mr. Kincaid,
you’re telling us
that your life has
been threatened?
‐ Aha, I got a very
disturbing letter
that said that they
were going to kill me.
‐ Oh no, they slipped
him some poison.
‐ Hope!
You’ve gone and put salt in
my coffee instead of sugar!
‐ I’m very sorry
sir, my mistake.
‐ So you really are
being threatened, sir?
‐ [Allan] Aha.
The Angel Brigade of the
Transvaal Imperial Forces, huh?
‐ [Jim] What do you think?
Isn’t it a beautiful planet?
‐ [Milfeulle] Yes, I’d love
to live in a place like this!
‐ [Ranpha] You
couldn’t afford to
on your meager Angel
Brigade salary.
‐ [Jim] I guess not.
(Jim laughing)
This planet is being
developed as a giant resort.
The construction should be
complete in about one month.
I’ve just come to
take a look around.
‐ [Forte] Any idea who may
be attempting to kill you?
‐ [Jim] None at all, really.
And what reason would
they have to do that?
‐ Does anyone hate you for
personal reasons perhaps?
‐ Hm, I can’t think of anyone.
‐ Well, let’s not worry
about that right now.
We just need to do our job
and make sure he’s protected.
‐ [Hope] What?
‐ What’s going on, Hope?
‐ I’m losing control here.
‐ What?
Oh, Hope, stop the launch.
‐ It’s too late.
‐ Aren’t you my bodyguards?
You’ve got to do something.
‐ Yes but what.
(Hope groaning)
‐ [Hope] We’ve leveled off.
‐ Well, it looks like someone
has been tampering
with the computer.
‐ [Forte] It seems that
these threats on your life
are real after all.
‐ Mr. Kincaid, are you sure
you can’t think
of anyone at all?
‐ [Jim] No, not at all.
‐ [Ranpha] What is it this time?
‐ [Milfeulle] It looks
like we’ve stopped.
‐ I think we know that much.
‐ At times like this, all
it takes is one good whack!
‐ [Milfeulle] Oh,
no, you broke it!
‐ [Ranpha] What were
you thinking, Forte?
‐ Well, I think that we want
to open these doors, don’t we?
(gasping)
‐ [Milfeulle] All
right, they’re opening.
‐ [Mint] Well, Forte is strong.
‐ Huh, this walkway is probably
going to break down next.
‐ At least we’d be
able to walk from here.
What’s up, Mint?
‐ I feel as though
somebody’s been watching us.
‐ What?
‐ What’s the matter?
‐ [Milfeulle] That
chandelier’s moving.
It looks a bit dangerous to me.
‐ You think it’s gonna fall?
No way!
(screaming)
Oh, look, it really
did come down.
‐ [Milfeulle] Oh no, we
could get electrocuted.
‐ I’m awfully sorry
about all this.
‐ [Ranpha] Hey,
it’s not your fault.
‐ Oh no, another one!
(screaming)
‐ Why is this happening?
‐ [Forte] Sir, maybe we
should go back to the offices.
‐ Yeah, this is dangerous.
‐ No, I’ve got to
make my inspections.
Hope, where are we going next?
‐ We will be heading
to the atmosphere plant
in 30 minutes, Mr. Kincaid.
‐ But sir, what if there’s
more trouble up ahead?
‐ I hired you precisely in
case something were to happen.
‐ Excuse me.
I’ve made us all some nice tea.
‐ [Hope] My, my.
‐ Hey, what do you
think we’re doing here?
‐ I’ve got orange pekoe
from Planet Monde,
and homemade cake
for you all to enjoy!
‐ I’ll try some.
Mm, delicious!
‐ My pleasure.
‐ Too much.
What’s this?
‐ [Ranpha] This
looks like trouble.
‐ Hey, there, robot.
That’s fantastic work
you’re doing over there.
‐ Look out.
‐ Argh, darn.
‐ Milfeulle, what are you doing?
‐ My tea set from Planet Guinea.
‐ Just get over here!
‐ It was expensive.
(screaming)
‐ Look out.
‐ [Ranpha] Why are
they coming after us?
Shouldn’t they be
going after Kincaid?
‐ Ranpha, I can barely keep up.
My feet are hurting right now.
‐ Just shut up and
don’t stop running.
‐ [Man] Target A
has entered Area 23.
Target B is headed
toward Area 18.
‐ [Allan] All right,
I’m going, too!
(panting)
‐ [Milfeulle] Maybe we can
escape by getting on that.
‐ [Ranpha] That sounds
like a good idea!
‐ Do you know how
to drive this thing?
‐ Oh, I think I can
probably figure it out.
(screaming)
‐ Hey, what’s happening?
We’re nothing but sitting
ducks in this thing.
Is there a weapon onboard?
‐ This looks like
it could be one.
‐ Give it to me!
(Ranpha groaning)
(screaming)
No, there’s a million of them.
‐ Look, a button, that’s it.
‐ The atmosphere
transformation plant.
‐ Oh, no, it’s Allan.
‐ Don’t you move!
‐ Look out, they’re
still after us.
‐ Don’t you think it’s
strange that the culprit
always seems to know exactly
where we’re going to go next?
‐ What are you getting at?
‐ Mr. Hope, aren’t you the
one who’s been managing
every aspect of Mr.
Kincaid’s schedule?
‐ Well, yes, of course.
(laughing)
‐ Hope has nothing
to do with this.
The culprit is up in that ship.
‐ [Girls] What?
‐ What is going on, here?
‐ Meet my grandson, Allan.
‐ The one in the picture?
‐ Actually, I was lying to you
when I said that someone
was threatening my life.
‐ Lied?
‐ I wanted to test you.
‐ Test us?
‐ That’s right.
To find the most suitable bride
I could for my Allan here.
‐ [Milfeulle] Suitable bride?
‐ There are many dangers
in this line of work.
We’ve been searching out
as many strong we women
like you as we can
to find Allan the best match.
‐ So, you’re gonna pick a bride
from among the five of us?
‐ Have you chosen
any other candidates
for this marriage to
Allan, besides us?
‐ Yes, about 500 have passed
the first phase of the test.
‐ Huh?
‐ So then, Allan,
what do you think
about the first
phase of the testing?
‐ Well, upon reviewing
the results of the test,
in terms of physical
and mental power,
I regret to say that one
of you did not qualify.
‐ Huh?
Just one didn’t make it?
‐ [Allan] As for the
ones who passed‐‐
‐ Now, just you wait a minute!
‐ Huh?
‐ We’ve all been listening
to you go on and on
about exactly what
it is that you want.
We have every bit as much
a choice in the matter
as you do, you know.
Now, I feel confident that I
have passed this first test.
But I’m sorry, I’m
turning you down.
‐ I believe I’ve passed as
well, but I’m passing on you.
‐ Excuse me.
‐ Well, I’m gonna go home now.
‐ That really pisses me off.
‐ Ranpha, you only
said that what you did
because you didn’t
want to find out
that you’d failed the test.
‐ And that goes for you, too.
(chuckling)
‐ How could you possibly
think that I failed?
‐ Or that I did.
(laughing)
‐ You know, Mint, I
can’t help but wonder
who it was that failed.
‐ Well, I guess
we’ll never know.
‐ Only God knows.
‐ Oh, who cares, anyway?
How about a race
back to the base?
The last one pays
for dinner, let’s go.
‐ That’s not fair, Ranpha.
‐ Here we go, Milfeulle,
hang on tight!
‐ Huh?
What?
Gee, I hope I’m not
the one that lost out.
You put the oil in after taking
the frying pan off the heat.
‐ [Ranpha] Milfeulle!
Get a grip, Milfeulle!
No, this can’t be.
Don’t die, don’t you die.
(soft playful music)
(singing in a foreign language)