‐ [Chef] Then we pour the
oil onto the hot frying pan.
‐ What?
You take the pan off the
heat and then put the oil in.
‐ Shut up!
Why do you even watch
these cooking shows anyway?
And who’s fault do you
think this whole thing is
in the first place, Milfeulle?
‐ Who’s fault?
‐ [Ranpha] Yours!
It’s your fault!
‐ Hmm.
(sirens blaring)
("Galaxy Bang!
Bang!" by Angel‐tai)
(singing in a foreign language)
‐ [Milfeulle] Pirate‐style
School Memory Terrine.
‐ [Duke Crizeman] Hello,
everyone, nice to meet you.
I’m Reiger Crizeman.
‐ Welcome, Marquis Crizeman.
And what do you need the
Angel Brigade to do for you?
A student ID card?
‐ Yes.
Normally something all
students must return
to the elementary school
when they graduate.
But I’d completely
forgotten about it,
and so I’ve been carrying
it with me all this time.
‐ And so, you would like
us to return this card
to the Memorial
Elementary School.
‐ Yes, that’s what I’d like.
‐ But why don’t you
just return it yourself?
‐ Hey, you know we
need the work, Ranpha.
So where is this whatchamacallit
elementary school anyway?
‐ In Area Enigma.
‐ [Forte] No!
‐ Hmm?
Don’t worry, I will
pay for everything.
‐ That’s not the problem.
‐ Is this Area, whatever,
a really dangerous place?
‐ It’s a pirate breeding ground.
‐ A breeding ground?
‐ I am very sorry about
this Marquis Crizeman,
but we can’t operate in
such a dangerous area.
‐ I see then.
Not having returned
my student card
has been nagging at
my soul all this time,
and at this rate I’m not sure
I can find the peace I need.
(Crizeman sobs)
(melancholy orchestral music)
‐ [Milfeulle] Marquis
Crizeman, don’t you worry.
‐ Hmm?
‐ We will do everything
in our in power
to make sure that your
student card is returned
to Memorial Elementary
School for you.
‐ Will you really?
Oh, I am so grateful.
(Milfeulle giggles)
‐ I’m not so sure about this.
We’re really vulnerable
to enemy fire.
(communicator buzzes)
(Ranpha gasps)
‐ I’ve got some
bad news for you.
Marquis Reiger Crizeman
has just passed away.
‐ He’s just died?
‐ Marquis Crizeman is dead?
‐ So, since our
client has passed away
the mission is invalidated,
and both of you
can return to base.
‐ Oh, right.
This is such a rough
place so let’s go home.
‐ But I want to keep going.
Besides Marquis Crizeman
he just seemed so sad.
‐ Then would you go alone?
‐ No, because you’re the only
one who can pilot this thing,
aren’t you?
‐ And, Ranpha, it was
you who suddenly decided
you wanted to go when
you say the tears
in Mr. Crizeman’s eyes.
‐ Yes, well, I suppose.
But I really think that.
Oh, darn I guess
we have to do this.
Let’s get it over with.
‐ [Milfeulle] Oh, maybe
we should go home.
‐ [Ranpha] You’re the one that
said you wanted to do this.
‐ But this is such a
scary and deserted place.
‐ So then, do you have any idea
where the school is located?
‐ I thought that you knew
where the school was, Ranpha.
‐ And why do you think I’m
the one who would know that?
♪ And reach into space ♪
‐ What could that be?
♪ Memorial ♪
♪ Elementary school ♪
‐ Wow, look, the school looks
like it’s going to collapse,
doesn’t it?
‐ Let’s be careful.
This place could very well be
a pirate hideout, you know?
‐ What?
‐ That school song,
it might be some kind of code
calling the pirates together.
‐ Oh, I’m not worried.
That song’s no code.
After all, that song
is what guided us here
to the school, isn’t it?
‐ But why?
‐ Well, precisely
because we were looking
for the school in
the first place.
‐ What kind of world exists
in that head of yours
anyway, Milfeulle?
And how would a school
building ever be able
to do something like that, huh?
Anyhow, we’ve come this
far so we might as well
go right in.
‐ Wait for me, Ranpha.
(footsteps echoing)
Is anyone here?
Wow, it’s even worse inside.
(wall crumbling)
(Milfeulle screams)
(lasers blasting)
(Milfeulle screaming)
(Ranpha shouts)
(staff thuds)
(Ranpha grunts)
(laser blasts)
‐ Oh, Ranpha.
(rocks cracking)
(Milfeulle screams)
(laser blasts)
Ranpha, help, help me!
Ranpha, help!
‐ I’ve got my hands full here.
You’ve gotta fend for yourself.
(laser blasts)
(Ranpha grunts)
(robot thuds)
‐ Well, what am I
gonna do, Ranpha?
I just don’t know
what to do. (screams)
‐ Milfeulle! (grunts)
(robot thuds)
Come on, now’s our chance
to get out of this place.
Let’s go.
‐ I’m so hurt I can’t move.
‐ Oh no!
You’ve hurt yourself?
Let’s have a look.
Oh come on!
It’s just a little scratch.
‐ But it hurts so much!
‐ Well, I’m sure you can run.
‐ But it hurts, I can’t run!
(dramatic music)
(girls scream)
There’s another one!
(Milfeulle screaming)
‐ See, Milfeulle, I told
you that you could run.
‐ Yeah, so I can. (giggles)
‐ Good god, you’re annoying.
Can’t you run faster?
(Milfeulle screaming)
Come on!
‐ [Milfeulle] That’s it, just
carry me and I’ll be fine.
(both screaming)
‐ Hang on, it’s okay.
(Ranpha grunts)
How much do you weigh anyway?
‐ That’s mean!
I’m not fat at all.
‐ Stop crying, you’re
driving me nuts!
(button beeps)
(energetic music)
‐ Oh no!
(Ranpha shouts)
(robot thuds)
(Ranpha grunts)
(energetic music)
‐ This is so exhausting.
‐ I thought I was going to die.
I think I might have
just lost some weight.
‐ Oh brother.
(rocks rumbling)
(upbeat music)
No!
‐ Another one! (screams)
(card clatters)
‐ Milfeulle!
No, Milfeulle!
Oh no!
Oh please!
This can’t be.
Don’t die, Milfeulle.
Please, don’t you die!
(robots rumbling)
(Ranpha sobbing)
‐ Yay!
Did you see that?
I got the enemy way
before anyone else did.
That means I win.
‐ Darn, and I lost.
‐ You’re kids?
‐ Aw, what a drag.
‐ Yeah, I was so
close to winning.
‐ But who are you guys?
And what’s this
all about anyway?
‐ [Kid] It’s a game.
‐ Game?
‐ People who come into
this school are targets.
‐ The one who gets the
intruder first wins.
‐ A game.
This is how you play?
‐ Yeah, and that was
an excellent one.
‐ Let’s do it again.
‐ Cut it out!
Don’t you know that
there are things
you should and shouldn’t do
even when all you’re
doing is playing around?
How could you kill
somebody in cold blood
and call it a game?
‐ [Kid] But that’s
just a paint pellet.
‐ Paint pellet?
It’s true.
‐ Milfeulle, what are
you trying to do to me?
‐ But, Ranpha, I truly believed
that I was actually dead.
Look over there.
Those kids have no shadows.
You can see right
through their legs.
‐ [Ranpha] What?
‐ Are you kids, are you?
Mr. Crizeman’s ID card,
it’s disappearing.
(both gasp)
Mr. Crizeman!
‐ Hello, I sure
kept you waiting.
(light music)
‐ Reiger, welcome back.
What took you?
‐ I’m home.
Now can we play together?
Thanks a lot, girls.
Goodbye now.
(light music)
(cards clatter)
‐ Do you think that those
kids could have been?
(ship whooshing)
‐ Ghosts?
‐ Yes, ghosts of the children.
‐ I’m sure that it was
just a hallucination.
And you and Ranpha both
saw the same thing?
‐ Well, maybe we did.
‐ Ranpha, I’m sure that
what we saw was real.
‐ [Ranpha] Mission
accomplished, returning to base.
‐ All right then.
‐ Ranpha!
But why?
‐ Just leave it.
Marquis Crizeman’s student
card was successfully returned
to his old school, wasn’t it?
Our mission’s complete.
‐ I guess so.
I guess you’re right.
I’m sure the spirits of
those kids are still playing
at their old school.
(children laughing)
‐ [Milfeulle] Look,
Forte, isn’t he cute?
‐ [Forte] What’s
so cute about him?
‐ [Milfeulle] You
wanna hold him, Forte?
It’s really no
problem, you know?
See, here.
‐ [Forte] I said I’ll pass.
‐ [Milfeulle] Forte,
what’s the matter with you?
You’re sweating
buckets right now.
(Milfeulle screams)
("Horoscope Rhapsody"
by Angel‐tai)
(singing in foreign language)