(screaming)
(panting)
‐ They’re coming this way!
Oh, this isn’t good.
I just can’t have them
all see me like this.
(traditional Japanese music)
(engine whirring)
(siren blaring)
(machine engine revving)
("Galaxy Bang! Bang!
Theme Song" by Team Angel)
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Bang bang ♪
‐ [Milfeulle] Bored girl’s
special secret fried roll.
(grunting)
(sighing)
‐ I can get out of this.
(grunting)
Thousands of people have
placed their heads here,
but here I am, stuck, and
completely embarrassed.
(screaming)
What could those two
be doing, racing so furiously
to get back to this platform?
My time’s out already?
That was too short!
Three coins left, I’ve
got to do something soon.
(beeping)
‐ Yeah, what?
‐ [Mint] Forte, what
are you doing right now?
‐ I’m trying to get
to higher ground!
‐ But why, what’s
happening down there?
Have you found out anything
about the lost technology?
‐ That’s not
important right now!
The island is sinking because
of an incredible tide!
(gasping)
Our Emblem Frame sank too,
what’s with this island anyway?
(bell chiming)
‐ So that’s why
they’re coming here.
They’re desperately trying to
get to this observation deck.
‐ [Mint Voiceover]
I’ve got a choice.
I can choose either Plan A,
lead them all to safety here
on higher ground and save them.
(laughing)
‐ [Forte] Mint, come on,
you’ve gotta be kidding.
‐ [Ranpha] This
is just too funny!
‐ [Milfeulle] It’s funny,
but it’s also cute,
so it’s like cute and funny!
(groaning)
‐ [Mint Voiceover] Or
Plan B, I prevent anyone
from getting onto the
observation platform.
(screaming)
‐ [Ranpha] I don’t wanna
die here like this,
save me, help me, get me out!
‐ This seawater is too salty!
‐ [Mint Voiceover] I have
only one choice, Plan B.
I have to do all I can to
stop them from reaching me!
(beeping)
‐ [Mint] Forte, could
you hold on for a minute?
‐ What for?
‐ [Mint] Are you sure we should
just abandon our research
into the lost technology?
‐ What, now is not the time
to be thinking about work!
‐ But that might create
a problem, Forte.
Especially in your case.
‐ [Forte] What do you mean?
‐ Remember how you
charged all that Oden
to your expense account?
‐ [Mint] You could
pay for it easily
with that salary that
you get, don’t you think?
(gasping)
If you can’t show that
you’re responsible,
you could end up losing
your whole bonus.
What do you think?
(sighing)
‐ [Forte] All right, I’ll
continue investigating.
‐ [Mint] Ranpha,
hang on a minute.
‐ Why, you know, I’m
kind of busy right now.
‐ [Mint] There’s some
birds stranded in a tree
on the other side
of that hill there.
If you don’t save them.
‐ Are you insane, if I do that,
we’re all gonna drown here.
‐ But I’ve heard that the
feathers of the birds here
are the most powerful
good luck charms anywhere.
‐ Are they really that strong?
‐ [Mint] Yes, they’ll bring
you incredible luck in love.
‐ No way, where are they?
Hey, get back here!
‐ I’m so impressed, Vanilla!
‐ You won’t beat me to them!
(grunting)
My lucky feathers for love!
(laughing)
‐ Just dangle a carrot
in front of a donkey,
and it’ll go wherever
you want, won’t it?
(gasping)
‐ I have some
cutlets on a stick.
‐ Not now, thank you,
but while you’re here,
would you happen to
have change for 1000?
(birds cawing)
‐ What’s the matter, don’t
you like cutlets on a stick?
(screaming)
(gasping)
‐ What’s happening?
‐ The water’s getting higher!
(screaming)
‐ Retreat, retreat!
‐ [Forte] There’s nothing
more important right now
than saving ourselves!
‐ People will change
their behavior
when confronted with
immediate danger.
A change of plan, then.
(rhythmic beeping)
(intense music)
‐ Ranpha, this is Mint
here, you got a minute?
‐ No, forget the lucky charms,
I’m trying to save my life!
‐ [Mint] No, that’s not it.
I want to tell you
the shortest route
to the observation deck.
(grunting)
‐ Just turn right
at the next fork
in the path you’re currently on.
There, you’ll see a
statue of a dancer.
‐ A statue of a dancer?
(gasping)
There!
‐ [Mint] Hurry, or the
tide will sweep you away!
(yelling)
Come quickly, I’m right up
here on the observation deck!
‐ I’m on my way!
‐ Forte.
‐ [Forte] Yeah?
‐ Do you see a big
bench of camellias?
‐ Yeah?
‐ [Mint] If you turn
right at that garden,
you’ll find the shortest
route to the platform.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ [Mint] Hurry up!
‐ Right, thanks.
(rhythmic beeping)
‐ Now then,
listen to me closely.
There’s a door at the
top of those stairs.
You’ll have to use
all of your strength
to open that door.
Then you’ll be able to make
it the rest of the way.
‐ All right!
‐ I’ll be at the
observation deck.
And move as fast as you can!
(beeping)
(ominous music)
And now it’s all set up.
(change rattling)
(birds cawing)
(screaming)
(panting)
(grunting)
‐ It won’t open, why?
Why won’t it open?
(grunting)
‐ What is wrong with this door?
(laughing)
‐ Aren’t they all so
incredibly obedient?
And now.
(beeping)
Hey, watch out, the tide
is closing in on you!
‐ What?
‐ No!
(screaming)
‐ Oh my god!
(camera snapping)
(beeping)
‐ So farewell then, my
friends of the Angel Brigade.
(laughing)
‐ [Forte And Ranpha]
We can’t die here!
(yelling)
(grunting)
‐ What’s going on down there?
(gasping)
Lady, I need change, change!
Please, can you give
me some change, lady?
‐ Hm?
(traditional Japanese music)
‐ Huh?
Huh?
(scoffing)
What’s this now?
(furious grunting)
(upbeat music)
(splashing)
‐ It’s just a hop, skip,
and a jump to the deck.
We’re almost there, Mint!
‐ Hey, Ranpha, you’re
looking good over there.
‐ Wow, look over
there, little bird!
‐ Thank goodness she
showed us the shortcut!
‐ It’s so cute!
‐ No kidding, we owe
our lives to that girl.
‐ Those birds are so sweet!
‐ [Forte] Thank you, Mint!
‐ [Mint Voiceover] Oh, what
incredible survival instincts.
Now it’s only a matter of
time before they see me.
‐ What’s that?
That’s pretty strange.
(gasping)
Hold it, lady!
(traditional Japanese music)
‐ But how did you know?
‐ I didn’t say anything.
(yelling)
So you’ve been the one
behind this all along.
This tide is not
rising naturally,
there’s another reason for it.
The water level is
not getting higher,
what’s happening is that
the island is sinking.
It wasn’t until I saw
those birds stranded
in their nest that I
figured everything out.
There’s no way birds
would build their nest
that close to where
the tide comes in.
(ominous music)
Now I realize that all
this has just been a ploy
to keep us from figuring out
that you’re hiding something.
‐ Why, you!
(yelling)
(glass shattering)
Why, you.
(screaming)
(grunting)
‐ Huh?
(gasping)
It’s come off!
So this remote control
belongs to you?
(beeping)
(rumbling)
‐ Now what?
(birds chirping)
(machine whirring)
(comical music)
‐ [Forte] Who would
have guessed there was
an illegal weapons
factory down there?
‐ That was pretty good
thinking there, Mint.
‐ That’s for sure, you really
stole the show this time.
(laughing)
‐ [Milfeulle] Hey, look!
‐ Huh?
‐ You know, I haven’t seen one
of these dress‐up
props in years!
I’m gonna try it out!
(laughing)
‐ Oh now, come on, Milfeulle.
Don’t be so silly,
all that stuff
is just for kids.
‐ Yeah, that’s for sure.
‐ Hey, look at me!
‐ [Forte] I’ll take a
picture of you, say cheese!
(giggling)
‐ Be careful, it’s easier
than you might think
to get stuck in that.
‐ [Forte] Yeah right,
how’s that gonna happen?
(laughing)
‐ [Milfeulle] This is great fun!
(Milfeulle laughing)
(Milfeulle grunting)
I can’t get out, what do I do?
‐ [Mint] I warned you.
‐ [Ranpha] What are
you going to do?
‐ [Mint] You might be
able to free yourself
by falling on top of someone.
‐ [Forte] Oh, come on.
(Forte laughing)
‐ [Milfeulle] I’m
really stuck, help me!
Hey, where are you
going, don’t leave me!
(Milfeulle grunting)
(crashing)
(Milfeulle laughing)
Hey, I’m free!
‐ [Vanilla] My futon flew away.
‐ [Milfeulle] What’s
the matter, Vanilla?
‐ [Vanilla] I love sukiyaki.
‐ [Milfeulle] Uh, are you okay?
‐ [Vanilla] The
cat took a catnap.
‐ [Milfeulle] Are you
sure you’re all right?
‐ [Vanilla] Ladybug like right.
(Milfeulle laughing)
("Holoscope Rhapsody"
by Team Angel)
(singing in foreign language)
♪ No no ♪