‐ [Forte] Normad!
(Forte growling)
‐ Forte, relax!
‐ Why you little!
‐ You gotta settle down!
Come on!
‐ I dare you to say
that again.
‐ [Normad] You just love
to fly off the handle.
‐ [Forte] I’m gonna...
‐ Hey, what’s the matter?!
Why is everybody fighting?
Aren’t you happy with
the recreation I planned?
It’s really a lot of
fun, the talking dice!
‐ [Forte] That’s
not the problem!
Normad said there’s no
way there’d be any talk
of love in my life,
the little jerk!
‐ [Normad] That’s
not true, I said‐‐
‐ Yes, I understand‐‐
‐ I said there’s no talk
for love in your life.
‐ That’s right.
Could you tell me what‐‐
‐ The nerve!
‐ Type of object it is?
Mm, sorry, could you
say that one more time?
‐ You don’t know anything!
It’s not like I was
the least popular girl
in school, you know!
(Forte growling)
‐ Whatever you say.
‐ Everyone, an
unidentified flying object
has been spotted
in the Law Sector.
Deploy immediately!
‐ What, that’s too bad!
’Cause I was just
gonna straighten out
the irritating know‐it‐all
about my love life.
But, work is work, I guess,
so, we better get going.
‐ [Normad] You’ve
never had a love life.
‐ [Forte] And you have?
(coughs) What are
we looking for?
‐ It’s kind of strange,
we’re looking for dice.
‐ Huh?
(engines roaring)
(alarm blares)
("Galaxy Bang!
Bang!" by Angel‐tai)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Milefeulle] Tear‐flavored
Missile Rice Bowl.
‐ It really is a dice.
Alright, fire!
(zapping)
(beeping)
(computer blares)
(dramatic music)
(Forte grunts)
(zapping)
(Ranpha and Milfeulle gasp)
(hands clap)
(computer beeps)
(Mint gulps)
(Mint gasps)
‐ Huh?
(Milfeulle gasps and yells)
(Vanilla and Normad grunt)
(crash)
(electricity zapping)
‐ We didn’t even
put a dent in it.
How’s Vanilla doing?
‐ [Mint] She’s stable
now, miraculously,
she got away with
minor injuries.
‐ [Forte] I see.
‐ Is the object still
on the same track?
‐ [Mint] It looks that way.
It’s coming toward us.
(computer beeping)
‐ I wish we could do
something, but I have no ideas.
All we can do is wait
and hope for the best.
‐ Wrong!
‐ Huh?
‐ There is a way to
defeat the Q‐Cube.
‐ [All] What?!
‐ How exactly?
‐ Oh!
‐ Wait a minute!
Hey, Normad, how do you know
that thing’s name anyway?!
‐ That thing is a Q‐Cube,
I guess you don’t
remember too well, do you?
‐ You knew that
and said nothing?!
‐ [Normad] One thing I knew
was you’d pull that gun again.
‐ Oh.
‐ That’s 2,071 times now.
(Normad laughs)
(Forte grunts)
It’s about time you knew
what I’m about to tell you.
Q‐Cubes have been roaming
the universe for ages
with one ultimate purpose.
You could say they’re the human
species’ ultimate nemesis.
Long before mankind
came into existence,
the Q‐Cubes anticipated
your civilization
reaching outer space,
and they became
determined to destroy it.
All I can pick up from it
is its complete
hatred of humanity.
You guys don’t realize
that you’re just not
welcome in space.
It’s an indication that
the will of the cosmos
is to exist without you.
The weapon designed to
destroy the Q‐Cube was made,
a T2R2000 missile.
My artificial intelligence
will not register
with the Q‐Cube as human.
Therefore, I can get close to it
without being noticed
and attack it.
So, you must return
me to my missile.
There’s no other
way to deal with it.
(laughs) What’s the matter?
‐ But what’s gonna
happen to you then?
‐ Oh, that’s not a big deal.
You’ll just be firing
me off with my missile.
Standard procedure, that’s all!
‐ [Forte] I don’t like it.
‐ Forte.
(Forte growls)
‐ What is the matter with
the people who built you?!
They made you able to talk to us
and understand our feelings,
but then, when the time comes,
you can become
completely emotionless
and just go out and
blow yourself up?!
It’s awful!
I don’t care what anyone thinks!
There’s no way I’ll‐‐
‐ You humans aren’t
very smart, are you?
‐ What?
‐ This is the only way
you’re gonna save your lives
and it’s quick and easy.
Why would you even think
of trying to stop me?
Don’t you people
wanna save yourselves?
Your foolishness is
really hard to understand.
(Milfeulle cries)
(melancholy music)
You will return me to
my missile, won’t you?
What is everyone so sad about?
Things will just return to
the way they were before.
I’m simply going to take
care of the problem,
so, you can all sit
back and take it easy.
There’s no relying
on the abilities
of low‐intelligent
life forms like you.
Just watch me deal with
this once and for all.
(computer beeping and blaring)
‐ The missile has been launched.
Trajectory is good,
it will make contact
with the target in five
minutes and 46 seconds.
(Mint sighs)
(Ranpha sighs)
(doors whirring)
‐ Oh, Vanilla.
(Ranpha gasps)
(gunshots banging)
(gun clicking)
(computer beeping)
(lens whirring)
(bells chime)
‐ The target’s been hit.
(Ranpha gasps)
It’s been completely destroyed.
(door whirring)
‐ Is it over yet?
‐ Yes, we were successful.
The Q‐Cube has been destroyed.
‐ We were successful, you say?
Our friend, Normad,
has been sacrificed
and you call that a success?
‐ It’s a success to
preserve and protect
what is most important, to the
point of giving up his life.
Well, Normad was
originally designed
to fulfill that very
mission, wasn’t he?
After all, he was just
a T2R2000 missile.
‐ Oh, Forte.
‐ Weren’t you, Normad?
Weren’t you?
‐ [Normad] What
sentimental bullshit.
‐ (all gasp and scream)
‐ Who was that?
‐ No, that couldn’t
possibly have been him!
‐ You heard me.
(Ranpha and Forte scream)
I said, what
sentimental bullshit.
‐ Wait a second, how
could you still be alive?!
‐ Huh?
‐ Didn’t you blow yourself up
along with the missile?!
‐ [Ranpha] How did
you get back here?!
‐ [Normad] What, didn’t
Colonel Volcott tell you?
‐ Oh, but I, I thought
I told you. (laughs)
I just made a copy of
the piloting system
and installed that
in the missile.
Then, I re‐installed
Normad back into his body.
I thought everybody
knew. (laughs)
Come on, didn’t I tell you all?
Well, I meant to tell you.
Didn’t you, let’s see...
‐ Think, if all you have to
do is navigate the missile
to its target, there’s
really no reason
why I should have to
go along for the ride.
It can be controlled
remotely with a program.
‐ Remote control?
‐ Well, it was quite
tricky, actually.
I’ve never piloted anything
by remote control before.
And since there’s so much
digital information focused
on that task, there’s nothing
left for my speech circuit.
I’m not used to being
speechless, you know.
When I think about it, it
might have been much easier
for me to out in a blaze
of glory with my missile.
Hmm, what’s the matter?
Why are you all staring
at me like that?
‐ You’re contemptible!
You don’t care about
all the grieving
we did for you, do you?!
‐ To tell you the truth,
all that noise you were making
only made it harder
to concentrate.
I wanted to say something,
but if I told you, I‐‐
(gunshots explode)
Why are you so angry?
I keep you telling you
that it’s not a big deal!
‐ Just shut up and you can
stop sucking up to us now!
‐ Normad, more Q‐Cubes are
heading in our direction.
‐ [Forte And Ranpha] What?!
‐ [Volcott] This time,
there’s 16 of them!
‐ [All] Oh no!
‐ You sure look worried.
They don’t have a chance
against a machine like me.
‐ They don’t?
‐ Copy more programs
into some missiles
and let ’em have it.
‐ Right.
(doorbell rings)
(missiles whistle)
‐ You can tell how much
they hate humanity.
They haven’t changed
a bit over the ages.
These Q‐Cubes can
show up anywhere.
They’re such pests.
(Forte and Ranpha quiver)
I knew it was the
time of the year when
we’d see more of them.
‐ [Forte] Like insects?
‐ [Volcott] I finished
copying the data.
‐ [Normad] Thank you, can
you make a dozen more?
‐ [Volcott] Certainly.
‐ [Forte and Ranpha]
A dozen more?!
‐ Well, thank goodness our
Normad is safe and sound!
‐ Yeah, right!
What’s with this stupid story?!
(Milfeulle laughs)
‐ [Milfeulle] A stupid story.
‐ [Ranpha] What’s the
matter, all of a sudden?
‐ [Mint] Something’s
wrong with me?
‐ [Forte] Do you have a fever?
‐ Yes!
‐ Did you eat something
at lunch?
‐ I did!
‐ Does it hurt anywhere?
‐ Yes, it hurts!
‐ [Ranpha] I see you
overdid yourself.
‐ It’s not good.
‐ I can do it.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ Uh‐huh!
("Horoscope Rhapsody")
(singing in foreign language)