(sirens blaring)
(upbeat music)
‐ [Girl] Five
Sukiyaki Lunch Boxes.
‐ [Girl Voiceover] As
far as missions go,
this one was turning
out to be pretty easy.
All we had to do was get a
certain man to a specific place
and that was just about
all there was to it.
‐ Do you have business
in Kalua City?
‐ Begin by very gently
mixing the eggs together
and then add salt and pepper.
Place some butter into a
well heated frying pan.
Pour in the eggs
and stir quickly.
Use the whisk briskly
and rhythmically,
bu be sure not to
overdo it or the
eggs will lose their form.
‐ Oh I see!
‐ You’re talking about
how to make an omelet.
‐ When the eggs
start to get firm,
draw them to one
side of the pan.
‐ So tell me, are you a
chef or something Johnny?
‐ The main thing is to
achieve the right texture.
(girl breathing heavily)
‐ Why do they need
all five of us
for such a simple mission?
‐ You knew all about this,
so why didn’t you
just turn it down?
‐ What?
Why not?
That’s because I was the one who
first heard about this mission
from the colonel, that’s why.
How come you didn’t
decide to turn it down?
‐ I don’t think this mission
is quite what it seems.
I think there’s something
more important going on.
‐ Okay.
So if that’s the case,
this Johnny is
probably a lot more
important than we think he is.
‐ If they only needed a driver,
they wouldn’t have brought
in the whole Angle Brigade.
‐ I’ll bet he’s rich,
so rich that he’s
employed the Angel Brigade
because he needs
the extra security
and he’s probably
traveling incognito.
‐ So you think a rich guy
would travel by truck?
‐ Traveling in secret.
Keeping it low pro.
(alarm beeps)
Good.
Time to switch drivers.
‐ [Girl] Rock, paper.
‐ [Girls] Scissors.
‐ [Girl] Rock, paper, scissors.
‐ So then, Johnny, I’d be
interested to know what line of
work you’re involved in.
Johnny?
‐ Well my good little children,
the chicken man is here.
‐ Excuse me?
(man laughs)
‐ Now, now, you
mustn’t pull on the
chicken man’s head like that.
‐ Pull on the
chicken man’s head?
Are you possibly
referring to a costume?
‐ Now, now.
You should never
stick your fingers
into his beak like that.
‐ Wow.
That’s really exciting.
‐ Johnny might look alright,
but if he’s into young girls,
(girl growls)
that would be a problem.
‐ [Girl] How would
that be a problem?
‐ Hey, did Johnny
say anything to you?
What he does for work?
Whether he’s married?
You know, that sort
of thing Milfeulle.
‐ Johnny works as a
professional chef.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ I’m positive.
(girl growls)
‐ Your brain only works when
it comes to food and cooking
so I can’t be sure
of your take on him.
‐ [Milfeulle Voiceover]
But it’s true.
‐ Okay, rock, paper, scissors!
(girl growling)
(girl yells)
‐ I’m sorry if I’m mistaken,
but aren’t you a sniper?
(girl chuckles)
I guess a real pro would
never readily admit to that.
‐ That’s a good observation.
(girl gasps)
‐ Now tell me exactly
what you two talked about.
‐ Listen.
It was really no big deal.
‐ If there was no big deal,
then I wanna hear about
everything he said!
‐ Like dressing up as a chicken?
‐ What did you just say?
‐ Yes.
That was it.
Seriously.
(girl chuckles)
‐ Look at you making like you’re
just some kind of
innocent little girl,
but you’re not
fooling me one bit.
I happen to know very well how
cunning and sneaky you
can be Mint Blancmanche.
I want to know everything
you talked about with Johnny.
‐ You know, one of
your biggest weaknesses
is that you lose your
sense of judgment
when a man you like
enters the picture.
Perhaps you just have a
weakness for men Ranpha.
‐ [Ranpha] Why you!
‐ Honestly.
‐ [Girl] Hey!
Anyone for tea?
‐ [Mint] I’d love some.
‐ [Ranpha] What are
you going to do?
‐ I don’t know yet.
‐ Oh come on.
What do you mean you don’t know?
I’m sure you must be
thinking of something by now.
‐ No, nothing.
‐ Are you leaving
it all up to God?
Alright, rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, scissors!
Paper!
(girl growling)
‐ Sorry I’m not more talkative.
I’m a pilgrim observing silence.
‐ May God protect us.
(girl yelling)
‐ Now with all this rain,
it’s getting impossibly
muggy in here!
‐ Stop it.
You’ll just steam it up more.
And you absolutely
stink of perfume too.
You’re making me feel
sick so just sit still.
‐ Well at least it’s better than
smelling like gun powder.
How dare you take that attitude
just because you’re a
little older than me.
Who do you think you are?
(girl growls)
(girls gasping)
Look, I was just telling
you how I feel, alright.
And now you wanna shoot me?
‐ Yeah you bet you
face painted tramp.
‐ You know, you’re always
resorting to violence.
You big, crazy,
gun toting bully.
(alarm beeps)
‐ Yay!
It’s time to switch!
Now it’s my turn!
Yoohoo!
Johnny.
If you don’t mind,
I’d be very
interested in knowing
the purpose of your trip.
‐ Oh sure.
Business.
I’m spending 80 billion GC’s to
convert the atmosphere on an
inhabitable planet nearby.
‐ That’s amazing!
You’re starting
life on a planet?
‐ While I’m there,
I’ll be getting quotes on
interplanetary spaceships.
Of course, they’re very big.
‐ That’s great.
It’s just as I
thought all along.
You really are a rich man.
‐ [Robot] Johnny’s a
professional character actor
in theater productions?
‐ Yes.
Apparently whenever Johnny
gets into any vehicle,
he just falls to sleep and
nothing will wake him up.
Then while he’s sleeping,
he recites his lines.
‐ [Robot] Well it seems you
move in many different circles.
(man chuckles)
‐ [Man] Yes.
‐ [Robot] This play he’s
in now, what’s it about?
‐ [Man] It’s about
a man who wears a
chicken suit for a living, but
wants to become a master chef
and ends up becoming
an apprentice
to a sniper when he
discovers a long lost
twin brother who’s
a wealthy tycoon.
It’s a heartwarming
success story.
‐ [Robot] Sounds horrible.
‐ Johnny, what do you find
attractive in a woman?
(screaming)
(groaning)
‐ I slept well.
For me, nothing at all
beats sleeping in a truck.
‐ Hey you!
I hope you’re feeling guilty!
Hear me?
‐ Well yeah, it was my mistake.
‐ It’s all about correct
timing with the butter.
Making omelets can be
very tricky, you know?
(girl giggles)
‐ Is that right?
Wow, you sure do know a
lot about good cuisine.
‐ [Girl Voiceover] After that,
we continued on
safely with Johnny
until we got to Kalua City.
Even with the problems
we had, in the end,
this mission turned
out to be pretty easy.
‐ [Girl] All of our missions
have been completed.
‐ [Girl] There you have it.
‐ [Girl] Thank you everyone.
‐ [Girl] I guess
everything worked out then.
‐ [Girl] How about we
all go to Sealth Island.
‐ [Man] Sorry folks.
There’s a job that’s
just come up suddenly.
Do you think you can
take this one on?
‐ [Girls] What?
(upbeat music)