(thrusters activating,
alarm blaring)
‐ [Narrator] Grilled
girl in a box.
(yawns)
‐ When you’re out on
a week‐long mission
the thing you really
start to miss the most
is the comfort of your own bed.
Huh, Ranpha?
‐ Thank you for all the
hard work you’ve been doing.
Ranpha Franboise
here to welcome home
my good friend, Forte Stollen.
‐ "Welcome home,
my good friend?"
That’s a bit unusual.
‐ Actually, I’ve
really been wanting
to see you for a
while now, Forte!
‐ Hm?
‐ I have!
(Ranpha laughs)
‐ [Waitress] Here you go.
Enjoy your coffee!
‐ Do you take sugar, Forte?
‐ No.
‐ Milk?
‐ Doesn’t this smell great?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Will you drop dead?
‐ What did you say?!
‐ I’m so sorry.
‐ [Forte] You want
me to drop dead?!
‐ [Ranpha] Relax, there
is a reason for all this.
‐ Yeah, well it
better be really good.
‐ [Forte] Who is this guy?
‐ Roddy Leifman, that’s his
name, you would like him.
I decided that I’d really
like to go out with him,
he’s such a dream!
‐ Ohh.
‐ We’ve liked each
other for a while now,
and after giving him
the hint the other day,
he finally asked me out.
But, I slept in and
missed our date.
‐ This is why you want me dead?
‐ I didn’t have an excuse
for not showing up,
so I just made up
the story that...
‐ What?!
You told him that I died?!
‐ Well it seemed easier than
saying it was a family member!
Oh, I just don’t want
Roddy to dislike me,
I’m serious about him.
‐ Okay okay, maybe I’ll go
along with you just this time,
but what’s the point of fooling
the rest of the Angel
Brigade about this?
‐ Well you know, the
funny thing about it is,
Roddy’s family has a
long‐standing relationship with
the military, and this
information somehow got back
to the Angel Brigade.
You know, these rumors
have a life of their own.
Forte, please, I beg you!
Will you play along
and be dead for me?
‐ You’re being
completely ridiculous,
why should I have to play dead
for this stupid reason
you’re giving me?
Now you go back and tell
everyone the real truth!
And that settles that, alright?
‐ Have you ever wanted a
Brander Bass flintlock pistol?
(Forte gasps excitedly)
‐ Is it real?
‐ [Ranpha] How do
you feel, Forte?
‐ I’m not sure, really.
‐ You know, there have been
a few of my clients lately
who’ve faked their
deaths in order
to start lives over again.
‐ That’s definitely not
what I’m trying to do‐‐
‐ I know, relax, you’ll be fine.
‐ But this undertaker
doesn’t seem to understand.
‐ No, I do understand.
After all, I’m a professional.
‐ You really understand?
‐ It’ll be a great funeral.
‐ [Undertaker, echoing]
It’ll be a great funeral...
funeral... funeral...
‐ Forte!
Oh, Forte!
‐ Milfeulle.
‐ I never thought
Forte would go so soon.
‐ I still can’t believe it.
‐ I always thought that even
if all humanity became extinct,
Forte would still be around.
‐ [Ranpha] By the
way, where’s Vanilla?
‐ [Normad] She’s in prayer
for Forte right now.
She said it was a ceremony
to resurrect life.
Vanilla is such a kind person.
‐ [Man] Ranpha!
‐ [Ranpha] Roddy!
‐ I just don’t know what to say.
‐ I’m sorry that I
broke my promise to you.
‐ What in the world
are you saying?
Look at what you’re
dealing with here.
I was told that she died
while saving a child.
‐ That’s right, without
even thinking twice
she jumped right in front
of a car to save a child
that was about to be hit.
She held that child
until the very end.
She was smiling
even as her life was
slipping away asking the
child, "Are you alright?"
Those were Forte’s last words.
‐ [Forte Voiceover]
She’s overdoing it.
‐ What self‐sacrifice.
I’d say she’s
practically a saint.
‐ Forte was always so
kind to us as well.
‐ [Normad] There were
times she was, I guess.
‐ She watched over us.
‐ We’ve lost someone
so very important.
‐ [Forte Voiceover] Hey, it
feels kinda nice to be dead.
‐ Ranpha, I’d be honored
to participate in
the funeral service if I may.
When is her cremation?
‐ Cremation‐‐ Ow!
‐ Huh?
Maybe it’s wishful thinking,
but did you hear Forte?
‐ Yes, we will
have the cremation
after a simple funeral tomorrow.
‐ I understand, I’ll
join you tomorrow then.
‐ How kind and generous of you.
‐ [Forte Voiceover] Hey,
hey, hang on a minute!
‐ [Undetaker] That
was good work.
‐ Are you out of your mind?!
Cremation?!
‐ Well it just
came out that way!
‐ I can’t play dead very well
if I’ve been cremated, can I?!
‐ You don’t have a
thing to worry about.
This casket is specially
designed to withstand
temperatures in excess of
1,000 degrees centigrade.
‐ And you’re positive
it won’t fail?!
‐ It’s certified to comply with
Space Funeral
Association standards,
but in the case of an emergency,
there is always
this button here.
‐ I see, so by
pressing that button,
you could escape
from the casket.
‐ No, it releases cyanide
allowing for a painless death.
‐ Then maybe you’d like
to test it out for us!
‐ Quick, someone’s coming!
‐ Hello, I baked
Forte’s favorite pie,
the unsweetened kind.
What’re you doing?
‐ Well, we’re...
‐ Yes, we’re just testing
the casket’s durability.
‐ [Reporter] Mister Leifman.
A comment please
about the present
low morale in the military?
‐ "Low morale in the military?"
Haven’t you heard
about the accident
involving the Angel
Brigade member?
‐ I’m getting lonely.
I don’t think one classic gun
is enough to make up for this.
‐ One lousy gun‐‐
‐ [Ranpha] Doesn’t fire.
‐ [Forte] Come in.
‐ Listen, about this cremation,
we’ve changed it to a
burial out of respect
for your family’s
long‐held tradition.
‐ And you call that
an improvement?
‐ There’s one more thing.
‐ [Forte] What?
‐ Your funeral tomorrow will
be sponsored by the military.
‐ Huh?
‐ Countless people everywhere
have been deeply touched by
the story of Forte Stollen,
the courageous Angel Brigade
trooper who sacrificed herself
while saving the
life of a child.
The military commander
has also announced
that she’ll be awarded the
Medal of Honor, posthumously.
‐ Did he say the commander?!
I think this is getting
way out of hand!
‐ It seems that Roddy has taken
the liberty of speaking
to the reporters.
Oh, what a silly
troublemaker, that Roddy.
‐ And what am I supposed to do?!
As far as the world is
concerned, I’m completely dead!
‐ Don’t you worry!
Just leave all this to me.
I’m switching from
the fake funeral plan
to the complete
self‐vanishing plan!
‐ Complete self‐vanishing plan?
‐ You’ll be able to live
out the rest of your life
on an uninhabited planet
and no‐one will ever know.
‐ These are gifts for Forte,
from several of
the local citizens.
They’re all guns she liked.
‐ Guns?!
[Forte Voiceover] Oh no,
I’ve gotta stay calm.
‐ Everyone has been so moved
by Forte’s act of bravery.
There’ll be a lot more gifts.
‐ [Forte Voiceover] More gifts?!
‐ [Mint] I’m sure
Forte is happy.
After all, she’s
a space hero now.
‐ [Forte Voiceover] Space hero!
‐ Er...
‐ Mhm?
‐ I’m really sorry,
it’s not fair
that I’ve caused all of
this trouble for you.
‐ "Dear Miss Forte, I
am sending you my gun,
please use it in Heaven."
Having come this far,
it almost feels like
I could just go ahead
and die now anyway.
I never thought
I’d be so missed.
Even if this is all fake.
‐ Forte...
‐ You could come visit
me on my barren planet.
‐ Forte, I’ll go with you too!
‐ Huh?
‐ Well this is all
my fault, really.
There’s no way I can just
leave you by
yourself after this.
‐ Now stop that!
Watch it!
Whoa!
‐ Hm...
This is good for the
military’s image.
(officer whispering)
What?!
(bell ringing)
‐ What’s this?
What’s happening to us?
‐ Where are we?
‐ [Normad] What the?!
She’s really come back to life!
Vanilla, you’re incredible!
But why is Ranpha here?
‐ Is this where the funeral is?
‐ [Normad] Hm, oh,
right, Forte’s funeral!
Well, some military
big shot passed away
so your funerals got switched!
Mint and Milfeulle were sent
to take part those ceremonies,
and our kind‐hearted Vanilla
has been persistently
carrying out the
resurrection ritual,
and fervently praying
on your behalf.
‐ Oh Lord...
‐ Okay, so tell
me, what’s the deal
with this crummy graveyard then?
‐ Well, because the commander
was a high‐ranking official,
he took precedence and most of
the budget went to cover
his funeral expenses,
and your insurance policy
doesn’t pay for your funeral.
(gusts of wind blowing)
They say the value
of the person’s life
becomes apparent when they die.
I guess this is what
your life was worth!
‐ Normad, you...!
(Normad laughs)
‐ Moving right along.
‐ Now look you!
I’m gonna live for 100 years,
or maybe even 1,000
years or more!
Do you hear me?!
(Ranpha gasps)
‐ [Milfeulle] Here’s a question,
what do you think will
happen to the Angel Brigade?
One, new members will be added,
and there’ll be 10 of us.
Two, a sister
organization called
the Cupid Brigade
will be formed.
Three, a new sub‐group
will be created.
‐ [Ranpha] One.
‐ [Milfeulle] Sorry, The
correct answer is number four!
‐ [Ranpha] No?
‐ [Milfeulle] No!