♪ Oh, we’re the
Happening Carwash Boys ♪
♪ We’ll polish and shine
any car, any time ♪
♪ ’Cause we’re the
Happening Carwash Boys ♪
‐ But we’re not polished.
All we are is a bunch
of amateurs, really.
‐ Put it out of your mind!
Don’t think about it!
Remember the night we
swore we’d forget it?
‐ Was there such a night?
(tank treads grinding)
‐ Hm?
(gulping)
(glass breaking)
(tank treads grinding)
‐ After all the work we did,
that’s the tanks we got!
‐ What a mess!
‐ I mean, really.
‐ No kidding.
‐ Who’s responsible?
(engine charging)
(buzzing)
("Galaxy Bang!
Bang!" by Team Angel)
‐ [Narrator] Canned
Angel With Gun Turret.
(cute theme music)
‐ Good morning everyone, meow!
Time for Digicoast
news hour, meow!
Now, our top story:
‐ Oh no, oh my god!
An advanced, state‐of‐the‐art
tank has been stolen
from a research facility
in Somewheretown!
The situation is
extremely dangerous.
Galaxy Angels, we
need your help!
‐ (sighs) Why does
this have to happen
on our day off, anyway?
‐ That’s really weird.
Who’d wanna steal a tank?
Something Forte
would probably do.
(gasps) Think about it:
she’s got enough weapons,
it would be easy for
her, and after all,
she’s the type!
There you go, we’ve
found our culprit.
(cannon firing)
(electronic warbling)
(celebratory music)
‐ How excellent.
Case solved.
Our work here is finally done.
‐ Mint, this is so fun!
A tank ride!
Hang on, here we go!
‐ Come on, Milfeulle,
get serious, will you?
This isn’t the time to be
quite so light‐hearted.
‐ Hey, I’m not
being light‐hearted!
I’m just enjoying my work!
‐ Okay, then how about
working on this problem of it?
‐ Hello there!
Is anybody home?
(gasps)
Hmm.
Hmm?
Should I be happy about this?
‐ Now what are
you talking about?
‐ Well, there doesn’t
seem to be anyone inside.
‐ Huh?
(gasps) Oh my, it’s true.
‐ [Normad] Hello,
this is Normad,
Normad calling my
lovely Vanilla.
Do you read me,
my sweet Vanilla?
I repeat, do you read me, over.
‐ Electrocute him.
‐ Aye, aye.
‐ [Normad] (groans)
Hey, I was kidding!
Just kidding, really!
I can see the tank from here!
It’s running out‐of‐control
south‐southwest
along Next Avenue.
And my mind is about run
out out‐of‐control too!
Help, Vanilla!
‐ [Forte] Sorry! I forgot
to turn off the switch.
‐ [Normad] Oh, no, Vanilla!
Mint and Milfeulle are
just barely hanging on
to the side of the runaway tank!
It always seemed like
Mint was just a little kid
and Milfeulle was a dimwit.
For the life of me, I can’t
imagine how they managed
to pull off a heist this major.
(screams)
‐ [Forte] Enough fooling around!
I’m apologizing to you and
you’re just going on and on,
talking to yourself!
(gasps)
‐ Forte, I can’t believe
they’re behind this!
‐ I guess we’ve just got
to find out for ourselves.
‐ Now wait a minute!
There’s no need for
you to use that!
‐ [Mint] For
goodness sake, stop!
(laughing)
This isn’t good.
Neither the brakes
nor the steering
seem to be
functioning at at all.
‐ [Milfeulle] Mint, Mint!
‐ Is something the matter?
‐ [Milfeulle] I’ve
got a question!
Which of the following
is lying directly
in the path of this tank?
One: a gremlin?
Two: a goblin?
Or three: a monster?
‐ [Mint] Number one?
‐ Sorry, incorrect!
It’s number four: a
bridge under construction!
‐ How was I supposed
to answer that?
(roars)
‐ Mint, can you believe that?
A monster, a real monster!
Don’t you think
that’s really lucky?
‐ It’s not my idea
of really good luck.
(gasps) I have an idea!
‐ (laughs) Woo!
Huh?
It’s not as easy to work
as a microwave, is it?
‐ Don’t worry so much.
Just try to figure
out the controls.
Give it a shot!
‐ Are you sure?
Then maybe I’ll just
see if, there! (groans)
Hey, it moved!
‐ [Mint Voiceover] I can
only count on Milfeulle
to get us out of this
crazy situation alive.
All we’ve got going for us now
are her amazing
streaks of good luck.
‐ What’s going on now?
‐ Beats me.
‐ Warp.
‐ [Mint] Why is
the tank warping?
‐ [Milfeulle] I don’t
know, but it’s not
that bad (laughing).
‐ Why is this happening?
(laughing)
(electronic warping)
‐ [Mint] (sighs)
This isn’t good.
To think the tank won’t stop,
even with all of
Milfeulle’s luck.
At this rate, it looks
like we’re totally doomed.
Heading for the ocean
into oblivion, too young.
‐ Ocean, I didn’t even
bring my bathing suit!
Huh?
‐ Have we stopped?
‐ It seems like we have.
‐ Free at last!
‐ Now I can go get
that bathing suit!
‐ Don’t come any closer!
(laughing)
‐ Mint, Milfeulle!
You really fell for my ingenious
trap this time, didn’t you?
‐ [Milfeulle] Hey, Fart‐e!
‐ Huh?
‐ Just what are you doing?
You should be ashamed,
leaving this tank lying around
after risking your
life to steal it.
I mean, I know you like
your firearms and missiles
and everything,
but don’t you think
stealing this tank is
overdoing it a bit?
Are you a gun lover or
a total weapons freak?
‐ (laughs) I don’t
know what you mean!
Let go, let go of me right now!
I’m innocent!
‐ Et tu, Brute?
‐ I don’t think so.
‐ Now listen here.
Just because the
ringleader has been caught
doesn’t mean that
you accomplices
are gonna get away with
this, do you understand me?
Now, lay down your weapons
and give yourselves up!
‐ All this is getting way
too complicated for me.
Why don’t we just
get off of the tank?
(pattering)
‐ It’s going to be alright.
If you just own
up to your crime,
the judge is willing
to show you some mercy.
‐ [Mint And Milfeulle]
Well, alright.
‐ You fools!
This isn’t some cartoon!
That could’ve hit us!
‐ Yeah, that’s right!
I haven’t yet
fulfilled my destiny!
I’m not ready to die!
‐ Who are you?
‐ You will have to direct all
your questions to my lawyer.
(grunts)
(groans)
‐ You shouldn’t have
done that, Mint!
No matter how unfair
Ranpha’s being,
it’s just not right
firing at her!
‐ Trust me, I didn’t shoot.
The tank fired that
shot all on its own.
‐ What, do you mean to
tell me that it’s the tank
that doesn’t like Ranpha?
‐ Not so!
In reality, I’m the one
the tank doesn’t like!
‐ Who are you, already?
‐ (cackles) Well, it’s
about time I told you.
I’ve been working in the
tank field for 60 years.
I’m the professor you’ve
heard of, Minami Asagaya!
‐ [Milfeulle] Woo‐hoo, ha ha!
I’m going to fall!
‐ [Mint] Don’t fall!
You’ll kill yourself!
(crashing)
‐ You can’t keep running away!
Get back to the research lab!
‐ [Milfeulle and
Mint] (pattering)
‐ [Minami] It’s not
you I’m talking about!
It’s the tank!
‐ Huh?
‐ What’s this all about, sir?
‐ Well, let me take
you back 12 hours,
five minutes, and
30 seconds in time.
‐ [Minami voiceover] I was
having my beef rice bowl dinner
during my routine
day at the tank lab.
Then, right in the
middle of my meal,
a fairy suddenly
appeared and spoke to me.
‐ Professor, because
you are so marvelous,
I’m going to grant you
one very marvelous wish.
What is your desire?
‐ [Minami Voiceover]
When I heard those words,
I didn’t hesitate for a minute.
I made my wish!
‐ I wish this tank were living!
‐ [Minami voiceover] And
then I couldn’t believe it!
It was the most incredible
thing I’d ever seen!
I realized the tank was eating
my beef rice bowl lunch!
‐ That’s right, it’s true!
There my tank was‐‐
(clang)
(groan)
‐ I think your stories
are ridiculous!
‐ They’re not!
These weapons program
developments are state secrets!
If they knew what
I was telling you,
I’d be in big trouble!
‐ So that’s how it is.
‐ Yes, yes!
‐ What do you mean?
Are you telling me
that all of our efforts
have been totally wasted?
‐ One might say.
‐ It would be fun
to meet a fairy.
‐ (sighs) We finally
managed to solve the case.
We’ve finished our work now.
‐ Huh, huh uh?
‐ What’s the matter, Mr. Tank?
Does your tummy
hurt or something?
‐ Tanks don’t have
tummies, silly.
‐ Hmm?
(tank whirring)
(melancholy music)
‐ The tank doesn’t
wanna go anymore.
‐ Huh?
‐ Hmm.
‐ But what can we do?
We can’t have a stray tank
wandering around town.
It’s not‐‐
‐ But he’s finally free!
I’m sure he wants to
do lots of fun things!
And eat lots of good
food, like any tank!
And, well, let’s see, I mean!
‐ Oh, Milfeulle.
‐ Hey, Ranpha, Vanilla!
Please tell me:
Am I being really weird?
‐ [Minami] Yes.
‐ [Ranpha] You’re
not being weird.
It’s just that tough
calls are part of our job.
‐ [Milfeulle] Does that
mean we should just
accept whatever happens?
(gasps)
I mean, I mean, maybe
it’s not too much to think
that we can really be
friends with this tank!
(melancholy music)
(missile shooting)
‐ [Normad] That does it.
The little kid and
the total dimwit
shall become my hostages.
‐ Wha?
‐ Huh?
‐ Hey, hold it right there, you!
‐ If you move, I’ll
kill the hostages.
‐ Hey, kid, that’s pretty good.
You’re quite the ventriloquist.
‐ (laughs) Wow,
Mint, we’re hostages!
Hostages, hostages, ha!
‐ [Mint] (sighs) Wasn’t
this a touching drama?
(laughs)
(upbeat energetic music)
(deep thud)
‐ I’m gonna tell you one
more time, I didn’t do it!
‐ Do you want a cutlet bowl?
‐ Don’t mess with me!
‐ How about tempura?
‐ You even listening?
‐ Some sushi, maybe?
‐ [Anchor] This is crazy, meow!
(spitting)
(triumphant music)
(animal noises)
(panicked animal noises)
("Horoscope Rhapsody"
by Team Angel)