(engines whirring)
(zapping)
(warning bell blaring)
‐ Oops, I did it again!
‐ What do you mean, oops?
We just installed
the new engine!
You pushed it too hard
without breaking it in first!
‐ Come to think of it,
even the maintenance
crew were complaining
that it wouldn’t
withstand 30 parsecs
with you behind the controls.
‐ [Normad] That’s
right, look at Vanilla!
(Forte growling)
Twice around the cave
without a problem,
that’s a big difference!
‐ Hey, you can shut up!
It’s not my style to just
putter around in these things!
‐ No need to get so upset!
(Forte growls)
So, what are you gonna do now?
‐ Uh, uh, well...
Hey, look at that!
I betcha this station’s got
all the parts I’m gonna need!
(computer beeps)
(engine roars)
(alarm blares)
("Galaxy Bang!
Bang!" by Angel‐tai)
(singing in foreign language)
This is Lieutenant Forte Stollen
of the Angel Brigade
requesting permission
to use your facility
for repair purposes.
Hello, do you read me?
Are you there?
‐ I’d say it looks like
their shields are down.
‐ I guess we’ll just have
to check it out then.
‐ I am a bit concerned that
there’s been no response yet.
(gears whirring)
‐ [All] Hmm?
Huh?
(comical music)
‐ (quivers) What a stinky mess!
‐ This really couldn’t be‐‐
‐ What in the hell
is going on here?
‐ Any more foul!
‐ [Forte] Bah, they should
clean this place up a bit.
No matter, let’s head inside.
‐ Okay, here we go.
(Mint grunting)
(Forte grunts)
‐ [Forte] Hurry up, Vanilla!
(gears whirring)
(all sigh)
‐ Thank goodness that’s over!
‐ Someone was out there.
‐ What?!
‐ Why didn’t you say so before?
(Mint and Forte grunt)
(elevator beeps)
‐ What an incredible
mess this place is.
‐ Something’s not quite right.
(grunts) Hey, give
that back to me!
‐ Forte!
‐ These people should keep
their pets on a leash!
(Mint and Forte heavily breathe)
(Mint groaning)
(growls) Oh!
(monkeys chattering)
‐ What’s going on here,
what’s with all these monkeys?
‐ Huh, there are too
many of them to be pets.
Anyway, doesn’t matter,
I’ve gotta get my hat back.
‐ Forte!
‐ This is a much faster
way to deal with them,
and I don’t like chimps.
‐ You mustn’t.
‐ Huh?
‐ They may only be monkeys,
but they are God’s
creatures all the same
and should be
treated accordingly.
‐ Yeah, yeah, okay,
I guess you’re right.
‐ In any case, I
think it would be best
if we got in touch with
Headquarters right away.
‐ Alright.
Hey out of the way, you monkeys!
‐ She’s so crude.
‐ [Normad] An example of a
life form lower than a monkey.
(Forte grunts)
(computer beeping)
‐ Hmm, yes?
This is the Angel Room.
Oh, it’s Forte,
where are you now?
‐ The Third Space Station of
the Cornelius planetary system.
We were forced to come
here for engine repairs.
‐ [Ranpha] Did you just
say the Third Space Station
of the Cornelius
planetary system?
‐ Yeah?
(Ranpha giggling)
‐ Hmm?
(Ranpha laughing)
‐ What’s so damn funny?
‐ Could there possibly
be a whole lot
of monkeys surrounding you?
‐ Yeah, there is, (groans)
crawling all over the place.
What’s the deal here? (grunts)
‐ They are people,
you know, humans.
‐ Humans?
‐ You see, that station is
a virus research facility.
A new biohazardous virus got
out of control there recently
and unfortunately, most
of the facility personnel
contracted it.
‐ (laughs) And so, they all,
they all turned into
monkeys! (laughs)
‐ Then, don’t tell
me, we’re going to,
we’re going to...
‐ Turn into monkeys!
(Mint quivers)
‐ Monkey, monkey, monkey!
(monkeys squealing
and chattering)
Monkey, monkey, monkey?!
Monkey, monkey, monkey?! (yells)
No!
No! (cries)
‐ How is the virus
passed on exactly?
‐ Well, let me just see here.
The virus is contracted
through the air.
(Forte groans)
‐ [Mint] Nooo!
‐ How do you treat it,
isn’t there a vaccine?
‐ A special research
team is in the process
of developing it as we speak.
Oh, but you needn’t
be concerned.
You only turn into monkeys
and there’s no
threat to your lives.
‐ Huh, who’s gonna
turn into a monkey?
‐ (laughs) Huh, where’s Forte?
Hey!
‐ Let’s get out of
here as fast as we can!
(Mint and Forte groan)
‐ Huh?
(Mint and Forte scream)
(monkey screaming)
‐ Did he do that?!
(comical music)
(buttons beeping)
(Forte crying)
‐ ’Key, monkey, monkey,
monkey, mon...
(alarms blaring)
‐ Wha, what could
it be this time?
What is it, what is it,
what’s going on now?
‐ [Normad] The monkeys set off
the self‐destruct mechanism!
(Forte groans)
‐ [Computer] 180 seconds
until self‐destruct.
‐ Let’s get out of here now!
‐ [Normad] But what
about the monkeys?
‐ They’re just
monkeys, forget ’em!
‐ Look, we can’t do that.
They may look like monkeys.
(Forte growling and groaning)
‐ [Computer] 170 seconds
until self‐destruct.
‐ Then what are
we supposed to do?
You say we should just die
with the monkeys? (yells)
(Vanilla imitating monkey calls)
(monkeys chattering)
(Mint and Forte quivering)
‐ [Computer] 30 seconds
until self‐destruct.
10 seconds until self‐destruct.
(metal clashing)
Self‐destructing.
(space station explodes)
(monkeys chattering)
(Forte and Mint sigh)
‐ Whew, we barely made
it outta there. (sighs)
Hmm?
(quivers)
What the hell is this?!
(slow, cheerful music)
‐ Yes?
Yes, we have recovered them all.
Yes, well, they’ve all
turned into monkeys,
and I can’t really tell.
Hmm, yes?
I can’t identify who’s who.
I agree, I think we’ll just
have to keep them all together
until the vaccine is ready.
What, feed them bananas
because they have a peel?
(laughs) That’s terrible!
Hmm?
(glass crashes)
(Ranpha screams)
(monkey grunting)
(monkeys screaming)
(items crashing)
‐ Oh, my, we still
have time left!
What should I do?!
Shakku!
‐ What is it, Yuri?
‐ [Yuri] Shakku, we
have 15 seconds left!
Could you say something?
‐ Now, can’t the writers
come up with some lines?
Okay, (farts), I’ll tell you
why only corned beef cans
are shaped like
corned beef cans.
Do you like corned
beef, Yuri, hmm?
‐ [Yuri] I love it!
‐ Corned beef is‐‐
‐ [Normad] Now listen,
if you drop your fart,
don’t pick it up yourself.
What are you doing?!
Don’t you realize that we
can’t just sit here like this
and pick all night?
Which is more important, your
life or your cake recipe?
I really don’t think
you understand.
So, I’ll tell you again.
Will you really get me?! (sighs)
("Horoscope Rhapsody")
(singing in foreign language)