(heavy rain and thunder)
(lighting cracking)
‐ I have odds that
Forte is actually evil.
Consider the mission
we’re on now.
If she hadn’t
disappeared like this,
I’ll bet we would’ve
been finished already!
She’s always acting like
she’s the leader or something.
She probably didn’t like this
mission and just took off!
What do you think?
(heavy rain)
You’re great, Vanilla.
You’d never lower
yourself and talk
about someone behind their back.
I’m sure she can learn
a thing or two from you!
Hey, this might be a good place!
I’ve got a hunch that Forte is
yet to show her true colors.
You’d better be careful!
(heavy rain)
Oh, excuse me, we’d like
to spend the night here.
("Galaxy Bang! Bang!")
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Narrator] Gun Shot
Bandage Roll Sushi Bowl!
(gun clicking)
(gun firing)
(gasping)
‐ Wonderful, wonderful,
bravo, bravo!
You have quite amazing skills!
‐ Yes I do.
The Colt Artillery Civilian.
Not a replica, but
a real one from
when the Wild West
was being won.
‐ Uh‐huh.
If you’d like, you can have it.
‐ What?
No way!
You’re gonna give me this?
‐ Sure, it’s yours!
May it be a symbol of
our new found friendship!
‐ Right on!
Thanks!
(gasping)
‐ If you’d like to come
with me to visit my hospital
in town, I’d love
to show you the rest
of my gun collection.
‐ Really?
Let’s go now!
‐ Well, alright!
Shall we then, Chief?
‐ Huh?
(laughing)
‐ What?
Chief?
(lighthearted music)
‐ [Old Lady] No, no!
You’re still quite
young, you know!
‐ [Angry Man] You
must be joking!
‐ Ma’am, this way.
‐ Huh?
‐ This is the
hospital I spoke of.
‐ Ah.
Very impressive!
(groaning)
‐ Okay, turn around.
(birds chirping)
Alright, that’s good.
‐ [Worried Mother]
How is he, Doctor?
‐ It’s nothing to worry
about, just a head cold.
Well, hang on, let me
get him some medicine.
‐ Oh, thank you very much.
‐ Give him this three times
a day after his meals.
‐ Sure.
‐ Alright, next!
(peaceful music)
‐ Oh!
Oh!
Oh, oh!
(cheering)
I can move!
My arthritis has been cured!
I can move it, I can move it!
My leg, it’s been healed!
Oh, come dance with me!
‐ It’s a miracle!
‐ It truly is!
‐ Thank you, Miss!
Oh, thank you!
‐ Oh, Vanilla truly is an angel!
(laughing)
(sighing)
‐ It’s very strange
that you don’t have
any patients here at all.
Are you closed down?
‐ Well, no, not exactly!
Hey, let’s go see my
gun collection, okay?
‐ Yeah!
‐ The former chief here was
quite the gun collector,
specializing in
the Federal Period.
‐ The Browning High
Powered Competition Model!
The Tokarev
Semi‐Automatic Rifle!
The Kalashnikov Carbine AMP69!
(gasping)
‐ Wow!
The Sterm Rooker
Percussion Revolver!
Absolutely beautiful lines!
Oh, it’s gorgeous!
I’d give anything
to own this one.
‐ So, whatta think?
‐ It’s fantastic!
This collection is incredible!
‐ If there’s anything you
want, you can have it.
‐ Are you serious?
‐ Under the condition that
you accept a particular job.
‐ A job?
Yeah, sure!
I’ll do anything!
(mysterious music)
‐ Thanks to that little
clinic over there,
we never get any patients here!
(laughing)
‐ Maybe that’s not
really the problem.
(laughing)
‐ We have the best facilities
available anywhere,
right here at this hospital.
‐ That ramshackle
clinic doesn’t even‐‐
(cheering)
‐ I’m thinking your
problem lies elsewhere.
(groaning)
‐ Well, to put it
bluntly, the job
that I have suggested you
carry out for me is this,
I would like you to do
whatever you can to throw
that doctor across the
street out of this town.
If you can do that
for me, you may take
what you like from
the collection.
‐ Alright then, leave it to me!
‐ Thank you so much!
(screaming)
(whacking)
(crying)
‐ Chief?
(gun firing)
‐ Just a test firing to see if
this gun is working properly.
‐ Test firing?
Yes, of course.
(grinding)
Uh, do you really
have to have us hold
these like this for you?
‐ The enemy won’t
be standing still.
Unless those targets
are kept moving,
this test will be
far from realistic.
‐ Uh, right.
‐ Okay, here we go!
Get a move on!
(gun firing)
(laughing)
(crying)
Not too bad.
‐ Is that okay?
Did we do alright?
‐ Yeah, sure!
(dramatic music)
‐ What do you people want?
‐ Listen, Doc, I have nothing
against you personally,
but in light of the
present situation,
I’m gonna have to ask you
to leave town immediately.
‐ So that greedy hospital’s
putting you up to this, huh?
‐ What?
What do you mean, greedy?
That’s it!
See, we’ve heard enough!
Just blow him away already!
‐ Huh, you sure?
Okay, look you’ll have to
do as we say and leave now
or I’m gonna have to shoot you.
And these bullets
are gonna hurt.
‐ Forte!
‐ Huh, Normad?
And Vanilla?
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Who me?
Well now that you’re
asking, I’d like to know
what you two are doing here.
‐ Do you want Vanilla
to just get up
and abandon these sick
and injured people?
Unlike you, she’s a
kind and gentle soul!
‐ Now wait a minute!
I have my own considerations,
I’m helping out these
people here as well!
‐ Take one look and you can
tell who the evil ones are.
(mysterious music)
This isn’t something
you have to think about!
(gun firing)
‐ You betrayed us!
You get nothing from
the gun collection!
‐ Well, I could have
guessed as much.
‐ Stop!
Don’t do it!
Are you mad?
You’ll blow us all up!
(laughing)
‐ This is just the moment
I’ve been waiting for!
No doctor can help you now!
(window breaking)
(dynamite going off)
(peaceful music)
‐ You really helped.
‐ I don’t think we’ll
be seeing much of
those three around here again.
(screaming and crying)
‐ Y’all take care of yourselves.
(peaceful music)
(humming)
‐ So, do you think that’s
the lost technology
we’ve been looking for?
‐ [Normad] Well, that’s
what we’re here to find out.
You know, if you had
your act together,
Forte, we would’ve
been done here already!
‐ [Forte] Wow, this
is a nice piece!
‐ [Narrators] What’s
the special service?
‐ [Narrator] Angel
Brigade, fight!
‐ [Narrators] What’s
the special service?
‐ [Narrator] We should
all work hard together!
‐ [Narrators] What’s
the special service?
‐ [Narrator] Hey, hey, pitcher,
you couldn’t hit
the side of a bus.
Or the side of a barn.
("Horoscope Rhapsody")
(singing in foreign language)