(dark piano music)
(gun cocks)
‐ [Woman] Alright
dinner’s ready.
‐ [Children] Okay.
‐ [Woman] Honey,
what is the matter?
‐ Uh, oh it’s nothing, (laughs).
Okay let’s eat.
‐ [All] Bless this food.
(electronic buzz)
(family gasps in unison)
(three alarm rings)
‐ It’s another order.
(engine charging)
(sign alarm beeps)
(electronic zoom)
(lively electronic pop music)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Narrator] Pitch
black laughing pepper.
‐ I thought that show
was quite funny actually.
‐ Me too.
I was laughing so hard.
‐ There’s nothing like
a good comedy film.
I can stand sappy, pathetic
romances, makes my ass itchy.
‐ I don’t know how
many times I laughed.
‐ Forte laughed 34 times.
Ronfa, 25.
‐ Why were you counting
how many times we laughed?
‐ Because I was really bored.
‐ Oh
‐ You know, I don’t
think I’ve ever
seen you laugh before, Vanilla.
‐ The devil lives in the
mouth of a forced laugh.
Very wise words.
‐ Vanilla, we are not saying
you should force
yourself to laugh.
‐ Hey, are you Vanilla Ash?
‐ No. Hold on!
(Gun cocks)
‐ Assassins?
‐ Hi, so how are you doing?
‐ That’s a phone!
‐ [Two Girls] Oh!
(crash)
‐ Well, we got their attention.
‐ Let’s do it.
(silly synthesizer music)
‐ Just the other day,
I was shopping at the
local department store
and happened to lose
something very important.
‐ [Woman] Oh really?
What was that?
‐ [Man] I lost a child.
He’s wearing a white
shirt and blue pants
and...
‐ [Woman] Careful,
or you’ll start losing
your friends too.
‐ Could this be...
‐ A comedy act?
‐ Yes, The Hurricane
of Laughter,
The husband and wife comedy duo,
Patrick and Patricia Wohatta.
and everyone who
sees their routine
ends up getting sucked
into a giant tidal wave.
(Forte laughs)
(waves crashing)
‐ [Man] Really?
(laughing)
(waves crashing)
(surprised gasp)
‐ I can’t believe there’s anyone
who doesn’t find
our routine funny.
‐ Time for the works.
‐ [Couple] Ha!
(cascading water)
‐ Did they?
‐ No, not yet.
(crash)
‐ No, we failed.
(thundering crash of boulders)
‐ Ah!
‐ Are our gags
really that bad?
‐ [Couple] Oh.
‐ It seems you just
don’t have what it takes.
‐ Oh, ah, Mr. God.
Please gives us
both another chance.
‐ No.
I know you will not be able
to make this girl laugh.
‐ Hey, what’s going
on around here?
And why are you trying
to make Vanilla laugh?
‐ Yeah, just who
are you guys anyway?
‐ Hello, my name is Mr. God.
I am known in the business
as the king of laughter.
‐ You’re the king of laughter?
‐ [Mr. God] Yes, but I am
no longer able to stand
upon a stage.
‐ [Girls] Why not?
‐ Something happened
to me three months ago.
That was the last
time I was on a stage.
‐ Welcome ladies and gentleman.
The act you’ve been
waiting to see.
The king of laughter, Mr. God!
(audience applause and cheers)
‐ [Mr. God] As usual the
audience was watching my antics
and having a wonderful time.
However, there was one
who wasn’t laughing.
No!
It couldn’t be.
Was there something
wrong with my routine?
Why?
Why won’t she laugh?
Ah, (cracking sound) my foot!
Ah!
(crashes with thud)
‐ (gasps) Father!
Father!
‐ I get it.
Vanilla was the one
who wouldn’t laugh at
your comedy that night.
‐ Yeah, I remember cause
I was at that show.
‐ That very day I retired
and made a resolution
that anyone who makes
Vanilla laugh or smile
should take my place.
‐ Father, I’m the one who
should take over for you.
What’s wrong with me.
(loud whip)
Ah!
‐ You don’t have
what it takes yet.
It’ll be years before
you can honor my name.
‐ Wow!
I didn’t know that
you’re fame was so‐‐
‐ Hey, are you kidding?
Mr. God is the
biggest act in comedy.
Whoever carries on his name,
will be considered the
greatest comic in space.
Mr. God is the absolute
master of the comic arts.
‐ True, Mr. God can make
you chuckle, giggle and howl
in ways thought not possible.
The world has never
seen anyone like him.
That’s why they call him
‐ [Couple] The king of laughter.
‐ That’s enough.
You guys really need to do
some work on your routine.
Maybe you need a booking
at the Tiger’s Den.
‐ [Couple] Ah, never!
‐ Please not that!
‐ The Tiger’s Den,
so what’s that?
‐ [Mr. God] The Tiger’s
Den is a tiger’s den.
‐ [Blonde Girl] But why?
‐ [Mr. God] It’s a comedy
club where comedians
risk their lives to
improve their skills.
(dramatic orchestral music)
‐ What, you don’t get it?
(low buzzer)
Ah!
‐ Thank you, thank
you very much.
(low buzzer)
Ah!
(water splashes)
‐ Hey, hey, how bout this one?
(low buzzer)
Ah!
‐ [Couple] No please don’t,
you can’t, you can’t, please!
‐ Comedy can be deadly.
Bad jokes can be as dangerous
as a laughter assassin.
But failing is not all bad.
People are real only when
they can laugh honestly.
You can become honest,
only after you fail.
(cat meows)
‐ [Girl] Wow, that
really is interesting.
‐ Yes it is.
I heard about all this Forte.
‐ And did she happen to tell you
what a laughter assassin
is supposed to be?
‐ Why, you’re Vanilla
Ash, aren’t you?
‐ [Girls] Hmm?
‐ A challenge!
‐ Multi‐ventriloquist,
Mr. Megaton T. Gasto.
Everyone who sees his
performance is overcome
with the sensation of
being carpet bombed.
(loud explosion)
(girls laughing)
(loud explosions)
‐ Don, we blew it.
That was a dud.
This can’t be.
(crying)
‐ Now, it’s my turn dude.
(ukulele music)
The Mount Vesuvius of comedy,
dawn of the Me‐har‐a.
‐ [Mr. God] A man who
can cause volcanic
eruptions of laughter
(booming explosion)
‐ [Man] No, I didn’t dig
my jokes for that dormant.
‐ [Mr. God] Even these comics
couldn’t make her laugh.
‐ Father, please let me try.
I can do it.
Ow!
‐ Don’t be a fool!
You’re not funny.
Now that it’s come to this.
I’ll have to take up my
mantel one last time,
and give it another shot myself.
[Woman] What da ya have there?
‐ Mr. God’s revenge performance.
‐ That’s right.
It was delivered to
Vanilla a little while ago.
(bass drum roll)
‐ [Son] Ladies and gentleman,
thank you for coming.
And now the return to the
stage of the great Mr. God.
(audience applause)
‐ I just flew in
from Tokyo and boy,
are my arms tired.
(playful circus music)
(audience giggling)
My arms tired.
Are my arms tired?
Are my arms tired.
(audience laughing)
Why?
Why won’t she laugh?
She’s the only one.
Why?
Oh, (cracking sound) my foot!
No!
‐ Father!
(bell dings)
I’ll do it.
I’m going to make her laugh.
(bass drum roll)
What do you call a
fly with no wings?
It’s a wok.
A wok, get it?
No wings.
So it’s a wok.
It can’t why fly
so it has to walk.
‐ This is pathetic.
‐ Come quickly,
please it’s Mr. God.
(heavy, labored breathing)
‐ [Mr. God] I think
I’m almost done.
I want you to hear
my last words.
(somber keyboard music)
‐ [Woman] Ah, Vanilla?
(Mr. God mumbles)
‐ (gasps) She smiled.
‐ Ah, she did?
‐ I don’t believe it.
‐ [Group] Ah!
‐ [Mr. God] Alright,
all together now.
‐ Are our arms tired.
(audience laughing)
Are our arms tired.
‐ Well, I guess we got a
happy ending after all.
It seems that Mr. God’s
got his health back
because Vanilla finally smiled.
‐ That was real special.
Seeing Vanilla’s first grin.
‐ I really wanna
know what it was
that Mr. God said
to her, don’t you?
‐ Yes.
Oh, Vanilla, please tell
us all what made you smile.
‐ Sure.
‐ [Girls] Yeah?
‐ Are our arms tired.
‐ Can’t be serious.
‐ You must be kidding us.
‐ Really?
‐ [Vanilla] It’s true.
‐ [Girls] Oh no!
‐ Yes, our arms were tired.
The flies arms were tired too.
I mean it didn’t have
wings either, now.
(playful circus music)
(cat meows)
‐ [Narrator] What do you
say before you have a meal?
‐ [Girls] Thank you for the
meal we’re about to eat.
‐ [Narrator] What do you say
to someone when you part ways?
‐ [Girls] Have a nice day.
‐ [Narrator] When you apologize?
‐ [Girls] I’m sorry.
‐ [Narrator] And again.
‐ [Girls] I’m really sorry.
(playful happy music)
(singing in foreign language)