(Galaxy Angel Theme)
‐ Angel Dark Space Chazuke
‐ I can’t think
like this! (yelling)
‐ That’s the seventh time
you’ve said that now.
‐ Oh, is that right?
‐ Yes and it’s only been 14
minutes and seven seconds
since you began.
You sure lack focus.
This air smells great.
‐ I had no idea we were so
behind in updating our database
‐ Just get on it!
‐ It’s no surprise.
We were out on missions
for a long time.
‐ Investigative reports.
Expense receipts.
Maintenance reports.
Processing for the
lost technology.
What?
Details of reception
party for new member.
From when Milfeulle
first joined us.
Who forgot this?
‐ Sorry. That was my fault.
‐ And you’re still gonna
bill the brigade for that?
‐ Hi, Everyone!
‐ Huh?
‐ I’ve just made some tea. How
would you like a break now?
‐ Well, aren’t you carefree?
‐ Is your report been
taking care of yet? If we
don’t all sort this business
out today. It will have
to come off our pay.
Do you understand me?
‐ Oh, I’ve already
submitted my expense report.
‐ What?
(tea pouring)
‐ You can’t just throw
it together like that!
Any mistakes and it will
be sent back to you!
‐ Hmm, well it looks to me
like everything’s in order.
I don’t see any problems here.
‐ Really?
(laughing)
‐ I can help you with
yours afterwards. How about
we stop for some tea now?
‐ What’s with you
all of a sudden?
‐ Could you be getting a fever?
‐ Or maybe you’ve
eaten some bad food?
‐ What is it?
‐ Something strange is going on!
‐ Are you feeling any pain?
Something’s just not right.
‐ Are you sure you’re okay?
‐ It seems to me
you’re not yourself.
‐ [Crew] What?
‐ You’re nothing but a fake.
You’re just pretending to
be Milfeulle.
Aren’t you?
‐ Oh, right! That
explains it then.
‐ Of course, that’s what
it is! A fake. That’s what
you are (laughs)
‐ And since that’s the
case, I hereby put you under
arrest. (snaps)
‐ Okay!
(marching footsteps)
‐ But Colonel, isn’t
this going a bit too far?
‐ No, the Angel Brigade
is part of the military.
For security reasons, we
must guard ourselves against
all imposters.
‐ I’m not so sure I understand
where you’re coming from.
‐ Tell us! Who were those guys
and where did they take her?
‐ So that Milfeulle
was an imposter?
‐ I’ll show you.
‐ What?
‐ Believe it or not,
this is the real
Milfeulle Sakuraba.
‐ [Crew] She’s so different!
‐ Her visual imaging
data was somehow
mistakenly sent to
another department
and only arrived at our
headquarters yesterday.
‐ But do you think you can
say, based on this data alone
that the Milfeulle that’s
been with us all along
is a phony?
‐ Yeah! That’s right!
Maybe she just got a
little thinner in the face.
‐ Or had surgery.
‐ Quite doubtful. The DNA
tests show conclusively that
she can’t possibly
be the same person.
(crew gasps)
‐ Does that mean we’ve
been working with a fraud
in our midst all this time?
‐ [Colonel] That’s
what it means.
‐ [Mint] I’d like to know
where the real Milfeulle is.
Right now.
‐ [Colonel] Her
location is unknown
but we are doing our best
to find her.
‐ [Mint] Accepting a new member
without her proper documents?
That’s a dereliction of duty.
‐ [Colonel] I’m sorry. I never
imagined that a fellow Angel
could have been an imposter.
‐ [Mint] You know, I
understand how you feel but...
‐ [Normad] The totality
of her empty headiness
was definitely not natural.
(soft music playing)
‐ What do you think
will happen to her?
‐ Who knows?
‐ Spying is a serious crime.
She’d be lucky to get a
life sentence.
‐ But that’s too harsh!
Milfeulle isn’t a trouble
maker in any sense of the word.
‐ The moment she joined
the military under false
pretenses she committed
a grave offense.
‐ Those who break the
law must pay for it.
‐ Vanilla’s absolutely right!
She is accountable.
‐ She could get
the death penalty.
‐ [Crew] What?
‐ Why you! Can’t you just
keep your mouth shut?
(Yelling)
What’s the matter? I
said answer me you!
(heavy breathing)
(crying)
‐ [Guard] Huh? What do you want?
(alarms sounding)
‐ There’s a small shuttle
craft on deck D‐22.
We’re gonna head
straight for it.
‐ Why are you helping me escape?
‐ Hey, over here!
‐ Don’t ask me anything.
It will be better that way!
‐ What do you mean?
‐ If I start thinking
about this too much
I might regret it later.
‐ Huh?
‐ And...
‐ Yes?
‐ Don’t ask me what my name
is or where I’ve come from
okay?
‐ Ah, okay!
‐ [Guard] Stop!
Now, slowly put your
hands on the wall
and I mean slowly
‐ So this is it.
‐ [Forte] Ah, I see you!
That’s it. You’re finished now!
Ha! Come here you
retched rodent!
‐ What the?
‐ You can’t run anyway
that I can’t find you!
Don’t think you can get away
from me, you little rat!
Oops, he stopped.
(windup toy cranks)
Alright! You’re
still in my sights.
I see you!
‐ That’s Forte!
‐ No it isn’t. She’s just a
mouse hunter doing her job.
‐ Stop!
What the hell?
Get out of here!
‐ Was that Vanilla?
‐ That was just a seeker
on her spiritual path.
‐ Stop!
(Chicken clucking)
‐ Who was that?
‐ Don’t ask me. I
don’t have a clue!
‐ I guess I’ll have to
submit a report for this too.
‐ Hurry!
‐ Alright
‐ What’s the hold up?
Just get out of here now!
‐ But I want to
say thanks, Ranpha.
‐ Mmmm. Hey, I’m just a
mysterious mask‐wearing soldier
who saw you needed some help.
‐ Is she gone?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Well, that girl sure
is quite the character.
‐ It was quite tricky
getting her on her way.
‐ I’ve always wished I could
figure out what makes her
tick.
‐ Even a computer
couldn’t figure her out.
‐ [Milfeulle] Oh, my goodness.
What in space are all of you
doing here?
‐ [Crew] Ahhhhhhhh!!!
‐ [Ranpha] I’m
confused! What are you?
Where did you? What
the? I don’t get it.
‐ I thought she was
on the shuttle craft.
‐ I’m absolutely
sure she got on it.
What are you doing here?
‐ Just listen to my
story! When I went to the
grocery store this
morning to do the shopping
for the Brigade
some weird people
started chasing me.
It was scary!
And then I got totally lost!
‐ What are you saying?
‐ Well, I did get some
shopping done before
I went on duty.
So we have enough
supplies to tide us over.
Please don’t be angry with me.
We’ve got food for the week.
‐ That’s not what I mean!
You were working on the database
with us this morning, right?
‐ Oh? Was I really?
‐ Yes you were!
‐ Oh, I see.
‐ So, do you get it?
‐ But who was the one
doing the shopping then?
‐ Well, not anyone I know!
‐ What? Not anyone
that you know?
‐ That’s not what I meant!
‐ What’s happening here?
‐ It might sound crazy,
but I believe she’s telling
the truth.
‐ Then you’re saying that
this is the real Milfeulle?
‐ No, to be accurate the
other one wasn’t Milfeulle.
‐ Beauty! I Vanilla Ash
of the Angel Brigade shall
hereby perform a DNA
test match on the subject
in question.
‐ [Computer Voice] DNA
match. It is confirmed that
the subject is
Milfeulle Sakuraba.
‐ What? That test can’t
possibly prove it!
‐ But what about her picture?
‐ Oh, my picture? What
a hassle that was!
I was in such a rush that
morning to get it taken
but the machine in the
studio was so old that
it almost took 30 minutes to
scan my face.
‐ You mean this is actually you?
‐ That’s right.
‐ Then tell us, why doesn’t
your photo look like you?
‐ Oh, they said they wanted
a very recent picture.
So I thought I’d just
leave it until that day.
‐ And what happened? Did
you suddenly get sick?
‐ Yes, it might
look a little funny.
But it is me.
I promise. It really is.
‐ Do you have the slightest
idea how much trouble
we went through today
because of our concern for you
and this mix up?
‐ Then who did we let out?
‐ The genuine fake is the
one you helped to escape.
‐ That’s what I
want to talk about.
‐ Colonel!
‐ Haha.
‐ So this girl here is
definitely the real one?
‐ Yes, your’re right. I know.
But we’ve also learned
that an extremely
important component
of the lost technology
was stolen from
the storage area.
‐ What? Don’ tell me she.....
‐ Listen, Angel Brigade!
‐ Hey, you’re the
"fake" Milfeulle!
‐ To think that you
fools were actually dumb
enough to help me
escape when I’m
the one you wanted in that cell.
(laughing)
[Crew] (surprised crying)
‐ And this is just a small
taste of things to come.
Next time you’re going to
see a lot more of the fake
Angel Brigade. So
I’m warning you now.
You better be prepared.
(laughing)
‐ But this is the last episode.
‐ It is?
‐ That’s right!
‐ [Forte] Hey, is
it really over?
‐ [Ranpha] No way!
‐ [Vanilla] Oh, come on.
We can’t end it like that.
‐ [Milfeulle] Oh, I can’t
wait for the next episode.
I wonder what’s going to happen.
Maybe there will be some
ancient robots or something.
‐ [Crew] We just told you!
This is the last one!
(theme song)