(sirens blaring)
(upbeat music)
‐ [Girl] Roast Beef
of Lost Technology.
‐ What’s your feeling
on this Forte?
Do you think it’s
possible that we’re
gonna find the lost
technology this time?
‐ Oh I don’t know
and I’m not sure we
can rely too much on
what Colonel Volcott
has to say about it.
‐ Excuse me, Ranpha?
‐ Yeah what is it?
‐ I need your help.
I can’t seem to find
the key to the gym room.
‐ [Ranpha] You don’t need it.
I left it open.
‐ Really?
That’s great!
‐ [Ranpha] You’re
free to use the room,
but don’t make a mess okay?
‐ I’ll do my best.
‐ What was that all about?
‐ She wants to exercise to
get herself into better shape.
I mean, she’s been
going on about
how her uniform was starting to
feel and look tighter
around her waist.
And that’s no
surprise considering
how many sweets she eats.
‐ Well you’re one to talk.
You know, you’ve been looking a
little pudgy yourself lately.
(girl yells)
‐ What are you talking about?
Pudgy?
I’m 161 centimeters
tall and 43 kilos.
That’s just right
for me, just perfect.
‐ Oh Lord, please save
these wretched souls.
‐ What did you say Vanilla?
‐ Ranpha look, you’ve
got a meat bun.
‐ What are you talking about?
This isn’t a meat bun,
it’s an imitation
bun, not a real one.
‐ Brigade, I think I’m
beginning to see it.
‐ [Robot] I see.
We didn’t discover it ’til now
because it was hidden above
these smaller planets.
‐ [Ranpha] It’s
really a ghost ship.
‐ That’s strange.
There are no hatches anywhere.
‐ [Robot] That light, and
there’s no mistaking it.
This spaceship was
definitely created
using the lost technology.
‐ [Ranpha] Looks
like the entrance.
Should we go in?
(robot yelling)
‐ Well it looks
safe enough to me.
Let’s go.
‐ [Robot] My memory’s
been shaken up and fried.
‐ Oh no!
The entrance!
‐ It’s closed.
‐ Duh!
As if I didn’t know that!
‐ Oh relax.
Don’t worry.
We’ve got lots of air.
Let’s just figure this out,
and if worst comes to worst,
we can use this
ultra miniature bomb
to blow the spaceship
to smithereens.
‐ But if you use that bomb,
we’ll be blown to bits too.
‐ [Forte] Boy, you’re no fun.
(ghost laughing)
(girls screaming)
‐ What was that, what
was that, what was that?
‐ Wait, I think we forgot Forte!
‐ [Girl] Forte,
we’ll make sure that
your death was not in vain.
‐ Were those proper respects?
‐ No, not even close!
(girls yelling)
‐ Get out evil spirit,
get out evil spirit,
get out evil spirit!
I’ll give you all
the money you want!
‐ Hey, do you think
he’ll take a credit card?
‐ [Ranpha] No!
(girl screaming)
‐ Don’t worry Ranpha.
I’ll be just as happy when
you’re gone and forgotten.
‐ [Ranpha] Out of the way!
Get out of the way!
(girls yelling)
‐ There are more of them!
Maybe we’ll just
blow them all up.
‐ I thought I told you already,
if you use that, we’ll
all be obliterated.
‐ How do you suppose
we deal with this
ridiculously insane situation?
‐ You think I could answer an
impossible question like
that any better than you?
(girl gasps)
I dropped them!
‐ I will haunt you
forever Ranpha.
‐ I’m sorry Vanilla, Mint.
I promise I’ll overcome my
dislike for stinky soybeans
and live life to the
fullest to make up
for how I’ve let you down.
‐ And you don’t like
pickled plum either, do you?
‐ [Girls] Hey, let’s just
blow ourselves to bits.
(girls yelling)
‐ It looks like we made it
and all still in one piece.
‐ Are we in heaven?
‐ If we are, I’ll
have one of those
heaven style spicy
bouillabaisses.
‐ [Robot] Hey,
there’s no such thing.
‐ Oh boy.
Looks like heaven to me.
‐ Then I want potato chips.
‐ Stew here.
‐ Stir fry.
‐ Boy, I sure can’t
get enough of this
tasty stewed daikon radish.
‐ Yum.
This spicy flavor sure
gets my appetite going.
‐ [Robot] How is it Vanilla?
‐ So how do you
think we’re going
to escape from this
spaceship you guys?
‐ [Girls] You mean
we’re not in heaven?
‐ [Mint] You really
thought we were?
(girls screaming)
‐ I’ve got some
good news Milfeulle.
‐ Wait!
You’re going to
tell me how well I’m
doing with my fitness
program, right?
‐ [Man] No.
I’ve come to inform
you that your
probationary period
is finally over.
‐ Really?
‐ Yes.
I’ve just now received the
word from headquarters.
There will be an official
announcement shortly.
‐ Alright!
This means that today
I’m part of the team
that will fight for justice!
‐ There’s more to it than that.
‐ There is?
‐ Please help me!
‐ I can’t take this!
I can’t take this!
‐ And because of this, we
request an emergency rescue.
‐ Listen Volcott,
they’re calling for help.
If I’m on the team now,
then I should deploy.
‐ Alright then.
Let’s just say that
you are now deployed.
‐ Alright!
‐ And Milfeulle.
‐ Yes?
‐ This means that you are now an
official member of the
Galaxy Angel Brigade.
Do your very best.
‐ Yes.
I promise to give it my all.
(upbeat music)
(sirens blaring)
‐ Lost technology’s mysterious.
I can’t be sure
what will happen.
You must be very, very careful.
‐ Roger that.
Now lucky star, begin
deployment immediately
for the Angel Brigade
rescue mission.
(upbeat music)
‐ [Milfeulle Voiceover]
I don’t know how this is
going to turn out,
but hang in there Angels
’til I get to you.
‐ Hey.
There’s a meat bun
flying around up here.
‐ Oh come on now Forte.
Can’t you see,
that’s no meat bun.
That’s a fake meat
bun that just happens
to look like a real
meat bun, you see.
‐ Oh it is?
Well now I’m thinking,
maybe it’s really
a bean bun that’s
pretending to be a meat bun.
‐ [Robot] They sure
seem to be having fun.
(girls giggling)
‐ What do you think
this could be?
‐ [Robot] It looks like
some numbers to me.
‐ You don’t really know, do you?
‐ [Robot] How dare you
suggest that I don’t know?
I swear by my 10,000
gigahertz CPU that this.
‐ What is that?
It looks like an
image on the outside.
That’s one of ours.
It’s Milfeulle.
She’s come to rescue us.
‐ I don’t like this!
Somebody help!
‐ Calm yourself down Milfeulle.
(girl yelling)
According to data we’ve
received from Forte,
it seems that the
spaceship has the
power to read
people’s intentions.
It’s my guess that
the spaceship has
intercepted your
thoughts and is now
acting to interfere
with the rescue mission.
‐ Well okay then.
I know!
‐ [Robot] Now what are those?
‐ Those meat buns
are scary looking.
‐ What are you talking about?
Those aren’t spicy
meat buns at all!
‐ I’m sorry for taking so long.
Look!
I brought you some apple pie.
‐ Now look you, what
are you doing here?
‐ What are you saying Ranpha?
I thought you liked apple pie.
‐ Why are you always
pulling this cute act
and trying to make yourself out
to be some kind of big star?
‐ [Milfeulle] What do you mean?
‐ [Robot] You think we should
just let them have it out?
‐ [Mint] I think we
should be thinking about
how we’re going to
get out of this place.
It looks like another column of
numbers is showing
on this monitor.
And they’re getting bigger too.
‐ [Ranpha] How’s this?
And that?
‐ Now Ranpha, you know if
you keep eating like that,
you’re going to turn into a pig.
‐ [Robot] Or a cow maybe.
(girl yells)
‐ Ranpha’s turning into a pig!
‐ Now they’ve stopped.
‐ [Ranpha] I’m gonna get you!
And you.
‐ Now they’re going back up.
‐ And get you again!
‐ [Robot] My 10,000
gigahertz CPU!
‐ Now they’ve stopped.
And now they’re going up again.
Could this possibly mean?
(clock ticking)
I’ve got it!
‐ Hey, wait a minute.
This number is my
exact desired weight.
I’ve got an idea.
Do you think this
spaceship could
actually be some kind of giant
diet, fitness, and
training machine?
‐ My moment of brilliant
realization ruined.
‐ What?
Then are you saying that those
ghost monsters were
only chasing us around
to make us run and exercise
so much that we’d lose wight?
Now I get it!
(girl laughs)
Wait a minute!
Are you trying to tell us that
this means we can’t
get out of here
until we reach our ideal
physical fitness condition?
‐ I think that’s
what this means.
‐ If that’s what you mean,
then considering
I just gorged out
on several giant meat buns,
I’m in big trouble, hear?
‐ Alright then, let’s
blow ourselves to bits!
‐ No!
Forte stop!
Don’t you dare use that bomb!
(girls yelling)
‐ I guess that
we’ll have to just
keep running until
we see an exit.
It’s our only choice.
‐ I can’t believe
that I’m losing weight
just trying to stay alive.
‐ Alright then, let’s just
all blow ourselves to bits.
‐ [Ranpha] But
that’s even worse.
‐ [Mint] This isn’t good.
We received a box
from a courier.
‐ [Ranpha] I don’t
know, what is it?
‐ [Mint] We opened
the box and there’s
a mysterious object inside.
‐ [Ranpha] What is it?
‐ [Mint] The mysterious
object suddenly grows.
It grows until it takes
the form of a human.
‐ [Ranpha] Wait a minute.
‐ [Mint] And it’s
completely naked.
(girl screams)
(upbeat music)