(trumpet fanfare music)
‐ Three.
Four.
(Mint scoffs)
‐ [Robot Players] Hey pitcher,
you couldn’t hit
the side of a bus.
(ball whooshes)
‐ Strike!
‐ Wow, so close.
‐ Come on, you can do it.
Give it your best shot.
‐ [Umpire] Strike.
‐ (laughs) Yeah.
Yeah, two more, that’s
it, just two more.
‐ Don’t worry about it, Mint.
‐ [Colonel Roger] Hey,
hey, hey, who’s gonna wear?
‐ What’s with him?
What a creep.
‐ Yeah, he’s got some
pretty strange tastes.
‐ What?
Is he going to put
on that lingerie?
‐ My beautiful moo‐moo.
‐ Okay, stop that.
Hey, colonel, do these Space
Navy guys really get off on
this kind of baseball game?
(colonel stammers)
‐ Yeah, they do.
But us, we’re not
into this at all.
‐ [Forte] And this
score is ridiculous.
(ball whooshes)
‐ Strike!
‐ [Ranpha] And the four of
us don’t even play baseball,
and we’ve got three
robots on our team,
‐ [Forte] And one stuffed toy.
‐ [Mint] Will somebody tell
me why we’re in this game?
(colonel stammering)
‐ (gulps) Well, well, I.
(sirens blaring)
("Galaxy Bang!
Bang!" by Angel‐tai)
(singing in foreign language)
‐ [Milfeulle] Glazed
Baseball and Negligee.
‐ [All] What?
‐ You mean if we lose this game,
we’ve all got to go out
drinking with that sleazeball?
‐ [Ranpha] Dressed in nothing
but those skimpy nighties?
(Colonel Roger singing)
‐ Forgive me,
I made a stupid promise to him
in a moment of carelessness.
‐ And if the Angel Brigade
wins against the Space Navy,
then what, colonel?
‐ Well, if we win,
then Colonel Roger will
dance naked for us.
(girls groan)
‐ As if we’d ever
want to see that.
‐ [Normad] Why don’t
you just tell him
he was drunk at the time,
and it’s all a misunderstanding?
‐ Yeah!
‐ Hey, that’s a great
idea, let’s do it.
‐ No, actually, he and I
have a written contract.
(girls groaning)
(Colonel Roger snickering)
If I break the promise,
then I will have to
retire from the military.
(groans)
Oh, right, if we lose the game,
the Angel Brigade will
also be consolidated
into the Space Navy.
‐ You mean, that screwball
would become our leader?
‐ That’s just gross.
‐ Oh, please forgive me.
‐ Hey, hey, where’s
the next batter?
Hurry it up!
Come on girls, who’s?
‐ Well then, we don’t have
a choice, we’ve got to win!
‐ [Forte] It’s 100 to nothing,
and we’ve only got
one chance at bat.
One shot left.
‐ We must win.
We absolutely must.
Otherwise, we’ll be wearing
those stupid negligees.
We will!
‐ Never!
‐ I’ve never worn
a negligee before.
I’d like too.
‐ [Mint] Milfeulle.
‐ Yes?
‐ By the time that happens,
we will no longer be
the Angel Brigade.
(Milfeulle groans)
‐ Let’s win this!
‐ [Normad] But it’s
100 to nothing,
one more out and it’s over.
We’ve all but lost this.
(bullet whooshes)
That’s my mouth.
‐ Enough of your useless talk,
think of some way
we can win this.
‐ [Normad] Come on,
that’s impossible.
Even with my 10,000
gigahertz CPU.
‐ Hey, wait.
‐ Huh?
I’m thinking, I’ve got an idea.
‐ Okay, why are
we wearing these?
‐ We might as well be
wearing the lingerie.
‐ That’s the whole idea.
Take a look over there.
Those Space Navy guys
are all distracted now,
they aren’t thinking
much about baseball.
I bargained for a 30 point
handicap for each run,
so we can win this
with four runs.
‐ Hey, good thinking.
‐ However, in exchange
for the handicap,
if we do lose the
game in the end,
you two have to give
them special service‐‐
‐ Huh?
‐ As part of the deal I made,
if you know what I mean.
‐ [Both] Special service?
‐ So, let’s all give
it our very best.
‐ Hey!
‐ Angel Brigade.
‐ [Forte and Ranpha]
What special service?
‐ [Normad] Come on.
‐ Normad, you get on base
even if it kills you.
‐ If you go out, I’ll get
you with a machine gun.
‐ [Normad] How rude.
I’ve got a perfect
record at bat.
Well, never mind those two,
I’m more worried about
my precious Vanilla.
What an undignified
position she’s been put in.
But if I strike out,
she’ll be put into a more
undignified situation.
Ooh, I’d like to see that.
Wait, I didn’t say that.
This hit, I dedicate
this one to you, Vanilla.
‐ So how are you
going to hit the ball,
if you can’t even swing the bat?
‐ [Normad] You don’t
understand, Ranpha,
batting is not so
much about power,
as it is about timing.
(ball thuds)
‐ [Umpire] Ball!
‐ [Normad] The moment the
pitcher releases the ball,
I shift my weight
to my pivot leg.
(ball thuds)
‐ [Umpire] Ball!
‐ [Normad] And the bat
will strike the ball.
(ball thuds)
(Normad grunts)
(Normad thuds)
‐ [Umpire] Dead ball!
‐ [Milfeulle] Normad,
that was incredible!
‐ [Mint] Four fouls,
and one dead ball,
that does give him a
perfect record at bat.
‐ [Girls] All right!
‐ Hey, don’t you worry,
this time we’re gonna
finish them off.
‐ Well, bring it on,
you’ll never strike me out!
Let’s see your best pitch!
‐ Okay!
‐ Come on, come on, come on!
I hit it.
Here I go!
‐ [Normad] Ranpha,
I can’t run my base!
‐ I’ll take care of you.
(Ranpha yells)
(Normad whooshes)
(player grunts)
‐ [Normad] Safe!
‐ Good work, Ranpha!
That was great!
‐ Now you all can see
the stuff I’m made of.
What are you looking at?
‐ A minor setback,
let’s finish this.
‐ Okay, it’s time
to get serious here.
Come on!
‐ Okay!
(ball whizzes)
‐ Bam!
(bat cracks)
(ball thuds)
(player groaning)
Sorry!
‐ [Normad] Oh no!
‐ I’m the new relief pitcher.
Time to get serious
about this too.
Special service, coming
right up. (laughs)
(girls screaming)
‐ Milfeulle, you
better hit this ball!
‐ Now let’s see some
of that luck of yours.
Come on!
‐ Roger.
What if I strike out?
‐ [Umpire] Strike!
‐ [Milfeulle] Oh,
if we lose here,
the Angel Brigade
will be through.
We can’t! (sobs internally)
‐ [Umpire] Strike two!
‐ Timeout!
Here, I’ve got a
little secret for you,
this chant will enable
you to hit the ball,
if you repeat it over and over.
‐ Hey, hurry it up!
‐ Okay, I’m almost ready.
‐ [Normad] Milfeulle, you
only have one pitch left.
I hope she hits it.
(Milfeulle chanting gibberish)
‐ I don’t know what that
was, but you are out.
(speaking gibberish)
(bat cracks)
(ball whizzes)
‐ [Normad] Wow, pop fly!
‐ No!
‐ Yes!
‐ [Player] Got it, got it!
‐ It’s in God’s hands.
‐ I got it, I got it.
‐ No, I got it!
‐ Oh no, I got it!
‐ I got it!
(players thud)
‐ Am I safe?
Does this mean
I’m gonna be safe?
‐ [Normad] Milfeulle,
you’ve got to run!
‐ Okay!
‐ All right!
Let’s go, Normad.
‐ [Normad] All right!
‐ Not so fast.(grunts)
‐ Here’s my lightning kick!
‐ Uh‐oh.
(kick thuds)
(player groans)
(Ranpha whooshes)
‐ That gives our team 60 points.
‐ That’s interference
with an infielder.
‐ What do you mean?
You want to make
something of it?
‐ Hang on a minute here,
I’m cutting you a lot of
slack ’cause you’re a girl!
‐ [Ranpha] Like hell you are!
How dare you!
‐ [Colonel Roger] You can
take this up with Volcott.
(ground rumbles)
(Ranpha screams)
‐ What the?
‐ A missile?
(missile beeps)
‐ [Normad] Is that you, grandpa?
‐ Grandpa?
‐ [Normad] Yes, the
NX 1855 Type Missile,
it’s an attack missile two
generations older than me.
‐ So, this is your grandfather?
‐ [Normad] Yes.
‐ I’d say it’s more
like your grand dud.
(missile beeps)
What’s that?
‐ [Normad] He saying,
"I am not a dud.
"I am an active NX
1855 Type Missile.
"A sleeping lion who’s time
of awakening has come."
(metal rattles)
(thrusters whooshing)
‐ No! Wait!
‐ [Normad] Oh, I forgot
to mention something,
my grandfather has
an attack system
that can identify key
commanders in the field.
Simply put,
it goes after the most
important officer in range.
In other words, you.
‐ What?
No!
‐ [Normad] Oh, yes,
Commander Volcott,
since you are also a
colonel like Roger,
you will be targeted as well.
‐ Huh?
Oh no!
(Roger groaning)
(missile whooshes)
‐ [Forte] There.
‐ I’m home!
(colonels yelling)
(missile whooshing)
Yay!
This means we win!
‐ Now this crazy game is over,
let’s get out of here.
‐ Yeah, let’s.
‐ [Mint] I wonder how long
those two are going to last.
‐ [Vanilla] They’ll
reap what they’ve sown.
‐ [Milfeulle] Uh oh.
(missile booms)
‐ [Normad] Grandfather,
that was a glorious ending.
(ground rumbles)
Huh?
What?
(ground rumbles)
(colonels groaning)
‐ I thought I was going to die.
‐ Me too.
(thrusters whooshing)
(colonels gasp)
‐ [Normad] What?
A TMAX 5000 Special?
That’s little Tama,
my childhood sweetheart.
Who’d have thought
I’d find her here?
(thrusters whooshing)
(missiles whoosh)
Run for cover everyone!
‐ [Forte] Why?
‐ [Normad] Little
Tama’s the jealous type.
She’s angry that I’m
around other women.
(girls screaming)
The moral of the story is,
it’s very dangerous
for good kids
to hang around training grounds
where grown‐ups play baseball.
‐ [Forte] What’s taking so long?
‐ [Mint] Sure is late.
‐ [Ranpha] Very late.
‐ [Milfeulle] Yes, it is.
‐ [Normad] Really late.
(Angel Brigade chattering)
(Horoscope Rhapsody"
by Angel‐tai)
(singing in foreign language)