(birds chirping)
(woman sighs)
‐ [Forte] Another
coffee, please.
‐ [Ranpha] And a
chili dog for me.
(bell chimes)
Is that actually
your seventh coffee?
‐ [Forte] And how many
chili dogs have you had?
(Ranpha munching)
‐ Forte,
exactly what do you
think the real purpose
of the Galaxy Angel Brigade is?
‐ Nobody ever told
us when we joined up
that we’d be picking
up after everyone
and walking their dogs.
‐ Last time it was babysitting,
and before that it was
cleaning the pig pen.
‐ Now we’re looking
for a lost cat.
We better reassess our goals
or we’ll lose our
focus completely.
‐ [Ranpha] We sure have
been unlucky lately.
‐ What?
You’re still not there yet?
I need to know you current
position right away.
‐ Current position, the Galaxy
Angel Brigade recreation area
in the cafeteria.
‐ Dimwit.
‐ [Captain**] Listen
up everyone, we’ve
got some work to do.
‐ [Both] Yes, sir.
Angel Brigade reporting.
‐ Forte Stollen.
‐ And Ranpha Franboise.
‐ [Both] Are
deploying immediately.
(siren blaring)
(ship whooshing)
(upbeat music)
(singing in a foreign language)
‐ [Ranpha] Resort‐style
Angel Preparation.
‐ [Forte] What was it again,
this fancy cat’s name?
‐ Baron Fitzgerald III.
He likes sitting in
the lap of beauty.
‐ So this cat likes sitting
in the lap of beauty, huh?
‐ [Woman] Milfeulle, can
you come here, please?
‐ Yes, I’m coming right away.
Now, don’t you go
anywhere, little Rollie.
(cat meows)
‐ Why, why?
What’s taking so long?
What could possibly
be the problem?
Haven’t we heard anything yet?
If we don’t find the Baron
soon I’m in big trouble.
‐ Unfortunately we haven’t
heard anything, sir.
(man uncontrollably weeping)
‐ No, wait, crying
won’t change anything.
I’ve got to think of something.
I’ve got to do something.
I know!
‐ A cat I see and
a cat I’ll find.
Lead us to Baron
Fitzgerald, please.
There!
(cat trills)
Here, little kitty.
Got ya!
(dramatic music)
You’re ours!
(laughs) We’ll that was an
easy job, wasn’t it, Forte?
(cat purrs)
Huh?
‐ Maybe not, Ranpha.
Take a look around you.
Don’t ask me why, but
you’re surrounded by cats.
‐ And which one is
Baron Fitzgerald?
‐ Ha, easy mission, you say?
Well we can’t let a
single one of these cats
get away from us.
‐ I hope you enjoy
your drinks, guys.
Oh no!
Get down before you
make a big mess.
‐ That’s okay.
Don’t worry about it.
I really like cats
if you wanna know.
‐ Oh, is that right?
This is my cat, Rollie.
He likes to roll
around in my lap
so I call him Rollie and‐‐
‐ [Customer] So you’re
saying this is your cat?
‐ Yes.
I was sitting on the
bench the other day
and he suddenly jumped
up right into my lap.
(paw whooshes)
(man grunts)
(Milfeulle screams)
(upbeat music)
‐ What can you see?
‐ Cats all over the
place, lots of them.
And another one.
Keep going, don’t stop now.
‐ [Woman] Hey!
‐ [Forte] Yes!
(upbeat music)
‐ Huh?
There you are.
(cat yowling)
(leaves rustling)
(Forte screams)
(cats meowing)
‐ [Ranpha] One more.
‐ [Forte] Another one!
(upbeat music)
‐ [Ranpha] Hey!
(cats mewing)
(Forte huffing)
(both sighing)
(upbeat music)
‐ Oh, Ranpha, we have
to pick up the pace
or we’ll never get ahead.
‐ Yeah, that’s for sure.
Look!
‐ Stop, thief!
‐ Hey, I was going to
win that contest anyway
so what’s the problem?
‐ Well, no matter
who the winner is
we’ve still got an
awful lot of work to do.
(Ranpha cheers)
‐ [Ranpha] Ah, yeah!
(upbeat music)
(engine rumbles)
‐ Well, Ranpha, now
we’re zookeepers.
‐ You’re right.
I’ll bet we’ve got,
like, 40 of them.
Huh?
Oh, and hey, look, Forte,
here’s another one.
‐ Rollie!
‐ Who are you?
‐ This is my cat.
I want my Rollie back.
‐ Rollie?
This one likes to
curl up in my lap.
I wonder if he’s
Baron Fitzgerald.
‐ No, he’s Rollie!
‐ You.
I’ll take you.
‐ Ow, you’re hurting me.
Ow, stop.
‐ Don’t pull so hard.
‐ It’s not your cat.
‐ Let go of him.
‐ I said it’s not your cat.
(metal thuds)
(Milfeulle screams)
(laser blasts)
(Ranpha screams)
‐ Get down!
(tires screech)
‐ Ah, damn.
Assassination attempt failed.
Let’s go to plan B.
‐ [Man] Roger.
‐ Hey, what’s your name?
‐ Milfeulle, and I’m 17.
Oh, and I really like to cook.
‐ I’m not asking that.
I want to know who that
was shooting at you.
‐ Well, I don’t have any idea.
‐ Oh, Ranpha.
‐ Huh?
‐ [Forte] What’s going on?
You haven’t been toying
with some boy, have you?
You’ve got that look.
‐ Well,
maybe I should ask you the
same question, Forte Stollen.
Why so quiet all
of a sudden, huh?
(car bangs)
(girls scream)
(tires screech)
(metal clanging)
(girls grunting)
‐ Are you guys okay?
‐ I think so.
‐ We’re okay.
‐ I wouldn’t be so sure.
Don’t any of you make a move.
‐ Hey, it’s the cat lover.
‐ So, Milfeulle, you’re
the one he’s after.
‐ Told ya, it’s boy trouble.
‐ Be quiet.
We’re in charge here, okay?
‐ [Milfeulle] I
want my Rollie back.
‐ Sorry, to disappoint you
but that cat’s name is
Baron Fitzgerald III.
Now that we have what we want,
we just need to deal
with the three of you.
‐ Well, if you’ve
got what you want
what do you care about us?
‐ Hey, we can’t let
them keep Baron.
‐ Well, we could but,
as far as I can tell
we’re still on assignment.
(Ranpha gasps)
(thug grunts)
‐ Run for it!
‐ Get them!
(guns blasting)
‐ Don’t stop!
These guys are really scary!
(gun fires)
(metal clangs)
‐ Are you guys okay?
‐ I think so.
Hey, you, still alive?
‐ Yeah, I’m okay.
Wow, I’m alive.
(men grunting)
‐ Hey, do you always
take chances like that?
‐ I just happen to
have very good luck.
Wait, you’ll see.
‐ What are you talking about?
You and your good
luck have gotten us
within an inch of our lives.
Are you listening to me?
‐ Looks like all of
our luck just ran out.
‐ You could have made it
easier on yourselves, you know?
But have it your way.
We’re taking the cat
and you’re through.
(trigger clicks)
(bazooka booms)
(missile whooshing)
(missile pops)
(metal clanks)
‐ Huh?
‐ You see?
Luck is on our side.
‐ Huh?
No way, it’s a dud.
I think this is yours!
(men screaming)
(missile booms)
(rocks cracking)
(water splashes)
(women chuckling anxiously)
Hey,
could this be that luck
you were talking about?
‐ Well, maybe.
(speaking in a foreign language)
(cat meowing)
Rollie?
You mean you were
a girl all along?
(Rollie meows)
Rollie!
What’s the matter with you?
(dramatic music)
Rollie, don’t go!
Please!
Rollie!
‐ [Man] Are you telling
me then, Baron is dead?
‐ [Ludwig] Yes,
I’ve had everything
completely checked out.
I have gathered you
all here to inform you
that the family cat, Baron
Fitzgerald III is dead.
And according to father’s
last will and testament,
as the heir I am to
receive all company assets.
‐ [Angel Brigade] Excuse us.
‐ Angel Brigade reporting.
‐ Baron Fitzgerald
did not pass on
without leaving
something for you.
‐ Who are you and
why are you here?
‐ Your cat’s name lives on.
Presenting Baron Fitzgerald
IV, and his sisters.
‐ You’re not interfering
here in any way.
‐ We Angels finish what
we start, Mr. Ludwig.
And you can be
sure that it’s you
who won’t be interfering now.
‐ Huh?
‐ Wait, Ludwig, there’s more.
Your father’s will also says
that if Baron Fitzgerald III
were to have offspring,
they would become
the rightful heirs.
‐ (sobs) No, no, that can’t be.
‐ Wow, aren’t you
the lucky kittens?
Huh?
And you assassins, I can see
you’ve been well taken care of.
‐ Hey, I don’t know anything.
‐ [Forte] I’ll leave
the rest to you, okay?
(upbeat piano music)
Sorry to drag you into all this.
‐ [Milfeulle] It’s okay.
It’s all for Rollie.
But are you sure I’m to
have some of the money?
‐ Yeah, don’t worry about it.
‐ She’s right about that.
We got some of that money too.
‐ I see.
‐ [Forte] Maybe this has all
been thanks to your luck.
‐ I sure hope so.
I guess I’ll be on my way then.
(money flutters)
Hey!
‐ Huh?
‐ What?
‐ Isn’t that a
little bit dangerous?
‐ [Forte] Uh‐oh.
(Ranpha screams)
‐ [Ranpha] I don’t think
this is a good idea, Forte.
‐ [Forte] Don’t worry
about it, leave it to me.
‐ But‐‐
‐ Quiet!
‐ [Ranpha] But.
‐ [Forte] Bring it
on, come on, come on!
(light midi music)
‐ [Woman] Forte, Ranpha,
where are you right now?
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)