(whirring and whooshing)
(alarm blaring)
(beeping)
(whooshing)
(dynamic pop music)
(singing in Japanese)
‐ Uh!
Hot!
But so very, very
delicious. (laughing)
‐ Oh.
So then I guess
Milfeuille is off today,
which can only mean that
the girl I saw this morning,
who was dressed to kill
must have been none other
than our fellow angel.
‐ Huh?
You mean you saw
her out on a date?
‐ You could say that.
‐ Uh.
‐ Well, she was
just with Normad.
‐ All dressed up?
‐ Yeah,
she won a couple of free coupons
for dinner at Marlo’s Restaurant
and she decided to
take Normad along,
so he could teach
her table manners.
‐ Dinner at Marlo’s?
Uh!
Darn, that girl
has all the luck.
‐ She may only be
going out with Normad,
but it’s still a
classy restaurant.
I’m envious too.
(light melodic music)
‐ [Normad] Now listen,
if you drop your fork,
don’t pick it up yourself.
‐ What happens if I drop
both forks? (laughing)
Should I eat with my hands?
‐ [Normad] No, you
call the waiter over
and ask him to
bring you a new set.
‐ Oh, you can get
seconds for silverware?
‐ [Normad] You might say that.
‐ Huh?
‐ [Normad] What’s the matter?
Hello?
(dynamic upbeat music)
What is it, what’s going on?
‐ Need some help?
‐ (laughing) I’d
like this and that
and that and this and that
and that there too, wow!
‐ [Normad] What are you doing?
‐ [Vendor] Here you go.
‐ [Normad] We can’t
just sit here like this
eating cake all night.
‐ But they’re so sweet!
Can’t you appreciate
just how wonderful
all these beautiful
confections taste?
The flavor of the butter, the
milk and the vanilla essence
meld together so deliciously,
it’s not just any cake shop,
that can pull this
off, you know.
‐ [Normad] What shop can then?
‐ Only a very special
cake shop can.
Mm, mm!
‐ Thanks for clarifying.
‐ Oh!
(gasping)
Oh my goodness!
This is a Grande Asche!
Well, isn’t it?
‐ Ah, ah, I‐‐
‐ There is no mistaking it,
it’s a legendary sweet pastry,
this recipe was thought
to have been lost
over 200 years ago!
Tell me, how on Earth
did you get this recipe?
‐ Ah, I, hm.
‐ [Pastry Robot] Quiet!
‐ Oh.
‐ Huh?
‐ [Pastry Robot] That’s
not a Grande Asche.
‐ Who are you?
‐ [Pastry Robot]
No one important.
‐ Oh, are you the one
who baked this cake then?
If you know that it’s not
really a Grande Asche,
you must know the real thing.
‐ [Pastry Robot] Perhaps.
‐ Wow!
This is incredible!
Will you teach me how
to make this cake?
Please, please, please,
please, please, please,
‐ Quiet!
‐ please, please,
‐ Be quiet!
‐ please, but you?
‐ [Pastry Robot] I’ll
show you how to make it.
‐ Yay!
So I’ll be your apprentice
for the day then?
‐ Apprentice?
‐ Yeah,
I want to learn by
practicing with you, master.
‐ [Pastry Robot] No.
‐ Oh, but why not?
‐ [Normad] Somebody’s
after you, am I correct?
‐ [Pastry Robot] You are.
(gasping)
‐ Oh!
(light suspenseful music)
Oh!
Argh!
‐ Oh.
‐ Argh!
Argh!
(dynamic music)
‐ [Pastry Robot]
Don’t follow me.
‐ But master, I want the recipe.
‐ [Normad] What’s
more important, a
recipe or your life?
‐ Argh!
My life!
‐ [Normad] Good choice.
(heavy breathing)
‐ [Pastry Robot] Why are
you still following me?
‐ I have to have that recipe.
Ooh!
(laughing)
(dynamic music)
‐ They’re gone.
‐ Where’d they go?
‐ Damn!
‐ I think we’re safe now.
‐ Shh!
‐ [Assassin Captain] Let’s
split up, we have to find them.
‐ [Assassins] Yes, sir!
‐ That was awesome!
(light suspenseful music)
‐ [Assassin Boss]
Who’s the girl?
‐ I don’t know, it’s possible
she’s just a tourist.
‐ Eliminate anyone
who gets in your way,
along with the target.
‐ Unfortunately quite a
few of the local residents
have spotted us
searching the area.
‐ I’ll report that there has
been a terrorist incident.
Getting rid of him
is our top priority.
‐ Roger, sir, we’ll expand
our assault immediately.
‐ [Assassin Boss] You do that,
I’ll join up with you later.
‐ Right.
‐ Hm.
‐ Having some
difficulty, are we?
‐ I’m very sorry, sir.
‐ [Mr. President] You
must do everything you can
to keep him from talking.
‐ I understand, this time I
will take care of it myself.
Just a few more
hours, Mr. President.
‐ Hm.
‐ That’s a convenient trick.
‐ [Normad] Now I understand
what you’re all about,
you’re a J2 model, aren’t you?
An ultra high‐level,
self‐functioning culinary robot.
‐ So master, should
I call you Mr. J2?
‐ [Normad] I heard it on
the news two weeks ago,
something about the robot cook
in the President’s mansion
escaping with stolen
secret documents.
‐ [Pastry Robot] I tell
you, I didn’t do it.
‐ [Normad] Then why
are they after you?
‐ [Pastry Robot] Because
I’ve come to learn
about the President’s
deep, dark secret.
(suspenseful music)
‐ Tonight we have a
report, that there’s been
a violent, armed terrorist
assault in District 14.
The government is taking
this very seriously,
imposing a curfew in the area
and deploying military forces.
We have heard that
the government
has just recently
regained control,
but as the damage caused by
the incident is considerable,
it will take some
time to stabilize.
‐ Uh!
We almost died.
‐ [Normad] We should have died.
It must be quite the
deep, dark secret.
‐ Oh,
oh, I’m hurt.
(light melancholic music)
‐ [Pastry Robot] How
about we have a rest here?
(gasping)
‐ [Normad] So this is where
dinner was supposed to be.
‐ Well, I guess dinner’s
canceled tonight.
‐ A restaurant?
‐ Someone saw them go in.
‐ [Normad] I’m not
sure if you understand,
but I don’t think this
is the time for this.
‐ Well, with cooking,
it’s much easier
to remember everything, when
you’re actually doing it.
‐ [Pastry Robot] We’re
almost done anyway.
Let’s just finish it off.
‐ Oh, thank you so much.
‐ [Pastry Robot] I’m
turning myself in now.
‐ Huh?
‐ Oh, nothing.
Let’s finish the cake.
‐ Right.
(light melodic music)
‐ [Pastry Robot] Good,
now the finishing touches.
‐ [Assassin Boss] Freeze!
‐ Huh?
‐ I have no idea how you
managed to survive our assault,
but your good luck is over now.
‐ Argh!
‐ Fire!
‐ Master, no!
Master!
(thudding crunch)
Master?
(crying)
(beeping)
‐ All the data is just fine.
‐ [Milfeuille] Really?
‐ Yes, it was all recovered.
‐ [Mr. President] What?
How did this happen?
‐ I guess the J2
memory survived intact.
They want 100
million GCs for them.
‐ Well, what are you looking at?
‐ Huh.
‐ So what
if we like to dress
up for a bit of fun?
Got a problem with that?
Well, answer me!
Wait, don’t go!
Can you believe that?
‐ Oh.
(crowd chattering)
‐ Oh, I’m sorry, there’ll
be a little bit of a wait,
because it’s such a
popular item, okay.
‐ [Hostess] Chef, how is the
Grande Asche coming along?
‐ [Pastry Robot] I told you
to refer to me as master.
‐ [Hostess] Yes, master.
‐ [Pastry Robot]
(sighing) It’s done.
(light melodic music)
‐ [Milfeuille] Ta da!
Here’s the scoop on
the next episode.
A guy that Forte and Ranpha
met on an uninhabited island.
(electricity buzzing)
What?
It must be some
sort of radio jammer
and a really strong one.
(dynamic pop music)
(singing in Japanese)