Kuroyukihime: The year is 2046,
a world where people manage their daily lives
on the virtual network with a portable,
wearable device called the neuro-linker.
One day, Haruyuki, a boy who was constantly bullied,
received a program from Kuroyukihime,
the most popular girl in his school.
( over neuro-link ) What I'm about to do
is send you an application.
I'm sending it directly to your neuro-linker.
( Haruyuki gasps )
Kuroyukihime: This program made it possible
to reinvent one's reality.
♪
It was called \"Brain Burst.\"
Haruyuki: \"Welcome to...
the Accelerated World\"?
Kuroyukihime: \"Brain Burst\"
accelerated the brain's processing speed
one thousand times faster than normal.
( over neuro-link ) Now shout it!
Burst Link!
Haruyuki: B-B-Burst Link!
Kuroyukihime, narrating: Or, to put it another way,
it made one second feel like one thousand.
( Avatar squeals )
Kuroyukihime: After learning the secret
of the Accelerated World,
the young boy vowed to fight by Kuroyukihime's side.
Want to accelerate?
Want to take this further, young man?
This, then, is the story of a boy
with the potential to become the fastest being ever.
Ash: I'm about ready to make you dance
to the beat of my bike!
Let's roll!
Kuroyukihime: In order to accelerate,
one must do battle with others and win Burst Points.
If a person loses all of their Burst Points,
\"Brain Burst\" will automatically uninstall itself
and can never be reinstalled.
Also, the person will lose
their memories of being a Burst Linker.
( Ash laughs )
Haruyuki: If this is just like the real world,
then that bike's gotta have a weak point.
( gasps )
- That's it. - ( Ash cackles )
Ready to dance some more?!
Haruyuki: Just this once, Silver Crow, move for me!
We gotta be faster than him!
Even if I can't believe in myself...
( yells )
Kuroyukihime: The key here is your heart.
It's what made that body.
You must believe in yourself, Haruyuki.
Ash: You really think a little shit stain like you
can stop a monster bike like this?
Haruyuki: I can at least believe
in everything she's said!
Almost there.
Okay, here I go!
- Avatars: Whoa! - ( Ash growls )
What the hell is this?!
Kuroyukihime: To continue to accelerate,
a person must win as many battles as possible.
Here's to your first victory.
At this rate, you'll reach Level Two in no time.
Haruyuki: Uh, yeah, thank you,
but I still have a lot to learn before getting that far.
Kuroyukihime: You do have a hard journey ahead of you.
Of the estimated 1,000 Burst Linkers
that are out there,
only a select few have ever made it to Level Four.
And if you run into a player from Level Seven or Eight,
it's safe to assume they're a Legion leader.
Haruyuki: W-What's a Legion?
Kuroyukihime: It's sort of like a team
that you would find in other online games.
It's just that here, we call them Legions.
Currently the Accelerated World has six major Legions
ruling over a number of different zones.
All these Legions are led
by Burst Linkers who have reached Level Nine.
Each has their own color--
blue, red, yellow, green, purple, and white.
They're known as the Six Kings of Pure Color.
Haruyuki: I've never heard of a game like this,
where only six people have ever reached the highest level.
Kuroyukihime: Not so fast.
I never said Level Nine was the highest level.
Haruyuki: Well, how many people are at Level Ten, then?
Kuroyukihime: \"Brain Burst 2039\" is something
people have been playing for seven years now,
ever since the program was anonymously released,
but due to the severe rules that come with the game,
no one has ever reached Level Ten.
Haruyuki: Is that because you have to fight all the time,
have, like, 10,000 wins or something?
Kuroyukihime: You only need five wins,
but those wins have to be against Level Nine opponents,
and if you lose just one of those fights,
you lose all your points,
and then the program automatically uninstalls.
Two years ago, all the young Kings
reached Level Nine at approximately the same time.
They soon received a system message
telling them the horrible rules in place for reaching Level Ten.
You would have expected
some sort of bloody power struggle to break out,
but instead the Kings chose
to remain at Level Nine indefinitely.
They called a truce and divided the Accelerated World
into realms each of them would rule.
The whole thing's a farce.
First they destroy countless Burst Linkers
to reach Level Nine, and then they create a truce? Why?
Haruyuki: So is that it? Is that what you're planning,
to challenge the Six Kings of Pure Color?
Kuroyukihime: No.
- I've already done that. - Haruyuki: What?
Kuroyukihime: There haven't always been six.
There used to be seven Kings,
and despite the fact that they were each essentially rivals,
there was also a strong bond between them.
But that changed two years ago.
One night, the Black King betrayed the others
and tried to hunt them all down.
Haruyuki: Who is this Black King?
Kuroyukihime: I'm the Black King,
otherwise known as Black Lotus.
I was the only one who rejected the truce
and instead argued that we should risk it all
and fight to the end.
( narrating ) Kuroyukihime was a wanted person
in the Accelerated World, but to her surprise, one day,
she was challenged to a duel while on the school's network,
( footsteps echoing )
She asked Haruyuki
to help her uncover the identity of Cyan Pile,
the blue Duel Avatar who was stalking her.
The prime suspect came as quite a shock...
Chiyuri Kurashima, Haruyuki's childhood friend.
Haruyuki: Uh...
- ( Chiyuri moans ) - Haruyuki: sorry.
( gasps )
Kuroyukihime: Believing his friend to be innocent,
Haruyuki cable linked with Chiyuri.
While searching through her neuro-linker's files,
he discovered something, a virus.
( Haruyuki gasps )
What was that lag about?
( beeping )
Hold on!
This is a back door program!
( rattling )
Both: Burst Link!
Kuroyukihime: Araya, the boy who was bullying Haruyuki,
tried to run him down.
After accelerating,
Kuroyukihime decided to confess her feelings to Haruyuki.
I suppose I deserve this.
It's punishment for toying with the lives of others
without caring how it affects them.
( Haruyuki crying ) Yeah, but...
Kuroyukihime: There's no reason to cry.
I have to say at least there's one positive thing
coming from all this.
Haruyuki: Like what?
Kuroyukihime: In a dire moment like this,
I think you might actually believe my final words.
At least, I hope so.
Haruyuki...
please know that I love you.
I've never felt this way about anyone,
and it's been very confusing for me.
I'm constantly thinking about you,
and these thoughts I have make me both happy and sad.
I guess that's just what being in love does to you.
Work hard. Get stronger and faster.
Climb your way to the top,
and see the world from there in my place.
Haruyuki: No! Don't! You can't leave me like this!
I'm the one who's supposed to protect you,
but I haven't.
I haven't done anything for you.
♪
Kuroyukihime: It's okay.
I'm sure we'll meet again someday.
Haruyuki: No! Please don't do this!
Please!
- Stop! - ( crashing )
♪
Kuroyukihime: Kuroyukihime sacrificed herself
to save Haruyuki, and now she was in critical condition.
Unconscious, she could not defend herself
against an attack by Cyan Pile.
Haruyuki: No. I won't let that happen.
I'll protect you.
( gasps )
Kuroyukihime: The next morning,
his best friend Takumu came to pay a visit.
Haruyuki: What? Taku?
Is he here visiting?
Taku!
Wait. Why is he here?
Takumu: Huh? ( chuckles )
( Haruyuki gasps )
Both: Burst link!
♪
Haruyuki: No way. That's Takumu?
He's Cyan Pile?!
So you're the one who installed a virus in Chiyu's neuro-linker,
spying on her, checking her memory and viewer apps
whenever you wanted!
Takumu: Weren't you poking around in her memory, too?
And you're not even her boyfriend!
But, hey, who gets chicks anyway?
You know, when I think about it,
Chi always did seem happier trying to take care of you
than she ever did going out with me.
It's always been like that, and I've hated it!
( Haruyuki yelps )
( gasping )
( gasps )
Takumu: This was inevitable, Haru.
Spiral Gravity Driver!
( Haruyuki yells )
Kuroyukihime: Takumu's Avatar, Cyan Pile, was Level Four.
At Level One, Silver Crow was no match.
Even so, Crow tried to protect Kuroyukihime,
and then...
Haruyuki: Senpai.
That's right.
Strength isn't just about winning.
Even if my attacks are ridiculous and pathetic,
even if I'm left lying in the mud
crushed and defeated,
as long as I don't quit, keep fighting,
keep looking up at the sky,
that's what really matters.
That's what true strength is!
Kuroyukihime: Silver Crow's true potential awakened.
Haruyuki: Are these wings?
Aah! It burns!
It's calling for me.
♪
Let's go. Hyah!
Takumu: Huh?
Kuroyukihime: His aviation ability
was the first of its kind.
Takumu: Take this!
Lightning Cyan Spike!
( Haruyuki yells )
Takumu: Haru!
Haruyuki: Taku!
Kuroyukihime: And I know that someday
the rest of the Accelerated World will know this as well,
that you are the fastest Linker to ever exist,
and by doing that, you will unlock the true potential
that lies deep within our minds and souls.
Haruyuki: I see it. I finally see it!
( Takumu gasps )
- ( armor clinks ) - ( Haruyuki gasps )
- ( gasps ) - Takumu: You win.
I'm sorry, Haru.
( Haruyuki gasps )
- ( Takumu gasps ) - ( sparks popping )
Haruyuki: In the real world,
you're better than me at everything,
but here, that isn't the case.
You can't beat me.
Now you and I are truly equals,
so stop trying to fight against me, and fight with me!
- Become my ally, Taku! - ( Takumu gasps )
Fight under her command, just like I do.
Come on. Will you do it?
Takumu: How can you still trust me?
I've betrayed everyone,
my Legion, \"Brain Burst.\"
I even betrayed the only two real friends I've had.
Haruyuki: That's why we need to tell Chiyu everything.
We'll tell her about \"Brain Burst,\"
about our fight.
We'll come clean.
We'll even tell her about all the feelings
you and I have kept buried all these years.
We can start fresh,
a chance to build our friendship all over again.
♪
( gasps )
( grunting )
Is that...
really you?
Senpai!
Oh, thank God.
I believed in you.
I knew you'd make it.
Kuroyukihime: You've taken so much damage.
Thank you, Haruyuki.
Haruyuki: Actually, the only reason I could do it
was because you told me to believe in myself.
Kuroyukihime: Look at this,
the real you. It's beautiful.
I'm glad to see my instincts were right about you all along.
Haruyuki, you're the one's who's going to change this world.
The time has come.
I must leave my peaceful cocoon and aim for the sky once again.
( Haruyuki gasps )
♪
Kuroyukihime: To all Burst Linkers
serving under the Six Kings, hear me!
I am Black Lotus,
the one who rebelled against your Kings's rule!
Me and my Legion, the Nega Nebulous,
have emerged from hiding to put an end to this ridiculous truce!
( narrating ) The news of Silver Crow's aviation ability,
along with the revival of Nega Nebulous,
spread quickly through the Accelerated World.
Then, three months later...
( aloud ) Listen carefully, Haruyuki.
The right to control a territory is decided every Saturday night
with a turf war between the Legions.
The Legions go against each other
with the same number of fighters,
regardless of their level.
To win, they must maintain
a winning percentage of 50% or higher.
Go on. We can take care of this.
( Takumu grunts ) We're counting on you, Haru!
Take 'em out with your usual attack!
Haruyuki: You got it!
Kuroyukihime: Nega Nebulous, now with Cyan Pile,
secured the Suginami area around the school
with only three members,
but conquering further territories was difficult.
Silver Crow's aviation ability, his biggest strength,
was vulnerable to long-range attacks,
keeping him from advancing past Level Four.
Haruyuki: Damn it!
Avatar: That move's gettin' a little old, don't you think?
Once people have seen it a few times
and figure out what it is, it makes you an easy target.
Haruyuki: Even so...
I have to try.
I want to get stronger!
Niko: Welcome home, brother.
Haruyuki: Wait. What?!
( gasps )
( Niko giggles )
♪
Haruyuki: She an angel?
( Niko giggles )
Haruyuki: Is this some kind of heavenly vision?
Kuroyukihime: Out of nowhere, a girl appeared
and claimed to be Haruyuki's distant cousin.
Niko: I hope you don't mind
that I used your kitchen without asking,
but I thought you might be hungry,
so I went and whipped up a batch of these for you.
Um, 'scuse me.
( Haruyuki gasping ) Ah, Crap!
Niko: Would you mind if I came in there and joined you?
Takumu: Okay, I'll get out now!
I'm sorry that you had to wait, but just give me a minute!
Niko: Look, we're cousins. It's really not a big deal.
Haruyuki: Uh, I don't know!
I kinda think that it is a big deal!
Huh?
Niko: But please don't stare at me like that.
It makes me uncomfortable.
( Haruyuki sighs )
Tomoko.
Niko: Yep, that's me. What is it?
Haruyuki: Okay, drop the act.
You're a new Burst Linker, aren't you?
- Niko: Huh? - Haruyuki: Look.
You've got tan marks on your neck.
( Niko gasps )
( sighs )
( Haruyuki gasps )
Niko: I can't believe you did all that digging around.
You are way too suspicious. You know that?
Enough of this crap.
You listen to what I have to say, and you listen good.
You've just insulted me, Scarlet Rain,
and because of that, I'm gonna make you pay!
( yelps )
( Haruyuki gasps ) Watch out!
( both gasping )
♪
( both screaming )
Niko: You're so dead.
( grunts )
Kuroyukihime: The girl was in fact
the Red King, Scarlet Rain.
She had figured out Haruyuki's identity in the real world
and broke into his home.
Haruyuki: Um, are you seriously the Red King?
( Niko chuckles )
♪
( Haruyuki gasps )
Niko: Hailstorm Domination!
Haruyuki: Here goes nothin'!
Silver Crow's All Or Nothing Kick!
( yelling )
( Niko chuckles )
( Haruyuki gasps )
( groaning )
( gasps )
Niko: Looks like I win.
Give up?
Haruyuki: Yeah. I surrender.
Niko: So will you listen to my request now?
Haruyuki: What request?
Niko: I want to meet your Legion master in real life,
the two of us in the flesh.
Kuroyukihime: So what is it
that made you want to meet Haruyuki that badly?
Had you perhaps, fallen in love with him?
- ( Niko gags ) Hell, no! - ( Haruyuki yelps )
Niko: I couldn't care less about this fatso.
What I want is his Avatar.
Silver Crow, I want to borrow your wings,
your ability to fly just once
so I can destroy the Armor of Catastrophe.
Haruyuki: Armor of Catastrophe?
♪
Kuroyukihime: What you're seeing is a VR movie
of a memory that I recorded 2 1/2 years ago.
The Armor of Catastrophe, also known as Chrome Disaster,
seven years ago, it committed atrocities
with its devastating abilities.
The strongest Linkers at the time defeated it,
but they failed to destroy its Enhanced Armament.
Like a parasite, it possessed one of the Burst Linkers
and turned him into a bloodthirsty killer.
Then it possessed another and another.
This here...
was the fourth Chrome Disaster.
Niko: That thing looks absolutely nothing