[Yata]
Hey, it's me! This place is
humongous!
I'm gonna focus on
guarding the front.
That's all I can handle.
But to do that I'm
gonna need a few more
guys over here, okay?
Copy that. Right away.
Hey! You two,
go back up Yata.
Yes, Boss!
[Munakata]
Let me be very direct.
Just peacefully relinquish
control of this school.
I'll try to overlook the way
you've been involving innocent
pupils in your search but I
can't guarantee it.
I'm sure I needn't remind
you of the very precarious
shape your sword of Damocles
is in at the present time.
And because the sword is
a symbolic representation
of a king,
it always reveals the
truest impression of
the king's condition.
Sad to say, your
sword will come
crashing down soon.
Don't believe it.
I know that right now,
your Weismann level is
precariously close to
the edge.
If you take on the added
burden of killing a king,
it will certainly exceed
your limit.
You will cause a
repeat of the Kagutsu
Crater tragedy.
And you will have to give
up your right to be a king.
Why not step down now,
and avoid all this?
Mm?
Huh?
Mikoto?!
Oh...
Lieutenant.
Are we going in?
How about we use a boat or
a chopper to gain entry?
Either way, they'll
burn us alive.
How long do we stay
here biding our time?
[explosion]
That must be the
Red King again.
SCEPTER 4,
Prepare to move in!
Mm?!
- Huh?
- What's goin on?
- Hey!
- My gosh what is it?
- What's happening?
What's happening?
Here they come!
Yeah!
Bring 'em on!
Listen up, Mikoto Suoh
and Red Clan members!
Put your weapons down and
surrender immediately,
or face the consequences!
Now it's war!
Yeah!
Woo-hoo!
All right!
Well, Captain?
Your orders?
Miss Awashima.
I'm leaving you in charge
of this offensive.
We will advance
with our swords
in our hands!
We will triumph,
because our cause
is just.
Everyone,
draw your swords!
Akiyama, ready!
Benzai, ready!
Kamo, ready!
Domyoji, ready!
Enomoto, ready!
Fuse, ready!
Goto, ready!
Hidaka, ready!
Fushimi.
Ready to go!
They're going down!
C'mon! Let's do this!
[cheers]
- Yeah!!!
- All right!
No blood! No bone! No ash!
No blood! No bone!
No Ash-h-h!
[mob chaos]
[explosions]
What was that?
Careful, sir!
Help me,
please help!
Just as I thought.
This is a trick.
I can guess
who's behind it.
Heh heh hehe!
Well then, it's you.
Captain!
[bigger explosion]
What?
Shit! What the
hell's going on?
[Kusanagi]
The Blues must have
brought a cannon!
They're shelling the place!
[Masaomi]
Hey, Boss!
Do you know
where the King is?
[Kusanagi]
Don't worry,
he can take care
of himself!
I need you to get back out
there and tell Yata to focus on
getting rid of those Blues!
[explosion]
Ah!
Anna!
[fighting]
I see you.
[glass breaks]
Aah!
Anna!
[bullet shot]
Is she alive?
Yeah.
[relieved sigh]
Hm?!
Huh?!
He he he ha ha ha!
You bastard!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I'll get that
scumbag!
This isn't working.
[Kusanagi]
What the hell
is going on?
No. He can't go
on like this.
[running and screaming in panic]
This is horrible.
What's happening?
Heh heh!
Are you alright?
[Yashiro]
Kukuri!
Huh?!
I forgot, you probably
don't remember us.
No big deal.
It's alright, we're
really just here to help.
Let me give you
a hand up.
Kukuri!
Excuse me, I mean,
Miss Yukizome.
It's too dangerous here.
We need to get you
somewhere safe.
[Mikoto Suoh]
Looks like I've found you.
[gasps]
[hissing]
Anna's been shot.
One of those
assholes did it!
All Blues are bastards!
Let's kill every single
one of them!
[crowd]
Yeah!
Do we have any confirmation yet
that the Captain is all right?
Damn Reds!
They're so
ungrateful!
The Captain saves one of them
and they still want to kill us!
[Seri]
Just calm down!
Resume control!
SCEPTER Four excels
at group combat!
No one can ever come
close to defeating us!
Where are you, sir?
Hyaah!
Yatagarasu?!
Damn right! The time has
come to settle this, now!
[Yata]
Hey, look sharp!
Eyes on me!
Gotcha!
Guess again, Misaki!
You'll have to get
past me first!
Remember, pal, we have
unfinished business!
Monkey...
Fine, let's settle it, then!
[Kuroh]
Stay back.
You can drop the act.
I came all this way
for only one reason.
You summoned me out here.
So go ahead and admit it.
Yeah?
Step aside.
Hmh.
Eeyah!
Kuroh!
[scream]
Huh?!
Dammit. I know
what you're doing.
Nyah!
Cut it out.
Don't interfere again!!
That's it.
Go now!
Now I get it.
No wonder Yata had a
hard time with you.
Hmm.
Not bad. In fact,
I'd enjoy playing
with you some more,
If it weren't for the
anger that's boiling up
inside of me right now.
Listen, I won't
repeat myself again!
Step aside, you're in my way!
Kuroh!
Hm?
Hah.
I understand the
situation now.
Then we can cut
to the chase.
I just need you to
keep quiet and watch.
Kuroh!
Tch.
Munakata,
don't interfere!
[Yashiro]
We should be safe here for now!
Their inevitable battle
has just begun.
I don't get it! He wasn't
affected by my illusions!
I've got nothing
else to use!
I'm totally burned out!
Let's go.
C'mon, Shiro.
while those guys are
fighting with each other!
Now's our chance.
Let's run far away,
while we still can.
Neko...
C'mon! Now that we've rescued
Kukuri, we can take her with us.
But...
Sorry, I wish we had more
time to explain it to you.
Don't worry, though.
We'll find you some place
that's safer than this.
I'm fine here.
But wait!
You've been injured!
Huh?!
I'm alright.
It doesn't even hurt.
Let me see it.
Eh.
Eh he he he he!
Huh?!
[gasp]
[nasty giggle]
[pain gasp]
[Kuroh]
Kukuri... Why!?
Heh heh heh heh!
[Kukuri] [stronger tone]
I have to say, I wasn't
expecting you to escape the
airship explosion.
You won't... escape now.
[Neko]
What?!
[evil laugh]
[posessed Shiro]
It appears you truly
don't remember a thing.
How convenient is that?
Ah ha ha ha ha ha!
I suppose you've walked
away from all of your
responsibilities without
even realizing it.
Mmm he he he he he!
When you lost before, you ran
away because you wanted to
lead a peaceful existence.
And you almost got exactly
what you wished for.
Hee hee hee!
Deep down inside, you
want a life like the
one you're living now.
But you've had that
life many times before.
He he he he! That's fine,
I guess. I can't really
find fault with your choices.
But this time, your memory will
go to sleep, permanently.
He he! Relax and let your
body drift into the silence
and the peaceful serenity.
Into nothingness,
Nothingness, Nothingness!
I... I...
Are you running away?
[Neko]
Shiro...
Shiro... Shiro!
SHIROOO...!!!!
Damnit! What're you doing?
Hey!
Are you okay?
Uh!
Heh heh heh!
Kukuri!
Gotta run! See you later!
Heh heh!
[Neko]
Shiro!
Shiro! Please don't leave us!
[Kuroh]
Stay calm! Let me see if
I can bring him around.
The war is finally over.
This is goodbye,
Lieutenant.
Are you running away?
Weismann!?
[gasp]
Hey! Are you with us?
You know Munakata,
You need tomstop this.
I'm afraid I'm starting to
enjoy our fight too much.
It's kind of a shame you're
not the person I'm after.
Huh?
Whoa.
Wait, that's...!
Shit, what the
hell is that?
A streaming,
silver light.
Now what's that?
Looks like those Blues
just won't give up.
[Anna]
Who are you?
Weismann. That man always seems
to show up and surprise us.
What happened?!
That's odd.
Your wound
is healing.
Can you hear
us, Shiro?
Are you alright?
Macht nichts. Ich bin...
unverwundbar.
Endlich habe
ich verstanden.
Then you're truly
the Colorless King?
Mmm.
Mein Name.
I know now that my real name
is Adolph K. Weismann.
The First King,
which means,
I am the Silver King.
[Kuroh]
Master Ichigen, this
man is just hopeless.
He is lazy,
irresponsible, cowardly,
and lacks commitment.
Yet, I find myself
wanting to stand by his
side, and fight for him.
Forgive me Master Ichigen,
it appears I am the one who
is truly hopeless here.
[Neko]
Ha ha ha ha!
Kuroh thinks
he's hopeless!
[Kuroh]
I suppose it takes
one to know one.
[Neko]
Hmph! Well, I'm not like you.
I'm Shiro's Neko.
As long as he's with me,
I will fight for him!
[Kuroh] [sincere]
That's the spirit. Make sure
you stay that way, okay?
[Neko]
Huh?
[Kuroh]
It is time I make
my own decision.
[Neko]
In that case,
you'd better
get it right!
[Kuroh]
Yes, I plan to.
Next time on
"K," episode 12,
"Adolf-K-Weismann."
Please watch over me,
Master Ichigen.