DIE!
[Kuroh]
[humming]
Fold the omelet
quickly while the egg
is still half cooked.
The outside should
be a golden yellow.
[sleep mumbles]
Meow!
Yashiro Isana, I've
prepared lunch boxes
for you as requested.
Do not put lids on the boxes
until the contents have cooled.
The omelets are sweet and
covered with fluffy rice, but
let me know if you would prefer
Dashi egg rolls instead.
[awe]
Aaah!
Mmm!
(OM giggles as she dodges the
laser light)
What are you doing?
Keep your paws off!
DIE!
Hey don't throw that away!
It's my school bag!
DIE!
You think I'm a
piece of trash too?
SHOW SOME RESPECT!
You hillbilly samurai!
Raah! Stop bullying Shiro!
[choking]
KNOW YOUR PLACE!
This is no time
for games!
What are you planning
to do today?!
What're you
talking about?
Obviously I have
to go to school!
I have to turn in
my assignment for
my classical
literature class!
Shiro isn't trash!
HAVE MERCY!
I might have known.
You've forgotten
what you promised
to do last night!
I HAVE FAILED.
I have won!
[Kuroh]
Do you have any intention of
ever proving your innocence?!
Alright, class, let's continue
where we left off yesterday.
Overcome with curiosity, the
Goddess Amaterasu, opened
the Cave of Heaven slightly.
And saw her radiance reflected
in a mirror that had been set
up outside the entrance by the
Goddess Amanouzume.
then the God Amenotajikara
closed the cave so she
could not go back in.
I'm glad you can
spend time with
your friend, Shiro.
Yeah, it's great.
Mm?! And who might
you be, young man?
I am a vassal of the former
Seventh King, Ichigen Miwa,
Kuroh Yatogami.
What he's trying to say,
is that he's sort of a
recent transfer student.
You may continue
with your literary
selection now.
Heh...
If you say so.
[sigh]
...And the other
celestials watched as
Amatersu once again...
You are very kind.
Thank you again for
all your help.
Since you're going to
be in our class I guess
it would help if you
knew all our names.
My name is
Kukuri Yukizome.
You can just
call me Kukuri.
And your name is Kuroh.
Funny - in Japanese, Kuro means
'black' and Shiro means 'white',
like pieces on a game board!
Oh, and just ask if you
need any more help.
Thank you.
Stop!
Huh?
You're brazen,
but at least you look
decent this time.
Eh, heh heh heh...
Um, heh heh heh...
If I may interrrupt,
Just who might you be, Miss?
Well, she's sort of a
transfer student too.
You brought a complete
homemade lunch!
What happened?
Did you get married
or something?
Yes, my loving wife,
Kuroh, made everything.
I suggest you watch your mouth.
One more insult like that and
I'll cut out your tongue!
That was good!
I want some more!
I've got extra if you want it.
Bleh!
You brought a bunch
of vegetables!
Hey, where did
you get that?
It doesn't look like our
school-issued PDA.
It belongs to
my loving wife.
Say farewell to
your tongue.
Huh?!
So, any new leads?
No, not really.
This image is
just too blurry.
What are you
looking at?
Mmm?
Heh hah!
Hey, Shiro! Wanna take a
look at my latest download,
It's a pretty nasty piece.
You're really hooked
on that stuff,
aren't you?
Listen, I've gotta tell
you I'm not as interested
in pornography as you
think I am.
Like hell you're not!
And this clip isn't porn.
Check it out look!
Oh, wait, before you do!
You didn't tell Kukuri
about that porno I showed
you the other day, did you?
No, of course not.
Good. Okay, here we go.
Get ready, pal,
check this out.
He looks exactly
like you, Shiro.
You're right about that.
Looks like the jig is up.
It's time to call the Coppers,
You're toast!
Not funny. But I am
curious about my
look alike, Sota.
Could you forward
this to my e-mail?
It's a disturbing
video I got from Sota.
Oh, he sent
you that?
Then, others must have it.
Privacy's just a
thing of the past.
Stop slacking
off and help us.
I'm not slacking,
I'm expressing an
opinion.
According to this video,
the crime occurred on
December Seventh at 23:45,
on the Hirasaka building
rooftop in the West Precinct.
Tatara is really dead.
Lieutenant Awashima!
[Awashima]
Do we know where
the suspect is now?
We do. Give me a
moment to bring it up.
Ashinaka High School.
So he's on the school island.
The video that streamed
across the city was
time-stamped and dated.
It was the night of
December seventh at 23:45.
Given the distance
between the crime
scene and my school,
there is no way I could
have made it there and
back in an hour.
Which means?
Which means I could
prove my innocence!
If I can demonstrate I was
on campus on the Seventh
of December, around
23:45 in the evening,
I would have an alibi.
All I need are witnesses.
Let's be very clear
about your alibi.
You can't simply claim
you were sleeping
alone in your room.
Furthermore, I wouldn't accept
anything this one says about
your whereabouts, as an alibi.
Aaahh!
I'm the best
one to ask!
We've been together
since the moment we met,
we're inseparable!
I know that my Shiro
is a good guy.
Just be quiet.
I told you I
don't trust him.
If he can't prove his
innocence, and I find out you
played a part in this crime,
you will pay with your life.
I hope I'm making
myself clear.
Hey, everything
will be all right.
We were permitted to work at
the school that night on
preparations for the festival.
I'm beginning to remember.
All kinds of things were
going on that evening.
Things?!
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure someone will be
able to vouch for the fact that
I was at school that night,
doing a lot of work
for the event.
C'mon! So how much
longer are you guys
going to be back here?!
Wow! You look good! And quite
authentic, just like Ebisu,
the god of good fortune!
Although you're not as fat!
Mm!
I don't know who you're
supposed to be, but you
look beautiful!
I guess that's because
I really am beautiful!
Kukuri, do you
have a second?
I need to ask you about the
night of December Seventh.
Almost...
Here it is.
Huh?!
He goes to the school
on the Island?
It'll certainly be tough to
get him out of that place
without making a scene.
We have to play smart.
[door opening ring]
The hell we do!
Hm? Mm? Yata?!
Ugh, that idiot!
[shouting]
Ms. Kukuri Yukizome!
It was love at first sight!
I knew it had to be you from
the first minute I saw you.
Please be my girl!
No!
Huh?!
I'm sorry!
Heh heh!
[exaggerating]
My heart is broken!
I'm ruined for life!
That was one of the
things that happened.
Why did you
bring that up?
I just wanted
to forget it!
[recording]
The feeling of love.
A shower of fireworks.
It bursts, then fizzles.
Mm.
Creepy.
But that fireworks
show was awesome.
It happened just before
midnight, if I remember
correctly, right?
Around 11:45 pm,
to be more exact.
That sounds right.
But why is that
important?
It just is. I was there
watching it, remember?
[Kukuri]
Hmm, I don't know.
Maybe you were, but I'm
not absolutely positive,
now that I think about it.
You've got
to remember.
Well, I don't!
That was the last
thing on my mind!
It looks like that guy
is going to set off all
the festival fireworks!
Someone needs to drag
him down here quick!
Here comes the
Student Council!
Last chance
to come down!
Remove the door.
[Shiro]
During that whole
December night incident,
I was there and
witnessed everything.
Do you remember seeing me?
Don't recall.
I was too busy dragging that
idiot down off the roof to
notice anybody else.
Yes, I remember the
whole situation was
pretty messy.
In my opinion, if you
hadn't acted so swiftly,
who knows what might have
happened that evening?
Hey, why don't we check the
news articles from that day?
[Shiro]
Two photos and I'm not
in either of them.
Well, if you're looking for a
photo of yourself during the
commotion, why not talk to
someone at the school newspaper?
They were snapping plenty
of pictures that evening.
Yeah, that's right!
I know they were taking
tons of pictures of you,
while you dealt with one
issue after another as
our class president.
You are so good at what
you do, And there's
nothing that you can't do.
By the way,
you're busted.
I realize we're all
getting ready for the
school festival, but,
you can't continue to walk
around this campus dressed as
outlandishly as you are now.
I don't care if those
are fake prop swords,
they're prohibited
just the same.
Ugh! These swords
are not just props!
Ha ha ha ha!
Stop laughing!
Thanks for your time.
Easy, boy, easy.
Calm down!
Dude, this is cool.
Watch it,
you idiot!
Ah! Aghh!
A-aahhh! It's
out of control!
Somebody get a
fire extinguisher!
Eek! Stop that horse!
Ah sweet! a hot story!
Go around that way,
See what you can get!
Use the zoom an' get
some good close-ups!
Right!
So far, I'm not seeing myself.
I'm pretty sure I was hanging
around this area at the time.
Are you sure?
We took a ton of photos on that
night, so if you were there, you
should be able to find yourself
in at least one of them.
Hm...
Where am I??
Just as I suspected,
you have no alibi!!
Why do you need an
alibi? Was there some
sort of an incident?
Do I smell a scoop here?
No, no. It's not
scoop-worthy at all.
You're too kind.
This is becoming
a real problem.
I was sure I would
find myself in one of
those photographs.
Hey, guys,
Where've ya been?!
Rgh! I'm super busy and I
still have a lot to do,
I could really use your help.
[giggle] Thanks a bunch.
Where do you wish me to take it?
Well, if it wouldn't be
too much trouble, could
you drop it off at the
teachers' main office?
I have to run this
over to the student
council room.
I'll do it.
Oh, the teachers' office!
I've got a new idea.
Oh, thank you.
If you would be so
kind, please leave
it right there.
I have a little
request.
You want to see a log of
all the students who left
the island through the main
gate on a particular day?
Yes.
Okay, but what do
you need it for?
Just to know I was here,
in case anybody should ask.
Guess I shouldn't mention
I might be killed if we
don't see it.
Mm? Oh, very well.
What day do you
want to check?
December Seventh.
Let's print it up.
Ido, Ikuno, and Inoue...
But no Isana!
You see?! There's
no Yashiro Isana!
Let's eat, Shiro!
I'm hungry!
This should clear me
of suspicion once and
for all, right?!
I want to eat!
Nothing to worry
about now.
Why don't we all go
get some snacks and
just enjoy the rest
of this afternoon?
Yahoo! Yahoo!
Yahoo!
Speaking of snacks, Kukuri said
she's got some delicious rice
crackers that she would share.
And her friend, Sumika, said
she'd buy me some tasty Daifuku
mochi! The hot ones ! Daifuku!
Daifuku! Oh, now I'm thirsty!
Shiro, can you
buy me a drink?
She has a lot
of energy.
[Shiro]
Like I told you, every
time a student comes to
or leaves this island,
they are scanned
at the automatic gate.
I'm not on this list,
which means I was on this
Island the whole day and
night of December Seventh.
And therefore, I couldn't
have been at the scene of
the crime. Get it?!
I want juice,
okay?
Oh! I didn't bring
enough change.
[can drops]
Did you forget
your PDA again?
You know it's a school
rule that you have to
keep it on you.
Besides, it's inconvenient
not to have it.
Kukuri. Are you saying
that Shiro doesn't usually
carry a PDA with him?
No matter how many
times I remind him,
he always forgets.
Shh...
Without a PDA it would be
a problem to get scanned
at the gate, am I right?
Not a problem for this guy.
Somehow he sneaks past it.
Kukuri. Something is about
to happen that I don't want
you to have to witness.
Please leave us now.
Wa- Wait a minute!
I'll search everywhere!
I'll find other proof!
I've heard enough!
It's become quite clear to
me that you are deceitful!
Mrowwr!
Step aside, Neko.
Unless of course,
as I suspect,
you've been working
with him all along.
So is it your desire to be
slain with your master?
I am Neko, Shiro's
domesticated house cat
and loyal pet!
I'm not letting you kill him,
He's my guardian!
He's a warm, caring human!
And I enjoy having delicious
meals and cat treats with him!
Easy. Calm down.
You're kinda making
things more complicated.
Shiro...?
I'm... sorry, Kuroh.
Give me one more chance,
I know I can prove I was here!
Come to think of it,
a lot more than fireworks
happened that night.
There was a
sprinkler that burst,
a toilet that overflowed,
and the ceiling in the
gym storeroom caved in.
I saw it all! Someone
had to have seen me, too.
Mmmm...
Wait a minute, I recall
running into the gym.
I was so upset that night
that it slipped my mind.
Hmm?
It's finally all
coming back to me.
After Sota embarrassed me
in front of everyone,
I ran into the gym.
That's when Shiro and I
found this hole together.
That's right,
I'd forgotten that!
You wouldn't by any
chance remember what time
we were both staring up
at the hole, would you?
Sure do,
Half past midnight.
Phew! I believe
that's within an
hour of the crime.
It would have been impossible
to sneak back in here from the
crime scene by then. So...
You know what that means;
I've got an alibi!
Shiro, what on
earth is going on?
Well, my dear friend Kukuri,
I owe you my life.
That's what's going on.
Hm?!
Focus, people! Focus!
We don't have much time
left before the festival!
Right!
[Kukuri]
It's amazing! Ever since
Kuroh took charge,
we're getting so much done,
We may even finish
ahead of schedule.
Hmpf! Nobody was focused,
It's taken a transfer student
to get anybody to work.
But Shiro's
disappeared again.
I was just thinking
about that.
Are those two newbies
really transfers?
It seems like they just
suddenly appeared in
class one day.
[Yashiro]
[humming Beethoven's 9th]
[siighh] I'm completely beat.
I can only take so many death
threats before my brain turns
into a pile of mush.
Uh! Must have left my uniform
in one of the classrooms.
Well, no big deal.
[humming]
Uh!
[humming Beethoven's 9th]
Hey, how're you doing?
It's a nice night out, isn't it?
I came up to film
the city lights,
since it's so clear.
[sinister chuckles]
It's beautiful!
I'm Tatara Totsuka.
What's your name?
I, my friend, am the Seventh
King, the colorless king!
I've been out here,
waiting for someone.
Nice night, you say?
Yes, it is. A very nice night!
[Neko]
Shiro!
Neko, what's wrong?
What are you doing home?
Is it snack time?
Kukuri gave me super
spicy rice crackers!
And then she asked
me to come here and
bring you back.
And if I do that, she
promised me ultra super
spicy rice crackers.
My mouth is tingling already!
Okay I'll go,
if that's what
you want.
Mm, what's wrong?
Shiro, do you have
a tummy ache?
It's nothing.
How can this be?
YOU'RE TOO KIND.
So this is where that
piece of shit hangs out.
Just you wait, pal.
I'll tear you apart
with my bare hands.
[buzz]
Huh?
[Fushimi]
I took the early shift and now
you have me working overtime?
[Munakata]
Is there a problem,
Fushimi?
[Fushimi]
No, nothing, sir.
[Munakata]
Please, have some tea.
[Fushimi]
Thanks. Ugh!
My foot's asleep.
[Munakata]
Is something wrong, Fushimi?
Can't drink the tea
I fixed for you?
[Fushimi]
Um, no, sir.
it's not like that.
[Munakata]
Hmm. Very well.
I suppose I shall enjoy
this tea for myself.
[Fushimi]
Damn it, nothing ever seems to
bother him. It's irritating.
Besides, what's so great
about green tea anyway?
I bet he's never had any
junk food in his life.
Now that I think of it,
the guys in HOMRA lived
on junk food.
And Mr. Kusanagi would give
them a hard time about...
Heh, what am I thinking?
I have no regrets in
leaving that clan.
That was simply not
the place for me.
Next time on "K".
Episode 5,
"Knife".
[Munakata]
Say Fushimi.
Is your foot asleep?
[Fushimi]
What?! Uh, no.
No, sir.
[Munakata]
Mmm.
[Fushimi]
Captain? No, wait.
Please, don't get any
closer, I mean it!
Don't!