[Kuroh]
Well, that's you, isn't it?
Answer me.
Yashiro Isana!
Mrowwwr!
Mm!
I was a vassal of
Ichigen Miwa.
He is the former
Seventh King.
I must now take...
Hold on a minute!
...your life!
Are you seriously
going to kill me?
Are you going to resist?
I didn't do it!
I'm innocent!
Did this Miwa person also
give you orders to kill a
man who's innocent?
Innocent?!
Hnn.. Yaah!
Heh heh...
Okay, so, I might
not look innocent
at the moment.
But as they say,
eyes can be deceived.
Don't be so quick to judge.
It's what's inside
that really matters.
What's "inside"
doesn't matter to me.
Nor do appearances.
I believe that a man should be
judged only by his actions.
H-heh heh...
[Yashiro]
I'm telling you,
though, That's not me!
You've got the wrong guy!
[Kuroh]
No matter how much you
protest, that is you!
Stop trying to deny it!
Okay, let's assume for a moment
that I did kill someone.
Why are you trying to punish me?
What gives you that right?
If you think I'm
guilty of murder, hand
me over to the police.
let the prosecutor
and judge determine
what happens to me.
Go ahead.
Take me in, then.
Isn't that how
things work in this
law-abiding country?
I don't serve this
country's court system,
only Master Ichigen Miwa.
[sigh]
I give up. I guess you've
pretty much made up your mind.
Do what you want with me.
Go ahead, get it over with.
You've finally
accepted your fate--
But before you run me
through with your sword,
will you grant me one
final request?
Speak.
Heh, Would you mind
putting me down first?
I'm getting a bit of
a kink in my neck.
Hmf.
Yeah, yeah,
don't worry,
I won't run.
What would be the point?
I wouldn't get very far anyway.
Hrrrrg.
You'd catch me before
I had a chance, right?
Heh, thanks,
I appreciate
your trust.
I need to write a farewell
letter to my little sister.
Your sister?
Yes, we've always
been very close.
I know I'll never be able
to prove my innocence,
But I just don't want my
little sister to believe
that I was executed for
committing murder.
She's always had a
very serious illness,
And has lived her entire
life going in and out from
one hospital to another.
She's in the hospital
right now.
Huh?
She's never had any friends,
I'm the only person she
knows and can talk to.
Without me, there's no-one
in her life. She's alone.
I need to prepare
her for that.
I see. What is your
little sister's name?
Huh?! Her name?
Ah, it's, ah...
Marilyn.
What?
Uhh! Mari!
Her name's Mari!
That's my sister.
Mari Isana.
That's a nice name.
Thanks so much. So now...
Here. I need a favor.
I would greatly appreciate
it if you would give
this note to her.
Come on, please say yes.
There's no one else I can
turn to for this favor.
It isn't much to ask.
I'm not going to be
around to do it myself.
When I'm gone,
she'll have no
family left.
Ah!?
What is this?!
[frustrated breaths]
Ngghh!!
[kicks]
[gasps]
Well, I managed to
get out of that alive.
Mew!
But I'm guessing if there's
a next time, he'll be ready
to kill me on the spot.
Meooww!
Did you put up the
bounty notices?
I'm sending them out...
right now!
[crowd interest]
Whoa. Did you see that?
Ooh! Wow! That's a lot of money!
HOMRA's offering ten million
to find that guy!
Hello, you've reached HOMRA.
Do you have information
about the suspect?
Yes, that's correct.
Ten million yen.
No, we're not joking.
Come on, now,
give us a little credit.
Hey, Anna. Having any luck?
He's around
that area.
[pleased]
Hmm.
Yatagarasu here.
All right,
I'm on my way.
I just went into an
alley that's not
even on the map!
A-huh huh huh!
Quit laughing, shithead!
Heh.
[eating]
Kamamoto here.
I've got a lot on my plate.
Give me a little more time.
Hey, pal, can I get a
side order of fried rice?
Let's go, dumbass.
You're not being
paid to eat!
What did you just
say about HOMRA?!
Is somebody talking shit
about HOMRA? Mark the
location, I'll head over
and show them what's up.
Focus on the boy.
Also, keep your distance
from the Black Dog.
Trust me, you guys
are no match for him,
not even close.
That's all.
Kusanagi out.
Wait a minute, Mr. Kusanagi!
What do you me-- [click]
Let's hope those boys
don't screw this up.
[woman]
Hey, do you think that
bounty's for real?
[man]
Get serious. You wouldn't know
what do with ten million yen!
[other man]
It's probably a stupid
prank by those HOMRA'S.
[other woman]
Be careful what you say,
you don't want to mess
with those dudes.
Come out, Yashiro Isana!
Show yourself!
Grrahh!
Hey, Black Dog!
Tell me where he is!
And who are you
referring to,
Red Clansman?
Don't play dumb!
I'm asking you,
where are you
hiding that bastard?!
If you know what's
good for you,
you'd better come clean
and answer me quick!
I don't have time for this.
If you know what's good for you,
you'll back off.
[Yashiro]
Hey-y!!!
Kuroh Yatogami!
Looks like we can
escape from here!
It's perfect,
but you'd better
hurry up!
What are you doing?!
Gotcha!
Please! you can take
that guy out without
even breaking a sweat!
Finish him off and
join me up here!
Yeah?! I'd like to
see that happen!
Once I'm done with your sorry
ass, I'm gonna tie your friend
down and finish this!
If you intend to fight me,
Don't expect mercy.
Fuck you!
Yyyahh!
Tch.
Hey! Are you all right?
You're lucky to be alive!
He's gone?!
I'll find you, Isana.
[relieved sigh]
Huh?
SHOW SOME RESPECT!
Oh! Sorry.
YOU'RE TOO KIND.
Mew!
Not at all.
Whew! I'm just wiped out.
Meoowo~
Who are all these people and
why do they want to kill me?
And that video...
It really looked like me!
I've got a feeling,
this is gonna be one
big pain in the neck.
[woman]
I know! It's especially
annoying since life was
so good up to now.
Ut... ???
D'YAHHHH!
Who... are you?
Huh?!
Hmm... Ah...
Don't you remember, silly?
I am a cat!
SHOW SOME RESPECT!
DIE! SHOW SOME RESPECT!
MOVING ONWARD!
YOU'RE TOO KIND!
DIE! DIE! DIE!
School hours are now over.
I repeat, school hours are
now over.
Students not preparing
for the school festival
are asked to promptly
leave the school grounds.
I thought that last
class would never end,
It was so boring.
I know. Hey, look
over there, what's
up with him?
I don't know,
but I think he's
kind of hot.
Maybe, but he's a little
strange for my tastes.
What's he doing there?
Posing, I guess.
[giggles]
[Kuroh]
I'll have to force
my way through.
Excuse me...
Can I help you
with something?
Hey! Is there a problem?
Do you know him?
No, but it just seemed like
he might need some help.
I'm looking for a boy
named Yashiro Isana.
By any chance do you
know him?
Isana?
Oh! Shiro! Sure.
He's one of my
classmates!
Do you know where
he is right now?
Well, I'm not really sure.
He went to run some
errands for me.
But that was a while ago.
He should be done by now.
If you have time, I can take you
over to his dorm to find him.
Ah...
There we go!
I got you in!
Just follow me. The boy's dorm
isn't too far from here at all.
Thank you very much.
I'm grateful for
your assistance.
[giggling]
You're so dramatic!
It's no biggie.
I'm just doing what's right.
I understand, but not
many do the 'right thing'
when it really matters.
That is what my master
always used to say.
So I promise I will not forget
how cooperative you have been.
Uh...
Ha ha ha! You're a funny guy!
You really crack me up!
[giggle] So why are you
looking for Shiro anyway?
I have something I must
personally deliver to him.
Oh. Must be a
special delivery.
His death warrant.
I'm sorry.
Did you say,
"wallet"?
No.
Mm?!
[gasp]
Here. You have to put
this on right now.
No way!
Listen to me, you can't
just go running around
here naked all day long.
Why not?
Clothes are too
restricting.
[echo]
Meow!
How 'bout we
play tag?
Come on!
It could be fun!
[Kukuri]
Hey, Shiro!
[gulp]
I brought your
friend to see you!
Who is it?
Gahh!
How is your little sister
faring, Yashiro Isana?
Dehhh!
Huh?! How come
he never told me
he had a sister?
I appreciate that
you escorted me
here.
No problem, Glad I
could be of help-- mm.
Yaahh!
Huh?!
Oh my goodness, it
looks like he's just
as forgetful as Shiro!
No!
How indecent!
I can't look
at you!
Uh... Oh! Cover up!
Here you go!
Yeeoww!
[echo]
Meow!
This way, Shiro!
Eh?!
What?!
Whoa! The hallway's
back to normal!
Did she do that?!
Okay. That's weird.
Stop right there!
[echo]
Meow!
Mrowww!
Is it an illusion?
[giggle]
His clansman, I guess.
[humming]
What was that?!!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Guess I must have
bumped into something.
Uh?
Dgh!
[echo]
Meow!
Not again!?
Here you go.
Thanks.
That's so nice.
Huh?!
Give it up,
Yashiro Isana!
You made a good run,
but the game's over!
[echo]
Meow!
More tricks! Is this wall
just another illusion?
Augh!
[giggles]
Aaah, ha ha ha ha!
Haa ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
[Kuroh]
You're not getting away!
[Yashiro]
Well I'm not giving up!
[Neko]
Stop chasing after Shiro!
[Kuroh]
Do not address me in
such an indecent state!
[Yashiro]
He's right.
take my jacket!
[Neko]
Anyone who bullies
Shiro gets this!
[Yashiro]
Don't do that!
[Neko]
Why not?
He's a meathead!
[Kuroh]
My head is
beginning to throb!
[laughing]
Perhaps that is
an illusion, as well!
Hey! What did you
do to my face?!
[Yashiro & Neko]
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[exhausted panting]
[Yashiro]
Hey! You finally
put it on.
Evil king...
Yashiro Isana.
(Heavy breaths)
Now as my late master...
ordered... I...
[stomach rumble]
What's that?!
[moans]
Shiro. Can we eat
something? I'm hungry!
Huh?
What do say we put this
matter on hold for now until
we all get something to eat?
Why should I?
[stomach rumble]
Oh.
Thanks for
agreeing with us.
[Yashiro]
I've cooked rice before,
but that's all I know.
What goes in first,
Dashi or Miso?
[Neko]
No Shiro, no green onions!
I really hate green onions!
But this dish,
And this one,
both call for onions.
[Neko]
I don't care!
No yellow onions, either.
They're toxic for me,too.
All right, all right!
I won't use any.
And no myoga.
Not even that?!
And no ginger!
It doesn't even
call for ginger.
And no cilantro!
Ohhhh...
But I'm fine
with garlic chives.
Great, I don't
have any!
Oh, and I want
mine spicey!
How are we going to do
that without any spice!?
We'll just use lots
of hot pepper!
Thank you, kind girl,
for bringing my bag.
Yes we are!
I want my mouth
to be on fire!
It will make it much too hot!
[sigh]
[humming]
Scrape the whites against
the bottom of the bowl.
tearing, tearing the yolk.
Mince finely.
Eat while it's hot!
[all in unison]
Thank you for the food!
[Kuroh]
First, you must
pick the fresh egg.
That means when you crack an
egg, the egg yolk doesn't lie
too flat on the pan.
Then, add soy sauce
and dashi to it.
For kids, you can also
add a pinch of sugar.
Mix them all gently.
Next add oil to the frying pan,
then pour in the egg mixture.
Once the mixture starts to cook,
push it to one side of the pan,
and quickly roll it into the
proper shape.
[Yashiro]
What're you doing
in my kitchen?
[Kuroh]
[gasp] You've been watching me?!
[Yashiro]
It's tough to ignore a
grown man reciting cooking
instructions out loud.
[Kuroh]
Your kitchen is utterly
useless! There's not
even one usable knife!
[Yashiro]
I'm not much of a cook. But you
seem well prepared. By the way,
is that your own kitchen knife?
[Kuroh]
You're not talking
about this, are you?
[Kuroh]
Are you seriously calling
my celebrated sword
Kotowari, a kitchen knife?!
[Yashiro]
No, I didn't mean it
like that, really!
[Kuroh]
Rest assured. Kotowari is always
ready to slay the evil king.
Next time on "K".
Episode three,
"Kitchen".
Here's how you properly
slay the evil king!
[Yashiro]
D'yahhh!