C'mon, Is that the
best you've got?
I hope you're not
going soft on me.
It's because I don't
have my glasses on.
Heh. You don't seem
to have your heart
in it, either.
I'm quite committed,
I assure you.
For you are the Red King
and deserve a worthy opponent.
Ehh.
Why do you always have to speak
to me in that overly formal
tone, like you're delivering
some commencement address?
Please, will y'just
cut the shit already.
I have an official
authority to maintain.
It is my duty as head of
SCEPTER Four and also as
one of the Seven Kings,
to detach myself from you,
and defeat you.
Personally, all I really
want to do is help you.
Hmm.
You're so full of it!
Uaagh!
Agh. Mikoto.
Looks like your
boss found himself
some trouble.
It's too late.
He's over-extended.
You bastard!
Rgh!
Gimme that!
This sucks!
[gasp]
OMIT
Mikoto. Take it easy or
you'll scare those kids.
[chuckle]
Hm.
Hey! Who you callin' scared?!
Instead of just sitting
around there wasting time,
Why don't you kids come
and join up with us?
We'll give you plenty of
opportunities to blow off
steam. What do you say?
Hm.
Don't you care anymore?
Have you forgotten everything?
You looked up to him
as your King, once!
I know you must still have
some respect for him!
[Kuroh]
Haven't you both
had enough already?
From what I've observed,
you're the only ones
still out here fighting.
[Rikio]
C'mon, Yata, let's get
out of here. Everyone
else has been evacuated.
[Yata]
That's not true! Mikoto hasn't
left. And he'll never leave!
He'll never give up!
Hrmm.
Put me down! Hey!
Y'listening to me??
Put me down and
leave me alone.
Believe me, it wasn't
my idea to do this.
But my King is
compassionate.
Despite the fact that you
turned away from him,
he isn't letting your
petty betrayal bother him.
[Yata]
Who do you think you are?
Just let me go!
I didn't betray him, I left.
Good work, Kuroh.
Well, as you can hear,
they aren't happy about it.
We took care of things
on our end as well.
The credit
belongs to Neko.
Now then,
let's go finish this,
once and for all.
Let's save Kukuri.
No second thoughts?
You're sure your
plan is solid, that
it's going to work?
Well, I'm hoping you'll
somehow be able to pull it
off without any hitches.
You've regained your
memory of being a King.
But it appears you're
just as irresponsible
as when you thought you
were a mere student.
You need to act with the
self-assured poise and
maturity that befits a King.
Prepare to be disappointed.
I don't think I'll ever be
your ideal King.
[exasperated sigh]
Huh?!
Kuroh! What are you doing?
Why are you bowing to me?
C'mon, get up!
I must ask you to be quiet.
Let me do this.
May I be permitted
to serve a new King,
Master Ichigen?
[pleased]
Mmm.
I, Kuroh Yatogami, do solemnly
swear to devote my life to
serve Adolph K. Weismann,
the First and Silver King.
I shall be his
loyal clansman.
Hey, lighten up.
This isn't necessary.
You and I are friends,
and I know I can count
on you to have my back.
C'mon, let's go.
[sinister]
He he he. Looks like
the first to weaken
is the Blue King.
That's surprising.
[bubbly]
I could devour him now
in his weakened state.
[sinister]
But then I might get myself
killed by the Red King and that
wouldn't be very much fun.
[calm]
It'd be smarter to wait until
the Red King wears him
self down,
and then I'll engulf him.
[sinister]
I can take my time with
the Blue King after that.
Once I get the power of two
Kings, consuming the others
will be a piece of cake!
And then, after I have
the strength of seven Kings,
I will be all-powerful! Yes!!
Who needs seven Kings anyway?!
That's what I say!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
One and only one is
more than enough!
[faints]
I'll be King...
by myself!
I'll rule the world!
[Kukuri's natural voice]
Help me please! Someone!
[Yashiro]
Hey you, in Kukuri's body,
stop making those nasty faces.
Rrr!
Shiro!
Heh!
Nobody's left.
We've evacuated everyone
from the island.
[Kuroh]
Anyone you could easily
possess is gone.
The few of us that are here,
are too resilient for you.
Hagh!
Kuroh! Don't hurt Kukuri!
Uh?
Kuroh!
My late Master
Ichigen's sword.
'Kotowari'.
This is only the second
time I've drawn it.
Do you understand the
significance of that?
It has been confirmed that
you are an evil King.
So in accordance with
Master Ichigen's last words,
I intend to slay you.
I know he would never
allow an evil being like
you to succeed him as the
Seventh and last King.
I will make sure of that!
C'mon, Kuroh, it's me.
I thought I was your
good friend.
You don't want to kill me.
It wouldn't be right.
You'd feel terrible!
Na ha ha ha ha!
Slay me, you say?!
Go ahead, I dare you!
No, don't listen to
him, he's kidding.
Please don't!
I'm begging you!
Please spare my life!
[gasp]
Wait, don't do it!
Please! No!
Shiro, help me!
Uh...
Kuroh, stop this now!
Eh he he he he.
Ah ha ha ha ha! You let
your guard down, Weismann.
I was going to save you
for later, but now is
as good a time as any!
Oh, damn it!
You coward! You're not
getting away this time!
Gotcha, big mouth.
You wouldn't know this,
but the real Kukuri
doesn't remember my name.
We set the trap and
you took the bait.
What?!
Hey! Let go!
Just stop it! You can't do
this to me, understand!
Help me, help me,
please help, somebody!
Oh, Shiro, won't
you please help me?
You'll regret this, believe me!
I'm going to murder you!
I pity you.
You've consumed so many
different personalities, your
sense of self is beginning to
disintegrate, bit by bit.
And sadly, you no longer
know for sure which one of
them is your true self.
I know who I am!
I'm the Seventh King!
Ich bin der erste koenig.
Das aelteste Koenig,
...mein Jung.
Eegh!
YAAGH!
[relieved sigh]
Well, we had a fifty-fifty
chance of success!
But it worked out alright!
Not what I'd call a
perfectly solid plan.
You could have
mentioned that.
You always take big
risks with everything,
no matter what it is.
All right, I get
it, you're upset.
You can lecture me later.
But right now, you need to
take Kukuri to a safe place.
What about you?
Are you totally insane?!
If you interrupt a battle
between two Kings, even you
won't emerge unscathed!
No big deal.
Don't forget,
I'm the Immortal King.
Now, you'd better get going.
I'm not leaving.
King's orders.
Huh?!
Anybody who is not a King
will only get in the way
from here on out.
[sigh]
Egh.
I'm sorry, Kuroh.
Look after Kukuri.
And keep Neko safe as well.
Rrrgh!
[struggling]
Will you just hold still?
I'm not sure how long
I can retain you, but I
guess we'll soon find out.
I won't underestimate your
powers, Colorless King.
You know, Lieutenant Kokujoji,
I honestly believed that
my research project had
the potential to make
everyone happy.
However, now I'm beginning
to see that the energy
force I discovered has
only brought loneliness.
Each King sees himself above the
Clansmen who are devoted to him,
and each has set himself
on a course divergent
from one another.
As I did on that day, long ago,
when I parted from you.
I wonder if there is any chance
for these men to move forward
and resolve their differences.
Can they co-exist?
Heh.
Hmph!
Nobody knows anything.
Chiho!...
Huh?
Kukuri's still missing!
We've looked everywhere
that we're allowed to go!
Who was the last person
you saw her with?
Let me think...
Oh, I'm pretty sure it
was that boy from earlier.
The one who led us out.
Remember him?
Yeah! You're right!
But I never got his name.
If she's with him I
have this feeling she's
gonna be all right.
Yeah, me too.
Even though we didn't find
out who he is, he must be
a really good person.
He saved all of us, didn't he?
[Yata]
I still don't understand
why the hell you did that!
[Rikio]
I told you why!
[Izumo]
Oh, great. The skateboarding
genius is back.
I was just trying to help!
"Help", fuck you! This is
just bullshit! I want to
know why everybody had to
be pulled out of there!
You know you've just
abandoned our King!
Dagh! Agh!
What was that
for hah?!
[Izumo]
Calm down! We're under
our King's orders.
This is how he wants it.
So be patient, like the
others.
You should be ashamed
of yourself. Man up!
Wasn't sure if you'd
rejoined your old gang.
It might have looked
that way for a moment.
[Seri]
Four Kings haven't come
together at any time since
the Kagutsu Crater incident.
[Fushimi]
Do you think a massive disaster
like that can happen again now?
The Captain will do whatever
it takes to prevent that.
I doubt he'd
sacrifice himself!
Let me remind you that the
man you're referring to is
a compassionate individual.
He gave you an important
position with us,
despite your past
ties with HOMRA.
Don't ever forget that.
I'm suspicious of
compassionate people,
especially if they're Kings.
They always make you
feel beholden to them,
so they can call upon
you whenever they need
something done that they
feel is beneath them.
[Fushimi]
Heh. We're just underlings
to them. They'll never see
us as their equals.
I hate to admit it but,
You may have a point. Kings
seem to keep to themselves
and only each other.
The guy you're
looking for is here.
I'm the one.
Stop! What are you doing?
They'll kill us!
Stop right now! Stop it! Stop!
Let me out!
Nnggh... Egh!
Hurry up!
Come on, do it!
Only a King can
murder a King.
Yeah. I'm aware of that.
Thanks for
bringing him here!
Stop, don't do it, Suoh!
Haaaaaaa!
Where am I?
What is...
Kuroh, what are
we doing here?
Kukuri, so you
do remember me.
Thank goodness.
Is everyone all right?
I was worried about that
cat-girl and, um...
...who else?
Huh? I can't think of who
I'm trying to remember.
It's weird.
I'm...
...lost.
Just rest. There's no
pressure to remember
anything for now.
[Mikoto]
Sorry for all this.
but I guess that's that.
Don't pretend to be
sorry when you didn't do
anything to prevent it.
You knew it would come
to this and did nothing
to help yourself.
This is the end.
But it didn't have to be.
[Mikoto]
There's nothing more
to say, Munakata.
[silence]
[gasp]
[Mikoto]
I'm sorry, Anna. But I
won't be able to show you
that lovely red anymore.
Mikoto...!
[Akiyama]
The Red King's Weismann
level just... vanished!
Huh?
[gasp]
Hm?
[Andy]
It's the Captain!
- Yeah!
- He did it!
- He's back!
- The captain won!
Welcome back!
[gasp] Shiro!
I can't get it out!
Give it to me!
I'm taking it to Shiro!
He's gonna want it back!
Neko, you can't.
It's impossible.
He's no longer with us.
Yes, he is! I'm taking this
to Shiro right now, because
he's gonna need his umbrella!
Listen to me! I'm sorry!
You're wrong! Shiro is immortal!
[gasp]
Don't forget,
I'm the Immortal King.
[crying]
I misspoke. You're right.
He's our everlasting King.
No blood!
No bone!
No ash!
[in unison]
No blood! No bone! No ash!
Egh!
A lovely red! Thank you.
[Kusanagi]
Do you hear them, Mikoto?
When all's said and done,
we couldn't have asked
for a better king.