[nervous]
Heh heh heh!
Creepy.
Huh?
Ngh.
[Seri]
Attention! Kuroh Yatogami
and your accomplice!
What the--?
SCEPTER 4 has you surrounded!
Be warned! In accordance with
Article Two of the Supernatural
Regulation Exemption Act,
we are now taking
you into custody!
Uh, what's this?
How'd they find us?
I don't know what's going
on, but can we talk?
We don't surrender!
Permission to use
our sabers, sir.
[Reisi]
Permission granted.
Everyone,
draw your swords!
Akiyama, ready!
Benzai, ready!
Kamo, ready!
Domyoji, ready!
Enomoto, ready!
Fuse, ready!
Goto, ready!
Hidaka, ready!
Awashima...
Ready!
Mmmrowwr!
Meow!
[Yashiro]
Huh?
What happened?
Neko, there you are!
Ah! Dg!
Where did these
civilians come from?
Hang on! Something's
not right here!
Headquarters!
Headquarters,
do you read?
Sensory interference!
Seal off the perimeter!
Look sharp!
Eaagh!
Meeeoww!
Mewo~!
Don't worry, I'll handle this
one! Man your posts!
Yes ma'am!
Shiro, stay back!
Go ahead,
draw your sword.
Listen to me.
This sword was never
intended to kill the
likes of you!
Then you can prepare
to be slain by the
likes of me!
We don't seem to have the
winning edge in this fight.
[sip]
Hmm.
Perhaps it's time for you
to do some work, sir.
Let's see you dodge this!
Mrowwrr!
What is that?
The Sword of Damocles!
[Kuroh]
It's announcing
someone's arrival!
It's the Blue King!
[Kuroh]
Reisi Munakata!
Well done, Ms. Awashima.
Thanks to your efforts,
I now have a clear grasp
of the situation.
Sir!
Now that I'm here, I guess
I'd better get to work.
Mr. Fushimi is growing
quite impatient with me.
Meow!
Hm.
Mew!
Yah!
[Reisi]
Just as I suspected,
a third party.
An unknown Strain was
behind all of this
from the beginning.
If you don't already know,
A Strain can project their
powers outward, to form a
perimeter around themselves.
Within that area they can
interfere with and manipulate
the senses and perceptions of
those humans around them.
As you can imagine,
it's a dangerous power.
meow...
Hey Kuroh,
shouldn't we
surrender?
Heh.
Here's what's
gonna happen.
I'll hold off
their leader.
You two will have to
find a way to escape.
Huh?
[saluting]
Mrow!
Haugh!
Ouaagh!
Get moving!
But, Kuroh!
Seal off the
corridor!
[Saruhiko]
Roger!
I'll send in the men
from the outside.
I see. So you chose to
sacrifice yourself.
[Reisi]
I recognize your sword.
Uh!?
It's called Kotowari, and used
to belong to Ichigen Miwa, known
as the Colorless King.
If you think you can kill me
with that, go ahead and try.
Heh.
What's the matter,
didn't you hear me?
I'm giving you permission.
Draw that sword.
That's more like it.
No?
Such a disobedient child.
Gyahh!
If you insist on
being so stubborn,
you leave me no
choice.
This is a silly exercise,
my friend. What do you say
we end this game now?
I refuse.
[Kuroh]
Yaaaaaaah!
Now then. Let's get to the
subject at hand, shall we?
Aah!
This way!
Shiro! We have to hurry!
I applaud your
self-sacrifice.
Let me ask you
something.
That young man
you've been helping.
Is he the master you serve now?
The successor to the late
Colorless King?
The Seventh, and
weakest king?
Rrgh.
He is not a powerful
presence by himself alone.
But in the current situation,
he is the wild card
who could end up tipping the
balance of power between the
remaining kings.
In other words, he is the one
person in this whole mix that I
need to handle carfully.
That young man is the new
Colorless King who will
replace Ichigen Miwa.
I'm right about
that, aren't I?
You would do well
to answer me.
Master Ichigen sent me to
evaluate that young man.
Very interesting.
So what is your verdict?
I won't let anyone
touch him until I make
that final decision.
I understand. But I'm afraid
that might have been the
boy's plan, from the start.
He doesn't have to take
the side of good or evil.
And as long as he maintains
that ambiguous position,
he can keep the 'Black Dog',
Kuroh Yatogami,
as his bodyguard.
He could not ask for
a more powerful pawn.
Using the powers of that young
female Strain, deceiving both
you and the other people around
him would be a simple matter.
We could be the fools.
All of us might be nothing
more than puppets in that
young man's scheme.
Wouldn't you agree, Kuroh?
You have a point.
He constantly laughs,
like some kind of fool.
And everything that comes
out of his mouth is a lie.
But, that's just the
kind of guy he is.
I guess you have to ask
yourself, Is that the
kind of guy worth
risking your life over?
Hm.
Hm...
Heh.
So! What brings
you back to us?
Did you forget
something?
Get out of here,
you fool!
Augh!
Well now. I thought about it,
and just didn't feel I could
go and leave my friend behind.
Selfless. So you came back here
to share your fate together.
That is a noble
gesture on your part.
But ultimately meaningless.
Actually, as I think
you'll see, it's not
all that meaningless.
Oh?
I just want to say to Kuroh...
Sorry!
I've been lying to
you all this time.
It's time to tell the truth.
This is who I really am.
[gasp]
Whoa!
[Yashiro] [thought]
Kuroh. Kuroh, can you hear me?
Captain!
[Fushimi]
The outer perimeter's
been breached!
What's that?!
Heh. I should
have known better.
I fell for it,
hook, line, and sinker.
All right, Fushimi.
Time to call in the
local authorities.
Roger.
[Kuroh]
[groan]
Kuroh! Are you okay?
My injuries are not serious.
I'll be fine in a
couple of minutes.
So, Neko.
Listen to me.
Uh?
I have to tell
you something.
You were great.
If those blue soldiers had
caught us, They would have
locked us away for a long time.
But the way you took over and
transported us to that
downtown street, was amazing.
There's no question about it.
You're the one who saved us.
[Neko]
I... don't know
what you mean.
I guess you don't realize
what kind of power you have.
The Blue Leader said
you have the ability
to interfere with
people's perceptions.
I'm not really
sure I understand
what that means.
Her powers aren't
limited to the visual
and auditory.
Apparently, in
manipulating perception,
she can even play with a
person's memory.
I've never heard of
such a thing.
[Kuroh]
She is what is called a Strain.
She can create false
memories in people,
even make people who've
never met before,
believe they're actually
dear, old friends.
You're brazen.
Not funny.
C'mon!
Here.
Thanks!
Yeah, okay!
I'm not eating all of mine!
Thanks!
Try this!
Whoops!
Ohh, I see. It's all
finally coming together.
That explains everything.
Okay, then.
Neko.
I need you to get
rid of my amnesia.
No more phony
memories.
That way, we'll finally
know the truth.
We'll discover whether or
not I'm that evil king.
You should be
aware, though.
If I find out you
are that evil king,
I'll have no choice but
to kill you on the spot.
Of course.
I understand.
Your life is at stake
in this decision.
Calm down and think
it over carefully.
I am calm.
I mean it.
Whatever you say.
I just want you to know,
I'm open to discussing this,
once we've successfully
escaped from here.
You know...
I'm tired of that.
Putting things off, that's
all we've been doing.
"We'll do it tomorrow".
"We'll think about it later".
That's not getting us anywhere.
If we can't deal with this
right here and now, then
we're just running in place.
I don't know who I
was in the past.
But the person I am this
very second needs to find
out what's going on and
finally take responsibility.
I don't think I'm evil, but I
need to know for sure.
More importantly, however,
No matter what I might
have done in the past,
I feel I should be judged
by the nature and quality
of my present behavior.
[Kuroh]
Such commendable ideas.
Are they really yours?
Heh heh heh!
Oh...
Let's see where
this takes us.
All right.
I'm ready.
[Yashiro]
Go ahead, Neko.
[Kuroh]
Undo your spell completely.
And remember, no tricks.
(Nervous meows as she faces off
Tsukumo)
You hillbilly samurai!
[fast-reverse sound]
[film flapping]
Meoooowww!!
Meow! Meow! Meow!
Mrooowwwwll!
Huh?
And who are you?
Mrowwww!
Mrowwwwl!!
I must have really
frightened you.
Sorry.
Mrrl?
Meow!
[door opens suddenly]
Yah!
Now that's really strange,
I thought I heard some kind
of loud noise...
Eek!
I was right!
What are you
doing in here?!
Oh uh. Hello, there!
Are you okay? I've never seen
you before. Who are you?
Where are you from?
Hm? My name is...
Hmf!
Meoww!
Yashiro... Isana.
You said Yashiro Isana?
Well, of course
you're Yashiro Isana!
But why in the world are
you hiding out in here?
Wait, I know! You were trying
to avoid helping with the
school festival preparations!
Sure, why not?
Huh?
[Kukuri]
Hey, how did that hole
get in the roof?!
Look at that.
It's so big!
Don't you play dumb, Yashiro!
[film flapping]
[Yashiro]
Huh? Is that all?
What about my
memories before that?!
This is where it started!
You had fallen from the sky,
and hit the ground hard.
[Kuroh]
He fell to the ground?
Mmm-hmm!
I was the first one to find you!
That's why you belong to me!
Finder's keepers,
losers weepers!
Shiro is Neko's Shiro!
I understand what you're
saying, but can't you
bring back memories from
before you found me?
[sad sigh]
That's the part I
want to know about.
But wait, If you found out,
wouldn't you disappear?
I mean, you wouldn't
be my Shiro anymore.
You don't have to
worry about that.
I'll always be your
Shiro, right?
Haa!
Okay! I'll try again!
[nasty laughter]
mm... heheha ha ha ha!
Bye-bye, now.
Huaaahh!
[gasp]
Who...
..was that?!
[Reisi]
Hm. I'm surprised to
say this, but you got me.
My glasses are loose now.
I suppose this is what I get
for taking part in activities
that I'm not used to.
But regardless, we must
make certain that Yashiro
Isana and his accomplices
are apprehende
d promptly.
Members of SCEPTER 4,
I'm counting on you all.
[door opens]
[Seri]
Care for a break, Captain?
[Reisi]
No, that won't be necessary.
[Seri]
I have brought you a
cup of tea, as well as
mountains of sweets.
Please take a moment
to enjoy them.
[Reisi]
Mountains of sweets, you say?
[Seri]
That is correct, sir.
Mountains of red bean paste.
[Reisi]
Well, I just noticed that I'm
missing a piece of the jigsaw
puzzle I've been working on.
[Seri]
Enjoy them while
they're hot, Captain.
[Reisi]
B-But I need to find the missing
piece. Or maybe two pieces.
[Seri]
You heard me, Captain.
[Reisi]
[Ahem]! Next time
on 'K', Episode 8:
"Kindling".
We will triumph,
because our cause is just.
[Seri]
Captain?