Just a reminder for all of you
who are busy preparing for the
upcoming school festival.
Please don't get
carried away with any
unofficial activities,
and always remember to
uphold the traditions
and honor of our school.
Your families will be joining
us on festival day and will
be able to see the results
of all the hard work you
put into this event during
these past few weeks.
[Kuroh]
Are these all of the costumes?
It's important that you check
the ones you're going to wear.
Once you do, be sure to let
me know if you're having any
trouble with the sizes.
How are the decorations
coming along?
We're not quite done yet.
Okay. I'll get
you some help.
Let's see who might
be free right now.
Rice crackers!
Hm? What do you
need, Kuroh?
I noticed your left sleeve
is torn at the elbow.
Oh. You're right.
Guess I must have
caught it on something.
When can I have
my rice crackers!
-I'll fix it. I have
a needle and thread.
It'll just take
a minute.
[Neko] [whimper]
Rice crackers...
When can I have them?
Be patient.
Hmm...
Half past midnight.
Phew! I believe
that's within an
hour of the crime!
It would have been
impossible to sneak back
in here from the crime
scene by then. So...
[Kuroh]
Yashiro, what are you doing?
Quit wasting time.
There's a lot of
work to do.
[Neko]
Shiro got in trouble!
Ouch! Kuroh! Please keep your
eyes on what you're doing!
Hm.
Sorry about that!
What was it I was
supposed to be
doing right now?
Well...
Let's all have some
rice crackers!
You're supposed to
be helping with
these preparations!
Can we please finish
up this patch job?
Oh! You know what?
Shiro, if you don't have
an assignment, can I ask
you to do me a favor?
[nervous]
Ahh?
[Seri]
Yes...
Yes, that's correct.
...At Ashinaka High School.
It happened a few minutes ago.
The Yuishiki System has
identified someone there who's
a 91 percent match.
That's right.
No question.
I want to go there, to
confirm this information
with my own eyes.
Yes, I understand.
I'll let you know.
We have authorization.
We will now head to the
school on the island,
to confirm the
suspect's presence.
Yes Ma'am!
Have a safe
trip, you guys.
Fushimi. You're
coming as well.
Are you serious?
What will you do if you
find this murderer?
Take him into custody,
of course.
And if he should resist?
That's a stupid question.
[panicked sounds]
Gyaahh!
Yahh!
So we use this to get in?
Psh. What a pain in the ass.
You ready?
Hyea.
We're going for
a walk! [giggle]
Please explain to
me why you keep
using this exit?
[Yashiro]
I told you before,
I mis-placed my PDA.
[Yashiro]
Oh, wait, maybe I should just
install my passcode into yours.
[Kuroh]
That's not going to happen.
Just get a new one.
[Neko]
Shiro! Hurry, hurry!
[giggles]
[Kuroh]
One of our assignments
is to go into town and
order more fireworks,
because you blew up the
other ones when you were
trying to escape.
I really didn't have
much choice, You were
trying to kill me.
Let's just get
this over with.
I'm very busy.
Wow, you're really
getting into this.
Hm?
DIE!
SHOW SOME RESPECT!
Okay. We're
all going in.
Yes, ma'am.
[Seri]
We apologize for this rather
sudden and unexpected request,
but we need your cooperation.
I want to reiterate,
we're just doing our jobs.
We don't want to
cause your school
any trouble.
We understand what
you're looking for...
But in this day and
age, releasing personal
student information is,
a breach of secur--
I need you to understand,
sir, that this is a
high-priority request.
If need be, we are prepared
to use legal means to force
you to comply.
Uh we can't have that!
We agree. That's why,
under the circumstances,
we'd like to handle things
as amicably as possible.
We'd prefer that you
cooperate willingly
with our request.
That's why we met with
you privately, rather
than get a warrant.
[Principal]
I understand. But asking us
to identify a student from
the entire student body,
when you don't even
have a name, is
nearly impossible.
[Vice-Principal]
With such short notice, there's
very little hope of success, if
we have to do this search today.
[Seri]
Let me make myself clear.
This investigation has
already been authorized.
If your school lacks the means
or the personnel to conduct
such an investigation,
we will step in
and do it for you.
What?! That's
going too far!
You have no right to
come in and here and--
I think you
misunderstand
what I'm saying.
We're not trying
to 'persuade' you
to cooperate.
That doesn't reflect the
gravity of the situation.
We're here to order you to
comply with our demands.
[Principal]
But that's...
[Seri]
As I said earlier, it is
not our wish to turn this
into a public issue.
However, I have no
reservations about using the
law to take the appropriate
action in this situation.
[sigh]
Hey!
You know this guy?!
Uhh.. Ahh!
Come back here!
Know where we can
find this guy?
Uhh...
Mm-mm.
Nah.
You know this guy,
don't you!
Ehh...
heh heh!
Yata, why don't we
ask those girls?
Gah...
Forget it!
Huh?
[heavy panting]
Wait up, Yata!
You're too
damn slow!
You know why? It's all
that shit you keep shoving
in your face everyday!
No wonder you're
so damn fat!
At least I
enjoy life!
You just work
all damn day!
You don't stop. How much
sleep have you gotten
since Tatara was killed?
Hmpf. I'm fine.
[knock on door]
Huh?
Hello?
Mm-mmf!
[Yata]
You know the guy
in this photo?
[gasp]
[Yata]
I saw that!
You shifted
your eyes!
No I didn't!
You know this guy!
That's not true!
I don't know him!
Leave us alone!
We don't know anything!
Where is he,
damn it?!
I can't tell you
what I don't know!
Come back here!
He he he...
[Yata]
Another dead end! Shit!
[Kamamoto]
Yata, this place is huge,
and nobody's talking to us.
This isn't gonna work. We're
just spinnin' our wheels!
Shut up!
I'm tellin' you, no matter
what it takes, I'm going
to avenge Tatara's death.
Even if I have to question
every kid in this school.
[female student]
[fear squeak]
Hey! You two!
Come here a second!
[fearful gasps]
We want to ask
you something!
Uh... We...
don't know...
Huh??
What's the deal?
I just said we want
to ask some questions,
that's--
Yowww!
Stop! fatass!
Don't go scaring girls like
that! or I'll kill you!
Hey! Sorry
about that!
[squeals]
Huh!?
Augh! Cut me some
slack, Yata!
Shut your mouth!
Haven't I told you
over and over, to
never threaten girls?!
Yeah, but I didn't
threaten them!
I mean, I had to
do something.
All this time,
you've only been
talking to guys!
We have to talk to
the girls, too.
No way, if you
want to find a guy,
you ask guys!
Whaaa?!
[Saruhiko]
You know, I can still
smell your virginity
a mile away.
You bastard.
Saruhiko!
What a shock to see you.
How did you find this place?
Right... It must
have been Anna.
And you can't be out here
on Mr. Kusanagi's orders;
he isn't stupid enough to
send the two of you out
alone. Right, Misaki?
I'm not surprised.
You never change.
Shut your mouth!
Don't you call me by that name,
damn it! And don't talk about
my people like you know them!
I know you. And you're
nothing but a traitor!
[chuckle] Can you blame me?
The fact of the matter is,
in the end, I wasn't like
you and the others.
My leaving HOMRA
was inevitable.
Yeah! You are damn right
about that part of it!
You sure weren't like
the rest of us!
You need to cool down, Yata.
The last thing we want to do
is make a scene.
So tell me, Mi-sa-ki.
How in the world
did you two manage
to sneak in here?
Let me put it to
you this way.
It's none of your
fuckin' business!
I happen to know that
security's pretty tight here.
Where's your pass?
Come on, show it
to me, MISAKI!
I just said,
it's none of
your business!
And stop calling me
by my first name.
When you do it, it
creeps me out.
That's right.
What a dummy I am.
I had completely forgotten.
You hate being called by
that name, don't you?
Mi... sa... ki!
You're really
askin' for it.
[Kamamoto]
Yata, stop!
Heh he he he he!
Don't get in trouble!
Remember what Mr. Kusanagi said!
We don't want Mikoto's
capture to be in vain!
Fighting that monkey
isn't going to
accomplish anything.
You're doing this
for Mikoto?
Really?
I'm afraid your hero
has lost his edge.
After all, he willingly
went to jail.
I wonder if that means
he's finally grown up?
He could teach
you a few things...
Mi... sa... kiiii.
[irritated sigh]
Let's get outta
here, Yata!
Hey, monkey!
You're gonna die!
He he he ha ha ha!
Fushimi,
Now ready for battle.
Heh! Not as sharp as
you used to be, monkey!
No...
Actually I'm stronger now.
In fact...
...I'm much stronger.
Bull shit!
Heh! What's the
matter, monkey?
Augh!
Yata!
Agh... Rrrgh...
Augh!
Didn't you hear what
I just told you?
Since I walked away from HOMRA
and the presence of Mikoto Suoh,
I've acquired even more power!
As you can see for yourself,
here's the proof!
Two colors!
Dual powers!
Damn!
Huh?
Keep your nose out of this
fight, punk! This is no
place for a loser like you!
You know what?
Agh!
He's actually right.
You need to stay out of this.
But Yata...
Heh heh.
Hey. Don't get cocky, just
because you've gained some
half-assed powers.
Whaddaya think you're
gonna take over control
of the country now?
I'm not interested in anything
as simple as controlling the
country. What I'm interested
in controlling...
is anything with
flesh and blood!
NnnngghRRAAHHH!
[chuckle]
[Seri]
Stand down!
Tch...
That's enough,
you two!
Put your sword away!
Now, Fushimi!
What do you think you're doing,
carrying on a fight like this,
out here in broad daylight?
Egh...
Your name's Misaki Yata, right?
Of the Red King's faction?
The skateboarding captain of
HOMRA's front-line. You also go
by the name...Yatagarasu.
Listen, lady,
I know all
about you, too!
You're the Blue King's
right-hand enforcer,
Seri Awashima.
Some people call you
'The Heartless Woman'!
Yeah, I've heard that
term used before.
But the only one who calls
me that is the owner of a
certain bar here in town.
Huh?
Be that as it may,
I must tell you that I cannot
condone your activities here
in the middle of a school day.
Unfortunately, there's too
much to lose if I decide
to make an issue of your
presence on this campus.
How about if the two of you
postpone your confrontation
to another time?
Tch! He's the one
who started the
whole thing!
I see. Perhaps
I didn't make
myself clear.
You will postpone this
confrontation. Immediately.
Or pay the price.
Was that better?
I have no reason to obey
orders from a Blue!
Wait a minute!
Let me tell you about your King.
[gasp]
All he does is complain
about how bad the food is.
Then he eats every crumb,
curls up, and goes to sleep.
I have to say,
he's quite a
piece of work.
Mr. Mikoto.
C'mon, let's go.
Bitch.
Should we be
letting them go?
We really have
no choice.
Fushimi.
Do you have something
you want to tell me?
I'm sorry for all this.
Save it. What did
you find out?
Find out about what?
Don't take me for a fool.
We both know you
were accessing the
school's database.
That should do it,
at least for now.
Hey, Yata. Let's get
our asses out of here.
Yata!
Yeah, I heard you.
And...? Huh?
We'll go.
After I get
an answer!
I want to ask just
one more person!
Come on, Yata!
Give it up!
[school chatter]
Hey! You!
Yes?
Shit.
I'm...sorry to bother you.
I'm looking for someone.
Have you seen this guy around?
What did you find?
Any evidence that
that boy is a student here?
He look familiar?
No, ma'am.
No. Sorry.
The suspect we're seeking...
...is not registered as a
student at this school.
I've never seen him before.
[Yata]
Fuck! I keep
hitting dead-ends!
Worse than that,
I had to run into
that monkey!
I can't afford to
waste any more time!
I've gotta find the
bastard who killed Tatara!
I'm not gonna let him
get away with this.
I had such crazy fun with
Mr. Mikoto and the guys.
And with one pull
of the trigger,
that son of a bitch
destroyed it all!
He's going to pay for
this with his life!
[Rikio]
Excuse me! Another order
of fried rice over here!
[Yata]
Damn it, do you
ever stop eating?!!
[Rikio]
You know, you should eat
something too, Yata.
You don't want to collapse
from starvation when we
find the killer, right?
[Yata]
Rikio...
[Rikio]
Yata.
But I'll tell you what,
why don't I finish your
plate for now?
[Munching] Oh yeah, can
I also get another plate
of pot stickers too!!
[Yata]
Hey! Ugh.
Next time on 'K'.
Episode 6,
'Karma'!
You fat-ass bastard!!