From now on, I'll be on my own.
Good-bye for now, Lieutenant.
Perhaps someday
we'll meet again.
The Silver King?
That's you?
Yes, it's me.
But at the same time,
I'm still Yashiro Isana.
The truth of the matter is,
Nothing's really changed.
[Seri]
Wait a minute! That was the
Sword of Damocles, but...
Misaki!
Keep your eyes on me, loser!
I'm the one you're fighting!
So stay focused!
Yeah... I hear you.
Fucking monkey!
Everyone stay on target!
We take control!
As quickly as possible!
Alright, let's take 'em out!
-Yeaah!
-All right!
-Yaaaahh!
[charge yells]
Yaaahh!
Huaaah!!
You don't have to stay.
You can go help your
forces, if you want.
Oh really? And ruin this
wonderful moment with you?
You have a point,
now that I think about it.
After all this will
be our last fight.
Munakata...
...Ready!
So. You came here to tell me
you're the new Colorless King?
Right.
I see. I appreciate you
coming all this way to
introduce yourself.
But I must say, regardless
of who or what you are,
I'm no longer
interested in...
What goes on
in the world?
Right. So...
Unfortunately for you,
I still do have an interest.
In your...
eternal...
immortality!
Hee hee, ha ha ha!
Bye-bye, now.
[Kuroh]
I see. And that's when
you swapped bodies?
Yes. Although it was more
like him snatching my body,
than us swapping.
But in spite of all his power,
He couldn't take over my
heart and soul.
That's the strength of
being the Silver King.
You may very well be right.
The Silver King is eternal.
His power can't be
harmed or destroyed.
Ah! That must be it!
The Colorless King's ability?
The power to affect other Kings!
Mmm.
When my power of
inviolability clashed with
his power to affect other
Kings, the result was mixed.
Sure, he took over my body,
But he failed to
capture my power.
which resulted in something
he may not have anticipated.
With nowhere else to go,
my soul escaped into the
body he had just discarded.
My amnesia was the result
of that transition.
I see! That explains why you
didn't get hurt when you fell
so very far from the sky!
No scar!
That means he murdered Tatara
Totsuka specifically, so he
could put the blame on you!
It was all part of
his master plan.
...the Colorless King.
I can tell you,
he's jumped from body to
body many times before.
He's already discarded
my original body, and
moved on to another one.
[Neko]
[gasp]
[Kuroh]
We have to find
Kukuri then!
[Shiro]
I've got to save her!
Can I count on you to help me?
Mm-hm!
Mmm.
[fighting]
[Seri]
Second Division!
Stay within your
perimeter!
Don't lose your formation!
At this rate, it's a
battle of attrition.
It's the Captain!
He's alive!
So is the Red King.
Mikoto lives!
[cheers from both sides]
- Yeah!
- Ha-haa!
- All right!
[nervous shouts]
- Ah!
- Oh no!
I'll be back.
You're in charge!
Wait! Lieutenant,
where are you going?
I'm coming to help you, Captain!
[Yashiro]
As I recall, you're one
of the people in charge
of SCEPTER 4, right?
Have you got a minute?
I'd like to talk.
Hold it right there!
Grr!
Bear with me, if you would.
It's been a while.
And this could take
me a bit to get
used to again.
Raa!
Trying to trick me with
another illusion?!
Uh?
Ah!
Whuaaa?!
Don't worry.
You're really
in no danger.
All I did was tune in
to the spectrum of
your biological wave,
which is synced to the Blue
Clan, and synched it to my
own, which is Silver.
In other words,
as my temporary
clansman,
I've given you the
ability to access the
Silver Sanctum's power
to manipulate gravity.
Uht! Put me down!
He he he he!
Take it easy.
Time to go!
[Seri]
Ah! AH!
Huuah!
Hell yeah! Let's get 'em!
Yeeeaahh!!
It's that guy!
The one from
the stadium!
[attack yells in unison]
Yaaaaaa!
We've got a problem.
What the hell?!
Black Dog...?!
I'm speaking to both clans!
On orders of the First
King, the Silver King,
you are hereby commanded to
cease fighting immediately!
Get outta here!
Why should we
listen to you?!
My King is the Red
King, Mikoto Suoh,
and no-one else!
I don't give a shit
about Silver!
- Yeah!
- Woo-hoo!
- All right!
That's right!
Blue King Reisi Munakata
is the only leader that
members of SCEPTER 4
will accept orders from!
We obey no other King!
Let me ask this!
If you're all so determined to
carry out this fight to the
finish, do you really know the
true intentions of both Kings?
Why did the Red King, Mikoto
Suoh, take over this island?
And why isn't the Blue King,
Reisi Munakata, taking
command of the fight himself?
Why are those two off trying to
settle their fight right now?
And doing it without bothering
to involve their loyal troops?
Even though your Kings may
have ordered you to fight,
I urge you to lay down
your weapons right now.
Lay them down and wait...
for your King's next orders!
Hm?
Shut your mouth, you stray dog!
You don't give orders here!
Hyaaah!
I hate to admit it,
but the Monkey's right!
There's no reason to trust
anything you have to say!
Bastard!
So be it. I never really
expected to settle this
battle with words alone.
Who wants to be first?
Mr. Kusanagi!
The Black Dog
is out front!
What?!
The Black Dog, eh?
The kid in the video
must also be here.
The King is... here.
Anna?
Huh?
[Yashiro]
Coming through!
[Neko]
Yaaa!
[Seri]
Ooof!
[moans]
That hurt. Hi.
Hope you don't mind.
U... Uh...
[Shohei]
Hey! What the hell?
What are you
guys doing here?!
I don't understand
what's happening!
Hssss!!
[sigh]
[Anna]
They're not the enemy.
These people are not the enemy!
[starts to faint]
Thank you for that.
Yes, the truth is,
I need everyone's help.
[all phones ring]
Huh? What the hell?
Seriously. I don't
get what's happening.
[Yashiro]
Um. I think I do.
Yeah sorry.
I'm pretty sure it's for me.
Would one of you
mind answering that?
[beep]
[all phones stop ringing]
Hello?
Am I speaking to Mikoto
Suoh's first in charge,
Izumo Kusanagi?
Uh, why, yes.
There should be a man standing
somewhere near you with a
silly look on his face.
Put him on the
line, would you?
Just a minute.
May I ask who's calling?
Daikaku Kokujoji...
...The Gold King.
We're not finished, are we?
More like we're just
getting started.
No more time-outs, pal.
We're going straight
through to the end.
Fine by me. It's not
like I would ever have
a choice in the matter.
Heh heh heh!
[evil voice]
That's right.
Fight to the end.
[voice reverts]
That's very strange.
It seems a little too quiet.
[evil voice]
You're right.
Okay, I'm
counting on you.
You'll have to hurry.
I can't believe it.
The day has gotten
really weird.
No kidding!
You can say
that again.
Sorry for all the trouble.
I'm afraid it couldn't be
helped.
[Kokujoji]
Hmph.
If you really feel that way,
how 'bout fulfilling some of
your responsibilities as a King?
Come on, that's mean.
You could give me a
little credit.
After all, isn't
that why I'm here?
You're there because
half of what's happening
is of your own doing.
You've gotten old and gray,
but you're still the same
old Lieutenant.
You just can't stop
lecturing me, can you?
[amused]
Hmm.
So, my friend...
How do you intend
to settle this?
I see. Well, that's
typical of you.
Just when I thought you had
finally returned, after being
gone for half a century.
I wish we could have seen
each other, one last time.
If that's how you really feel,
then stop this.
Not that you're
going to listen to me.
You know me too
well, Lieutenant.
But thanks for the offer.
Unfortunately,
just like the last time,
...this is 'so long'.
Alles gute mein freund.
Viel erfolg, Weismann.
[small sigh]
So...
Silver King,
your highness.
Just call me Yashiro Isana.
Very well, then. Yashiro.
As you proposed to us,
there's an escape plan
to evacuate the students
from the school.
At present, both clans
are under control,
and they're escorting
the students out.
Everything's
going smoothly.
However, we do
have one concern.
If the Colorless King
possesses a student,
he could escape our net.
Don't worry, he's
only targeting Kings.
That's the primary
reason he lured the
Red and Blue Kings here.
But that's not the only danger.
That's why we have to get all
the students evacuated.
If the swords were to fall,
there'd be mass destruction.
He's here!
[gasp]
[evil colorles king]
Me hee, ha ha ha ha!
None of you are getting
out of here alive!
Oh, you can run,
but you can't hide!
You're all mine,
and I have big
plans for your demise!
This voice is killing me!
Where's it coming from?!
You'll form a circle around
my fingertips, and I'll make
you dance until you drop!
I can't stand it, Shiro!
He's in my head!
Your experiences,
your strengths,
Guess he's finally
making his move.
your weaknesses,
all of it belongs to me, now!
He couldn't have caught
us at a worse time!
We're not ready for this!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
[trembling with pain]
Nnhhahh...
Neko!
I am going to
need your power.
More than you've
ever used before.
What? What do you
want me to do, Shiro?
Something extremely important.
Y'see, to this day, I've never
had my own clansman.
I've always had to work alone.
I'm asking...
Will you be the very
first one to help me out?
Of course I will! [sob]
Silly, I would do anything for
you! After all this time,
don't you know that by now?!
I'm not going to let
you hurt these people!
Are we going to be killed?
I can't stand this anymore!
Think about it! While
they're fighting each other,
we have a great opportunity!
Now's our chance
to escape!
How are we gonna do that?!
They're everywhere!
We'll never be able
to get away!
Face it, we're
gonna die here!
- Oh man!
- [crying]
- Oh no!
Hey, stop it!
We can't give up here!
[crying]
[gasp]
Aren't you...?
Hey! Wait a minute!
You're the guy in
that video aren't you?!
It's your fault that this
whole thing is happening--
Hold on a second!
It is him!
Have we met?
...somewhere before?
Yeah, you're--
Uhh...
I can't remember.
Isa-- I almost had it.
It's very important that you all
get off this island, right now.
And trust me when I say,
I won't let anybody hurt you.
That's good, but,
who exactly are you?
Just a friend.
I don't know you.
So why should I
trust you?
I'm confused.
Why are you here?!
Hm? I'm here to
protect you.
I know all of you.
But how can that be?
It's quite simple.
You're my precious friends,
every one of you.
I'm going to show you
all the way out now.
Please trust me,
and follow my lead.
Damn it!
Weismann!
[Yashiro]
I found you.
Don't involve
innocent bystanders.
Let's you and I
put an end to this.
[weak breaths, faints]
Neko!
Shiro...
Did I... do okay?
Yes. Thank you
for all your help.
So he is the
Silver King.
Truly.
Were you able to get
everyone out safely, Anna?
Mmm.
Thank you so much,
both of you.
Watch over her,
if you would.
Of course we will.
And Munakata
and Suoh?
Please!
I wish I could reassure you.
I can't promise anything.
But I'll do the best I can.
To all of you,
Viel glück!
[panting]
End me?
Heh heh heh heh!
An exercise in futility!
[giggles]
Once I've overcome and
neutralized the power of the
Red and Blue Kings, everything
will be mine for the taking!
[giggles]
But can you seriously
pull it off?
What a question!
Of course he can!
After all, he is the King!
I'm the strongest
King of all!
[giggles]
Heh!
He he he he!
Hehe.. he... eh.
Help me!
I am the First King, also know as The Silver King.And I am eternal.
Time has stood still for me since thatfateful day back in 1945.
Or so I had hoped.
But nothing can stay the same forever.
We must change at some point.
No, we gradually change as we interactwith the people around us.
Neko, thanks to your unconditional love, I was able to find my own place to call home.
Kuro, without your tacit belief in me,
I couldn't have faced the truth about myself.
I am Adolf K. Weismann.
But now I am also
Yashiro Isana.
And my friends
call me 'Shiro'.
I am here to protect them.
They're dear to me, and I won't let anyone hurt them. Ever.
Lieutenant, my dear sister... I won't runaway anymore.
Next time on "K",
The final episode:
"King".
Everything will be just fine,because Shiro is our King!