JANUARY, 1945 DRESDEN
[German]
Die apparatur ist bereit.
Das Kamera aäuft schon.
Die Schiefertafel
ist in Ordnung.
Experimentieren
sofort anfangen.
Und wo ist die Maus?
Doctor Weismann will
be arriving with it
at any moment.
[Adolph Weismann]
Here I am.
It's all up to you,
my furry little
rodent friend.
I'm counting on a
perfect performance.
So make me look good.
[researcher]
They're calling it the
Extra Alpha Group.
The mouse is a prototype,
and it's under the
influence of the Slate.
The blue mouse
is in place.
The Slate is reacting.
Sword Aura is confirmed.
Huh??
[Daikaku]
Amazing! Could it have the
same effect on human beings?
It's just the tip
of the iceberg.
The intensity level of the link
with the Slate, is proportional
to the complexity of the brain.
More precisely, the deviation
from the law of causality,
creates the Fieldback Group.
which engulfs beta bodies in
the vicinity as its intensity
increases in a manner of
geometric progression.
As a result...
An army of super-humans
is born, huh?
No...
That is not my goal.
This will bring
everybody happiness.
[explosion]
[coughing]
[Klaudia Weismann]
Addie!
Huh?!
Oh! Hi,
sis!
Hmm.
Hello, Lieutenant.
Is my baby brother
bothering you again
with his nonsense?
No, I was just showing
him my experiment.
Right, Lieutenant?
And his results are
quite astounding.
I must say I am
truly amazed.
I told you, sis.
However,
I'm worried that the
Lieutenant thinks I've been
working on some kind of
advanced instrument of war,
and that wouldn't be good!
What a horrible thought!
That's enough!
Mh! Augh!
You need to learn to
hold your tongue.
Don't forget, we're
receiving a very nice
stipend for your research.
C'mon, please let go!
That really hurts!
Eh...
[nervous giggle]
Ha ha!
Lieutenant Kokujoji.
Disregard that, please.
Could we make this
off-the-record?
Oh! That's no problem.
I'm unable to understand
the technical jargon
most of the time.
Uh?
[giggling]
[sigh]
[air sirens]
[bombs dropping, explosions]
Huh?!
[sobbing]
Lieutenant...
My sister's gone.
[Adolph]
All has been swept away
and lost forever.
The war is finally over.
But everything
is not lost.
Yes, it is.
at least for me.
I must ask you
once again.
This is good bye,
Lieutenant.
Are you running away?
Why would you give
all of this up?
Weismann!
Good afternoon. We will
now resume our coverage of
the mid-air collision
between the Himmelreich,
owned by international magnate,
Adolph K. Weismann,
and a Metropolitan
Police helicopter, which
occurred earlier today.
A police statement released
after the incident
identifies both crafts.
Oh! You mean that
airship that crashed?
Well, I believe they said the
whole thing was caused by a
cult leader or something.
I have heard that the man
up there is so incredibly
powerful that people refer
to him as a living god.
Well if that's true, Amen.
Oh, wow! Take me on a
heavenly shopping spree!
That would mend
my broken heart!
[giggle] Well, that's not
gonna happen to you now!
His blimp crashed!
I'm with Scepter Four.
Who's in charge here?
Well sir.
I guess it's them.
[ringing]
Go ahead.
[Himori]
The Usagi are here already!
[gasp]
All right.
They certainly
are quick.
[police officer]
No, ma'am. We haven't found
any bodies here at all.
In fact, we were told that
the cockpit was empty.
Hmm.
[Yujiro]
Lieutenant!
Mm?
Chopper Seven crew's been
located! I have the report!
They were found unconscious
inside a hanger at Suzugaya
airport, but they're
responsive now.
Unfortunately, the last
thing that any of them can
remember is getting ready
to board their helicopter.
What?
Then the only question is,
who was actually flying
this chopper?
Damn!
Ah! Shit!
Hey, give me a pry bar?
A pry bar, a crowbar,
anything useful.
Uh?
Huh?
[Kukuri] [megaphone]
Hello, everyone!
Thanks for all
your hard work!
As your Student Council
Representative, I am very proud.
Are you running short on
any equipment, do you have
your paper work ready,
and would any of you
be available for a
new task right now?
Hey! Look around.
Everyone's already busy
working on something.
[Sota]
How about getting that
guy to help you again?
He must be around
here somewhere.
[giggle]
Right, right!
Who're you talking about?
Well, you know who I mean!
Uh...
We're almost finished, Sota.
We can spare you.
Why don't you go help her?
Huh?!
Uh-h... Oh.
Well, if you wouldn't mind.
Ah, hmm.
Well, that was awkward,
but at least it got me
off the hook!
Sumika, I could use
your help as well!
Augh!
[Kukuri]
The storeroom's completely
crammed with stuff,
so we borrowed a
vacant room in
the dormitory.
[Sumika]
Why there?
[Kukuri]
If we keep the finished
costumes in there,
all we have to do is
go to a nearby room
to change into them.
That makes sense.
What's the matter, Kukuri?
[Sumika]
Hey, what are you doing?
Ah!
I'm sorry.
I spaced out.
The first thing we need to do
is clear the room before we
can put our things inside.
The resident advisor told me
that everything here could go
into the trash. So let's start
throwing everything out.
[both]
Yes, ma'am!
SHOW SOME RESPECT.
Nice to see you!
I can use your help, too.
From what I can tell It
isn't quite unoccupied,
even though no one's
here right now.
Maybe someone was living
here and just moved out.
He he! Or maybe someone
with nothing better to do
just comes in here to nap.
Hey, I bet that
guy uses it.
Yeah!
Kukuri's friend?
Yup, that one.
Who is he?
Uh...
Huh!
Huh...
Mm.
Fourth King,
Reisi Munakata is here.
I will show him in sir.
So tell me, are you
here to fight or talk?
A King coming to the Slate is
an extremely rare occurrence.
Hm.
I come without my sword.
I'm here to have a
conversation.
That is all I plan to do.
It is good to
see you again,
Your Excellency.
Let's dispense with
the pleasantries.
Very well, but you must allow
me to express my gratitude to
you for interceding in the
recent Royal Blue situation.
We were able to use all the
information obtained through
extralegal means, for the good
of the public. I'm sure you--
I'm running out of patience.
Get to the point.
Very well. Then let
me jump right in.
[Reisi]
I believe that the body your men
retrieved earlier from the wreck
of the Himmelreich airship,
is the Silver King,
also known as
Adolph K. Weismann.
That's correct.
The origin of all the
Kings began with Weismann,
as he was the First King.
And his physical components
are such that they can
never change, correct?
Just what are you implying?
The 'Immortal King', who
retained the youth and vigor of
his prime for more than half a
century, has now suddenly died.
I have questions about the
circumstances of his passing.
I'd like your permission
to examine his body.
Hmm.
Well that was pleasant.
It's good that some
things never change.
The old man is as
stubborn as ever.
But he's indispensible.
He still functions as the
backbone of this country.
However, as mighty and
powerful as he is, the one
thing he isn't, is immortal.
I wish that were also true
about the Silver King.
We'll continue to
treat this as a crisis.
Remain alert and ready.
Yes sir!
[ringing]
Mm?
Hello there! Helloo!!!
Got a minute?
Oh, you're wondering who
I am, aren't you?
Well, I'm the guy you've
been looking for.
Hrrh.
I'm calling about your pal.
His name was Totsuka, wasn't it?
I was the one
who killed him.
I feel bad for him now!
Ooh hoo hoo hoo!
He's probably lonesome all by
himself in the other world.
Don't you think he
could use some company?
I could kill everyone,
starting with Kusanagi,
and then Yata.
You like that idea? Huh?
Shall I do it?
C'mon, just say
the word!
Hey, man, are you
alive in there?
Maybe next time,
I'll get that young
girl to entertain me.
You know who I mean,
that pretty one you
always have with you?
Her name's Anna, right?
I'm sure she's gonna be
lots of fun!
I like 'em young
and innocent!
Oh! That was a real eye opener!
Ah ha ha ha ha ha!
Must have hit a nerve!
Gotcha now!
So long, loser,
you're all mine!
Not so fast.
Two can play
this game.
Huh?
Ah!
Aaaahhh!!!
Hmf.
[gasps]
Was that explosion
from the room we
were just in?!
[panic]
Whoa!
I found you.
Mikoto...
Huh?
[alarm buzzing]
I'm still getting nothing
over here.
Mister Fushimi!
Don't make a move. Stand down.
We're not to do anything.
Those are the orders.
But, sir!
[chuckle]
Third King,
Mikoto Suoh.
It is my duty to remind you,
that you are in the custody
of Scepter Four.
You have not been granted
permission to leave!
Stop right now!
I said stop!
Call in the second team!
It's no
use...
Hey! Good
to see you!
Sir!
We're glad
you're out!
[Izumo]
So, Boss...
Mm?
Did you find who you've
been looking for?
A school-boy on the Island.
All right!
Awesome!
Aww yeah!
Just where I said he was!
I was right!
Uh, hee hee!
[Kamamoto]
I thought I
said that?
[Yata]
You never did!
[Kamamoto]
Well, I was thinking it!
C'mon, let's go.
[Yata]
We're ready!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Mikoto, yours is the only red...
But I know that you've already
made your decision...
So I won't try to stop you from going.
What's wrong, Anna? Getting a little nervous?
No
You're a strong girl. Now, let's take of things
so we can go home
Okay.
Don't worry. Everything's going to work out.
We both know how strong Mikodo is, right?
Ismo?
Yes?
Thank you.
Next time on 'K'. Episode 10
'Kaleidoscope'
I'm the one who should be saying that.
Thank you, Anna.