[doorbell]
Who is it?
Hello there!
I have a pizza
for you!
What?
Uhh, I have a
delivery, pepperoni!
Y'see?
Okay, time to go.
[snicker]
Augh!
[over phone]
Yata, it's a go. Move it.
You idiot! What do you
mean, 'you don't know'?!
Go find them!
They went after our guns
and even our explosives?
They pulled our guys
over and robbed the car.
We don't want those
guns traced ba--
[shatter]
What the hell's
going on?!
Are you little
brats from HOMRA?!
Hah!
So, This is the guy
we're looking for.
You see?
Look at the gun he's holding.
It comes from your place.
Any idea how he might
have been able to get it?
(Small CT pain breaths)
Now relax. Just
take your time,
and try to remember.
[explosion]
Huh? Hm.
Yo!
You're here a little
too early, Mikoto.
[flinches]
[sigh]
It says he doesn't know.
Too bad.
Let's go.
T'ch! This was a
huge waste of time!
All this action
made me hungry.
[explosion]
Huh?
[exhausted sigh]
We have enough personnel.
Keep the others out.
As you wish.
They're on the next floor up!
[explosion]
The Blues are here!
SCEPTER Four has
entered the
building, gentlemen.
What do you want
to do, Mikoto?
Burn them all.
Heh! All right!
Let's do it, guys!
[chanting together]
Yeah!! No blood!
No bone! No ash!
The Third King, Mikoto
Suoh, has apparently
activated his sanctum.
Weismann level
at 75, 80...
Vertical over!
Any minute now,
we should see the
Sword of Damocles.
It's huge!
Very well, then.
We will advance with our
swords in our hands.
We will triumph,
because our cause
is just.
Everyone, draw
your swords!
[unison]
Ma'am!
Akiyama, ready!
Benzai, ready!
Kamo, ready!
Domyoji, ready!
Enomoto, ready!
Fuse, ready!
Goto, ready!
Hidaka, ready!
Munakata. Ready!
[transit announcer]
Now arriving on Track Two,
the 8:05 train,
which will be departing
for the campus of
Ashinaka High School.
Please stand clear
of the doors.
Just a reminder for all of you
who are busy preparing for the
upcoming school festival.
Please don't get carried away
with any unofficial activities,
and always remember to
uphold the tradition and
honor of the school.
DIE.
[alarm jingle]
[hums choral movement
of Beethoven's 9th Symphony]
I can't believe this,
but I forgot to bring
my lunch today!
I've heard that
one before!
Will you share?
The last time I did
that, you ended up
eating everything!
You know Shiro...?
What?
Doesn't anybody cook
at your house?
Oh, you mean Yashiro Isana?
Do you think he has
any friends at all?
Oh, please!
I don't know how he gets away
with this stuff, but he seems
to be really popular.
Maybe it's because
he's such a joker.
But now that I think about it,
I've never seen him hang out
with anybody in particular.
I know one thing.
He's not getting
enough veggies.
Really...
His diet has way too
much meat in it.
'cause he only eats
main courses!
So today, I'm
gonna fix that!
I'm doing it by giving him this
nutritionally balanced
combination of nimono, salad,
and cooked veggies!
Huh?
He's gone!
Where did he go?!
[humming Beethoven's 9th]
Hey Shiro!
You want some?
Yes, please, and thanks!
That looks really good!
You can have
mine, too!
Yummy!
I'm not eating
all of mine!
Try this!
Thanks!
Here's another one!
Let's go!
Sure!
Whoops!
Caught ya, you thief!
Hm?
[humming Beethoven]
Whoop! Sorry!
YOU'RE TOO KIND.
SHOW SOME RESPECT.
He sure disappears quickly!
Mmm?
Now where did you go, mister?
YOU'RE TOO KIND.
You're pretty upset.
I guess it must be love.
No, that's not
what's going on.
Hm?
It's a strange feeling
I can't explain.
It's like, if I take
my eyes off him,
he'll just fade away.
Mm?
[deep inhale]
[meow]
Huh?
Oh! Hello, there!
Everything's just great here in
Japan! What a wonderful country!
Japan will soon be
destroyed, Weismann.
[nasty chuckle]
[gasp]
Neko, did you just
say something?
[meow]
You are like a
sweet, red rose
to me, my darling!
That won't work!
Say your line like
you're singing it!
You gotta project
from your diaphragm!
What's going on?
Where's the teacher?
We're all prepping for
the school festival!
He said we could have
the afternoon off.
Hey, guys!
Can someone run an errand
for the student council?
Someone who's free? Anyone?
Huh?
Hmm.
Thanks a lot, 'Shiro. This will
be a big help. Here we go!
I've sent you the list.
You should be getting it now.
Okay?
Hm?
Uh...
Hmm...
Weird...
What? You don't have
your PDA with you?
[embarrassed]
Heh heh...
Fine. I'll write
it down for you.
Oh wait, but you
need to have your PDA,
or they won't let
you off campus!
Heh heh heh!
Don't worry
about it.
I want to get a snack on the
way home, do you have time?
Sure. Where do you want to go?
Let's try that new place
the guys told us about.
No problem at all.
Let's see. First I go to the
Kagitama Store over in Shizume
and pick up the fireworks,
Hand them the voucher
and the money,
then head back to the Ashinaga
High School Student Council
and turn in the receipt.
Nice weather!
Mreoooww!!
Ah!
Oh, right. Don't lose focus.
Complete the assignment
and get the receipt back
to the school by six.
[sigh] Okay, so where's
this place again?
I'm supposed to turn right...
when I reach the giant screen.
What?!
Shit, let's go!
Tch.
The fire lights glow.
shadows of a foreign king.
Hm?
Meow?
Come again!
Thanks!
[chuckles]
Oh!
Huh?
Mroww!
Ungh!
[mew]
Uh...
Hello?
Ah... Ahh... Aahh!
Excuse me!
You're not getting away!
HYAHH!
Aughh!
Ah!
Hmf.
Sorry! Coming through!
Agh!
Augh!
[gurgle]
Huaah!
Shit!
Who was that guy?!
Kuroh Yatogami,
the Black Dog.
Apparently, this is
going to be more
difficult than I
thought.
Oh well.
No way around it...
We'll have to go with Plan B.
Yaahhh!
Meoow!
Mew?
You brought us back
to the station!
Thank you.
You saved
our butts.
See ya.
I am a vassal of the
former Seventh King,
Ichigen Miwa.
Kuroh Yatogami.
"Vassal of the Seventh King,
Ichigen Miwa?"
Ah! That's an
interesting name!
How do you do? I'm Yashiro.
Yashiro Isana--
In compliance with my
Master's dying wish,
I will slay the evil king,
now.
Huh?
What... uh... King?
Huh? That's weird.
I don't understand...
[confusion from crowd]
[Humming Beethoven's
Ninth Symphony]
Hey, how're you doing? It's
a nice night out, isn't it?
I came up to film the city
lights, since it's so clear.
[hearty chuckling]
It's beautiful.
I'm Tatara Totsuka.
What's your name?
[bang]
I, my friend,
am the Seventh King,
the colorless king!
I've been out here,
waiting for someone.
Nice night, you say?
Yes, It is.
A very nice night!
Someone's hijacked the
city's urban network.
Track the signal source
and shut him down!
That's what we're
trying to do.
Heh.
It's so unlike you to pull
off such a cheap move.
Hm.
Mrowr!
That's you, right?
Answer me.
Uh...
Well, it sure
looks like it.
Hi, I'm Yashiro Isana, the
protagonist of this show,
who's in the middle of
getting himself killed.
I mean really, What do
you think of someone who
points a sword at a
person they've just met?
I'd say they're rude,
and should go back where
they came from!
What did I ever do to
bring this on? I'm just
a regular kid, trying
to get through school!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Hey, why are you
stabbing me?! Cut it out!
I'm bleeding!
Next time on 'K';
Episode 2, 'Kitten'.
Uh, does anyone have a
bandage I could borrow?