[tired sigh]
Huh!?
Hey! What's the matter?
[Kukuri]
Look! What is that thing?
- Whoa!
- What just happened?!
- Huh??
[crowd panic intensifies]
[megaphone feedback]
I want everyone to
stay calm, alright?
Haven't you kids learned
anything in this school?
During emergencies like this,
there should be no pushing,
no running, and no talking,
whatsoever.
It's important that
each of you obey these
three rules right now.
Please try to understand
that we're not here to
hurt any of you.
If we get your full cooperation,
we won't be here long.
So you want us to find the
young man in the video, at
which point we're through?
Does that about sum it up?
That's right.
Just see to it that you
guys find that kid.
I'm just one of
the "guys" huh?
Find Totsuka's murderer!
Even if you have to
tear this place apart!
-Yeah!
-Alright come on!
-Let's get him!
Where'd Mikoto go?
Don't worry about him.
Just focus on the job you
need to be doing right now.
Go on.
Get going, Yatagarasu.
[Kusanagi]
As of this moment,
the island of Ashinaka
and the high school itself
is under the control of HOMRA.
Let me repeat. HOMRA is
now in complete control
of Ashinaka High School.
All students are ordered to
follow our instructions.
As long as you do that, you'll
have nothing to fear from us.
We are trying to locate
a friend of ours.
We have projected an image
of him on all screens,
so take a look.
If you recognize him, please
inform the nearest member of
HOMRA immediately.
Any of you got
information for us,
or what?!
Once he's been located,
we'll leave and you can
return to your normal routine.
I've got a feeling you
know him, am I right?
C'mon, talk!
I've never seen that guy!
I know nothing about him.
Why is this happening?!
All clear here.
Class A check
is finished.
Class B! You're up next!
C'mon!
Hurry up!
[Chiho]
Don't be
so nasty!
Huh?!
What was that?!
[disapproving grunt]
Tch!
Shit!
I'm so scared.
They won't stay long.
Our first priority is the
safety of the students.
Huh?
Yes. Understood.
The West A Area is clear.
Huh? A student
is resisting?
Well, do what you have to do.
But only as a last resort.
We're not here to
hurt these kids.
[click]
[ring]
Mm?
Oh! Yata!
Is that so? It didn't take
them long to show up.
Prompt as usual.
Be sure to keep me posted
if they make a move.
Attention HOMRA. Attention
HOMRA. The Blue Dogs are paying
us a visit. Men near the gates,
tighten up your guard.
You think the
suspect is actually
on campus right now?
He is.
However...
You can't quite
pinpoint him?
Uh huh.
Well, it doesn't really matter,
we have the whole island sealed
off anyway.
If he's here,
he's trapped like a rat.
-what are we gonna do?
-this sucks!
-I hope we get to move out soon.
The tension
has grown.
Do we know what's
going on inside?
You're getting on my nerves!
Stop bugging me.
[in unison]
Yes! Sorry, sir!
Meow!
[Seri]
It is inexcusable. Not only did
I allow the Red King to escape,
but I'm also responsible for
what has happened afterward.
I take full responsibility.
It's highly unusual to
see you so humble, but I
must say, Lieutenant,
I'm liking this new look.
Thank you, Captain.
However, I think it
is extremely arrogant
for you to assume
that you are the one and
only one responsible for
stopping the Red King.
Yes, sir.
[Reisi]
Let's put that behind us.
Right now we're facing a more
troublesome situation.
How so?
Mikoto Suoh and his red
clansmen have taken over
the island high school.
This takeover can
mean only one thing.
That he's after Tatara's
Totsuka's killer.
I'm convinced that's
his main agenda.
But, we might have a total
disaster on our hands if the
person he is after,
is also a king.
The Colorless King, I assume.
[Reisi]
Yes. The Seventh King, the
Colorless King, is unlike
any of the other kings.
Each successive generation
exhibits a unique power
different from the prior ones.
And no-one knows what that
power is, until it shows itself.
So it could possibly
disrupt the relationships
between kings.
And would have an effect
much like a joker in a
deck of cards.
You know, I've always
despised the joker.
Even the picture of
the jester on the card
reeks of trickery.
There's no sense
of honesty or
fairness about it.
Especially when it's
not in the hand that
I happen to be playing.
Good grief.
It would have been so
much simpler if he had
remained a recluse like
his predecessor, Miwa.
[Seri]
So the fact is that,
at any moment,
the short-fused Red King could
come into contact with the
unpredictable Colorless King.
If that happens, it could
create an extremely
volatile situation.
And what's more troubling,
we don't really know if the
Colorless King can even be
captured.
Our only alternative is to
restrain the Red King again.
At this point, an all-out
war with the Red Clansmen
seems inevitable.
Mm.
All units are ready
for battle, sir!
You may give the order
whenever you wish!
Seri.
Do you mind if I make a
rather selfish request?
Eh?
[Reisi & Mikoto]
Snow.
What brings you here?
I saw it had started
to snow, Mikoto.
Sure has. So?
Your Red needs to stay visible.
Don't let the snow cover it.
Hmm.
Your Red is the prettiest
aura I've ever seen.
Are you sure you're
not too cold?
When I'm next to you
I don't feel the cold.
It's not too hot
or too cold.
It feels just right.
[Izumo]
Well, what can I say?
I've had a lot of experience,
but I've never had a girl come
on quite as strong as you.
I don't know what
else to tell you.
Yep. Okay, sure,
I'll take care of it.
But listen, for the time being,
I want this to be a secret just
between the two of us, alright?
Yeah. Okay.
I'll call you later.
[whistle]
What is it?
And will you stop whistling for
me like I'm a pet dog you're
going to sic on the mailman?
You've got it all wrong.
You're like a crow.
with superior hi-def
night vision.
How does it
look out there?
Nothing unusual to report.
Everything is under control.
[Yata]
A few idiots tried to make
an escape, but not the
shithead we're looking for,
so we chased them back into
the school's main building.
It looks like the
Blues have the area
beyond the bridge
completely surrounded.
If they crash the party,
we'll have to engage them
in all-out war.
I say, why not
bring it on?
I'm ready for a scrap!
Don't get yourself
all worked up.
It's a well-known fact
that your abilities
are much sharper,
when you don't let
your emotions get
the better of you.
And just how on earth am
I supposed to stay calm?!
Yata, I'm just telling
you for your own good.
But I guess you wouldn't
be you if you didn't go
around acting like an
idiot at times like this.
Hey, man!
I've noticed that you go
beyond ballistic whenever
Fushimi is in the mix.
Since you two were
partners back in the day,
I really shouldn't blame you.
With all due respect,
you're about to make me
go ballistic right now!
Fushimi betrayed me
and that's never
gonna change!
Oh!
[Kusanagi]
By the way, since you'll
be guarding this area for
the rest of the night,
there's something I have to
tell you, but I need you to
keep it to yourself.
That's awesome, Boss!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[sigh]
[Yata]
You bastard!
You did what?!
You heard me, Yata.
I said I went and
joined SCEPTER Four.
You've betrayed us!
Why, Fushimi, why?!
It doesn't make sense!
Why join up with the
Blues of all people?!
Egh!
Did you forget
this mark?
The symbol of
our true pride!
We've sworn our loyalty
to HOMRA with this!
Loyalty.
See, Misaki, I just wiped
out my true pride in HOMRA.
It's all gone.
I'm sorry if you
think I betrayed you.
But I need to go in a
different direction.
I want to use my special
power to engage in something
other than playing games
with gang bangers.
I'm sick to death of
being a punk from HOMRA.
Nice! This is your
gratitude to the
man who took you in
off the streets?
How dare you
disrespect him!
I know, but I must move on.
[chuckles] I don't wanna
waste my life playing the fool.
I want to be somebody who's
a lot more important.
You think you're
better than us?
Fuck you!
One day I'm going
to kill you!
Fuse.
Yes sir!
Did we get the go-ahead
for the raid yet?
No, sir. We're to
stay put unless
something out of the
ordinary happens.
Orders from the Lieutenant
remain unchanged.
Heh.
[Kusanagi]
I wonder how your boys feel
about you relaxing as they run
around all over the island.
The king naps
while they work.
That's what you're supposed
to do when you're king.
I think you may have a
misconceived impression
of your ruling duties.
I'm not saying you have to
necessarily work with us,
but do you intend to just
lie around waiting?
Yeah.
You think he'll
make a move?
Yeah.
Hm.
Well we, your loyal subjects,
will do our best to catch
him, in the event that
doesn't happen.
[Kusanagi]
The first time I saw
Totsuka looking at you,
I thought the guy might not
be dealing with a full deck.
You gave him a death stare, but
he approached you anyway, like
you were a pair of old buddies.
What made him go around
boasting that you would
someday be a king and he
would be your vassal?
And then you actually did
become a king, like he said.
I had thought you weren't
right for the job.
All I saw was that you were
like a bomb with a short fuse.
But Totsuka saw
something different.
He thought you could
bring people together
and protect them.
Hmm. I think your
assessment of me was more
correct than his was.
[Kusanagi]
To my surprise, you gave
up your quick temper and
became a strong king
who looked after his
people and served side
by side with them,
never making them feel
that you were superior
because of your position.
And we used to have so much
fun hanging out with you,
and laughing about all our
adventures together.
You were truly one with
the people you ruled.
[sigh] Stop traveling
down memory lane.
Yeah, you're right. There's no
point in clinging to the good
old days. What's past is past.
Anna, you better
come with me now.
Mikoto needs to take
care of some business.
Mmm.
Somebody's here
to see you.
[Kusanagi]
When all is
said and done,
we couldn't have asked
for a better king.
Mm?
Hm.
Isn't sharing the same
air with me supposed
to be toxic for you?
Not any more toxic than
the air I'm about to
blow in your direction.
Heh.
[Munakata]
Let me be very direct.
Mm?
Just peacefully relinquish
control of this school.
I'll try to overlook the way
you've been involving innocent
pupils in your search, but I
can't guarantee it.
However, if you agree to comply
now, we can settle this before
things get out of hand.
Gee, that's a really
super suggestion.
[Mikoto]
But you can't actually
think I'll do it.
[Munakata]
It's not a suggestion.
It's an ultimatum.
You've gone too far,
Suoh.
You need to let me find
Totsuka's murderer.
I promise this guy who claims
to be the Colorless King will
be caught and convicted.
Mm...
If you give me your consent
to go after him, I'll give
you my word that you can
chose how he'll be executed.
That's an offer that's
almost too good to pass up.
But I have to
say no thanks.
I'm sure I needn't remind
you of the very precarious
shape your sword of Damocles
is in at the present time.
And because the sword is
a symbolic representation
of a king,
it always reveals the
truest impression of
the king's condition.
Sad to say, your
sword will come
crashing down soon.
Don't believe it.
I know that right
now, your Weismann
level is precariously
close to the edge.
If you take on the added
burden of killing a
king, it will certainly
exceed your limit.
You will cause a
repeat of the Kagutsu
Crater tragedy.
And you will have to
give up your right
to be a king.
Why not step down now,
and avoid all this?
I have never taken any action
as king but this is one thing
I want to accomplish.
Think about the innocent
students who could be
harmed by your actions.
And you know what will
happen to your own men.
Am I making
myself clear?
I have to settle my
business on my own terms.
And you do, too.
Am I making
myself clear?
If that's all,
I think we're
done here.
You are stubborn.
It's impossible to
ever reason with you.
C'mon, you didn't come here
yourself because you thought you
could change my mind did you?
That's not like you.
No, it isn't. I just came
here to see a an old friend.
Hm.
Better go back.
You're positive?
Last chance to
walk away.
Nope, my mind's made up.
Ugh.
Fool.
[Yashiro]
Finally, we're back!
[gasp]
Uh!
Whoah! It looks like we must
have been burglarized!
On what planet would
burglars blast a hole
in the floor just to
get in and out?!
[Neko]
No-o-o-o-o!!!
Look what happened
to my bowl!
It was my favorite!!
We were lucky to escape
when the airship burst
into a massive fireball,
And it looks like we're lucky
to have been away when this
apartment was trashed.
We had to come back when we
heard the entire school island
was under HOMRA's control,
[Kuroh]
But I never thought the Red
King would be here as well.
And the outside perimeter of
the school is guarded by the
Blues. The island has been
taken over by the clans.
[sigh] Guess hunting for
my true identity will be
put on hold for a while.
Unfortunately,
it had to come
to this.
In a worst-case scenario,
this island could become a
battleground for a clan war.
Maybe we shouldn't have
come back after all.
I've told you already!
This is our home,
we have to stay here!
It's the best place to be!
Let's get busy and clean it up!
[Yashiro]
Neko's right.
We need to do a major
cleanup job to make
it livable again.
Once we're finished with
that, we have to figure
out what to do next.
Why don't we ask
Master Ichigen?
What?
You said he was
supposed to have the
ability to see into the
future, am I right?
Maybe he would have some
insight, and could lend us
some advice on what to do;
it would sure be helpful.
I doubt it.
We know what to do next.
Think about it for a minute.
Oh!
We need to go rescue
Kukuri and all the other
students at the school.
We don't need Master Ichigen
to tell us what's obvious.
Mm-hm!
Yeah. You're right,
as usual.
Now, first things first.
We need to start by
discovering where Kukuri
and the others are hiding.
Neko! Let's go!
Huh?! But what about..!
It's alright. We'll
come straight back here
as soon as we're done.
Bye bye.
[Kusanagi]
Oh boy. Looks like there's no
turning back now. Right, Mikoto?
[Mikoto]
Yeah...
[Kusanagi]
Just between you and me,
there was a time when I
thought everything would
work out for HOMRA.
You, me, Yata, Rikio,
Anna, Totsuka.
We'd all be fighting and
arguing every single day,
but still have a good
time and always end up
at the usual place.
[Mikoto]
Yeah.
[Kusanagi]
But oh well. We've come
this far, so we might
as well finish this.
Heh. Let's do it.
[Mikoto]
Hey... Izumo.
[Kusanagi]
Yeah?
[Mikoto]
Sorry for all the trouble.
[Kusanagi]
No problem.
[Mikoto]
Next time on K,
Episode Eleven,
'Killer'.
[Kusanagi]
We're going out with a bang.
There'll be no blood,
no bone and no ash.