[SHIGURE grunting]
[SHIGURE]
Hmm?
Okay.
[yawns]
[HIROYUKI snoring]
[panting]
[SHIGURE]
Good morning!
Hey, Genzo. Nice day, huh?
Are you hungry?
I have some yummy
nom‐noms for you.
[snoring]
Wow, I can't believe
Carmilla stayed out all night.
Jeez.
Ahh...
Just another
typical morning, huh?
Okay, I'm gonna
start on breakfast.
There you are!
[groans]
[coughing]
[ANIMAL MASK]
What do you want now, Katherine?
My name's Altena!
I happen to be the
princess of this kingdom!
How can you confuse those names?
They aren't even that similar!
Honestly? I don't care.
Gah!
Ugh! How rude!
[growls]
No. None of that is important.
Please listen.
Today, I need you to promise me
that you'll fulfill
your duty as a hero!
No way.
[groans]
You've been coming
here every day, Princess.
Starting to feel
a little stalkery.
Are you saying I'm a stalker?
By the way could you be
a dear and fetch me some salt.
Meals in this house seem to be
lacking in the taste department.
And to think you have
the nerve to call us rude?
Now then.
Since we're done eating,
let's get straight to business.
Listen, Genzo.
Here we go.
I'm afraid I have terrible news.
According to my knights, the
Demon King from another world
attacked a nearby orc village.
Yeah, more like old news‐‐
the orcs already told us that.
I can't help but wonder.
What do you think the
other Demon King's like?
Hold on.
You knew of the attack,
yet you did nothing?
For starters, the guy goes by
the name of MAO, 'kay?
[gasping]
You know the Demon King?
Wow, that's like super cool!
Will you tell me about him?
The Demon King
from another world?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hmm. I don't know that much,
just the whole MAO thing.
Please, Mistress,
he's obviously lying.
Genzo may be
cruel and heartless,
but there's just no way
he knows someone that cool.
Wait a sec, are you serious?
What sort of life did
you live before you came here?
Listen to me!
[PRINCESS] While I don't know
his motives, this Demon King
mercilessly struck down
the orcs on his own side!
That's highly irregular.
There's no telling what else
this monster is capable of.
Yeah, that does seem a bit odd.
You can tell he's
from a different world.
Otherwise, he'd definitely
care more about
the friendship
between us monsters.
Uh, "us monsters"?
It's nothing! Just ignore her.
[chuckles nervously]
Well, even so.
I can't help but worry.
What if the poor people
of this town are
the Demon Lord's next victims?
Which is why...
[PRINCESS]
Ah...
Princess...
Oh, um... Yes?
I need to take
Hiroyuki for a walk.
Move it or lose it.
Gahh!
[blabbering]
Hello?
I said move, not stand
in the same place.
Never mind, I'll just
go around you, then.
[SHIGURE]
Hmm...
[ANIMAL MASK screams]
Hey, what is going on here?
[ANIMAL MASK whimpers]
Hiroyuki is gone!
[JOANNA]
We have to find the hero.
Judging from the orcs'
reactions, he's nearby.
I'm sure of it.
[MONKEY 9B] Would you
get off my case, already?
[MONKEY 9C]
Come on, just one glance!
‐‐[MONKEY 9B] I said no.
‐‐[JOANNA] What's wrong?
Why all the fuss?
‐‐Oh. Lady Joanna!
‐‐[MONKEY 9B] Lady Joanna!
It's no big deal,
just this paper.
Get this.
He found it in the orc village,
and it's super naughty.
Hey! Don't tell her.
You better watch out,
this guy's a real perv.
I am not! Just shut up already.
It's naughty?
I'm not sure I follow.
No matter, let me see the paper.
Um. Yes, ma'am.
Don't you dare
show her your smut!
Ah!
[gasps]
[MAO laughs]
This angle. This
bridge. It's him!
There's no doubt in my mind,
that is Animal Mask!
We've finally found him!
Look, my lady.
The woman in
the picture is Carmilla.
And she's flashing everyone.
What an idiot.
I bet she fell under the hero's
spell just like the orcs.
Heh! Well, of course she did.
And I'm sure her worthless
mistress failed to help her.
I bet Lindabulea's entranced.
[ROSE]
Yes. No doubt that is the case.
Guess I'll avenge them, then.
It's the least I can do for
those pitiful creatures.
[laughs]
[laughter]
Aw. Man. They stole our smut.
It had titles like "death grip"
and "unbearable shame."
That's my kinda reading
right there. Damn...
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hiroyuki! Hiroyuki!
Come out, come out
wherever you are!
[giggles]
Genzo!
Have you seen my dog?
He's missing.
[WOMAN 3A]
No. Not recently, anyway.
[ANIMAL MASK]
I see.
Peace out.
Hey! Hiroyuki!
[WOMAN 3A]
How strange...
Normally, Genzo would notice
that I changed my shampoo,
but he didn't say a word.
Ah! Goodness,
what am I thinking?
How silly of me. Jeez.
Here, Hiroyuki!
I've got a yummy treat for you!
Come back or I'll eat it!
Oh, please.
Why should we have to
go through all this trouble
to look for Genzo's animal?
You know why!
After all the stuff
Genzo does for us,
it's the least we can do!
We have a responsibility
as his housemates
to help him look for his dog!
And what about my feelings?
Hiroyuki is very important
to me, you know!
For reasons...
[CARMILLA]
Uh. "Reasons," huh?
Um... Hi.
Oh. Princess Buttocks.
Uh, I mean, Princess Altena!
[PRINCESS growls] I was
wondering, have you seen anyone
named Hiroyuki around here?
It's an animal.
And I would say it's
probably about this big.
Uh, no. Sorry, ma'am.
Oh. Right.
[BOY 10A]
Look, I'm the princess!
[BOY 10B]
Princess Butt! Princess Butt!
‐‐[PRINCESS growls]
‐‐[gasping]
‐‐[PRINCESS snarls]
[PRINCESS whimpers]
[SHIGURE sniffing]
This is where
the scent disappears.
Which doesn't make sense.
Makes me think
he was probably stuffed
in a bag or something else.
Which would mean...
...this whole thing was planned.
[CLAUSE] Hi, there.
What are you up to, Shigure?
‐‐Huh?
‐‐[CLAUSE] You okay?
[SHIGURE]
Oh, Clause! Uh, actually...
You saw Hiroyuki? Where?
[CLAUSE]
Well... You see, earlier today,
I was out visiting a nobleman's
mansion and saw him there.
Weird, what's he
doing at a mansion?
Who the hell cares?
Let's go!
Daddy's coming, Hiroyuki!
[SHIGURE]
Hold up, Genzo! Wait for me!
[GENZO] Papa is gonna bring
you back home safe and sound!
I swear!
‐‐Hurry up, Shigure!
‐‐[SHIGURE] Hey!
[GENZO]
This is life or death!
‐‐[MARIA giggles]
‐‐[HIROYUKI barks]
C'mon, hurry up, Catherine!
You can't catch me!
[HIROYUKI barking]
Darling?
Why don't you go give Catherine
a little something to snack on?
'Kay, Daddy!
Well, girl? Are you hungry?
[HIROYUKI barking]
Try not to fall down!
Tell me again why I should
give her back to you?
I purchased her legally this
morning for a hefty price
from a local merchant.
My daughter's taken quite
a liking to Catherine.
He's a boy!
Whose name happens
to be Hiroyuki.
And somebody stole him from me!
Not my problem.
I bought her fair and square,
so her name is Catherine now.
[ANIMAL MASK growls]
Yes, but...
Hiroyuki belonged
to us originally.
We'd like him back.
I'm sure you understand.
Actually...
As much as I hate it,
I have to agree with him.
Oh? But...
[HANAKO] While it's true
he was stolen from us,
if this gentleman
purchased him legally,
then there's not really
much we can do.
I don't quite understand,
but my mistress is brilliant!
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK snarls]
‐‐[CARMILLA groans]
Hush, the adults are talking.
Well... What if we were
to purchase the
animal from you?
Wait. Are you
that butt princess?
No, I am not!
Just tell me how much
you paid, already!
[NOBLE 10A groans]
This is a receipt
from when I bought
her this morning.
For real?
That's a lot of numbers.
Daddy, look what
Catherine can do!
‐‐[HIROYUKI yips]
‐‐Huh?
[ANIMAL MASK gasps]
Hiroyuki!
[HIROYUKI howls]
[ANIMAL MASK sighs]
[gasps]
Is it yummy, Catherine?
[barks]
Do you hear that?
She likes her food!
Well, of course she does!
After all, I had our private
chefs whip this up
especially for her,
using the finest ingredients!
Hiroyuki...
[PRINCESS panting]
This is the perfect opportunity
to put Genzo in my debt!
I'll look in
the castle treasury!
There should be plenty of
money to cover the expense.
If I buy back that
small animal for him,
then Genzo will have
no choice but to do what I say
and finally become the hero!
At long last, Genzo
will fulfill his duty!
All right. Let's go.
Like, right now?
But are you sure?
We don't have a choice.
We're poor as F.
Fine. I'm glad you understand.
Now, good day to you, sir.
[ANIMAL MASK whimpers]
Poor Genzo.
Genzo. Are you‐‐crying?
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK whimpers]
‐‐[CARMILLA] Eh‐heh!
Ha, what a big baby!
[groans]
[rasping]
[ANIMAL MASK whimpers]
I hope you have
a good life... Hiroyuki.
[HIROYUKI whines]
Ah. Hold on.
Did Catherine used
to be your doggy, mister?
Yeah.
He and I have been through
everything together.
Hiroyuki's more than
a dog‐‐he's my family.
[panting]
[MARIA groans]
Hey, Daddy?
Yes? What is it, Maria?
It's just...
Would it be okay
to give Catherine back?
[gasping]
I don't think you know
what you're asking here.
And, well... She was expensive!
Money doesn't grow
on trees, you know!
All I know is that if I owned
Catherine my whole life
like that man did, but then
someone else took her,
I'd be really sad!
What's more, I kinda feel like
Catherine herself is sad.
That's why...
[NOBLE 10A]
Oh... But darling...
How generous of you!
Let's go home, Hiroyuki!
Hold on!
I can't let you
take her for free!
Do you see how much
I paid for this creature?
You have to
pay me at least half!
Half that amount...
is still too much.
That's so mean, Daddy!
[NOBLE 10A groans]
Please don't look at me
with those giant,
watery eyes, Maria.
You have to understand,
she was very expensive!
[MARIA whines]
[NOBLE 10A]
Okay, half of the half, then!
[MARIA sobs]
Bah! Okay, half of that, then!
No wait, another half!
‐‐And another half.
‐‐[gasping]
[NOBLE 10A]
And another half?
Does that work? No?
‐‐Another half!
‐‐[MARIA whimpers]
[NOBLE 10A growls]
One more half.
'Kay? You all should
at least pay that much.
And if you still
can't afford that,
then Catherine would be better
staying in our home anyway!
[MARIA gasps]
Thank you, Daddy!
[NOBLE 10A groans]
[ANIMAL MASK]
It's no good!
Even with all the halves,
we're still too poor!
[CARMILLA] Mistress, just look
at the shape of my poor stomach!
Genzo is such a ferocious brute!
Won't you
pretty please rub this
pain‐relieving lotion on
it until I feel better?
I wanna feel your soft fingers.
That's the only way my tummy
will heal up properly!
[groans]
What are we gonna do?
If we don't pay, Hiroyuki
will have to stay there.
With Maria...
At least she's a nice child.
What do you mean Genzo?
I just mean that
maybe Hiroyuki would be
better off if he lived with
someone like Maria.
Then he'd get to eat crazy
fancy food every night.
Have you lost your mind?
[ANIMAL MASK]
That's the whole reason why
I wanted to open a pet shop.
It's beautiful.
Meeting an animal.
The perfect one.
That's what it's all about.
Maybe he'd be happier
if I let him go.
[whimpers]
C'mon, you can't
be serious, Genzo!
This is crazy talk!
Fine.
Be right back.
[sighs]
[ANIMAL MASK sniffs]
Is that money?
Whoa! I didn't know
we were secretly loaded!
[groans]
I guess you could say
I was saving it for a rainy day.
I kept it secret because
I knew everyone would just
try and spend it.
Use it to buy Hiroyuki back.
Shigure...
Don't cry!
I was hoping that we
could save it and open up
the pet shop soon,
but maybe now's not the time.
Whether we use it
today or in the future,
it's there to help you.
And as long as it does that,
then I'm happy.
[NOBLE 10A]
Per our discussion,
I'll sell her back to you.
[HIROYUKI whines]
Catherine...
'Bye... [sobs]
Hey, it's okay.
Come play with him sometime.
[MARIA]
Ah... Heh.
So, uh...
Do you mind if
I ask you something?
I was wondering if you
know who the merchant was
that sold you Hiroyuki.
I remember it was
actually three of them.
They were a very peculiar lot.
It was a bearded man,
a wolf man, and a cat woman.
[ANIMAL MASK growls]
[EDGAR laughs]
Aw, yeah! It's a great day!
I heard that pervert
was running all over town,
sniffing and sobbing
like a pathetic baby.
[chuckles]
Why exactly are
you petting me again?
For effect, of course.
Man, I haven't felt
this at ease in a long time!
Drink up! You deserve it, buddy.
To our vic‐‐
[MISHA]
Huh?
[ANIMAL MASK] So you lowlife
scumbags think you can just
sneak up to my house
and steal my dog, do you?
[screaming]
You're not even
worth petting anymore,
you mangy criminals!
[WOLFGANG yelling]
Hey! Damn you!
Stop smashing up my new shop!
You pervert!
You'll be sorry you attacked me!
[ANIMAL MASK growls]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK snarls]
‐‐[EDGAR whimpers]
[groaning] It hurts in
ways I can't understand...!
Ahh...!
[whines]
Please don't hurt me!
Denied!
‐‐[MISHA screams]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK bellows]
[MISHA groans]
Genzo stop it!
I have avenged you, Hiroyuki.
[SHIGURE]
Did you kill them?!
[barks]
[PRINCESS panting]
I've returned at last, Genzo!
Please accept this money!
[panting]
Huh...?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Who's a good boy?
It's dangerous out there,
so I want you to sleep
‐‐with daddy tonight.
‐‐[yawns]
[yipping]
[ANIMAL MASK]
What's wrong?
Ah. Hey, you're...
Mister Birdy! Mister Woofy!
What are these
animals doing here?
[SHIGURE] Yeah, right!
Don't act like it wasn't you!
Hold on, I smell
something off here.
There's somebody
weird inside of our home.
Heh. Well, it's about time.
[gasping]
Lindabulea.
I never imagined I'd see you
living in such a wretched state.
And you are?
You forgot me again?!
I go by the name of
Draculius Joanna...
[MAO] I'm glad to see
you're doing well.
It's been a while, Genzo.
Or is it... Animal Mask?
[SHIGURE]
It can't be...
You attacked the orc
village. Didn't you?
[MAO]
Heh.
[CARMILLA]
Wait, so that means...
MAO! 'Sup, buddy?
What? Here I thought
you were just a stupid liar.
But you actually do know the
demon king from another world?
Yeah, we go way back.
So that means...
You're the one who summoned him?
I can't believe you would bring
another world's demon king here.
And what of it?
You should be
defeating the hero,
but instead, you've
both joined his cause!
You're nothing more
than a despicable traitor.
Yeah, what she said!
Well, kinda.
Let's just say that I have
my reasons for being here.
I'm sure.
Let me take a wild guess:
you lost to the hero
and then begged him
to spare your life.
What a wuss!
Don't talk about
my mistress like that!
Looks like we've
stumbled into loser town,
population: you two!
[BOTH growl]
Everyone just
shut your traps already!
Fight me!
You and I are
gonna have our match!
And I won't leave
until you agree to do it!
But, like, what's a "match?"
[JOANNA grunts]
You don't know?
He's obviously talking
about an evil match.
Hmph. That's what it is!
Two men enter the battle,
but only one leaves alive!
What? Are you serious?
[JOANNA]
Lindabulea!
I challenge you
to an "evil match!"
‐‐[ROSE] Lady Joanna!
‐‐Uh, calm down!
I don't know any of you,
but you're too loud!
You're going to upset the
neighbors, so please be quiet!
Splendid idea!
[SHIGURE]
Huh? Clause?
Where'd you come from?
You know, I was just
thinking that it would be
a good time to host another one
of Genzo's special tournaments.
Whoa. Another one?
Heh.
So, it's a fighting
tournament, is it?
Then you can count me in.
I'll bury you
in front of a crowd.
You better not run away
when I'm about to win again.
The time has come...
I'll make you pay
for what you did!
Will you face me, Lindabulea?
Oh, it's on!
My mistress and I are gonna
grind you up into little pieces!
Another tournament?
I wonder if there will be more
yummy food like last time?
Man, I can hardly wait!
We're in! This is our
chance to get rich, Genzo!
[whines]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Pay back, huh?
Okay, then. I accept
your challenge, MAO!
[HIROYUKI snoring]
[ANIMAL MASK grunting]
All right.
This time, I'll be facing
another pro‐wrestler.
It's totally different from the
other people I've fought here.
‐‐[footsteps]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Mm?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Carmilla? What's up?
[CARMILLA sighs]
[ANIMAL MASK grunts]
There's somebody
that I need to beat.
No matter what.
And I'll do whatever it takes.
[CARMILLA]
Genzo...
Will you... please teach me
how to be a pro‐wrestler?
[CARMILLA sighs]
Let's do it.
[ANIMAL MASK] Next time:
"Pride and Loyalty!"