[PRINCESS]
Keep up the good work.
Yes! It is our honor,
Princess Altena.
Pfft!
[SOLDIER 4B] More like
Princess Buttocks, am I right?
‐‐[SOLDIER 4C shushing]
‐‐[laughter]
[SOLDIER 4A]
All hail Her Royal Butt Cheeks!
[PRINCESS] My soldiers have
lost all respect for me,
and worse, they call me Princess
Buttocks behind my back!
This all happened because of...
Because of...
Because of that man!
That's why they mock me!
‐‐Afternoon, Princess Buttocks.
‐‐Hello, Princess Altena.
[PRIEST 4B growls]
Oh. Good afternoon.
[PRINCESS]
Even the priests?!
Sorry, Princess.
It seems the demon beasts
continue to wreak havoc.
Perhaps we should call
a conference to determine
our next course of action.
[PRINCESS]
Very well.
By the way, how is the
search going for the man
that I summoned?
Have you found him?
[PRIEST 4B] No. So far,
he's managed to elude us.
Then we need to
double the search efforts.
Right! Your wish is our command!
No one insults our Buttness.
I mean, our beloved
Princess Altena!
[WOMAN moaning]
Mm... Yeah...
[PRIEST 4A laughs, yells]
Ahem!
I'm sure you're upset,
but please be patient with us.
I swear we're doing
the best we can.
[WOMAN moaning]
Hahhh...
[chuckles]
This foolishness is
all the hero's fault.
[BOTH PRIESTS laughing]
[PRINCESS] I don't care
if it's the last thing I do,
I'm going to find that man!
[CARMILLA snoring]
[SHIGURE] Almost there,
just three more boxes to fill up
and I'll be finished.
[sighs]
[snoring continues]
[SHIGURE]
Hmph...
[HANAKO slurping, chomping]
[liquid sloshing]
[HANAKO]
Mm! It's so yummy!
‐‐[SHIGURE] They're really good!
‐‐[MERCHANT 4A] Yeah, I'm sure.
‐‐Here ya go!
‐‐That's it?!
But they're worth much more!
Of course, but here's the thing:
This is a buyer's market.
Let's roll.
[MERCHANT GUARD 4A, 4B]
Right.
[SHIGURE gasping]
[ANIMAL MASK] There you go!
Eat up, precious babies!
[SHIGURE growls]
Only the best food
for the best pets!
[laughs]
Eat all you want! [guffaws]
‐‐Fill up those fluffy tum‐tums!
‐‐[SHIGURE growling]
[GUILD murmuring]
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B]
All right!
Let's take down a griffon!
[GUILD SOLDIER 2A]
Yeah!
Here's to the hunt, my friend!
Oh, hey. You gonna do it?
[GUILD SOLDIER 2A] Yep! As soon
as we've completed this quest,
I'm gonna ask that girl out.
I hope her dad
will approve of me.
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B]
Who wouldn't?
[SHIGURE]
Genzo is driving me crazy!
Here, we're on
the verge of poverty,
and he keeps bringing in
more mouths to feed!
Ugh! I can't believe
he'd just bring home
a bunch of girls like that.
Talk about gross.
He's constantly
dragging in strange tail.
Hmph!
Look girl. The guy is
obviously playing you.
[SHIGURE]
Hmm... You think?
I dunno, I really wanna help him
achieve his dream, y'know?
I want humans and
demon beasts to coexist!
[laughs]
‐‐[giggles]
‐‐[yapping]
So, I'll cheer him
on or whatever.
[BARTENDER 4A]
Hold up!
Last time I checked,
you can't eat dreams!
Girl, you've gotta
be stern with him,
or he's just gonna keep
walking all over you!
[SHIGURE]
Huh...?
[SHIGURE sighs]
Huh?
The truth is, I love you!
I want to share
a house with you.
[HANAKO whimpers]
Say yes, and we'll
spend our lives together!
[squeals]
[CAT growls]
Please answer.
[sniffing
[HANAKO gasps]
I'm so happy you
accepted my feelings!
[laughs]
[giggles]
From here on out,
I'll call you Akemi!
Daddy loves you so very much!
[meows]
[HIROYUKI yaps]
I'm sure you two
will be very happy!
[
Me, too! [laughs]
[WOMAN 3A giggles]
Hi, Genzo.
Hey! Um... It's you.
And wow! Don't you
look lovely today?
Your coat is looking
especially luscious.
Stop. You really
are incorrigible.
Besides, I'm too old for you.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Not in my eyes.
Listen, if it were up to me,
I'd bury my face in
your fur this instant.
Oh! Such a flirt!
You should really save that
flowery language for Shigure.
After all, I'm married.
Oh!
Your husband's a kobold, right?
So it's no problem, I can love
you both at the same time.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Miss...
Ohh...!
But... I'm a mother, too.
I have over 20 children, you
know! Not another word, mister.
Don't go! Come back!
[SHIGURE] Do I even wanna
know what you're doing?
Oh. Welcome home, Shigure!
Hey. You're back.
Check it out.
This is the newest addition
to our family, Akemi.
Mrowr.
[SHIGURE growls]
No, please, don't you
dare do it, Mistress!
You're the worst, you know that?
[laughs]
I'm serious!
Wait, what are you doing?
‐‐[wham]
‐‐[CARMILLA groans]
‐‐[SHIGURE] Hmm?
‐‐[CARMILLA coughs]
Mistress! Morning.
Ah! Hey. Can you
give me some money?
[SHIGURE]
Huh?!
[CARMILLA]
Take a look at this.
Obviously, my artistic talents,
awesome though they are,
could never do
the mistress justice.
Which is why I need cash to
commission a professional artist
to draw a portrait of her.
Then we can make copies of it!
Everyone will scramble to buy
a copy for themselves,
and then we'll be
so rich we won't know
what to do with ourselves!
Ahh?!
Aw...
Listen. It's urgent.
Look deep into
sweet Akemi's eyes...
...and tell me
this cat doesn't deserve
a brand‐new bed and only
the best food money can buy!
[AKEMI mews]
Meow.
‐‐[SHIGURE] Nope.
‐‐[AKEMI yowls]
[ANIMAL MASK gasps]
Come back, Akemi! Don't go!
How dare you!
I hate to burst your bubble,
but money doesn't grow on trees.
‐‐[CLAUSE] Excuse me.
‐‐Huh?
My name is Clause.
I'm from Cluster Bank.
As you may recall,
today is the deadline.
[GROUP]
Uh...
Thanks very much.
[CLAUSE] So, do you
have the down payment
for the loan we discussed?
For your‐‐pet shop‐‐was it?
Nope, I forgot.
We're flat broke.
Fortunately, you have all these
capable people living here.
If you all worked, you should be
able to raise the money quickly.
Not gonna happen.
If I leave, then who will
look after my fur‐babies?
I'm allergic to work.
Unless it's for my mistress,
which is a totally
different story.
Oh, is there a job that
involves stuffing your face?
Because I am so there!
[SHIGURE growls]
[CLAUSE]
How unfortunate...
Well then, I suppose
I have no choice
but to withdraw the loan offer.
What?! We were
just kidding, duh!
All right! We've got work
to do! Move it or lose it!
Tch. And why should
I listen to a lowly human...
[screeches]
[ANIMAL MASK]
I said we have work to do!
Not to worry,
Genzo, I'll help you!
Without any money,
I can't stuff myself silly!
[SHIGURE]
Really, Hanako?
I'm so happy you've decided
to stop being a worthless bum.
Now, let's go!
[SHIGURE, HANAKO]
Yeah!
[SHIGURE]
Here's your order!
[ANIMAL MASK bellows]
[HANAKO chomping]
[SHIGURE]
Here's your order!
‐‐[MEN yelling]
‐‐[CARMILLA whimpering]
[SHIGURE]
Here's your order!
[ANIMAL MASK yells]
[HANAKO chomping]
‐‐[MEN yelling]
‐‐[CARMILLA screams]
[EXPEDITIONER 4A] Just hang on,
we're almost there.
[EXPEDITIONER 4B]
I'm trying!
[SHIGURE]
Hi, here's your order!
[ANIMAL MASK cackling]
Such loving babies!
‐‐[CHEF 4A chuckling]
‐‐[HANAKO slurping]
‐‐[MOB yelling]
‐‐[CARMILLA screeching]
Fire the bum! Fire the bum!
[yells]
[SHIGURE growls] Who wants to
explain why we have less money
than when we started?
It was so weird!
For some reason they started
charging me for food!
And I honestly tried
to do some work!
Then when I went into town,
the men were all like,
"How much for
a roll in the hay?"
But there wasn't any
hay to roll in!
That's not what they meant!
I took their money, but then the
hay‐less liars chased me down!
My boss was a total tool!
All I did was love on these
sweet animals for a couple
of hours, and he fired
me for no reason!
Shingen was there!
Squawk! Fire the bum.
Stop bringing home
more freeloaders!
I'm hungry, gimme yummy food!
[snarls]
I said gimme yummy food,
ya dumb broad!
That's enough!
I'm gonna turn you into
yummy food, you useless bird!
‐‐[SHINGEN] Crazy lady! Help!
‐‐[SHIGURE] What?! Who's crazy?!
‐‐Dumb chicken!
‐‐[CARMILLA] Calm yourself!
I'm gonna bake you
into a pot pie!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Don't eat Shingen!
[SHINGEN screams]
[GUILD murmuring]
If we can't even
afford to eat,
then how will we ever
open up a pet shop?
[GUILD MASTER 1A] Hmm...
If things are that bad,
why not take on a quest?
[gasps]
But...
The Beast Killer.
[gasping]
This is the perfect job
for someone with his skills.
[ANIMAL MASK]
A griffon?
[SHIGURE]
Yes! The guild master thought
it'd be a good job
for you. Take a look.
[ANIMAL MASK squeals]
I'm in! I would
love to hunt it down!
[SHIGURE]
Oh, yeah! Hunt it down
and get that sweet,
sweet, bounty!
I'm starting to think
they're not actually
on the same page.
Honestly, I'm not
even paying attention.
With the money
we make from this gig,
we'll be back in
the black in no time flat!
And you can finally
open up your pet shop!
[HEAT HAZE]
It sounds like, once again,
you and I are going
after the same quest.
Too bad.
Because we're going to be
the ones to bag this bounty.
Behold!
[HEAT HAZE] The sage of
the west presented me with
this holy sword, Durandal!
So sorry, pal.
Looks like there's about to be a
new Demon Beast Killer in town.
[HEAT HAZE FOLLOWERS gasping]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Don't you...
‐‐[HEAT HAZE shrieks]
...dare!
[HEAT HAZE FOLLOWERS whimpering]
Oh, hello there.
Poor little sword,
did someone leave you behind?
[HEAT HAZE FOLLOWERS screamin]
Okay, then. Who's ready?
Let's go.
We've got a griffon to see.
Hard pass.
Uh?!
Get this through
your thick skull:
I don't take orders from
pathetic humans.
So you're on your own.
I wanna go! Please, Genzo?
Huh?!
It's always been
a dream of mine
to nibble on a griffon.
[chuckles]
I don't know how
to tell you this,
but I doubt griffons are
supposed to be chew toys.
[HANAKO]
I'm ready when you are!
Have fun being a bump
on a log, Carmilla!
[SHIGURE]
Good call‐‐the sooner we leave,
the sooner we can get our
hands on that bounty money!
‐‐Hey, uh...
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] For sure!
Can't keep the newest member
‐‐of our family waiting!
‐‐Don't leave me!
[whimpers]
[sniffs]
[CARMILLA] Actually, on second
thought, I'm bored...
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
What an odd party...
[CARMILLA] I can grace
you with my presence!
[CARMILLA laughs]
Just leave it to me, guys! Ha!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Her tune's really changed...
Get ready, because I'm about to
school you on griffon hunting!
‐‐Ahh‐‐
‐‐No!
‐‐My back! Aahh! My back!
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK bellowing]
Wow, I never knew
you were so limber!
[ANIMAL MASK]
By the way, are griffons really
tough demon beasts?
Huh?! How could you take
the quest without knowing?
‐‐[CARMILLA grunting]
‐‐The moment I saw its picture,
I knew it was a creature
I would absolutely adore.
Its murderous rage
doesn't bother me.
‐‐You're crazy.
‐‐[CARMILLA] My spine...
[SHIGURE]
Educate yourself.
‐‐[CARMILLA groans]
‐‐Ooh!
Griffon: A dangerous beast
with A+ combat capabilities.
Gives birth to
two children in a litter.
[SHIGURE]
Wow.
Your reading skills have
improved dramatically, Genzo.
I'd like to thank
my love for animals!
The Griffon parents then
make the two children fight
and only raises the one
winner to adulthood. What?!
It goes on to say that
the loser is abandoned by
its mother to fend for itself,
where it'll most likely die.
Heh. No matter, those dumb
griffons are no match for me
and my burning love
for the mistress!
[ANIMAL MASK] Are...
we supposed to be impressed?
[SHIGURE] Be on your guard‐‐
this place is a danger zone,
and there could be demon
beasts lurking anywhere!
[HANAKO] Hunters only come
here if they have a death wish,
or they're stupid.
Like these dorks right here?
Huh?!
‐‐[GUILD SOLDIERS groaning]
‐‐[BABY GRIFFONS growling]
[SHIGURE]
Look over there!
Oh. That's cool. They're huge.
If it weren't for
this wretched sunlight,
I'd crush them!
It's super cloudy.
Genzo, I'll let you handle
them just this once,
so you can have all
the sweet glory to yourself!
How sweet.
[CARMILLA] Ow! Stop it,
that's my favorite face, stupid!
So that's them? The griffons.
[CARMILLA]
Hello, I said my face!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Such beautiful feathers!
And talons that could
gouge your eyes out!
Forget that! Look over there!
[BABY GRIFFONS snarling]
It's just like
the book explained!
They're being forced to fight!
[caws]
[gasps]
[yells
[GIRLS]
Genzo!
[yelling]
‐‐[BABY GRIFFON 4A yelps]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Go!
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Run away!
‐‐[HANAKO] 'Kay!
[SHIGURE]
Wait for me!
[BOTH roar]
What the heck are you doing?!
What's happening, Genzo?
The bell's already
been rung, so...
I won't let anyone hurt
this poor baby anymore!
[SHIGURE] But Genzo! You just
ran up and cold stole it from...
...the mom!
This one lost, so that means
she's up for grabs, doesn't it?
I mean, they were just
gonna abandon her anyway!
What about
the bounty, you idiot?
[GRIFFONS roaring]
[GROUP screamin]
[roars]
[CARMILLA grunts]
[HANAKO]
Carmilla!
It's fine, mistress!
Forget about me and run!
I'll handle this fight! Go!
‐‐[GRIFFON 4A growling]
‐‐[CARMILLA yelps, groans]
Wait, Genzo!
They've got Carmilla!
[CARMILLA]
Mistress...
[HANAKO]
Do something!
[ANIMAL MASK]
She's done for. Leave her.
More importantly!
What about Kyoko?
You already named it?!
Who's more important to you?!
Our friend, Carmilla,
or a baby griffon
you literally just stole?
Easy‐‐one of them lacks
animal ears, a tail, fur,
and never pays rent,
so I'm gonna go Kyoko.
[growls]
Are you serious?!
Look at this baby!
Her luscious fur,
her beautiful beak!
She's gonna be quite
the looker when she grows up!
You need to stop being
an idiot and give her back
before we all end up dead!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Denied!
Kyoko deserves to be
raised with love and care!
From here on out,
I'll be her papa!
Come on!
[gulps]
[ANIMAL MASK growls]
It can't be helped. Okay!
Huh?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Take Kyoko.
[SHIGURE]
Huh...?
Hanako, you try
and get Carmilla.
If you don't think you can,
then give up or whatever.
No way! I'm staying here.
I can't leave.
With so much plump
griffon meat available...
...I should try and placate my
taste buds with a quick nibble.
I'll hold them off here.
So go! Take Kyoko and
escape while you still can!
What? But I can't.
And certainly not all by myself!
If you two make it
back home safely,
I'll let you put meat
or veggies in the soup tonight.
Later, nerds!
No more boring, salty water
disguised as soup for this lady!
[ANIMAL MASK] Bring it!
Let's do this, feather bro!
[GRIFFON 4B growls]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Run, Shigure!
[SHIGURE]
'Kay! Bye!
[yells]
[caws]
Be careful!
‐‐[GRIFFON 4B growls]
‐‐Do your worst!
[grunting]
[caws]
[grunts] C'mon,
is that the best you can do?
Wait. I don't get it‐‐
how are you holding your own
against that creature?
Because...
...I train hard!
[yells]
I've been waiting
for this opening!
[yells
Yes! Now... Go! Great!
Aim for the head!
Uh...
Caw?
Oh, wow, this fur
is the softest thing ever!
‐‐[HIROYUKI whining]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK giggling]
Huh...?
It's like a fusion
between a bird's feathers
and an animal's fur coat!
Simply amazing!
Fluffy feather fantasy!
Now, let me feel up that chest.
[GRIFFON 4B growling]
[ANIMAL MASK groans]
[HANAKO]
Genzo!
[growls
How could you?
You'll pay for that!
[HANAKO]
Breast meat. Thigh meat.
Belly meat. Leg meat.
All the meat.
Meat sweats, here I come!
‐‐[chomp]
‐‐[GRIFFON 4A bellows]
Huh?!
[HANAKO] Hey, Shigure,
we're finally home.
That's great! I was
starting to get really worried.
I took a big bite out of
one of the griffons,
and it was disgusting,
so we ran away.
Oh, sorry for your loss?
[SHIGURE]
So, uh... What is he up to?
[HANAKO] Carmilla comes back
to life more quickly
when she's buried
in impure soil.
[yaps]
[SHIGURE]
Uh...
[SHIGURE] Since we got our butts
handed to us by the griffons,
we didn't get the cash reward.
[SHIGURE]
And then...
[ANIMAL MASK sighs]
Man. The food. It eats so much.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Kyoko!
You're just the biggest,
sweetest girl, aren't you?
[SHIGURE]
She's too big!
And such soft fur!
[SHIGURE]
But what about the food costs?!
[ANIMAL MASK] I hope you grow
to be three times bigger!
[SHIGURE]
Well, I don't!
[sighs]
You're not gonna believe this.
Genzo brought
yet another girl home.
What, again? How rude.
You'd better give that player
a piece of your mind.
I don't know.
He loves everyone so openly,
it's kinda charming.
Are you serious?
Come on, What about
the money problems?
Actually, I found a pretty
lucrative cash flow recently.
[SHOP OWNER 4A]
Whoa! Do my eyes deceive me?
It's really the
magic sword Dainsleif
and the holy sword, Durandal!
Please, I simply must know,
where did you find these
incredibly rare items?
I must have, like,
some crazy good luck,
because I just find
them lying around!
[SHOP OWNER 4A]
Here's your payment.
You're welcome
to come back anytime!
Thank you,
I'll be sure to do that.
[chuckles]
[JOANNA]
I see, a human hero?
[ROSE] Yes. Our preparations
are almost complete.
Lady Joanna.
[chuckles]
[ANIMAL MASK] Next time:
"Animal Mask and MAO."