[CROWD cheering]
[ORC MC] The fourth match
ended pretty much the way
we all expected,
with Rose's victory!
It only took one
little distraction.
In the end, Carmilla was
the loser we all knew her to be,
the most losiest of losers!
I lost! I'm so sorry, Mistress!
There, there now.
[ORC MC]
Let's recap!
The winner of our first match
was the esteemed Hero army!
[CROWD 12A]
That match was awesome!
[CROWD 12B]
I love you, Princess Buttocks!
[PRINCESS gasps]
They love me! How grand!
[pants] It's strange,
and yet... I love it!
Even that silly name,
"Princess Buttocks,"
doesn't bother me anymore!
Now I wear it with pride!
Weird kink for
a princess to have.
[ORC MC] In the second bout,
the Orc King and the Kobold
came together to claim
an impressive victory
in the tag team match!
Your skills
are quite remarkable.
I'm honored
to be your partner.
I'm pretty sure that's my line!
Wow, you were incredible, sir!
That's why you're the king!
You're an inspiration!
[ORC KING]
Hmm.
[WOMAN 3A]
Darling!
[KOBOLD KIDS]
Yay!
[KOBOLD]
Hey, kids!
[KOBOLD KID 12A]
You're the best, Daddy!
[KOBOLD laughing]
Darling. I'm so glad you won.
I've fallen in love with you
all over again.
[WOMAN 3A]
I'm sorry, Genzo.
But I'm afraid this
is how it has to be.
Unfortunately, you and I were
never meant to be together.
But don't worry.
I'm sure you'll find the one for
you. So please don't give up.
What color is the sky
in your world?
[ORC MC] Lastly, winning the
third and fourth matches,
we have the Demon King from
another world and his team!
Were you watching me
up there, Lady Joanna?
I destroyed that
lesser vampire!
She was no match
for me! Amazing, huh?
Hell no, you almost lost!
[JOANNA] Hmph. Yes. Things
have gotten quite exciting.
And once the Demon King
from another world
defeats the Hero in battle,
I'll find Lindabulea.
I'm rather eager to discuss the
results of the match with her.
[HANAKO]
You shouldn't underestimate him.
[BOTH gasp]
Lindabulea?!
[HANAKO]
Joanna.
I don't know squat about this
demon king from another world,
but things won't go
the way you think they will.
[JOANNA]
Wait. What do you mean?
You'll know when
you watch the match.
That's the only thing
I can tell you.
Hold on a minute!
Is that supposed to be a threat?
Chill out, you don't
have to be so violent!
[bones crunching]
[HANAKO]
Well, then. I should go.
Whoa. Well, she sure
seems confident.
Why?
The Hero. He's got a mask!
How strange. I wonder why?
[SHINGEN] In the blue corner,
weighing in at 178 pounds,
it's the leader of the Demon
King Army, the man himself,
the Demon King from
another world!
[CROWD cheers]
[MAO growls]
The name is MAO, okay?
[SHINGEN] In the red corner,
weighing in at 198 pounds,
it's the leader of the
Hero Army, Animal Mask!
Bring it, yo!
[CROWD cheers]
It's the final match
of the evening, folks!
The one we've all
been waiting for!
Who will walk away the victor?
Will it be the Demon King?
Or will it be the Hero?
It's a battle
for the ages! Fight!
[CROWD cheering]
[ORC MC]
The battle has begun!
What do these two warriors
have in store for us?
Ya feel that? So much tension.
Indeed, it's like
a killing rage.
They're each planning
their first move, huh?
Genzo...
[PRINCESS] This aura...
I see why he's the Hero.
Be careful...
Genzo...
[HANAKO gulps]
[ORC MC] It appears
as though they're both
feeling the other one out.
Neither of them
have made a move!
[ANIMAL MASK]
MAO's usual style is to go
straight for the throat.
But he hasn't moved.
Why not?
[MAO]
Stay calm.
If I go straight for the
throat like I always do,
then he'll just counter
my move and shove me
face‐first into the mat again.
[ANIMAL MASK grunts]
[MAO] The one who outsmarts
the other will win the day.
But you already know that, huh?
[ANNOUNCER 12A]
The winner is Animal Mask!
[ANNOUNCER 12B]
Animal Mask has a knack
for reading his opponents.
Heck, Mao couldn't even manage
to land a single hit on him.
[MAO]
I will defeat Animal Mask.
I will defeat Animal Mask!
Don't push me!
Stay back!
[yells]
It burns!
[grunting]
Just you wait and see,
Animal Mask!
Then, at the match...
[MC] They disappeared!
Animal Mask is gone!
He's vanished from the ring!
[MAO] Ever since that day,
my life's been nothing
but suffering! He has
no idea what kind of hell
he's put me through!
How he made me feel!
But that all changes today!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hyah!
[MAO] What the hell?!
Why are you attacking first?!
'Cause! You were
just standing there
lost in thought!
Check it out! See there?
The crowd fell asleep
because they were so darn bored!
‐‐[CROWD groaning]
‐‐[MAO] They did?
[grunting]
Damn! I can't believe
things are actually
going down like this!
After I spent all those months
preparing the perfect comeback,
how on earth did you manage
to still get the jump on me?
Oh, come on‐‐it's not
my fault you left yourself
wide open! We're pro‐wrestlers,
and we need to show the crowd
what it means to
take this seriously!
So put your crap in
a bag and get it together!
Finally, the two of them are
doing something
worth watching!
It's about time!
[gasping]
[MAO] Don't you dare
lecture me with that bullshit!
You wanna tell me what
it means to be a pro?
After you ran away from
our match like a little baby?
Hold on. I did what now?
[MAO] You know what I mean!
In our last, match you ran away
because I was finally
about to beat you!
I didn't run away!
[MAO] You ruined everything!
I was supposed to beat you
that night and become
the new champion!
Oh, that's rich!
I was supposed to beat you!
I was gonna retire
and open a pet shop!
But instead, I ended up
coming to this strange world!
Wait... How'd you
even get here, anyway?
[MAO] I just woke up
in some weird old castle.
Hold on, is that
what happened to you, too?
[ANIMAL MASK]
I didn't see it, but probably!
[MAO] Then... You didn't run
away from your match with me?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Of course not!
A wrestler accepts
all challengers!
So are you saying
you'll finally fight me?!
Duh, what do you think
we're doing right now?!
[MAO]
Yeah!
[laughing]
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
Ahaha, stop laughing!
Are you two gonna
fight or aren't you?
So, tell me.
Is there a reason why you
accepted this challenge?
There's only one reason
why I agreed to do this.
I told you that I have a dream,
and that's to open a pet shop!
[MAO]
A pet shop?
You mentioned it before.
Were you actually serious?
[ANIMAL MASK] Yeah. After
our original match that night,
I was going to begin
a new chapter in my life.
[MAO]
You were?
[ANIMAL MASK] I decided
I wanted to own a pet shop
so I could live
my life surrounded by
all my sweet furbabies!
[MAO] Wait, this is a lot
to take in and I'm kinda lost.
A pet shop...
Nothing makes sense.
Maybe I should focus
on the match.
[ANIMAL MASK] They told me
I had to beat a Demon King.
I thought it had nothing to do
with me, but then you showed up.
What about you?
[MAO] I was told I needed
to defeat the Hero.
Is that supposed to be you?
[ANIMAL MASK] I keep telling
them I'm a wrestler,
but I guess?
What the heck? What's going on?
Do you hear the things
that the Demon King
from another world is saying?
Wait, what if that guy's
actually a moron?
Please don't state the obvious
when it's way too late
to fix it, Rose!
It doesn't matter,
because I'm going to defeat you
no matter what! I'm through
losing to you, Animal Mask!
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK groans]
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
[MAO]
Hah!
[barks]
[MAO squeals]
[MAO] That was a dirty trick!
Why does he always have to
pull this crap every
time we fight?
He knows that
I'm terrified of dogs!
[ANIMAL MASK]
I was not aware.
[MAO] What kind of pro‐wrestler
makes his little dog
into his manager?
Jeez. That dog
is part of the reason
I've never been able
to beat him before.
[KIDS chatting]
[MAO] I worked so hard
to overcome my fear.
[TEACHER 12A] Hello, everyone!
Aw, isn't it adorable?
[MAO whimpering]
[screams]
[ZOOKEEPER 12A] Hey! That's
dangerous! Don't go in there!
[MAO]
You jerk!
[sobs]
I'll get you next time!
[ZOOKEEPER 12A screams]
Why?!
‐‐[barks]
‐‐[screams]
Seriously?
That big strong man is scared
of teeny, little Hiroyuki?
[MAO whimpering]
Um, Lady Joanna,
I could be wrong,
but I think the Demon King
might be afraid
of cute little demon beasts.
‐‐Yeah.
‐‐What did I say earlier?!
Don't state the obvious
when it's impossible to fix!
Oh. I've got an idea.
We can use that beast.
I get it. Very clever.
[JOANNA, ROSE]
Sneakity‐sneak, sneak.
[GROUP]
Joanna!
Who wants a little snack?
Come and get it, cutie!
[HIROYUKI whines]
[gasps]
‐‐Aw, you're such a good boy.
‐‐Come on.
My dog!
Good job, we've got him!
Now you can't use him
to torture the Demon King!
Yeah, suck on that, Hero.
Let go of Hiroyuki right now!
Now nothing can stand in my way!
[GUILD MASTER 1A groans]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Get back here!
[ORC MC] There is
no running outside the ring.
‐‐Walk, please.
‐‐[yelling]
They're headed right for us!
But we didn't do anything!
Get back here!
[ANIMAL MASK panting]
[MISHA] Why are we
having to run away, too?
[EDGAR]
Dunno!
[WOLFGANG]
Run for your life!
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK yells]
‐‐[screaming]
[GROUP yells]
Here, keep him safe, Jeeg.
Both the wrestlers
have left the ring. One...
Come here and fight me!
Was kidnapping my poor dog
part of your plan
to beat me, MAO?
[BOTH grunt]
[yelling, grunting]
I'm so sick of this crap!
What'd you say?
You pickin' a fight, pal?
[yelling]
[ANIMAL MASK groans]
[SHOPKEEP 12A]
Not my shop!
‐‐[MAO groans]
‐‐[SHOPKEEP 12B screams]
[ORC KING]
Oh, so you want to tussle, eh?
[KOBOLD]
Let's dance, buddy!
[HEAT HAZE] I'm the strongest
fighter in the guild!
[CELES]
I may be part lizardman,
but I'm a hundred
percent bad ass!
You guys are doin'
great‐‐give 'em hell!
What are you all doing?!
‐‐[CLAUSE] Hmm!
‐‐Huh?
Uh, Clause? Are you
actually enjoying this?
Who, me? 'Course not.
[SHIGURE groans]
Nineteen.
‐‐[yelling]
‐‐[blows landing]
[BOTH panting]
I will win! Me! MAO!
This is for the animals!
[BOTH yell]
[MAO] Check it!
This is my special move!
Cannonball 450!
[ANIMAL MASK groans]
Heh!
[yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[ANIMAL MASK]
This is it!
[ANIMAL MASK groaning]
[yells]
One!
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
Two!
[MAO yells]
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
Three!
[CROWD gasping]
[gasping]
[bell dinging]
[CROWD cheering]
I lost again, huh?
I can't match your
love for creatures.
Or your passion.
[panting]
People who have something
to fight for are different.
But it didn't matter.
I wanted to have
another match against you.
Heh! Then let's do
it again, sometime.
[chuckles]
[MAO] Pro wrestling
really is the best.
[ORC MC]
The winner is Animal Mask!
[CROWD cheering]
[HANAKO giggles]
[ANIMAL MASK] Animals really
do make everything better, huh?
[ANIMAL MASK, MAO]
One man uses a move.
And one man takes the hit.
That's how pro‐wrestling begins.
[OGRE MC] And the winners are...
the Hero Army!
[CROWD cheering]
Congrats, Genzo!
I'm so happy for you.
Thank you, Shigure. We did it!
[CROWD cheering]
And on that exciting note,
the hero and his team are
taking home the trophy!
An official representative from
Cluster Bank will now award the
winning team their prize money.
It's Clause!
Thank you‐‐
it's such an honor to be here.
[CLAUSE]
Genzo.
That was truly
a wonderful match.
Let's do it again.
Oh, yeah?
And here I thought you were
only interested in money.
[CLAUSE]
Hmph.
[CLAUSE] At least your dream
will finally become a reality.
True.
I can't wait! My own pet shop.
How ridiculous.
Right.
There's no sense
in lingering here.
[HANAKO]
Are you leaving?
[BOTH gasp]
Lindabulea.
Just tell me one thing.
[HANAKO]
Hmm?
Is that bumbling buffoon
really the Hero?
[HANAKO]
Yes, he is.
The one true Hero that was
summoned from another world.
[gasps]
And if I may,
I'd like to make one thing
clear to you:
Carmilla and I will continue
to observe and keep tabs
on the Hero by ourselves.
Your help is not needed.
[BOTH whimper]
[JOANNA] This isn't over
yet‐‐just you wait!
I will get my revenge on you!
[ROSE]
Yeah, you suck!
[HANAKO]
Have a nice day.
I'm hungry...
Shigure. Great work today.
Thank you‐‐
you were pretty awesome, too.
[CLAUSE] I believe we have
business to attend to.
We exceeded today's expectations
in a number of ways.
Not only in ticket sales, but
merchandise and food, as well.
Just look at it all.
[SHIGURE squeals]
Oh?
Huh...?
There were some
complications, though.
The damage from Genzo and the
other wrestlers far exceeded
the event's profits.
This is the repair bill
to cover the damage.
Wha‐‐?
[CLAUSE] We also have
to factor in Hanako's food
as well as Carmilla's drinking.
Since they both can be a little
"over‐zealous" in their vices.
This is what I have
left for you.
[gasps]
Surprise‐‐
it's actually another bill.
Heh.
Shigure?
You okay, what's wrong?
[SHIGURE growls]
"What's wrong"?!
You both just ate
and drank us into debt
for the rest of forever‐‐
that's what!
[GUILD laughing]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Cheers!
[GUILD]
[ANIMAL MASK laughs]
[KOBOLD]
Watch me!
‐‐[WOLFGANG yells]
‐‐[MISHA groans]
[grunting]
This is great!
[WOLFMAN 12A]
Hmm!
[BARTENDER 4A chuckles]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Come on! Drink up!
[SHIGURE snarls]
Where is he?!
Oh, Shigure, that tournament
you helped put on
was simply splendid!
And might I add,
you have truly
spectacular timing!
Regarding this invoice,
how would you like to pay?
[SHIGURE growls]
How much have you guys
had to eat and drink,
you dumb jerks?!
Oh?
[laughter]
[SHIGURE]
My goodness.
Wrestling contests are fun.
You know,
I can't wait for
the next tournament!
‐‐[giggles]
‐‐Uh... What did you say?
Oh. Nothing important.
[SHOP OWNER 4A] Hey, Shigure!
What do you got for me today?
[SHIGURE]
Feast your eyes on this baby!
Uh, I don't know.
We typically only deal in
weapons and that sort of stuff.
[SHIGURE] I know. But you can
craft this into a weapon.
Look.
[SHOP OWNER 4A]
Hmm?
Mythril, huh?
That's different.
Color me interested!
[SHIGURE]
Yeah?
[ANIMAL MASK]
You hitting the road?
Yep.
I wanna get back to training,
so we can have another match.
I mean so I can be
a real pro‐wrestler.
I see.
[MAO]
Take care, Animal Mask.
[ANIMAL MASK]
See you around, MAO.
[MAO]
Heh.
[MAO] I wonder where
this new road will take me.
‐‐[GARM barking]
‐‐[MAO screams]
At least let me
finish my monologue!
[ANIMALS calling]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Such cute babies!
Who's ready for
lunchie‐munchies?
[giggles]
[SHIGURE]
Why're you still here?
Oh, Shigure!
I said to go to
the guild and get a quest
to pay off our debts! So skip
the happy ending crap!
Jeez. I'm going.
There's no need
to nag me so much.
[SHIGURE] Where are
Hanako and Carmilla?
[CARMILLA groans]
Seriously, guys?
None of you do any work around
here unless I tell you to do it.
[ANIMAL MASK] What? Don't lump
me in with the freeloaders.
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
Hey!
[GROUP]
Hmm?
[GUILD MASTER 1A panting]
There's demon beast trouble‐‐
Yeah, what about them?
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
There's been a minotaur sighted
in the southern valley!
Oh, wow, really?
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
Yes, and it's quite violent!
Violent as in
it's a high paying gig?
I wonder if it's yummy?
Will you be
going, too, Mistress?
I'd be happy to help you
change clothes for the journey!
[ANIMAL MASK chuckles]
Okay! To the minotaur!
[SHIGURE, HANAKO, CARMILLA]
Yeah!