[CELES]
Excuse me?!
[BEASTS growling]
‐‐Hmm?
‐‐Huh?
Uh?
I'm the hunter known as Celes!
Pardon the intrusion,
but I'm looking for a man
by the name of Genzo!
[growls
Are you the man
I'm searching for?
The Beast Killer?
Special attack: Head Chop!
[yelps]
[sobbing, whimpering]
How dare you!
Uh. Hey! What are you doin'?!
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK growls]
‐‐Ow! Holy crap, that hurts!
Please stop! I'm begging you‐‐
have mercy on me!
[GIRLS groan]
[ANIMAL MASK grunting]
[ANIMAL MASK]
That fight was pitiful.
Five seconds with my figure four
leg lock and she was done for.
[CELES sobbing]
[HIROYUKI whines]
I'm so sorry, are you okay?
That stupid jerk employs all
kinds of weird techniques.
And then, if you try
and get out of them,
it only makes everything
hurt a lot more.
[CELES whimpers]
Oh. Thanks, that's
very sweet... of you...
[ANIMAL MASK]
So, what do you want?
If you want an interview,
go through the maid.
Whoa, I am not your maid.
Who would serve a creepy,
perverted, human like you?
‐‐[CARMILLA, ANIMAL MASK growl]
‐‐[HANAKO] Fight! Fight! Fight!
Anyway, is there something
we can help you with?
It's like I said:
I go by the name of Celes.
I'm a hunter by trade, and I'm
new to the town of Cluster.
The thing is,
the guild master told me
that Genzo, the Beast Killer,
is the best hunter around.
Sounds like you're
ready for round two.
[gasps]
I'm definitely not!
I don't know what I said
to piss you off, but I'm sorry!
That ancient, bearded geezer!
Next time I see him,
I'm gonna give him
a figure four beard lock!
So, uh... Did you come
here looking for Genzo
because he's famous and you
wanna, like, challenge him
or whatever so you can
raise your hunter profile?
No, not at all! The opposite.
I came here... to ask a favor.
Make me your student!
[GIRLS]
His student?
[CELES]
Look, there's a special reason
that I wanna become stronger.
So, please... Say yes!
[ANIMAL MASK]
No.
Huh?
I'm an incredibly busy guy.
My schedule is packed today,
because I'm gonna go lay down
in front of stray cats and
see if they'll step on me
with their widdle feetsies!
[chuckles]
[SHIGURE]
Yeah, so, um...
The neighbors asked you
to stop doing that.
Plus, laying in the middle
of the road is dumb, duh.
Please! I'm begging you!
I don't have much to offer,
but I promise to try!
[SHIGURE grunts]
And... if you wanted...
Uh... I could always
pay you... with my body.
‐‐[SHIGURE] Uhh...
‐‐[HANAKO gasps]
No, thank you.
Come back when you're hotter.
If you had soft, silky fur
like a kobold,
I might consider it.
Did you just say I'm less
attractive than a kobold?
Please! I need to get stronger!
Jeez, lay off!
Now get outta here before
I show you how painful
a cobra twist can be!
‐‐Hmm?
‐‐[gasps]
Whoa, hold on.
On second thought,
sorry I bothered you.
Please forget about me
asking to be your student.
I'll go now.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Wait.
Hey. Let go!
[CELES whimpers]
No way...
You should have said
you're a lizardman, silly!
‐‐[GIRLS groan]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK chuckles]
Sorry I didn't tell you.
See, my ancestors
were lizardmen.
We look like demon beasts,
so people are afraid of us.
But we can also appear human.
I have lizardmen genes, clearly.
The scales you saw on
my stomach make it obvious.
They're on my back, too.
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK gasps]
‐‐Uh, Celes!
Ladies don't show off their
goods, at least not for free!
Sure, he's weird,
but Genzo's still a man!
He'll go after
anyone or anything,
and he's got that
crazy sparkle in his eye!
Normally, you would be right.
But this time it's different.
[CARMILLA] If that's true,
why not make her your student?
That was already my plan, jeez.
Get on my level, Carmilla.
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK, CARMILLA growl]
‐‐Wow. You really mean it?
[SHIGURE] Y'know, it's never too
late to find a normal teacher.
Maybe I could be
your teacher instead.
I'll show you my patented
special move, the "Death Roll!"
[CELES]
No. He accepted me even though
I'm a lizardman,
and that means a lot to me.
For that reason...
I trust Genzo!
[CARMILLA]
I think I just died again...
Right. In that case, we're off
to train in the mountains!
You might as well
count us in, too.
We wanna help with her training.
Yeah, as much as we can!
[ANIMAL MASK] Strength starts
with the posterior!
Now, hands above your head
and give me 20 squats.
[CELES]
Right! You got it!
One...
[CELES]
Two...
Three...
[CELES]
Four...
Tell me. Do your lizardmen
genes only show up
on your stomach and
backological regions?
Or like, do your thighs or
biceps ever get scales, too?
Uh. No. It's pretty much
just limited to my midriff.
That sucks.
In that case,
forget the squats Celes.
'Kay. Wait, wha...?
You heard me!
It's time to work out your core!
Chop‐chop, missy!
[CELES] But... I only
did like four squats.
Come on, Genzo.
Would it kill you to at least
try and be a little discreet?
[CELES groans]
[SHIGURE] Listen, if you wanna
train up your legs and core,
then I'll be a much better
teacher than Genzo.
Just do whatever I do, okay?
Uh, right! Let's do it!
Whenever you're ready.
And she's gone.
If you wanna get big,
then you gotta eat big!
Stuff your face
without prejudice!
Yeah, I'm gonna
have to pass on that advice!
Lizardmen and lizards are super
different when it comes to food!
And we definitely
don't eat bugs!
I mean, technically,
it's an arachnid.
Fine. Ahh...
‐‐[chomping, sloshing]
‐‐[CELES whimpering]
[HANAKO slurping]
Uh, you don't
have to copy Hanako.
Strong women are beautiful!
Give this a try!
Sexy pose attack!
Uh. So then, I just
say, "sexy pose attack"?
Super ineffective.
[BOTH growling]
[ANIMAL MASK, CELES panting]
[BOTH gruntign]
[CELES whimpers]
[gasps]
[ANIMAL MASK growls]
[CELES groans]
[CARMILLA chuckles]
[rasping]
[HANAKO chomping]
[CELES growls]
[ANIMAL MASK, CELES grunting]
There's nothing more
I can teach you.
You've reached the
end of your training.
[GIRLS sigh]
[CELES]
Really?! Thank you so much, sir!
There's not
a female wrestler alive
that could possibly match you!
So, I'll bestow you with
a wrestling name!
From this day forward you'll be,
"Celes Double XL"!
Yes, sir! It's an honor.
I'll use it with pride!
I never would have gotten
this far without you!
Except, no!
What's wrong?
Let me guess, you don't
like your wrestling name?
Hey, Carmilla,
what do you think?
I think it accurately describes
her physical attributes.
Though maybe she should
be Celes Triple XL?
Believe it or not,
the name isn't the problem!
When I asked you to train me,
I didn't think
it'd turn into this!
Oh, I see.
You don't wanna have to fight
with a mask on. Right?
Oh, right.
[CELES]
That's not it!
I'm not trying to
become a pro‐wrestler‐‐
I don't even know what that is!
Okay, then.
I realize now that we
probably should have led
with this question.
Is there a specific reason you
wanted Genzo to be your teacher?
Good question.
I guess I should
have started with that.
Don't get me wrong,
it's not like it's a super
interesting story or anything.
It's gotta be better than
anything Carmilla says.
What the heck?
Who hurt you, Genzo?
Here's what happened...
[HIROYUKI panting]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Are you serious?!
[BEASTS yelping]
[bellows]
I will bathe in their blood!
[gasping]
[panting]
Hey, you! Guild master guy!
Get your old ass out here!
If you don't...
...I'll start executing every
hunter in this room one by one!
Hey, man, calm down.
I am calm!
[gasps]
Pull yourself together, sir!
Jeez, you're making a scene!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Let me go!
Hey, wait a sec she's that
half‐breed lizard thing, right?
[GUILD SOLDIER 2A]
Yeah, she is!
I can't believe she's still
hanging around here.
I thought she was long gone.
Yo, want me to
hunt that girl for ya?
[gulps
[ANIMAL MASK snarls]
Try it!
[GUILD SOLDIER 1C groans]
[gasping]
‐‐[GUILD SOLDIER 1A] Hey!
‐‐Guys, we've gotta stop him!
Quick, before he
destroys the guild!
[ANIMAL MASK snarls]
[SHIGURE whimpers]
Man. This is bad.
[yelling]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Die!
Execution!
Wait. Please. No!
‐‐[groans]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Death for you!
Go get 'em, Genzo!
Destroy them all!
Be quiet! Why are
you being so loud?!
Hey...
What's going on here?
What happened?
Okay, Demon Beast Killer!
Out with it! Explain yourself!
You know how I feel
about that awful name.
Call me that one more time
and I'll rip off your beard.
[ALL]
Uhh...
Now, now.
Just take a deep breath.
Let's all calm down.
Using your words‐‐
What's got you so riled up?
You wamna know
what's wrong, huh?
Ow, ow, that's attached!
Listen, geezer!
You know that I'm an extremely
kind‐hearted man whose soul
is filled with a fiery
passion for all creatures,
big and small, right?
Uh... Yes. I'm aware.
And, while I'm not sure
what you're saying,
I know that you're a strange
man who's oddly in love
with demon beasts.
Look, I'm here because of
your piece‐of‐shit hunters!
They've been bullying a
lizardman and doing all kinds
of unspeakable things to her!
[CELES]
Can you please calm down, sir?
[ANIMAL MASK]
[CELES] Also, stop
making it sound so dirty!
All they did was
tease me a little,
and they kind of messed with me.
They messed with you? No way!
How did they mess with you?!
Tell me right now!
Was it your stomach?
Did they do something bad to
your gorgeous, perfect scales?
No! What made you jump
to that conclusion?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Oh, my bad.
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
Hold on...
So basically, you destroyed the
guild and KO'd all my men
because they were
actually harassing Celes,
who happens to be
a lizardman, is that right?
And then Celes tracked you down
and asked you to train her?
Yeah, pretty much.
I wanted to teach
the others a lesson.
But then, I had a realization.
When it came down to it,
I was upset over something
that didn't matter.
Now that my teachers have
taught me how to master the art,
and taught me
the value of true strength,
I don't care about it anymore.
I guess... it's okay.
Because, from here on out,
I wanna be a better person.
Just like my teachers.
That's so sweet!
We're sorry.
Yeah, and I'm sorry
for calling you
a half‐breed and giving
you such a hard time.
We were just mad.
Our hunts have sucked lately.
It's not your fault.
But we took it out on you
because you're the new girl
and a demi‐human.
[GUILD SOLDIER 2A]
Sorry...
[CELES gasps]
[chuckles]
Uh. Yeah, I call BS.
‐‐[GUILD MASTER 1A] Huh...?
‐‐[HUNTERS] Wha...?
[GUILD murmuring]
Listen, Celes.
If there's one thing I know,
it's life is a battlefield.
That's why humans
have to be tough.
Uh, yeah, but I'm a lizardman.
You're still
my student and a wrestler.
And a wrestler accepts
any and all challenges
that come their way!
Except... I'm actually a hunter.
Whatever! Point is, you can't
show these jerks mercy
just because they gave you
some half‐hearted apology!
And don't forget!
They were mean to you!
So, apologies are for chumps!
It's time to pay the piper!
As your teacher,
I order you to fight them!
Crush them! Sweep their legs!
Make them fear you!
[GUILD]
Wow, this guy really is crazy.
Look, thing is...
I'm really not that mad anymore,
so this is all unnecessary.
You take revenge
on those jerbronies,
or I step up and give
them all a smack down!
What?
[CELES]
Hold on...
Could it be that Genzo really
cares about me that much?
Uh, somehow,
I highly doubt that.
You guys should
apologize for real!
Trust me, you don't want
to make Genzo mad!
Just say you're really sorry,
strike your most
submissive pose,
and pray that it's
actually sincere enough
to not get you executed!
[CELES]
I understand now, sir.
I'll do it as long as
the battle lasts until one side
gives up, and it's not
a fight to the death.
I'm actually curious.
It'll be nice to see
how strong I've become.
Let's put it all to the test!
Sounds kinda fun!
Well, if that's the case,
I'll be your opponent!
Fair warning, I won't hold back
just because you're new!
Celes, use your legs!
Just like how we practiced!
[CELES grunting]
Whoa, what the heck?
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐Ha! [growls]
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B grunting]
Come on, bite him,
just like we practiced!
Use your teeth and sink them
into his soft, delicious sides,
devouring his intestines
like spaghetti!
Ha!
I won't lose!
[panting]
Hey, man, if you're
gonna fight her,
then you better not lose!
You gotta show that lizardman
who's boss in this town!
Keep your head
in the match, man!
She's a feisty one‐‐
don't let your guard down!
You've got this, get her!
[yells]
Ha!
Don't give up,
Celes, you can do it!
Aim for the thigh!
It's the most meaty, delicious
part of the human body!
If you lose this match,
then no food!
[GUILD yelling]
[CLAUSE]
Hmm.
[CLAUSE] My, it seems to
be rather lively today.
Oh, hey.
It's good to see
you again, Clause.
[CLAUSE]
What is this? A duel?
Oh, it's a mock battle.
To be honest,
it's a bit of a long story.
Huh.
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B,
CELES grunting]
[CLAUSE]
Hmm...
[CELES grunting]
Okay! Time to finish him!
[CARMILLA, CELES]
Sexy Pose Attack!
[WOMAN moaning]
‐‐[GUILD SOLDIER 1B] Uh... Huh.
‐‐[CELES humming]
Wah!
Owwie, what'd I do?!
[ANIMAL MASK] You're not
allowed to give advice anymore!
Teach her a lesson!
Make her pay!
Quit it! The fight's not
over yet, we need to focus!
[SHIGURE]
Celes is in big trouble!
[CELES groans]
What kind of
stupid attack was that?
When you told me
you'd been training,
I didn't think it would
be so freakin' weird!
I thought I had the
wrong idea about you,
but now I feel like a moron!
Yeah, well, what would you know?
[gasps]
Give up, this battle is over!
Look, Celes! His waist is open!
[CELES grunts]
[CELES yells]
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B gasps]
What is happening?!
[VOICE 1A]
One! Two! Three!
‐‐[bell rings]
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
[CARMILLA]
Yay, Celes is the winner!
You totally crushed that guy!
And bonus‐‐
I just found another sword!
Whoa, that fight was amazing!
Yeah, for sure.
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B]
I admit defeat.
I gotta say, I'm impressed.
Guess I really
underestimated lizardmen.
Please. It was nothing.
I thought it was
a splendid match.
Also, I can't really claim
a perfect victory, can I?
I lost not one, but both of my
weapons during the fight.
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B] I suppose
we could call it a draw, then.
[CELES chuckles] Sure, I'd love
to have a rematch in the future.
And next time, I'll beat you!
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B, CELES laugh]
Yeah, I call BS.
[BOTH]
Uh...
Not again. What is your
malfunction today, Genzo?
Seriously, you're an even
bigger pain than usual.
Just let the episode have
its happy ending already
so we can go home.
No way!
You really want me to be okay
with the moral of this story
saying it's cool
to bully someone
as long as you're sorry?!
Exactly! That's how
morals and stories work!
Let me go, Shigure!
I've got a point to prove!
I gotta make sure they know this
kind of behavior's unacceptable!
[SHIGURE groans]
Listen, if you just let it go,
I'll let you rub my ears
when we get home.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Huh...?
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
Excuse me, Genzo?
Huh?
Please calm down.
Everyone's just a little
frustrated because their hunts
haven't been going
all that smoothly lately.
Like I give a crap.
Oh, yeah,
they mentioned that earlier.
It's the strangest thing.
See, there's this
barbarian‐like beast man
who just appears out of nowhere.
Beast man, huh?
Yeah, we suspect that it may be
a weretiger or something.
Whenever we catch a demon beast,
that guy pops up and steals
our prey before we
can even do anything.
It's crazy.
Oh, and he was wearing like
a weird cape or whatever.
It's as if it just
appears out of the shadows.
Then it beats us
using weird techniques.
Even if we catch
our prey, he takes it.
[CARMILLA, SHIGURE groan]
But none of that is your fault,
so we're sorry.
Well, I guess
we can accept that.
If you want to,
you can forgive them.
Oh. Um... Yeah.
Okay, then.
[GUILD] We're really, really
sorry we were mean to you.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hm!
[SHIGURE] Genzo. Can I
have a word with you?
Not right now.
About the masked
barbarian they mentioned...
Give it up. You know
it's a waste to even ask.
[ANIMAL MASK]
It's a mystery.
[SHIGURE] I've been wondering
where those new demon beasts
were coming from,
but it was you, huh?
Huh?
Might I have
a moment of your time?
You wanna have a big tournament?
Yes. I was very impressed by
that mock battle I saw earlier.
From what I gathered,
the public seems
to enjoy watching people
fight each other.
In addition to selling
tickets to the event,
we could also sell
food and merchandise.
I assume it will be
a profitable venture.
[SHIGURE squeals]
That sounds amazing!
Plus, I'll do anything
to help fix our budget!
If you're going to
make merchandise,
might I suggest modeling
it after my mistress?
It will surely sell.
I only heard the part
where you said
there will be food. And if
that's the case, I'm all in!
But... I wanna open a pet shop.
[CLAUSE] If you agree
to take part in the fights,
then we'd be happy
to compensate you.
You could use that money
to fund your business.
Fight money?
So it's come to this.
[gasps]
[ANIMAL MASK]
What the..?
My pecks are trying
to tell me something.
It's like they're excited
to get back in the ring
and fight again!
[BEASTS roaring]
[ANIMAL MASK] My training
has led me to this moment.
And if it will help the animals.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Very well!
A wrestler has to
accept all challenges!
‐‐[CARMILLA giggles]
‐‐[SHIGURE, HANAKO gasp]
[ANIMAL MASK] Looks like
I'm returning to pro‐wrestling!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Next time: "Animal and Event!"