[CLAUSE]
Well, Genzo? How is it?
[MAN 8A] We made it to the
specifications you gave us.
Great! The mat
and ropes are perfect.
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B]
Man, I can't wait!
Hey do we get paid for this?
We had better!
This is awesome!
Check out at all the
people who showed up!
[CLAUSE]
With this many people,
we'll have more than enough
participants for the tournament.
No. Hold on.
Huh?
There's something missing.
But I don't know what.
[HIROYUKI whines]
[barks]
[ANIMAL MASK gasps]
That's it! Animals!
[GUILD SOLDIERS]
Huh...?
This event needs more animals.
I'm not sure
we should involve animals
in a fighting
tournament with humans.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Too bad! Make it happen!
No animals, no tournament.
Come on, are you
really throwing a fit
like a spoiled little kid?
[CLAUSE] What if we
compromise and recruit
a couple of beast men to fight?
It might get people talking.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Ah! Good idea!
[ANIMAL MASK] If I turn
beast men intro wrestlers,
it'll give me
an excuse to touch
their luscious fur
during the match!
Great, it's that
weird look you get
when you think about animals.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Anyway, do you happen
to know any beast men
who would wanna
participate in the fight?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hmm...
Hey. Hello, miss!
[WOMAN 3A]
Hi, Genzo. Well, now.
Fancy meeting you here.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Ah You're stunning. Wow!
O‐Oh!
[ANIMAL MASK] Your lush
coat... your beautiful tail...
‐‐[WOMAN 3A sighs]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Just gorgeous.
[WOMAN 3A]
O‐Oh, you. You're too much!
Don't look at me that way.
You know I could
never leave my husband.
Husband? Wait, that's it!
‐‐Miss!
‐‐[WOMAN 3A] Uh?
I must go now.
I'm off to see your husband!
‐‐What?
‐‐Hold on.
What are you planning
on doing, Genzo?
Oh, no. Is he off
to challenge my husband?
Genzo, you can't!
[ANIMAL MASK] Miss! I'm headed
to your place right now!
‐‐[WOMAN 3A] Genzo, wait!
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Okay, bye!
Dear? Hey, I'm finally home.
Ah?
Who the heck are you?
Say something, dammit!
You can't just barge into
a man's house like this!
Oh, wow.
You're pretty jacked,
aren't you?
Thanks?
Please stop it!
Don't fight over little ol' me.
We're fighting over you?
Ah. That means...
I was wondering why she
was taking so much time
to pick bugs out of her
fur and do her nails!
How dare you!
You think you can come here
and steal my wife?
I'm not a thief. I'm a wrestler.
Don't insult me
with your weird lies.
You thief!
[yells]
[ANIMAL MASK groans]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hmph!
[KOBOLD grunts]
Take this!
[yells]
[ANIMAL MASK growls]
Try again!
[KOBOLD yells]
[bellows]
No way! You're strong.
[grunts]
You're not half bad.
[yells]
[ANIMAL MASK, KOBOLD grunting]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Have another!
‐‐Darling. He's fighting Genzo.
Uh...
[BOTH panting]
[KOBOLD] Weird.
What's this heat in my chest?
It reminds me of something.
[KOBOLD]
That's right. I remember.
This is how I felt when I
used to let my fists
‐‐do all the talking!
‐‐[KOBOLD yells]
[KOBOLD gasps]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK bellows]
‐‐[KOBOLD groans]
[sighs]
Looks like I lost, huh?
Yes, you did.
But it was still a good fight.
Come be a wrestler with me.
Heh. Because of you,
I remembered something today
that I had almost forgotten.
I'm sorry, dear. I have to go.
I want to chase
that light once again.
Darling! No!
Did Genzo steal your husband?
Whoa, plot twist.
[MISHA] Come on, bro!
Let's go outside already!
You've been cooped up
in here for days.
I can't, it's too dangerous!
What if that perv's
waiting for me?
I won't, no.
Please, I'm begging‐‐don't
make me leave the house!
I just don't get it,
he's completely changed.
This would have
never happened if it weren't
for that pantless bully.
Ever since we met him,
my bro's been traumatized.
You have to be brave
and face your fears!
Besides, if we just avoid his
weird pet shop of horrors,
then nothing bad
will happen to us!
[BOTH scream
Holy crap, what the hell
are you doing here?!
Why?!
Hey, fluffy wolf man.
Y‐Yeah? What do you guys want?
‐‐Be a pro‐wrestler.
‐‐[MISHA hisses]
Uh... A pro what now?
Yes, pro wrestling
is the ultimate martial art.
No, the ultimate entertainment!
[SHIGURE]
Here. The info's on this flyer.
So, it's like a tournament?
Hold on, are you trying
to say you want me
to fight you?
No! Nope! Nope! No!
‐‐No way, never, noperoni!
‐‐[MISHA] Calm down, bro!
[WOLFGANG blubbers]
[MISHA] That creep is why
he's in such bad shape.
Well what about me, then?
Can I be a pro‐wrestler?
You?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hmm...
Sure, accepted.
Uh, Genzo?
Just where were you looking
when you made that decision?
Here's what we have so far:
Misha and Mister Kobold will be
participating. Sound good?
It'd be better if we could
get a few more fighters
Huh?
[ORCS murmuring]
Did I plant this right?
As long as you
aren't planting it too deep.
Whoa. Are those
orcs planting flowers?
‐‐[ORCS] Huh?
‐‐Hey, check it out,
it's the king.
It's been a while
since we've seen you.
I guess that's true. What's up?
We're trying to find
good things we can do
for the town and
level up our karma!
We're plantin'! Cool, right?
Ah?
Just gonna put this tree here.
Whew.
Oh. Well, look there,
if it isn't the king!
Yo.
[CARMILLA guffaws]
It smells
just like the mistress!
[moans, sniffs]
[ANIMAL MASK] Do I wanna
know what you're doing?
Oh! Genzo! Shigure!
You guys are home
kind of early, huh?
Oh, come on,
I only want a couple!
That's my food!
Stupid freeloader!
Yeah, it takes one
to know one, doesn't it?
[SHINGEN] I said no!
Give it back, you dumb broad!
Obviously, I can't
leave you home alone.
Too dangerous.
So, it's wrestlin' time!
[barks]
Um, why are the orcs here?
No idea.
[HEAT HAZE]
To be honest,
I don't know what this
whole "pro‐wrestling" thing
is supposed to be,
but if it's a quest,
then count me in.
Behold! The magic spear, Guy
Belg, found in a northern cave!
I can take on anyone
if I have this baby.
Don't you dare!
[HEAT HAZE yells]
[CLAUSE]
Hmm. Things are looking good.
Oh, look, it seems
I've stumbled upon a new spear!
'Kay! Gather 'round.
I'm going to explain
pro‐wrestling.
It is the ultimate artform.
Wrestlers fight
in a square ring
using nothing but
their brute strength!
What makes
it wonderful, you ask?
It's the combination of skills,
the coordination,
the friendship between
team members,
and the love from our dear fans.
[SELLER 8A] Hey, I brought
everyone some snacks.
[HANAKO] Yay! Perfect
timing, I'm starving!
It's just some
leftovers that we had,
but I'll bring some more later.
I've got a fresh batch in
the oven, but of course
you'll have to pay
for whatever you eat.
[GUILD SOLDIER 1C] Eat up,
we gotta refuel for the fight!
[PRINCESS]
Hero. Wherever can you be?
[SOLDIER 8A] Princess Altena!
I've been looking for you!
[PRINCESS]
What is it?
[SOLDIER 8A] You see...
It's this flyer we found.
[gasps]
This technique!
[CLAUSE] What if we put
the names of our sponsors on
the ring and the
fighter's clothing,
and then charge them a fee?
Excellent idea!
Oh, and we can charge the
vendors extra if they want
prime spots at the event!
Today, we'll focus
on live sparring.
[GROUP]
All right!
[HIROYUKI barks]
May the best man win.
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B]
Take this!
There's no biting in wrestling!
Hi‐yah!
Eat this!
[BOTH groan]
I could probably down another.
Bet I can beat you!
[CROWD shouting]
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
All good,
but next time, I'll win!
You may be small,
but you're super strong.
You are, too!
By the way,
your stomach is delicious.
Mistress, if you don't
wipe off all that sweat,
you might catch a cold.
Go and get changed, I'll take
care of those clothes for you.
[groans]
[wheezes]
[HIROYUKI whines]
Still not good enough.
Look, there's more
to being a pro‐wrestler
than just fighting.
You have to follow
the rules of the sport,
and still manage to keep it
entertaining for fans!
As long as the crowd's
having fun, why does it matter?
No! Those are the rules!
It's my way or the highway.
So intense.
Ah! Check it out, Genzo!
Food as far as the eye can see!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Would you look at that?
Shigure's set up
a stall of her own.
[HANAKO giggles]
Let's go!
[SHIGURE]
Welcome, Genzo!
What's wrong with your face?
You look dead.
I've been super
busy teaching people
how to wrestle, and I still had
to prepare for the tournament.
[ANIMAL MASK, HEAT HAZE yell]
[ANIMAL MASK] Good wrestlers
know how to take a hit!
Good wrestlers
can endure the pain!
[ANIMAL MASK]
You didn't train hard enough!
Argh!
[ANIMAL MASK] Man up! This is
the life of a pro‐wrestler!
I also had to
write up a script
for the announcers to read.
It reminded me of when
I first started and had to do
all the grunt work.
Wow, you've been pretty busy.
Hey, Shigure.
I can't help but notice that
you don't have any food here.
[SHIGURE]
We only sell merchandise.
[HANAKO squeals]
I see...
[SHIGURE]
You can get food other places.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Still, it's a cool booth.
It looks like you're milking the
fighters for all they're worth.
Of course I am.
It costs a lot of money
to feed you freeloaders.
[HANAKO]
C'mon, Genzo!
I wanna go get some of
that fried dark tiger meat!
[ANIMAL MASK]
How much more can you eat?!
Now!
Do you got any more
of that muscle merch?
Do I? Feast your
hungry eyes on this.
[GIRL 8A whoops, shrieks]
Hello, muscle mania!
These prints are limited.
So, you'd better act fast.
[GIRL 8A]
I can't!
But if I don't buy them,
I'll have regrets!
Okay.
At long last, I'll finally
avenge my brother.
I'll make that perv
beg for mercy.
[CROWD cheers]
Come on!
You've got this!
[ORC KING groans]
[CROWD cheers]
I wish I could have fought
in the wrestling match, too.
You were disqualified
'because you tried
to eat your opponent,
ya dumb broad!
The Orcs are tying
to win with raw power,
but I think the hunters
may have better technique.
What are your thoughts
on the fight, Hanako?
Good question.
In my opinion, orc meat
isn't very tasty,
but the shoulder meat
tends to be the exception
to that particular rule.
Personally I like to
add some salt to it
which enhances the flavor.
[ORC MC whimpers]
[ORC KING]
Hmph.
[groans]
One...
Two... And three...
That's match
That's incredible!
Did you see that?
Wasn't that an amazing
fight, Hanako?
[HANAKO]
Yes! Though I have to admit
I hope the next round of
fighters will be a bit tastier.
Now, in the red corner.
It is the muscular, yet furry,
strong, but still
cute, kobold man!
[ORC MC] His passion for
fighting burns once again!
[SHINGEN]
And in the blue corner,
put your hands and claws
together for Celes XXL!
[CROWD cheers]
[SHINGEN]
The Lizardman returns!
We've all been waiting for this!
The crowd seems
to be very excited.
Word of the tournament
has spread all over town,
and we're selling a lot
of same‐day tickets.
This is a huge success!
Not good enough.
Huh?
We're missing
the drama and rivalries
that make
pro‐wrestling exciting.
Whatever. I'll take
your word for it.
But for us normal people,
this is super fun!
No way, it sucks!
You have to have rivalries!
It's an absolute
must‐have, okay?
This again?
You can be a real pain,
you know that?
Especially when it
comes to stuff you love.
[CELES yells]
[KOBOLD yells]
[CELES grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
One, two, and three!
[KOBOLD gasps]
‐‐[CELES] Yeah!
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
[KOBOLD]
Hey, you counted way too fast!
And Celes XXL
wins with a huracanrana!
Hanako, your thoughts?
[HANAKO] Kobold muscles have
pretty slow reaction times,
but they're very
tender and juicy!
I recommend the thigh meat.
Grind it up and make it
into hamburgers.
[ORC MC] Now, the sky has begun
to darken for some reason.
Perhaps because it's
time for the main event!
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
‐‐My turn.
[SHINGEN] In the red corner
is our resident loser,
Vanstein Carmilla!
[ORC MC]
And wouldn't you know?
She's wearing sweat pants.
[SHINGEN]
And Genzo Shibata!
[CROWD cheers]
[ORC MC]
He's the only guy in town
with a weird
obsession for animals!
[yells]
[ORC MC] It may look
like Beauty and the Beast,
but with this tag team, it's
more like Beast and the Beast!
Oh, what's this?
I guess you're a man
after all, Genzo.
So, did you make me
your tag team partner
because I'm so attractive?
Huh? No, it's just,
despite my desperate pleas,
you're so terrible
to work with that no one
else would put up with you.
‐‐[CARMILLA] What?!
‐‐[BOTH growl]
[SHINGEN]
And in the blue corner,
give it up for the
hero, Heat Haze!
[ORC MC]
They call him Mister Sandbag!
[WOMEN screaming]
[SHINGEN]
And Misha!
[ORC MC]
Known as the tomboy cat girl!
[MISHA]
Time to pay the piper, you perv!
You've got this! Crush 'em!
[ding]
[CROWD cheers]
[SHIGURE] You seem to be into
this pro‐wrestling, Clause.
[CLAUSE gasps]
Who, me?
I mean, it's all right.
Yeah, sure.
I shall make the first strike!
I'm reclaiming the top fighter
title, Demon Beast Killer!
Not today!
[grunts
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
‐‐Hey!
Okay! He's yours!
[CARMILLA grunts]
Oh, oopsie!
‐‐Oh no, I missed!
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK groans]
That's my bad, Genzo!
I have terrible
depth perception!
You liar! That was
definitely deliberate!
No, it was an accident!
Your face is an accident!
[ORC MC] It seems the two beasts
are fighting amongst themselves.
‐‐Now's our chance!
‐‐[HEAT HAZE] Right!
[MISHA, HEAT HAZE grunt]
[ANIMAL MASK, CARMILLA grunt]
[CROWD cheers]
What in the heck?
Hey!
[CARMILLA growls]
[MISHA yelps]
[WOLFGANG gasps]
[MISHA] I knew it. I'm not
strong enough to avenge him.
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
One...
‐‐Two...
‐‐[CROWD] Two...
Huh?
No way... It's you!
It's Wolfgang!
[gasps]
Wait. For real?
Did you come here
to get your revenge?
N‐N‐N‐No, you're wrong,
that's not why I came!
A brand‐new challenger
has appeared.
You have any comments
on the new guy, Hanako?
A werewolf, huh?
They have a lot of meat
that's deliciously tender,
and you can use it in all
kinds of things like stew,
but I personally think
it tastes the best
when you smoke it
first, you know?
On behalf of
the event's sponsors,
I'd like to request a sub.
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
‐‐A sub? Wait, me?
Put your hands together,
'cause we have a new challenger!
Give it up for the lean, mean,
‐‐wolfman machine, Wolfgang!
‐‐What the‐‐? Hold on!
I didn't come here
to fight anybody!
I'm so glad you're here!
[CROWD]
Wolfgang! Wolfgang! Wolfgang!
Everyone's excited!
So, this is rivalry and drama.
Some of you may know
our new challenger Wolfgang,
as the beast man who
was attacked by Genzo
not too long ago.
He was swung around like
a ragdoll and easily defeated.
You could even say
he was traumatized!
But today is different!
It appears that he's
overcome his past traumas!
We are witnessing
the rebirth of Wolfgang!
Are you ready to rumble, rover?
[microphone feedback screeches]
Bring it!
When my brother and I work
together, we're unstoppable!
I wouldn't go that far.
We'll completely destroy you!
[grunts]
[CARMILLA growls]
[WOLFGANG groaning]
[ANIMAL MASK giggles]
Get ready, because
somebody is about to get
their fur rubbed all over again!
Wait, you're going to do what?!
Uh! Ah! No! Stop it!
Get your hands off of me!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Rub, rub, rub!
Who's a good boy?
Where's your spot?
There it is! There it is!
Who wants scratchies?
[WOLFGANG]
Have some decency!
Please, c‐cut it out!
[howls]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Cheers!
[ALL]
[laughter]
Awesome work‐‐
the fight was a success!
Eat and drink your fill,
you've earned it!
[cheering]
Congratulations!
The event was a huge success.
I'm not sure we should count
the last match as a success.
The good news is we made a ton.
So, we can pay you a substantial
amount for the fight.
Yes! We're one step closer
to getting the pet shop!
[GUILD]
♪ Blessed be a brand new day. ♪
♪ We fought together
and we got paid! ♪
♪ As fighters,
we've paid all our dues, ♪
♪ now we rejoice and
fill up on booze! ♪
You know, this kinda
makes me feel happy.
So this is what Genzo wants.
I get it now.
[SELLER 8A]
Excuse me, Shigure?
Yes?
It's the bill.
[SHIGURE]
Huh...?
What the hell is this crap?!
Do you see all these
bills we got for repairs
on the stalls and buildings you
wrecked during practice?!
Look at the tab for the booze
Carmilla guzzled down!
And don't get me
started on Hanako's tab!
Plus, there's the money we owe
the baker for the tons of bread
everyone ate and this
stupid after‐party!
Now all the prize money we won
and the money from my stall
is completely gone...!
[ANIMAL MASK, HANAKO, CARMILLA]
We're sorry...
Looks like we're going
back to watered down soup
and salted potatoes.
[ANIMAL MASK, HANAKO, CARMILLA]
Fair.
The hero has had ample
time to prepare for battle.
I'm sure he's used it to
assemble a powerful army.
A team match, huh?
Yeah, he's good at those.
[JOANNA] I propose
we try and strengthen
our own forces as well.
[MAO]
Do you have a plan?
Yes. We recruit
the demon beasts to help.
Demon beasts?
Do you mean animals?
[ANIMAL MASK] Next time:
"Princess and Panties!"