[MC]
It's time for the main event!
Will this bring an end to
their long‐standing rivalry?
What sort of match do these two
warriors have in store for us?
[MAO grunting]
[MAO]
Time's finally come.
[grunting]
‐‐[CROWD cheers]
‐‐[MAO groans]
[grunting]
‐‐[CROWD cheering]
‐‐[bell ringing]
[yells]
‐‐[CROWD cheering]
‐‐[MAO groans]
[BOTH grunting]
‐‐[bell ringing]
‐‐[CROWD cheering]
[MAO]
Stupid memories!
The losing streak ends tonight!
No more games‐‐I'm gonna
pin Animal Mask to the mat
or die trying!
[grunting]
You ready, MAO? You're up next.
[MAO grunts]
Right!
[MAO]
It's ass kicking time
[MC] Making his way to the ring,
weighing in at 178 pounds.
It's the Macadamian Ogre!
‐‐[CROWD]
‐‐[MC] AKA, MAO!
[MAO]
Let's do this!
[MC] Now, The man with the
awkward love for animals,
weighing in at 198 pounds,
it's Animal Mask!
[MC]
The day has arrived!
Will MAO beat
this long‐time rival?
[MAO]
Animal Mask.
I hope you're religious,
because you're about
to meet your maker!
[CROWD cheering]
[MAO]
Heh...
[MAO laughs]
This is it! This is finally it!
[ANIMAL MASK grunts]
[MAO]
This is the day...
...you go‐‐down!
[MC] And a flying move
off the turnbuckle.
[MC]
What's happening?
Now he seems to be glowing!
What sort of move is this?
[MC]
They disappeared!
Wait, what's happening?
Animal Mask is gone!
He's vanished from the ring!
[MC]
S‐Seriously, what's happening?
Is this part of
the show, or, um...?
[MAO snarls]
[COMMENTATORS gasping]
[MAO panting]
You pathetic coward!
Get back here!
[MAO]
He ran from the fight!
I mean, who runs away
from a title match?
Come and face me.
You gutless chicken nugget!
But all nuggets are gutless.
It's processed meat.
Hey, it's a sick burn, okay?
You listening, Animal Mask?
You can't run away
because you were losing!
You finish what you started!
So get back here
and take it like a man!
[microphone feedback screeches]
[groaning]
[MAO growls]
[MAO grunts]
[REPORTERS yelling]
[sighs]
Oh, boy.
This is weird‐‐I have
no idea where he ran off to.
[sighs]
Come on, Animal Mask.
[SAIGO sighs]
Poor Genzo.
Grieving over!
I'm off to the magical world
of women's pro‐wrestling!
[giggles]
[gibbering]
[SHIGURE]
Genzo!
Now, eat all you want!
Then you'll grow up
to be big and strong!
‐‐[SHIGURE] Genzo!
‐‐Won't you?
[phone buzzing]
[MAO sobbing loudly]
[MAO'S MANAGER 5B]
This is serious!
The guy won't answer
any of my calls.
[MAO'S MANAGER 5C]
It can't be helped,
we'll have to find
him a new opponent.
[MAO'S MANAGER 5B] But he
says he refuses to fight anyone
but Animal Mask.
[MAO'S MANAGER 5A]
I see.
Probably because Animal Mask
is the only wrestler
he's never beaten, the one
mountain he hasn't climbed.
[MAO'S MANAGER 5A] He can't
beat someone we can't find.
[MAO'S MANAGER 5C]
Yeah.
[MAO grunts]
[MAO sighs]
[MASCOT 5A]
Hey, check out our new location!
[MAO growls]
Animal Mask.
[MAO]
Where are you, you coward?!
[gibbering]
[SHIGURE]
Genzo! What are you doing?
I've been calling you.
Yeah? I'm sorry.
Just go do whatever you
need to do without me, okay?
What? Are you serious?
Yeah, of course!
I have to stay here, just in
case my darling Masao needs me!
[SHIGURE] Hmph.
He's asleep‐‐what could he need?
Yeah, maybe for now,
but think about it.
Masao hasn't been here long.
What if he wakes up,
and I'm nowhere to be found?
[MASAO]
Hmm?
[MASAO whines]
[MASAO whimpering]
[ANIMAL MASK] Doesn't that
just break your heart...?
I mean, it's hypothetical,
so no, not really.
I wanna be at his side
for every waking moment.
At least until he gets
used to his new home.
Aren't cù‐sìth
harbingers of death
with the ability to
steal a human's soul?
Not really the ideal pet,
if you value living.
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Hmph!
‐‐[SHIGURE grunts]
So, Masao is going to
be a bit of a project.
What? I said he can kill you.
Anyway, no more excuses.
[ANIMAL MASK]
But the little guy needs me!
[SHIGURE]
Denied! Let's go.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hey! No!
I won't go quietly! Shigure!
He needs me!
You're the only monster here!
Let me go!
[SHIGURE] All right, Hiroyuki,
we're heading out now!
‐‐Hold down the fort.
‐‐My babies need me! Please!
‐‐[HIROYUKI yapping]
‐‐No, wait! Masao!
[wails]
[SHIGURE]
Right.
Carmilla and Hanako are waiting
for us, so stop struggling.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Stop manhandling me, Shigure!
Ugh. I thought
they would never leave.
I was afraid we'd
have to come back.
Hey. Are we really doing this?
[WOLFGANG] I've never seen
a demon beast like that.
That drooly ankle‐biter's
gotta be worth a fortune!
Rich chumps love
owning rare things.
That's why we're
gonna steal him!
[MISHA] Hmm. Yeah, but what
if that muscle‐bound moron
comes back early?
Look, if you want my opinion,
I think we're better off
avoiding that gross
pervert altogether.
You don't get it!
I refuse to rest until
I've had my revenge!
[growls]
After what he did to me,
I hate that perv
more than anything!
[MISHA]
What did he do to you?
[MISHA snickers]
Are you thinking
about it right now?
[MISHA]
Mm‐mm, mm‐mm!
No! Stop it!
Don't you dare think about it!
And don't laugh at me!
[MISHA grunting]
I'm sorry!
[WOLFGANG]
Now come on, let's go!
[MISHA]
Okay...
Is this really gonna work?
[WOLFGANG]
Of course!
And even if it doesn't
work, then too bad!
Make it work!
[MISHA] No need to shout.
Anyway, what's the plan?
[WOLFGANG] Don't you fret. This
idea is literally fool proof!
[chuckles]
First, we tie an
expensive ham to a string
and throw it in
the dirt close to him.
[MISHA]
And waste a ham?
[WOLFGANG] Next, we use the
dirt ham to lure him to us.
[WOLFGANG] As soon as the
little guy gets close enough,
you swoop in with a bag!
And then we make tracks!
Isn't it genius?
If you say so.
Ham time!
[MISHA]
Okay!
Still seems like
a waste of a good ham...
[sniffing]
[barks]
You know, I don't see
a dradradogola anywhere.
Same here.
Maybe they aren't in this area.
I guess, but the clerk
at the guild said
this is where we
would find them.
Welp, looks like she was wrong.
There's no food
here either, this is boring.
[gasps] Please don't
give up yet, mistress.
I promise I'll
figure something out!
‐‐[HANAKO] Hmm?
‐‐Hold on.
I suddenly have
a bad feeling about this.
We should head back to the shop.
This again?
Give it a rest, Genzo.
Listen. I'm being serious!
‐‐[whimpers]
‐‐[HIROYUKI whines]
[ANIMAL MASK]
I know it sounds crazy,
but I think I'm getting a
message from the spirit world,
telling me that my precious
furbabies are in danger!
[sniffing]
Yep, I was right.
Smells like bull crap.
Hey!
I can tell you're lying, 'kay?
At least be honest and
admit you don't care about
these goblin root things 'cause
it's a plant and not an animal!
Not true!
And what about that one time,
with Keiko? Remember?
[SHIGURE] I remember
the lie about Toshihiko.
[ANIMAL MASK groans]
Hey. I'm ho‐‐
[gasps]
[WOLFGANG groans]
Crap! Are they dead?
[MISHA groans]
Ah! [sighs] Good.
What happened to ya?
Oh. It's you, Edgar.
You see...
My brother convinced me
to go with him to kidnap
that tiny beast thing.
Because he really wanted
to teach that weird pervert
a lesson, I guess.
Yeah?
And you geniuses did it
without lettin' me know?
Well, I did try to tell him
that you wouldn't
like it, but...
[HIROYUKI sniffing]
[chuckles] That pervy creep's
gonna cry his brains out.
Sure, whatever floats your boat.
Okay. Go!
Aye‐aye.
[WOLFGANG grunts]
[HIROYUKI whines]
It's working! Misha!
Ready whenever you are!
[HIROYUKI sniffing]
[barks]
He barked at me!
You know, I actually think
the little guy's kinda cute.
Hey there, fluffy britches,
you like the taste of
that spiral ham, don't ya?
Uh, why are you talking to it?
We've gotta get it in the bag!
Yeah, you can have all
the yummy ham you want!
[MISHA] This is no time
for shiny dream filters,
you gotta snap out of it!
Are you listening?
That's enough!
We're kind of in a hurry here!
But look, he's
so cute and cuddly!
Aw...!
[MISHA]
I've lost him...
[BOTH]
Huh?
Oh, crap! I think
that ant means business!
[crashing]
I only survived because
I'm naturally agile
and a fast runner, but he's not.
Giant ant... Help...!
No, please stop!
I'm so scared right now...
‐‐[MISHA sighs]
‐‐That's just great.
Guess we can add this
to his list of issues.
[sighs]
[DRADRADOGOLA screeches]
[GROUP gasps]
That's the cry of
the dradradogola!
What? They can cry?
Which way?
[SHIGURE]
Hmm... That direction!
[ANIMAL MASK] I knew there
had to be demon beasts here!
I can't believe you idiots
thought they were plants!
[GIRLS]
Uhh...
[ANIMAL MASK]
Yoink!
[DRADRADOGOLA screeches]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Yoink!
[DRADRADOGOLA screeching]
[ANIMAL MASK shrieks]
Not good! You okay there, chief?
You think the
dradradogola got him?
‐‐Oh, no!
‐‐So Genzo finally croaks, huh?
What kinda loser
gets offed by a plant?
It can't be!
Plus, no one said anything about
the plants being that dangerous!
Genzo!
[HANAKO]
Hey, Genzo!
Don't worry guys,
I can always make his dead
corpse serve us for eternity!
Or not.
[DRADRADOGOLA screeching]
Hey, what happened?
Great. He's still alive.
Gross. They are just
human faced plant things?
[DRADRADOGOLA screeching]
Look, I know this is
kind of disappointing,
but we still have a job to do.
The only thing better
than that stupid look
on your face is if the
screams from these creatures
forced you to soil yourself.
Let's just finish, okay?
Nah, hard pass‐‐ you guys do it.
I'm going home.
[SHIGURE gasps] Just because
they're not animals
doesn't mean you
can't stay and help!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hmph.
[CARMILLA laughs]
Aw, is the man baby scared?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Aw, is the vampire stupid?!
[CARMILLA]
What?! Who ever said I was
the charmingly noble creature
they call a vampire?
[screeches]
Hey, guys, look at this one.
If you squint real hard
it's kinda cute, huh?
Not even close.
Shigure. Have you ever
had your eyes checked?
By a doctor?
Shut up,
I said it's cute, Carmilla!
You see? Adorable, right?
Gross. Nope. It's hideous.
Ah?!
[SHIGURE]
Ah! I mean, it's a little cute!
[ANIMAL MASK] You can't
make me like plant goblins!
They're just creepy!
See ya, I'm out.
[SHIGURE]
Wait! I said we have a job to do
and we're gonna do it
whether you like it or not!
[DRADRADOGOLA whimpers]
Shigure.
I thought you were a person
who truly understood me.
What do you mean?
I don't care about money.
There's only one thing
that motivates me,
and that's my undying
love for animals!
You're such a liar.
Every man on this planet
is motivated by money,
even a perv like you
No! I'm not like other guys!
[BOTH gruting]
Knock it off.
I'm so over your squabbling!
You two need to shut up
and get to work!
[GROUP]
Huh?
[ANIMAL MASK]
The dradradogola stopped crying.
[SHIGURE]
Oh, no.
[CARMILLA]
What happened?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hanako, please don't tell me...
[HANAKO]
Hmm...
[GROUP groans]
[SHIGURE]
Hey, we're back.
Say what?! Some thieves
tried to take Hiroyuki?!
But you fought them off?!
Right! What did those
dirty dog‐nappers look like?
[GROUP gasps]
It's okay, I promise
I'm gonna figure out a way
to get revenge on that guy
so you can rest easy,
but until then,
I need you to stay put.
Okay. Since you promised.
I'll leave him alone.
‐‐[slamming]
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Hey!
[gasping]
Remember me?!
[screaming]
Did you really
think you could take
my sweet Hiroyuki away from me?
[yelling]
[ANIMAL MASK]
I was trying to be nice to you
because you were fluffy.
[screaming]
But now I can see
that I made a stupid mistake.
[screams]
And I'm not gonna make it twice!
[WOLFGANG gasps]
[WOLFGANG groans]
[HIROYUKI barking]
[CITIZENS gasping]
Listen to me, jabroni!
Don't ever touch my dog again!
[CITIZENS gasping]
[gasping]
Play stupid games,
get stupid prizes!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANIMAL MASK growling]
[ANIMAL MASK grunting]
[WOLFGANG yelling]
[screams]
Yeah!
[applause]
[BOTH whimper]
[ANIMAL MASK] It's been
a while since I've wrestled
in front of an audience.
[ANIMAL MASK] The last time
was against MAO, huh?
[MAO]
Get out!
[MAN 5A grunts]
I don't wanna see
your lame faces again!
‐‐[MEN gasping]
‐‐[MAN 5C] MAO!
[DOCTOR 5A] You're suffering
from Animal Mask
withdrawal syndrome.
What?
Listen, man.
You're too obsessed with
a dude in a weird costume.
That's impossible!
Besides, he only
ran away because
he was all scared of losing!
Uh, yeah, like I said,
you're obsessed.
What?
[DOCTOR 5A] Look, if you want
my advice, find a new hobby.
You know, something to distract
you from the animal guy.
[MAO]
Hmm...
[MAO gasps, growls]
Ahh! Stupid knitting!
[MAO growls]
[JOANNA] It is said that
Princess Altena of Edgardo
was able to summon
a hero to this world.
This is a serious threat.
I, the next leader of
the vampires and one
of the Four Dukes of Darkness,
asked the Demon King
for permission‐‐nay, the
honor‐‐of defeating the hero.
I will certainly prevail.
I've gathered you all
here to aid me in my plan
to summon a Demon King
from another world.
Once he's arrived,
the Demon King and I
will join forces to
stop that pervy hero.
O darkness of the dark!
Grant this servant's
plea for your power!
[MAO]
Animal... Mask...
It worked!
[MAO growls]
I'm one of the
four Dukes of Darkness,
a servant of the
mighty Demon King.
The daughter of Wallen
Joannascore Adorian Uljika.
I'm Joanna Joannascore
Adorian Uljika.
Demon King,
who's been summoned here
by the dark gods of darkness.
Will you help us on our noble
quest to defeat the hero?
Huh?
Tell me, what is your name?
I go by MAO.
[JOANNA]
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Demon King from another world.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Next time: "Loser and Master."