[GUILD chatters]
[HIROYUKI sniffs]
[ANIMAL MASK sighs]
There ya have it!
It all comes down to showing
them that you have nothing
but love in your heart!
If you can do that much,
then the demon beasts
will never try to harm you.
Oh, man, my head!
Damn it, I hate those beasts!
They got you good. Are you okay?
Yeah. I swear I'll make
those monsters pay.
[GUILD SOLDIER 1B, 2A]
Death to all demon beasts!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hey. Don't you agree, Shigure?
Well. I don't disagree,
I'm just not sure why
you keep bringing it up.
[ANIMAL MASK]
'Cause it's important!
[GUILD SOLDIER 1C] Damn.
It looks like the eastern guilds
took some pretty
heavy damage, too.
When it comes to monsters, it's
either kill or be killed, huh?
Put love out in the world,
you get love back.
[GUILD SOLDIER 2C]
We've been attacked!
‐‐[GUILD MEMBER 2A] Honey!
‐‐[GUILD GIRL 2A] Daddy!
[BAR PATRON 2A] Father!
Don't worry, we'll kill
those monsters for you!
[sobbing]
[sighs]
Yep, you heard me!
We'll spread the love
for animals everywhere!
[GUILD SOLDIER 2C]
Man, I hate those stupid beasts!
[ANIMAL MASK]
And I've got the perfect plan!
Uh, and what is that?
I've decided I'm going
to open a pet shop.
That sounds great! But...
What's a pet shop?
[ANIMAL MASK]
You don't know?!
[SHIGURE] Letting a demon
beast live in your home?
Is that really possible?
[ANIMAL MASK] Did you space out
for my whole explanation?
I'll raise the monsters
so they can live with humans.
Thus forming a bridge
between humans and beasts.
'Cause that is the one true
purpose of a pet shop!
Uh...
The best part
is it's a great way
to make a living.
Here's my plan.
After we raise the demon beasts,
we'll charge people money
to buy them from us.
Hold on, so we'll be
taking quests from the guild
and accepting payment
for capturing monsters.
Then we'll train the demon
beasts we've captured.
Which we'll then turn around
and sell to our customers
for more money? So, we
basically double our profit!
[ANIMAL MASK chuckles]
Exciting, isn't it?
Drowning in all those animals!
[SHIGURE]
Drowning in all that cash!
I'm in! I'll help you!
Together, we'll totally open up
your weird pet shop
or whatever you call it!
[HIROYUKI yips]
So first up...
We need to find a place to live.
Big enough to keep the
demon beasts there, too.
And that means...
we'll need more money.
[SHIGURE]
Yeah, that's true.
Don't forget the part where
I still have to pay back
what I owe Edgar since
he didn't get to sell me.
Look, I understand
if you don't want to,
but maybe you and I could
form a party, what do you say?
I'd love to!
That's an absolutely
splendid idea!
[laughs]
[SHIGURE] Uh. Hey, now.
My eyes are down here, buddy.
[ANIMAL MASK sighs]
Hmm...
So we can choose
a job from this board?
Yep.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hmm? What's that?
[GUILD SOLDIER 1A]
A book.
It contains everything you need
to know about the demon beasts,
and the best way to defeat them.
But I guess someone like you
wouldn't need it.
Would ya, Beast Killer?
[ANIMAL MASK] I'm sorry,
but what the heck
did you just call me?
Everyone's talkin' about you!
About how you took down those
five Cerberuses all by yourself!
Word on the street
is they're calling you...
...the Beast Killer!
[ANIMAL MASK] Screw that
name and your sparkle!
[gasping]
[GUILD SOLDIER 1A groans]
Jeez. That's the dumbest
wrestling name
I've ever heard.
Plus, mine's awesome.
But this guide does look like
it could be useful. Now.
We just need to book a good
match with a high payout.
What's it say?
Oh. Well, uh...
Maybe we shouldn't rush things.
This is our first quest,
so it might be wise to start
with something simple?
But being smart
won't get us rich quick.
I can't read this language, so
tell me which one pays the most.
I guess this one.
Defeating a Salamander.
Sounds good.
Yeah, don't say
that so casually.
Like I just said, we should
really pick something easier
for our first quest.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Listen to me, Shigure.
Whenever I'm prepping
for a match,
I've always emphasized
the mental aspect of battle.
When you run away,
it becomes a habit.
I've seen it happen
to a ton of wrestlers.
No offense, but I
really have no idea
what you're saying.
[ANIMAL MASK] So, which one
of these is the Salamander?
[SHIGURE] This one. The giant
fire‐breathing lizard of death.
[ANIMAL MASK]
For real?
[sighs]
[SHIGURE]
You heard me say "death," right?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hmm. But it's so cute.
Anyway, I'm definitely
going to have to learn how
to read this language.
[HEAT HAZE]
A salamander, eh?
‐‐[SHIGURE] Huh?
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Hmm?
That's not an easy
beastie to take down.
[HEAT HAZE FOLLOWERS]
Mm‐hmm!
Whoa, it's Heat Haze!
The strongest man
in the whole guild
is talking to the Beast Kil‐‐
Don't call him that, you idiot!
[GUILD SOLDIER 2B, muffled]
Why not? What's gonna happen?
[GUILD SOLDIER 1A groans]
[HEAT HAZE] Let me guess,
you're a new hunter?
Ew, gross. I'm a pro‐wrestler.
I'm not sure what that means,
but how bout we join parties?
And after we defeat
the salamander,
we can split the reward.
You mean it?
That's so generous of you!
[HEAT HAZE] Well, it's to
celebrate your first victory.
Don't you worry,
I'll take down that salamander
with a single blow
from my sword, 'kay?
[ANIMAL MASK]
I won't let you kill animals!
[HEAT HAZE yells]
[GUILD SOLDIER 1A grunting]
‐‐[HEAT HAZE groans]
‐‐Our leader!
Are you okay?
Stop being dramatic.
That's what you get
for saying stupid things.
I don't get it, did Heat
Haze say something stupid?
Who knows?
Hey. Let's go.
Uh... Coming!
Huh?
[SHIGURE]
Ah...
Uh‐oh, somebody left
their sword behind!
Finder's keepers!
[gasping]
Wasn't that Heat Haze's?
I'm not sure,
but I think he just got robbed.
[ANIMAL MASK] Look, Shigure!
What a majestic beast!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Majestic and hot!
Aw, thank you for
the flame kissies!
You're just the sweetest lizard
ever, Yoshiko, oh, yes, you are!
Wait, he gave it a name?
Yoshiko belongs
to me now, so pay up.
Sorry, but... who's Yoshiko?
It's the salamander!
[screams]
[GUILD CLERK 2A] That was
a pretty tough first quest.
I guess the rumors are true.
You're a true Beast Killer!
[ANIMAL MASK] Why does
everyone keep calling me that?!
And now, our
business has funding.
Well, let's get going now.
[SHIGURE]
Huh? Where are we going?
[GUILD CLERK 2A groaning]
[MISHA] Man, I am,
like, way beyond bored.
Come on, what do you
say we go into town
and stir up some trouble?
Huh? Sure.
Ah‐‐
[whimpering
Uh... Actually, I'd rather not.
What?
[MISHA]
Poor guy.
He's probably still traumatized
by that handsy pervert.
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK] Hello!
‐‐[gasps]
[whimpers]
Whoa! What do you want?!
Uh... Sorry.
We're looking for Edgar.
[MISHA]
Tough! He's not here right now!
Oh, but I came to make payment.
[MISHA]
Put it over there!
I promise to make
sure Edgar gets it!
[WOLFGANG whimpering]
[HANAKO humming]
Oh! Look at this!
It looks so yummy!
[knocking]
[MAID 2A] Mistress?
Your dinner is ready to eat.
It's always the same old thing.
Gross orc, goblin,
and troll meat.
[growls]
I'm sick and tired of
all this nasty meat!
I wanna go out
into the wide world!
And stuff my face
with delicious food!
Food!
This quest is soldier monkeys.
The paper said there was
sizable number of them.
Please tell me you have some
sort of plan for this.
You know what?
I bet these monkeys have
the cutest little tushies
in the world!
[SHIGURE] I was asking
if you had a plan,
not what you thought
of their butts.
[HIROYUKI whines]
[sighs] I wonder
how many of them there are?
You think it's a lot?
I really hope so.
Never mind...
I think they're close by.
Ah‐ha!
[SHIGURE gasps]
There's so many!
Yeah, isn't it wonderful?
No, it isn't wonderful.
It's terrifying!
They look like
they wanna kill us!
[ANIMAL MASK]
It'll be fine.
[SHIGURE wails]
Watch this.
Bring it on, monkeys!
Come here!
‐‐[SOLDIER MONKEYS whooping]
‐‐[SHIGURE] Don't come here!
[bellows]
[SOLDIER MONKEYS screamin]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Behold!
An apple.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Apple.
[SOLDIER MONKEYS gibbering]
Uh...
How did you manage to
befriend all of them?
Magic?
Not magic.
I call it... love.
[HIROYUKI yips]
[SHIGURE]
What an interesting talent.
‐‐[SOLDIER MONKEY 2A growls]
‐‐[SOLDIER MONKEY 2B hisses]
[hisses]
Whoa. You've got
quite the collection here.
This doesn't seem normal.
Yeah.
It's more like a dream
come true, am I right?
[sighs]
I'm so happy!
[SHIGURE]
Genzo.
How are you little floofs
so stinkin' adorable?
[SHIGURE]
Genzo! Wake up!
[gasps]
Thank goodness.
You're finally up.
Something wrong, Shigure?
I was having the best dream.
In it, I was surrounded by
amazing, magical creatures.
It was absolutely heaven!
I don't know why,
it's not like your reality
is that much different.
I mean, just look
at all these critters.
If someone finds you
with these demon beasts,
you're gonna be in
a mountain of trouble.
You're right! What if
someone tries to steal them?
[SHIGURE] Uh, that's
not really what I meant.
Well, we can't
keep staying out
in the open like this. I gotta
find these guys a place to live.
[SHIGURE] What about us?
I want shelter, too!
Yeah, sure.
I hate to burst this
dream bubble of yours,
but it's gonna take a lot
of cash to get a house.
[ANIMAL MASK] Sounds like
we'll need a big quest, then.
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK bellows]
‐‐[GUILD gasping]
[ANIMAL MASK] Which of one
of these pays the most?
[SHIGURE] Uh... This one right
here. It's fighting orcs.
Basically, it says they need
someone to go and take care
of the orcs who have been
stealing people's crops.
Orcs, huh?
[SHIGURE]
Take a look.
[ANIMAL MASK]
What?
[groans]
What's wrong?
You kinda have this
weird gloomy vibe to you.
'Cause these are just
people‐looking creatures.
Ah, how sad for you.
But hey, at least they
can understand speech.
Great, so they're
pretty much humans.
I said they're orcs, dummy!
Check it out, some of them even
have long hair and big fangs.
What's up with you?
You have a more
excited vibe than usual.
Of course I do‐‐
this gig pays a ton of money!
If we pull this off, we'll
definitely be able to get
a house for you
and your monsters.
[ANIMAL MASK] What?!
Why didn't you say so sooner?!
Let's do it!
[GUILD SOLDIER 2G]
So now it's orcs?
No way he can handle
this quest on his own.
Well. Agree to disagree.
[CARMILLA]
What?! The mistress is gone?!
[MAID 2A]
Um... Yes, ma'am.
[CARMILLA growls]
I will bring her back,
and if anyone dares to
stand in my way, then...
...I'll kill them.
[thunder cracks]
[SHIGURE] Do you think
we should take a break
at the lake up ahead?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Good idea.
The last thing I wanna do is
spend the whole night walking
and then exhaust myself
before the big fight.
[HIROYUKI whines]
I've never seen
you this serious
about a fight before.
You don't have to worry,
the orcs and demon beasts
are totally in the
same category.
Don't compare them
to my precious babies!
Of course not.
Because we can actually
communicate with the orcs.
I'm not sure how
to explain this in a way
that'll make sense.
There are times when words
can get in the way, y'know?
[SHIGURE]
Huh...?
[SHIGURE sighs]
Honestly. Genzo says
the strangest things,
I just don't know
what he's talking about.
He's such an odd guy.
Still though.
At least he likes beast people
like me, so that's good.
‐‐[leaves rustling]
‐‐[SHIGURE yelps]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Ahh...
[SHIGURE screams]
Genzo, you pervert!
Huh?
Hello there, beautiful.
[giggles]
[HIROYUKI barks]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Mami dearest!
You are simply
gorgeous, yes you are!
[giggles]
‐‐Aren't you, girl? You are!
‐‐Somehow... This ticks me off
‐‐I love you! Yes, I do!
‐‐more than peeping does.
[sniffing
You smell that?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Yeah, up there.
[SHIGURE grunts]
You stay out of this.
I'm gonna go talk to them first.
Hold on. Just because
you can talk to them
doesn't mean
they'll listen to you!
[ORCS chattering]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Okay, let's get ready to rumble!
What the‐‐? Who's that?
You itchin' for a fight, pal?
[ORCS chuckling, mumbling]
Huh? What happened to talking?
All right! Which one of you
jabronis is the strongest?
Show yourself!
[ORC 2C]
Say what?
Somebody after a butt whoop‐‐
[grunts]
[ORC KING] Hmm.
He wasn't speaking to you.
[wham]
[ANIMAL MASK]
Hmph.
[ORC KING] Hello,
I'm the one in charge here.
Do you have something you
would like to say to me, human?
[ANIMAL MASK]
I do!
I heard you're stealing
crops from the villagers!
[ORC KING]
That's true, but what of it?
[ANIMAL MASK grunts]
[ORC KING] To be honest,
I really don't think
it's any of your business.
You know, I was
hoping we could resolve
this conflict peacefully.
[ORC KING grunts]
‐‐[ORCS gasping]
‐‐[SHIGURE] Ah!
[ORC KING groans]
There! Your gong just got rung!
[gasps]
I don't understand
what that means.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
But I do have to admit,
that was a pretty
formidable kick.
My patented animal dropkick.
Don't forget it.
[ORC KING] Again, I don't
know what that means.
Honestly, it really
doesn't matter.
What matters is that you've
managed to piss me off!
Then come at me, bro!
[yells]
[ANIMAL MASK groans]
[SHIGURE whimpers]
[ORC KING gasps]
Yeah! That human
is a beast in a disguise,
he even took a direct
punch from the king!
[ANIMAL MASK]
Nice!
[ORC KING grunts]
[ANIMAL MASK] That was a
good attack from you, too.
I bet you could even star
in like a main event.
[ORC KING gasps]
Who are you?
[ANIMAL MASK]
I am a pro‐wrestler!
[ORC KING grunts, rasps]
‐‐[coughs]
‐‐[gasps]
[whimpers]
[growls]
[ANIMAL MASK yells]
[ORC KING groans]
[ANIMAL MASK grunts]
[yells]
[BOTH yelling, grunting]
[ORCS gasping]
[bellows]
[yells]
[SHIGURE]
Genzo..
[SHIGURE whimpers]
[ANIMAL MASK growls]
[ORC KING yells]
[SHIGURE]
All right!
[ORC KING growls]
[whimpers, gasps]
[yells
‐‐[ANIMAL MASK grunting]
‐‐[SHIGURE] Yeah! Woo‐hoo!
‐‐[ORC KING grunts]
[rasps]
[ORC KING gasps
[SHIGURE]
Take. Him. Down!
‐‐[grunting]
‐‐[VOICE 1A] One. Two. Three!
‐‐[bell rings]
‐‐Oh, yeah!
[CROWD cheering]
[gasping]
[ORC 2A]
You see that?!
The king has made
the pose of submission!
[ORC 2B]
We have a new king!
‐‐[ORCS cheer]
‐‐[CROWD cheering]
[SHIGURE] Seriously? I'm not
sure how this works, but...
Genzo won,
that's all that matters!
[ORC KING] You're truly amazing.
You know that, right?
I'm impressed.
Yeah, it was a good match.
[ORC KING, ANIMAL MASK]
Hmm!
All right, then.
I've decided to leave
the old king in charge.
Everybody do what he says, okay?
[ORCS]
Yeah!
[SHIGURE] Hey, so
whatever happened to you
talking things out?
Oh, that? We discussed
things the manly way.
Doesn't sound like a discussion.
I wonder if Little Mami
is doing okay?
I'm confused. Who's Mami?
[ANIMAL MASK] She's that
precious little unicorn
we saw in the lake.
Ahh! I've been
so worried about her,
I hope she's still there!
Let's hurry, Shigure!
[SHIGURE groans]
All right, I'm coming.
[GUILD MASTER 1A]
What? You made the orcs submit?
I don't believe it.
Do you know how
many talented hunters
have fallen to their wrath?
Please. You must
tell me how you did it.
They talked
it out with their fists!
[GUILD MASTER 1A] You really are
an amazing man, Beast Killer!
[ANIMAL MASK growls
For the last time,
stop calling me that!
[GUILD MASTER 1A whimpering]
[BANKER 2A]
Hmm. Yes, I see. So, then.
Have you already
purchased a store?
Yeah! We sure have.
We were able to buy it
using all the money
we made from the
multiple guild quests.
It has a barn,
fences, everything!
And now you want to procure
a loan to cover the fees
needed by the government
to open your business, yes?
[ANIMAL MASK]
That's right!
In order to qualify for a loan
for the full amount listed,
you'll need to have
a least 20% of the amount
in hand to put up
as a down payment.
How much would that be?
Seriously?!
We don't have even
close to that much cash!
One more thing.
I hope you don't mind
my asking, but...
This pet shop.
What is its purpose, exactly?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Doesn't anybody know?!
[ANIMAL MASK] Next time:
"Runaway Girl and Attack."