It worked!
[MAO]
What is this place?
A few minutes ago,
I was inner‐monologuing
in my bedroom!
[gasps]
[MONSTERS growling, murmuring]
Welcome to my castle.
I am one of the four
Dukes of Darkness,
a servant of the
mighty Demon King.
I also happen to be
the proud daughter
of Wallen Joannascore
Adorian Uljika.
And I go by the name of Joanna
Joannascore Adorian Uljika.
Demon King from another world,
summoned here by
the gods of darkness,
will you help us
to defeat the hero?
Huh?
Tell me your name.
It's MAO.
‐‐[MONSTERS murmuring]
‐‐[MONSTER 6A] You hear that?
[MONSTER 6B]
We actually succeeded in
summoning the Demon King!
You are the Demon King
from another world?
[JOANNA] This is a picture of
the hero that Princess Altena
of Edgardo summoned
not long ago.
No, it can't be!
[ROSE]
He fled the castle shortly after
he was summoned to this world.
[MAO grunts]
Wow, it's him!
This is where that coward
has been hiding all this time?
[JOANNA] We're giving you
the task of defeating him.
[gasps]
[laughs]
You want me to
defeat Animal Mask?
I was made for this.
What are you insinuating?
Do the Demon King
and Hero know each other?
No way. It goes beyond
just knowing the guy.
Our relationship is complicated.
Words could never begin
to describe our rivalry!
[laughs]
That's wonderful news.
Wouldn't you agree?
Indeed.
[MAO coughing]
[ROSE]
What a coincidence.
One could even go so far
as to say it's "destiny."
The Demon King
from another world
already hates the hero.
[JOANNA]
Yes.
Between my own hatred, and the
feelings of the Demon King.
The darkness will grow stronger.
Combine them together
and it's quite powerful.
[ROSE]
Indeed.
I'm done playing around.
This time, I'm going
to crush that girl.
My nemesis...
Fafnir Gildomela
Grind Lindabulea.
[SWORD MASTER 6A grunts]
[JOANNA grunts]
[SWORD MASTER 6A laughs]
Good form, Lady Joanna.
You improve more
and more everyday.
At this rate,
you'll surely be the victor
at the next tournament.
[JOANNA gasps]
[JOANNA yelps]
[ANNOUNCER 6A] Winner: Fafnir
Gildomela Grind Lindabulea.
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[applause]
[HANAKO] Thank you
very much for the match.
[JOANNA]
Wh‐‐ Ah‐‐! Hold on a second!
Yeah?
I request a rematch!
[HANAKO groans] A rematch?
Like right this moment?
Yes!
Nah, I'll pass.
Wha‐‐?! But why?!
Well, I'm just
too hungry to keep fighting.
[HANAKO]
Ahh!
It's so good!
Wow, have you ever noticed how
someone else's food can taste
way better, but it's only
'cause it's different
than what you're used to eating?
Thanks for feeding me!
[JOANNA] I lost to this
insatiable glutton?!
So, ready to fight?
Ah. Yeah.
[JOANNA gasps]
[JOANNA]
No!
One more time...
One more time!
Just one more!
[JOANNA] I'm really getting
tired of looking at that sky.
[JOANNA panting]
I... I don't get it!
[JOANNA] She was the first
person with the capability
to defeat me in combat.
I was flummoxed.
[JOANNA] After my defeat, I
became obsessed with Lindabulea.
I watched her every move to see
if I could find the secret
behind her power,
but my observations
yielded no answers.
I grew increasingly
frustrated that I lost to a girl
whose only ability was having
a bottomless pit for a stomach!
And then, there
was that one time...
Lady Joanna.
[JOANNA grunts]
[CARMILLA] Come on,
we need to hurry up, Mistress!
[ROSE]
Carmilla.
So that's the lesser vampire
who serves the dragons.
I've been told that
all four of the duke's families
are going to be
at this party,
so we need to be on our best
behavior, Mistress! 'Kay?
Meh...
Ooh, and I heard
that they brought in
the nation's finest chefs
to do the catering!
Seriously? You should
have led with that!
[CARMILLA]
My bad.
Hold it!
[CARMILLA, HANAKO]
Huh?
It's been a long
time, Lindabulea.
[CARMILLA, HANAKO]
Uhh...?
You are...?
You forgot her?!
She's Joanna
Joannascore Adorian Uljika!
[HANAKO]
Hmm. Oh...
Are you for real?
You fought her!
Cool story. See ya!
[JOANNA]
Hold on!
What is it now?
I'm kind of in a hurry here.
The finest chefs are all in
charge of the cooking.
If I don't get there quickly,
it's all going to be gone.
Heh! I see you're
as gluttonous as ever.
Oh, you. There's
no need for flattery.
[JOANNA]
That was an insult!
Heh!
[gasps]
Tell me, isn't your
servant a lesser vampire?
[CARMILLA groans]
[JOANNA]
Lindabulea.
As I'm sure you know,
when it comes to vampires,
there are three
different classes.
The great ancestors, the elders,
and below them are the lessers.
Naturally, my own servant,
Rose, is an elder vampire.
Okay, what's your point?
[JOANNA] At her rank,
she shouldn't be able to serve
the family of one of
the four dukes' daughters.
Honestly. I knew you were
strange, but I thought even you
would put more thought into
choosing your servants.
You've got it all wrong‐‐
she never even chose me!
I begged the mistress
to let me serve her!
Silence! A worthless
vampire like you
has no right
to address my lady.
[CARMILLA whimpers]
[JOANNA]
Here's an idea.
If you like, I'd be happy to use
my authority to assign you
a servant better suited
for someone like you.
One more befitting your station.
[JOANNA] Hmph. I heard
rumors about Carmilla.
She's an incompetent moron.
Even an odd girl like
Lindabulea must be sick of her.
[JOANNA]
So, what do you say?
‐‐[HANAKO] Hmm...
‐‐Are you serious?!
You're actually
thinking about it?!
‐‐Can you un‐think about it...
‐‐[JOANNA] This is perfect.
I'll send her an elder
vampire in my control.
Then I can finally
uncover her weakness!
Well, then?
[HANAKO] Thanks for
the offer, but I'll pass.
Excellent. I'll make
the arrangements‐‐
Ah. Wait.
Did you just refuse?
Sure did. Please excuse me.
Hey! I don't think
you understand!
Your servant is as
useless as wallpaper!
‐‐Yeah, no duh!
‐‐Ahh!
Allowing that moron to serve
a noble lady like yourself
is an absolute embarrassment.
But if you truly insist upon
keeping her in your service,
why not have her and Rose
face each other in a match?
If Carmilla somehow
manages to win,
then I'll accept her.
[HANAKO]
Carmilla?
[CARMILLA whimpers]
She says yes!
Did not!
[HANAKO] We can work
out the details later!
Why'd you accept
her proposal, Mistress?!
Because! If we don't hurry,
then all the good food's
gonna be gone!
Ignore your stomach for once!
Rose is an elder vampire!
She'll mop the floor
with my lifeless corpse!
[HANAKO]
Carmilla.
Huh?
If you wanna be my servant,
then you're gonna
have to work hard.
Right. As you wish, milady
[HANAKO]
Now, pick up the pace!
I'm wasting away here!
[CARMILLA]
Yes, ma'am!
This should be interesting.
Yes, this time,
we'll win for sure.
[CARMILLA whimpers]
So, you made it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[JOANNA] Let's clarify
the terms, shall we?
If Rose wins, Carmilla is fired,
and you will replace her
with an elder vampire based
on my recommendation.
[HANAKO]
Understood.
Well.
[CARMILLA whimpers]
[ROSE]
Let's begin!
[CARMILLA gasps]
[CARMILLA grunts]
[ROSE yells]
[CARMILLA yells]
[CARMILLA, ROSE yelling]
[ROSE yells]
[grunts]
‐‐[CARMILLA groaning]
‐‐[slashing
[CARMILLA gasps]
Give up. The match is mine.
[panting]
No, it's not over...
[CARMILLA groans]
[yells]
[CARMILLA grunts, rasping]
It's obvious that
Rose is the winner.
There's just no way
a lesser vampire can defeat
an elder vampire.
Tell her to surrender.
Sparing your pathetic
servant any further shame
is the least you can do.
[CARMILLA groans]
[CARMILLA]
Even if it kills me...
I'll never give up, y'hear?
As long as I serve
my mistress, then I'll fight...!
Ugh. Wow, you really
are pathetic.
Why don't you just admit
that you'll never be able
‐‐to defeat me?
‐‐[CARMILLA] I can't give up...
I can't lose!
Cut it out, you're gonna
pull my skirt down!
Quit it, you weirdo!
[sobbing]
I can't! Not yet!
I just gotta win, for her!
Ugh! Let me go!
‐‐[CARMILLA sobbing]
‐‐[ROSE] Stop it, you freak!
Off! Down, girl, down!
Bad lesser vampire! Bad!
I said let me go! Now!
I request that
we stop the match.
[gasps]
[HANAKO]
Carmilla can't win.
There's no reason
to continue fighting.
Fine. If you insist.
The winner is Rose.
Please. I doubt we could
even call it a fight.
‐‐[CARMILLA groans]
‐‐[gasps]
[ROSE humming]
I failed you... I'm sorry...
[sobbing]
But I don't want
to leave your service!
Please don't make me, Mistress!
Well, that's too bad.
I won the match fair and square.
Please, Mistress!
Don't make me go!
[whimpers]
I'm begging you!
[sobbing]
[JOANNA]
Stop your sniveling.
I'll send your new servant
first thing tomorrow.
I have the most
perfect elder vampire.
Take her, Rose.
[HANAKO]
Hold on a moment.
It's true that Carmilla
is quite literally useless.
But I can't just abandon her.
Ah...?
[HANAKO] And so... I would
like to continue using her.
Say what?
Sorry, but that would
be just ludicrous.
[ROSE]
Yes, it's very unexpected.
[JOANNA chuckles]
If you're going back
on your promise,
then you'll have to do
something for me in exchange.
[HANAKO]
Okay. Like what?
[CARMILLA gasps]
[ROSE, JOANNA gasp]
Mistress, why...?
What are you doing...?
[JOANNA] This is ridiculous.
She'd go this far for a servant?
[laughs]
[JOANNA]
Have I finally won?
[laughs]
We can go now, Rose.
Yes, milady. And the vampire?
You may leave her.
[ROSE]
Right.
[ROSE, JOANNA laughing]
[JOANNA] I can't believe she
bowed in the dirt like that!
[ROSE]
It was quite a sight.
To think I viewed that
pathetic girl as my rival.
Yes, but now, it's very clear
which of you is superior.
[BOTH laugh]
[crows cawing]
‐‐[horse whinnies]
‐‐[BOTH gasp]
What now?
[gasping]
Lindabulea...
I can't help but notice
how lovely the moon is tonight.
[HANAKO] Allow me
to apologize for earlier.
I swear, Carmilla can be such
an embarrassment sometimes.
She fails at
any task you give her.
She's a giant loser.
Like, the worst I've ever seen.
If that's really what you think,
then you should have gotten rid
of her when you had the chance.
Perhaps. But even if
she goes about it
in the wrong way sometimes,
everything that Carmilla does,
whether it's right or not,
is to make me happy.
It's odd, but I feel so
at ease when she's around.
That's why...
...she's precious to me
in a way I can't explain.
What are you saying?
Do you want me
to apologize to her?
To accept her?
Is that why you're out here?
No. She's always been
an incompetent sack of meat,
and I doubt that
will ever change.
Besides, it was a fair fight.
I didn't come here to complain
about her embarrassing loss.
[JOANNA] So, then,
what did you come here to do?
As you may know,
the Fafnirs are the most warlike
of the four houses.
If she loses and I don't
do something about it,
then I'll never hear
the end of it.
That's just the way
my family is.
I get it.
So, you've come here because you
don't want me telling anyone
that Carmilla lost,
is that right?
You'll have to do something
in exchange, of course.
And you've already
humiliated yourself
by kneeling down in the dirt.
So, you'll have to do something
to top that little display.
[HANAKO] No, I won't be
doing anything like that.
[gasps]
Let's say...
...that I'm here for
a moment of your time.
Whoa! What are you doing?
Are you stripping naked to beg?
That is so not necessary!
Yes, please don't strip!
No. I'm only removing my clothes
so that I don't
accidentally rip them.
I am a lady, and I've
always been told
that it's important to stay
in control at all times,
no matter what.
But, it seems
I still have a lot to learn.
[JOANNA, ROSE gasp]
Even a loser like Carmilla
is important to me,
and I'm sure she must
be very upset right now.
That's why...
...as her master...
...it is my duty
to avenge her loss.
[horses whinny]
[HANAKO (monstrous)]
On behalf of Carmilla,
I, Fafnir Gildomela
Grind Lindabulea,
hereby challenge
you both to a duel,
and I sincerely hope
that you'll accept.
[ROSE, JOANNA scream]
[JOANNA] Just thinking about
that night makes my blood boil.
[ROSE]
Yes, I feel the same way.
[JOANNA]
According to my numerous spies,
Lindabulea snuck out
of her castle shortly after
the Hero was summoned
to this world.
She probably intends to
find him before anyone else,
thus stealing the
glory for herself.
And here I thought that glutton
was only interested in food.
She's quite the adversary.
If anyone's going to
defeat the Hero, it'll be me!
I can't allow Lindabulea
to find him first.
Of course.
[JOANNA] I will track her down,
and this time,
I will thoroughly crush
her like the bug she is.
Here, help yourself.
Lady Joanna wanted
me to tell you
you can take anything you like.
But using any of these weapons
would be against the rules.
It's been long enough.
We need to go on
a quest, already.
Not yet.
I'm still recovering from
the wounds I received
on yesterday's dangerous
quest, so until I heal,
I'm not leaving
this impure soil.
But you didn't even
do anything yesterday.
You may shower me with
praise at any time, Genzo.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Why would I?
You didn't do anything
worth praising.
As I recall,
I even tried to stop you.
Don't do it!
Don't worry, Mistress,
I'll get you a nice, big,
tasty snack, okay?
[ANIMAL MASK]
Despite my warnings,
you still got turned
into giant worm chow.
Now stop slacking off.
Time to unbury yourself
and get to work.
‐‐Up and at 'em! Any day now!
‐‐[CARMILLA] Stop it!
‐‐I will end you, mortal!
‐‐Come on, slowpoke.
Outta the dirt. You can do it.
Are you just gonna take this?
[sighs]
Well then, see ya later.
[HANAKO]
Ah...
[snoring]
Please forgive me...
Huh...?
[gasps] Oh! Mistress!
You're finally back.
I was so worried! You're here!
[groans, yells]
I was so afraid that you'd
given up all hope for me
and run back to Lady Joanna
to ask for a new servant!
I was trying to heal
my wounds as quickly
as possible so that I could
come and find you
and beg for your forgiveness!
[sobs]
Where have you been all night?
I was beside myself,
I couldn't sleep!
I've missed you!
[groans]
[CARMILLA]
Owwie...
Goodness. What a useless potato.
[ANIMAL MASK]
Here, let me help you.
If we cover you up,
you'll heal even faster, right?
[CARMILLA] Fine, I'll let
you go just this once!
But only if you stop
burying me, I'm not that dead!
[ANIMAL MASK] Hey, do you
call that stuff impure soil
because it's where Hiryoyuki
makes boom‐booms?
[CARMILLA]
What?!
[ANIMAL MASK] Next time: "First
Student and Pain in the Butt."