Miharu, I, uh...
[thud]
Is Miharu... okay?
She will be.
Her condition has stabilized.
However, it may still
be a little while
before she wakes up.
We understand.
But that's all I can tell
you boys for the moment.
You should go on home now.
[MAMI] So Miharu's
gonna be all right?
[TOWA] Yeah, looks like she's
out of the woods for now.
[MAMI]
Thank goodness.
[TOWA]
I know.
[MAMI]
What about Haruki?
[TOWA chuckles] I think I'd
better keep an eye on him.
[MAMI]
Yes, please do.
I think he'll feel better
if you stick around.
[TOWA]
Thank you.
Talk to you soon.
I told class rep about Miharu.
Oh, good.
Thanks for today.
I owe you one.
Yeah, you got it.
Why don't we get
some sleep, dude?
I'm gonna turn out
the lights now, okay?
[HARUKI]
Sure.
Hey, Towa, are you awake?
I am now.
I told her I like her.
At least, I started to tell her.
What the hell is
wrong with me?
Am I blind?
She was suffering, and I didn't
even realize how badly.
That's why it's my--
Stop that.
Don't overthink it.
Or do. I know you will anyway,
but it's not worth it, man.
[HARUKI]
What's your problem?
[TOWA]
Nothing. Goodnight.
[birds chirp, door opens]
[TOWA grunts]
I can't sleep.
I'm going to the hospital.
Ah, all right.
That's a good idea.
See you later.
Okay.
Are you Haruki?
[chuckles]
Please come in.
[HARUKI]
Uh, thank you.
I hope it's all right.
Looks like she's still asleep.
That's too bad. I'm sorry.
It's okay. Please, sit.
Oh, thank you.
I'd like to say thank you.
You called the ambulance for
my daughter, didn't you?
Yeah. I just wish I'd
thought to do it sooner.
I'm sorry.
Nothing to be sorry for.
The reality is, she was
pushing herself too hard.
[HARUKI]
Hm?
[MIHARU'S MOM] You see, Miharu
was born with a weak heart.
She'd originally planned
to take some time off
before summer,
but things got too busy.
After much deliberation,
her doctor recommended surgery.
We wanted to wait a bit
to see how things went.
[HARUKI]
It was that serious?
[MIHARU'S MOM] I told her that
surgery was her best option
to regain her health,
and the sooner the better.
But she kept insisting
we postpone it.
I've never seen her so adamant
about anything in her life.
Thank you. It was lovely
of all of you to come.
I'll tell her when she wakes up.
[HARUKI sighs]
[STUDENTS talking]
[NOZOMI] You're kidding!
Miharu's in the hospital?
[AKI]
Yeah, I think it's bad.
Do you think it'd be okay
if we visited her sometime?
Not sure. Maybe we
should try to. Let's see.
I know, I'm late. Sorry.
It's fine, no bigs.
And besides, I was
just hangin' with Aki.
Yeah, it's totally fine.
Pudding.
Pudding? Huh.
Oh, right, these pans.
Come on, we'll all
make it together.
Keep your aprons on.
I'll show you how to do it.
[FEMALE CLERK 11A]
Is that everything?
Okay, one hot milk tea,
and three cups of ice cream.
That'll be 712 yen, please.
Knock, knock. It's Haruki.
Miharu, I'm coming in.
[MAMI] We just have barely
enough time to stop by.
Where's Haruki?
[TOWA]
He's already there.
[NASA]
You're visiting Miharu?
Oh, Nasa.
Here.
[MAMI]
Pudding?
For Miharu. I made it.
Could you please give
it to her? Thanks.
Not so fast.
[NASA]
Hm?
How long have you known
about Miharu's heart
and not told us?
Wait, what?
You're not in
the same class,
but you seem familiar
with her situation.
Hey, man, we're worried.
She's our friend.
[NASA]
Mm.
It's not really my place to,
but I guess I can
tell you what I know.
[NASA]
We met at the hospital as kids.
My family and I
were often there,
and she was there
with hers a lot, too.
And she always had
a friend with her.
[MAMI]
Who was this friend?
[NASA]
I never knew her name.
But when we were little,
the three of us played together.
We'd go find some place
away from the grownups.
Heh. It was me, Miharu,
and the other girl.
--Oh, hi.
--[HARUKI gasps]
For you.
Thank you, ma'am.
No, I should be
thanking you again.
Sure.
Um, can I come back tomorrow?
[MIHARU'S MOM]
Of course you can.
Huh. You look
familiar to me.
Did you happen go to
Wakaba Kindergarten?
[HARUKI]
Huh?
I couldn't put my
finger on it yesterday.
I see now,
you look a lot like a boy who
was once friends with Misora.
Misora?
[HARUKI gasps]
[MIHARU]
Mommy, I'm ready now!
No, wait!
I wanna come with you!
[MIHARU'S MOM]
No, sweetheart.
You should stay in bed
and get some rest today.
[MISORA groans]
Merman Prince .
[gasps, giggles]
I love that book.
Me, too!
Are you bringing it to school?
Yeah, I am!
[PRESCHOOL KIDS laughing]
[MIHARU]
Mommy!
[MIHARU giggles]
Misora's over there.
[MISORA]
My mom's here!
[MIHARU giggles]
[MIHARU] Don't run,
you'll trip and fall down!
Okay.
[MISORA and MIHARU giggle]
Hey, wait!
Where's the book at?
I gave it away!
[MISORA giggles]
[MIHARU'S MOM]
Misora! My baby!
[NURSE 11A]
Ma'am, you can't go in there.
[MIHARU'S MOM]
Misora!
[NURSE 11A]
Try to remain calm.
[MIHARU'S MOM]
Misora! [sobs]
[NURSE 11A]
This way, please.
[MIHARU whimpers]
--[door latch clacks]
--Good, you're finally back!
Guess what?
We're having hamburgers!
[HARUKI] Sorry, Let Mom know
I'll be skipping dinner tonight.
[AKIRA]
Huh?
'Kay...
[AKIRA sighs]
[HARUKI] That book, it didn't
belong to me originally.
There was a girl
who read it to me,
and then she let me have it.
And since then,
it's stayed in my mind.
Because of that, she's always
been special to me.
[HARUKI gasps]
Are you possibly...?
[TOWA]
Hey, I'm here.
[HARUKI]
Towa?
Called ya, why didn't
you answer your phone?
[HARUKI] Sorry.
I guess I didn't hear it.
[TOWA]
Whatever, it's fine.
Here you go.
Thanks, man.
So, um, I had a talk
with Nasa today.
The girl who gave
that book to you...
--Yeah, I know.
--Huh?
[HARUKI]
It was Misora, Miharu's sister.
Yeah.
Towa, I get it now.
See, it all makes sense.
All my memories of her are
also the most important ones.
But that's why I've always
thought about Miharu.
If I didn't have those memories,
I would never have had
the guts to talk to her.
We took a walk in the park,
had ice cream, we laughed.
Without experiences like that,
I never would have
known or understood
how it felt, to feel like this.
I like her.
I like Miharu Mashiki.
I've never seen you
be this open before.
When Miharu wakes up,
you'd better tell her.
And don't you dare
hold back now.
Say it all.
--[MIKI] Hello there!
--Hello!
Heh. Where do they
get so much energy?
[CLERK 11A]
Welcome, come in!
[HARUKI]
Coming in.
Haruki Mishima,
new second-year student.
And I really like
swimming a lot.
[MIHARU gasps]
[MIHARU]
Um, Haruki?
[gasps]
Good morning.
Hey, you're awake!
[HARUKI]
Oh, yeah. Are you hungry?
I brought some food,
just in case.
But I didn't know
what you might want,
so I just picked up a
bunch of random things
at the convenience store.
Have you been here
this whole time?
Well, I, uh...
Here's some more snacks.
[gasps]
[MIHARU whimpers]
[HARUKI]
Oh, no. What's wrong?
Should I go and get a doctor?
[MIHARU sobs]
I can't eat all this by myself.
Uh...
Ah!
[HARUKI and MIHARU laugh]
[laughs]
You're okay. I'm so happy.
[MAMI, TOWA]
Can we come in?
[BOTH gasp]
[MAMI giggles]
[TOWA]
Heh!
[NARRATOR] March, the season of
his and her renewed beginning.
"Since you stood
next to me that day,
I've never been
able to forget you.
I'll keep swimming toward you,
so I can stand by your side,
and hear the sound
of your voice.
So I can learn what this
feeling is truly called."
Next time, on
Convenience Store Boyfriends :
Episode twelve: "March."
And this is the place
where their story begins.