Hey, where do you want me
to take this thing, Haruki?
Uh... I think over to the
third-years' head teacher.
You got it, dude.
Right, guys.
When you're finished,
then start on the next project.
Keep me posted.
Okay, Mikado,
I'm all done with this.
Good job, Nozomi. Thank you.
No problem at all.
Just keep the work
coming to me. I love it.
Well, take these, then.
Sure, you bet!
Well you seem
to be having fun.
[NOZOMI]
How could I not?
Now everyone gets a chance
to try Nasa's amazing food.
He's making it?
Hey, Mikado,
you're okay with it, right?
Of course, it'll be
a huge help to us all.
[NOZOMI giggles]
I would do anything
for the cooking society!
Woo!
Wow, what's with her?
High on life.
[STUDENT 4A]
Wow, Towa.
You're in every event.
[TOWA]
You know it.
Attention whore.
[TOWA] Come on!
They asked me to.
What that really makes
me is dependable.
Right, you're an
attention whore.
Hey, wait.
You misunderstand
what I'm trying to--
Hang on, we haven't
chosen anyone
for the three-legged race.
Would any of you
students like to volunteer?
Why don't you do it?
Dude please, no.
You'd have to pay me first.
Listen up, guys are allowed
to run with girls, okay?
[STUDENT 4D]
You serious?
[STUDENT 4B]
That's even more embarrassing.
[STUDENT 4A laughs]
Well, fine.
Then I'm gonna do it.
What? You, Towa?
[TOWA]
Let's see.
Class rep, are you entered
in any events yet?
It looks like a no.
You in?
[HARUKI]
Really?
You two are gonna
do that race together?
[TOWA]
Yep, it kinda just happened.
Maybe it was destiny.
Am I right or what, class rep?
Um, sorry, but--
She doesn't seem very into it.
[TOWA]
What?
What the heck
are you talking about?
That's not true, right?
Are you, or aren't you?
I can't do it.
I'm not even remotely athletic.
Don't worry about that!
Your partner will help.
[TOWA chuckles]
[MAMI]
That's even worse.
[TOWA]
Come again?
It's impossible.
I just know I'm going
to trip and fall down.
It's not fair to a real athlete
to get stuck with
a klutz like me.
Come on, class rep.
[HARUKI] Well, then Towa's
the perfect partner for you!
Huh? What do you mean?
When you're with someone good,
they can help pull you through.
Your time will improve.
Oh, yeah,
I didn't even think of that.
He's got a point.
Whaddya think, Mami?
Oh, I don't know.
[TOWA]
I'll train with you!
[MAMI]
Huh?
You'll train with us
also, Haruki.
[HARUKI]
Me? Why?
[TOWA]
Thanks, buddy.
Wait a second.
Where can we possibly train?
We can't do it at school.
[MIKI]
Then, I can recommend a place.
[HARUKI]
Oh.
He was right.
There's nobody else here.
[MAMI]
What?
You, uh...
You look good
in your track suit.
Please don't say that,
it's so embarrassing.
Aw, but how come?
It's the truth.
Just don't do it!
A three-legged race...
I mean, it's so humiliating.
I'll never get through it.
[HARUKI]
Towa, quit screwing around.
Let's get started.
We're wasting time here.
Yeah, man,
I couldn't agree more.
So what kind of training are
you gonna torture me with?
[TOWA]
Here.
[MAMI]
All of this?!
Wow, that's pretty intense.
I can't. Don't make me.
[TOWA]
Of course you can, silly.
We'll start slowly at
your pace, nice and easy.
Well, worrying about it
won't get you anywhere,
so how 'bout we go
for a run now? C'mon.
No, wait! Stop.
Well, it's only your first day.
Hang on. Miharu?
Hey! [laughs]
Wow, I needed that!
Thanks so much!
[MIHARU] Oh, it was the least
I could to help you guys out
in some way.
Miharu, do you know what
events you're participating in?
None, actually.
I'm not supposed to do
strenuous activities.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I had no idea.
Besides, even though
I can't run with everybody,
I can still cheer you on.
When is our class
practicing tomorrow?
Oh, it'll be during
our study period.
[TOWA]
Prep committee reporting!
[MIHARU]
Thanks, glad you made it.
[MIHARU] Here, do you
mind taking these?
Happy to.
Seems like your club's
been really busy.
[MIHARU giggles]
Nah. You're much busier.
That's definitely not true.
You're working just
as hard as us.
Yes, I guess so.
[MIHARU]
But still...
I wish I could participate
a bit more.
Then you should participate
in any way you can.
I'd love to.
But how?
Well, let me think. Maybe...
What's that pink thing
hanging off your bag?
[MIHARU]
What thing? Oh. This charm?
[TOWA] Yeah, why don't you
make stuff like that?
As a matter of fact,
he would love one.
Wait a minute. I didn't ask...
But just think about it, bro!
You know you want
your own lucky charm.
It'll inspire you!
Well, yeah,
of course I do, but...
I mean, I can't be the only one.
[MIHARU]
Is that true? Really?
For sure!
What I mean is, ya think
other people would want 'em?
I know they would.
Without a doubt!
They're personal motivators!
[MIHARU]
Then I'll make them!
For the whole class,
in time for the festival.
Wait, what?
The entire class will get one?
I don't know, guys.
Do you think she can do it?
It might be too much, though.
We don't want to
wear her out, you know?
I guess.
But she said she wanted to.
You really think
it'll be that strenuous?
In fact, I know so.
To do all that, she must
really want to be involved.
So I should work harder, too.
Awesome, class rep!
Then, should we
train even harder?
Not what I meant.
[TOWA]
What? Why not?
[knocking]
[HARUKI]
Prep committee here.
Here's what we collected.
Thank you.
Wait. Where's the other guy?
Apparently he's
occupied at the moment.
Oh, did you want
to talk to Miharu?
[HANDICRAFT CLUB 4B laughs]
Good luck with that!
She's still crazy busy.
--Bye, thanks a lot.
--Bye, thank you very much.
And thank you.
Yeah, all right.
[TOWA]
Oh, crap. I'm late!
[MAMI]
Uh-huh, training again today.
Yes, I'm aware.
I'll call you when I'm leaving.
Oh, didn't see ya there.
Uh, sorry I'm running
a little bit late.
Wanna start?
Haruki, could you check
on the equipment in storage?
Sure.
Oh, and take
Natsu with you too.
He's off, remember?
[MIKADO]
You're right.
Is there anyone else
here who can help?
It's cool.
I can take care of it.
[MIKADO]
Good man.
I wish we could find you
a new partner, but...
No, really.
I can handle as much
work as you need me to.
[MASAMUNE]
What a go-getter.
As long as I'm
working on this project,
I want it to be successful.
I like your attitude.
Keep it up.
I will.
You're much faster today.
I did some research.
And all of it says
it's very important
to try and match your
partner's breathing.
So I am. Or I'm trying.
All right, then I'll
match your breathing.
So don't overdo it, okay?
Don't burn yourself out, okay?
Let's go!
All right.
[TOWA]
'Kay!
We'll start off slow, and
gradually pick up the pace.
I can't!
[TOWA]
It's how the race works,
so you'll have to get
used to it sooner or later.
[MAMI]
Please, no more.
[TOWA] This is exactly why
we're training this way.
Just run in time with my voice.
[MAMI]
Okay, fine.
[TOWA]
Here we go.
Tied foot goes first.
[TOWA]
Ready, and go.
One, two. One, two. One...
[MAMI gasps]
Got your balance back now?
[TOWA]
I'll wait.
Just take your time.
We can go whenever you're ready.
Do you want to try it again?
You got it this time, and...
One, two. One, two.
One, two. One, two. One...
How is it?
It's wonderful!
You flatter me.
Try this.
[TOWA] Haruki, how's the
preparation going?
[HARUKI]
Like clockwork. I'm all over it.
How are you guys doing?
[TOWA]
Couldn't be better.
We're bound by a common destiny.
Why are you always so dramatic?
You doing more
training after this?
[TOWA]
Hell yeah.
[MIHARU]
Good luck, Mami.
Oh, thanks!
And you too, Miharu.
Shake a leg, class rep.
[BOTH laughing]
Sorry, practice ran kinda late.
Hey!
Will ya just hurry
up and dry your hair?
We're going shopping.
Wait, we are?
Yes, you've earned
yourself a break.
Awesome!
Hello, ladies.
From the student council.
[GIRLS gasp]
[HANDICRAFT CLUB 4C]
Oh, great!
[HANDICRAFT CLUB 4D]
Awesome!
You're so thoughtful.
[MAMI, TOWA]
One, two. One, two. One, two.
[door opens]
[NOZOMI]
Thanks for your patience!
Feast your eyes on this!
Incredible.
Isn't it?
So Nasa prepared this?
Uh-huh! He did. Try some!
It looks good.
[starting gun fires]
Hey, guys.
Have you seen Miharu?
She's not here?
[MIHARU]
Good morning.
Does that bag have the--?
[MIHARU]
Mm-hmm!
[GROUP laughs]
[TOWA]
Yo!
Class three, c'mere!
Yeah, what's up?
[MIHARU]
Uh, I made these.
Oh! Are those charms?
Totally, and she made
all of them by hand.
Wow, cute!
Wait, are these for us?
Mm-hmm.
They are.
Cool, thanks!
We'll go hand them out!
That was great.
Hey, they're gonna
start soon. Let's go.
[MIHARU]
Oh, wait just a minute.
Here.
For you.
[TOWA]
What? For us, too?
Yeah, absolutely!
Aw, Miharu. You're so sweet!
[MIHARU]
Good luck!
[MAMI]
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
[MIKADO]
Attention, everyone.
The 32nd annual Aokisora
High School Sports Festival
is now ready to commence.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[ASUKAI] Nozomi, where
should we take these?
[NOZOMI]
Uh... Over there is fine.
[MIHARU]
Hi, Nasa.
Oh, Miharu, hi!
I see you made lunch.
Yeah, we're almost ready.
Have fun today.
[NASA]
Thanks, you do the same!
How are you feeling?
Are you okay?
[MIHARU]
Yeah, I'm fine.
I have an idea!
You wanna help us out
for a little while?
Me?
[NOZOMI]
Welcome, everyone!
Who wants a delicious
gourmet lunch?
I'll take two.
Here you go.
Thanks, enjoy!
Come and get 'em, everyone!
They're going fast!
[MIKADO] The afternoon events
are starting soon.
[MASAMUNE]
This food is amazing.
[MIKADO] You'll be so full.
Good luck trying to run.
[MASAMUNE]
Done. Time to head over.
[STUDENT 4E] The grade-based
relay is starting.
[STUDENT 4F] Yeah, the student
council president
versus Masamune.
[MAMI]
I'm so nervous.
You're gonna do really great.
You trained super hard.
Just have a little faith.
Do you mean in you?
No, I mean, in yourself, 'kay?
[TOWA] And look,
Miharu's cheering you on.
[MAMI]
You're right, I'm ready.
All right, Towa!
Get 'em, bud!
Go, Mami!
[STUDENT RACE OFFICIAL 4A]
On your marks! Get set!
[starting pistol fires]
[STUDENTS cheering]
--[starting pistol fires]
--[STUDENTS cheering]
[CLASS 3 4C]
Class rep!
Way to go, you were awesome!
Nicely done, class rep!
[CLASS 3 4E]
Class rep, you're my hero!
Thank you so much.
Ha, I told ya!
You rocked it! See?
[chuckles]
I'm glad we did this.
[STUDENT 4G]
Bye, you guys.
[STUDENT 4B]
Bye!
[GIRLS giggle]
Hey, you two! [laughs]
Hi, Miharu.
Go on, take a break, Haruki.
I got this, okay?
[MIHARU]
Sorry about that.
I know you still had
more to clean up.
[HARUKI] No big deal,
we were almost finished.
Besides, Towa said he'd
handle the rest of it anyway.
[MIHARU]
Well, good.
Hey, uh, thanks again
for the charm. It's cool.
I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
[HARUKI]
Huh?
Well...
For most of my life,
I've barely been involved
in any sports festivals.
I figured it was a lost cause,
and sort of gave up on it.
But you helped create
a unique opportunity
for me to join in,
so for the first time in years,
I finally got to participate.
Happy I could help.
Rain out of nowhere?
[HARUKI]
Come on, this way.
[HARUKI] We might be
stuck here for a while.
Is something wrong?
Nothing. I'll be fine.
[HARUKI]
Put this on.
Oh, thank you.
[NARRATOR] August,
when the sun is scorching hot,
and the air is heavy.
Her straw hat rippled by the
wind raises his temperature.
The chirping of cicadas
excites her uncertain heart.
On nights when giant
flowers blossom,
their hearts cross paths,
and the friction raises their
temperatures even higher.
Next time on Convenience Store
Boyfriends episode five:
"August."
And this is the place
where their story begins.