[TOWA]
You looking at that again?
Yeah, I guess.
Man, that was a fun
New Year's Day.
[TOWA]
Check this out!
Awesome, am I right?
I'll hang onto this picture for
the rest of my life, for real.
You said that
like a million times.
[TOWA] Well, you two should've
taken one together.
Whatever, it's fine.
You're such a candy ass.
I wouldn't want to
bother her with it.
What? I thought you two
were doing just fine.
[HARUKI] She was just being
nice, it doesn't mean anything.
[TOWA]
Just being nice?
[chuckles] Seriously, bro?
I think it means something.
Oh, yeah? Like what?
I mean, the two of you
guys just need to like--
[phone buzzes]
Oh.
It's the class rep.
'Kay, I'm outta here.
See you at school tomorrow.
I take it everything's okay?
Yeah, man.
[door closes]
[TOWA] Oh! It's so
frickin' cold out here!
Man, I hate winter so much.
I wish spring would hurry up!
[HARUKI] Looks like things are
already warming up for you.
Hey, do you have practice now?
Hey, class rep!
Yeah, but I think
I'm gonna bail on it.
I can't deal with
going outside again!
Pull yourself together.
But it's so chilly.
I'll freeze to death!
You're unbelievable.
What am I gonna
do with you, huh?
[TOWA]
What? I can have it?
Yes, you can. I have two.
Oh, wow! Awesome! Thank you!
Work hard, okay?
How can I not when you
gave me this gift?
Idiot. Put it away. Stop.
[HARUKI]
Well, I better get goin'.
Kick ass at practice, bro!
[HARUKI chuckles]
[SWIM TEAM CAPTAIN]
You guys workin' hard?
[SWIM TEAM DUDES]
Yeah!
[SWIM TEAM DUDE 10A]
Wait, captain,
don't you have entrance exams?
I gotta light a fire
under your asses.
You have a big meet coming up.
Good luck, Mishima.
[HARUKI]
Uh...
I've got my eye on you.
Thanks, captain.
What about us?
What about you?
Just ask your girlfriend
to wish ya luck.
Wha...? How'd you know that?
I didn't even know!
A girlfriend, seriously?
No, just a friend.
But if...
If your crush wishes you luck,
wouldn't that motivate you more?
[MIHARU]
Good luck.
[MIHARU chuckles]
[HARUKI chuckles]
I think I'm heading out soon.
What about you?
[MAMI] I'm going to stay
a little while longer.
Uh?
You meeting him later?
[MAMI]
Yeah.
You are so lucky.
[MAMI]
I wouldn't say that.
He whines if I
leave without him.
Oh, I heard Haruki has
a swim meet coming up soon.
Uh? He does, really?
[MAMI]
He didn't tell you?
Uh-uh.
That's out of character.
I would've assumed you'd be
the first person he told.
Unreal. I can't believe it.
And after you gave him
that beautiful scarf
for Christmas, too.
[MIHARU]
No, wait.
Wow, he doesn't get it. Boys
can be so stupid sometimes--
[KOKONO]
Shhhh.
--Sorry, we'll stop talking.
--Sorry, we'll be quiet now.
[door chimes]
[MIKI]
Welcome, come in.
Look, they're here
again today. So cute.
Please don't gawk at
the customers. It's creepy.
Can't help it.
You've been practicing
a lot lately.
I have a big
meet coming up.
I know. Mami told me.
She did? Really?
I'm still not sure if I'm gonna
get to be a starter yet, though.
Good luck either way.
Okay.
Thank you.
[SWIM TEAM DUDE 10B]
My times should be better.
I don't know what
I'm doing wrong.
[whistle blows]
Maybe it's my form.
I could try a wider
stroke, maybe?
What's wrong?
Not sure.
I'm feeling off today.
Off how?
[HARUKI]
I can't explain it. Just off.
[whistle blows]
Yeah. Yeah.
Be right there.
I got it.
[HARUKI]
Miharu! You leaving now?
Hi.
Yeah. Are you done
with practice already?
[HARUKI sighs]
I guess.
Wait, is something wrong?
Sorta. It's nothing
serious, though.
But, I--
[phone buzzes]
One sec.
What'd you need?
[HARUKI] It's fine.
Sorry to have bugged you.
[MIHARU] You didn't.
I'll see you later.
[phone continues buzzing]
[TOWA]
Oh, loverboy!
I see what's going on here.
Dude knock it off already,
you're so annoying.
Relax, take it easy.
I can just tell you're starting
to have real feelings.
What do you mean?
[TOWA]
Dude...
It's kinda bizarre that I even
have to point this out to you.
Hang on a sec.
There's a lot of pressure on
you to win the meet, right?
Did you tell her about it?
What? No.
This is your big chance
to show off for her.
Is there a chance?
Yes, dumbass!
Who wouldn't want their
crush to cheer them on?
Shut up.
How would I even--?
[TOWA]
Just call her, would ya?
Mom, I'm home!
Guess it's dinner
for one again.
Aw, man.
You've gotta be kidding me.
[gasps]
[inaudible]
[clears throat]
Oh, uh, excuse me.
[HARUKI]
She's not here?
You mean you haven't
heard anything?
I told you to give
her a call, didn't I?
Well, yeah, but I just...
Apparently, she just
has a little cold.
Oh, I see.
Why don't you just call her?
That's okay.
I'll just see her tomorrow.
Prob'ly.
[TOWA]
Wow. Five days?
Yeah, I can't believe
she's that sick.
I'm really worried.
Me, too.
Then, Haruki, why don't you--?
No, wait I...
I think I should call her.
Maybe it's better if
she hears from me first.
Right, good idea.
Tell her Haruki's worried about
her and wants her to call him.
That way you can't keep
skipping out on it.
I-I, uh, okay.
Regardless, I'll let her
know you asked about her.
After all, it's
the truth, isn't it?
Yeah, thanks.
[HARUKI sighs]
[phone buzzes]
Uh, hey Mom?
[TOWA'S MOM]
Hm?
Do you have a patient,
last name, Mashiki,
first name Miharu?
You know that's confidential.
Oh, right. I forgot.
Stew's awesome, by the way.
She a friend?
[TOWA]
It's been a week, now.
I was thinking I'd try to
visit her at home maybe.
She told me she was fine,
but I'm still pretty worried.
Hey. You all right?
Class rep, listen.
[MAMI] Wait, you saw
Miharu at the hospital?
Do you think I should
tell Haruki about it?
Maybe, but we don't
know if there's anything
seriously wrong with her, right?
Well, no, we don't, but still.
[MIHARU gasps]
Oh, hello there.
Are you meeting someone?
[HARUKI]
Huh? Uh, no, I'm not.
Hi. How can I help you?
[sighs]
[knocking]
Food?
[HARUKI]
I feel really strange lately.
It's as if I'm not
even myself anymore.
I don't know exactly
how to describe it,
but when I'm swimming,
I can't seem to focus at all.
Hell, I almost can't even feel
the water, y'know what I mean?
Maybe you're just in a slump.
Crap, I don't know.
[TOWA]
That's happened to me before.
I was too distracted by
other things to focus.
Yeah, so you get it.
Please don't make fun of me
when I tell you this, okay?
[TOWA]
Not even a little bit?
[HARUKI] It's Miharu.
I'm worried about her.
[TOWA]
We all are, bro.
[HARUKI]
Yeah.
I know, but, it's not just that
she's sick; there's more to it.
Since before she
started missing class.
Maybe forever ago.
I'm not sure what
the thing is exactly.
Miharu herself hasn't
changed at all.
But there's still something
that's different about her.
I'm not making any sense.
It just sounds weird
when I say it, man.
[sighs]
What's wrong with me?
I'll tell you.
You're invested now.
What do you mean?
[TOWA] If Miharu had
given me that scarf,
then it would just be a scarf.
But, if it was from the class
rep, it'd be priceless.
It's the same way
this is for me.
In fact, I'll prob'ly
keep it forever.
It's just the way it goes.
I know.
But, see, this is different.
Miharu doesn't--
Is that what she
actually told you?
Uh...
[TOWA] Then it's possible she
feels the same way you do, man.
And since you're too damn
chicken to say anything at all,
I bet Miharu just thinks that
you only see her as a friend.
What?! That's not true.
You know I like her.
[TOWA]
Hold up. Stop it.
Why are you whining
to me about it?
[gasps]
[TOWA] Maybe its finally time
for you to make things clear.
Or it could all end
before you're able
to tell her the truth.
[HARUKI]
Yeah.
Your test results should
be ready next week.
Can I go back to school again?
Of course you can.
Hey!
As long as we're out, is there
somewhere you'd like to go?
[MIHARU chuckles]
[MIHARU]
Haruki!
Huh?
I had a hunch that
I'd find you here.
Are you finally feeling better?
[MIHARU] Yeah, sorry
I made you guys worry.
That's all right.
It's so nice to be
back at this place.
I just feel so
comfortable in here.
[HARUKI]
In the convenience store?
[MIHARU]
Mm-hm.
This may sound a little silly,
but I daydream about
it all the time.
You daydream?
Yeah.
[MIHARU] I know it's only your
basic, average store.
It's not like there's anything
special about it.
But I just imagine so many
interesting stories
happeing in that place.
[MIHARU] That's what I
like to think, anyway.
[MIHARU]
But, you see,
it makes everything seem
so bright and happy.
Like the whole world is a gift
and nothing could ever
go wrong, you know?
Is that why you love books?
Uh-huh!
And it's also the reason
that convenience store is
such a special place for me.
[MIHARU]
I wonder whether this is what
standing next to the person
you truly love feels like.
[MIHARU] I can only see him
at the convenience store.
Nobody knows about my
very own secret boyfriend.
My convenience store boyfriend.
For a little while,
I let myself daydream.
I guess that's all it
was meant to be, but...
...then I thought, maybe
I'm being punished for this.
Punished for choosing
you to be my boyfriend,
but...
[MIHARU]
I was so surprised.
Normally my daydreams
end as just that. Daydreams.
But, sometimes they turn
into something else.
Way back then, I was
totally nervous and shy.
Then you showed up.
And, you jumped straight
out of my daydream.
It's like...
It's like you're my...
...my actual boyfriend.
[MIHARU]
That's weird, right?
No, not weird at all.
[MIHARU sneezes]
Should we wander back now?
Miharu, wait!
[MIHARU]
Hm?
Can we stay a bit longer?
Do you mind?
That okay?
[MIHARU]
Mm-hm.
Hey, listen.
I, uh...
Actually...
Look there!
This place is so
incredible, isn't it?
Right here.
Yeah.
[HARUKI]
Um, Miharu?
[MIHARU]
Yeah?
--So, I--
--[MIHARU] Wait.
Please, wait.
I have to say it.
[HARUKI] So, not being able to
see you for those few days
was actually really hard for me.
Without even trying,
I think about you.
You just come to mind.
Always you.
I didn't know why.
I couldn't figure it out,
so I kept going over it--
again, and again.
And then I answered
my own question.
[MIHARU grunts]
I understood it.
Miharu, I uh...
Miharu?
Miharu!
[NARRATOR] February, when
winter hints at its departure.
The warmth of that
fateful day they shared.
The clouds in the sky.
The red sunset.
Her hair in the wind.
The picture book held
carefully in both hands.
Those fragments of memory of
that innocent young girl
have now become distant.
Too far away to reach.
Next time, on Convenience
Store Boy Friends.
Episode eleven: "February."
And this is the place
where their story begins.