[MAMI] Towa, how did you
know about this place?
You've been wanting
to try it, haven't you?
[TOWA]
Hey!
Class rep, you like
this kinda stuff?
Oh, you remember that?
[TOWA]
Yeah.
That's why we're here now.
So, let's eat!
Thank you!
Please come again soon!
[TOWA]
Did you like it?
[MAMI]
Yes.
[TOWA]
I rule at dates!
But it would have been
nice if you had shared
a little bit of
your cake with me.
You wouldn't even let
me have, like, one bite.
Well, no. Of course not.
But why couldn't I?
[MAMI]
What do you mean?
Because you just can't.
Aw, you're no fun.
I was really hoping to
try some of your cake.
You always say weird
things like that.
[TOWA laughs]
[MAMI laughs]
[phone vibrates]
[MAMI]
My curfew.
Sorry, I gotta go.
Is this enough?
[TOWA]
Huh? Hang on.
[MAMI]
Bye.
[TOWA] Wait a sec!
I'll walk you home.
[MAMI]
It's fine.
I'll see you later.
Thank you. This was nice.
[MAMI] I'm sorry,
things ran a little bit late.
Yes, I know.
I'm on my way home now.
[phone vibrates]
[HARUKI]
You had cake?
[TOWA]
Yeah, and it was awesome.
Check it out.
How manly of you.
Oh, whatever.
I just wish we could have spent
some more time together, though.
Yeah, that's nice.
Thanks for all the support.
I'm telling you, I wanna
be with her all the time.
She even answers my texts
really fast lately.
What a breakthrough.
[TOWA]
Jealous, bro?
[HARUKI]
Bite me.
[MIHARU]
You had cake?
[MAMI]
Mm-hmm.
Well that sounds
like a lovely date.
Really, you think so?
[MIHARU]
Definitely.
[MAMI]
Yeah, it was.
[TOWA] Class rep, do you
have time for tea later?
Maybe?
I need to go
to the bookstore.
Then I'll walk you there.
[MAMI]
I'd like that.
[horn blares]
[MAMI]
Actually, I have to go, sorry!
[TOWA]
Morning, class rep.
Yeah, good morning.
[TOWA]
Hey, uh...
[MAMI]
I'm sorry.
[TOWA]
It's okay.
So, uh...
It was my brother.
He passed by and saw us.
Hang on. Did he
give you a hard time?
No, he didn't.
Don't worry, it wasn't
anything that serious.
But...
[TOWA] She says we can't walk
home together for a while.
[HARUKI]
No wonder they're worried.
She's hanging out with you.
Mami's family?
They run a big florist.
Everybody knows them.
[TOWA]
Oh, really?
I had no idea.
[MIHARU] Not only that, her
father's a big-time lawyer.
And her brother's
studying to be one, too.
[HARUKI, TOWA]
Lawyers?
Yeah, so they're pretty strict.
Her family only lets her
stay out past curfew
if it's for school-related
events or activities.
[HARUKI]
That sounds rough.
[MIHARU]
Yeah.
[TOWA]
Now I get it.
[HARUKI] Mami does seem
pretty formal sometimes.
[TOWA]
That's true.
I'm fine with that,
but as for the family thing...
I didn't know.
Man, I'm so lame.
Damn it.
Oh, hi, Mami!
I didn't think you
were coming today.
[MAMI] I'm going to be taking
more classes for a while.
[FRIEND 8A] You study
more than anyone I know!
Towa?
Hey, do you have
a minute to talk?
[MAMI]
Uh... No. I can't.
Someone's coming to get me.
[MAMI]
Towa, my hand!
[TOWA]
Sorry.
[MAMI]
You surprised me.
I'm sorry about everything,
class rep.
Don't be.
I had no idea you'd
been pushing yourself so hard
this entire time.
It's my fault for not
telling you about it sooner.
[TOWA] Is there anything
I can do to help?
That's so nice,
but I have to get
through this myself.
I've thought about it.
If by doing this
I can get my grades up,
my family might be less strict.
And then I might
actually get to have
a social life again.
Wow, class rep.
So then, this means
from now on,
you're even busier.
Yeah.
Okay, then.
Well, good luck.
[MAMI]
You mean that?
Yeah, if that's your
decision, okay.
I understand.
Just, will ya take it easy?
Remember, you still have a life.
[MAMI]
Thank you, Towa.
[TOWA]
Hey. I'm home.
Just in time.
I was worried I'd miss you.
But why?
You know you can
always email me.
I thought it'd be
better to talk in person.
[HARUKI]
What are you doing here?
[TOWA chuckles]
Came to tuck you in, bro.
[HARUKI]
You're such a cheeseball.
Did you eat yet?
[TOWA]
Yeah, I'm good.
Hey! Akira, you up?
[AKIRA]
Towa, the monster's coming!
Help!
[TOWA]
I got your back, kid.
I'll use my miracle
bomber on it.
[game music]
All right, Towa!
We killed it!
Hell yeah! Go me! Rock on!
Okay, let's do
the next quest now!
[HARUKI]
Soccer practice this early?
[TOWA]
It's voluntary.
I can't see the class rep, and
I don't feel like going home.
So, might as well do some laps.
[HARUKI]
Ah, so that's how it is.
Hey, man.
It's a big deal to me.
It's getting so nippy out there.
Maybe I should order
some extra steamed buns.
Nasa, how much longer, y'think?
[NASA] I'm pretty sure
we're almost there.
[TOWA]
Thanks, excuse me.
[MAMI]
Sorry, Towa!
I should've helped
you with those.
That's all right, I can manage.
Yeah, but you...
No, really.
At least let me do this.
Okay, thank you, then.
Really?
Towa delivered them
to the office?
[MAMI]
Uh-huh.
I'm so happy he remembered.
I've been completely swamped
with all this extra work lately.
He picked up the slack for you.
Like you traded places.
Sort of.
Hey, what do you mean by that?
[MIHARU] I mean,
I can't believe you forgot
your class rep duties.
You've been pushing
yourself too hard, Mami.
[TOWA sighs]
What are you doing?
I don't wanna go home, man.
Oh, no. Again?
[TOWA]
Shut up, dude.
I'm, like,
deeply troubled, okay?
[HARUKI]
That bad, huh?
Wanna come over?
Cool! Can I?
Come on,
before I change my mind.
[TOWA laughs]
Aw, you're the best, bro!
Thank you! [laughs]
[HARUKI]
Cut it out!
[AKI]
Uh, 'scuse me.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Hey, Nozomi! I found them!
[NOZOMI gasps]
You did?
So awesome!
Uh, hey.
What's that you're wearing?
[NOZOMI laughs]
Are you guys free now?
I could use your help
with something.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Nicely done, Nozomi.
And I have you
to thank, as well.
Miharu's here?
[NOZOMI]
All right!
Let's start collecting
ginkgo nuts!
[HARUKI]
Are you kidding?
[TOWA] Ugh! How can you
stand doing this all day?
[NOZOMI]
Are you kidding?
We're the cooking society!
We live for stuff like this!
Nasa, look how many we found!
Wow, Nozomi! That's great.
Oh, my gosh!
Now we can make
some chawanmushi !
[NASA]
Good idea.
Hey, I could go for
some chawanmushi , too.
Oh, so now you're
all about this?
Chawanmushi
is super delicious.
Oh, I see one over there.
[HARUKI]
Where?
[MIHARU]
Right by the leaves.
You see it?
Oh, yeah! Good eye!
Okay, Haruki,
get in position, quickly.
[HARUKI]
Gotcha.
[HARUKI laughs]
[phone camera clicks]
[HARUKI]
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
Just noticing how
beautiful the leaves are.
I thought I'd take a few
pictures for the class rep.
You're not gonna send it?
Nah, I'll do it later.
I mean, she could be studying.
I don't want to bother her.
Right, good point.
Aw, Towa.
[TOWA sighs]
Oh, man. I really wish
she could be here.
[TOWA] Ugh, I reek
from gingko nut hunting.
[HARUKI] We'll clean up
when we get home.
[TOWA]
That was kinda fun.
[HARUKI]
Yeah.
[TOWA]
I still want chawanmushi !
[HARUKI]
You're gonna have to wait, bro.
[phone vibrates]
What's the matter?
[TOWA]
Sorry, Haruki.
I gotta go home.
[TOWA'S MOM]
Welcome back.
Oh, honey.
You're wearing your track suit?
[TOWA] I thought you were
gonna be working tonight.
Oh, I was able to
get my shift changed.
Now we'll have
more time to talk.
All right.
Then I'm go gonna take
a shower real quick.
[TOWA]
I understand how you feel.
I guess I'm just being
a little selfish.
Actually, your stepdad
is the one
who said it would be
better to live here
until you graduated.
You aren't selfish.
[TOWA]
Fine.
Then why are we
talking about this now?
Well, you know how
busy I've been lately.
So we just haven't seen
much of each other.
But next year, well,
we'll have to begin
discussing your future,
starting with entrance exams.
Your stepdad thought he'd
be able to help us with that.
And then, he also
said that he cou--
Blah, blah, "stepdad."
Do you always do everything
he tells you to do?!
I'm sorry, Mom.
That was wrong.
I shouldn't have said that.
It's freezing.
[MAMI]
Towa, wait!
Good morning.
Yeah, good morning, class rep.
Hey, um, yesterday--
[BOY STUDENT 8A]
Towa, you got a sec?
Hang on. I'll be right there.
I gotta go.
[MALE TEACHER 8A]
Hi, Mami.
Towa took the notebooks
to the office.
Oh, I see. Thank you.
[BOY STUDENT 8B]
Stand. Bow.
--[STUDENTS] Goodbye.
--[TEACHER 8A] Goodbye, class.
[BOY STUDENT 8C]
Hey, Towa,
how far did you get
in Wild Monster ?
I got up to the
dungeon in Area Ten.
[BOY STUDENT 8C] Aw, seriously?
How'd you do it?
I'm still stuck in the area
right before that one.
[TOWA]
Look it up, dude.
There's a strategy guide.
[BOY STUDENT 8C]
Yeah, I did that already.
It's not helping me at all.
[MAMI]
Um, Towa?
You're never up here this late.
What's up?
[MAMI]
I wanted to talk to you.
Did... Did something
happen yesterday?
[TOWA]
Yeah. It's fine, though.
I'm over it.
[MAMI]
But...
I swear, I'm sorry, I'm just
really busy right now.
You can't help it.
It's sorta like you're
working hard enough
for the both of us, right?
And your family's worried
because they think
I'm not good enough for you.
[MAMI]
Wait, but you're...
[TOWA]
It's fine, really.
And I mean like, you're
still willing to hang out
with me in spite of all that.
How noble of you.
Sorry I'm unreliable.
I promised that I'd
be supportive of you,
but now I'm just sulking.
I guess I'm just not as
rational of a person as you are.
Towa, wait, please listen...
[phone vibrates]
How long do you
expect me to wait?
Am I ever gonna be
first priority for you?
I don't know, Towa.
When are you
gonna live for yourself,
and not just for your parents?!
[MAMI]
All right, I see.
I guess maybe we
can't work things out.
[NARRATOR]
December, the season of couples.
Christmas songs
sweeten the chilly air.
Twinkling lights
reflect in their eyes.
His and her feelings,
slowly begin to thaw
their frozen hearts.
They pray for them to melt.
They hurt, and are hurt,
but they still want to see
each other no matter what.
Next time, on Convenience Store
Boyfriends , episode nine:
"December."
And this is the place
where their story begins.