[MIKI]
Huh? Halloween stuff!
Do you wanna dress up together?
Stop talking crazy.
Here, put this up.
[MIKI]
All right, Christmas!
Well, in that case--
[SAKAMOTO]
No.
[MIKI]
Okay, okay.
[TEACHER 8A]
Hashimoto.
[HASHIMOTO]
Here.
[TEACHER 8A]
Hirabayashi.
[HIRABAYASHI]
Here.
[TEACHER 8A]
Fujimoto.
[FUJIMOTO]
Here.
[TEACHER 8A]
Honda.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[sighs] Honda!
Uh! Oh, uh, here!
[STUDENTS laughing]
[BOY STUDENT 9C]
You all right, dude?
[gasps]
[sighs]
[MIHARU]
Here.
Thank you!
Glad this is warm.
[HARUKI]
Right? It's cold out.
Yeah.
[MIHARU] Are things not working
out between Mami and Towa?
They both seem so unhappy.
[HARUKI]
Who knows?
It looked like it was going
great before, but now...
I'd hate to see them
just drift apart.
After all this time.
Yeah, I really hope they
can patch everything up.
[MIHARU]
Is there anything we can do?
[HARUKI]
Whaddya mean?
I mean, to help Mami and Towa.
But what can we do?
Let me think...
Uh?
[laughs]
[door creaks]
[ANNOUNCER 9A] Twenty
minutes into the second half,
they've managed to
tie up the score.
He's dribbling down the pitch,
looking for an
opening somewhere.
But the defense is tight, and
now he's trapped at centerfield.
[sighs]
[phone vibrates]
[ANNOUNCER 9A] Neither team
wants to go to penalty kicks
after regulation
and stoppage time.
[sighs]
[TOWA]
Yeah? What do you want?
[HARUKI]
Hey, you got a second?
[TOWA]
I guess.
[HARUKI]
I, uh, well, actually...
[TOWA]
Spit it out.
[HARUKI]
Uh, are you free on the 24th?
The night of the
closing ceremony?
[TOWA] Christmas Eve?
Are you desperate dude?
Why're you asking
me out on a date?
[HARUKI] I'm not, you idiot.
It was Miharu's idea.
[TOWA] So you're asking me to go
on a date with you and Miharu?
That's even weirder, bro.
[HARUKI]
Don't be so dense.
No, we thought we'd
throw a little party.
[TOWA]
A Christmas party. Great.
[HARUKI] She said she
wanted you to come, too.
[TOWA sighs]
[TOWA] You invited the
class rep, didn't you?
[HARUKI]
What?
[TOWA chuckles]
I get it now.
[HARUKI]
Come on, Towa!
[TOWA]
She won't show up.
[HARUKI]
What?
[TOWA] I think she's been
avoiding me at school lately.
I haven't been able
to talk to her.
[TOWA] Plus, her family's got
her on a short leash.
[HARUKI] Anyway, Miharu said
she'd try to invite her, but--
You there?
Sorry, I already have
other plans that night.
[HARUKI]
What, really?
Yeah, really. I got some
family stuff to deal with.
[HARUKI]
Oh.
I guess that'll make it tough.
You can't even come
for a little while?
[TOWA laughs]
You all right?
[TOWA]
Dude, I'm scared.
Huh?
About the class rep.
I'm scared to talk to her.
[HARUKI]
Why?
[gasps]
Never mind. It's nothing.
I'll try to head over there
once I'm done with dinner.
Oh, okay!
[TOWA] I have no idea
when that'll be, though.
Wait! What now?!
[TOWA]
Later.
Hey! Damn him!
[TOWA]
Of course I'm scared.
It might be over between us.
All done!
[MIKI]
Great, I'll take care of it.
[phone chimes]
Uh?
As you all know, winter
break begins tomorrow.
Although you'll be enjoying the
Christmas and New Years holidays
while you're on vacation,
I want you to bear in mind
exam students in
particular should
still take care of themselves,
and study harder than
ever as they enter
the final sprint towards the
end of the school year.
[doorbell rings]
[footsteps]
Hi, Haruki!
Good evening, Miharu.
Hi. Come in.
[HARUKI]
Uh, here.
Oh, wow. Thank you so much!
[laughs]
[MIHARU'S MOM]
Hello, welcome.
[HARUKI]
Thanks for having me.
Please, make yourself at home.
[HARUKI]
Uh. Okay.
Goodbye, sweetheart.
Bye, Mom. I'll see
you guys later.
[MIHARU] My parents are
going out for the night.
[HARUKI]
Oh, really?
[MIHARU]
Yeah.
I've never had my friends
over for a party before,
so I think they were just
trying to be considerate.
It's nice to see you.
[HARUKI]
Mami! You made it.
I couldn't tell my parents
until the last second. Sorry.
It's okay. I'm really
glad you're here.
You said you have about another
hour to hang out, right?
Only an hour?
[MAMI]
Yeah. I have a strict curfew.
But, Towa... You think
he'll make it?
I'm not sure he can.
[MIHARU] Well, let's get
the party started.
Could you guys maybe help
me bring all the things out?
[MAMI]
Okay.
Oh, yeah!
[TOWA'S MOM]
Were you nervous?
Huh? Oh, sorta.
I mean, you know I really
haven't seen that much of him.
You're right.
When's the last time the three
of us had a meal together?
[TOWA] I don't know, but we
didn't talk about family.
[TOWA'S MOM] Your stepdad's
nervous, too, you know.
He has a hard time
discussing it.
He's being respectful.
[TOWA'S MOM]
You both are.
Uh? [laughs]
[TOWA'S MOM]
Listen, Towa.
[TOWA]
Yeah?
Were you upset that
I got remarried?
[TOWA]
Well, yeah. Of course, I was.
And even though it was a done
deal, I kept running from it.
What?
I've been such a jerk. Sorry,
Mom. For the other day, too.
You're the most important thing
in the world to me, Towa.
Please know, your stepdad
understands that.
I wish you'd value your
own feelings more.
My feelings don't matter.
[TOWA'S MOM]
Towa...
[TOWA] I always act like
I have it all figured out,
but I'm just a pathetic coward.
And that's the truth.
No, Towa...
[TOWA]
I try to be nice to her,
but then I just get mad
at her, over nothing.
[TOWA]
I know what I should do, but I--
But I...
[gasps]
I'm cutting the cake.
[HARUKI]
I'll go get some plates for us.
[BOTH laugh]
[TOWA'S MOM]
Towa?
[TOWA]
Sorry. I gotta go.
[TOWA'S MOM]
Where?
[TOWA panting]
I'm so scared, but I
can't keep running away.
Because now I know
she feels the same way.
[TOWA'S MOM]
Huh?
Say "hi" for me
when he gets back.
Tell him I look forward
to talking to him later.
I won't run away anymore.
I'm sorry, guys. I wish I
could stay a bit longer.
It's okay. I'm so glad
you came. It was fun.
Thanks again.
Aw, poor Towa.
Sad he didn't make it.
It couldn't be helped.
Besides...
[MAMI]
Please excuse me. Gotta go, bye!
[phone rings]
Who's that?
[MAMI]
Hello?
Class rep, are you still
over at Miharu's house?
Don't leave!
Huh?
[TOWA] I want to talk to you in
person, and don't say you can't.
Wait for me okay?
Even for a minute, or a second!
Class rep!
You okay?
[phone rings]
What's up?
[TOWA panting]
[panting continues]
[TOWA]
Huh?
[sighs]
[MAMI] I'm sorry,
but I can't come home yet.
Just a little longer.
[MAMI] No. Please,
it's really important.
In fact, it's what's most
important to me right now!
You don't get it!
This is my priority!
[MAMI]
Okay, I will, thanks.
[TOWA]
You could've stayed at Miharu's.
Were you so desperate to see me
that you just couldn't wait?
[laughs]
[TOWA]
Here.
Thank you.
Uh, am I too close?
Maybe.
About the other day.
Yeah?
I took things out on you.
I'm sorry. I feel awful.
Can you forgive me?
All I want, is just to be
acknowledged for what I do.
[TOWA]
Uh?
I've always tried so
hard to be perfect.
But, you were right,
there's no such thing.
Wait, I--
But, now I know what matters.
It just feels so weird to be...
bound by your family.
Does that make sense?
But it's not weird!
You're bound because
they're your family.
I'm actually the same.
My issue wasn't that bad,
but it was really hard
for me to deal with.
And so, I kept
running away from it.
Which is lame.
What? No, it isn't.
Hey, thank you.
[MAMI]
Why?
It's all thanks to you,
class rep.
I think about you.
Like, all the time.
Whether you get mad
at me again, or,
if I make you smile,
I don't care.
I want all of it.
[MAMI gasps]
You're the one who
helped me realize
what's most important
to me, class rep.
It was always you.
I realized how important
you are to me too, Towa.
You changed me.
And we'll keep
changing, together.
Yeah.
[TOWA] I'm growing up,
little by little.
[MAMI]
Me, too.
[TOWA]
I'll do my best.
[MAMI]
Yeah. So will I.
That guy is such
a pain in the ass.
It's just like Towa, though.
He's always so direct.
[giggles] I just thought
of something.
Way back last spring, we asked
you about Towa, remember?
Yeah, sure.
That was the first
time we talked.
Actually, no it wasn't.
Huh?
We'd talked before then.
It wasn't the first time
we had talked.
[inaudible]
[MIHARU laughs]
[MIHARU]
Look, it's snowing.
[HARUKI]
Oh!
I guess we should get going.
Yeah.
[gasps]
I wish we had more time.
So, does this mean
we're okay now?
Idiot.
[laughs] Right.
Uh, you say one thing
and do another.
I'm not sure what to do.
Heh.
Ah! It's freezing.
[MIHARU]
Here.
[HARUKI]
Huh?
It's for you.
A Christmas present.
Wow! But I didn't
get you anything.
[laughs] It's okay.
[HARUKI laughs]
I hope you like it!
Huh? Are you kidding me?
I love it! Thank you!
[SAKAMOTO] January.
A new season, a new year.
But, spring still feels
so far away.
Feelings that were flickering
faintly, begin to take shape.
Transparent and
undefined like water,
flowing through one's fingers,
but unquestionably there.
A significant, unignorable
feeling, born in his heart.
Next time on Convenience Store
Boyfriends, episode ten .
"January."
And this is the place
where their story begins.