[HARUKI panting]
[HARUKI chuckles]
[HARUKI]
And here it is.
[HARUKI, MIHARU] This is the
place where our story begins.
Breakfast is ready!
Come on, get up!
Okay, okay. I'm getting up now.
Towa's here? Again?
[HARUKI]
We're off.
[TOWA]
See you later.
Man, my neck is killing me.
Well, you did sleep
on the floor.
Yeah, good point.
How 'bout the bed
next time, huh?
Fat chance.
Fine, jerk.
[TOWA] Oh, yeah.
Brazil's playing today.
I should make plans to
watch it with your brother.
[HARUKI]
You mean at my place?
[TOWA] Yeah, and the European
League is on CS at midnight.
[HARUKI]
You're staying over again?
You'd better make sure
you let my mom know.
[TOWA]
Yeah, I will.
There's an unusual number
of students around for a Sunday.
Because it isn't Sunday.
[TOWA]
Heh. Look at that!
[HARUKI] Man, these high-school
clubs really go all out
to recruit new members,
don't they.
[chuckles]
It's practically a carnival.
You going out for soccer?
Think I'm gonna
head right to the pool.
Will you please stop
being such a loser?
Just wait and hang
with me a little longer.
[HARUKI]
What?
Hey, guys! How do you feel about
joining the handicraft club?
We could use some
new blood around here.
Uh, handi-what, now?
Yeah, I don't think it's for me.
[HANDICRAFT CLUB GIRL]
Aw, come on!
What are you guys afraid of?
It'll be great.
Okay! We've got two
new men on board now!
--[TOWA] What the--
--[HARUKI] Hang on--
[MASAMUNE]
Hey, Handicraft.
Eee... Mr. Sakurakoji!
Dishonest recruitment
tactics are strictly forbidden.
That's a yellow card.
[HANDICRAFT CLUB GIRL gasps]
[whines]
[MASAMUNE]
All right, listen up.
Don't be such an easy target,
or you're gonna end up
in every club on campus.
You got that?
--[TOWA] Okay.
--[HARUKI] Uh, 'kay.
[MIKADO] Hey, lighten up, man.
Don't scare them.
But Mikado--
You interested in liberal arts?
'Cause if not, you should
try checking out
the school grounds or the gym.
A lot of clubs are pretty
aggressive, so be careful.
Those dudes are weird.
I hope I don't end up
on their radar.
Aw, don't worry about it.
S'not like they're not
gonna do anything to us.
Besides, the handicraft
club was scarier.
Yeah, you got that right.
[HARUKI]
Don't you have soccer now?
--[TOWA] Yup.
--[HARUKI] Well,
guess I'll see you later, then.
[TOWA] Hey. Let's meet up
at the convenience store
on the way home.
[HARUKI] Seriously? We're
walking home together, too?
[MIKI]
Welcome.
[MIHARU gasps]
I'm so sorry.
--[MIHARU gasps]
--[crashing noise]
Are you all right, miss?
I hope you didn't hurt yourself!
No, I'm okay, thank you.
I'm terribly sorry.
[MIHARU]
I didn't look where I was going.
It was my fault.
[MIKI]
Oh, look at your skirt.
I'll get you something
to clean it with.
Wait here.
Hey, thanks a lot.
That's so nice.
Please accept
our apologies, miss.
[MIHARU]
No, don't be sorry.
I was careless and absentminded.
[HARUKI]
Uh, I have to get going now.
Oh. Thank you so much
for your kind assistance.
[HARUKI]
Oh, it's fine.
Would you be willing to provide
your contact information?
'Scuse me.
Thanks for helping me.
Uh, you're welcome.
Okay, bye.
[TOWA]
That was just adorable!
Oh, man!
Just make a move already.
[coughing]
Come on, Haruki,
reacting that way every time
is getting really old.
But I keep telling you,
she's not like that.
[TOWA]
That excuse is getting old, too.
Ugh, well, it's not like you're
making a move or anything.
[TOWA]
Real talk, buddy.
I know you take that
kind of thing seriously,
but if you never
practice using it,
you won't be able to
when the time comes.
[HARUKI]
A dick joke, really?
No, ya dumbass.
I'm talking about your heart.
[HARUKI]
What?
You and your princess
were finally reunited, duh.
You get it?
You never give up, do you?
'Kay, it's morning!
Good morning.
Hey! Towa, it's time
to get up now!
[TOWA yells]
--[HARUKI] We're off.
--[TOWA] See you later.
I think Akira might
have broken my damn neck.
Nah, you just slept funny again.
[TOWA]
Yeah, you're right.
So, let me sleep
in the bed for once.
If you want to sleep
in a bed, then go home.
[TOWA]
That's cold, man.
Some best friend you are.
[HARUKI]
Try your only friend.
Welcome, come in.
[MIKI]
Good morning.
[TOWA]
What to eat, what to eat...
So, you lookin' for someone?
[TOWA chuckles]
[HARUKI]
Man. You just won't let it go.
[TOWA chuckles]
[HARUKI]
We were only kids, you know.
I'm an adult now. I can't
hold onto the past forever.
[TOWA] Please, you're
so full of it, Haruki.
I know you're really
a closet romantic.
[HARUKI]
Shut up, dude!
[TOWA]
Ooh! You mad, bro?
[HARUKI]
Listen!
I understand you're girl-crazy
and I can accept that fact.
But some of us have
more important things
to worry about, okay?
[TOWA]
Ugh.
Exactly the kind of
thing that losers say.
[yelps]
Hey, that's my
scoring leg, you tool!
[HARUKI chuckles]
[school bell ringing]
Hey, Towa, you free today?
[TOWA] When?
You talkin' bout after school?
Nah, I have practice then.
Wow, you're so responsible.
[TOWA]
Hang on.
Class rep!
Hey, are you handing those out?
I would've taken care of it.
[gasps]
Don't make me laugh!
You forgot about the committee
meeting during lunch,
didn't you?
What?
Uh...
Why did you even bother
becoming a class rep, anyway?
Uh, 'cause it seemed
like a good idea?
Then take it more seriously!
Hey, you're actually pretty
cute when you're angry,
you know that?
Just hand these out.
[TOWA]
Huh?
Don't be mad.
[GIRLS gasp]
I'm sorry! That was so clumsy.
Are you okay?
No, I'm sorry.
I bump into people all the time.
It's so embarrassing.
Are you okay?
You're Mami Mihashi, right?
Uh, right, and
you're Miharu Mashiki.
How do you know my name?
[MIHARU] I happened to see you
the other day and I realized,
"Oh, I think I
recognize that girl."
[MAMI] And I saw you
in the faculty office.
You were with your mother,
I think, right?
Yeah, that's right!
I also know you
like to read a lot.
[MIHARU]
So do you.
You've borrowed
that Montgomery book
a whole bunch of times.
[MIHARU]
Anne of Green Gables .
[MAMI]
Agatha Christie.
Yeah, Poirot and Marple.
[MAMI]
Michael Ende.
[MIHARU]
The Neverending Story !
[LIBRARIAN 1A]
Shh!
[BOTH giggle]
[MIHARU] Why were you
in such a hurry before?
[MAMI]
What?
[MIHARU] You were like
Cinderella running from the ball
before her coach turned
back into a pumpkin.
[MAMI laughs]
You're such a romantic.
[MIHARU giggles] I know.
I do love fairy tales.
[MAMI] It's a cute thought,
but it's not even close.
The truth is,
I was trying to get away
from a shallow idiot boy.
[MIHARU]
Really, who?
[MAMI] Towa Honda,
one of my classmates.
He never leaves me alone.
He entertains himself by
teasing me all the time.
Do you know any guys like that?
[MIHARU] Well, maybe
in grade school, I did.
[MAMI] Yeah, he's a child.
A truly annoying child.
[LIBRARIAN 1A clears throat]
Be quiet, girls.
--[MIHARU] Oh, so sorry.
--[MAMI] We're very sorry.
I feel bad that you
got in trouble, too.
Oh, that's okay.
I was having fun!
Me, too. I'm so relieved.
I've been wanting to
tell someone about it.
'Cause there's no
point in telling him.
[MIHARU laughs]
[MAMI]
Thanks for listening to me.
[MIHARU] You know,
if he bothers you so much,
do you want some help?
[MAMI]
What?
Well, Towa Honda's in class two,
and he's also on
the soccer team, right?
[MAMI]
Wait, you know him?
[MIHARU] Yeah, we went
to the same middle school.
He definitely stands out.
Yeah, you aren't kidding.
And in more ways than one.
[chuckles]
There's a class one boy.
He happens to be
on the swim team,
and I always notice him
hanging around with Towa.
And actually,
he's a really nice guy.
Want me to see if he'll
talk to him for you?
Oh! No, no, no--
you don't--I'm fine!
It's not like he was violent
or anything like that.
Thanks so much for
the offer, though.
If the situation gets worse
I'll let you know, okay?
--[ATHLETES] One, two. One, two.
--[COACH] Come on!
--[COACH] Move it, ladies!
Hey.
Why aren't you swimming?
[HARUKI] First-years
focus on building stamina...
We'll be in the pool later on.
[TOWA laughs]
You're a fish out
of water, for sure.
[HARUKI] Anyway, when's
Aoki High's forward
becoming a regular on the team?
[TOWA] As soon as they
witness my amazing skills.
Center forward, here I come!
[HARUKI]
Wow, I can't wait to watch you!
[TOWA] Ha. Shut up.
I know you're messing with me.
[HARUKI laughing]
Was it that obvious?
[TOWA]
Ahh, whatever, dude.
I'm still awesome.
Anyway, did you get
that thing you mentioned
the other day?
[HARUKI]
Huh? What thing?
[TOWA] That thing Akira's
been yapping about wanting.
[HARUKI]
Oh, the game, yeah.
I did, but I haven't
been able to play.
He already took it from me.
[TOWA laughs] Sweet!
Then I'll play it with him.
[HARUKI]
Wait a minute.
Does that mean you're coming
over to our house again?
[TOWA]
Yeah.
Akira needs a master
gamer to guide him through.
[HARUKI] You're at my house
more than my dad is.
[TOWA chuckles]
Anyway, let's walk home
together after practice.
[HARUKI] Can't.
I've got too much homework.
[TOWA] Okay, we'll meet at
the convenience store then.
[HARUKI] Dude,
stop trying to plan my life.
[TOWA] Oh, crap!
Upperclassmen incoming!
[HARUKI]
Hey, wait!
[TOWA]
Hey, class rep.
You read this kind of thing?
I'm so shocked!
[MIKI]
Thank you, come again.
[TOWA]
Hey, wait up!
Class rep!
Why are you running
away from me?
Stop freaking out.
You're making it seem
as if I said something
inappropriate to you!
'Cause you did.
Huh?
[MAMI] Please, just let go.
You're embarrassing me.
Huh? I'm embarrassing you?
How's that?
[MAMI]
This is all a big joke to you.
That's how.
You think it's really weird
that I read shojo manga,
don't you?
You think that in order for
girls to have cute things,
they have to be cute, too.
So what you're saying is,
that none of it suits me.
But class rep, you are cute.
I don't understand you.
What could you be
so embarrassed about?
I know how cute you are.
I tell you, like every day.
Please, stop.
I know you don't mean it.
Just quit making fun of me!
Hey. Seriously.
You're pretty.
--[TOWA yells]
--[MAMI] Idiot!
[TOWA]
Wait a sec! Hey!
[NARRATOR]
May.
The season of light
breezes and fresh leaves.
A young man's heart
slowly begins to awaken.
That first step...
...brings him and her closer.
A special place...
...a special time.
Each and every
moment, irreplaceable.
Next time on Convenience
Store Boy Friends.
Episode two: "May."
And this is the place
where their story begins.