[STUDENTS cheering]
Man, it's so hot!
Hope I don't burn.
Ah, suck it up.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[TOWA] It's amazing that
he's made it to Inter-High
two years in a row.
[HARUKI]
I know.
They're excited!
Hey, class rep,
it's not a date if you're
gonna hide out up there
the whole time!
I wish he wouldn't
say things like that.
I'm impressed you
got Mami on a date.
Actually, she suggested it.
Thank me?
You know, for the
three-legged race.
[MAMI]
What do you want?
[TOWA]
Hmm...
A date. With you.
But she wasn't too
thrilled with that idea.
So she turned you down, then.
She only agreed to come
if you and Miharu did.
You are unbelievable.
I don't care.
[TOWA] The point is,
she's here, isn't she?
It's starting soon.
[MAMI gasps]
Thank you, Towa.
You're very welcome, class rep.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[MIHARU] I bet they'll
probably put one of those up
for Natsu soon.
"One of those"?
Yes, a big one at school.
Saying "congratulations"?
Yeah, I bet.
--It's a banner.
--Exactly!
You know everything, class rep!
Hey, aren't you and
Towa going to participate
this year, as well?
Us? Nah.
We'll be starting next year.
You can come cheer us on then.
[HARUKI]
Hang on.
Towa, didn't you say
you'd definitely be
a starter right away when
you first made the team?
[TOWA]
Well, you know,
you have to respect
the third-years.
I'm planning to make my
superstar debut next year.
[ALL laugh]
[TOWA]
You taking the train?
[MAMI]
No, the bus.
Okay, I'll walk
you to the bus stop.
What about you, Miharu?
[MIHARU]
Me, too.
The bus? Okay, come on.
[MAMI]
Don't bother.
It's just right over there.
Aw, come on.
Let's all go together.
Besides, it's no trouble for me.
[MAMI]
I'm fine, really.
Goodbye.
[TOWA]
Class rep, wait!
[MIHARU]
See ya!
Man, she's no fun.
[HARUKI] It's because you
push her too much.
It's called being tenacious.
[HARUKI]
Sure.
[MIHARU]
Hey, Mami?
Is something wrong?
What?
Well, uh...
I thought maybe something
happened between
you and Towa that was upsetting.
[MAMI]
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Yeah, it's all good.
I won't be out that late.
I promise, okay?
Don't worry, I'm totally fine.
Oh, I know.
It's just for today. Honest.
Thanks.
'Kay, bye-bye.
Did your parents
say it was all right?
Uh-huh.
I know this was last minute.
[MAMI]
That's okay!
Glad I'm here.
It's the last day I get
to relax and have fun.
'Cause tomorrow, I have
to dive into my studies.
I haven't quite been able
to put my finger on it.
For some reason,
things just seem different now,
ya know?
"Different"? What do you mean?
I hate him.
So what you mean is
you really like him.
No, I do not!
How could anyone
like that idiot?
[MIHARU laughs]
But...
I think he might
actually be a nice person.
He probably just
wanted to make sure
that you got home safe before.
You're really lucky, Miharu.
[MIHARU]
Huh?
[TOWA yawns]
[TOWA'S MOM]
Good morning.
I know you're on summer break,
but try not to sleep
the day away.
Whatever.
So you're back, then?
[TOWA'S MOM] Well, I'm
leaving for work in a minute.
There's breakfast.
You didn't have to
do that, you know.
Let me be a mother
to you sometimes, yeah?
Have it your way.
[TOWA'S MOM] Besides, I can't
keep inconveniencing
Haruki's mother.
[TOWA]
You working tonight?
Yes.
Your stepfather gets off
work tomorrow morning.
He said he might stop by.
Uh, yeah, sorry,
but I have practice.
I see. Well, I'm off.
[TOWA]
Cool, see you later.
[ANNOUNCER 5A] Various
fireworks displays will be held
at the following locations.
As you can see,
numerous exciting events
are planned for this
weekend, so rest up.
Since mostly clear skies
have been predicted,
going out in a yukata
should be no problem.
Events are large in scale,
so you should
expect heavy traffic.
Give yourself enough
travel time to spare.
Also, temperatures will be high,
so don't forget to stay
hydrated to avoid heatstroke.
[phone vibrating]
Um, hello?
[TOWA]
Hey. Are you free now?
[MAMI]
What do you want?
Uh, do you like want to
see the fireworks tomorrow?
Not with everyone, I mean.
Just the two of us...
...I thought.
[MAMI]
But didn't I repay the favor?
Oh, no. It wouldn't
be a favor this time.
Hello?
[knocking]
Yeah, I'll be right down,
gimme a second!
Can't, I have cram
school tomorrow.
[TOWA]
What about the day after?
Or the day after that?
[MAMI]
Aren't the fireworks tomorrow?
I don't care.
That's not really
the point of it.
I just want to see you.
[MAMI] I'm busy during
the whole break.
[MAMI]
Goodnight.
Sorry. I know I'm late.
Um...
...tomorrow...
Uh, never mind.
[CHILD 5A]
Mama!
[DUDE 5A]
This big!
[DUDE 5B]
It's hot out, huh?
Should I...?
[ATHLETES panting]
[whistle blows]
[ATHLETES sigh]
[COACH 5A]
Ten-minute break, ladies.
[TOWA] Hey, what are
you doing here, man?
[HARUKI]
Jeez, I just wanted to say hi.
Sue me.
Well you're about
to get wet anyway.
So, what're you
guys doing tonight?
"You guys" who?
You're not seeing
the fireworks with Miharu?
I'm sitting for Akira.
Oh, well that sounds lame.
And what about you, huh?
[TOWA]
She shot me down.
Man, I don't get it.
She's such a mystery.
Come on, man, cheer up!
[HARUKI] Hey, get off me!
I can't breathe!
[BOY STUDENT 5A]
Later, Towa.
[TOWA]
See ya.
Miharu!
[TOWA]
Here, it's on me.
You sure?
[TOWA]
Yeah.
Ah, thank you.
So, uh...
Ugh! Ow, brainfreeze!
Still, it's summer,
totally worth it.
[MIHARU giggles]
Haruki eats these things
like they're going out of style.
I think he might
actually turn into one.
Yeah, I definitely
noticed he's fond of them.
Ah, I see you've been
watching him closely, then.
So, anyway were you girls
all right the other day?
You didn't get, uh,
bothered by any weirdos
at the bus stop, did you?
No, we were just fine.
That's good.
Then afterwards,
we had tea at my house.
Oh, yeah?
Having some girl talk?
Well that's nice to know.
Seems like you guys are close.
Towa, you really
are a nice person.
Maybe you could let
the class rep in on that fact.
All I get from her
is the cold shoulder.
She totally hates me.
She doesn't hate you!
Yes, she does.
Listen to me.
Mami's aware.
Probably, anyway.
I think... she--
She just can't seem
to work up the courage.
She wants to trust you...
...but she's having trouble
being honest about that.
Often in shojo manga...
...the girl likes the boy, but
tells him that she hates him.
[TOWA] Miharu, do you
know where she lives?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
Tell me.
[TOWA panting]
So, uh...
A quick date until cram
school would be nice.
That's random.
[MAMI]
Don't you have to be somewhere?
Being with you is
more important right now.
[MAMI]
Stop teasing me.
It upsets me.
"Stop teasing you"?
How can you still say that?
Why don't you believe me?
I promise you. I am serious.
[GIRL 5A]
What do you want to eat?
[GIRL 5B]
Candied apples!
[GIRL 5C]
I want a hot dog.
[GIRL 5A ]
Why don't we get kebabs?
[GIRL 5B]
What? Kebabs? Ugh, no way.
[GIRL 5C]
Yeah, but I want meat.
[GIRL 5A]
Hey, Towa, that you?
[GIRL 5C]
Oh, hey!
[GIRL 5A]
Wow, it's been forever!
[TOWA]
Yeah, hi.
[GIRL 5B] What're ya doin here?
D'ya live nearby?
[GIRL 5A]
Look at my yukata.
Cute, right?
Yeah, sure.
It's very nice.
[GIRL 5A]
"Nice?" That's it?
Oh, I don't know anything.
Don't you guys have
to get going?
Actually, the dumb boys
we were supposed to meet
said they were gonna be late,
so we ditched them.
[GIRL 5B] We'll have
more fun without them.
[GIRL 5C]
Girls' night out.
[GIRL 5A]
Wait!
Since he's already here,
let's invite Towa to tag along.
[GIRL 5B]
Oh, good idea!
[TOWA] Um, what do
you mean, tag along?
[GIRL 5B]
Exactly what it sounds like.
[GIRL 5A]
Come with us. It'll be great.
[overlapping chatter]
[GIRL 5B] We can all scoop
goldfish together.
[GIRL 5C ]
I love goldfish!
[TOWA]
Class rep!
Uh, bye, I gotta go.
[MAMI gasps]
[TOWA] You okay, class rep?
Did you hurt yourself?
[MAMI] Sorry, but you
seemed pretty preoccupied.
No, forget about them.
What's really wrong?
I don't know.
Just please leave me alone.
You tell me you're serious
as if it's no big deal.
And I am...
But I'm not like them!
I'm not confident like
all those other girls.
I'm not cute, either.
I'm just so different.
[TOWA]
That's not true.
[TOWA] You're perfect
just the way you are.
You are cute.
I like how serious you are.
I like you, class rep.
Hear me?
Hey, how do you feel?
I hate you.
Hate you too.
The show is starting!
[NARRATOR]
September, when autumn breezes
caress their skin.
In brilliant sprays of water,
he recalls an innocent
young girl.
That day, he fell in love
with a little mermaid,
and started swimming towards
her as fast as he could.
His childhood memories
overlap with her past,
and in that moment,
there's an epiphany.
Next time on Convenience Store
Boyfriends episode six:
"September."
And this is the place
where their story begins.