[GIRL STUDENT 7A screams]
[CROWD gasps]
So, um... So, do you
know what you want?
Have you decided?
Come on, quit acting
so depressed.
[HARUKI]
I'm not depressed.
Please, man.
You're not fooling anybody.
[yelps] What are you
taking it out on me for?
[TOWA]
Miharu's not here yet?
[HARUKI groans]
[TOWA]
That's too bad.
It's the day of the festival.
Is she sick?
[HARUKI]
Is she?
Miharu, are you possibly...?
Hey, wait.
Are you okay?
--Is something--?
--[MIHARU] I'm sorry.
[HARUKI]
Huh?
I might have done it this time.
What?
Hold on, does that mean
what I think it does, dude?
[HARUKI]
Huh?
Whoa, you were
holding out on me!
As another dude,
I can totally relate
to how you feel,
but you should never
do that without consent.
[HARUKI]
What the...? What?
N-No, you idiot!
Would'ya get your
mind out of the gutter?
[TOWA sighs]
So, what did you do?
I don't know.
But I think maybe
she's avoiding me.
'Cause you told her
how you felt?
Well, actually,
I didn't tell her.
[TOWA sighs]
Ow!
[MASAMUNE]
That's enough, you two.
Why don't you guys
settle down a little, huh?
[HARUKI]
Sorry.
[TOWA chuckles]
But I like your energy.
You've both been helping
us out a lot around here.
We appreciate it.
Awesome, Masamune! We knew
you'd be cool about this.
[MASAMUNE] Yeah, well...
Don't let it go to your head.
[phone vibrates]
[HARUKI]
Your shift?
You need to get going?
Yeah.
But I can probably have
someone else cover for me.
[HARUKI]
No worries.
It's almost time
for my shift as well.
[HARUKI, TOWA]
Excuse us.
Those first years
have a lot going for them.
I'm slightly jealous.
It's practically heartwarming.
[MIKADO]
I'm going to have to disagree.
What?
[MIKADO] Sometimes people's
feelings never amount
to anything.
Just take it from me.
[WAKA]
Big Bro!
Come on, hurry up, 'kay?
[MIKADO]
Careful, you'll fall.
[WAKA]
What?
[gasps]
What did I just tell you?
I know, you're right.
Once you get to high school,
you'll have to learn how
to pull yourself together,
you know.
[WAKA]
Okay.
Know what? Starting this spring,
I'll be in school with you.
Yeah.
[WAKA gasps]
What's the matter?
It's iced over.
You think it'll be
okay to cross it?
[MIKADO]
Too dangerous.
Apparently this bridge has
an eerie history behind it.
What?!
[MIKADO laughs]
But there is a weird
story surrounding it.
At my school, the students
have nicknamed it
"The Lovers' Bridge."
Isn't that funny?
A bridge that's only for lovers?
I think that's,
like, really sweet.
Oh, you do?
So, student council
elections, huh?
Not that any of it
concerns me at all.
Watching Mikado makes
being on the student council
seem like a total drag,
don't you think?
I wouldn't do it
if they paid me.
Wait. That's actually
so not true.
I have the hardest time
saying "no" to people.
Hey, man! Where are you?
Am I talking to myself?
Listen to me...
Attention!
Did everybody get one?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GIRL STUDENT 7B]
Uh, so...
Does anyone have any questions?
[knocking]
[MIKADO]
Yes?
[WAKA]
Sorry to bug you.
Whoa, it's a total mess in here.
This always happens when
you get too busy with work.
Hey, are you even
listening to me?
Can you please
just leave those there?
If you move them around,
I won't be able
to find them later.
But can you even find any now?
You are so weird.
[MIKADO]
Sorry I'm weird.
Don't touch anything.
Okay, fine.
I gotta say, Masamune's
a pretty incredible guy.
He'd have to be
to keep putting up with you.
Yeah, I could never
manage without him.
[WAKA]
Seriously.
You should be kissing our feet
with all the things we
do to make your life easier.
[laughs]
Not yours, Waka.
Rude much?
[MIKADO laughs]
So, what are you doing?
Is this election stuff?
That's right, more or less.
Preparing for my successor
takes up a lot of time.
I need to make sure
the next president
doesn't have any problems.
You're the perfect president,
aren't you?
Wow, you really are amazing.
I'm really proud
of you, Brother.
"Brother," huh? Great.
[MASAMUNE]
Hey.
Oh, hello there.
Nice to see you again, Masamune.
Thank you so much for helping.
It's fine. All good.
[MASAMUNE]
Are you here to see Mikado?
Should I leave?
Uh-uh, I just thought if
he was almost finished here,
then we could
walk home together.
[MIKADO sighs] Sorry.
I'm gonna be here a while.
I see.
But I still need to talk to you.
Okay.
I'll call you when I get home.
Cool. I'll talk to you, then.
Buh-bye, Masamune.
You have a good day now.
Goodbye, I'll see you later.
She's a very nice girl.
Yeah, I know.
[MASAMUNE]
Apparently her class loves her
and puts her on a pedestal.
I wonder what that's like.
Stressful, probably.
You may be right.
I'm sure it's a huge relief.
To have you, I mean.
Well, I sure hope so.
Hey, Prez.
Aren't you forgetting something?
[WAKA] I'm really proud
of you, Brother.
[MAMI] It's almost like they
went back to square one.
[TOWA]
Huh?
Miharu and Haruki.
[TOWA]
Oh.
[MAMI]
Things haven't changed?
[TOWA]
Mm-mm.
Did Miharu say anything to you?
[MAMI]
Mm-mm.
Oh, I see.
Do you think it's my fault
for getting involved?
And maybe I should have
just stayed out of it?
Well honestly...
She's the only one
who knows the real truth.
Well look at you, class rep.
Sounding all super
smart and stuff.
Be serious!
Okay.
Well, fine.
But listen, don't you
want it to work out?
Even if we have to pry?
We wouldn't be prying.
I feel the exact same way.
So come on. Cheer up.
Let's finish
hanging these, okay?
I might cheer up if you
go on a date with me.
Don't jump the gun.
Hey, watch it!
Did Mikado ask you to come?
[HARUKI]
Oh, no.
[MASAMUNE] Well, I'm
locking up for the day.
I, uh, I was just wondering
if I could help out
with anything.
Hmm. That's a good question.
I can think of one way
you can help Mikado.
Have you thought about running
in the upcoming election?
Me? Oh, no, I'd be
a terrible choice.
Waka's the best candidate
in my class by far.
[MASAMUNE]
Waka? Interesting.
I wasn't aware she
was in your class.
[HARUKI]
I don't know if she's up for it,
but the election officials
are trying really hard
to convince her.
And then of course,
there's Mikado.
Those two... um...
Well, they're...
They're together, right?
Like a real couple, I mean?
What?
Uh... oh. Heh!
Is that how it seems?
Well, yeah.
[laughs] Of course it does.
And you'd be right.
What?
[GIRL STUDENT 7B]
Please, I'm begging you!
I can't do it.
But... Waka, you're honestly
the most perfect candidate here.
And aren't you like
really close with Mikado?
Sorry, I don't think
I can run in an election.
The truth is, I'm too shy.
Aw, man. That's too bad.
Well, I guess
I can't force you to.
Again, I'm sorry.
[GIRL STUDENT 7B]
No, I'm sorry, too.
I just thought if
you were elected,
Mikado would know
he could exit the position
with some peace of mind.
And he'll be leaving anyway.
[WAKA]
Big Bro!
I have no idea how
you found out about it,
but I should've told them
not to say anything.
[WAKA]
Why?
Why didn't you say anything?
This is important.
[MIKADO]
Sorry.
[WAKA] I'm not asking
you to apologize.
Hokkaido, is it?
So tell me.
Are you moving away?
Yes, I am.
It was always the plan.
[WAKA]
You can't live in Tokyo?
No matter what?
We won't be able
to see each other.
I won't get to visit
you at your house.
We won't be able to tell
each other about our days,
or go out for snacks,
or have any more fun!
I can't handle that.
Please just stay with me.
I wish that I could stay, too.
I've watched out for you.
And I've always protected you.
But you just don't understand.
[WAKA]
But brother...
Stop it!
I'm not your brother.
Please don't think of me
that way anymore!
Because I...
I love you.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Hey, are you okay?
[MIKADO]
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
I just didn't get
enough sleep last night.
Any reason why?
[MIKADO]
Don't you have practice?
Thanks. You can go now.
But I'm worried.
I don't know if there's
anything I can do to help,
but I'd like to try.
I'm sure things
would work out
if I were as honest as you are.
Oh, well.
What?
Have you heard the story of
"The Lover's Bridge," Haruki?
What story?
When I was a first-year,
there was a legend going around.
If a boy and a girl crossed
the bridge together at dusk,
they'd be together forever.
It was just a silly fantasy,
but perhaps if I'd
been more sincere,
God might have decided
to smile upon me.
You don't believe the story?
Did any of it
even happen at all?
What's to believe?
God abandoned me long ago.
[school bell ringing]
Waka.
Haruki, hi.
Oh, thank you, that looks good.
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
[HARUKI]
Thanks a lot.
Uh, sorry if I'm in the way.
In the way?
[HARUKI]
Oh, um...
You're not in the way.
You've actually been helping
Mikado, haven't you?
Uh, yeah.
Sometimes.
[WAKA]
I'm sure he appreciates it.
He's been so busy lately.
Yeah, definitely.
You mean with the election
and entrance exams?
I'm not sure.
To be honest with you,
he doesn't tell me
much about that stuff.
He seems to be very guarded.
And if he ever were
to lose his cool one day,
it would have to be something
major that sets him off.
Oh, sorry, Waka.
I'm sure you know
more about him than me.
[MASAMUNE]
Hey.
Good morning.
You're moving slowly
today, Mr. President.
I do sometimes.
I have to hold things together.
I understand.
[GIRL STUDENT 7C]
Vote for me!
You won't regret it.
Oh, thank you!
[MASAMUNE]
Ah, they're campaigning.
Hey. Mikado.
Well, this is a
sudden development.
[GIRL STUDENT 7B]
Attention, everyone:
The class one election speeches
are now ready to begin.
And here's our first candidate.
Fellow students.
I'm Waka Kisaki, and I'm
running for vice president.
She's doing all of this for you.
What?
[WAKA] I intend to carry on
the current president's agenda,
and I will support the new
student council president
as I help...
Hey, Mikado, isn't this great?
Check it out!
Everybody got an
e-mail late last night.
I hope you decide
to vote for her.
Hey, Haruki, c'mon!
Quit slacking off!
Gotta go. Sorry.
Vote for Waka.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[HARUKI]
Hey.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Good morning.
[NARRATOR] November, when
a carpet of ginkgo leaves
covers the ground with
the color of the sun.
The footsteps of winter
quietly approach.
As they move closer,
hearts move apart.
One-word messages
float back and forth.
He wants to see her, but can't.
He hurt her. His heart hurts.
He can't even say he's sorry.
Next time on Convenience Store
Boyfriends , episode eight:
"November."
And this is the place
where their story begins.