[MIHARU]
"The Merman Prince."
"Once upon a time, there was
a royal family of mermen
who lived at the bottom
of a deep, blue ocean."
"This is a story of the tiny
prince of the merfolk kingdom
who went on a quest
to find a girl."
"His journey was
long and tiring,
and he traveled far across
the sea to find her ship.
Once he finally found
the one she was on,
he gathered all his strength,
swam up beside it,
and called out to her."
"'Please don't cry anymore.
I've come to rescue you,'
the merfolk prince
said kindly to the girl."
"'Look at your eyes!
They glitter like coral.
They are so beautiful!'
Then the girl asked him,
'Where is this coral
you speak of?'
He said, 'It's at the bottom
of the deep, blue sea.'
'I'd like to see it,'
the girl replied.
'Come with me,
and I'll show it to you!'"
[MIHARU]
Oh!
My mom's here!
Bye bye.
[HARUKI]
Ma... shiki... Mi...
[MIHARU]
I'm Miharu Mashiki.
Miharu.
Mashiki.
[alarm ringing]
[HARUKI]
Towa, wake up.
[TOWA groans]
Please, just gimme
one more hour.
Get your butt out of bed;
you're gonna be late.
[HARUKI]
Okay. I'm ready.
Man, I don't get it.
How do you know
what's okay to do
and what isn't?
This again?
Oh, yeah, this again.
Come on, what you did was
totally sexual harassment.
Aw, man, it didn't come close.
Besides, these shojo
manga are pretty racy.
Like dirty.
Please, just stop talking.
Hey. Dude.
We'd better get a move on.
Huh, I didn't even
know boys were reading
that kinda stuff these days.
Don't mind me,
but you should probably
wrap it up soon.
Okay.
[MIKI]
Thank you, come again.
Those crazy kids.
Listen, man. Take it easy.
What do you mean?
Just like, try not to bother
that class rep so much.
Tone it down a little.
[TOWA]
Jeez, man.
[HARUKI] I mean it, dude.
She doesn't like it.
[TOWA]
What?
But when a girl says
"no," that's a "yes"!
Isn't it?
Not really.
You know, if you're not careful,
that attitude is gonna get
you in big trouble someday.
[HARUKI]
Huh?
[TOWA] It's the
student council president.
[HARUKI]
Yeah.
Is that Waka Kisaki?
[TOWA] Huh!
I guess they're dating.
What? Ya think?
You still have a lot
to learn, my friend.
I'll see you later.
[TOWA]
Hey, class rep!
There's that sour face again.
You're a hundred times cuter
when you smile, y'know.
Come on, lighten up!
[TOWA]
Nothing?
Hey, wait up. Class rep!
Boy, Towa never quits.
[TOWA]
You're still mad at me?
I'm sorry.
I promise I never meant
to make you so upset.
I guess I didn't know
what I was doing.
Now I do.
You didn't even realize.
You're awful.
I'm awful?
[MAMI]
Are you enjoying yourself?
[TOWA]
What?
[MAMI]
This really does bother me.
But I appreciate
you not saying anything
about that incident
the other day.
[TOWA]
"That incident?"
Oh, right, the manga.
Yeah, your secret's safe.
[TOWA laughs]
Sorry.
I swear it, I know when
to keep my mouth shut.
Well, you sure
could have fooled me.
Just leave me alone.
Notebooks.
It's fine, believe me.
You can count on me
for this kinda stuff.
Then thank you.
See, it's only natural.
When there's a fragile girl
who needs some help,
it's a man's job to save her.
So that's why I wish you
would rely on me more often.
Ha, kidding.
I mean...
[school bell ringing]
[MIHARU]
So, nothing's changed?
[MAMI] Not only that,
it's even worse now.
Now that he has some dirt on me,
he's ramping up
the teasing more.
Dirt? Are you sure?
He did promise you he
wouldn't tell anybody, right?
Yes, he did, but maybe
he's saving it for later.
Huh? What do you mean?
For when he really needs it.
And when would that be?
I'd have to say...
[laughing]
It almost sounds like a manga.
The most popular boy
in class suddenly starts
talking to you out
of the blue one day.
When you really need his help,
he might gallantly
come to save you.
So funny!
That only happens in manga.
Besides, I prefer boys
who actually choose
to use their brains.
Maybe now's the time
to talk to Towa's friend
I told you about.
[MAMI]
You mean that guy in class one?
[MIHARU]
Yeah.
If you're up for it,
I bet he'd be willing to listen.
He might even have
some insight for you.
Hello again.
[whistle blows]
[splash]
[COACH 2A]
Hey, Mishima!
Sorry, coach!
[MIHARU]
Haruki.
If you can, will you meet
me after practice today?
What?
I need to talk to you.
Uh, sure.
[COACH 2A]
Mishima!
[HARUKI grunts]
[HARUKI gasps]
Hey, sorry. I'm late.
That's okay.
We just got here ourselves.
Ah!
This is my friend Mami.
This is Haruki.
Nice to meet you.
[HARUKI]
Nice to meet you too.
Uh, huh?
Don't worry about it.
So uh...
[HARUKI]
Yes?
So there's--there's
actually something we wanted
to get your advice about.
Advice? Me?
Oh, I see.
You don't have to.
Oh, no. It's fine.
Well, what's up?
It's about Towa.
I don't believe he's
a bad person.
But would you mind maybe
having a little talk with him?
[HARUKI]
So, in other words...
[MAMI] I'd like him to
leave me alone, please.
[HARUKI]
Oh. I hear you.
I've known him a while and
he really doesn't mean
any harm.
He just has some
trouble with respecting
personal space and boundaries,
regardless of whether
it's girls or whoever.
I understand that,
but I, I don't--
I just can't.
[MIHARU]
Haruki!
[HARUKI]
Miharu.
What's wrong?
[MIHARU]
So, thanks for today.
Hope I didn't put
you on the spot.
Sorry if I did.
[HARUKI]
Oh, it's totally fine.
I mean, I haven't done
anything for you yet.
But I was right.
I knew you'd be willing
and able to help out.
Huh? But how did you--?
I just did.
Hey, you're sweating. Here.
Oh, uh...
I'm, uh... I'm fine.
Okay, goodnight, then.
[doorbell rings]
[TOWA]
Honey, I'm home!
Oh, Towa!
You're back again?
[TOWA] Yeah, I thought
I'd help you level up
in that game later.
Cool!
Hey, what's up, Haruki?
Towa, we need to talk.
Okay.
[TOWA] So, what did you
want to talk about then?
[HARUKI clears throat]
Well, it's about Mami,
the class rep.
[TOWA coughs]
Easy.
Sorry. [coughs]
I just wasn't expecting
to hear that name.
Anyway, why?
Well, we had a
conversation today.
Uh, you did? About what?
She told me you've
been bothering her a lot,
and it makes her
very uncomfortable.
[TOWA]
What?!
For real?
For real.
To you, I'm sure
that sorta stuff's
just like saying hello,
but dude, please,
you have got to leave her alone.
So stop. She doesn't like it.
[HARUKI]
Hey, man.
Wait. Do you...
...really like her?
Ugh!
In that case,
you should've taken
a more sincere approach.
To be honest,
she's not getting it at all.
xactly what I did.
I told her she's cute,
and like... pretty.
That just makes you seem
even more insincere, though.
You do come off as a joker.
At least I make an effort,
unlike you who's too
scared to say anything.
What?
You barely have the stones
to say hi to that Miharu girl.
I keep telling you,
it isn't even like that.
With that rotten attitude,
you're never gonna get
the chance to find out.
Look who's talking, you idiot!
What's that?
You little wussy!
Shut up, you bastard!
Make me, closet perv!
[BOTH grunting]
[TOWA]
You asshat! Get offa me!
[HARUKI]
You never let anything go!
Shut up!
[HARUKI]
Aki, wait--
[AKIRA]
Mom! I knew it!
Haruki's gay!
[laughs]
[TOWA]
Yeah, it's fine.
Right, I know.
Bye.
So, what'd your mom say?
[TOWA]
Nothing, really.
She's actually still
working tonight, late.
Guess it woulda been better
to call them earlier.
[TOWA]
Hey.
[HARUKI]
Yeah?
[TOWA]
Never mind.
[HARUKI]
Come on, what?
[TOWA]
Was the class rep... angry?
Uh, well, to be honest with you,
she seemed more sad than angry.
[TOWA]
Really?
[TOWA] We're totally
different, aren't we?
[HARUKI]
Yeah.
[TOWA]
Think we're a good match?
[HARUKI]
Dunno.
[TOWA]
Don't be such a shitty friend.
You're supposed to say yes.
[HARUKI] But I can't.
I really don't know.
One thing I like--
She's just so honest
about her emotions.
[TOWA] One minute, she seems
bored, then she gets mad.
She has that sort
of awkward smile.
She can be friendly,
or terrifying.
I have to admit...
[TOWA] You know me.
I pretty much like all girls.
There's something... special...
...about... class rep.
Well then, I've got your back.
[HARUKI sighs]
[HARUKI] So the truth is,
the only thing he really wants
is to be friends with Mami.
[TOWA]
Mm-hmm.
[HARUKI] But he can
be a little impulsive,
so if he happens to do
something that upsets you,
tell him directly.
No need to hold back.
[TOWA]
Hold me accountable!
[HARUKI]
I know he can be shallow,
and inappropriate sometimes,
but he has some
great qualities, too.
I can totally vouch
for him as a friend.
Please stop barking
out "class rep"
when you want to talk to me.
And no more
unsolicited touching.
I don't like it.
I got it.
If you don't need anything,
then don't pester me.
Aw. Come on, you're no fun.
[HARUKI]
Towa.
I see.
Do you really hate me that much?
No, that's not it.
You still don't get it, do you?
Gah. Never mind.
What?
I said never mind, okay?
We're done talking now.
[MIHARU]
Go on.
So, we're good.
Well, I'm gonna head
off to school now.
Wait...
Ow! What--?!
[TOWA grunts]
Miharu!
Huh?
Hey, uh, so do you
want to walk to school?
Together? Like as a group?
Oh, yeah, the four of us!
Sure.
Please get back to work.
What are you smiling about, huh?
Oh, nothing.
I just like seeing nice things
happen to nice people.
[NARRATOR]
June.
When the sweet song
of birds can be heard
after warm summer rains.
Puddles of water that
glimmer in the light.
Boys making splashing
sounds as they run along.
The showers at season's
arrival gift hydrangeas
their brilliant color,
and every passing day,
brings him and her
closer together.
Next time, on Convenience
Store Boy Friends .
Episode three: "June."
And this is the place
where their story begins.