[CIEL]
Once we search the
first-tier performers' tents,
we can go home.
My initial plan
was to work our way
quietly up the ladder.
But with these
wretched conditions,
I simply can't last that long.
I'm already
approaching my limit.
[SEBASTIAN] Personally,
I would find brute force
easier than infiltration.
The reaper keeps me
from moving freely at night.
Unfortunately, the fact
that the reaper is here
isn't enough to prove
the circus guilty of anything.
So behave yourself for now.
Yes.
The time to strike
is during a show,
when we can expect them all
to be away from their tents.
Before anything, I need
to find a way to slip free
of that freckled chap
who tails me everywhere.
If I can't assess the
tent's contents personally,
there's no point.
[CIEL] I want to go home.
I'm long overdue
for something sweet.
[SEBASTIAN]
I think you would benefit
from a nice hot
cup of tea, as well.
[WENDY] Where's my headpiece?
Has anyone seen it?
Here you are.
Oi, there aren't enough knives!
Hurry up with those spares.
[CIEL] Here!
Right, you lot!
It's almost show time,
so look lively!
Come on!
At this rate, I may
collapse from exhaustion
before I even have a
chance to check the tents.
Oh, sorry!
What can I do nex--
[CIEL] Sebastian!
I managed to
lose Freckles somehow.
Let's check the tents
while we have the chance.
We should only need
ten minutes or so.
Of course. Yes, my lord.
[JOKER] Black!
We've got a problem.
Wendy here seems to
have twisted her ankle.
Show's already started,
so I need yeh ta get in there
and take her place
on the trapeze.
[SEBASTIAN] But surely
I'm not a fit substitute.
From what I seen you do,
I'd say yer more
than fit for the job.
We're counting on yeh,
yeh understand?
And there isn't
much time afore the act,
so yeh'll need
ta be quick about it!
[SEBASTIAN]
He leaves me little choice.
My lord. I must attend to this.
We'll find another chance.
My lord?
We don't know if there
will even be another chance.
Freckles follows me around
every second of the day.
You may be
needed in the show,
but I should have some time.
The only trouble is the snakes.
All right, then.
Come. We must move quickly.
[SEBASTIAN] Yes, my lord.
I believe that
should be all of them.
According to the program,
your act ends at seven fifty,
and the encore
is at eight o'clock.
If that schedule is correct,
then that should allow you
roughly a ten-minute window.
To do what?
[CIEL]
As soon as your act ends,
come and release the snakes,
then return for the encore.
I'll take this opportunity
to look through their tents.
But are you certain you shall
be all right by yourself?
I'll be fine.
Now hurry on back
to the show tent.
They'll be getting suspicious.
[SEBASTIAN]
Very good, my lord.
At once.
I don't understand.
I thought Wendy
was the only one injured.
Well, yeah, but you
can't very well expect Peter
to hold your weight, can you?
And this was the best solution?
I can't begin to express
my distaste for this idea.
While I don't much
care for it, either,
what option have we?
[WILLIAM]
Working with vermin like him!
How could I have sunk so low?
Honestly!
[SEBASTIAN]
Half seven. Almost time.
[CIEL] These are rather
sparsely decorated quarters.
[CIEL] An old photograph.
Are these the main performers?
[CIEL] Who is that?
What precisely are you doing?
They can tell me
to perform with you,
but I would sooner die than
take your filthy hands, vermin.
[SEBASTIAN] This won't make
for a very good show.
[WILLIAM] Hmph!
There just swinging up there!
What're they doing?
Ugh! My bodice.
[BEAST] Oh! My bodice!
Ah, nothing to see here!
Move along! Nobody look!
[DAGGER]
Er, you can go change, Beast.
There's time before the encore.
[BEAST] I suppose I should.
[SEBASTIAN] Oh dear.
[CIEL] That's him again.
This is the same man
who was in the other photograph.
Will you stop this nonsense
and put out your hands?
I meant what I said before.
I'd sooner die!
My fingers might rot off.
[SEBASTIAN] Oh, very well.
In that case,
I shall simply improvise!
[CROWD gasping]
[BEAST]
The crowd sounds mighty excited.
[CIEL] That sign behind them.
It says "workhouse".
An orphanage?
[CROWD gasping]
Unhand my death scythe now!
I don't think I will.
[CROWD gasping]
Careful!
[WILLIAM] I said let go!
Oh, all right.
[CROWD cheering]
[cheering continues]
[JOKER] Although,
we first-tier performers
all come from the same place.
[CIEL]
So that's what he meant.
They literally came
from the same place--
The same workhouse.
[CIEL] Well and good.
But where is that, exactly?
Maybe there's a
better image of it in here.
[BEAST]
Blasted thing ripping on me.
And it was my favorite.
[BEAST] Well, this'll do.
[SEBASTIAN] A good thing
I returned ahead of schedule.
I thought you might need me.
Yes. Now get off, will you?
[SEBASTIAN] Interesting.
You think these
photographs you've found
are important, then?
Yes. Here, take a look.
Do you notice anything?
I do, actually.
The imprint
from this signet ring.
I think I've seen it recently.
[CIEL] Signet ring? Imprint?
You mean you can make out
details that small?
[SEBASTIAN] Yes.
Now then, if memory serves,
this matches the seal at the
joint of Beast's prosthetic leg.
[CIEL] The signet ring,
the seal, the workhouse.
We need to know more.
Who is this man?
It's almost eight o'clock now.
I think we had
better stop for today.
I need to free the snakes
before the encore begins.
[CIEL] I still have to
look through Joker's tent.
[SEBASTIAN] My lord.
[CIEL]
I should be able to manage it.
I think the encore will
give me just enough time.
I want all of this
to be over today.
You'll need to go back
so they don't suspect us.
After the encore,
simply return to the tents
before they do
and set the snakes free.
Now move!
Yes, my lord.
[CIEL] His dress marks him as
either wealthy or a nobleman.
Given that he appears
in photographs
with workhouse children,
he could be a philanthropist.
A letter?
It's labeled
"Tom, the piper's son."
The Mother Goose character?
[gasps]
[CIEL]
What the devil is going on?!
This is my name!
Well done, everyone!
Good show!
Oi, where did Black go?
He ran off
right after the encore
without so much
as a "by your leave".
Maybe he needed
to go take a piss, eh?
[JOKER]
Haha, could be!
Might've even leaked
a little up there!
[snakes hissing]
[CIEL]
This doesn't make sense!
What is my name
doing in this letter?
Surely they aren't onto us.
[outside chattering]
Oh hell, it's the main cast.
Are they back already?
[JOKER]
I'm feelin' a mite peckish.
[DAGGER] Let's go eat, then!
[CIEL] I should've
stopped searching sooner.
I have to get back
without being seen.
[gasps]
[snake hissing]
Oi.
What do you
think you're doing?
[DOLL] Don't move.
Sebastia--
Be quiet.
Oi, Doll!
What are you waiting for?
Come on and get changed
so we can go--
One of Snake's
snakes was loose.
He needs to be more careful.
We've told him
not to let them out.
Snake! Get this
blasted creature of yours!
[DOLL] I don't like risking
my life just by walking around.
Please keep them
locked up, mate.
Well, I'm off to the mess tent.
Come with me.
Move faster.
[DOLL] Don't touch the rope.
[DOLL] Right, we should
be in the clear now.
[CIEL coughing]
Thanks, but why
did you help me?
You still haven't
figured it out, eh?
Let me show you.
It's me.
[gasps]
Freckle-face, it's you?
Hey, now, is that
any way to address a lady?
You're a bloke, but you
wear a dress on stage?
[DOLL] You are very rude,
aren't you?
I'm a genuine maid, thank you.
Here, I'll prove it.
There, see?
Want to have a look-see
down below while you're at it?
No, thank you!
So what were
you doing back there
around Snake's tent, anyway?
They must've told you
it was dangerous.
[CIEL]
Well, I--
[CIEL] I'll have to lie.
An unsavory cover story
will be most convincing.
You caught me! I'm sorry!
But I haven't stolen
anything today, I swear!
I'll be good, I promise!
Only please don't run me off!
What are you--Wait, "today"?
[CIEL]
I might as well tell you.
I lived on the East End
before I became a page.
I did whatever
I had to to get by.
I know that stealing is wrong,
but old habits
are hard to shake.
My last master gave me the sack!
If the circus turns me out,
I'll have to go back to
scraping by on the East End!
[CIEL] Oh, drat.
I may have laid
it on a bit thick.
[DOLL] You swear you didn't
take anything just now?
Yes! I swear on my life!
Well, all right.
I don't know
how to thank you!
[DOLL] It's fine.
Guess I owe you one, anyhow.
We've all got
our secrets, don't we?
I certainly understand that.
And I've been feeling rotten
about what I did to you earlier.
Tell you what.
I'll keep this quiet
from the others.
That'll make us even.
But no more sneaking about,
all right?
Or I will have to say something.
[CIEL] Got it!
[coughs]
So, uh...
If you don't mind me asking...
Why are you sharing my tent?
You're in the main cast.
[DOLL] Well, truth is...
I don't like sleeping alone.
It's easier for me to sleep when
there's somebody else nearby.
Hey, will you still
share a tent with me
now that you know who I am?
Yes. Of course!
[Oh, that's good.
Right then, what happened here
stays between
the two of us, yeah?
Yes.
[CIEL] Words are cheap.
There's no guarantee
she won't tell anybody.
Why wouldn't she?
Humans lie like
it's second nature.
[CIEL]
Myself included, of course.
[CIEL coughing]
[SEBASTIAN] My Lord!
Bastard!
One of those
blasted poisonous snakes
could have easily bitten me!
You knew I was
still there, didn't you?
[coughing]
Yes.
You did tell me to return
before the others and free them.
I was only
following your orders.
Is there a problem with that?
Really, now!
What are you glaring about?
Rest assured, my lord.
I won't let you die.
Not while our
contract is in effect.
But if you give
the wrong orders,
you may be in
for some suffering.
Of the non-fatal variety,
of course.
But you already knew that.
Every game should have
an element of danger to it.
You're such an
avid player yourself,
I just assumed you shared
my opinion on the matter.
Ha!
You know what I'd call
your stupid little game?
Demonic.
You do flatter me.
Oh, never mind.
What's of greater import now
is the letter I found
in Joker's tent
mentioning my name.
[coughs]
It included my rank and the
location of my family estate.
There was even a brief
biographical sketch.
As for the sender, he--
[WILLIAM] Mind yourself.
[CIEL] Ow!
You are three
centimeters into my territory.
That is unacceptable.
The master must observe
our agreed-upon boundaries.
If he fails to do so, what's to
distinguish him from the dog?
[coughs]
[CIEL] Come, Sebastian.
Let's go outside.
[SEBASTIAN] Certainly.
[CIEL] Anyway, as I was saying,
the sender used the name
"Tom, the piper's son."
[SEBASTIAN] A character from
a Mother Goose tale, isn't it?
[CIEL] Yes, though it seems
like a strange alias.
[coughs]
Also, the wax was
sealed with a crest
bearing a horse
and the letter K.
[SEBASTIAN] Indeed?
Then it's the same
as the seal that I saw.
Signet rings
are generally engraved
with a motif and
initial that represent
the bearer or his family.
[CIEL] Yes.
[SEBASTIAN] And that means...
Tom the piper's son must have a
coat of arms featuring a horse.
The equine motif could indicate
someone awarded a knighthood,
or perhaps even a soldier?
[CIEL coughs]
[CIEL] Possible,
but not necessarily.
He must have
some status, though.
If he is a philanthropist,
that would be essential.
The heraldic authorities
have all coats of arms
in their registers.
We have enough criteria
to narrow it down.
So however many there may be...
[coughs]
You should be able to
identify the correct one.
The missing children,
the circus,
Tom the piper's son, and me.
They're connected some--
[coughing]
My Lord?
[CIEL] We'll have to go back.
The town house will have--
[coughing]
[SEBASTIAN] My Lord!
My Lord! What is happening?
[CIEL wheezing]
What's going on? Smile!
What's wrong?
It's an asthmatic fit.
Asthma? Are you certain?
We've lived together
for three years now
and I've never known
anything of the sort
to afflict him before today.
[DOC] If he hasn't had
an attack in three years,
he may be more or less cured.
But sometimes patients relapse
if they catch a cold or
experience sudden stress.
He has had colds before.
They weren't like this.
[DOC]
It seems probable there were
multiple triggers this time.
And I hear he had
a bath outside earlier
with the rest of those loons.
It's no wonder he took a chill!
Wa... ter.
Awake, then, are you?
Here, drink this.
[coughs]
Tell me, Smile.
Has this sort of thing
happened before?
Were you asthmatic as a child?
Asthma can be deadly,
so even if he hasn't
had a fit in some time,
you must remain vigilant.
Aunt Angelina...
[DOC] Not good.
His mind appears to be muddled.
We shall have to keep a sharp
watch until the fever goes down.
I'll fetch ice!
Be right back!
And what about you,
then, Black?
I'd like to stay and help
if it's no trouble to you.
[DOC] I'd be much obliged.
[JOKER] What's that?
Black and Smile snuck in?
After what?
[SNAKE] "Now that I'm afraid
I couldn't tell you, my boy,"
says Wordsworth.
Are you serious?
You really think your serpent
friends speak to you?
"How dare you presume to
doubt my word, you simpleton!"
says Wordsworth Longfellow.
You might have mentioned
this ability before,
don't ya think?
"I did suggest that we
report it straight away,"
says Emily.
Well, never mind
that now, thanks,
and off to bed with all of yeh.
[SNAKE] "Good night, old chap."
"Do sleep well."
Come, Wordsworth Longfellow,
Emily.
[JOKER] This isn't good.
They might suspect something.
That Doll is a bleedin' fool.
I told ya we never
should've brung her!
She's too young to be anything
but a bloody nuisance.
So who are Black and Smile?
And what are they after?
[PETER] I say we should
get rid of them.
Maybe tonight.
No that's a bad idea.
[PETER] Why?
[JOKER] Jumbo's right.
If they're with the Yard,
killing them
will draw attention.
And that'd put us
in a right big bind.
[JUMBO] At the very least, we'd
have to break up the troupe.
Go our separate ways.
[JOKER] Right you are.
What to do?
I think I should be
asking Father.
I'll be on me way now.
But remember, what Father
wants most is the target.
So keep an eye on those two.
If they get up to anything...
[JUMBO] We know what to do.
[PETER] If they start causing
trouble, we'll move without you.
[CIEL coughing]
Sebastian.
[DOC] How is our patient doing?
[SEBASTIAN]
He still seems poorly.
I thought as much.
I just remembered that mint oil
can help with these fits.
I should have some.
If I can find it.
[CIEL] This is an order.
Go to the heraldic authorities
and identify the man
who was wearing the signet ring.
The registers are located
in London and Edinburgh.
If I attempt to go with you now,
the doctor will
likely make a fuss.
Come back in the morning.
Fetch me then.
[SEBASTIAN] Yes, my lord.
[DOC] There we are!
Found it at last.
Now we'll just pour
some on a rag and--Er.
Hello?
[DOC] Finally asleep, are we?
[SEBASTIAN] Very well.
I think I shall begin
with the clo--
[SEBASTIAN]
You're interfering again?
Well, this won't do at all.
[WILLIAM]
And where are you going?
You aren't to be
wandering about
without your master...
Now, are you?
[SEBASTIAN] You seem to
have a rather large number
of vipers, Snake.
Do they all have names?
[SNAKE] "Of course we do!"
says Wilde.
"I'm Goethe."
"I'm Emily!"
"Wordsworth Longfellow here!"
[SEBASTIAN] I could
let him go on indefinitely,
but I'll be merciful
and stop this.