[SEBASTIAN]
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for coming to visit
the Phantomhive manor today.
Alas, your timing
is unfortunate.
The master and I must be off.
We are traveling to London,
where we have some pressing
business matters to attend to.
Very serious business.
It is fortunate that the
weather turned out so fine.
The perfect day
to go to the circus,
don't you think, master?
Circuses are generally
held in large tents,
aren't they?
Thus rendering the
weather quite irrelevant.
Bardroy. Finny. Mey-Rin.
The master and I will be
staying in Town for a while.
Do try to behave
yourselves, won't you?
Have fun!
You take care
of yourself, all right?
We'll be seein' you!
Please travel safely, master.
[CIEL] You three.
[ALL gulp]
Remember why I hired you.
Look after the place well.
[MEY-RIN, FINNIAN, BARDROY]
Yes, my lord!
[QUEEN VICTORIA]
"Greetings, dear boy.
I hope you found your
Christmas holiday enjoyable.
My attempt to make
a Christmas pudding
with Phipps
was a great success.
I am pleased to report
that the results were met
with high praise
from John and Grey.
I hope you will have
occasion to try it sometime.
Now then, you must be curious
as to the enclosed tickets.
A circus is expected
to arrive in London soon.
It's a traveling troupe,
and supposedly quite good.
However, my sources inform me
that a startling number of
children have gone missing
from towns the
circus has visited.
The police are doing
all they can, to be sure.
But even so, not a single
child has been located.
The circumstances
are always similar.
They vanish without a trace
in the middle of the night.
It's almost as if
they have been lured away
by the Pied Piper of Hamelin.
Is there any
sorrow that can compare
to that of losing
a family member?
Every moment must
be agony for them.
It is my sincere hope
that these poor children
will be returned
to their families soon.
Victoria."
Where will you begin
your investigation, my lord?
The usual place, naturally.
[CIEL] Very convenient
that Sir Arthur is away
from the station
at the moment, is it not?
[ABBERLINE] Eh...
I'm begging you, please, stop!
If the commissioner
were to find out--
[CIEL] Best make sure
he doesn't then, eh?
How did you even
get up to the third floor?
No one asked for
your credentials?
Sebastian? Anything yet?
No bodies have been found
that match the
missing persons reports,
but I'm not certain
those reports are complete.
We'll leave when
you're finished copying.
And we might as well
borrow the photos.
--You can't do that!
--Ugh. Oh, tosh.
If you're found out,
just say that I took them
and you'll be fine.
That'd land me
in even more trouble!
Yes, well...
So sorry, Underline, isn't it?
[ABBERLINE] It's Abberline!
You've been very helpful,
and we thank you.
[gasps]
I am not for sale, my lord!
I just want those children safe.
And I will do whatever it takes
to ensure that happens!
You're willing to do
"whatever it takes," eh?
Very flexible of you--
You have a bright future.
Hey, wait!
[CIEL] I hope I'll be hearing of
your promotion soon, Abberline.
At least it seems
they're still being treated
as missing persons,
rather than murder victims.
Yes, as far as respectable
society is concerned.
But somebody in the underworld
may well have disposed
of them already.
[SEBASTIAN] Given that,
am I correct to assume
we'll be paying him a call?
I don't like it
any more than you do,
but when needs must, and all.
Let's be off.
Quite.
[CIEL]
Undertaker. Are you about?
[UNDERTAKER giggling]
[UNDERTAKER] Hello, my lord.
It's so lovely to see you.
[low rumbling noise]
What's it to be, then?
Do I finally have the
pleasure of fitting you
for one of my coffins?
[CIEL] Look, you--
Have a seat, my lord.
I've got a batch of biscuits
still fresh from the oven.
[UNDERTAKER]
Children's bodies, is it?
[SEBASTIAN] The authorities
still consider them
missing persons.
And no corpses have
turned up that we know of.
Well, tragic as it may be,
dead children are part
and parcel of life
in the old underworld.
A fact I'm sure
you're aware of, my lord.
I have their
information here.
Look through these
and tell me if you've
"taken care of"
any of these children.
Have I seen that face before?
I don't know.
I'd wager my memory
would be a right bit sharper
if I had myself
a good laugh, though.
I think you know
what I'm after, my lord.
All you've got to do
is give it to me.
Just give me the
gift of true laughter.
One joke and all my
information is at your disposal.
[giggling]
See to it, will you?
Certainly.
[UNDERTAKER] Oh? Having him
do your dirty work, then?
That's the trouble with
you upper-crust blokes.
Can't do anything
without your butlers, eh?
Well, it's all the same to me.
I'm only after a laugh.
Don't matter who gives it to me.
I'll take care of this.
Are you quite certain?
[CIEL] Sebastian, wait outside.
Go!
Do not attempt
to listen to this!
That is an order!
As you wish, my young lord.
[UNDERTAKER laughing]
Who would've thought
the Earl Phantomhive
would have that up his sleeve?
That kills me!
[giggles]
Whatever did you do?
[CIEL] Don't ask.
Performing tricks
on command like that
for the Queen's sake, my lord.
You truly are a dog, aren't you?
Shut it. That's enough.
There. I've paid
your ridiculous fee.
Now, what do you know
about the missing children?
Well, nothing.
What?
None of these poor,
unfortunate little souls
have been my customers.
Nor have I heard any rumors
that match their descriptions.
So you're saying
you don't know a thing
about this, and I
came here for nothing.
That's not how I would put it.
You see, what I know
is that I don't know.
[SEBASTIAN] A good point.
If he hasn't heard
anything about it,
that certainly
suggests that no one
in the underworld
killed them.
Would you not agree?
Yes.
And if their bodies haven't
been found in either circle,
then that suggests
they're still living.
In which case...
I suppose our only option
is to personally investigate
that travelling circus.
[CIEL]
We'll go there straight away.
Come, Sebastian.
Undertaker, contact me
if you learn anything further.
[UNDERTAKER]
Don't forget, my lord...
Each of us is
only given one soul.
Take good care of yours.
I hardly require such advice.
[UNDERTAKER]
Are you sure about that?
[UNDERTAKER giggling]
[CIEL] So this is it.
[SEBASTIAN]
It is quite elaborate.
[CIEL] Yes. But no more so
than any other circus.
[JOKER] Ladies and gentlemen!
Boys and girls of all ages!
Welcome to the
incredible, stupendous,
unparalleled Noah's Ark Circus!
I'm Joker,
this evening's ringleader.
A pleasure to meet yeh, it is!
[CROWD laughing]
A prosthesis?
Tonight, you're sure
to see performances
that'll stun and amaze yeh
and leave yeh breathless!
[CROWD applauding]
And now, with a great broze
from our very own
fire-breathing Jumbo,
the greatest show
of the century begins!
[JUMBO yells]
[JOKER] First up, we have our
two talented trapeze artists.
[JOKER] Peter and Wendy!
[JOKER] Our knife-thrower,
a perfect shot,
who never misses his target!
Dagger!
[CROWD applauding]
[JOKER] And now,
a daringly beautiful dance
by that rarest of rarities, our
serpent-man, the amazing Snake!
Their acts all seem
like standard fare to me.
Yes, and if there are children
being forced to perform,
there is no evidence
of it that I can see.
And our next performance...
If yeh'll look above yeh,
ladies and gents!
A death-defying walk
across the tallest tightrope
by the lovely
circus princess, Doll!
What would a circus
want with children
if they didn't intend
to use them as performers?
Could it just be a coincidence
that all the disappearances
happened on the
same route as the circus?
[CROWD gasps]
[JOKER] Last but not least, the
brightest star of our troupe!
I bring yeh the famous
tamer of wild cats!
[JOKER] Beast!
[CROWD cheering]
[JOKER]
This very special act
calls for some
audience participation.
Are there any volunteers, then?
[CIEL] It doesn't seem
as if there are any children
in the final act, either.
Excellent. This was a
complete waste of my time.
Why are you standing?
Did you see something?
[JOKER] Hohoho!
The gent in the tailcoat
there sure looks eager, eh?
Please, come up on stage!
Well? Step right on up, sir.
[CIEL]
I see what you're up to.
An opportunity for
a closer inspection.
Go on, then.
We simply must find a clue
to those disappearances.
And it seems our
best chance of doing so
is by learning all
we can about this circus.
All right.
You've established
initial contact,
but hundreds of eyes
are on you.
I'm curious to see how you
will conduct this investigation.
Very good, sir.
Now, if yeh'll please lie dow--
Ah!
Those big, round eyes
positively glow!
Your ears are so soft!
[CIEL] Of course!
Tigers are bloody cats!
I've never seen such
vivid black stripes before.
Breathtaking!
Oh dear,
your claws have gotten
a bit too big,
haven't they?
We shall have
to groom them, then.
Attractively plump paw pads!
I hope you'll
pardon my saying so.
[CROWD gasps, screams]
Release that man
immediately, Betty!
She has done nothing
to warrant punishment.
The fault lies with me.
I was so overcome by her beauty,
I behaved rudely.
Furthermore,
I doubt that
indiscriminate whipping
will prove an
effective way to tame her.
[BETTY growls]
[CROWD gasps, screams]
[BEAST] Betty!
Spit him out this instant!
[SEBASTIAN] Goodness,
you're a feisty one, aren't you?
I admire that.
[CIEL] I didn't intend
for you to take it that far.
My apologies, my lord.
I've lived many years,
but cats are
such fickle creatures,
I still can't
quite read their moods.
I simply adore that about them!
What were you thinking?
You attracted
unnecessary atten--
[sneezes]
Damn it!
You know perfectly well
that I'm allergic to cats,
you idiot!
Stay away from me!
Yes.
[JOKER] Oh! I found yeh!
Hullo, sir!
Bloke in the fancy tailcoat!
[JOKER] I caught you!
I'm sorry for earlier.
No, please, it is I
who should be apologizing.
[JOKER] Frightened me, the way
you traipsed up to that tiger
like she was a kitten.
Sure yer all right, then?
Not hurt anywhere?
Best look you over.
Happens we have
a doctor on staff.
He'll be glad to take
a look at you, I reckon.
All right?
Please, come on back.
Thank you.
I don't mind if I do.
[JOKER] It's just
back this way a tad.
The 'ole place is a
bit of a mess, I'm afraid.
Well, good evening there, Snake!
Do you know if doc's
back in the medical tent?
Oh, maybe making rounds, then.
[WENDY] Say, isn't that the lad
that got bitten by the tiger?
[PETER] Aye, that's him.
What a stupid little boy.
Good. There he is!
Oi, Doc!
Yes?
Joker, what can I do
for you tonight?
Is your hand acting up again?
Ha, no.
I brought a
different patient. See?
Wait, him? He's that bloke
from tonight's tiger act!
He was the one that
got bitten by Betty!
Hold on. What?
Goodness, how terrible!
We need to get you
to the infirmary!
[DOC] Are you quite certain
you've been bitten by a tiger?
I don't see any
gashes or broken skin.
It was just an
affectionate nip.
Affectionate, eh?
Nip, eh?
Well, I'm just glad
you're all right.
That could have been
a serious injury indeed.
[JOKER] Too true, too true!
Imagine, letting
a customer get injured!
If I did that,
the troupe leader would kill me.
I had the impression
you were the troupe leader.
No, not me.
Afraid I'm only the hired help.
The real leader's
downright scary.
Not someone you want ta cross.
Brave of you to say so.
That kinda talk
could get you in trouble.
Better be careful.
[BEAST] Hey Doc?
Do you got a minute
to look at my leg?
Hello, Beast!
Why are you here?
Same as you.
I came to have Doc
take a look at my leg, too!
It's just further proof that
we're destined to be together.
[BEAST]
You're that dandy from earlier!
What do you think you're doing?
After the way you ruined
my act, you ought to be--
[DOC] That's enough!
Speaking that way to a guest
is just plain unacceptable.
This wasn't his fault.
It was yours for not being
able to control Betty properly.
But he just walked up
and started touching her!
No excuses.
You are a professional, madam!
Let's take it easy there, Doc.
What's our guest
going to think of us,
yelling and screaming like this?
Joker's right.
Beast's leg is
what's really important,
so let's focus on that
instead of fighting, shall we?
You'll need to spend some time
retraining Betty
before the next performance.
Understood?
Yeah.
All right, then.
Show me your prosthesis.
A prosthesis?
You'll find us
Noah's Ark performers
are a bit of an irregular bunch.
Sort of a gathering of people
with a certain type of problem,
you might say.
Jus' look at me.
Missing an arm,
but the Doc 'ere gave me a
right fine replacement for it.
Pretty nice, don't you think?
That one needs
constant adjusting, though.
I should never have
let you choose the design.
Coming in every day,
asking me to look at it.
You craft prostheses
for the performers?
That is your main task?
[DOC] Essentially.
And quite a task it is!
I do everything, from carving
the parts to the final fitting.
What material do you use?
You said carving them.
Are they wooden, then?
Not wooden.
Ceramic, actually.
Ceramic?
I know what you're thinking,
but I use special materials,
so they're always
light and sturdy.
Feel this and
you'll see what I mean.
Indeed, I do.
Quite smooth
to the touch, as well.
[DOC] Of course.
And you'll notice that I use
spherical parts for the joints,
to ensure fluidity of movement.
[SEBASTIAN]
This is truly fine work.
I'm impressed.
What's this?
A seal of some sort?
What do you think
you're doing, pervert?
Oh...
I most humbly beg your pardon.
It seems I have
read you incorrectly.
I had not assumed
you were possessed
of such a
modest temperament.
Stop that!
Beast, stop at once!
Do something, you two.
You wretch!
How dare you even think about
touching my lady's skin?
Bastard!
Even I haven't touched it yet!
To be fair, I didn't
actually touch her skin.
It seems I did
touch a nerve, though.
Terribly sorry about that.
Put the knives away!
You'll shred the tent
at this rate!
I'm protecting Beast's honor.
That's more important
than some bloody tent!
[DAGGER] Blimey!
[whistles]
I'm gonna take you down a peg!
Ta-da!
All right,
that's enough fun for now!
What? That's not fair!
Come on, Beast.
Aren't you being a bit touchy?
[BEAST] Touchy?
But he's the one who--
[JOKER] Now, now.
It's such a handsome leg.
Can hardly blame the fellow
for wanting to feel it,
now, can yeh?
Go on, dear, take the flowers.
[JOKER] Well!
That was quite a feat
of acrobatics there, sir!
I reckon I would
hire yeh, I would.
Right quick!
Is your offer sincere?
[SEBASTIAN sighs]
Honestly, I might not
mind a change of occupation.
My current master is so spoiled,
I would be happy
to be done with him.
[sneezes]
[JOKER] Oh, "Master," is it?
A servant then, are yeh?
That's a bit of a surprise.
I thought for sure
you were one of the gentry,
dressed up all fine
and dandy as you are.
Me, one of the gentry?
Assuredly not.
Oh, no. You see, I am
simply one hell of a butler.
[SEBASTIAN] Now, then.
Was your offer a serious one?
If so, I would very much
like to take you up on it.
[JOKER] Not having
a jest at me, are yeh?
I think you'll learn
I'm not one for jests.
[laughing]
Funny ol' fellow, aren't yeh?
All right, me hansome.
Join us if yeh'd like.
We'd be happy to have yeh.
What are you doing?
You can't just make
a decision like that!
Hey, easy now.
You saw him.
He's got real talent.
Sorry.
If I may be so bold,
there's someone else I'd very
much like to introduce you to.
[sneezes]
If he's anything like you,
I'm sure he'll work out well.
I reckon we'll be
wanting to give him
an audition
all the same, though.
[SEBASTIAN] But of course.
I shall return tomorrow, then,
and bring him with me
so you can see if he suits.
Thank you for an excellent day.
Leaving us already?
There's no need to see me out.
I'll be fine.
[SEBASTIAN] Now, then.
[SEBASTIAN] Before one
reaches the medical tent,
there are nine tents,
and ten carts.
And further along, we have...
...tents of substantially
higher quality.
I'm already here.
Might as well inspect them.
I don't sense
the children at all.
However, I do sense
something a bit... off.
What is it?
[SNAKE] I'm afraid this area
is off-limits, my friend.
[UNDERTAKER]
What's this I hear, butler?
You're joining
the circus, are you?
I can't wait to see your act!
If you do the same bit
you showed me that time,
you'll bring the house down!
You know, the one where--
[SEBASTIAN] So sorry,
but we're out of time.
I'll just stop you right there.