[ASSOCIATION PRESIDENT]
Grell Sutcliff,
we've reached our verdict.
Yes, sir?
[ASSOCIATION PRESIDENT]
As of midnight tonight,
you will be released
from confinement.
We expect you to be on your
best behavior from now on.
You will apply yourself
solely to your work
and never again will you break
our established regulations.
[GRELL] Thank you.
[laughs]
[imitating chainsaw]
Oh yes!
Guess who's back? Me!
[GRELL laughing maniacally]
You're really
wound up, aren't cha?
I take it you're
glad to be released.
[GRELL] The beasts made me
clean and do chores
for my entire confinement.
It was positively ghastly!
You can't know how
I've longed for this day!
And this!
It feels so good
back in my hands!
This is the best death scythe
a reaper could ever have!
You're lucky you
still get to use it.
Getting permission wasn't easy.
If I hadn't asked that girl
in General Affairs about it...
Yes, I know.
You don't have
to harp on about it.
I'll pay you back
by working diligently,
and besides, this mission is
special, I need the proper tool!
Oh yes.
I expect tonight will be
very entertaining.
It won't be long now,
darling Bassy!
I'm coming!
[laughing maniacally]
I've been filled with regret
ever since that fateful day.
The same question keeps
playing through my mind.
"Why, oh why, couldn't
I have been by your side?"
"By my side?" "Fateful day?"
You loon. What the
devil are you on about?
[KELVIN] Alas, there is
no amount of regret
that can turn back time.
But I have realized something.
We can't go back, it's true,
but we can recreate history.
Here, take a look!
[KELVIN] It took me so long
to get everything just right.
[KELVIN] You know, my lord...
I remember it perfectly.
The day we met is crystal
clear inside my mind.
Indeed.
This is the culmination of what
began that day five years ago.
[BURTON]
Ah! Lord and Lady Kelvin.
I'm so delighted you came!
We wouldn't miss it,
Lord Burton.
It's quite the soiree
you're putting on, old chap.
And of course, I look forward
to speaking with you later
on our philanthropic efforts.
[BURTON] As do I.
Oh, yes, and...
There's somebody here
I want to introduce you to.
Let me see.
Ah, there he is!
Over there.
The Earl Phantomhive.
I wanted you to meet...
This is the Baron Kelvin.
It--It's a pleasure.
The pleasure is mine.
[VINCENT] Go on. Introduce
yourself to the baron now.
Yes, sir.
Hi, Baron Kelvin.
It's so nice to meet you.
My name's Ciel.
Do excuse him.
He can be a touch shy, you know.
His health is a bit fragile,
so I don't take him out much.
[CIEL]
Oh! Uncle Chlaus is here!
[CHLAUS] Well, Ciel! Guten Tag!
It's good to see you.
[VINCENT]
Chlaus! You're finally back!
Vincent, my friend!
The whole family is here?
That's rare, indeed!
[VINCENT]
He insisted on coming with us.
He's still weak
from his illness, though.
I say!
Why, it feels as if
you left us ages ago.
German beauties
require some patience.
Find it a chaste lot.
[VINCENT] Indeed?
He's more sympathetic
to philanthropic causes
than most men
of his age tend to be.
Why, he was even generous enough
to invite my orphans
to his estate
on Guy Fawkes Day and Christmas.
[BURTON]
Are you quite all right?
[KELVIN] There are no words
to express my rapture.
I couldn't take
my eyes off them.
They were all
porcelain and ebony,
as quietly beautiful as
the moon in the coal-dark night.
Sublime and forever
out of reach.
I knew immediately
that they were special.
[KELVIN]
After that I devoted myself
to investigating everything
related to the Phantomhives.
I wanted to know what it was
that made them so special.
And, oh,
the things I learned!
I uncovered their activities
as "villainous nobles."
Roses all have thorns,
don't they?
I was utterly captivated,
flooded with a helpless yearning
for their life of
intrigue and mystery.
Well, then,
what was so important
you felt it necessary
to call me back from Germany?
As it happens,
there's a little job
I'd like your assistance with.
Your jobs are never little!
Well, perhaps not,
but I believe you owe me
for that little matter
in Windsor two years ago.
You will at least
hear me out, won't you?
All right, fine!
Let's hear about
this job of yours.
Oh, hello,
Lord Phantomhive!
It's such a pleasure to see you!
Hello.
I, er...
We should go somewhere else.
This place is full
of interruptions.
Now, now, Diederich.
There's no need to be
so testy, is there?
Er, uh, I...
I hope you'll excuse me.
[DIEDERICH]
Who was that Alter man?
[VINCENT] Hmm?
[DIEDERICH] Someone you know?
He did seem to want to
strike up a conversation, so...
Probably?
[DIEDERICH] I thought as much.
[KELVIN] Yes, I see it now.
Those who are special
will forever be untouchable
to those who are not.
[DOLL] What is it, Father?
[DAGGER]
Why are you up so late?
Just stay away from me!
[KELVIN] I've never
realized how hideous I am!
I don't belong among
those paragons of beauty!
It's no use.
An ugly, common man
like me can never hope
to become part of that enchanted
world of night and shadow.
And what about him?
Will the young rose
one day bloom bright
with beautifully
dangerous thorns?
Will he be
without peer, as well?
Will he shine coldly,
like the moon in the
infinite midnight sky?
Forever distant. Out of reach.
Phantomhive!
I want... to touch him!
[KELVIN] I want...
I can't change
everything at once,
but in time you will have
the face that you desire.
Trust me. You are in good hands.
[KELVIN] I want
to be someone special.
Like a perfectly
crafted bisque doll.
With porcelain skin,
big jewel eyes,
a slight, fragile body.
That's what I will become!
What do I care if
my hag of a wife leaves me?
I'll grow more beautiful
by leading a beautiful life.
I'll become a man
worthy of his perfection!
[JOKER] Forgive me, Father.
I've distressing news to report.
It seems someone attacked the
Phantomhive manor last night.
No, it can't be!
Was anybody injured?
I'm afraid
they were all killed.
The earl, his wife
and child, as well.
[KELVIN] And that quickly, the
moon had vanished from my night.
How could this have happened?
Everything I'd done
had been for nothing.
My life had no meaning.
My days were dust,
and my nights were ashes.
Until...
What are you telling me?!
[PERVERTED NOBLE 8A]
Hush! Lower your voice.
You're shouting.
Just tell me. Is it true?
Yes. I am one hundred
percent certain.
It truly is the Phantomhive boy.
Our purchaser seems to have
happened upon him the other day.
Can you believe
our good fortune?
The chance to make
the Phantomhive heir
one of our lambs...
Everyone is simply having fits!
[chuckling]
Take me with you!
Surely you jest.
[KELVIN]
As quickly as it had vanished,
my lost moon returned to me.
Only now it was within my reach.
Lord Kelvin...
You can't, Father!
You've only just had surgery.
[KELVIN babbling]
Please, just take me with you!
I'm begging you!
I must be there!
Now, old chap.
No need to get so excited.
You were unlucky this time.
It happens to us all.
Wait, no!
Please, take me with you!
If it eases your mind,
the others and I
will be sure to lavish
extra affection
upon him for you.
If you'll excuse me.
You have to take me!
Please!
Stop this, Father!
You're not well.
You must take care of yourself!
I'm going! Just let me go!
[KELVIN] I've never
forgotten that pain.
I, who had given up
everything to meet you,
was the only one
who wouldn't be able to.
I couldn't understand
why cruel fate
was so bent on keeping us apart.
And then one day...
Just like that...
They were all gone.
You did it. You killed them.
It was you, was it not, my lord?
How I envy them
such a death!
To meet your end with the cold
moon gleaming above you--
How beautiful!
Please, I beg you!
Allow me to share their fate!
Look around!
I've prepared everything
exactly as it was then.
A perfect copy!
The ritual chamber.
The lambs in their cages.
And the most
important part of all...
You, my lord!
[gunshot]
No! Father!
[yelling]
[SEBASTIAN] I'm afraid
I'll have to ask you
to please stay out
of my young lord's way.
[JOKER yelling]
It hurts, my lord!
Please, it's such agony!
Kill me. I'm ready to die.
Only give me the same
death you gave them.
Is that asking so much?
You want the
same death they had?
Then you'd best prostrate
yourself like the worm you are
and beg a demon to kill you.
Please don't shoot!
Let him live, I beg you!
Whatever else he may be...
Whatever else he's done,
he's still our savior!
[JOKER] Abandoned by our
parents, ignored by the State,
we lived each day in fear of
starvation before he came.
And there are young ones
back at the workhouse still--
Our brothers and sisters
who rely on his support.
They'll die without him!
So I beg you! Please--
[CIEL] I see now.
That's why you kidnapped
all the children.
You were only too
happy to obey this worm
and sacrifice others' lives
to save your own skins.
That's right, we were.
[JOKER]
You nobles may not see it,
but England is a living hell
for people like us.
We had nothing--
No money for bread,
not even whole bodies with
which to protect our friends.
Then Father came.
He rescued us from the streets
and gave us the limbs we
needed to make our own way.
That's why we agreed
to do what he wanted.
Even if another hell
is waiting for us.
In all this time
I've never once doubted
that what we
were doing was wrong.
But I couldn't stop.
In my opinion,
it wasn't wrong.
You fought to
protect the only world
in which you felt safe.
What's wrong about that?
Really, justice is
nothing more than a line
drawn by those in power
to serve their own ends.
It falls to each person
to look after his own.
If you're careless,
you'll be robbed.
It's that simple.
You see, there are only two
kinds of people in this world.
Those who steal and
those who are stolen from.
Today I am the former:
The person who has come to steal
your futures away from you.
That's all this really is.
[laughing]
And I can't stop you!
But you know...
You'll lose something
precious tonight, too.
Even as we speak,
the troupe is on
its way to your manor.
[CIEL] Elizabeth!
Surely you don't
think it was pure luck
that we managed to abduct
all those children
without getting caught?
No, you see.
All the witnesses disappear.
[PETER] This is the place?
It's enormous.
[DAGGER] Looks like
we'll have a job of it
just finding the target's room.
We'd be better off splittin' up.
Fine. Go.
All right, then,
Beast and I can take this side.
[DAGGER] You comin'?
[BEAST] I'm comin'!
We really do have
a lotta area to cover.
We need to find him fast and
get out before the sun rises.
[FINNIAN] Who's there?
A guest, this late at night?
What are you doing out here?
I'm real sorry,
but you'll have to go.
My orders are not to let any
strangers into the manor
or even onto the estate
while me master's away.
If it's not too much trouble,
maybe you could
come back another--
[JUMBO growls]
At this point,
we're professionals.
If anyone crosses our path
on the job for any reason,
we eliminate them.
You're the target, of course,
but you're not there.
I wonder how many will be killed
while they search for you.
Witness elimination?
Exactly. Everybody,
even the servants.
[CIEL] My servants?
[chuckling]
What's so damn funny?
[CIEL] Your friends
are in for a surprise.
They're not just any servants.
They're Phantomhive servants.
I hate doing this.
[FINNIAN] You can't go in there.
It's loads of trouble
I'll be in if I let you.
Those are the
young master's orders.
Not to mention Sebastian's,
and you don't want
to cross him, I promise!
So what it
comes down to, mate,
is you're not goin' anywhere.
[loud pounding noise]
Oh my goodness!
Has the party gotten
started without me?
Mighty impatient, aren't we?
Never fear!
I won't be much longer, Bassy!
Aw! Such a mess.
Look at all that blood!
You were mean, though.
That hurt. And it's
not nice to hurt people!
Peter, Wendy,
there's something
wrong with this place!
Get out of here
while you still can!
[PETER] Jumbo?
[WENDY] What happened?
Impossible!
He took out Jumbo?
Please don't shout like that.
It's the middle of the night.
You'll wake the
Lady Elizabeth if you don't--
Oi! You killed Jumbo!
You're gonna bloody pay!
[FINNIAN]
Now you've got me riled up!
That was my favorite hat,
you know!
I need it to hide
something important.
That hat was given
to me by the young master.
[PETER] What the hell?
The young master never
locks me up like an animal.
He never makes me fight
in death matches with me mates.
This place is my home, too!
He's some kind of monster!
Slower than us, though.
So no matter what...
I will protect it!
Let's go!
We'll cut you in half!
[PETER] Wendy!
What the--Damn it!
[PETER]
From the roof to the west?
Bloody hell,
it's raining bullets!
How big an army does he have?
The little brat's
gonna have to wait.
Sorry, Wendy.
[PETER] What's going on?
I don't understand it.
These rifles don't
even have scopes on em.
They got her in one shot at
this distance without scopes?
[MEY-RIN] Always follow the
young master's instructions.
Welcome the master every day
with a manor
that is spotlessly clean.
That is a maid's job, after all.
When this place gets dirty...
I get rid of the filth!
[MEY-RIN] I missed!
I can't get
anywhere close to 'em.
How many shooters
can they possibly have?
Just one? There's only one?
Then that means...
All those rifles up there
were so she wouldn't
have to waste 'er time
reloading any of 'em.
[PETER]
Jumbo had the right of it.
We gotta clear
outta here right now.
[PETER]
These people are bloody mad!
[PETER] Hold on, though.
Is it possible?
Roof full of rifles or not,
random shooting
wouldn't work at that range.
[PETER] This is bad.
[MEY-RIN] It's useless.
No matter how far
you run, you little rat,
I can still see you
clear as day.
[glass shattering]
What... was that noise?
Oh, you're awake,
Lady Elizabeth.
Whatever is the matter?
I guess I was just startled.
Did you hear a loud noise
just a moment ago?
Oh ho ho!
I haven't heard
a peep all night.
You must have dreamed it, Lady.
It seemed so real, though.
But I suppose if you
didn't hear anything...
Now, please, my lady,
get back into bed
before you catch cold.
There is nothing to
worry about, I can assure you.
[ELIZABETH] All right.
[SEBASTIAN] I hate to do this,
but I must leave
the estate to you.
[TANAKA]
Oh, stuff and nonsense!
I'll do whatever
needs to be done.
You see...
I am simply one
hell of a butler.
[SEBASTIAN] What?
[TANAKA] Something wrong?
[SEBASTIAN] No, nothing.
Yes. Quite right!