[CIEL] Hello?
Isn't anybody there?
[CIEL] Father? Mother!
[CIEL panting]
Help me!
[panting]
Somebody please help! Anybody!
Ooh! Look at this one.
He's easily worth more
than two children, I'd say.
[screaming]
[CIEL] What is this?
Why are we in this cage?
Nobody is going to save us.
There is no God, is there?
[CIEL] Kill them!
Kill them! Kill them!
[SEBASTIAN] Goodness!
Look at you... so small.
I wasn't expecting
such a tiny master.
You have summoned me here today.
That can never be changed.
And nothing sacrificed
can ever be regained.
Now choose.
[CIEL] Then I choose.
[WILLIAM]
And where are you going?
You aren't to be wandering
about without your master.
[SEBASTIAN] I'm afraid that
my master is indisposed,
so it falls to me
to run his errands.
Surely even you
can understand that.
[WILLIAM] You must return
to the tent immediately.
I cannot allow you to move
independent of your master.
Even the smallest of mistakes
can lead to overtime,
and I so loathe overtime.
[SEBASTIAN] I am sorry
for the inconvenience.
However, I do have my duties
as a butler to consider.
Under no circumstances
will I allow you
to disturb my
young lord's sleep.
And, like me,
I feel quite certain
you would like to
avoid making a scene.
Would you not?
So I propose that
we make another deal.
You allow me one hour
free from your interference,
and in return I shall promise
never to eat a soul
in your territory again.
One hour is all I ask.
[WILLIAM] No, that won't do.
Demons seduce their prey
into darkness with sweet words.
It's the oldest cliché
of your kind.
I was afraid that
would be your decision.
Oh, well, it is no matter.
I shall simply explore other
means of getting what I need.
[DOLL]
Got the ice. How is he?
Asleep at present.
Seems to be having a devil
of a nightmare, though.
[distant rain]
[ANGELINA] So why this?
What brought you here?
You must've had
other options in life
besides policing
England's underworld.
I'm sure my sister, your mother,
wanted something else for you.
And yet--
I did it for myself.
[CIEL] The need for
revenge is a funny thing.
It won't bring the dead back.
Nor will it
bring them happiness.
I want to find
the people responsible
and make them
experience the same
pain and humiliation
that I suffered.
That can't be too difficult
a motivation to understand.
[ANGELINA] My darling nephew,
how unfortunate
this turned out to be.
If only you had been
willing to let it go,
we could have
played chess again.
[ANGELINA] Damn you, brat!
You shouldn't have
been born in the first place!
[CIEL] Stop, Sebastian!
[ANGELINA] I can't kill him.
I can't kill
their beloved child.
[CIEL] One wrong move
can cost you your life.
Just like chess.
She hesitated and
lost sight of her next move.
That's all there is to it.
So I won't make the
mistake of hesitating.
Now that's what
I expect to hear.
Always skillfully
manipulate your pieces.
That's how you survive.
Use me and Madam Red.
Any piece within your reach.
Even if the bodies
of your pawns pile up
at the foot of your throne.
Because if the king falls,
this game is over.
I have already said
I won't hesitate.
Nor will I regret
the moves I've made so far.
That I vow.
As for you, you are the one man
who can never betray me.
The one man who can
never leave my side.
That is an order.
[SEBASTIAN]
Yes, my lord.
Sebastian?
That's right.
He's not here,
because I ordered him
to identify the
man with the ring.
It was just a dream.
[BEAST] Joker.
What's wrong, lass?
Having trouble sleeping, are ya?
[BEAST] Let's stop this.
[BEAST] We're running
a successful circus.
We don't need anything more.
We can start over together
and wash our hands
of the rest of this mess.
We'll run someplace
where Father can't find us!
Someplace "over the
hills and far away," huh?
Yeh know we cannot do that.
And I don't have time
to talk about it.
Sorry, lass.
[BEAST] Please wait!
[JOKER] Yeh all right?
This isn't like you.
We made this here decision
together, didn't we?
Said we'd do
whatever we had to,
no matter how hard it was.
To protect what really matters.
I know, but I hate this.
I can't stand to
watch you suffer so.
It hurts me.
Joker, You must know that I--
[JOKER] That's enough!
There's no turning back.
You know that, same as me.
Here, take this.
It's a mite bit
chilly out tonight.
Please, Joker.
Good night, Beast.
[BEAST sobbing]
[SEBASTIAN]
Oh, my. What happened?
Do I hear someone weeping?
It's none of your
damn business, Black!
Just piss off, all right?
It's no use, my dear,
I'm so sorry.
Pursuing a man like that
is a waste of time
for a lady like you.
He can't return your feelings,
so he decides to be kind and
play the considerate gentleman.
All the while knowing such
behavior only hurts you more.
Rather cruel of him,
don't you think?
How long have you
been allowing him
to make you cry like this?
Carrying on a one-sided affair
that will lead to
nothing in the end.
And what would you
know about it, huh?!
Not a thing, I'm sure.
However, there
is something I do know, my dear.
If you would be interested,
I know how to take your mind
off the pain for a while.
That's rubbish! Let me go!
[SEBASTIAN]
I am serious, I assure you.
What good is constant sadness?
Why should you suffer
this kind of agony?
[SEBASTIAN]
He has trapped you, my dear.
Unable to move forward.
Shout all you like, but he'll
never turn to look at you.
You poor, sweet thing.
Haven't you been through enough?
Wouldn't you like to
forget him for a while?
Forget his cruelty
and his kindness.
[BEAST] I don't...
[SEBASTIAN]
Why not forget everything?
Even if it won't last
any longer than tonight.
Choose pleasure, not pain.
It is a sweet poison.
Take it into
your deepest depths.
[WILLIAM] You seduce your prey
into darkness with sweet words.
You whisper and cajole.
Cleverly, sweetly, softly.
So that it won't notice
the monster behind the mask.
And then, you devour it.
You... You have
a demon's tongue.
[SEBASTIAN] I simply want
to know that secret place.
The one you keep hidden.
Deep inside.
This is the way
he's always been.
The words I need are
the only ones he can't say.
Things changed when Father
put him in charge of the circus.
He grew distant,
even from his closest friends.
[SEBASTIAN] Who is "Father"?
That's what we call
the man who's our patron.
He paid to develop
our prosthetics.
He gave us new bodies,
made us whole again.
[SEBASTIAN]
Is that what this is, then?
Father's seal?
[BEAST] Yes.
The seal marks us
for who we are.
We all belong to Father.
Very interesting.
And what might his name be?
Why do want to know that?
[SEBASTIAN]
I want to know all about you.
He's an important part
of your life.
[SEBASTIAN] Besides,
we're on intimate terms now.
Are we not?
[BEAST gasps]
[SEBASTIAN]
You can tell me his name.
What's the harm?
His name is...
Father's real name is...
You?
And a good morning
to you, my lord.
Yes.
[SEBASTIAN] Your fever
seems to have come down.
[CIEL] Freckles must've
gone off to breakfast.
Are you on the mend?
How are you feeling?
Not well yet, but I am
better than yesterday.
[coughing]
[SEBASTIAN]
Here, drink some water.
You appear to be
missing your gloves.
Your nails and our
contract seal are showing.
Ah, yes...
I'm afraid I might have
soiled them just a touch.
The errand I gave you.
I assume you have been able
to complete it by this point?
[SEBASTIAN] Yes, of course.
There's no need to
remain here any longer.
We can leave unobtrusively while
everyone is breaking their fast.
Did you sleep well?
Not to worry, my lord,
your secret is safe with me.
I shan't inform Lady Elizabeth
that you shared your bed
with another young lady
last night, I assure you.
Wha--
[SEBASTIAN]
Have a care, my lord.
We can speak more
once we're home.
[SEBASTIAN] We've finished
our business here,
so we'll be taking our leave.
I trust that's not a problem.
Not at all.
So long as your master
is with you,
where you go is
of no concern to me.
By all means, be on your way.
Now, without those distractions,
I can get my work done
in an orderly fashion.
[SOMA]
Ciel! Where have you been?
You left for two whole days
without even bothering
to tell anybody!
It's very good to see you.
Where I have been
is none of your affair.
[coughing]
[SOMA] What is wrong?
You look as pale as a ghost.
[CIEL] It's nothing, I'm fine.
Leave me be.
It sounds serious!
I think you're lying!
You've obviously
caught a very bad cold.
Do you have a fever, too?
No. I've no fever.
You're lying again!
[CIEL] No, I'm not.
[SOMA] Ciel!
I am surprised, my lord.
You're even fonder of secrets
and lies than I'd thought.
To think you've been
chronically ill since infancy
and I'd no idea.
That is quite a secret
to keep, indeed.
I'm curious as to why
you didn't tell me.
You didn't ask,
so I didn't tell.
It's as simple as that.
And I've grown
out of it, anyhow.
[SEBASTIAN]
A childhood affliction, then?
Perhaps.
Still, there's no harm
in being cautious, is there?
I'll acquaint myself
with the latest
medical texts on asthma,
just in case.
Is that part
of your "aesthetic"?
A proper butler is
prepared for any situation,
as well you know.
[CIEL] Hmm.
If we're done
chatting about my health,
perhaps you could
report what you've gleaned
from your research this morning.
[SEBASTIAN] There is a coat
of arms that matches the seal.
It belongs to the Baron Kelvin.
[CIEL] Kelvin?
[SEBASTIAN]
Do you know him, then?
[CIEL] Well, we certainly
don't have a close,
personal acquaintance,
as I don't much fancy
"philanthropists."
But I think we may
have been introduced before.
At a party the
previous earl took me to.
Well, no matter.
His name is the only thing
we really require.
[CIEL] We're going out.
Ah. Yes, my lord.
[CIEL] Uh...
[SOMA] Ohoho!
Not so fast, Ciel!
This townhouse is
under my supervision.
Do not think you will
escape it so easily!
[SOMA] Whatever you say, I know
you've caught a nasty cold.
As viceroy of this estate
and your dear friend,
I cannot allow you to venture
out in your current state.
[CIEL] Don't be daft!
Since when are we
"dear friends"?
Agni!
Do not let Ciel past you!
[AGNI] Jo ajna.
Listen, you bloody nuisance.
I have important work to do!
I haven't got the time
to play these infantile games!
[coughing]
Now, step aside!
A sick person's
only job is to stay in bed
and be looked after.
I've a stronger
constitution than you!
I can manage on--
[coughs]
Lord Phantomhive!
I beg you, please return
to bed, my lord.
Your symptoms suggest
that you suffer from asthma.
You cannot possibly
be well in this state!
Don't you presume to touch me!
Sebastian, get these two
out of my way!
Very good, my young lord.
[AGNI] Sebastian, you should
hang your head in shame!
You call yourself Lord
Phantomhive's khansama?
Sorry?
I speak as a
fellow khansama, and more,
as your friend
and one who respects you.
The health of our masters
is our first concern!
Don't you think you
are bound by duty
to stop Lord Phantomhive
for the sake of his health
even if doing so
goes against his orders?
We ensure our masters remain
in good spirits and good health,
no matter what we have to do.
As you know...
That is the butler
aesthetic, Sebastian!
[SEBASTIAN] I've long
considered my role to be
the fulfillment of
my young lord's wishes,
but you make
an excellent point.
Yes, indeed.
Perhaps there is something to
your way of thinking after all.
Wait!
Don't let him turn you!
My orders are--
Now that that's sorted,
let's get you to bed.
Come!
Nursed back to health
by a crown prince?
You should be flattered, Ciel!
Agni! Porridge and some herbs.
[AGNI] Yes, at once!
[CIEL] No, you can't just--
[SOMA] Ciel's khansama,
bring fresh nightclothes
and ice packs!
[SEBASTIAN] Of course.
[CIEL] Oi!
There.
I feel much better, don't you?
Yes.
[CIEL] I've no time
to play invalid.
I'm busy!
We've made substantial
progress on the case.
Set your mind at ease.
You can afford some time
for rest and recuperation.
[SEBASTIAN]
My, you're burning up.
[SEBASTIAN] Rest now.
Let it wait until tomorrow.
[loud slap]
I told you not to
trust outsiders, didn't I?
But... But I thought--
I thought what was the harm?
He's just a boy and he said
he's got no place else to go!
And he promised me!
We even shook on it!
[PETER] I knew you didn't have
a thick enough skin for this!
[JUMBO] Peter, wait, hold on.
[PETER] What is it?
Smile's not the only one
who's disappeared.
Suit and Black
have gone missing, too.
[JUMBO] As far as we know,
they could work for the Yard,
which means it's dangerous
for us to stay here.
[DAGGER] Yeah, that's true.
So, what do we do?
Joker's already
gone to see Father.
[PETER] We agreed we'd do it
without him if we had to.
The decision's already made.
[JUMBO] We shouldn't forget
what Father said, either.
Something about
this target's special.
If we fail...
I imagine he'll be very angry.
[PETER] Jumbo's right.
It's time for us to strike.
We gotta get this thing done
before we pack up
and leave London, anyway,
'cause this is the closest town
to the target's home.
All right?
It's almost morning now
so we can't go tonight.
Tomorrow, then.
Everybody better be ready.
[PETER] Now that that's settled,
we should report to Joker.
[BEAST] I'll go after him.
[WENDY] No, not you.
If you go we'll be down
a fighter we might need.
Doll, you should go instead.
Whatever you say.
[BEAST] Come with me, then.
We'll get you a horse.
[horse whinnying]
I'm real sorry about this.
It's all my fault.
You're not to blame, Doll.
What?
Nothing. Never mind.
Off you go, now.
Best get to Joker.
[WILLIAM] Lovely.
It isn't enough I'm being forced
to clean up after a colleague.
No. It's also a task
that's outside
my administrative expertise.
[WILLIAM] Not to mention the
dreadful month of night duty
that no civil servant
should ever be made to suffer.
Honestly!
[WILLIAM] Ah, well.
At least it will
all be over tomorrow.
[SEBASTIAN]
Everything will end tomorrow.
[SEBASTIAN] Yes, indeed.
We shall end this tomorrow.
[SEBASTIAN] Agni, I am deeply
grateful for your advice.
[AGNI] No.
I'm afraid I spoke out of turn.
[SOMA] Not at all!
Ciel needs better care!
[AGNI] Well, maybe you
could sing him a lullaby?
[SEBASTIAN]
Ah, that might be nice.
[AGNI] Then sing we shall.
Ready, and...
[SEBASTIAN, AGNI]
♪ Rock-a-bye... ♪