Surely you know the truth,
who's responsible for Shinji's death.
Yes.
You're finally finished pretending you can't see.
After all it endured to grow, breaking it
down proved more troublesome than I expected.
In a perfect world, you would have
done it by personally betraying Sakura,
but it pays to have a backup plan.
Backup plan? He's dead.
It's a half-assed awakening
that retains its humanoid form.
Though this is quite possibly the
first time she has been worthy of praise.
Zouken, where is Sakura?
Hey, what does it feel like, being a sister?
I'm not ungrateful to you, either.
Before you, that girl endured everything,
but you taught her how to desire other humans
and gave her a reason to fight back.
Now that she's killed her older brother,
she cannot stand still any longer.
Next, she will claim Archer's
soul from the Einzberns' Holy Grail,
and then she will take the key to the gate,
and it will all be over.
Zouken!
Now, Sakura, you shall finally accept the shadow.
As you wish, grandfather.
Sakura.
I wondered if you'd be here, big sister.
Of course. I'm not like Shirou, you know.
I wouldn't run off to save you.
And I knew you'd be back.
You were going to come back for Illya sooner or later.
You're so mean, big sister.
Honestly, am I that bad of a person?
Of course you are.
you were too weak to trust the
one person who swore to protect you,
so you ran away without a word like a coward.
You're right.
That's the person I've always been.
But that's all over.
I'm not weak anymore.
From here on, I'll protect Shirou.
I'm strong.
Nothing can stop me, not even you.
Verschmelzen!
I wouldn't do that.
If you use that kind of Magecraft,
you'll cause the whole house to fall apart.
Delicious.
Your magical energy's wonderful, big sister.
Except...
it's not enough, not yet.
If I don't finish you,
you'll get back up.
Because you're a hero.
I have no choice.
Sakura!
Shirou...
Why?
Sa...
Tohsaka!
What is this?
Why are you rushing to protect my sister...
without saying a word to me?
Why aren't you scolding me?
You saw what happened to my brother, what I did.
You're wrong.
Zouken set you up. It wasn't...
I killed him.
You see, Shirou, I'm crazy.
In fact, I have been since the very beginning.
Sakura.
Isn't it painful to be with me?
Isn't it, Shirou?
That's why I had no choice but to get far away from you.
But that doesn't work for me,
'cause you're the only thing that makes me happy.
I can't live without you.
And you can't distance yourself from me, either,
because you can't betray yourself
any more than you already have.
Which is why I have to kill you.
Your suffering will end,
and you'll be by my side forever.
This was the last order you gave me, Sakura,
"Protect Shirou, no matter the circumstances."
Think you can stop me? Bad girl.
Sakura, don't follow this path.
You'll find nothing at the end,
nothing but darkness, and you'll be all alone.
But I'm here. Follow me, and
I'll guide you back to the light.
Sakura...
You serve no Master now.
Rider, I'm going to absorb you.
No, don't!
I have all the power I need,
but I'll make an exception and put you to use like Saber.
Stop it, Sakura. That's enough.
You can take me with you.
Illya!
Have you lost your mind?
You realize if you come with me, that I will kill you.
But it's useless to resist.
I mean, you're too powerful for anyone to stop you.
I'm too...
powerful?
You want the last key, but it's not here.
I'm afraid you'll have to come
back to my castle with me to get it.
That's the only way you can open the gate.
All right, then.
Whatever you're planning, I'll play along.
Shirou, please don't let me see you again.
I'll have no choice but to kill you.
It's over.
I've had a lot of fun, Big Brother.
Goodbye now.
Please, Saber! Let me through!
What do you think you're going to do?
Sakura will claim the Holy Grail
one way or another.
Even if she has to die in order to do it,
Sakura Matou will find salvation.
This is your last warning.
If you're still stubborn enough to try to follow us,
I will cut off your head.
The outcome has been decided.
Actually, I suppose it's been decided for a long time now.
This Holy Grail War was altered.
There should only be one Holy Grail.
But in this place, a second Grail has already existed.
Its vessel was deemed fit to
hold the contents of the Grail,
and thus it became one itself.
If that vessel had been unworthy,
surely it would have become
nothing more than a mound of flesh.
But the stage is now set,
and soon I will have my answer.
The birth will reveal it to me.
If there are some thing that simply
can't be seen from the audience...
well, then, I shall rise onto the stage myself.
Kotomine!
It's Tohsaka.
Help her.
You're awake.
Is it difficult to move?
Kotomine.
Where's Tohsaka?
She had been drained of all her magical energy.
She'll be fine by tomorrow.
I buried her.
buried?
In the yard on the Tohsaka estate.
The soil there is special.
Oh, okay.
Thanks for the help,
but I gotta get going.
Care to tell me where you're headed?
Illya let Sakura take her.
We'd be dead if she hadn't.
But now...
I take that to mean that Sakura
Matou has become your enemy.
Come with me.
I suspect Zouken's objective is to possess Sakura
once she becomes nothing but a hollow shell.
Therefore, if we're going to stop that from happening,
we must rescue Illyasviel
and defeat Zouken before it's too late.
At least for the time being, you
and I have that objective in common.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I'll help.
Now let's get going.
Wait a second. What about Rider?
Out of the question.
Even without Command Spells, they're still connected.
We'll have no chance if Sakura
catches on before we get there.
...two nights since the mysterious
disappearances in Fuyuki City.
The total number of missing persons
is still unknown, as is the cause.
A power outage that coincided with the event,
lasting several hours appears to have
been centered around the New City train...
You know, if it were him,
he wouldn't have let Sakura live
long enough for any of this to happen.
For the sake of "justice,"
your father felt he needed to detach
himself from all of his emotional entanglements.
I disliked Kiritsugu Emiya's way of life.
It was difficult to witness.
He abandoned everything he had since the very beginning,
while I never had anything that
would have been worthy of sacrifice.
It's all the same in the end,
but the path we took to get there made a difference.
We were so similar, and yet I despised him.
If you're going to throw it away,
why bother with it in the first place?
But he kept trying to hold on to it.
Even after discarding it, he picked it back up.
But truly, your father knew happiness.
Kiritsugu was happy?
Love yourself. Love your neighbors.
Forgive sins. Accept punishment.
All the nourishment a life needs.
The things people of your ilk call "happiness,"
they never brought me any joy.
That's all I can tell you.
Then I have a question.
Why did you save Sakura?
Humans are meant to die,
but she wasn't the only thing that was dying.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have
done nearly so much to intervene.
However, it is my role to bless the
birth of the darkness inside of Sakura Matou.
Are you insane?
That shadow thing, it kills people.
And yet it still hasn't been born.
Were that the case, it would be assigned
sins and punished for them accordingly.
But it still deserves a birth.
Or perhaps you believe the son of a criminal
is also a criminal before ever leaving the womb
and must therefore be aborted?
Let me pose you this question.
When it comes to Sakura,
you can't deny that she's quite literally a man-eater.
Now that you know that, do you still intend to help her?
Countless people have lost their lives to her.
Even she must be ashamed of what she has become.
Wouldn't it be fair to assume, then,
that she would be happier in death?
It would also grant her atonement
for the lives she's taken.
No, that doesn't make things better.
Doesn't it?
I suppose that means you won't be
following in Kiritsugu Emiya's footsteps, then.
I'll check it out.
Beginning synchronization.
Tracing basic structure.
Tracing component materials.
On the third floor...
in the room on the left.
Sakura.
That's enough.
Don't lose sight of your priorities here.
Yeah, I know.
Well then, Shirou Emiya...
do you have any experience with mountain climbing?
Miss Illya, are we really going to be fully
preparing your formal attire for these people?
Did you forget?
We only have one purpose,
to make sure the Holy Grail is completed.
As long as it's suitable,
the vessel doesn't have to be me.
Did you really have to throw me at the window?
You looked pathetic plastered to the wall with one arm.
I thought I'd speed things up a bit.
We don't have all night.
What are you doing here? Who are you?!
Are you thieves?
Oh, no, not at all! We're not bad guys!
Shirou.
Illya...
Why are you here?
You need to go home.
There's nothing left for you to do now.
Just forget about Sakura, and leave everything to me.
Go on.
This is my burden to bear.
So stupid.
What is it?
That doesn't matter.
I don't care what you think your burden is!
You can try to act all tough,
you can try to pretend you're all right,
but I won't be fooled by any of that!
I'm not trying to act tough!
I'm the Holy Grail, you dummy!
That is exactly what I'm talking about!
You are Illya!
So don't sacrifice yourself,
not for the sake of someone else!
You say that,
but look who's talking.
Let's go.
I can't do this.
I know it will never work.
As I said before, we don't have all night.
Hold on! Stop! Put me down!
Uh, shouldn't we...
This castle is where we belong.
Don't worry about us.
We entrust Illya to you.
You okay?
You always surprise me.
Jumping from the third story without using Magecraft.
Are you suicidal?
Give me a break! I thought I'd be able to pull it off.
Archer is influencing your mind.
You came for me after all.
Shirou.
Let's move.
He's fast.
But I can keep up.
Berserker.
I guess I was wrong about you.
You're not just a doll.
Take her and go.
Emiya...
if you decide to rescue a woman, be sure not to kill her.
Seeing her die before your eyes,
it'll haunt you for the rest of your life.
Okay, let's go.
The White Holy Grail will not escape.
I need her. I have a wish for it to grant as well.
Is he looking for me?
Shirou...
you have to leave me.
Huh? I can't do that!
What a pleasure to see you again, Kirei.
Zouken Matou.
Well...
I wasn't expecting you to show up.
You're finished.
Do me a favor, and show him some mercy, Assassin.
It's strange that I'm reminded of it now,
but since the moment I was born, I've had a flaw.
For I have always found happiness in agony.
Despair is what gives me pleasure.
I know what that makes me.
Any creature that lives their life in
that manner is the very definition of evil.
It's a terrible flaw.
But even though I knew I was
a heretic, I had common sense.
I wanted to change
and did everything I could to accomplish it.
When nothing worked, I made one final attempt.
I fell in love with a woman.
Or more accurately, I tried to fall in love.
We even had a child together.
But it didn't matter.
Try as I might, I never could love you.
You're wrong. You love me, and I know you always have.
Noble Phantasm...
Zabaniya!
It's all over.
Impossible. You bastard!
Know this.
I will kill. I will let live.
I will harm, and I will heal.
None shall ever be able to escape my grasp.
None shall ever be able to escape my sight.
Damn you. Get off me!
Be crushed.
I welcome all who have grown old or been defeated.
Devote yourself to me, learn from me, obey me, and rest.
Do not forget song, do not forget prayer,
and most of all, do not forget me.
I am light, and I shall relieve all your burdens.
Aha! Are you going to kill me?
Your solace is in my hands.
I shall pour oil unto your sins, and I shall mark you.
For it is only through death
that one can be granted the gift of eternal life.
Beg forgiveness now.
I, the reincarnation, shall absolve you.
What will that change, huh?
There is no salvation in you.
Kyrie eleison.
Using the holy words of Scripture
to attack the spirit itself.
My lord's only weakness.
How did you survive?
You were his natural enemy.
You were already corrupted, weren't you?
That was my mistake.
See? Look at you. You're crying.
Don't misunderstand me.
I won't deny that I was saddened,
but it wasn't her death that caused my tears.
If she was going to die,
I wanted to kill her with my own hands.
Shirou?
Illya, are you all right?
Y-yes.
You have to run. Go on.
I'm the only one Berserker's after.
Get out of here!
A big brother's gotta protect his sister.
You can't...
It's okay.
You called me your brother, so that's what I am.
I'll protect you.
Blood or not, you're my little sister.
Shirou...
you can't use Archer's arm.
You won't come back!
I know.
You're going to die.
Wrong.
I'm using it so I stay alive.
Why?
Why do you always put yourself through so much suffering?!
You have never done anything wrong! It's not fair!
Not true.
I've done plenty wrong, no matter what you think.
But...
thank you.
I don't know what using this
arm will do, but I have to try.
It might take away all my memories,
the fact that I swore to protect Sakura
or why I came here, to bring Illya back with me.
Doesn't matter.
He trusted me with this for a reason,
so I'll do what I have to.
I'm taking him down.
That okay?
My mind and body crumble,
and I feel nothing.
I can't remember why I'm here.
I can't remember why this is happening.
I can't remember what I'm fighting for.
Think you can keep up?
Who the hell do you think you're talking to?
Are you confused?
That's my question to you!
You keep up with me!
Trace on!
Trigger off.
Nine Lives Blade Works!
Protect her for me.
Shirou.
It's Saber.
How does it feel,
someone clutching your heart in their grasp?
Oh, I see.
It seems you died ten years ago.
And you only came back because of...
Uh, I ate him the other day.
The man in gold he was showered
with the contents of the Holy Grail.
But because he couldn't be corrupted by it,
all his dark energy flowed into you, his Master.
Isn't that right?
Seems you've changed, Sakura Matou.
Yes, I certainly have.
I've changed a lot.
I'm not the same Sakura that I used to be.
Now she doesn't exist.
She was far too weak.
You don't need to hide it from me.
What do you mean? Hide what?
You're not some kind of alternate personality.
The version of you intoxicated with violence
is still Sakura Matou.
You're the one who made me this way, priest.
I won't deny it.
I had my own reasons to keep you alive.
And just look at you now.
You've met all my expectations,
and very soon the Avenger will be born.
It was almost easy.
It hasn't felt easy at all!
You have no idea what I've had to endure,
the pain that it's caused!
No, I don't.
And I don't need to know.
Berserker?
Please, no.
Don't come inside.
Sakura is calling.
Lucky for you, I have to go.
No. It's not luck.
You earned this for yourself...
for now.
Shirou!
Shirou.
It's all right.
It's all right now.
Let's go home.
That's what happens when I use it.
Oh, you're finally awake. How nice.
Tohsaka!
You're all right.
Of course I am.
Especially compared to say, you?
Well, at least you're still alive.
Wait. What is that?
Oh, it's... it's, um...
It's something special.
I need to keep it until the end.
What the...
That was weird.
What did I say?
Hold on to it.
Looks like there's a little magical energy left.
Could be useful.
Sounds like that was your plan anyway.
Um, yeah.
Now hurry up, and get ready, okay?
We're heading out now.
You are the last two masters left in this Holy Grail War,
so I'm going to tell you the truth.
I'll cut to the heart of the matter.
It should explain some things.
However, the first part is
nothing that concerns either of you.
You know the rules of the War.
Using seven Heroic Spirits, participants kill
each other to determine the rights to the Grail.
But the truth is those rules are only a ploy.
In fact, Masters are merely the catalysts
to summon the Servants to this world.
Only the Heroic Spirits are
required to complete the Holy Grail.
Their souls are harvested and placed into
the Lesser Grail created by the Einzberns.
The Greater Grail requires them in order to be activated.
Uh, the Greater Grail?
It's a magic circle on the Tohsaka family land,
the overseer of the Holy Grail War system.
It all started 300 years ago.
The three founding families,
Einzbern, Makiri, and Tohsaka,
wanted to use the Holy Grail
to reach outside of the world.
That's the true objective,
the ritual once thought lost to the Einzberns,
great magic that could make true immortality possible.
The Grail of Heaven,
Heaven's Feel.
The secret to materializing the soul.
Now then...
the rest of the story does concern you two.
You mean Sakura, right? Please, Illya.
I need to know what the hell's happening to her.
Zouken has changed her,
because he is trying to get control of something,
something called Avenger.
It's the eighth class within the Holy Grail War.
It fused with Sakura
and used her to project those black shadows,
Angra Mainyu.
It's a story from an ancient village
that practiced Zoroastrianism.
The people wished to find a way for
humans to live a pure and just life
and believed that, to do this,
they must first be freed of all their evils.
So they randomly selected one unlucky young man
and singled him out.
They placed all the sins of the world on his shoulders,
using his "wickedness"
to prove the "goodness" of all humans except him.
They tortured him,
and thus a hero was born.
He was resented by the people,
yet worshipped as a god at the same time,
someone who was no one,
the anti-hero, Angra Mainyu.
During the Third War, the Einzbern family
summoned Angra Mainyu to act as their Servant.
However, he was very weak.
He was quickly defeated and
absorbed into the Greater Grail.
And then, as a result,
the Holy Grail accepted a certain wish.
It is an existence made by those
who willed its evil into being.
And now because of the Grail,
it has become a reality.
It is the embodiment of all the world's evil.
Given the chance, it will curse the
lives of every human on the planet.
That is the true identity of the shadow.
At the end of the last War,
Kiritsugu destroyed the Grail.
Because of that, there was no
way for Angra Mainyu to be born.
It was left inside the Greater Grail.
Part of it attached itself to Kirei Kotomine,
and Zouken turned Sakura into an artificial Grail.
He took a shard of what remained
and planted it inside her.
But Avenger's still a Servant,
and a Servant must obey its Master.
And since Zouken controls Sakura,
he made her a Master,
giving him control of Avenger.
Master...
and Servant.
Optimistically, she has half a day left.
If that thing is fully born,
she will transform completely.
No one will be able to save her.
No one will be saved at all.
Okay, Shirou, I want you to do something
before we go running into enemy territory.
To be honest, you may have saved
us all by bringing Illya back.
The two of you are going to need to work together.
Take the memories of the Einzberns
and the memories of the land where the Leyline flows.
Use them to project a special weapon,
the Jeweled Sword.
Why? What is it?
The Tohsakas have held that
treasure's secret for generations,
and now...
we're going to use it to fight Sakura.
All right.
The Azoth Blade closely resembles it.
I've infused it with ten years of my mana.
Use it to support your projection.
Shirou...
tell me the truth.
How long do you think you can last?
I honestly don't know.
But hey, I'll keep going as long as I'm alive.
I'm gonna be okay.
Focus on the sword.
Only look at what you need to.
Uh, okay.
The ocean?
Shirou.
Shinji?
No.
It's not here.
Let's jump further ahead.
Little bit further. Let's go.
Uh, what...
...all forms of evil eradicated.
To do this...
This is the right place.
Shirou, don't take your eyes off of him.
This objective has my full support.
Because they wish to reach the Root,
the three members, Einzbern, Tohsaka, and Makiri,
will cooperate with each other to open the path.
Declare your contributions to this cause.
So declared, the Tohsakas offer the
spiritual grounds to build the Holy Grail.
So declared, The Makiris offer the Command
Spell for the Servants so they may be sacrificed.
It is so declared, the Einzberns offer
the magic circle to reach the Third Magic.
Good. I, Kischur Zelretch Schweinorg,
will be acting as the witness for this ritual.
You may now begin.
Our gate connecting to the Root...
be released.
Be released.
Shirou!
You look terrible,
like death itself.
Uh, R-Rider?
I've been watching you from a distance.
My sworn duty is to protect you, Shirou Emiya,
but you've created a weapon to use against Sakura.
As long as you plan on bringing harm to her,
I cannot protect you.
So, what, you here to kill me?
Shirou, you should know.
Sakura summoned me without the use of a catalyst.
When that happens, the Servant that is
chosen is very close to the Master's state.
Honestly...
I didn't want to turn her into a monster.
But now...
Shirou, I cannot let you make Sakura suffer.
I'm not gonna kill her.
I'm going to save her.
I promise. I'm on Sakura's side.
No matter what comes to pass, I'll choose her.
On her side?
Is this your answer to my question?
But can I trust you?
For this to work, there's someone I still have to beat,
and I could really use your help now.
Do we have a fair chance of winning?
Yes.
Then I'm with you.
Your Servant, Rider.
It's only temporary,
but I shall become your wings.
We'll go as far as we can for Sakura.
For a second there, I thought
you were actually coming back.
But you only flew out your shadow.
Flexing our muscles, are we? How cute.
Big sister...
please take Shirou, and run away.
If you do that for me,
I promise I'll give my life to kill it.
I gotta ask, even though I know the answer,
do you want to cut ties with Angra Mainyu?
No, I don't.
For the first time in my life, I have power.
Even if I did want to let go of it, I couldn't.
So you're saying if I take Shirou away,
you'll stop this by killing yourself
and taking Angra Mainyu with you?
Yes, that's right. Please.
That's a lie.
The truth is you don't know how much
longer you can keep holding yourself back.
Didn't you notice?
Oh, come on. You can't even keep your story straight.
First you said you'd give your life to kill it.
Then you said you could never give it up.
Just be patient,
because I'm coming for you.
And then I'll be sure to kill you myself.
Yes.
I'll be waiting for you, big sister.
Big sister.
Good to see you make it back here, Assassin.
Lord Magus, you're alive?
I am. But in my current state,
I cannot supply you with magical energy.
Sakura, this will put a burden on you,
but you must forge a pact with Assassin.
Sakura.
My Lord, I think the girl... is gone.
What a disappointing conclusion.
What will you do, proceed with the plan?
You can hardly call it that,
but there's no choice.
Farewell, Sakura.
You've endured more than I ever
expected from a mere guinea pig.
Delightful.
There's no need for that, grandfather.
Oh, that's why.
You were hiding the fact that you don't even have a face.
Damn you.
You're a nobody belonging nowhere.
You're never going to become the one-and-only anything.
I just want to know my...
Wh-What do you think you're doing, Sakura?
That's obvious.
You no longer needed to be
protected by him, did you, grandfather?
I spent so much time
wondering how, wherever I went, you were always with me
and why you had me, do whatever you wanted.
It's exactly what I expected.
The real you has been hiding inside my body all along.
Honestly, grandfather,
I thought for sure you were going to be bigger than that.
No!
Sakura, please, wait!
This is goodbye, grandfather.
First my brother,
and now grandfather's gone, too.
Next, I...
Next, I can...
What?
What am I going to do now?
We're not finished.
Not yet.
There are more.
They'll be here soon.
Go, please.
Only let big sister pass through.
And Shirou Emiya?
I'm amazed, but it's more than I realized.
I care about Sakura. She means everything to me.
This is it.
Good luck.
Rin...
Rider...
Shirou.
Illya...
after this battle's over,
you may not have a place to go back to,
but you could keep living at my house.
Are you going to replace Kiritsugu?
Uh, no. Kiritsugu and I are different people.
But I will...
Shirou, crouch down, please.
O-okay.
Be careful, Shirou. You got that?
Be home by morning,
and make sure you bring Sakura back with you.
I sense something,
a field of power being generated up at the lake.
The field up there is the dummy gate.
But we're here to find the Greater Grail,
so...
We're gonna have to go down and not up.
Going down.
What's the matter?
Uh, nothing.
Don't lose focus.
From this point forward, just worry about your own life.
Saber.
Rin.
Oh, I get it.
Sakura's taking this seriously.
Sorry, guys. I'm gonna go ahead without you.
If you're planning on saving Sakura,
Shirou, you'd better catch up quick.
Saber, I'm sorry, but we're coming through.
You won't.
This is the role I was given.
Using all my powers, I can hold her off for two minutes.
I'll find an opportunity for you.
Wait here, and watch,
but don't miss your chance.
Saber, we will eliminate you right here.
I'm going to save Sakura.
Which means I'll kill you.
This is it, the Greater Grail.
You came all the way here instead of running.
I've been thinking.
And I've realized...
I hate this world.
The house, you, grandfather,
my pathetic big brother,
the whole "peaceful" city.
Everyone who never made an
effort to save me is unforgiveable.
I'm taking my anger out on them,
and I realize that it's not healthy.
But I've become so much stronger.
I can do anything I want to now.
Really?
You've gotten used to murder, have you?
Yes.
Grandfather and Assassin can't bother me now.
And all that's left...
And what about Shirou?
That fool.
He still has it in his head that he can save you.
Shirou is the only person in the whole world
I want to kill.
How sad.
You've already given up on your humanity.
You act so tough.
You're jealous of this power, aren't you?
You want to take it from me
so that you and you alone can be happy.
You can't have it.
But there are two things I will give you,
regret and despair.
You shall drown inside the Grail of Heaven,
like a bug dropped into a lake.
Damn it.
The curse of Mystic Eyes.
Rider, I wanted to ask,
about Saber, is it possible for someone
to damage her if they're not a Servant?
Yes. Sakura's captive Servants are all incarnations.
A powerful Mystic Code should be enough.
That's good news.
Then I know what we need to do to beat her.
Yes, that strategy could very well do the trick.
Except...
We'll have to trust each other.
Do we?
Shirou, are you able to stand by when an ally's in danger?
This will require you to use your worst skill.
I believe in you!
He's not going to move.
He trusts me.
He'll wait for me to defeat you.
Oh, but he did try to help you.
Stop talking!
You think this is enough to contain me?!
Phantasm!
Bring it on!
Now projection start.
Searching.
Select.
Analyze.
I am the bone of my sword.
Rho...
Ex...
Aias!
...calibur!
Bellero...
phon!
Shirou?
Thank you, Saber,
for all the times you saved me.
I'll go on ahead.
Catch up when you can run again.
Full of surprises.
You work people harder than expected.
Why, you...
No way.
How did you...
Isn't that obvious?
This is purely a contest of power.
Your weapon...
there's something about it.
Do you know what this is, Sakura?
Take a look. You're facing off
against the Jeweled Sword of Zelretch.
It connects to an infinite number of parallel
universes and channels magical energy from them all.
Sword of Zelretch?
Honestly. You've never even heard the name Zelretch?
Don't mock me!
No matter how much energy you've banked up,
you can only use so much of it at a time,
and I can match that easily.
I only need enough to defend each attack.
I can always draw in more next time.
You've pooled up a ludicrous amount of power,
but in your hands, it's a complete and utter waste.
It's not fair.
Not fair.
Not fair!
That's all the power you can manage.
Have you cooled your head now?
It's not fair.
How could you?
How could you?!
I am your sister, aren't I,
but most of my life, I haven't
even been treated like I'm human!
Makiri's Magecraft was carved into me.
All of my meals were poisoned.
Eating was painful, and worse, it terrified me!
In the worm pit, I needed to
ask for permission to even breathe.
Whenever I cried,
they would only rejoice as they kept on violating my body!
Meanwhile, you were always shining so bright.
Growing up, everything was easy for you,
and I hated you for it.
I wanted to win!
Just once, I wanted my sister to praise me,
to tell me I was amazing!
Because I was born into the Tohsaka family,
I always believed you would
come for me one day to rescue me.
But no.
You never bothered with me at all!
I waited 11 years.
My life's a disaster.
But is any of it really my fault?
So much pain.
Every day full of pain!
I didn't want things to be this way.
This was all I could do.
I had no choice!
That's a terribly sad story.
So what?
I mean, you're not exactly in pain anymore, are you?
That's my point!
You don't even care!
I'm sorry, but I don't really
understand other people's pain.
That's how I am.
No matter what kind of torture you had to go through,
I'll never be able to relate.
But, Sakura...
even as insensitive as I happen to be...
even after hearing you cry about of your problems,
I never thought of myself as being blessed.
How dare you?
You were!
How can you say that?!
Sakura...
Welt, Ende.
Oh. This isn't good.
Big sister?
I'm a complete idiot.
But I can't stand it when people try
their hardest and end up with nothing.
I really do love you, Sakura.
I've always wanted to see you smile.
I wanted to believe that as long as I suffered,
it would only make your life that much easier.
I guess I can't really criticize Shirou, can I?
Once I saw you up close, I realized
that I really couldn't kill you.
I'm sorry.
I'm a selfish big sister.
But I'm happy, because...
you've been wearing that ribbon all this time.
She loves me?
I've been waiting to hear her say that.
But now...
I killed her.
She's gone.
Oh. Shirou.
She's dead.
I... I killed her!
My sister, she's gone.
She always told me not to give up,
but I was too stupid to understand!
I hate this!
Now I have to stop it!
Nice job, Tohsaka.
You just won.
Sakura, Tohsaka's still alive!
It's not too late.
You and I can save her together!
Oh, no! You have to get away from here!
No, that's...
I don't want to do this.
Get away!
Yeah, I know,
but that little brat's being a sore loser!
Shirou, take my sister, and get out of here!
I can't hold it back.
Go now, please!
Please stop this!
Let me go! I can die here alone!
I don't want you to see this!
Let me die!
Why won't you stop?
I don't deserve to be saved.
No, I shouldn't be saved at all!
Hang on!
Sakura.
You see, Shirou?
That's what I mean.
I... This is what I have become now,
so just go!
Look at me.
I've killed so many people...
my brother, grandfather,
and now even my big sister!
So tell me, do I really deserve to live
after the terrible things I've done?!
You do!
Can't you see?
You took their lives.
Now take responsibility!
Shirou, you...
I don't know your sins or your punishment.
I've no idea what they are.
But I'll protect you from everything,
everything that's coming for you, Sakura.
I'll be right there!
And sure, that may be hypocritical...
but I will defend the one I love!
Now trace on.
Time for your punishment.
It's not going to to be easy.
You better grit your teeth.
Okay.
Let's go home, Sakura.
Cut your ties with this thing.
It won't stop, will it?
Shirou.
Oh, uh, it's you.
Perfect timing.
Can you help take Sakura and Tohsaka
and get them out of this place?
R-Ri...
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
Oh, and...
Can you give this to Sakura?
No, Shirou. Do that yourself.
Fine.
Good luck.
Kotomine?
It's you.
Yes. And it seems...
you and I are both barely clinging to life,
Shirou Emiya.
Even if this thing gets out,
your wish will never be granted.
But that is my wish.
I have but only one objective here,
and that is to ensure the successful birth of this curse.
But why? Why are you protecting it?
It's evil, the definition of the word.
It is not evil yet,
nor is it good.
Humans become either good or evil
through the process of learning,
but they begin at zero.
At the start, the only truth
they know is the existence of truth.
Humans are capable of good and evil.
It's up to the individual to determine the difference.
There is no crime in one's birth.
There's a life longing to be born into the world.
Allowing that miracle to happen is love.
What a crock of shit.
That's what it means to me, Shirou Emiya.
You find your bliss in seeing the happiness of others.
I can only find mine in witnessing their suffering.
That body of yours is troublesome.
Whoever attacks it risks their own life.
Tell me, who are you to say that all killing is evil?
You're protecting Sakura Matou, the murderer, aren't you?!
How quintessentially human of you.
Evil men occasionally flirt with goodwill,
and saints willfully commit sins on a whim.
It is this contradiction that makes us human.
To live is to harbor both.
Good and evil coexist in us all.
That's bullshit. This thing only
exists to kill everything it touches!
Yes. That's right!
But we don't know how it feels about that.
That's what I want, to learn its true nature!
Will it lament its evil actions or laugh them off?
If it has no doubts about its function,
when it was humanity who wished for it to be what it is,
it cannot be evil!
When its life begins,
it will kill everything, just as it was asked.
When it stands alone as the sole survivor,
will it be able to forgive itself for what it's done?
That is exactly what I'm dying to know.
That's the lame wish that you want granted?
That's your excuse?!
An excuse? Nothing else in the world matters to me.
Do you understand?
You and I are on opposite extremes,
because you want nothing for yourself.
You only think of others.
However, our desires are very similar!
Oh, I get it.
We're similar because we both
think of ourselves as sinners.
But we both chose our path,
looking for salvation that would never come.
You'll never back down, will you?
I also have to admit I'm taking out my anger.
I envy you people for what I could never have.
Seems fair.
I guess talking was a waste of time.
I don't mind.
Neither of us has much time left anyway.
I don't want to die.
I don't...
I ask you, my mortal enemy...
why do you wish so fiercely not to die?
You want all forms of evil eradicated.
To do this, you sought out a miracle.
There is no salvation in this world.
As long as we're human,
we cannot be separated from evil.
We seek utopia, but we know that it lies in
a place that can never be reached by humans.
We wish to surpass humans,
to discover a new shape of humanity.
Yes. In order to eliminate all the evil of this world,
we promise we will risk our lives to achieve this dream.
It's been 500 years,
but, looking back, that desire only lasted an instant.
Disappointing. To think I was just one step short.
It's over.
It appears it was a game of inches.
You are the last remaining Master.
Go and fulfill your sacred obligations.
This is it.
This will be the end.
One more projection.
But wait.
Is that really the way?
No.
You won't die here, Shirou.
I'm the one that's going to close the gate.
Shirou, tell me,
do you want to keep on living?
In whatever form you can hold?
Do you want to live?
No. I...
I have to...
take it down with me.
Don't worry. Please.
Do you?
I do.
I do! I wanna live!
I'm so glad.
No, wait. Come back.
I'm going to show you a miracle,
and this one will be amazing.
Watch closely now.
You're about to see real magic.
I don't care.
Please! Please just come back!
Damn it.
What's your name?
I don't remember.
You told me a big brother protects his little sister.
Well, I'm really your big sister, Shirou.
Which means I have to protect my little brother.
Illya!
Illya! Illya!
Shirou?
Well, that's our next team captain for you.
It looks like I can rest easy when I retire.
Why is it taking him so long to come back?
The Holy Grail War has finally come to an end.
The Greater Grail has been destroyed,
and it took the war with it.
I had to deal with the fallout
caused with the Mage's Association
while I waited for Sakura to recover.
Now I'm back, and I'm walking alongside her...
making up for 11 years of lost time.
And time is moving again.
At least we're together now.
Although he's not around anymore.
Because Shirou Emiya's body disintegrated.
Sakura...
Rin's just come back home.
That's great.
Thanks, Rider.
So, Sakura, how have you been?
Good. It's been a slow process,
but I think I'm finally in a place where
I can accept things for what they are.
If I let myself be crushed by guilt,
it's the same as running away.
Things that have changed
and things that need to change.
But I wonder how I'll tell if something has or not?
Hard to say right now.
I'm still looking for a path.
And yet...
In a world that never stops changing...
some things always stay the same.
Sakura, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Hey, come on! Let's go!
Jeez, are you a little kid or what?
Hey...
Sakura, are you happy?
Yes.