[attacking yell]
[self chuckle]
[groaning]
[attacking grunts]
Get all of them!
Zap yourself with this!
[groaning]
Like they say,
don't resist arrest!
[humming]
Domyoji, you shouldn't
go charging in like that.
What, why not? I mean,
come on! The Reds have
got our backs, don't they?
And those guys act fast!
So all that we really
have to do is scatter
the Greens, and after
that, the Reds will
just go ahead and
handle the rest of it!
Well, speaking tactically,
you aren't wrong about that,
but we shouldn't rely on
other clans too much.
[chuckle]
Akiyama, bring the police
transport vehicle around.
Yep, we got 'em
all rounded up.
Look, the Reds' have their
own network to track crimes.
And they also employ
resources that our clan
tends to overlook.
It's thanks to them
we subdued these
suspects so fast.
It wouldn't hurt to
show them gratitude.
I will admit that they have
helped drastically improve
the ease and effectiveness
of our patrols.
In the end, this
whole partnership has
worked out just fine.
We'll handle the prisoners.
Alright.
Oh! Thanks for this!
So should we just put 'em
in that car now, or what?
Yes, please do so.
Make sure they're
tightly restrained.
All of this buddy‐buddy
stuff is making me sick...
But why can't I go in?!
You just can't.
Meow‐Meow? Hmph!
Meow!
It's the first time I've been
in your room, Lieutenant.
So this is where you
lived all those years.
All alone.
Guess what, Lieutenant.
My sister left behind
something amazing for us.
They dug it out from the
remains of the shelter next
to my old research lab
several years after
we went our separate ways.
It was simply stored in a
random box and ultimately
donated to the library,
where it stayed until
Mr. Kusanagi
rediscovered it.
You know, he's the
Reds' second in command.
I think Sis knew that
this was going to happen.
About how you'd stop
at nothing to make sure
that the dreams we
shared were fulfilled.
And how I would stumble
once that dream all
of it became too big.
[chuckle]
"Irren ist menschlich."
Huh?!
Shiro!
Are you all finished?
Yeah. There really
wasn't much to go through.
Hardly any personal
effects at all.
Meow?!
[chuckle]
I know the Lieutenant's
original order was for you
to assist me until I
returned to the surface.
I'm sorry to make you
extend that term for so long.
Thank you for those thoughtful words
from the friend of our King.
As per our King's dying
orders, the Gold Clan's
Tokijikuin will
engage solely in
the maintenance of
the existing system.
And we ask for your
approval to cease
active participation
in this matter.
Permission granted.
[chuckle]
For your service to
Daikaku Kokujoji, I
offer my heartfelt thanks.
It's somewhat unfortunate
that we can't rely
on the Gold Clan for
military support.
That group is not
only a fighting unit.
They hold an important
post, managing the Slate
and secretly maintaining
the whole country.
So we can't try to
recruit them carelessly
and risk losing them.
The Lieutenant knew
that fact all too well.
That's why his orders to
assist me extended only
till I came back
and no further.
So, with the Gold King
gone is the one who's
going to manage the
Slate now the Blue King?
Hold on. Don't tell me that
you still hold a grudge
against him because
he defeated you?
The boss with glasses goes
flash! Dodge! Step! Swoosh!
Wham! Bam! "I'm
over here." "What?!"
Achoo! Bitch slap!
Jab! Jab! Jab! Kaboom!
"Ha, ha, ha, ha..."
And then...
[chuckle]
Yup, he totally kicked
your butt, all right!
It's nothing personal like
that! I mean, it's just...
[chuckling]
So, as I already explained,
oversight of Mihashira
Tower and the Dresden
Slate has been officially
turned over to
us, SCEPTER FOUR.
You should also receive a
letter from the Gold Clan.
So you get to act like
a king now that His
Excellency is gone, huh?
I'm certainly not "acting."
I was chosen by
the Slate for this.
One other thing: the
authority, now possessed
only by the Gold Clan,
to issue orders to every
government agency
will need to be
transferred over to us.
[gasp] Now?! Just when‐‐
"Just when the weight
that was hanging over
my head is finally
gone?" Is that it?
Let me reassure you,
Mr. Prime Minister.
We have no intention
of controlling this
country's future to pursue
our own self‐interest.
Currently, we are going
up against the Green
Clan, an organization
that threatens the
peace of our
entire nation.
And I simply want to
request cooperation from
various quarters. That's
the entirety of it.
You demand the sole
authority to give orders
and call it a "request"?
One must have a solid
foundation if one
wishes to maintain order.
So, Mr. Prime Minister, I
"request" your cooperation.
In other words, I have
to obey you, is that it?
If you wish to put
it that way, yes.
It seems the partnership
with the Blue Clan is going
far better than we ever
could have expected.
Uh‐huh.
Aw man, they're so lucky.
Hey, Mr. Kusanagi. Why
do I have to be here
on standby, anyway?
We're supposed to be
crushing the Green Clan.
HOMRA is gonna look
pretty damn bad without
Yatagarasu joining
the party, you know.
Listen, Yata, you're
like the reserves.
We need you here at the
ready just in case something
happens to go sideways out
there with all of the others.
So what you're telling me is
that I'm a benchwarmer?!
[chuckle] Don't get
all bent out of shape.
Besides, aren't you the
one who said you're
going to make sure that
Anna stays protected?
Well yeah, but...
Yata, you have to learn that
you don't always have to be
at the center of everything.
This is a good chance
for you to practice!
Fine!
[sigh]
[chuckle]
The Green King himself
has actually been pretty
quiet for a while now.
Ever since that incident
over on school island.
As usual, the ones
acting up are only the
low‐ranking clansmen.
Blues in public and
Reds behind the scenes.
As long as he's being
watched by both sides like
this, he can't do anything
drastic. But still...
He's not really being
pressured now. He's just
saving up his strength.
So he's merely sharpening
his fangs before he makes
his next big move, huh?
That sure makes me uneasy.
What is there to be
afraid of? I mean, we've
got Anna and two other
Kings on our side!
Even if those green worms
bring out their boss, we can
still crush them, no problem!
[fumbling grunts]
Even with three kings
it won't be easy...
Mr. Kusanagi, please tell
the Red King to keep an eye
on the Blue King's condition.
His condition? How so?
Honestly, I can't
exactly say for sure,
but he's unstable.
Like when...
[gasp]
The burden of
killing a king?!
It's starting to show.
Don't tell me you haven't
noticed it as well?
If you mean his Sword
of Damocles, I have...
It's not like something's
going to happen immediately.
But we can't ignore it.
So we'd better be
on high alert.
There's no guarantee how
much help we can count on.
I just really wish that we
didn't have to worry about more
casualties coming out of
this whole damn mess.
I guess it's not going
to be that simple.
It's all because of the
Slate that I was able to
meet Mikoto and all of the
other people in HOMRA.
But still, if the Slate is
going to continue to cause
people to meet the same
fate as Mikoto did.
Well, then I‐‐
Anna, what're you saying?!
Is it really that bad?
I mean with the Blue King?
Shiro? Shiro?!
Shiro?
Hey!
Shiro!
Where is he?
Where is he?!
Hey, where's Shiro?
He stepped out a moment ago.
What?! Where'd he go?!
I want to go, too!
Please, Neko, just leave
him be for right now.
He probably wants some
time to think things over.
Aw! But I just got
to see him again.
[grumbling] Fine!
Meow!
This country will come
to an end unless we
do something... fast.
Seems the Blue King decided
to ignore your warnings.
And after all the
trouble you went through.
I feel sorry for you.
I really don't appreciate
being spied on, not one bit.
Green King, Nagare Hisui.
My eyes are everywhere.
It's my only true freedom.
So you come crawling
out the moment that
the Lieutenant dies.
I have to say, you
really are quite
the cunning person.
This coming from the man
who decides to act only
after his best friend dies?
It's quite ironic...
That one stung. Well, I
can't really deny it. You
certainly got me there.
So what now?
Well, now that we've
exchanged pleasantries let's
move on to the main topic.
I've been waiting for
your return for a while
now so that I can give
you this proposal.
First King, Silver King,
Adolf K. Weismann.
Would you like to
join forces with me?
[chuckle]
I thought you came here
to join our Coffee Table
Alliance, so that the
four of us could work to
bring peace to the world.
But now it doesn't
sound like it.
Coffee Table Alliance?
I do respect the name.
But no, that's not
the reason that I'm
contacting you now.
Instead, I want to talk
about forming a new
alliance, just you and me.
Together we'll advance
mankind's evolution.
That used to be your
life's goal, didn't it?
Back in Dresden,
seventy years ago.
The Dresden Slate. It makes
us kings and gives power to
our clansmen. It's an
evolution accelerator.
But for decades, the
all‐powerful Gold King
kept it under control.
As a result, only a minimal
number of Strains were born.
He even managed to
contain the birth of kings
within the Kanto region of
Japan. But this great power...
We will release it.
I see. So that's your goal,
is it? For what purpose?
Like I just said...
Simply to advance the
evolution of mankind.
That is all of it.
If that's true, that means
you're even more dangerous
than I thought you were.
I think that I'll choose to
take that as a compliment,
but in any event...
That is my dream.
Your dream?
That dream...
Has been shattered?
Then rebuild that dream
again, this time with me.
The situation is entirely
different than seventy years
ago. This time there
is nothing to stop us.
We simply have
to take action.
[gasp]
Respectfully, I refuse!
But why?
Because everything is
different from the way that
it was seventy years ago!
And here I thought
that you would find my
proposal to your liking.
But it appears I
was wrong about that.
Well, no matter.
I'm just going to
have to take the
Slate by force, then.
[gasp]
The Blue King foolishly
thinks he can suppress
the Slate's power, just
as the Gold King did.
So I was just going to
wait until that rookie
exhausted himself. That
was my original plan.
But this calls for a change.
Now that I've come
back you won't be able
to do as you please.
I see...
I wanted to partner with you
and move the world forward.
However, if instead you wish
to choose confrontation...
I'm happy to oblige.
There's one other thing I
want to confirm with you.
The incident last year...
Is it safe for me to
assume that you were the
one who dragged me
into this little game?
Oh, so you figured
it out, huh?
This body I'm in, not even
the Blue Clan's Yuishiki
System could identify it.
Only you could've pulled
off a stunt like that.
So that means that the
person who made all of
the arrangements for
the actions taken by
the Colorless King
and who sent him to
attack me, was
in fact you!
Yes, I see. Removing every
trace of his existence,
making the death appear
accidental, and of course
providing critical data.
All of the things that I
took such pains with turned
out to be my downfall.
I do have a habit of
being too elaborate.
But why do all of this
just to get to me?
Because your role is
not to be a spectator.
It's to be a player.
After all, everything
started with you.
Do you intend to
control the Slate?
Or rather,
unleash its power?
You could say that.
So just relax, sit back, and
entrust your dream to us.
And what happens
if I say no?
If that's your choice,
then it means war.
I never wanted
any of this...
But still, I will
not run away.
Not this time.
The three Kings
assemble at the tower.
To stop the Green King from
reducing the world to chaos.
But we have not yet
witnessed the terrifying
power that will
shake everything up.
There are those who
must fight and those
who must defend.
Next time on K RETURN OF
KINGS, Episode 6 "Keeper."
Mikoto, do you think I can
fulfill my role as King?