We'll be in the airspace
over the site shortly.
What's the situation there?
Enemy clan confirmed.
Special Police Forces
are also on the scene.
Roger. Now entering site
airspace. Alert the Special
Police Force to be on guard.
Copy that.
Target confirmed.
Shall we descend?
No, that won't be necessary.
[harrumphing chuckle]
That group is
nothing but trouble.
Captain, please!
Let us at least
touch down first!
[gasps]
I'm sorry, but it would
be very rude of me to
keep the Red King waiting.
Both of you, please
return to the base now.
[gasp]
He just dropped out of
the sky! Did you see that!
Wow, now that's what I call
making a grand entrance...
Third King Mikoto Suoh...
Your actions are as
unruly and chaotic
as they always are.
Fourth King Reisi Munakata...
Your face looks as awful and
annoying as it always does.
Why don't we have
some fun, Misaki?
Nice kick!
And nice catch
too! [laughter]
[chuckle]
Burn them all.
No blood! No bone! No ash!
We will advance with our
swords in our hands.
We will triumph because
our cause is just.
Men! Draw your swords!
[chuckle]
Akiyama, ready!
Benzai, ready!
Kamo, ready!
Domyoji, ready!
Enomoto, ready!
Fuse, ready!
Goto, ready!
Hidaka, ready!
Fushimi, ready!
And Awashima, ready!
Munakata ready!
[harrumphing chuckle]
Totsuka...
You got it.
C'mon, let's go, Anna.
Mikoto...
You continue to use
your power recklessly.
You're incorrigible.
I don't need a lecture.
Then I'll have to
stop you with force!
Fine by me, Munakata!
Let's see you handle
this, Mikoto Suoh!
[chuckle]
Is that all you've got?
That flame...
It's quite impressive.
However...
Mr. Mikoto!
Saruhiko!
Come here an
play, Misaki!
I'll play, but don't cry
when I plaster you!
Over here, you
damn Monkey!
You're going down today...
...ya good for
nothing traitor!
[chuckle]
Sounds interesting!
Let's see you try!
[chuckling]
Like that'd stop me!
What's wrong? You
look pretty rusty!
Look, Saruhiko, why don't
you just shut up, already?
You stupid monkey!
It's time to end this.
I'm done with you.
Why don't you go take
a nap or something?!
This is nothing!
You'd better watch out,
or you're seriously
gonna get it!
Since you're not
paying attention! See!
[chuckle] Misaki!
So sorry about this, but
I'm in a hurry. Excuse me!
Hey, watch it!
That's dangerous.
Sorry for scaring you!
Daddy, look! Look!
Well, that was
a fancy move.
Huh? Uh‐oh, heads up!
Oops... Oh, boy.
I guess I overdid
it a little bit, there.
Whoa! [chuckle] Sorry...
I didn't mean for
that to happen, Seri.
[nervous chuckle]
And just what's so funny?
Don't underestimate
Scepter 4, Homra!
[gasp]
Come!
Right...
Well, let's get
on with it, then.
This one's mine!
Woo! This pumps me up!
Submit to your arrest!
If you stand in my way,
then I'll blast you away!
Take this, damn Blue!
You're pretty fast
for a guy your size!
Time to cut loose!
Sounds like your attitude
fits our team better!
Trying to recruit
me? No thanks!
Sorry, but you're not strong
enough to bring me down.
[chuckle] See if you
say that after I show
you my cool moves!
[gasps]
Stay back.
I've got this.
Don't worry, Anna. It looks
like everyone is just having
a great time tonight.
But they're fighting.
Yes, that is true.
But doesn't it also
look to you like they
might be dancing?
Just like this butterfly.
So pretty!
The Dresden Slate, a
mysterious relic that
selects seven Kings and
bestows upon them each
a Sword of Damocles along
with its great power.
[defiant chuckle]
Taken into the country
by Daikaku Kokujoji
after World War
II, it brought
unprecedented
prosperity to Japan.
Every so often, a
new king is selected.
Some live to wield its
power. While others died to
protect their friends.
While still others choose
to watch over the world.
And now, as an era
comes to a close...
A peculiar bond will
merge all the Kings'
paths into one.
[humming]
[chuckling]
High Score Kill.
Found ya!
By the authority given
to me by my J‐Rank,
launch Mission 2086.
[chuckling]
Voiceprint verified. Mission
2086 authorized by J‐Rank.
Activate!
Thanks!
[chuckle]
Hey, Kuroh! When
are we gonna eat?
[giggle] Wow! A bird?
[giggle]
Well, you can't eat
it, whatever it is.
Hey!
Target acquired. You've
earned 100 JUNGLE points.
How's that incident report
from the other day coming?
I'm putting it together
now, but I don't know.
Something's off.
Damn, I'm exhausted.
I know, right? You
can say that again.
It's been like
this every day!
Hard day, huh,
Mr. Domyoji?
Yeah I'm completely
wiped out, Hidaka.
Domyoji, Kamo, let me get
this straight, you've been
sent out two days in a row?
[harrumph] That is rough.
Yeah, it's the same for you
and Benzai, right, Akiyama?
Three days for me, and today
is Akiyama's fourth day.
We just got back here and
barely had enough time to
take a shower and change.
The reports just
keep coming.
There's no time
to rest at all.
Enomoto, Fuse.
Are there any leads on
Kuroh Yatogami? Have you
discovered anything
about where he went
after the explosion?
No, not a thing.
Fuse pressured that
informant they brought in
really hard, but we ended
up with nothing useful.
This is only a hunch,
but I have a suspicion
that he must've gone
into hiding with
that female partner of his.
I wouldn't be surprised.
After all, the Green Clan
did go out of their way to
target him in particular.
The truth is, we're
already spread so thin
with all the trouble
happening everywhere.
I don't know how
we'll keep up.
Goto, what do you think
the Green Clan is thinking
about right now?
Well honestly,
I have no idea.
Are you guys
stupid or what?
Aside from their leaders,
the Green Clan foot soldiers
aren't thinking anything.
Huh? What do you
mean, Mr. Fushimi?
[sigh]
Oh. Thanks so much.
Let's see, here. This reads,
"I've finally made it to
N‐Rank status."
"I'm gonna keep on
earning points, and the
more that I have,
the more power I get."
Mr. Fushimi, what is this?
"Your mission: to keep on
bullying the Black Dog. And
keep on toying with
the Blues, as well."
It's the underground
website for users from
Jungle, the Green Clan.
To their sick minds,
all of this is nothing
but a game.
It seems the Green Clan is
giving us quite a hard time.
Yes, much to our dismay...
They're using an advanced
tool to remain anonymous on
the Net and orchestrate
incidents across the city,
as if it's all just for fun.
Last night, in the midst
of our investigations in
Shizume, we had an encounter
with the Red Clan that
ended in a stare‐down.
Something wrong, Captain?
So, they still had
that option, did they?
Huh?
It's merely the method
that they're employing
to harass us.
Ms. Awashima,
contact the Red Clan.
And please do so as
quickly as possible.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Yata. It looks
like Anna fell asleep.
You guys...
Don't just stand
around doing nothing.
Put a blanket on the little
lady or something, would ya?
Yeah, it is getting
pretty chilly these days.
Chitose.
Is it true what I
heard? You and the Blues
got into some kinda
tussle again last night?
[confident chuckle]
Well that was only a run‐in
with the pretty lieutenant.
I'm guessing that they
wanted to save face or
something like that.
But they had come on
to our turf so we
couldn't back down.
In the end, Mr. Kusanagi
stepped in and got
things under control.
Oh, I see.
You know Eric and I
almost got into it with
the Blues, as well.
But the whole thing just
fizzled out, no big deal.
Those guys have really been
on constant alert lately.
They're even starting to
step into our territories.
They're stirring
up a lotta shit.
[chuckle] Hey there, San.
Just what're you
up to over here?
Hm... Someone just posted
something online that
seems to be grabbing
a lot of attention.
Hold on, what is this?!
Hm?! [gasp]
What's the matter, Shohei?
Just look!
Why do you guys
look so freaked out?
[gasps]
Hi, there! Hey, listen, I'm
sorry about yesterday, Seri.
But I'll make it up to you.
Yeah, I know. We're
supposed to be pushing
the guy who has the
Slate, the Blue
King, to the point
of exhaustion.
And we also want to bully
the Silver Clan so we can
get their King to come
out of hiding, right?
So I got to thinking. Why
not make things even more
exciting by having the Red
Clan join the event, as well?
Yup, I already
gave the orders,
Nagare.
Damn it!
That's the one thing you
bastards should've known
better than to disrespect!
You won't get
away with this!
Those times were
something really precious!
I was here that last time.
[gasp]
Oh, it's you...
What are you doing
here, Saruhiko?!
You figured out the source
of the feed too, huh?
Convenient how the
address of this building
was encrypted into the
message posted online.
You idiot. This is
obviously a trap!
I bet Mr. Kusanagi
was the one who
actually figured it out.
And you must have heard the
location and rushed here
right away, all by yourself.
Right, Misaki?
Look, just shut up. I'm here
on Mr. Kusanagi's orders.
The rest of Homra is
gonna be here soon.
Sure, we know that
we're being lured here,
but a lead is still a lead.
I mean, that is why
you're here too isn't it?
Hey, Saruhiko...
What you did for us before,
it was thanks to you that‐‐
All this fuss over
some stupid video.
Monkey, what did
you just say to me?!
Oh?
Honestly now, can you
really say that I'm wrong?
I'm happy to say it
again it's stupid.
Take it back.
[chuckle] Stop being
such a fool, Misaki.
Take it back!
Mikoto Suoh is dead. Just
face the truth, he's gone!
Monkey!
Take it back, or else!
[fighting grunts]
[chuckling]
Yata! That's enough now!
Fushimi!
Stand down!
Always interfering.
Monkey, you had
a narrow escape!
Well, well, well. All of you
seem to be quite upset.
Aren't you, Homra?
You're damn right we are!
Mr. Mikoto and Mr. Totsuka
were both slandered!
And we're going to make
whoever the hell did it pay!
Izumo Kusanagi, we would
like you to back down.
We will deal with the
Green Clan by ourselves.
Lieutenant Awashima,
I'm sorry...
But Yata's right. The
idiots responsible have
to learn the hard way,
that messing with any of
us means they'll get burned.
And I mean that literally.
That's the only way
Homra will be satisfied.
Well, if you must
insist on putting it that
way, then we have been
taken for fools as well.
After all, choosing this
location is no coincidence,
wouldn't you agree?
[gasp] They're here!
Don't watch from behind the
scenes. Show yourselves.
The bait was so obvious
and still you took it!
Reisi Munakata, the Blue
King, a hundred thousand
Jungle points.
Anna Kushina, also a
hundred thousand points?!
Oh, man! If we get
them, we'll jump up at
least three ranks!
Hey, the one with the big
hooters is Awashima, right?
She's worth six
thousand points.
And that guy with the
shades, Kusanagi, is
worth six thousand, too?
Four thousand for Fushimi
and three thousand for Yata.
So anyway, listen. We've got
nothing against you guys,
but we have no choice!
We gotta get those points!
So die for us, will ya?
[cocky laughter]
[laughing]
[gasps]
What's going on?!
Why aren't they dead?!
Vile and disgusting.
We won't tolerate
these anarchists.
Our lock‐up is not what you
call comfortable. I hope
you're prepared for that.
You said that HOMRA
is dead, didn't you?
I guess you
didn't know.
We've just recently
gotten a brand new King.
A strong king who
rivals even Mikoto Suoh.
You laughed at the
lives that Mikoto
and Tatara lived.
I won't forgive you.
Very well, then. Shall we
begin now? We will triumph
because our cause is just.
Men! Draw your swords!
Right!
Akiyama, ready!
Benzai, ready!
Kamo, ready!
Domyoji, ready!
Enomoto, ready!
Fuse, ready!
Goto, ready!
Hidaka, ready!
Munakata, ready!
[chuckle] It's
time for us, too.
Those Blues can't
take all the glory!
No Blood!
No Bone!
No Ash!
Do not let the Red
Clan outshine us!
Just leave this to me!
[chuckle]
[attacking yell]
What is that?!
What's going on?!
What the hell was that?!
What are they, monsters?!
[gasp] You two?!
Yeah, and we'd really like
to have a word with you.
[chuckling] And don't
think you can get past us!
Hey, don't underestimate me!
I'm an N‐Rank in Jungle!
And I don't just
work with explosives!
I have powers too!
[screaming]
All right, I'll ask
and you'll answer.
Was your King the one who gave
the order to carry out this assault?
Or was it one of
your top Clansmen,
like Yukari Mishakuji?
What are your
King's intentions?
And lastly, do you know
anything at all about
Yashiro Isana?
Damn it! Eat this!
Mission failed. Mission
failed. You have now lost
all of your Jungle points.
You will be stripped
of all powers.
What?! No way! After I
worked so hard to earn those
points?! Damn it, come on!
I'm an N‐Rank! An N‐Rank
that was just about
to get to meet with
the King himself!
How could this happen?!
How?! It's not fair!
You're done with
him? Already?
That guy is merely
another expendable pawn.
I highly doubt he
knows anything.
Does that mean
no one does?
Can't we find anyone who
knows where Shiro is now?
Are you worried?
Mm‐mm! He's our
Shiro, after all!
I know that we'll
see him again!
We just have to
keep searching
harder, that's all!
Looks like things are
getting pretty interesting
thanks to those losers
that we threw in, Nagare.
Of course, it sucks that
we weren't able to lure
out the Silver King.
But guess what? The
Blue King's running
out of time, quickly.
Lieutenant, just as you
did, I will move forward
until my very last breath.
No running this time.
I'll face it head on.
This is the second time
I'm descending from
the sky but it's
different from last
time when I was
hurled down.
This time, I'm descending
of my own free will.
The Green rustles with
malice as it takes root
deeply and extends its
branches far and wide.
Meanwhile, Scepter 4
summons Kuroh, and Neko
makes a visit to Homra.
As they become targets
of Jungle, those two
think of their missing
King and patiently
wait for his return.
Next time on K ‐ RETURN OF
KINGS: Episode 2, "Kindness."
May those two be
reunited with the person
they wish to see.