Douhan Hirasaka, former
U‐Rank member of JUNGLE.
Saruhiko Fushimi.
What do you want?
I just came by to laugh at
the foolish covert agent
who's trapped in a cage.
What happened to your power
to walk through walls, huh?
Only the top handful of
J‐Rank members in the Green
Clan JUNGLE actually
possess genuine powers.
But anyone below
that rank is merely
borrowing a portion
of the Green King's
power through his
online network.
So what you're saying is
that the Green King Nagare
Hisui is the one with real
power, and he gets to
decide who can share it.
To him, you're all
just like PDAs.
You're just convenient tools
used to transmit his powers
and then tossed aside when
you're no longer useful.
It's just a part of doing
business. It's my policy
not to concern myself
with a client's interests.
Then what exactly are you
in this little game for?
What, is it to earn some
JUNGLE points so that you
can become a J‐Rank
member of the Green Clan?
[harrumphing chuckle]
Such bullshit...
It's to earn a living. All
that concerns me is money.
[chuckle] That's
good enough for me.
I'm being released?!
Not quite.
You're breaking out.
[chuckle]
Hey, isn't that the guy?
He's worth ten
thousand points!
Should we take him out?
Yeah, right. We don't
stand a chance.
At least get a picture
of him! Even intel
is worth some points.
Hey, he's getting away!
Shit!
I got a shot of him!
Mission complete. You've
earned 5 JUNGLE points.
[gasps]
That wasn't me! Was it?
[screams] ‐What's going on?!
‐Did you see that?
Next up, the latest news on
those strange incidents of
people developing
unnatural powers.
Since the beginning of
the year, there's been an
increasing number of
reports of such incidents
throughout the Kanto
region. In response,
the authorities have
established a special
countermeasure team.
And in conjunction with
that, the ministry is also
expected to submit an
emergency bill‐‐
Well, would you take a look
at that! It appears that the
field test for the Slate is
going very well indeed!
And it seems that old fart
Kokujoji's media blackout is
no longer functioning.
Going well! Going well!
Yes. The number of people
that have now been empowered
by the Dresden Slate is
increasing every single day.
It's satisfying.
[chuckle] And with these
changes will come a new age
where everyone can express
their own individuality.
I say we call it the
age of JUNGLE, where
chaos breeds life.
A true paradise for the
survival of the fittest.
It'll be a paradise, huh?
Well, if you ask me, it
sounds more like the kind of
place that people
usually call "hell."
What's wrong, old
man, you getting cold
feet or something?
Caw! Old man! Cold feet!
Hey, come on! I never said
that I have any gripes!
After all, a hell that one
can foresee is at least a
little better than one
that you can't see coming.
That's the kind
of choice I made.
In order to make this
forthcoming new age
arrive sooner and
more definitively.
I have issued several
special missions for our
JUNGLE players to carry out.
You mean like tracking
down any newly born
Strains for recruitment.
Keeping watch over the
other clans' activities.
And, of course, laying the
groundwork with other
influential parties for the
next phase of our plan?
All that sounds like
a huge pain in the ass.
A sumptuous meal requires
lots of preparation before
serving, my dear Sukuna.
But you were just
talking about
"survival of the fittest."
This is winner take all,
right? Eat or be eaten?
Wait, isn't she
that ninja girl?
Yes, Douhan Hirasaka.
During our first attack on
Mihashira Tower in October,
she was captured by
SCEPTER 4 and as a
result, she ended up
losing a lot of points.
But in the past month, she's
recouped her losses and
returned to being U‐Rank.
Really?
In any event, it's wonderful
to see skilled players make
it back onto the battlefield
the way that she has.
I welcome her return.
Who's that guy?
The new face that
everyone's talking about.
Caw! New face!
Whoa! He has over
ninety thousand points!
It's possible he's been
exploiting some kind of
loophole. I find it
quite amusing.
You mean he's cheating?!
You know, if he's able to
complete another big
mission, then he could
move up to J‐Rank.
That's a real possibility.
I'm looking forward to it.
Very much.
Well I guess this
place is gonna liven up
in just a little bit.
[annoyed scoff] Those
guys are no big deal.
Huh? where are you
off to, Sukuna?
I'm gonna hunt down
some easy missions.
What's the matter? You
worried that the new guy
might catch up to you?
Of course not!
Hey Yukari, stop making
fun of the kid so much,
would you? It's not nice.
But being mean is
a part of love too.
I'm home.
Welcome back!
I'm making myself at home!
Huh? Is it raining outside? Hold
on, let me get you a towel!
No, it wasn't rain. I just
ran into someone with
unnatural powers again.
Oh. Right...
I've heard that stuff's been
happening all over the place.
Oh! I've gotta get to my
student council meeting.
Kuroh, I brought some cookies,
so please help yourself!
I'm already eating
them! Mm! They're delicious!
I'll see you later on,
Shiro! Good luck with
all of your studies.
Thanks, Kukuri!
Public safety seems to
be declining every day.
And it's all because of
the Slate falling into the
hands of the Green King.
It's even bestowing
powers to civilians who
aren't in a clan.
Sorry, I'll hurry up
and find a solution.
Oh! I'm not blaming
you or anything.
You seem like
you're very focused.
[chuckle] Well, I am the
one who messed everything
up back at Christmas time.
But still, I can't
just give up now.
'Cause the Dresden
Slate and the Green King
simply have to be stopped.
My sister often scolded
me when I was little.
She'd say, "Learn to
clean up your own mess."
You've been pushing
yourself quite hard
for the past month.
I'm ashamed that I
couldn't be of more help.
Yeah! You're
doing great, Shiro!
And Kuroh is useless!
Although, Kuroh does
prepare our meals every day.
Don't try to be funny.
I'm serious.
So am I!
If you didn't cook, then I'd
probably die of starvation.
If I don't do something
about the Slate,
mankind is screwed.
That's why I have to come up
with a countermeasure for
the Slate soon. And why
you have to cook our
meals for us, Kuroh.
Yeah, what Shiro said!
I'm thinking maybe I could
use the Resonant Hammer
Effect on the Slate.
By unfolding the Sanctum
under special conditions,
we'll cause an irreversible
change to the Dresden
Slate's own Weismann phase.
The idea is based on
my sister, Professor
Klaudia Weismann's theory
called the Secondary
Methodology of Schwert
Regulation. This
illustrates the basic idea.
Mm‐hm! That's a
good plan, Shiro.
Okay...
Well, we're having
curry for dinner.
[excited gasp] Yay! Yay!
[chatter]
Oh, I see. So Fushimi
is still missing, is he?
Did your Captain
say anything?
No, nothing much
at all, really.
I don't know what's going on
with him or with Fushimi.
Come on, now, try to put
away the long face.
I mean, we're at a
party, so let's try to
have fun. Okay, Seri?
[sigh] Be serious.
Please log in for
admittance to the hall.
Ah, Mr. and Mrs.
Izuru Kusakabe.
Thank you so
much for coming.
The entrance is
just over that way.
Right. Thank you.
So I'm your wife now?
That's right, my darling.
[laughter]
Man, I've heard about
celebrity parties, but this
is beyond what I pictured.
Politicians from around the
world, leaders of industry,
world‐famous authors,
actors, and over there,
even the Japanese
Prime Minister.
Ladies and gentleman.
Thank you all so much for
attending the JUNGLE
Boot Up Reception.
Representing the JUNGLE
Corporation, the sponsor of
this gala, is CEO Yukari
Mishakuji, who'd like
to offer a few
words of welcome.
Welcome. You're all
about to enter a new era.
It's Yukari
Mishakuji of JUNGLE.
He's not hiding his name
or face. Pretty bold.
It's obvious that
they no longer feel
any need to hide.
Our JUNGLE information
network is no longer just a
communication tool. It's
become a way of life.
It will redefine what it
means to be human.
The future spreading out
before us is limitless.
Those people getting
powers must've helped
push this deal through.
I hear the JUNGLE system
is to be installed in
government agencies.
This is truly a day to
celebrate for many
different reasons!
Now after so long...
I'm finally going to be able
to dismiss that intolerable
young know‐it‐all brat!
I guess that we should
call this the dawn
of the age of JUNGLE!
[laughter]
[groaning]
Oh, I beg your
pardon, ma'am.
I'm sorry. I'm
feeling faint.
Yeah, but, uh, ma'am!
That was a pretty bold move,
Seri. It's not like you.
I'll do whatever it
takes to get the job done.
I found it. The invitation
list for this party.
If we can get this out
of here we'll know the
identities of the
people who are under
JUNGLE's thumb.
Found them!
This way!
It looks like we've
given them the slip.
Oh, no! The PDA!
Damn it!
Emergency mission complete.
You've earned three
thousand JUNGLE points.
Is that?
You've ranked up!
You've been promoted to
the J‐Rank of JUNGLE!
Congratulations,
Saruhiko Fushimi!
[gasp]
Fushimi?!
Fushimi, I'll hear your
excuses once I put
you in the hospital!
A Green Clansman!
Fushimi...
Why, Fushimi?!
Seri...
This way! Shoot
'em if you have to!
Seri, we have to
call it a night.
I never knew there were
underground passages
like this in the
heart of the city.
They have tight security.
And it runs deep...
This is a secret passage
that leads to our hideout.
It also connects to
over a hundred exits
inside this city alone.
Such as main subway
lines, the basement floors
of skyscrapers,
and so forth.
Is it really wise of you to
leak all this intel to me
without any hesitation
whatsoever?
Of course. Because
you are now a J‐Rank
member of JUNGLE.
You're a comrade with whom
we share all our secrets.
That was quite a feat today,
Saruhiko. You managed to
take on HOMRA's and
SCEPTER 4's number twos.
And even did so
all by yourself.
[chuckle]
You should've called for
help, though. There's no
need to try so hard.
I don't work well with
others. I'm just not a fan
of that kind of thing.
Liar.
I know you hired
U‐Rank member Douhan
Hirasaka to work for you.
By doing so, you were able
to obtain twice the JUNGLE
points, allowing you to
move up in rank more quickly.
That was very clever.
You're quite the cheater.
Your system doesn't
have any rules against it.
Is there some kind of problem?
Of course not. I thought it
was cunning and brilliant.
Besides, our Nagare
isn't bothered by foul
play such as that.
The Green King,
Nagare Hisui.
In fact, I believe he
prefers people to think
outside the box.
That's just who
our King is.
Well we're here.
Welcome, Saruhiko Fushimi.
JUNGLE's secret base extends
its hospitality to you.
Can anyone explain what the
hell that idiot's thinking?!
Look, just calm down, Yata.
First, that asshole
betrays us.
Now he betrays the Blues?
And for what?! Huh?!
What the hell is the
point of all this?!
I mean, why would
he go this far?!
I see... Then this is
conclusive evidence of
Saruhiko Fushimi's
defection from us.
I guess this is what is
known as, biting the hand
that feeds you.
I hope you can
forgive me, sir.
My poor management
caused this.
Well in any event, we'll
have to work quickly to fill
the void he created.
To reinforce the front lines
for now, I'll have several
members transferred to
the Special Police Force.
We'll need two people from
the general riot squad,
three from the
intel division,
and one from general
affairs and records.
Excuse me.
Hold on, you're‐‐
[gasp]
Pardon me, sir.
Impressive.
The man responsible
for killing the prior
Blue King, Jin Habari.
Goki Zenjo, also called
Zenjo the Ogre.
From this moment
forward, your assignment
will be to watch my back.
Well, well! It's nice to
meet you, Fushimi!
As they say at times
like these, "Welcome!"
Thank you for coming here
to meet us, Saruhiko.
I am truly delighted.
Delighted! Delighted!
Thank you.
Hey, let's not stand around
gabbing! Sit down, sit down!
Mr. Iwa, the homebody,
actually went outside to
bring this feast
back here for you.
Real sushi! Not that
cheap, pre‐packaged crap.
So? What would you like?
Fatty tuna? Sea urchin?
Salmon roe? Or Shrimp?
I'll have the egg...
[harrumph]
That's for kids.
Hey, come on, now! You
just speak for yourself,
all right, Sukuna?
We have more than sushi,
like fried chicken!
You like chicken?
Chicken! Chicken!
You know you're a bird,
too, you stupid chatterbox!
What's bothering
you, Sukuna?
Why are you in
such a bad mood?
[annoyed harrumph]
You feeling shy? Hmm?
Now, Saruhiko, I'm sure
you're aware that you moved
up five ranks in just
barely just a month.
And in doing so, you beat
the previous best time held
by Sukuna. Now you've
set a new record.
Very impressive.
[annoyed harrumph]
Nagare...
We can talk about
that another time,
don't you think?
But why do you say that,
Mr. Iwa? I'm quite puzzled.
Just because.
Look, Sukuna, stop being in
such a bad mood, all right?
A first impression is what
counts in building a healthy
relationship. So smile!
Right? Don't you agree?
No, sorry not
really. I don't care.
Oh? Really?
Okay, then! That's fine!
Act all cool if you want!
Well, I didn't come here to
make friends, you know.
Oh, yeah? Then tell me,
why exactly have you come?
No reason. This is
all a game, right?
I was simply curious to
discover what was going to
happen if I were able to
push the score to its limit.
To learn if it would change
the way I see things.
And that's all.
Don't tell me that I did all
of that just to get a party
with a sushi platter.
No, of course not. The
remainder of our plan
starts from here on out.
Ready, set, go!
From now on, I'll also be
counting on you. As one of
JUNGLE's top clansmen.
J‐Rank...
Saruhiko Fushimi.
Just tell me what to
do and I'll do it.
I will complete any mission
that you assign to me.
I'd rather spend my time on
missions than on shit like
interpersonal relationships.
As the Blue Clan
deteriorates, Yashiro makes
up his mind. Will Reisi take
the path toward destruction?
Next time on K RETURN OF
KINGS, Episode 10 "Keystone."
Mikoto, your red will
always be my favorite.