Uh‐‐
Uh!
[sighing]
Misaki Yata of HOMRA.
Uh... yeah. What's up?
I understand that you've
been friends with our
Fushimi since before you
joined HOMRA.
He's no friend of mine!
He betrayed me and Mr.
Mikoto by becoming a Blue!
It may very well come to be
that he will share my
destiny and have to die.
If that happens, then I'm
sorry. I apologize in
advance.
What the hell does that
mean?!
Didn't he betray you and
turn his back on the Blues
just like he did with us?!
And right now... that
double‐crosser's with the
Greens!
By my command.
Huh?!
Before the mission at
Christmas... I gave Mr.
Fushimi my orders.
If through some unforeseen
circumstances the mission
were to fail, and the Slate
were somehow stolen away...
I ordered him to use any
means available to
infiltrate JUNGLE'S
central command.
Because he had been a
turncoat before, he was
perfect for the job.
What?!
But isn't that a dangerous
plan?
If Saruhiko's found out, the
Greens will just go ahead
and kill him,
no questions asked!
That is true.
[gasping]
I sent Mr. Fushimi on a
mission with no guarantees
that he'd return alive.
Because frankly, he's the
only one who could pull it
off.
And of course, he accepted
the mission fully aware of
the risks.
Why...?! How could you even
consider giving your own
clansman a mission as
dangerous as that?!
Tell me!
Why?
Because no matter what the
cost, we can't let JUNGLE
have their way.
SCEPTER 4 stands for order.
We won't just sit back and
watch the world fall into
chaos.
As a member of SCEPTER 4,
Mr. Fushimi concurred.
However, there is one sure
way for him to live through
this.
And that is for him to
betray me and join JUNGLE
for real.
Do you believe that he would
actually do such a thing?
I ask since, as a former
friend, you probably know
|
him best, don't you,
Misaki Yata?
Uh‐‐
Beneath the ground where
that pillar of light is
emerging is a water intake
station that was built then
abandoned.
It seems that JUNGLE has
made it their hideout.
We believe that the Slate
was taken to that facility's
lowest level.
So that's where we're going
to go.
And the Red Clan will back
you up. We'll make sure that
the three of you get down to
the lowest level.
Right, everybody? Let's show
those guys what we're made
of!
Yeah!
Let's do this!
Here's yours, Misaki.
Hmm? Oh, right... You can
count on me!
I'm in charge of Basement
Level 9, isn't that right?
Yata, it's okay.
Okay...? What the hell's
that mean?!
Go and save Fushimi. You can
take your position after
that.
But if I'm not in time,
then...
You'll be fine.
Uh!
I believe in you, Misaki.
Uh‐
This is it!
Everyone, hold onto
something!
[grunting]
[struggling]
Meow, meow, meow!
[grunting]
Aren't you gonna help him
out, Zenjo?
No, that isn't my
assignment.
Is your only job to cut down
Kings like Habari who've
lost control of
their powers?
[grunting]
You can't afford to be
distracted!
[grunting]
[scoffing]
Just what are you clinging
so tenaciously to, Munakata?
Aren't you just being
stubborn? Face it, the die
has been cast. The world
you're so determined to
protect has already been
destroyed.
Yes...
I am being stubborn. I
despise the fact that I lost
our battle to you far more
than I ever imagined I
would.
Do you really hate
me that much?
Yes, I do. I hate the way
you live.
Well, if we're talking about
likes and dislikes, I don't
care for you either.
Watching you reminds me of
just how deluded I used to
be.
Hmph!
Didn't having your sword
broken teach you anything?!
Flaunt your childish ideals
all you like, but you still
won't be able to change a
damn thing!
[grunting]
Hmm.
All right,
they're coming!
Hold it right there!
Just in the nick of time!
[chuckling]
Don't charge in on your own,
Domyoji!
[grunting]
Akiyama! Benzai! Let's go!
Benzai! Look sharp!
Right, you too!
I'm gonna go
in first!
[grunting]
[gasping]
You okay, Captain?
[chuckling]
And just what do you all
think you're doing here?
We've decided that at the
present time, our most
crucial responsibility is
the swift suppression of the
JUNGLE stronghold.
So we've come to assist you,
Captain.
I have issued no such
orders. Besides, I'm no
longer your captain...
SCEPTER 4 isn't made of
aimless followers who just
sit around waiting for
orders, sir.
We just use the name "Tokyo
Legal Affairs Bureau Civil
Registry Department Division
4" as a cover for SCEPTER
4's actions.
He's right. It's just a
façade. That's all.
It doesn't make a difference
where or when, your cause is
our cause, Captain.
We all are clansmen of Blue
King Reisi Munakata!
Currently, every member of
SCEPTER 4 has been mobilized
and assigned to quell riots
and render aid to the
citizens.
We, the Special Police
Force, will take control of
JUNGLE's stronghold. And
until we suppress the source
of the uprising, we're ready
to give our lives to prevent
the chaos from spreading.
Your orders, Captain?
We of SCEPTER 4 fulfill our
duties as men of the sword.
We do not allow disorder!
We do not allow violence!
We clear the fog that
threatens us!
Men! Draw your swords!
Akiyama, ready!
Benzai, ready!
Kamo, ready!
Domyoji, ready!
Enomoto, ready!
Fuse, ready!
Goto, ready!
Hidaka, ready!
Awashima, ready as well!
That's the Blue Clan's code
of honor, huh?
It sounds lovely.
I really hate to break it to
you, but reality will never
be that pretty.
[grunting]
You're a man who ran away
from the tragedy that
unfolded before you.
You see the world through
clouded eyes...
...and obscure what you
should see with vague,
non‐committal actions.
Nagare Hisui died long
ago...
You're just aiding a dead
man who wants to create a
fool's paradise!
Oh, come on! Like I didn't
know that!
[grunting]
[gasping]
[struggling]
We will advance with our
swords in our hands.
We will triumph because our
cause is just.
I can't believe you won...
Fine, then...
Go on, stick to your
stubborn ideals... See how
far it gets you...
[struggling]
[chatting]
Uh!
Captain! Please, sir, you
have to undo your Sanctum
immediately!
I already did. But my will
alone is no longer enough to
make it disappear.
Go! All of you, get back,
now!
Yes, you too, Mr. Zenjo.
I am the Blue King's
lieutenant.
If necessary, then I will...
Hm.
This is Akagi. B2, standing
by!
This is Bando. B3, standing
This is Chitose. B4 is
standing by!
This is Dewa. B5, standing
by!
This is Eric. B6 is standing
by as well.
This is Fujishima. B7,
standing by.
Thanks to the Blue King
keeping upstairs under
control, we
still have a chance.
What about Izumo and
Misaki...?
Sorry, no time for that! I'm
in a hurry.
I'm coming through!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Sorry I'm late.
All done. Kusanagi, B8
standing by!
All right, this is as far as
I go.
I can't accompany you
further, Mr. Shiro. But good
luck, okay?
Right.
Mr. Kusanagi, thank you.
We're grateful for the Red
Clan's help.
See you later, sunglasses
guy! Make me pancakes again,
okay?
Sure thing, Neko. When this
is over, I'll make you a
tower of pancakes.
[grunting]
Yay!
Now... Die!
[grunting]
[struggling]
You're so lame! You're
s'posed to try to beat the
final dungeon after you earn
enough experience points.
It's too bad for you that
I'm not gonna let you return
to your last save point.
Shut up, you game obsessed
brat...
This is reality, and here
you don't have the luxury
of a reset button to
save your life.
There are times ...
...when you still have to
keep playing the damn
game... even if...
...you know that you can't
win!
[chuckling]
[groaning]
I can't believe that I'm the
one lecturing some kid about
reality...
This whole reality pretty
much sucks...
Even considering the hazard
pay, this is nowhere near
worth it.
Why the hell did I ever
agree to take on this damn
job in the first place?
Saruhiko!
Misaki...?
Bastard! Where the hell are
you, Saruhiko?!
Idiot... I can't believe
that guy actually came after
me...
Saruhiko!
Fire!
Damn you, trying to make
yourself look good, doing
this alone! If you die
before giving me some
answers, I'll never forgive
you!
Uh!
[grunting]
Hm!
Oh, are you switching
players, now? That's fine by
me!
[grunting]
Uh!
Get back here!
Saruhiko! You alive?! Hey!
You're late...
Uh‐‐
And you call yourself a
hotshot?
What a joke...
Hey! Shut up! And why didn't
you tell me, anyway?!
You know I can't talk about
top‐secret missions, idiot,
but couldn't you guess?
[grunting]
Come on, how was I supposed
to guess that?!
You've always been like
this, you know.
Yeah, fine! So, I'm stupid!
That's why I won't get
something unless you explain
it!
Would you have understood
even if I told you?
You could've figured
something out!
Explained till I got it.
If you never told me
anything about this, and you
died in here...
I would have
never known!
Then I would've thought
you were a traitor forever!
But I am a traitor,
remember?
No, you're not!
You took this huge risk,
putting your life on the
line, for the Blue King...
Just like I would've done
for Mr. Mikoto or Anna...
That means the Blue King
really was your true King
all along!
[grunting]
So in my book, Saruhiko
Fushimi of SCEPTER 4 is a
real stand up guy!
[screaming]
[yelling]
[grunting]
Saruhiko's in critical
condition, and your health
bar's turning yellow, so
what'll you do now?
Hey, you little punk! Don't
you have any friends to play
games with?
I've always been a solo
player. It's a hundred times
better than having to deal
with weak idiots who just
slow me down.
I'm strong enough on my own,
anyway. The only one who's
fun to play with is Nagare.
That's why anyone who gets
in his way...
...is gonna get crushed!
[grunting]
So JUNGLE was your refuge,
huh? You remind me of how
Saruhiko and I used to be...
But...
It's time to go home, kid...
You're full of it! I'm still
way stronger than the two of
you put together!
Yeah, right! Guess again!
[grunting]
[groaning]
[grunting and fighting]
Just like old times...
Fighting side by side with
you.
It's not the same...
...as back then.
Yeah, I guess you're right,
it's not quite the same.
Misaki Yata, Red Clansman...
Say it!
...and Blue Clansman,
Saruhiko Fushimi...
...will take you down!
Do you has‐beens really
think that you're cool?!
[charging]
[grunting]
I've got a job to do here,
and I can't waste any more
time playing games with some
kid like you!
[grunting]
Heh!
Saruhiko!
Why can't you just die
already, you old bastards?!
[gasping]
[panting]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[struggling]
Misaki, you came all the way
out here by yourself, then?
When did you grow up?
Just shut up!
I don't know if I'm actually
grown up, but I'm sure not a
kid anymore.
Yata! Hey, Yata! Can you
hear me? Where are you?!
Hey, Kamamoto! Saruhiko's
okay!
Well, more or less...
That's good news!
Anna, Fushimi's okay!
But please hurry! We can't
start until you get to your
assigned floor, Yata!
All right... Got it.
Just go.
Count me out of this one,
okay?
Or I'll be working overtime
without pay.
What? But you're...!
Who matters to you the most
right now?
Uh!
Anna, of course.
Then hurry up and get going.
You have a job to do, so go
do it.
Don't worry, I can get out
of here by myself.
Misaki...
Mm‐
I'll think about how to say
things...
...so even a fool can get
it.
Uh‐‐
All right! Let's talk more
later!
[breathing heavily]
There he is! Move in!
[sighing]
I've used up all my
knives...
He's simple‐minded, stupid,
and ignorant. He barely
understands anything...
But despite that, he's
somehow able to come up with
the perfect explanation...
That means the Blue King
really was your true King
all along!
No wonder I'd go through all
this trouble just for him...
An escape route has been
secured.
I don't recall asking for
your service.
That's okay. I already
received payment from your
superior.
Hm!
Bright and shiny teeth that
can light up the abyss, bring
a healthy life.
You understand, don't you? I
won't let you get past me.
I'll fight you with
everything I've got.
[hissing]
Yukari Mishakuji...
This battle will be...
one on one.
Kuroh?!
You two go on ahead. I must
face this man alone.
Please, Shiro, let me do
things my way, just this
once.
Oh‐
This is the first time
you've ever insisted on
anything.
Hmm.
I admire your spirit, but...
Kuroh...
Remember, if you can't
defeat me, I'll waste no
time whatsoever in going
after your king.
Hm!
The King who seeks change,
the King who prepares for
her final destruction...
Next time on K RETURN OF
KINGS, episode 13 "Kings."
The first King will put an
end to everything...