We will attack on the
24th, on Christmas Eve.
We will summon up
every ounce of power
that we possess and
we will seize the
Dresden Slate, the
ultimate sacrament.
With it, we'll fulfill
our goal as JUNGLE too.
Are any of you even
listening to me at all?
Sure, Nagare, of
course we're listening.
Oh dear, I've got a
wrinkle right here.
Yes, I see, Yukari. Well
then, I shall continue.
Currently, the Slate is
kept inside Mihashira Tower.
Originally, my plan was
this. Now that the Gold
King is no longer around
to suppress its power
the Slate should be able
to serve its original
purpose of advancing
mankind's evolution.
After all, Daikaku
Kokujoji was an exception.
I was sure there was no way
the young and inexperienced
Blue King could control
the Slate's power.
That's why I left it
there, untouched, and yet...
Are you sure that you
all are listening?
Yeah, of course, Nagare.
Yes! All right!
I leveled up!
Oh, did you?
Congratulations, Sukuna.
In any case, the Blue
King has proven me
wrong by lasting longer
than anticipated.
Impressive...
And to make matters
worse, the Silver King has
returned, and a new
Red King has been born.
Now, they've joined forces
to guard Mihashira Tower.
Which means that there is
only one other option left
to us, to bring the
Slate under our control.
Come on. Not one of you
is really listening to me.
I can tell.
Hey, come on,
now, you two!
Pay attention to him,
would you? I know that
he may not look it, but
he is still our King.
Stop joking! Show
him some respect.
It seems to me you're the
least respectful one, Mr. Iwa.
Please, don't
misunderstand, Mr. Iwa.
I am simply beautifying
myself in preparation.
I want to make sure
that I look gorgeous and
elegant as I walk
through the battlefield.
But my heart is filled with
excitement. I'm ready to
draw my beloved
Ayamachi at any time.
Yeah, and the
same goes for me.
This game's just
to stay busy.
It's keeping me
distracted from how
badly I want to
go out and fight.
Seriously, Nagare, don't
get all bent out of shape.
I totally understand
what you've been
saying this entire time!
Oh, I see. So both of
you are fully prepared
then, are you?
I'm quite impressed.
Well then, after we take
possession of the Slate,
we'll celebrate with a
lavish Christmas party.
Chicken, chicken!
Juicy and delicious!
Kotosaka, I expect you
to do your share, too.
No need to worry. Every
one of us here is totally
pumped up and ready to go!
Oh. Well, you guys all
know how I do things.
I'll just be relaxing around
here and drinking my beer.
Come to think of it, Nagare.
Isn't it a bit unusual for
you to hold an official
meeting like this
before assigning a job?
I wonder, could it be,
perhaps, that you're
starting to feel a little
nervous? After all,
you are taking
on three Kings.
[chuckle] Give me a break.
As if! Right, Nagare?
Well, I must admit, an
alliance of the Silver,
Red and Blue Kings is a
very formidable challenge
to have to overcome. But...
[humming]
Welcome. Thank you
so much for coming.
And how are all of
you doing today?
Well, it appears that
you're not too happy.
Perhaps in deference to my
position as the Silver King,
you don't want to come
right out and do or
say anything to
blatantly oppose me.
However, do I detect a
little resentment at my
calling you out so often
and at my taking charge?
Excuse me, Silver
King, may I have your
permission to speak freely?
By all means, Mr. Kusanagi.
Right now, we're
going on the premise
that the Green
Clan is going to
attack Mihashira Tower
to steal the Slate.
Are you positive that's
really their plan?
Yes I am, and if they do
get their hands on the
Slate, the world order
that the Lieutenant...
I mean, the Gold King
and the Blue King
here worked so hard to
preserve, would collapse.
At the very least, the
world that all of us know
would cease to exist.
The reason is that the Green
Clan's intent is to pass on
the power of the Slate to
the entirety of mankind.
I can speak for the Red Clan
and I'm pretty sure that I
can do the same for the Blue
Clan over there as well.
When I say I can assure
you that none of us would
even dream of questioning
your status as King.
But still, that status and
whether or not you're
capable of leading
this operation are
two completely
different matters.
Mm‐hm.
I apologize, but I have
to be frank about this...
I'm not sure if you
have what it takes.
[growl] I'll have you
know Shiro is amazing!
Settle down, Neko.
Kusanagi...
I realize that I may sound
biased, but this man's more
than qualified for the task.
He has the intelligence,
the leadership,
the good judgment.
Kuroh...
Thanks for that.
You too, Mr. Kusanagi.
You chose to play the
devil's advocate for
everyone, right?
[chuckle]
Now, there's a simple
reason why I should be
the one who's directing
this counterattack.
It's because I know
everything that there is to
know about the Green
King, Nagare Hisui.
Hey, wait a minute!
How's it possible
for you to know that?
I thought that the Green
King went out of his way to
avoid being seen in public!
Unless you're
telling us that you're
connected to the Greens!
I'll put this very simply...
The Green King, Nagare
Hisui, once challenged the
Gold King, Daikaku
Kokujoji to battle.
All by himself.
Video and images of
that incident remain
intact in their entirety.
The Lieutenant passed
that data on to me,
and I also heard the
details from him directly.
Is it all right if I say
something too, Silver King?
Yes of course,
Ms. Awashima.
And please, just call me
Shiro, if you'd prefer.
Understood.
Mr. Shiro, if I may
be frank, I'm having
some real troubles
believing all of this.
Why would the Green King
ever have issue to challenge
that's as reckless as
that would have been?
Because maybe it isn't as
reckless as you think.
I say that because although
he did lose in the end, at
one point the Green King
was managing to hold his
own against the most
powerful King and the
battle was nearly even.
And another thing, he
actually explained his
reason for wanting to
overthrow the Gold King
in the first place and it
was absolutely ridiculous.
Before the Green
King escaped he left a
parting message, quote,
"I just wanted to fight
the game's final boss."
That's mature.
That guy sure is messed up.
Then after he barely
managed to get away from
the Gold King, the
Green King dropped
completely out of sight.
His clan didn't make a
move till now because the
Lieutenant was still around.
But I'm afraid
that the Lieutenant
isn't here any longer.
And so that is why I
would like to be the
one who's in command
of this counterattack.
I'm certain that I know how
we can defeat Nagare Hisui.
The Green King is
unbelievably strong, but
still, he can be defeated.
It's just that it isn't
going to be possible
without help
from all of you.
I get what you're saying,
and yet at the same time.
Okay.
Anna?!
I've made up my mind.
Okay, then!
Well, I guess I'll have to
take back what I said.
Silver King! I mean, Mr.
Shiro! The Red Clan has
decided that we're
going to help you out.
Great. Thank you. What
about the Blue Clan?
It will depend on the
details of your strategy.
Naturally, of course.
Then let me move on to
discuss that
point right now.
Kuroh?
I'm on it, sir.
The fight against the
Green Clan won't center
on Nagare Hisui, but
rather on these two.
Yukari Mishakuji
and Sukuna Gojo.
Remember these
faces well.
Our first priority will be
to keep these two at bay.
Okay? Now in
order to do that,
what we must do is...
Mr. Shiro? I
think your strategy
makes a lot of sense.
We'll just have
to do our best.
Thank you, Mr. Kusanagi.
I'm counting on you, Anna.
Sure!
By the way, what is your
opinion regarding him?
He never seems to let on
what he's really thinking...
Can we count on him or not?
I don't know. However, we
can't win if we don't have
his help. That's how
strong our opponent is.
Reisi...
Besides, since the
Lieutenant passed
away, he's the one
who's been keeping the
Dresden Slate suppressed,
and he's been doing so
all by himself.
That's an exhausting
burden to bear.
I don't blame him for
being extra cautious.
That thing needs a king's
strength to control it,
otherwise mankind will
evolve without limits.
Mr. Munakata has taken
over and continued the
Lieutenant's work.
All of us and especially
me, should be very
grateful to him for that.
Two Green Clansmen sighted
at the main entrance!
It's Yukari Mishakuji
and Sukuna Gojo!
They're coming in!
Surveillance cameras in all
areas have been destroyed!
They're here! Men,
draw your swords!
[chuckle]
[humming]
Merry Christmas, everyone!
We've come to take the
Slate as our special gift!
The only one worth
any points here.
Is Seri Awashima,
their number two!
Well, It sounds like
things are getting
started out there.
Shiro, believe me, I
have the utmost faith
in your strategy, but
are you absolutely
sure about this decision?
Leaving the first floor
to just the Blue Clan?
As I said during the
strategy meeting,
the first task in our
counterattack focuses on
the Green King's
two heralds.
We have to hinder their
progress, slow them down as
much as possible, if this
plan is going to succeed.
Their goal right now
is to weaken us, to
reduce our fighting power.
So we're going to do the
opposite and weaken theirs.
I've told Ms. Awashima
to withdraw her men when
it feels right. Don't worry.
And is what you said during
that meeting true, that the
Green King can only stay
active for a short time?
Yes. The Green King
is almost invincible.
If he gets serious, I
honestly don't know
if even the Blue King,
the Red King, and I
together can defeat him.
In fact, he's probably
capable of taking down
every person in this
building single‐handedly.
However, the good news
is that he can't sustain
that level of power
for very long.
That's good to know...
Meow!
Hey, Shiro, isn't this
all just so exciting?
What on earth are you
talking about now, Neko?!
What do you think, silly?!
I mean, Shiro's here and
you're here, too, Kuroh!
We're all together again!
Working as one
to do our best!
And that just makes me
feel so happy inside!
[laughter]
Good grief, Neko! You're
always so unbelievably
optimistic about everything.
[chuckle] Yes, she sure is!
We're all in on this, so
I'm sure that it'll be okay.
And Once this is
over, we'll have
a grand Christmas
celebration together.
Bring it!
Finally. You going
to stop running now?
Sukuna!
Don't go after her.
Yeah, but...
You know what the plan is.
By now the both of us ought
to be heading upstairs.
Upstairs! Upstairs!
Nagare can only fight for
a limited amount of time,
remember? Our job is to
open up a path for him.
[disappointed sigh]
Yeah, okay, you're right.
This isn't the place to
use up our resources.
Caw!
Seems you Blues
concocted quite a
scheme, but it's useless.
Because I'm the beautiful
flower that blooms in the
rich green known as JUNGLE.
And you are nothing more
than nutrients to provide
sustenance to me.
You only make
me look better.
Yeah, whatever.
The new Red King's power
to let us communicate
telepathically is so useful.
With this, we don't have to
worry about the Greens
intercepting our messages.
Yukari Mishakuji and
Sukuna Gojo have
infiltrated the building.
Okay everyone,
let's do this.
I suppose that at this
point, we'll just have to
hope that everything
goes according
to the plan that Yashiro
Isana has put together.
We're not done yet!
Join the team upstairs
and stop those two
by using a pincer attack!
Cameras have picked
up Mishakuji and Gojo
on the tenth floor!
Roger that. As planned,
I'll manually activate
the Mihashira Tower
security measures.
Entrapment 10E. Plus 3,
plus 4, F minus 4.
Deployment confirmed.
And heaven and nature sing!
All traps ready.
Needle ceilings,
pitfalls, tasers.
Just try to
dance past these.
[gasp] They cleared
all the traps!
Entrapment 11D minus 3,
minus 4, minus 5. S
plus 4, plus 5, Z the
whole nine yards.
Entrapment normal
deployment confirmed.
Yukari Mishakuji and
Sukuna Gojo have
finally been separated!
However, it appears
they've only suffered very
minimal damage at best!
Why those damn monsters!
Those two are extremely
powerful, so we'll lure them
in and separate them. We
Reds'll take on Sukuna Gojo.
And the Silver Clan will
surround Yukari Mishakuji
and bring him down.
This strategy would be
impossible without Fushimi's
complete grasp of this
building's security system
and without his flawless
operational set‐up.
Isn't that right, Yata?
[scoff] Mr. Kusanagi...
Even I have to admit just
how good the guy is when it
comes to stuff like this.
Where's that brat
we're in charge of?
Isn't it about
time he showed up?
Damn right! That's one
thing I gotta thank Shiro for.
That Green bastard's
gonna pay for what he did!
[gasps]
What's this?
What in the hell?!
What is that asshole
doing here, Monkey?!
Those two are
ridiculously strong.
Look, I lured them in
and separated them.
If they got switched around,
that's a minor issue!
You wanna complain?
Then do this yourself!
So the three clans will put
every resource available
toward pinning down
Mishakuji and Gojo and
then the Silver,
Red, and Blue Kings
will attack the
Green King together.
I suppose this is the
only strategic option
we have left to us.
Although...
Kuroh? What's the matter?
I'm simply disappointed.
If only I had been stronger.
If only I could at least handle
Yukari Mishakuji on my own.
It would make this
battle easier for you.
For everyone.
Kuroh...
Look, I've heard stories
about your battles,
and I know how
they've turned out.
But I don't believe
for a second that you
are inferior to
Yukari Mishakuji.
Why do you say that?
I'm only saying that
previously you weren't able
to fully access your power
as a Silver Clansman.
Kuroh, the way that
I see it, you display
your true strength when‐‐
Hm? Meow!
Shiro! Something's
coming closer!
Is it Yukari Mishakuji?
Neko, if the parrot is
with him, can you take
care of it, please?
Yeah! I'll turn him into
roast chicken and then I'll
eat him up for a yummy
Christmas dinner!
[gasps]
Whoa, it's the Silver King!
Of all the places to
meet the final boss!
You know, I was getting
really irritated with all
those traps, but now
I say, lucky me!
Shiro, let's get him!
Guess I'll save
Nagare the trouble of
having to deal with you!
Plus I'll earn
massive points!
Thanks, Silver King!
Don't get cocky!
I wonder how the
Red Clan is doing...
Hey, Yata, this is bad!
Like, very, very,
very, very, very bad!
Just shut up and run!
Bang!
Really? Is there
no end to all this?
It's obvious that they're
merely trying to stall us.
How ungraceful...
Time to go for
the middle boss!
I feel so light...
Is it because Shiro is near?
Hey! Don't ignore me!
Neko!
I'm on it!
W‐ What is this?!
Damn it!
No fair!
[harrumphing chuckle]
Complain all you want to.
Hey, Shiro's got that
evil look of his!
Now...
This is as far as you go.
This'll be the end for
you as a power that's
able to fight against us.
[growl] The end, my ass!
Well now, those guys are
really putting up a heck of
a fight, aren't they?
I'd say that we've
cleared maybe seventy
percent at best.
You think we got here a
little too early, Nagare?
I don't. Not
even a little bit.
I'm going to enter the fray.
Huh?!
Listen, you know there
are three Kings waiting
for you up there, right?
I think you should
wait here 'til Yukari
and Sukuna clear
a path for you?
I will not wait.
Seriously? So you're not
even going to listen to the
person who's been
like a father to you?
Yes, that's right. I will do
whatsoever I please to do.
[chuckle] So, you're
turning rebellious
on me, is that it?
All right, fine!
Go if you must.
Mr. Iwa, thank you.
I appreciate it.
I have to admit that the
alliance of the Silver, Blue
and Red kings is
indeed very powerful...
However for me, it's easy!
Well go and have a
blast then, Green King.
Not even the steel prison
can contain the green beast.
As the Green King
climbs to the top,
the other kings stand
ready to face him.
His wish: A game
with no rules.
Where only the
strongest will reign.
Next time on K RETURN OF
KINGS, Episode 7 "Kickdown."
However, our feelings
are no game!