The Dresden Slate... the
treasure that has given
birth to Kings.
We are now witnessing...
...its true brilliance.
It's simply... magnificent!
The light that will
revolutionize the world...
It really is
incredibly beautiful.
Hey, Nagare... So does this
mean that this world is
finally gonna start changing
into the new one?
No, it's not going to start
changing. The change has
already happened.
What? Already?
The Dresden Slate... is an
apparatus meant to evolve
all of mankind to the level
of Kings like us.
The Silver King was the one
who initially awakened it...
But then that stubborn Gold
King went and put a lid on
its capabilities.
Which means this whole time
that thing's only been
running on what you'd call
"safe mode."
But now... there really
isn't anyone left who's able
to suppress the Slate.
It's returned to its full
power... And with its
reawakening... comes the
opportunity for all of
mankind to evolve into
Kings!
An opportunity for all
mankind...
You mean, outside is...
Hmph...
Outside's probably total
chaos.
Yes. When the masses who
were powerless before at
last come into
their powers...
...the existing order will
be destroyed and a new world
will be born.
A world where one controls
one's own destiny and forges
one's own path.
Where one stands a chance
against meeting a senseless
death...
That's correct.
Huh?
Are you saying... that from
now on, I'm gonna be able to
just up and fight Kings
like you, Nagare?
That sounds awesome! I can't
wait! The stronger the
opponent, the better it
feels when you beat them!
The birth of a new world...
...where Kings battle
against Kings.
It'll truly be a paradise of
natural selection.
And we're going to be the
flowers that bloom... in
that brave new world!
These guys are nuts...
Do you know where we're
going on Saturday yet?
Oh, well, I dunno, where
do you wanna go?
What's that? Uhh...
It almost looks like that
red light we saw before...
[gasping]
This is so weird...Whoa...
Oomph...
Mish, what's happening?
Uh? Mishina? Are you okay?
[panicking]
Not good, not good!
This is... just like that
time a year ago.
[gasping]
What's going on?
Ahhh!
Kukuri!
Huh?
Thank goodness...
That was too close!
Shiro!
Kukuri... We have to ask you
a big favor.
Me? Help you?
That's right.
It's something only
you can do.
Uh‐mm!
This just in. We have the
latest developments
surrounding the most recent
outbreak of people...
...manifesting strange
powers.
Since the start of this
year, there have been
numerous reports of people
suddenly displaying
unnatural powers. But around
noon today, the number of
reports abruptly
skyrocketed.
The government has issued a
state of emergency and is
asking all citizens to
remain indoors.
Similar phenomena are being
reported throughout the
world.
Have we gotten any word
from JUNGLE yet?
Nothing yet, sir.
Outrageous! I mean...
...I wasn't told that any of
this would happen! It's
utter chaos out there!
At this rate, we'll have a
diplomatic crisis on our
hands!
Well yelling at me isn't
going to help!
[gasping]
What was that?
What's going on?
What the...?!
I'm able to see right
through the wall!
What?
Rioters in the minister's
mansion! [gasping]
Uh, you! Call a bodyguard
for me! And get me Captain
Munakata!
But Mr. Prime Minister, sir!
You already dismissed him as
captain.
Oh no, that's right!
[panicking]
Munakata! I'm so, so sorry!
Please save me!
Hey, look... the Prime
Minster has sent an urgent
request for help.
So? What should
I do with it?
In the present situation,
the importance of the
existing government's power,
honestly, could
not be any smaller.
I see no need to help them.
Please... just ignore it.
Gotcha.
We've come a long way,
haven't we?
Undoubtedly.
In order to evade the Gold
King's endless pursuit...
...we had to go into hiding,
away from anyone's prying
eyes, for a long time indeed.
Oh, yeah. I gotta say, you
definitely scared the hell
out of me with that one.
I mean, trying to pick a
fight with the invincible
Gold King?
And the fact that you got
your ass kicked didn't help!
An innocent boy got into a
little mischief, and he
became so upset about it.
Daikaku Kokujoji was quite
immature for an old man...
I thought I was going to
die. I regretted what I'd
done.
Oh, well... it's over. All
that is long in the past.
The Gold King is dead now.
And the Slate belongs to us
free and clear.
It's not over yet.
Hm?
This time, it's the opposite
of a month ago. It's our
turn to protect,
and their turn
to attack.
It looks like blue boy
hasn't learned his lesson.
Is that why you ordered all
passageways except the
Yomito Gate to be closed?
Yes.
We've also cleared all
civilians from the Yomito
Gate area, and we've
assembled U‐Rank players at
this secret base.
Does that mean...
...you're seriously
entertaining the notion that
they're going to be able to
infiltrate even here, our
secret base?
The possibility...
...of them making it here,
to where the Slate and I
reside, is not zero, after all.
However...
As long as I'm connected to
the Slate, I have no time
limit holding me back.
My powers are
inexhaustible.
And the chance that they can
defeat me when I'm like this
simply does not exist.
It's zero.
Therefore, there's no need
for two Kings to stand guard
over this place.
So, Mr. Iwa, I'm going
to ask you to welcome
the Blue King.
Hm?
You're really expecting that
to happen, as well?
Everything possible has a
chance of happening.
Since you can tap directly
into the Slate's power, you
can manifest your
manipulation ability to its
highest degree now, right?
Then I wonder...
could it be...?
Hmm.
...that you're also able to
manipulate things that
happened in the past?
For example, could you make
my losing ticket at the
horse races turn into a
winning ticket...
Or, you know...
I'm terribly sorry, Mr. Iwa.
Just what are you sorry
for...?
I'm afraid I can't do
that... Even with my
powers...
Changing the past is
impossible.
[sighing]
Yeah, I figured that it
might be...
I imagine that it would be
too good to be true...
I suppose it just means that
honesty and hard work are
still the quickest and most
reliable ways to achieve
happiness.
Well, I'm going.
Yes, please be careful.
It does make
sense, I guess...
Changing the past and
redoing it just isn't
your style.
Your power is to correct the
present and to change the
future.
So use that power, Nagare...
Use it to reshape this giant
toy box called the world...
The way you see fit...
Please, please try to stay
calm and act rationally.
I know how scary it must
feel to suddenly have these
strange powers...
But, still... it's possible
to suppress them!
All of you, just try to
remember what happened a
year ago. That time when
this school came under
attack.
What we have to do is become
like the man who saved us
back then.
These strange powers don't
have to be used only for
destruction!
They can also be something
that we can use to protect
ourselves! So please...
A year ago...?
Yeah, that's right! You
remember? There was that guy
who helped us all out!
We can do this!
Mm.
I'll do my best over here,
Shiro, Kuroh, Neko...
[gasping]
[grunting]
Everyone...!
Hey! Look.
Huh? Yeah, just
as we were told.
I still can't believe the
Blue King would show up like
this.
I suppose this removes any
doubt that JUNGLE's
headquarters is up ahead.
Well, that pillar of light
was glowing for over fifteen
minutes and thirty
seconds, after all.
It's hard not to draw
attention.
There are quite a few of
them. Shall I lead off, sir?
No, that won't be necessary.
Your task today isn't to
clear the path.
You're going in yourself,
Captain?
Mr. Zenjo, I am no longer
the Captain.
I'm just an ordinary King.
They went through the
blockade tape! Activate
Protocol A!
Fire! Just attacking earns
you points!
But watch your aim! There's
only two of 'em!
Hold your positions,
everyone! All teams ready?
All right! Fire at will!
[chuckling]
Incidents of superpowers
have skyrocketed!
It's like everyone in the
country has turned into a
Strain now!
Seems that some situations
are escalating into
violence...
It's unconfirmed, but
reports say the Prime
Minister's official
residence was attacked.
Lieutenant, with all this
going on, are we still
supposed to just stand by?
As long as we still have
standing orders, there's
nothing we can do,
but obey them.
If that's true...
Well, then... what's the
point of us being here?
Fuse!
All we can do right now to
help is gather intel.
And the Captain? Has there
been any progress in getting
in touch with him?
No...
Hm.
Lieutenant, take
a look at this.
What is it?
We've been keeping that
pillar of light that
appeared in Yomito under
constant video
surveillance...
And this is what showed up
on the feed!
It's the Captain! And
Mr. Zenjo, too!
Against... the
whole Green Clan?
They're going into enemy
lines with just the two of
them? That's suicide!
The Green Clan... Could one
of them be Mr. Fushimi?
Don't be stupid!
Why'd he... take just Mr.
Zenjo with him?
Captain...
I've decided...
As of now, I resign from
SCEPTER 4!
[gasping]
As long as I remain with
SCEPTER 4, I'm not allowed
to leave the premises.
I also can't involve the
rest of you or force you to
disobey your orders!
I realize this may sound
selfish, but I have now
reached my limit...
However...
I still want to remain the
Blue King Reisi Munakata's
right‐hand man.
Even if he's no longer a
public servant...
...I want to continue to
serve him...
...and do what must be done.
That is my duty!
Lieutenant...
Sorry, Akiyama. As of this
moment, you're the one who's
in charge of SCEPTER 4.
I'm leaving now.
I understand.
As you just heard, I am now
in command of SCEPTER 4.
So here are my orders as the
acting captain!
We will now proceed to the
headquarters of the Green
Clan JUNGLE, who
masterminded this entire
scheme...
...and we'll neutralize the
situation!
What?
Hm.
During this operation, the
safety of the citizens is
our top priority.
[smiling]
Do everything in your
power to protect them.
Yes, sir!
Stop this! Don't be foolish!
Weren't you listening?
You're disobeying‐
It's no use, Lieutenant...
No... Miss Awashima.
You're merely an ordinary
citizen now, remember?
You're someone that we're
supposed to protect.
Here, take it.
This is an emergency.
By the authority of SCEPTER
4, it's loaned to you for
self‐defense.
Okay, Akiyama?
[gasping]
Yes. As acting captain of
SCEPTER 4, I authorize it.
All of you...
[chuckling]
All right. Let's go.
SCEPTER 4! Move out, now!
Yes, sir!
[yelling]
Oh, crap! Move out!
Your moves are starting to
get old. This plasma bullet
packs the same amount of
power as the Lightning Bolt
Jutsu.
This ought to take down even
the Blue King!
[grunting]
My apologies for intruding
like that, sir.
If you'd done nothing, it
might have saved you some
trouble down the road.
Hmph.
Surely, you jest.
Shit, it didn't work!
The gate can still only be
opened from the inside,
though! Even the Blue King
can't get through it alone!
Now, we wait...
Hello, Saruhiko. You sure
work fast.
I'm impressed.
I already know what you're
up to. You intend to invite
the Blue King inside.
Then I guess you'd better
hurry up and kill me before
then.
There's no need for that.
And there's no reason to
either.
As long as you don't open
the gate... then you won't
be considered a traitor.
A J‐Rank has the right to
freely walk around this
secret base of ours.
And a duel between clansmen
is also not prohibited.
So once I open this gate,
I'll be considered a traitor
and disposed of, is that it?
You understand things
quickly, and that saves so
much time. You must know the
Blue King cannot reach this
place.
You'll just die
meaninglessly, a dog's
death.
Is that a threat?
No, an invitation, Saruhiko.
I'm offering you the chance
to truly become one of us.
Your personality isn't a
good fit for HOMRA or
SCEPTER 4.
We both know you're best
suited to be a member of
JUNGLE. Which celebrates
free will.
[sighing]
It's true...
If I stay here, I won't have
to deal with idiots, or be
forced to obey a superior's
reckless orders anymore.
That's right.
Then the choice is an
obvious one.
Go to hell.
[squawking]
Unfortunate.
You're dead! Dead!
Hm‐
If you're no longer on our
side...
[chuckling]
Then I can kill you now,
right?!
No way! The gate's opening!
But how can that be?!
Who is in control of
that thing?
We gotta get outta here,
man. I don't trust this.
Hey, wait! That's...!
Holy cow...! They actually
managed to open the gate!
Nagare's foresight always
amazes me.
[grunting]
I don't need assistance. For
now, just stay focused on
the task that you've
been assigned.
Right.
Ah! Munakata!
And that face the one behind
you, there, certainly brings
back memories!
Goki Zenjo, the right‐hand
man of Jin Habari.
So, Gray King Seigo
Ootori... It's been
fourteen years.
Wow, you sure have
aged and not well.
And you, King...
have dried up.
That's for sure!
Hm.
Bring as many as you want,
none of you will get past
me.
No more holding back, no
more showing mercy...
...and no more stalling.
Let's go...
What?!
Well, look at that...
I guess I'm not able to stop
a vessel of such
magnitude...
...when my attention and fog
are directed toward you.
That's so unlike
you, Munakata.
I mean, volunteering
to act as decoy.
There seems to be some kind
of misunderstanding. That
had nothing to do with me.
I am still your main
opponent.
Well, not that it matters, I
guess...
My role right now is simply
to welcome you!
Munakata...
...ready!
We clash because we cannot
yield. And We must fight to
protect.
Next time on K RETURN OF
KINGS, episode 12, "Knuckle
bump."
Two former kids must face
the most powerful kid...