Lieutenant, just as you
did, I will move forward
until my very last breath.
No running this time.
I'll face it head on.
This is the second time I'm
descending from the sky, but
it's different from last
time when I was hurled down.
This time, I'm descending
of my own free will.
Shiro, as your loyal Silver
Clansman, Kuroh Yatogami,
I'll do everything in my
power to complete my part
till the day you return.
Captain Munakata is waiting
for you in his office.
Hey, where's that
partner of yours?
Neko didn't want
to come here.
She's a disobedient
stray cat just as
her name implies.
'Kay...
[sigh]
First of all, I wanted to
thank you for contributing
to the arrest
of our suspect.
I'm glad to see that you're
safe. My men had informed me
that you two had gone
missing following the
bombing incident
orchestrated by the
Green Clan Jungle.
Yes, we just barely
escaped the blast.
But since it seemed that
we were the ones they
were actually after,
we decided that we
should go into hiding.
I'd say that's a very
prudent decision.
It's also the reason why I
came here to speak with you.
Were we both targeted
because we're the Silver
King's Clansmen?
It is a fact that the
Green Clan is searching
for the Silver King.
And who could provide a
better lead than Silver
King Adolf K. Weisman's
own clansmen?
The first he's made
since emerging from
over half a century
of solitude.
That would be you,
Kuroh Yatogami.
You and that young Strain
girl you travel with.
It's only natural
you were targeted.
I don't understand. What
exactly is the Green Clan?
They're quite out
of the ordinary.
While they do have some
clansmen, it seems that very
few of them have ever
actually met the Green King.
I have heard they use
the internet for their
organization in unique ways.
Still, it's quite odd
that they've never even
met their own King.
I agree completely.
Perhaps "clansmen" isn't
even the correct terminology
to describe them.
Nagare Hisui, the Green
King, maintains control of
his Clan through a
social network service
known as Jungle.
And this is what
their site looks like?
Yes.
People unaware of the
existence of clans or their
power log into Jungle
thinking its just another
social networking site.
These normal users are
called "E‐Rank," based on
the last letter of Jungle.
As the lowest ranked Clan
members, they complete
"missions" and when they
do, they earn points,
allowing them to
move up in rank.
You mean that the crimes
committed around the
city by Jungle
are actually...
Yes. They're missions
undertaken in order
to gain Jungle points.
It's like they've
taken an online game
and made it real.
As they earn points,
people move up to L‐Rank,
G‐Rank, and so forth.
And they acquire
special though generally
temporary powers.
If they fail at a mission,
they lose their points.
And depending on the
circumstances, they
could lose their temporary
powers altogether.
Once these culprits are
cut off by Jungle and left
powerless there's really
nothing that we can do
except turn them
into the police.
But there must be some
clansmen out there who've
managed to acquire real
power, too, correct?
We know of a few
who've made it to the
Clan's highest level.
And they have true powers.
The J‐Rank. Their powers
were bestowed upon them in
person by the Green
King, Nagare Hisui.
And yes, one of them is
the man you're probably
thinking of right now.
Yukari Mishakuji.
Has Yukari Mishakuji made
contact with you since
your last encounter?
No...
What about the
Silver King, has he?
I wouldn't be here, then!
Can you remember the Silver
King ever saying anything at
all about the Dresden Slate?
No...
After his memories of being
the Silver King finally
returned, the time we spent
together was too short.
We had no chance to talk
about anything like that.
That's unfortunate...
Has something
happened to the Slate?
No, nothing.
However, with the Gold
King still missing, the
safekeeping of the Dresden
Slate rests with me.
The Silver King knows more
about it than anyone. If he
had left any information
regarding the Slate,
I'd merely like to
know. That's all.
I'm sorry, I'm afraid I
can't be of much help.
If that is all,
please excuse me.
Kuroh Yatogami...
As I recall, the Silver
Clan has no territory
of its own, correct?
Yes, that's right. Why?
Given the situation, not
having a base of operations
must be rather inconvenient.
So if you'd like
I can offer you
Scepter 4's protection.
We'd allow you to take up
residence in our home base.
And I'll promise you
protection should any
emergency arise.
[gasp]
I do appreciate the offer,
but I can't accept it.
My, my how disappointing.
I thought that you and I had
a pretty good chemistry with
each other, don't you agree?
Uh... It isn't
about chemistry!
You don't want to find
yourself beholden to
another clan, is that it?
It's not that either.
It's simply that I...
Mr. Fushimi, do
you have a moment?
Have you already completed
your questioning of
Kuroh Yatogami, sir?
Yes. I would imagine that
he's probably signing
out of the building
at this very moment.
Mr. Fushimi,
please tail him.
Why?!
There's a very good chance
that the Green Clan will
attempt to target him again.
So keep an eye on him.
Very well, sir.
Make sure Ms. Awashima
is kept up to date
with your findings.
That is all.
Where're you
off to, Captain?
Mihashira Tower.
What, again?
Lately, you spend more
time there in the Chamber
of the Slate than you
do here at home base.
A cat?
[chuckle]
Kuro!
Yes? What is it?
Oh...
I was actually just
talking to the cat.
Ah yes, I understand.
"Kuro" as in black cat.
Sorry.
[meow]
Mr. Zenjo...
Could I perhaps have a
moment of your time?
Now then, what can I do to
help you out, Lieutenant?
Today I'd like to talk not
as the lieutenant, but just
as someone who wants to
speak with Goki Zenjo.
Known as Zenjo the Ogre,
the name you used as the
right‐hand man of the
previous Blue King, Jin Habari.
To be honest, I doubt that
I'd have anything useful to
tell you, Lieutenant.
You're the only one Captain
Munakata personally
recruited from the clan
of the Blue King prior
to him, or so
I've been told.
But I am merely a clerk in
the Clan's Documents Office.
In the Kagutsu Incident
fourteen years ago, the
ex‐Red King's Sword
of Damocles crashed
to the ground.
You lost your left arm
during that disaster.
I've heard that without
you, the change in Japan's
topography would have
been far more cataclysmic.
Had you not been there the
entire Japanese archipelago
could have been torn apart.
The Weismann level of
the then‐Red King Genji
Kagutsu had become
terribly unstable.
The influence of that
threatened your king, Jin
Habari the Blue King, with
a Damocles Down too.
However, the
worst was averted.
Because before
that could happen...
Mr. Zenjo, you slew
the king yourself.
Yes.
[gasp]
I realize that this is
an impudent question
to ask you, but...
Please tell me, did you
notice anything different
about the previous Blue
King's behavior before
his Sword of Damocles
reached its limit?
You're worried about Captain
Munakata, aren't you?
[gasp]
I know that the Captain's
Sword of Damocles is
damaged. And it seems
clear that there are others
who have noticed
this fact, as well.
How is the Captain?
He seems to be
his usual self.
But ever since he's been
put in charge of Mihashira
Tower, he spends more
and more time in the
Chamber of the Slate.
And every time he goes there
I sense a change in him.
I understand.
Frankly, I'm afraid that the
reason the Captain asked
you to join Scepter 4 is
so you'll be able to carry
out the very same task
you once did years ago.
Are you sure that's my job?
I'm not Munakata's
right‐hand man. You are,
Lieutenant Awashima.
[gasp]
Thank you for the
refreshments. It's been
quite a while since I
had something sweet.
It was delicious.
Dresden Slate, possessor
of mysterious power.
I command you to obey me.
[growling]
It's no good! It's not
working! I can't see Shiro!
Are you one hundred percent
sure it actually showed
you the Silver King?
I know I saw him! I looked
into the marble and saw
Shiro inside! I'm
not lying, you know!
It's working just fine. I
infused energy into that
marble to let you
see the person
you want to see the most.
All right, well, if you
say so, Anna, then I
guess that it must be true.
Yeah, but I only got to
see Shiro that one time.
Come on, Anna! Let
me see Shiro again!
Sorry you can't see
him all the time,
but there's no doubt
you're connected to him.
The one who is precious to
you just might be looking
at you, as well!
What, really?!
Shiro! Shiro! You there?!
Hey, listen!
What's the big idea, acting
like you own this place?!
You're from a whole
other clan, you know!
Yeah, but the boss with
glasses was trying to take
us away for questioning
or whatever he was doing!
Oh, I get it. So you
escaped and took
refuge here, is that it?
I gotta say that was
a pretty smart move.
The Blues can't
come after you while
you're here in
our territory.
What the hell?! Homra isn't
your personal litterbox!
But I hate the
boss with glasses!
And the jerk with glasses!
I don't wanna go to
the Blue Clan's place!
So what's the Black
Dog doing over there?
I dunno.
You dunno?!
I'm not worried
about Kuroh.
I can always see him
even if we're apart.
[chuckle]
You said for
questioning...
I guess even the
Blues are stumped.
No one really knows what the
Green Clan is up to now...
Well, I know those
guys are a creepy bunch.
The city's crawling with
people who're part of the
Greens, but most of them
are just normal dudes!
We can't even figure out
if they're actually real
clansmen or not!
And then there's the people
who look like they're going
about their business with
their PDAs who do turn out
to be linked to the Greens.
What a pain in the ass.
You guys don't think those
assholes are gonna come
after Anna again, do you?
Well, Anna is now
the new Red King.
They won't be able
to move against her
that easily anymore.
Even if they try,
I'll be fine.
I have inherited the red
from Mikoto and I can use
it to fight against
them. I won't lose.
Are you sure
about that, Anna?
Because I thought that Kuroh
had said something about
the Red power being
destined for destruction.
The King's power
isn't gonna make you
go kaboom, right? Or
something like that?
[chuckle]
Hm?
I may not be as strong
as Mikoto right now.
But I have this feeling
that I'll be just fine.
Hey, take it easy.
What do you want? I didn't
call for you, Totsuka.
Yeah, but just look
around, it's all over.
Any further destruction
would be meaningless.
Destruction is destruction.
There's no meaning to it.
Well, yeah. That's true.
Bet you wanna say that
this is a power that should
be used to protect,
is that right?
It is unchecked power
itself that's destructive.
It's like a monster.
But it's really all
just a matter of how one
uses their power.
If you have something
that's precious close to you,
then it can become
a power to protect.
And the monster will
become your friend.
Right?
Mikoto, your red
is very pretty.
[sigh] You think so?
I inherited this power
to protect everyone.
My power comes from
Izumo, Misaki, Rikio,
and everyone at Homra.
Tatara and Mikoto, too.
That's why I'm sure I'm
going to be fine. Because
this pretty red
is my friend.
Mm‐hm!
And I, I'm gonna
protect you too, Anna!
I mean, I know that you're
on a whole other level of
strength compared to
the rest of us now.
But still...
All the time I kept saying
how great Mr. Mikoto was,
but I never really
tried to understand him.
I guess there's still a lot
that I don't know about.
But I want to be someone
you can rely on, Anna.
I am willing to do whatever
it takes to be someone
you can lean on.
Wow, Yata! That
was so touching.
Yeah, you'll be fine,
Anna! I'm so happy!
Yes!
And I'll bring Shiro to see
you when he comes back!
He's been a King for a
seriously long time, and
that means, that he can
teach you lots of stuff!
Yes.
I'd love to talk to him.
Hey, hold on! That isn't the
way things are done! Kings
aren't supposed to be
all buddy‐buddy with
each other, you know.
But why not?
Huh? Well, hell
if I know what the
goddamned reason is.
Look, that's just the
way it is, all right?
It's better to get along!
Yes, Neko is right.
[sigh]
Now, now, let's stop
all of this bickering
guys and eat up.
Yay! Snack
time! Awesome!
Mr. Kusanagi, I
want some too!
Me, too!
Wow, it looks
so yummy! Yay!
Come and get it, then!
Yeah!
Hey!
Hey! That's my
pancake, Rikio!
You know what? Kuroh made
this dish for me just the
other day, too. [chuckle]
And he said things like,
"Master Ichigen used to put
dark molasses on these."
"He liked pancakes, too."
Kuroh sure can get pretty
annoying with his long,
boring talks, but I
do love his cooking!
Oh! I like yours too,
sunglasses guy!
Thank you very much.
Black molasses. That's
not a bad idea at all.
So, Neko. You like
Kuroh, too, not just
his cooking, right?
Hmm...
Well I like Shiro most of
all, and Kuroh is more like...
I guess that he'd rank
right after fish, maybe?
Neko...
Meow?
Why don't you and Kuroh come
and live with us right here?
Meow, meow, meow?!
You'd both be
welcome to stay here
until Yashiro returns.
It's safer here.
Don't you guys have a
territory of your own?
Oh wait, I guess not, since
your King went missing
right after you
became his clansmen.
Hm...
Uh, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Seriously, though...
I mean it! You guys are
welcomed to stay here,
just like Anna said.
Don't worry!
Neko?
Because even
without a territory...
Hey, Kuroh! [giggling]
So, where have you been
all this time, anyway?
[giggle] I didn't want to
see the boss with glasses,
so I was hiding out
over at Anna's place.
Seriously?
[giggle]
What is it?
You remember this marble?
Well, apparently it won't
always be able to show
Shiro to us.
But Anna is sure that
it's connected to him!
And she even told me
that Shiro just might be
watching us, as well!
Is that so?
Everything's gonna be
okay! So let's go home!
I can offer you Scepter
4's protection.
I do appreciate the offer,
but I can't accept it.
I don't have a territory
but nonetheless, I do
have a place I call home.
You'd both be
welcome to stay here
until Yashiro returns.
It's okay.
Because even
without a territory,
I still have a
home where I belong!
Yes, you're right.
Let's go home to the
place that we belong!
[chatter]
You're too kind. You're
too kind. You're too kind.
The place where Kuroh
and Neko belong, the home
they've sworn to protect.
But the Green's vines begin
to invade even this most
precious place, and the
blade of Kuroh's former
role model comes
to take his life.
Will Neko's desperate cry
for help be able to reach
her King while
he's so far away?
Next time on K RETURN OF
KINGS, Episode 3, "Kismet."
Welcome back...