See this?
It's the Slate that we stole from your
previous King after he was defeated.
Yeah? So? I don't really
care.
[gasping]
Yeah, well, you'd better
care!
Now that you've reached
J‐Rank, you aren't just
another player... you're
also an administrator of the
game.
But don't let it go to your
head.
Hm?
Just because you beat my
record for reaching J‐Rank
in the shortest time doesn't
mean that you‐
Oh, I get it.
Huh?!
You're sulking 'cause I beat
your score. This is why I
hate dealing with kids.
What?!
You only made it to J‐Rank
as quickly as you did
because you had help from
Hirasaka! Man, I can't stand
guys like you who have to
depend on other players to win!
I don't depend on anyone.
But I don't mind using them.
After all, that's my
specialty.
[grunting]
Say, you wanna go a round
against me?
We'll each put up ten
thousand of our points,
winner take all. I'll go
easy on you, just to
make things fair.
What a pain...
Relax, I won't kill you.
We're "comrades," right?
[chuckling]
All right, I'd say that's
enough...!
...both of you!
[grunting]
Stop being so hostile to
each other.
It's truly unattractive.
Caw!
Fine, but... why did you
have to hit me?!
Damn it! Was that really
necessary?!
Listen, it's fine to fight
amongst yourselves... but
this is a very critical time.
We need you to act more
responsibly.
Very soon, the Slate is
going to bloom.
At this point, it's just a
matter of time.
And then Nagare's new world
begins, right?
I can't wait!
You're right. Sukuna can be
petulant at times.
But he's really very
strong.(
It's true that he's far from
polished, but when it comes
to raw power, he's my
equal ‐and perhaps even my
superior.
If he challenges you again,
I would turn him down.
A clan consisting of two
Kings, two clansmen, and one
bird...
Yet you all interact with
each other as equals, even
the Kings.
What a strange place...
Think so?
Well, you know, in the new
forthcoming era...
...every person will have
their own power,
unsupervised by anyone else,
and will have to take
responsibility for their own
life with it.
I think that it will suit
you very well.
Hmph.
I guess this really is the
only option...
I demand an explanation!
Why's the Captain being
dismissed?!
It's quite simple.
[gasping]
I had Munakata step down as
captain, effective
yesterday, in order to take
responsibility for the
incident that occurred at
Mihashira Tower over
Christmas.
He was fired.
But by what authority could
you do that, Mr. Prime
Minister?
The authority is mine.
Mm.
The executive and
administrative rights for
SCEPTER 4 rest with the
Legal Affairs Bureau Civil
Registry Department Division
4.
Ultimately, you are all just
public servants and must
abide by orders issued by
the government.
Yes, but‐
You were able to behave so
arrogantly until now due to
the influence of His
Excellency, Daikaku
Kokujoji.
It seems Munakata had the
gall to try to take His
Excellency's place... and
now, just look at the
results of his hubris.
His Excellency protected our
national treasure for
nearly seventy years, and
then, within two months of
being placed under
Munakata's supervision,
it was stolen!
You cannot deny that he was
unqualified.
Besides, Munakata has
already agreed to accept his
dismissal as captain.
He did what...?!
The rest of your members are
to wait for further
instructions.
Here, this is the order.
With just a sheet of
paper...
An important sheet of paper.
I do value protocol above
all else.
Damn it!
What are you saying?! He's
been fired?!
He's the Blue King! Why
isn't he doing something?!
Calm down, Domyoji!
The government never
interfered with us like this
before.
Do you think it's connected
with the rumors that the
executive branch is tied to
the Greens?
First Mr. Fushimi defects to
them, and now this. It's
like one unthinkable thing
happening after
another...
I wish I knew what they were
thinking, both the Captain
and Fushimi!
[chatting]
[sighing]
[exhaling]
[chatting]
Hey! Anna!
Thank goodness... you're
back.
Where've you been, anyway,
Anna?!
I went out to meet
with Yashiro.
Look, if you told me, I
would've taken you!
It's pretty dangerous
out there right now.
Sorry.
By the way, Anna, it sounds
like Mr. Munakata got into a
lot of trouble.
Mm‐hmm.
I can't believe a King could
be fired as easily as that.
And from what I've heard,
the guys over at SCEPTER 4
aren't taking the news too
well, either.
The members are all on
stand‐by, and they aren't
even allowed to leave their
home base.
I hope Seri is okay...
You know... there were a lot
of politicians and other
government types among the
guests at the JUNGLE party
that Seri and I infiltrated.
I guess all this means that
the government chose the
Greens over the Blues...
If this keeps up, then the
entire world is gonna turn
green.
Is that why?
Huh? What's that?
Is that why Saruhiko left
like a rat deserting a
sinking ship...
...and betrayed just about
everyone by switching his
loyalty from the Blues to
the Greens?
Misaki...
Huh?
Well, I'm gonna go patrol
the area again.
[sighing]
Anna, how'd everything go
with the Silver King?
Anna...?
Yashiro has completed his
research.
You mean...
Mm‐hmm. He's gonna
destroy the Slate.
I see... So you're saying
Mr. Shiro has finally
||
figured out a way
to do that, huh?
Yes... Yashiro's made up his
mind to destroy the Slate,
the symbol...
...of his dreams.
Are you okay with this?
The Slate's been responsible
for taking so many things
away from me...
And yet at the same time, I
love this red. This red
saved me.
Anna...
Still, I wouldn't mind
losing it.
All my life, the only thing
I could do was watch fate
unfold from the sidelines.
But it's different now.
If my fate as the Red King
is to destroy, then I'll
destroy the fate that tries
to hurt the ones that I care
about.
Yeah, I understand...
Ever since I found those
documents back in Germany, I
knew that this day was bound
to come.
All that's left...
Hm?
Reisi...
Hello.
What, may I ask, was the
purpose of calling me out so
abruptly, Red King?
I needed to speak with you.
We are going to make an
attempt to destroy the
Slate.
I see.
I do have to admit that
would certainly be one
option to try to break the
current deadlock.
I didn't know that you
smoked.
Only on rare occasions.
I assume that to you,
destroying the Slate would
mean getting revenge for
Mikoto Suoh's death.
That's true,... but I'm
afraid it's not quite that
simple.
The Slate gave him life but
also killed him... It gave
us many things,
but took many
away, too.
I'm not saying destroying
the Slate will give me a
sense of satisfaction.
It's just....I've come to
believe that it's something
that must be destroyed.
Well, I do agree with you
that the Slate is something
that's extremely dangerous.
[blowing smoke]
However, it's largely thanks
to the late Gold King
Daikaku Kokujoji that our
nation has become what it is
today.
Or to put it another way,
the Slate system is a very
deeply rooted part
of the nation.
I don't believe that we can
afford to lose it.
What we can't afford is to
think like that anymore.
Hisui plans to release the
power of the Slate in order
to give every person in the
world superpowers.
And if that were to come to
pass...
[exhaling]
You're right... That
eventuality must be
prevented at all costs.
But if the way this is
unfolding is that the Green
King is hoping for a
revolution and the Red King
has decided on destruction,
then I, the Blue King, will
aim for order.
It is my firm belief that
the Slate must be regulated
and used appropriately.
With the condition you're in
right now, I doubt you can
pull that off.
Oh?
And... Anna is quite worried
about you as well...
Is she...?
Your sword is at its limit.
Right now...
... if you overexert
yourself, it will fall.
[chuckling]
What's so funny?
Sorry, I just thought it was
ironic that the situation
has exactly reversed itself
from a year ago.
What...?
I tried reasoning with the
Red King like this once,
too.
[inhaling and blowing smoke]
But it was all in vain.
You're wrong.
In what way?
You are not the same as
Mikoto.
[gasping]
I must ask you to leave here
immediately, Red King. This
matter comes under the
jurisdiction of SCEPTER 4.
Not my problem.
This is about those Strains
you arrested a moment ago...
They came into our territory
and pulled some stunts.
We have a few questions that
we wanna ask them, so could
you hand them over to us?
Uh, Captain...?
Look... you know we're not
able to comply with such a
request.
As always, you people are
nothing but trouble...
Burn them all.
No blood! No bone! No ash!
We will advance with our
swords in our hands.
We will triumph because
our cause is just.
Men! Draw your swords!
[chuckling]
Akiyama, ready!
Benzai, ready!
Kamo, ready!
Domyoji, ready!
Enomoto, ready!
Fuse, ready!
Goto, ready!
Hidaka, ready!
Fushimi, ready!
And, Awashima, ready!
Munakata...
...ready!
Totsuka...
You got it.
C'mon, let's go, Anna.
Mikoto...
[chuckling]
You continue to use your
power recklessly.
You're incorrigible.
I don't need a lecture.
Then I'll stop you with
force!
[grunting]
Let's see you handle this,
Mikoto Suoh!
[grunting]
Stand down, now...
...Izumo Kusanagi!
[grunting]
Sorry.
No can do.
Is that all you've got?
That's quite impressive.
However...
Mikoto...
It's okay.
What you just saw is merely
the way that Kings say hello
to each other.
Tatara, be serious.
[chuckling]
Sorry.
But I really don't think
it's something to worry
about.
Yes, the King and Mr.
Munakata are fighting, but I
bet that they're actually
communicating through their
swords.
Oh‐
I must say, you're a
thoroughly unpleasant man.
I've lost count of how many
times you've interfered
since I've become the Blue
King.
That should be my line.
The power that both of us
possess as Kings shouldn't
be wasted in such a
frivolous manner as this.
Yeah? And who decided that?
Surely, it's not a matter of
who decides?
To put it very simply,
whoever wields power must be
responsible in its use.
That coming from you? You
seem to be enjoying
yourself.
Surely, you jest.
Using power without order,
rushing forward without
a goal,
destroying without
creating.
The title "King of Fire"
suits you very well indeed.
You simply burn up into
ashes without purpose.
Honestly, you‐
Make me sick?
Yes. exactly.
Good, we see eye to eye.
[grunting]
The name "King of Order"
suits you just fine, too.
Always meddling in other
people's lives with your
long, boring lectures.
Seriously, you‐
Make me sick?
Exactly...
[grunting]
Don't you ever get tired of
always being such a straight
arrow?
No, of course not, I'm not
like you.
Guess not.
You're not like him.
I never dreamed the day
would come where I'd be the
one who's being admonished.
I was so certain that Suoh's
path was a foolish one...
Reisi...
In any case, the alliance of
three Kings is no longer
valid.
What does that mean...?
Simply that yesterday, I
received a notice from the
government relieving me of
my duties as captain.
And as a result of that
dismissal, I'm no longer
able to assist you as the
leader of my clan.
Maybe, but even if you're no
longer the captain, you're
still the Blue King.
What's going to happen to
the rest of the Blues, your
clansmen, who will now be at
a loss without you?
[chuckling]
Reisi!
We'll use this method to
destroy the Slate.
Is such a thing actually
possible, Shiro?
Before now, it was believed
that the Slate was
indestructible.
So even the Green King
wouldn't expect this. It's
the one way to fix this
hopeless situation.
But the method you're
proposing... isn't it too
dangerous?
Well, I guess I'm just going
to have to ask you to trust
me as a researcher.
I do! I do, I do!
I believe in you, Shiro!
Thank you, Neko.
You're a good girl, you know
that?
[groaning]
I believe in you, too!
Uh?
[clearing throat]
I believe in you. We will do
what we have to do,
together, and afterward, we
will come home together as
well.
[gasping]
[chuckling]
Huh?
Don't you worry.
I made sure that this plan
of mine includes me coming
out of it alive.
Mm‐hmm.
Huh??
Oh, I almost forgot.
There's something that I
want to give to both of you.
Here, look.
Huh?
But what are those things?
Well, I'll explain: the
thing is, we don't actually
have a clan name or
a clan symbol.
To be honest, I was a bit
jealous of the other clans
that do!
Oh, I see...
So this... is to be our clan
symbol?
[excited squealing]
And while we're at it, I
thought we should give the
clan a name, too...
Kuroh, will you do the
honors?
What? Me?
Try to think of something
really cool!
All right...
Hm, let me see...
What's a name that best
describes us?
Huh‐
White rice...
[eager humming]
[clearing throat]
I have decided.
Mm!
Our clan name will be...
Will be...?
[grunting]
HAKUMAITOU!
What?!
Yes...
Rice is a staple of our
diet. It's the foundation of
a healthy body.
Most of all, you love white
rice, isn't that right?
Uh, yeah...
HAKUMAITOU!
Inside of white rice Is where
you will discover Your true
happiness
Well, I guess that since
we're always eating at the
table, that name really does
fit us perfectly.
Fine. We're HAKUMAITOU.
We'll always stick together
and do our best!
Yes! We'll do it!
Neko, Nagare Hisui called
you Miyabi Ameno, which
means that he must have
looked into your past and
knows about who you were
before you became Neko.
If we question him...
Shiro!
I'm Neko! I'm your cat!
That's who I will always be!
Uh. you're right, I'm sorry.
Never mind, Neko.
Listen to me carefully,
Shiro: both Neko and I are
here as your friends.
That's all that matters.
I'm going to follow you
until the end...
And this time, Shiro, I
won't fail you.
Yeah, me too!
Yes! We'll do it together.
And the first thing to do...
is for us to find JUNGLE's
secret headquarters.
[struggling]
Shiro!
[grunting]
What's wrong, Shiro?!
Oh no, Shiro! You okay?
[gasping]
Anna?! What is it?!
It's... the Slate...
[struggling]
So...
It's finally happening.
Yes, at last... The Slate is
about to be liberated, to be
set free.
And then...
...revolution!
It seems it has begun...
Then again, it saves me the
trouble of having to find
them.
Although I don't know how
long I can last...
I suppose that I'm just
going to have to find out...
That's not like you,
Munakata.
[gasping]
I know, right?
The Slate awakens to change
the world, and the Kings
assemble
before the pillar
of light.
Next time on K RETURN OF
KINGS, episode 11
"Kali‐yuga."
I will not let you have your
way!